Theory: if the female guest on "Love It!" were remote-controlled by an army of comedians, she would steal all the laughs from the regulars
Okay, good morning everyone!
Good morning.
It's 6:00 AM right now.
Kuu here's a regular on "Love It!".
Well, I'm a regular on Fridays.
And on "Love It," there's this thing they do...
where they ask questions like an oogiri show, right?
It starts as a quiz show but kind of turns into oogiri.
Right, I see.
But there isn't anything like that for the first two hours.
Yeah, but as soon as I open my mouth it becomes oogiri.
"Love It," the program we're featuring today, is a news-variety program that airs Monday and Friday mornings on TBS.
However, because of the MC, Hajime, and other comedians in the studio, the quizzes have been turning into oogiri.
It has since become a news show with a strong comedic flair.
Just so you know, this plan of ours...
isn't known to anybody, including the MC, Kawashima.
We've only told a couple of producers about it.
[Studio members for today's program]
Tamura, your partner is on the show...
How is it? Do you watch it?
Ah, yeah, of course I do.
Since you're his partner, we figure you'll know all of Kawashima's weak points.
Oh, definitely. Leave it to me.
This is the lineup we'll have to test the theory today.
So, to help us with our plan today...
the guest appearing on "Love It" will be...
ANO
That's right, it's Ano-san.
She's got a weird vibe.
The guest on "Love It" this time will be a former member of the idol group Yurumerumo, Ano.
Now working as a solo artist, she's gained popularity among young people for her unusual character.
I think we've worked together once before.
But with Kawashima...
Have you met Kawashima before?
Who-whuh?
Kawashima? Ah-no.
No, right?
Since he doesn't know her at all...
I want to make him think he's met the funniest girl ever.
You really could!
I guess so.
But wouldn't it actually make her seem super scary?
I mean she's already pretty intense...
if she brings out that intensity...
wouldn't it scare the MCs?
It's gonna be tough to get the hang of this, so...
let's practice first.
For phrasing and stuff like that.
For the practice, Ano-chan's been brought to another room.
We'll start with previous questions from "Love It!"
Ano-chan, can you hear me?
Yes.
Ok, great.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Thank you for coming today.
I'm going to give you a topic and some instructions...
so please tell us whatever your thoughts are on it.
Okay.
Great.
Feeling a little peeved today, are we?
Thanks for having me on.
Okay then, let's begin. Number one:
ANSWER: The ratio of kaki-no-tane to peanuts changed to 7:3, based on a national survey
When Kameda redid the packaging last year for their kaki-no-tane, what changed?
Buddhist sutras are written all over them.
Yuck.
Buddhist sutras are written all over them. Got that?
Junior relays the answers via earpiece
Buddhist sut-ras're...written all over em.
Yeah, that's it! Good tone.
Scary tone.
And then...
A: Pineapple buns
Q: What are melonpan called in Hong Kong?
Alcindo's head.
* Alcindo Sartori, retired Brazillian footballer who played for Japan
Nice.
Kawashima really loves soccer players from his generation.
Now that they've got the hang of things, we'll go into standby for the real deal.
And then...
Finally, the broadcast of "Love It!" begins.
Okay everyone, here we go!
Love It!
Good morning everyone! I'm Kawashima, your MC for this Wednesday edition of Love It!
And I'm Tamura Mako, from TBS.
Thanks for joining us today.
If Tamura's there, maybe it's no problem.
If I was hosting, things might get too heavy.
Today we welcome the multi-talented actor, model, and singer, Ano.
Yeahh, Ano-chan!
You've got this.
And if I'm not mistaken...
it looks like we've got five comedians in the stand today as well!
We are her stand, actually.
Her special ability.
When does the quiz start?
They have to get through some other stuff first.
So not that soon, then.
They have a sort of "ranking" segment first.
They rank some things, and then...
they have a quiz based on that.
About twenty minutes into the program, the aforementioned ranking begins.
I'm super nervous.
Really makes you nervous.
And finally...
Today we've got a quiz for you about spicy snacks.
Oh, it's a quiz.
Oh yeah, here it comes.
There it is!
On the top left!
It's a garlic-themed quiz.
Here we go!
A garlic quiz?
It's not about spicy snacks?
Drinking milk is one known way to wash down the taste of garlic...
but there's another well-known way, too. What might that be?
Okay everyone, do your best!
Let's hear from Shibata-san!
Brushing your teeth.
So fast!
And with that, the "Love It!" oogiri-quiz begins.
Apply baking soda.
To your teeth?
Light and integrate a small firework.
That's good.
Saran wrap your tongue.
Let's go with that.
Ano-chan, say "wrap your tongue in saran wrap."
Wrap your tongue in saran wrap.
Wrap your tongue in saran wrap?
Can't say I was expecting that...
They're going for a big shock right away.
Good tension.
* Japanese ventriloquist
Close your mouth and talk like Ikkoku-do.*
Let's try wood glue.
Yogurt?
Ah, because it usually helps with spicy foods, right?
Unfortunately that's not it.
Okay, Ano-chan.
Let's try wood glue.
Wood glue?
Said it perfectly.
Your answers are scaring me.
Let's tone it down, yeah?
For our second hint...
Ah, go ahead.
Burn some incense on your tongue.
Seems like you've been corrupted by Ano-chan.
She's powerful.
Let's try wood glue.
Wood glue?
With Ano's unexpectedly hard oogiri answers, the whole show gets shaken up.
And then...
I'll give you a hint:
it's a fruit.
Yeah, there's a famous—
ah, did you have an answer?
Okay, Kasuga.
Swallowing a watermelon.
Ano just keeps on raising her hand.
That would be a hippo's answer.
A hippo's answer!
He's good.
Kawashima's really something.
And then...
Yes, go ahead.
Swallowing an apple.
Answer: eating an apple
Oh, they got the answer.
They capped it!
They're capping it.
Shibata must've thought he had to call it there.
Yeah, since Ano's on a rampage.
They put a stop to her rampage.
Reading the air of the room, Shibata stopped the action.
They were probably wondering how many times that hand was gonna go up.
She did have her hand up the most.
She had the overwhelming majority of hand-raises.
After ten minutes pass, they move onto the next one...
It's a chili pepper quiz!
A chili pepper quiz.
A chili pepper quiz?
The following ingredients are included in Yagenbori's seven-flavor spice blend:
Red pepper, roasted red pepper, poppy seed, hemp seed, sansho pepper, and black sesame.
What is the remaining, seventh ingredient?
This is a good question.
Okay, Moriyama.
* "Kou Shui Ji", a Sichuanese dish
Powdered mouthwatering chicken.*
It should probably be the other way around.
* Buddhist deity
Bishamonten.*
You're thinking of the seven gods of fortune.
There aren't any gods in a seven-spice blend.
Shibata's glasses.
Another company's seven-spice blend.
Ooh, that's good.
Okay, Nishida.
* Cigarette brand
Unrolled Red Larks.*
Would she even know?
Okay...Mishima!
Pine tar.
With these answers it's like we're on Panel Quiz Attack 25.
You said it so politely that I can't even be mad.
Ano-chan.
Unrolled Red Larks.
Unrolled Red Larks?
Unrolled...relarks.
Red Larks.
- Like, the cigarettes?
I wonder what the people watching it on air were thinking.
Unrolled Red Larks.
Just what the hell is this girl saying?
"Unrolled Red Larks" do not appear in any of the quizzes today.
That kind of pissed him off.
The red part of a 7 Bamboo tile.
Ano-chan.
7 Bamboo? Like, in Mahjong?
The top part.
Give it a rest, will you?
Did you bring a fifty-something writer with you here?
He got us!
He's catching on! Oh man.
What are you going for here, exactly?
That 7 tile though...
The studio went totally quiet.
Ms. Yada's shaved-off gums.
Okay, we're getting pretty close. Here's a hint:
It's something you'd find at the supermarket.
Ms. Yada.
White sesame?
It is not white sesame.
Although sesame is often included.
Ano-chan.
Ms. Yada's shaved-off gums.
It would be no big deal if Kuu said it, but...
The atmosphere's getting so intense.
This is getting crazy.
Ano-chan...
I think, uh...
maybe you should leave?
There's no way.
It's a bit much, so early in the morning...
"So early in the morning!"
It's the skin of a fruit.
We've really come to a halt here. Nothing like this has happened before...
Unrolled Red Larks
The red part of a 7 Bamboo tile
Ms. Yada's shaved-off gums
A superb triple combo from Ano-chan.
After all she'd done to the studio already, what could be in store next?
Go ahead.
Mandarin.
Mandarin, that's correct!
They're getting away!
Hey, c'mon now...
Shibata made a clean escape.
He won't let it to get any crazier that it is now.
Shibata might be the most freaked out of them all.
He's thinking this girl is really nuts.
She's a menace.
Nobody else gets a chance to talk.
And then, during the pre-recorded segment with Suwehiro Garizu...
Do you know about colored contacts?
You mean ----?
----- colored contacts.
Now, we have a question for Mitorizu's Moriyama!
What sort of Japanese reference did Mishima come up with to explain color contacts?
* manga character based on eyeball yokai
Medama-no-oyaji...*
changing his clothes. Something like that.
That's pretty good.
You have seven seconds to answer. Go ahead!
A colorated pupil...
A colorated pupil donning twelve-layer kimono.
Oh, well...
Better try again!
Ano-chan!
Oh, here it comes!
Medama-no-oyaji changing his clothes.
That's great.
We did it!
He even said it was great!
We just witnessed something incredible.
I'm getting such a rush.
Look at Moriyama's face!
Not a single laugh!
Embarassing.
Medama-oyaji changing his clothes.
Playing not only the mischief-maker,
but a hard lined oogiri talent,
Ano-chan continues to surprise and impress.
You mean a color-plated pupil?
Weak.
The answer was "medama-oyaji changing his clothes."
Damn.
The real answer was weak!
About one and a half hours have passed since the program began.
Okay, now it's time for a banana juice-quiz.
Here it comes.
This brings us to the last quiz of the day.
To make banana juice like you saw in pre-recorded footage earlier,
what special step do you have to take?
*Keiji Muto, Japanese pro wrestler
Ice Muto's knee.
Moriyama.
* Referring to a joke from Tomonori Jinnai that bombed
All you need is to buy a D'agostini every month.
You just add a little bit in each month.
Might get a discount with your first order.
Okay, moving on. Ano-chan?
Ice Keiji Muto's knee.
- Use Keiji Muto's knee?
Ice his knee.
Yeah, that's not it.
They didn't take it.
He's looking pissed.
Kasuga.
Let the old guy at the store chew it up for you.
How about calling it a day?
Every one of your answers is disgusting.
How's Kawashima really feeling?
Probably angry.
He really manages to keep it all under control.
And with that, the quiz comes to an end.
Answer: mash it with a wooden mallet
But finally...
Before we go, we have a little something for our viewers:
an auspicious keyword, this time as conveyed by Ano.
Oh, there's more!
A keyword?
We could say the dumbest thing.
Okay guys, do your worst.
We're gonna come up with some keywords for you, Ano.
There's a lot of content to pick up on from today's show.
I wonder if this'll work.
How about "Kakko-Integra?"
* cool + Integra, pun said by Michael J Fox in famous Honda Integra ad
That takes me back.
Moriyama's D'agostini.
I know, I couldn't believe he went there either.
Everyone just looked the other way.
And so...
We look forward to seeing our viewers use the keyword in your retweets from the program's official twitter page.
And now for the keyword:
Ano-chan, if you would!
Here's the keyword.
Moriyama's D'agostini.
She's ragging on you!
That was my answer, wasn't it?
He got ragged on by the kid.
What is the keyword for, exactly?
Well it's usually not a comment that cuts so deep.
I thought nobody'd remember that.
Everyone, please write "Moriyama's D'agostini" in your tweets.
Nobody's gonna get it, right?
They don't know about the banana juice.
And that concludes our keyword segment.
I wish I could read his mind right now.
He got burned.
And with that, the broadcast ended smoothly.
Okay everyone, that's a wrap!
And now, to reveal the prank...
Huh?
What's all this?
That was really something.
Wait, what? Now I'm really scared.
How was today's Love It?
I mean...it was pretty funny, but...
no, really, what's going on here?
What was the funniest part?
Probably the end, where Tamura came out.
Okay sure, but how about the rest?
The whole show, we mean.
You can't just burst into the studio like this...
I'm still kind of in shock.
Do you understand why we're here?
Huh?
With TBS?
What day is it today?
Wednesday.
Wednesday!
Which means...
Wait, this is Wednesday Downtown?
A pleasure to work with you.
What? What was it? Or who?
There was a weird atmosphere, right?
Well yeah, to be honest...
there was, but...
Speaking personally...
Halfway through, I was too afraid to say a word, actually.
I mean, these insane oogiri answers just came one after another.
I was so freaked out I couldn't raise my hand.
Right?
It's true.
Wait, Ano?
Ano was really you guys?
A theory that poses: if the female guest on "Love It!" were remote-controlled by an army of comedians, she would steal all the laughs from the regulars.
We've proven it to be true.
It took all of you to prove it?
That's one hell of a team!
"Unrolled Red Larks" was him.
So it was you.
Red Larks was the weirdest answer of them all.
So that's it.
I was really freaked out.
And who was "Moriyama's D'agostini?"
"Moriyama's D'agostini" was me.
That was some hard shade you threw.
That one really was cruel.
But your cleanest hit was "medama-no-oyaji."
This is your medama-no-oyaji, right here.
That came really out of left field.
Shibata kept giving the right answers, so...
We were like, "don't let 'em get away!"
Usually we comedians don't give straight answers, but...
but Ano's answers left us with no choice.
We thought things would fall apart if we didn't.
They were trying to wrap it up.
So, then...what do make of the theory?
I would say it's been substantiated.
That really was scary.
Thank you for tuning in to this special broadcast of Love It!, an Oogiri show airing on TBS from 8:00AM!