THIS PROGRAM WAS PRODUCED
UNDER THE SUPERVISION OF MEDICAL EXPERTS,
TAKING INTO CONSIDERATION THE HEALTH
AND SAFETY OF THE STAFF AND CONTESTANTS.
The army continues its charge
into four paths.
After the battles at the third stronghold,
only three warriors remain.
3 WARRIORS REMAIN
Will they be able to turn things around?
THE THIRD FORTRESS
ENNOSUKE CASTLE
-Fun times. Right, my lord?
-Yes.
-Next, we have the Dragon God's Pond.
-Yes!
OSAMU SHITARA - YUKI HIMURA
-Here it comes!
-I can't wait.
ENNOSUKE ICHIKAWA
DRAGON GOD'S POND
USE THE STONES TO GET ACROSS THE POND
Let's see how it goes, shall we?
Start over there and come this way.
Be careful. Yes, like that.
-You move so lightly.
-Very good.
It's too easy for you.
-As long as the stones don't sink.
-I know.
-Right.
-You're good.
Otherwise, it'll be like that.
I know you'll hit your face.
That's what happens in Takeshi's Castle.
-That's funny though.
-I know.
I slept so well.
Taking a nap is a good thing.
What?
GENERAL TANI
It's him again.
I finally became the captain...
What?
Hey, everyone, have you seen General Tani?
No.
-He was here earlier.
-Really?
Did he leave to command another game?
Well, whatever.
THE CAPTAIN
SUBARU KIMURA
The next game is the Dragon God's Pond.
This is Takeshi's Castle's
most famous game.
Here it comes.
Can you make it?
All that water will make it slippery.
Charge!
This is the Dragon God's Pond,
and I, Nasu, will be reporting.
How many challengers
will be able to finish the game?
I think there's something there.
-Something's lurking in this pond.
-Who is that? What?
That butterfly stroke...
It must be Kasuga.
Yes, it's him.
Here comes the merman.
Hey!
MERMAN
TOSHIAKI AUDREY KASUGA
DRAGON GOD'S POND
DIFFICULTY RATING: 100%
EDITOR FOR LIGHTNING MAGAZINE
ADO SHIRASAWA (44)
GET TO THE GOAL BY JUMPING STONES
IF YOU FALL, YOU FAIL
He's doing great.
-He hit his face.
-Oh, dear...
EDITOR FOR LIGHTNING MAGAZINE
MASAHIRO SASAKI (47)
Let's go!
Your senses change a bit
when you start jumping.
-He couldn't stay on.
-It's a shame.
They tend to jump to the right
because the distance is shorter.
Choosing the right path
is important in this pond.
The key is how to jump over the areas
where the stones are too spread out.
Good luck!
I'll try my best!
She's fast!
She jumped into the water.
-She jumped into the water.
-Should've done it slowly.
Koga took off at a brisk pace.
She jumped to an area without stones.
She fell vigorously.
TAKAHIRO OGAWA (51)
The next challenger is Ogawa. He's been
writing articles on leather jackets
for men's American culture magazines
for 20 years.
I write about leather jackets and boots.
Here I am.
-Are you gonna be okay in those?
-Sure.
Is he okay? He's wearing engineer boots.
He has been writing articles
on leather jackets and boots.
He's wearing his favorite leather jacket
and boots, worth 260,000 yen.
TAKAHIRO OGAWA (51)
-Let's go!
-Good luck!
-Hey!
-That stone!
-Did it move?
-No.
-He jumped to the farthest one.
-He did.
Everyone does that.
Ogawa chose a path that bypasses
the stone-free zone.
It looks like it was difficult
to move in those boots
and he fell into the pond,
along with items worth 260,000 yen.
Oh, my God. I'm drenched.
-Look.
-Oh no.
-It's a nice picture.
-Yeah.
-The next challenger is...
-Who is he?
I'll get to the end.
Just watch me, Takeshi.
It's Tetsuro Degawa... No.
This is an impersonator, Taa Shimizu.
I'll get to the end.
IMPERSONATOR
TAA SHIMIZU (37)
-He sounds like him.
-You got this!
-That's good.
-Go slowly.
-That's great!
-It's dangerous.
-It's dangerous!
-Okay!
-Be careful.
-Always that stone!
-Yeah, that one.
I did it.
RULE
MERMAN MAY ATTACK USING THE WATER GUN
-Is Kasuga staying there?
-Yeah.
-All the time?
-Yes.
-He's been using his water gun.
-He's great.
-Kasuga, are you stupid?
-That was me, Degawa. I'm sorry.
All right! Let's go!
GOLDEN BOMBER
YUTAKA KYAN (37)
-I hope Kyan makes it.
-Good!
-Be careful.
-Is that stone safe?
That stone! You never know.
He sank slowly.
What a shame.
He sank slower than anyone before.
-Yeah. Not faster than anyone.
-No.
-It felt like being on the elevator.
-Yes.
ADDITIONAL RULE
Here comes another additional rule.
That rule is, obviously...
It's him!
TOGI MAKABE
I'll go after anyone who's slow.
It's Makabe!
Takeshi's army will go after you as usual.
Next, two black belt holders
from Yoinjyuku karate school.
They're amazing.
They must have great motor skills.
This is a good chance.
Let's go!
KARATE BLACK BELT
MAIKO ARAI (36)
Makabe is around.
-Is he trying to scare her?
-He's coming.
Is he also jumping across?
He fell into the water.
-His body is...
-Oh dear!
Makabe got in the way.
-I'm out.
-It's scary.
-Let's go!
-You can do it!
KARATE BLACK BELT
RIRIKO KOHINATA (24)
You're doing good!
-She's fast.
-Yeah, she's fast.
You can do it!
Makabe!
You're so good!
He's too slow to catch her.
Two at the same time.
What's the point of him being there?
-You nearly made it.
-I'm so disappointed.
It's funny that you both fell
at the same time.
Really? I couldn't tell though.
I knew he was chasing me,
but I kept my own pace.
-Were you worried he'd catch you?
-Not at all.
-I ignored him.
-Ignored?
-She didn't even notice him.
-Damn you!
-Oh no.
-You're actually scared, right?
No. I am a black belt.
I see.
He's actually being kind.
The next challenger is...
the runner-up
in the Andorra Ultra Trail Race,
which is considered
the toughest race in the world.
Really?
Kenichi Yamamoto,
a leading trail runner in Japan.
A trail runner.
This is similar to using
trail running techniques.
I think trail running is similar
to the Dragon God's Pond.
That's what I came here to find out.
-His intro is long, so he'll succeed.
-Probably.
KENICHI YAMAMOTO (42)
Let's go!
You need the speed. That's right.
-Right! Good!
-He's stable.
What happened? Did he slip?
-No.
-He sank.
-I failed.
-I'm sorry.
-I was terrible.
-It was so close. Well done.
Not even a leading professional athlete
could conquer it.
Is there anyone capable
of conquering the pond today?
There's someone who is passionate
about clearing this game.
REVENGE
I'm here to try again.
MAJOR OIL COMPANY EMPLOYEE
HIROAKI SHINGA (62)
Seriously?
-After 35 years.
-He was in the show back then.
I'm Shinga, from Chiba prefecture.
He was 26 years old.
-General Tani looks so young!
-Amazing!
I work for a lubricating oil company.
Hiroaki Shinga participated
in Takeshi's Castle 35 years ago.
He went to the final!
HE LOST AT THE KARTS BATTLE
35 YEARS AGO
He reached the final battle,
but unfortunately he lost.
These are my daughters,
and this is my son-in-law.
He came here for a second chance,
with his family this time.
-Good luck, Shinga family!
-All right!
The eldest daughter, Megumi,
who almost qualified in high school tennis
for the national tournament,
takes up the challenge.
MEGUMI ISA (36)
I can do it!
Hey, the eldest daughter!
-Did she hit it?
-She hit her face.
The eldest daughter, her face...
Next, Midori, the second daughter,
who participates to celebrate
her mother's 60th birthday,
because she wanted to impress her.
MIDORI SHINGA (32)
Let's go!
Second daughter, good luck!
That area... Oh no!
-Why do they jump there?
-Is it just the momentum?
-It's scary.
-Wow. Amazing.
At the same place...
They jumped to the same place.
They're sisters.
They're awesome.
While Megumi fell
into the stone-free area,
Midori also dove boldly.
They are in perfect synch, Shinga family.
Shall I go now?
Dad.
-Here he comes.
-He's a legend. He's back after 35 years.
Good luck, Dad!
What a nice family!
HIROAKI SHINGA (62)
I'll make it!
Good luck!
-Dad!
-He's the best one so far.
-So close.
-He even stepped on a sinking stone.
Maybe you can continue with the momentum.
-It was close.
-So close.
You almost made it.
I'm out. Damn it.
-He hasn't changed.
-What an amazing guy.
He overcame the first sinking stone
with determination.
But he eventually fell.
Once again, Shinga has been defeated
by Takeshi's Castle.
-What a shame.
-I'm so disappointed.
-I couldn't get my revenge.
-I know.
-What a shame!
-Try again.
-It's a pity I couldn't do it.
-Well done.
-Thank you!
No one cleared Dragon God's Pond.
The Fighting Spirit Award was given
to the three members of Boys and Men
who showed boldness in the challenge
and came close to the finish line.
So close.
4 SURVIVORS
Four people who received
the Fighting Spirit Awards
made it through.
Move forward
to bring down Ennosuke Castle!
What an incredible Dragon God's Pond!
My lord, Ennosuke, we have no survivors.
-There's no favoritism.
-That's right.
The guy who participated 35 years ago
came back again.
I'm quite moved.
-He brought his family.
-I know.
-That's right.
-It's the history of Takeshi's Castle.
This show has been on for so long that
eventually someone comes back for revenge.
-You're right.
-"I'll avenge my great-grandpa."
-That'd be great.
-Indeed.
Let's put them all down in the pond.
All right, the next one's Star Bowling.
Do you remember this?
FIFTH STRONGHOLD, STAY STILL IN A COSTUME
WHILE A GIANT BALL IS COMING AT YOU
-Star Bowling? With Ritsuko Nakayama?
-You remember.
Have you got AI Ritsuko?
I think Ritsuko Nakayama is good.
Star Bowling featured Ritsuko Nakayama,
a famous professional bowler back then.
What transformations have taken place
over the past 34 years?
Let's talk to them.
It looks like a lot of work.
SHIGEKI NAKANISHI
-Hi, there.
-Hello.
-We're too busy right now.
-Are you?
-I'm nostalgic!
-It's called Star Bowling.
-I'm 1.63 m tall, but it's hard to keep...
-You'll fall!
...the balance.
-Is it hard?
-Besides, I'm squatting.
Really? So is it bad
if it sways even a little?
-Please don't rock me.
-Are you saying you want me to?
No. Never.
What? He rejected my call?
What is he doing?
Excuse me.
Have you seen a guy in a black cape
and a whistle around here?
Over there.
Over there? I'm not sure which way to go.
It's been 34 years since I've been here.
-But he's over there.
-Yes.
I have no choice.
I feel happy to be up here.
GENERAL
HAYATO TANI
Looks like fun.
You have survived, my elite warriors.
-Fantastic.
-He's great.
It's Star Bowling. It's a team game.
You have to help each other.
What a stage!
Did you get it?
Charge!
-Go!
-Keep going!
STAR BOWLING
DIFFICULTY RATING: 72%
If you're still standing after a huge
bowling ball is thrown at you, you win.
It must suck to be the number one pin.
If you can stand until the end
and overcome the fear
of the incoming ball,
you have completed the game.
-It's scary, right?
-Yes.
Who's that?
-Wow!
-There she goes!
-Kyoko Hamaguchi!
-Yes!
FORMER FREESTYLE WRESTLER
KYOKO HAMAGUCHI
Takeshi's Castle!
-It's Star Bowling!
-Oh my, she's here.
Are you ready?
-She'll be out of control again.
-Right.
Good. Mr. Daruma is...
THE BATTLE AT NAOMI CASTLE
At the battle of
Mr. Daruma is Falling Down,
she was out of control,
ignoring all rules. Now she is back!
It could never end peacefully.
That's not fair!
There's someone I want you to meet.
My precious dad.
Animal Hamaguchi came to join us
as a special guest!
-Fantastic.
-Great.
-We love Kyoko.
-Kyoko!
Here comes her dad.
Let's call our fighting spirit 10 times.
Let's go.
Fighting spirit! Fighting spirit!
They're great. Awesome.
FORMER PRO WRESTLER
ANIMAL HAMAGUCHI
All right!
-They're wonderful.
-Nice.
We have these 10 pins for the first round.
The Female College Student Team
has participated in every battle so far.
Beach Tennis Friends, that includes
a coach of the Japanese national team.
-They can help each other.
-Right.
-Wait and see. We'll have a blast!
-All right! Let's begin!
I feel bad for number one.
FIRST THROW
10 PINS LEFT
I'm gonna push hard. There!
Get the ball rolling.
Keep it rolling!
-It went to the left.
-Keep going!
It went off to the side. That's lucky.
Wow! Only one pin fell.
MINAMI SUDO (22)
SECOND THROW
9 PINS LEFT
-I'm aiming at number one.
-Okay.
-She can throw twice.
-I see.
There it goes!
All right! Come on!
-That's okay.
-It's not going straight.
-The pin at the back fell down by itself.
-It's down!
No way!
How dare you?
Hey, Kotaro!
KOTARO AIZAWA (42)
I'm out.
HIROMI OKAZAKI (44)
I'm counting on you guys!
DAISUKE TSURUOKA (38)
THIRD THROW
6 PINS LEFT
Come on!
She can throw as many times as she likes?
Does she decide?
In Star Bowling, Kyoko Hamaguchi
throws the ball and decides the rules.
THE BATTLE AT NAOMI CASTLE
She was out of control at the battle
of Mr. Daruma is Falling Down.
Hamaguchi can throw the ball
as many times as she feels like.
You are out!
-That's so unfair.
-That's not fair.
It should be two throws, tops.
THIRD THROW
6 PINS LEFT
-Come on!
-That's not fair!
Let's go!
Go and get it!
It's unfair that she can go
as many times as she wants.
That's going at number one.
MIYUKO ISAKA (21)
Two pins fell down!
I'll leave it to you now!
NAOAKI YAMAMOTO (32)
I don't know why the contestants
don't say it's not fair.
Come on!
Number three, did you say "come on"?
I love that attitude.
FOURTH THROW
4 PINS LEFT
I'll go hard on the next one too.
-Let's go!
-Come on!
Show us what you've got!
-All right!
-Come on!
-Let's go!
-Keep it rolling!
What's this? How will this game end?
Keep going!
Honestly, how do you end this?
Number three!
TEAM WORLD RANK BEACH TENNIS PLAYERS
KEITA ISEKI (30)
She got me!
Let those three win now.
-We want those three to win.
-I think that's fair.
Next, number two.
She's still doing it.
Why is that?
There are three pins left.
Will they all fall?
-I just hope one of them stands.
-Yeah.
-I hope so.
-Good luck.
-Airi!
-Stay there!
FIFTH THROW
3 PINS LEFT
-Hit number two, then four and eight.
-Two, four, and eight.
Can she really still throw?
-Brutal is the right word.
-I agree.
Was this game always like this?
-Keep it going!
-Looks good.
Oh dear. It'll hit them.
-Wow! This is amazing.
-Isn't it?
He withstood it! That pin withstood it!
-She'll stop now.
-For sure.
If she does it again, she's a devil.
She's crying, but the rule is so unfair.
What's your name, number eight?
I'm Michan!
Dad, Michan is awesome!
Okay. Fantastic.
You win the battle
against the Hamaguchi family!
At last, it's over.
Finally, it's over. Number eight.
Michan! Michan!
-Congrats!
-Thank you.
MITSUHIRO OGAWA (54)
He's great.
You're so emotional. How was it?
While everyone was losing,
I couldn't lose,
so I kept strong for them.
By the way, those two at the front
were college girls.
In that case, it was a terrible game.
Look at his T-shirt.
It must've been so hot.
He's soaked as if he fell
into the Dragon God's Pond.
Indeed.
These are the 10 pins
for the second round.
Fellow bartenders
led by the muscular Ichikawa.
Fellow motorcycle media members
participating in matching outfits.
FIRST THROW
10 PINS LEFT
Take them down with the first throw.
Show us your power!
-Number one...
-Aim straight at the center.
All right!
Right at the center!
Come on, you fool!
"You fool."
-Go! Keep going!
-Keep going!
-Number one.
-Oh no! It hit them.
-It stays up.
-It did.
Okay.
Why did I fall? I didn't get hit.
KINA SHIMADA (28)
SECOND THROW
8 PINS LEFT
Which number shall we aim at?
Number three?
All right!
-The pins at the front have no chance.
-No.
Keep going!
-Oh no.
-Stay there.
Keep going!
-Number three stayed up.
-It stayed.
-That's amazing.
-It hit on purpose.
I got hit.
TAKAO AOKI (49)
But it was fun.
He said it was fun. That's good.
THIRD THROW
7 PINS LEFT
Number three was great.
He withstood the hit.
Keep going!
Wow.
-Look at that.
-I did it!
-They're trying to support each other.
The ball came straight at me.
AKITOMO AMAI (26)
I had no choice.
He's right.
FOURTH THROW
4 PINS LEFT
-Hit them all.
-Okay.
The fourth throw now?
That's good.
-This is a good one.
-Keep going.
Hit it!
They're all down!
-You did it!
-I did it!
Why did she hit them all?
This game is unfair.
ALL FAILED
You all failed! You all failed!
What a terrible phrase. "You all failed!"
This is the third and final round.
Yutaka Kyan is an important pin.
And four members of BMK,
the junior group of Boys and Men,
who performed well at Dragon God's Pond,
are up to the challenge.
Fighting spirit! Fighting spirit!
Well then.
Decades ago, there was a Takeshi's Castle.
A SUDDEN SPEECH BY KYOKO HAMAGUCHI
TAKESHI'S CASTLE AND DREAMS
Some of these people
wanted to participate then, but didn't.
But today, their dream has come true
and here they stand.
Those people are here.
What is she talking about?
I used to watch Takeshi's Castle
and loved it.
But now I'm here with my dad.
-This is the moment your dreams come true.
-It's a dream.
Life is a dream!
Make your dreams come true!
It's nice that Kyoko Hamaguchi
has gotten into this story setting.
Make your dreams come true!
They'll die. It's too hot.
That was a long speech. Let's begin.
YUTAKA KYAN (37)
My legs hurt.
The Hamaguchi family speaks passionately,
but the shooting took place in August.
Inside the costume, the challengers
are losing their strength.
They just want to get on with it.
FIRST THROW
10 PINS LEFT
Okay. Let's go. First, it's number one.
-I'll aim at the center.
-So scary!
Okay. Let's go.
Wow. It's scary.
It's gonna hit Kyan.
-Kyan is so light!
-Oh, Kyan!
A clean sweep with a single throw?
-It's gonna hit Kyan.
-Good luck, Kyan!
-Kyan is so light!
-Oh, Kyan!
-A clean sweep with a single throw?
-It hit right at the center.
So many of them fell down.
Kyoko Hamaguchi's best throw so far,
knocking down six pins in one throw.
Sorry, everyone.
YUTAKA KYAN (37)
I couldn't stay up.
As a referee I can say
her throw was a foul!
REFEREE
GANDHARA SUZUKI (50)
SECOND THROW
4 PINS LEFT
Next, number two.
-He's angry.
-This is fun.
Dad, you go next.
-Let's go!
-Bring it on!
They're up for it.
-Keep going.
-Go!
They'll all fall down.
-Number eight and nine!
-I thought all of them were doomed.
Number eight and nine!
-Great.
-You got two, Dad.
Will they let them be?
He's a legend. I'm so disappointed.
RAITO SHIMIZU (29)
Okay.
It's the worst scenario. Eight pins
knocked down after just two throws.
I'll go see them.
Two members from BMK are still standing.
KYOSUKE KOMETANI (25)
KENNOSUKE MATSUOKA (21)
Will the game end here
and will they survive?
That was left to Kyoko,
who has a weakness for handsome men.
Well.
What?
Number eight and nine, you win!
-They cleared the game.
-They're BMK members.
-We did it!
-They did it.
Two members of BMK,
a junior group of Boys and Men,
got through this game!
-They must have a good balance.
-Well done! Well done!
She says "well done,"
but she knocked the others down.
I know.
3 SURVIVORS
Three survivors withstood the relentless
attacks from the Hamaguchi family.
Ennosuke Ichikawa's castle
is almost there!
The game was so unfair.
-Wasn't that fun?
-It was fun.
Some could overcome being hit.
It may not be just luck.
Some tried to hold others.
Everyone tries to help each other.
-Let's call the count.
-Yeah.
-Our lord!
-It was fun.
-The Hamaguchi family is wonderful.
-Yes.
Rentaro Mikuni and Koichi Sato
wouldn't do that.
-No, they wouldn't.
-No.
Here, we have three games for the losers.
The last chance
for those who lost the battle.
I'll try my best!
HOKKAIDO UNIVERSITY STUDENT, GERMANY
FRANZISKA HEUMANN (29)
Here's the first quiz.
Question.
Which country is next to Italy?
That's difficult.
A, France. B, Spain.
-I don't know.
-Spain?
Which is correct?
-She's from Europe.
-Yeah.
-It's B.
-Do you think so?
The UK is next to France, right?
She's sliding that way.
It looks fun, but it might hurt your back.
Men can't do that.
Yeah. You hurt your crotch.
Keep going.
-She's going for A.
-Isn't France in the north?
-Is that so?
CORRECT ANSWER
A: FRANCE
-It's A.
-I see.
RETURN TO THE FRONT
-It's C.
-It's Tug of War.
-All right.
-He can do it.
PINUP MODEL
JUN AMAKI
FORMER SPANISH EMBASSY EMPLOYEE, SPAIN
MARC AURA RODRIGO (22)
Ready, go!
-Hey!
-Wow!
He was lucky.
RETURN TO THE FRONT
Takeshi, wait for me!
AKIYOSHI SAGAWA (30)
Okay, let's go!
-Hurry up! That's right.
-He's fast.
You'll make it.
-Pick up a container.
-To the left!
You can get it!
You can do it!
He's got it!
-He did it.
-He got it!
I did it!
-Congrats!
-He did it.
RETURN TO THE FRONT
All right!
TRANSLATOR, PERU
DAVID RAMIREZ (30)
JULIANA NO TATARI, LEADER
AYU ENATSU (36)
It's because I'm a drummer.
Hang in there!
FORMER SPANISH EMBASSY EMPLOYEE, SPAIN
ALVARO CAMACHO CRIADO (27)
BOYMEN AREA TRAINEE
YUKI NAKASHITA (20)
What happened?
INTERNET ENTERTAINER, USA
AJ ERENDS (33)
DATA ANALYST, SPAIN
RUBEN BARRENA (34)
ANIMATOR
CHANG SHIN YUAN (31)
JULIANA NO TATARI
FUYUYUKI DUNK ASUNARO (34)
Dive!
BODYBUILDER
NAOTAKA YOKOKAWA
PRO WRESTLER
TOMOAKI HONMA
Damn it!
For Katsumi Yamada, who dreams
to get the title of Mr. Takeshi's Castle,
this game is his very last chance
to survive.
MR. SASUKE
KATSUMI YAMADA (56)
-I'm counting on you!
-All right!
-I can't help but cheer for him.
-I hope Mr. Yamada gets through.
-To the left! Hurry!
-It's coming!
-That's good. At the center.
-Get it!
He did it. It got in.
Yeah!
Katsumi Yamada finally cleared the game
for the first time.
RETURN TO THE FRONT
He's back to the front line again.
I'm so glad.
The army, which had been split into four,
finally came together.
LOSER RESURRECTION
Including those who won the loser's games
and got the Fighting Spirit Award.
Twenty-four brave challengers
take on the sixth stronghold
to survive the final battle.
24 SURVIVORS
Everyone, you've survived this long.
THE CAPTAIN
SUBARU KIMURA
Do you have any strength left?
-They're pumped up.
-Fantastic!
-That lady in a blue jacket.
-Me?
How do you feel now?
-It's too difficult.
-Okay.
Thanks to my good luck, I got this far.
-Thanks to your good luck. Keep it going.
-Thanks!
-Good.
-I think I used up all my good luck.
She used it all up.
Don't say such a thing. You'll be fine!
I'm sure you'll make it to the end.
Are you up for it?
Can you make it till the end?
Fantastic!
Now you'll play a tough game, Block Block.
All right, let's go.
Looks amazing!
Charge!
Good luck!
Nice! That's good!
BLOCK BLOCK
DIFFICULTY RATING: 92%
-Block Block, go and get it!
-Good luck!
The spirit of the army that gathered
from the four strongholds is at its peak.
They can use this momentum
to bring down the next stronghold!
It's like a festival.
I'm the biggest Takeshi's Castle
geek of all.
It's Murphy!
The first challenger of Block Block
is a frenzied fan of Takeshi's Castle,
Joshua Murphy from America.
-Murphy.
-Good luck.
Murphy!
DIEHARD FAN OF TAKESHI'S CASTLE
JOSHUA MURPHY (31)
-Go, Murphy!
-To the next block.
Why?
Why? How come?
-Is it so hard?
-It was the wrong timing.
He just gave up.
-Why did you come?
-He didn't even try.
He was just sitting there.
-Good luck!
-You're now rooting for them.
You'd rather cheer for them
instead of trying.
Charge!
-They need to watch out for the triangle.
-You're right.
-The rotation of the triangle.
-Right.
They're so excited.
RUBEN BARRENA (34)
I'll do it for my fellow participants.
-Go, Ballena!
-Let's go.
GET TO THE GOAL
BY JUMPING ON ROTATING BLOCKS
Those blocks are huge!
-Get there.
-Quick!
That's it! Next one!
Watch out!
It's so dangerous!
It's so much fun.
The next challenger...
She came to Japan
because of her love of Japanese animation.
Erika wants to promote Japanese anime
through her own costumes.
SUPPORT ENGINEER, SPAIN
ERIKA MARTINEZ (30)
I'll try my best!
-Good luck!
-Be careful!
Erika! Erika!
-This is so much fun.
-It's amazing.
You got this!
Erica!
Keep calm.
That's it! Go!
What was that?
SIGH...
-It's tough. No chance.
-No chance?
She's right.
-Can anyone finish this?
-I know.
Who created this game?
-She's pissed off.
-Yeah.
They're crazy.
She says we're crazy.
Next...
Aren't those the Boys and Men?
Next, three members of Boys and Men
who got the Fighting Spirit Award
at the battle of Dragon God's Pond.
BOYS AND MEN: TAMURA, HONDA, HIRAMATSU
They'll be fine.
-Charge!
-They have a good sense of rhythm.
I'll clear this. Come on, Boys and Men!
Good luck!
BOYS AND MEN
YUKIHISA TAMURA (31)
Tamura!
Keep going!
-He's good.
-Great!
-Great.
-He can do it.
Oh, no! He'll fall.
He overcame the triangle.
-He rushed to the next one.
-He couldn't get on it.
Why?
That was a nice try!
You need to jump when it's like this,
-otherwise you can't get on it.
-Indeed.
Charge!
All right! I got this.
BOYS AND MEN
TAKAFUMI HONDA (29)
Prince! Prince!
Prince!
Go, Prince!
Prince! Prince!
Show them what a real prince is made of.
He's okay.
You're doing great, Prince!
-Prince!
-He's fine. Great.
-He's awesome.
-He's gone that way? No!
So close!
I've got it now.
-I can say whatever I like as an observer.
-Yes.
The next challenger from Boys and Men,
Kento Hiramatsu.
BOYS AND MEN
KENTO HIRAMATSU (27)
Keep going!
That was too late. It's difficult.
He couldn't overcome
the blue plus sign either.
All three failed
at exactly the same place.
They're good friends.
The same spot.
-At exactly the same place.
-The three of us at the same place.
The hardest part of Block Block
is clearly the blue cross.
Getting over the blue cross
is the key to clearing this game.
YOUNGER BROTHERS BMK ACCEPT THE CHALLEGE!
These young brothers
come to settle the score.
The next challengers are members of BMK,
a junior group of Boys and Men.
Two Star Bowling winners
who endured the relentless attacks
from the Hamaguchi family,
now take on the challenge.
Get on the updraft!
They're young. They can do it.
Charge!
All right! I'll do my best!
BMK
KYOSUKE KOMETANI (25)
-Komechan!
-Good!
Get to the blue cross first.
You're doing good! You can do it!
-He got there.
-Awesome!
The next block is the star.
Can he make it? Oh, no...
When someone clears it,
the others will know how.
That's right.
Kometani reached the yellow star
for the first time.
A brilliant attempt to encourage
the army to follow suit.
-Komechan was great.
-Yeah. He showed us his spirit.
As his fellow team member, I feel proud
and I want to clear this game.
-Come on!
-Awesome!
Go for it!
-I'll do it!
-Good luck!
BMK
KENNOSUKE MATSUOKA (21)
They're so pumped up.
It's like a festival.
Too slow! No, he did it.
Get on it quick!
Good!
All right!
Great! He did it!
-Keep going!
-Get over there!
Quick! Go quick!
His strength is running out!
-Go back to the blue one!
-Go back!
Almost there!
So close!
Matsuoka was very close
to the finish line,
but the rotation of the block
pushed him back and he fell.
He couldn't conquer Block Block.
-You were so close.
-I'm sorry!
One more step...
-He's losing his voice.
-This is so much fun.
-You did so well!
-Thank you.
-Well done!
-Thanks!
The next challenger
is Risa Okuma, the only challenger
who cleared From Right and Left.
It's Okuma!
Can she conquer Block Block as well?
-She's hopeful.
-Charge!
RISA OKUMA (22)
I'm the only one to have cleared
the first game. I believe I can do this!
We know! Good luck!
Risa!
Good luck!
-Keep calm!
-You got this!
-Good luck!
-Those blocks are huge.
-Yeah.
You're doing great. Stay calm.
Keep calm.
-Next one. She'll jump. Oh no...
-Not that way!
Keep calm.
-Next one. She'll jump. Oh no...
-Not that way!
That was the wrong timing.
She was too late.
Is that the right timing? Really?
I know. So does everyone.
She seemed to have timed it carefully,
but she crashed head-on into a green wall.
Takeshi's Castle is not that easy.
I'm so disappointed.
Was it difficult?
Well. I couldn't think properly.
You were too hasty.
When should I go?
Hey, Kyan!
YUTAKA KYAN (37)
The army's elite continue to take on
one difficult challenge after another.
WORLD RANK BEACH TENNIS PLAYER
MITSUHIRO OGAWA (54)
That's amazing.
CLEARED MUSHROOM PLOP
RYOTA YOSHIDA (18)
He's great.
Yet, no one has succeeded.
The fiercest challengers
are falling into the water.
OTTER FAIRY
CHIITAN
That's too dangerous.
It says "Mostly successful."
-Really?
-Not even close.
-Was it mostly successful?
-No way!
Haru Yamaguchi,
a current high school student
who successfully cleared
a very difficult game, Mushroom Plop.
-He's sporty.
-Sure.
I'd like to be the youngest
to clear this one and get everyone going.
-He'll be a hero if he makes it.
-Charge!
-Good luck!
-He might make it.
Let's go!
-He's hopeful.
-He's a fast runner.
Show us what you've got!
Haru! Haru!
HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
HARU YAMAGUCHI (16)
Haru! Haru!
-That's right!
-Great!
-Fantastic!
-He's still going!
-Go!
-Awesome!
-You got this! Go!
-He'll make it!
He did it!
-Go!
-Awesome!
-You got this! Go!
-He'll make it!
He did it!
-You got this! Go!
-He'll make it!
He did it!
You got this! Go!
-He did it!
-Seriously?
All right!
Is he for real?
Fantastic!
Awesome!
You did it!
Well done!
-He's awesome!
-Seriously.
-He's so lean.
-The only survivor?
Why could he clear it that easily?
He overcame the blocks so smoothly,
and finished in a spectacular fashion!
A high school student, Haru Yamaguchi,
will advance to the final battle
at Ennosuke Castle!
Well done!
-Congrats!
-Thanks!
-You're the first one to clear it.
-You're awesome.
When I was interviewed earlier,
I said I would clear it first.
-I'm so glad I actually did it.
-You're super cool!
With this spirit,
you can win the final battle.
-Let's do that!
-Congratulations!
Thank you!
Mr. Yamada's coming.
-It's him.
-Mr. Yamada!
This man's time has finally come.
We believe in him.
He came here dreaming to get
the title of Mr. Takeshi's Castle.
Yamada didn't perform well at all.
That was awful.
At the Loser Resurrection,
he cleared a game for the first time.
With this momentum,
can he make it to the final battle?
I'm sure he'll pull it off!
I'll run through the red, green,
and blue blocks to get to the yellow one.
I'm not afraid of falling anymore.
I've fallen over and over again.
-Good luck.
-Thanks.
Good luck.
"Everyone calls me Mr. Sasuke.
"It can't end here.
"Younger fellows love me.
Other challengers shed tears.
"I owe it to all of you
to live up to your expectations.
"I'll prove it to you right here and now.
"Katsumi Yamada can still do it!"
-Mr. Yamada, show us you're a legend here!
-Please!
Good luck, Mr. Yamada!
-Good luck!
-You got this!
Will Mr. Sasuke be able to get the title
of Mr. Takeshi's Castle?
Katsumi Yamada, 56 years old.
The timing is key.
I'll get through this. Count on me.
Yamada!
They're cheering for Yamada.
He's a legend after all.
Can he take those cheers
and turn them into power?
Can Mr. Sasuke get across in one go?
He said he was going to run through it.
He got to the green one.
-Is he okay? He's calm.
-Watch out.
Can he clear Block Block?
-You got it!
-Is he okay?
He needs to get over this one.
Otherwise, he'll fall backwards.
He's getting slower. Yamada!
Yamada!
What a way to fall!
-What was that?
-What a way to fall!
-You got it!
-He's all right.
The sixth stronghold,
Block Block in the dark of night.
Katsumi Yamada,
in a dark Takeshi's Castle,
again disappearing beneath the water.
He doesn't show us
any prowess at Takeshi's Castle.
What was that then?
He didn't panic, not even once.
How come he's so calm?
I tried to get over it with my legs.
Look at his hair through those holes...
A student settles the score
for his master.
Here he comes.
Sasuke finalist, Yoshiyuki Yamamoto.
He's great.
To reach the final of Sasuke,
it was Mr. Yamada who guided him
through hard training.
I can still do it.
He and Yamada always
worked together at Takeshi's Castle,
and Mr. Yamada has been
his biggest supporter,
working together
and improving each other's skills.
For his master's sake,
he wants to advance
to the final battle at all costs.
-Here he goes.
-Charge!
-His student is good.
-He can make it.
Sasuke finalist, Yoshiyuki Yamamoto,
29 years old.
I'll clear this!
He's the ace from the Black Tigers.
Katsumi Yamada couldn't get the title
of Mr. Takeshi's Castle.
Now he entrusts his spirit to his student.
YOSHIYUKI YAMAMOTO (29)
He started moving,
while he hears his name.
He jumped onto the green one.
He's calm.
The same green block
his master couldn't overcome.
He needs to jump to the blue cross.
He's very calm.
He moved onto the blue block.
He did it.
He's the absolute ace, expected
to win a flawless victory in Sasuke.
He's getting over the rotating blue cross.
-Cheering and clapping.
-There he is.
His master's cheering for him.
His master entrusted him
with the title of Mr. Takeshi's Castle.
Getting over the yellow star
and he threw himself onto the goal!
-Wow!
-He's awesome!
Yoshiyuki Yamamoto!
His steel-like body
and his cheerful nature.
-He looks proud.
-Yeah. He did it.
He settled the score for his master!
The second winner!
I did it!
2 SURVIVORS
Thanks to his success,
now two challengers cleared Block Block.
Finally, we'll have the final battle
at Ennosuke Castle.
Wow! Two challengers!
Two of them. They got through.
That was Block Block.
I thought I was done,
but now I have to go to the castle.
-That's right.
-You have to.
Two challengers made it to the final.
-That boy with super motor skills...
-Yamaguchi!
-He's fantastic!
-I know!
-Yes.
-He's awesome.
We should be careful.
Plus Yamamoto, Mr. Yamada's student
from the Black Tigers.
-He avenged his master.
-Sure.
-Count!
Are you gonna be okay?
We'll have a head-on battle now.
You can't afford to lose.
Ennosuke, make sure you win. All right?
Of course, I will.
I'll get ready and be on my way now.
Don't rattle on. I'm counting on you.
Trust me!
He says, "Trust me,"
but the count says, "Don't rattle on."
This isn't a conversation.
The AI is starting to rattle a little...
We'll fight for you, our lord.
I trust you. I'm counting on you.
-Shall we go now?
-Yes, let's go!
-Let's go!
-Yes!
The brave warriors who have conquered
the impregnable strongholds
and made it to the final battle,
now charge toward Ennosuke Castle.
I can't wait.
Are you excited?
Here comes the lord of the castle!
LORD OF THE THIRD FORTRESS
ENNOSUKE ICHIKAWA
It's time for a battle!
He was born for it. Excellent. So cool.
He looks so cool.
"It's time for a battle."
You're right, Lord Ennosuke.
You're an Omodakaya. You're so cool.
Omodakaya!
But how was it? Amazing, right?
I thought it was like Disneyland.
-Isn't it?
-I got so excited.
-Takeshi's Castle, right?
-That's great.
-Wait a second!
-What?
What is this?
-Hey, you. I've finally found you.
-What?
That is my line.
-What's up with him?
-Something's going on.
I'm the one who appointed you
as the captain.
Right...
-But, I heard a rumor.
-What is it?
I hear you are fighting this battle
out of spite.
That's right. You're so right.
That hateful Beat Takeshi...
That hateful Beat Takeshi
who took my mother's life.
I'll avenge her.
-No!
-Shut up!
-Is this Takeshi's Castle?
-Oh dear.
-No, you can't do that!
-Shut up! Shut up!
Why can't I do that, Father?
-They're father and son.
-I see.
Are you done?
Sorry. We got so into it.
-I'm sorry.
-Sorry!
Lord Ennosuke is here.
Shall we begin the battle?
Shall we fight?
-Let's fight!
-Yes, let's fight!
-Right.
-Here they are.
-Here comes the army's elite.
-Sorry for keeping you waiting.
-A word, please.
-Yeah. Let's hear it.
I'll dedicate our victory to Mr. Yamada.
-I'll try my best!
-All right!
So far I've never failed.
So I want to win this battle and...
-move on to the next one.
-Okay!
They're not good with speeches,
but they're the elite, right?
-They're good.
-He's the youngest challenger of all.
-How old are you?
-I'm 16.
-Wow!
-Is he that young?
-It's better to pick young shoots early.
-Well said!
He's a nasty guy.
I want the young shoots to grow.
You're so nice.
-Be strong and fight.
-A word, please.
Sure.
All right!
-Prepare yourselves!
-Yes!
-We're up for it!
-Let's do our best!
That's great.
YABUSAME
The final battle of the night
is called Yabusame.
Both parties will board their carriages,
but only the army's will be mobile.
From there, they will aim at the target
on the other person's carriage.
The army wins if they can get
a ball into the red basket.
Takeshi's army wins
if their ball hits the blue banner.
But if both succeed, it'll be deemed
a draw and neither wins.
Come on, bring the shooting machine!
Finally!
-Here it comes.
-This is the one!
-Looks great!
-Yeah!
There you go.
Ennosuke's shooting machine looks so cool.
Looks quite rugged.
ONLY ONE WIN IS NEEDED
TO RECEIVE A MILLION YEN
The first challenger
is a high school student, Haru Yamaguchi.
He's a physical monster who cleared
the tough games Mushroom Plop
and Block Block,
and survived till the end.
This is great. I feel like a pilot.
-Can you do it?
-Of course I can. I'll try my best.
I'm nervous.
FATHER
MINORU
But I believe he will win.
-Wonderful.
-I know he can do it.
THE FIRST FORTRESS
UEDA CASTLE
At the battle of the first fortress,
Shinya Ueda's castle,
and the second fortress,
Naomi Watanabe's castle...
THE SECOND FORTRESS
NAOMI CASTLE
...the army unleashed a fantastic attack
and almost caught the enemy by surprise.
Today is the day
to throw the ball in and win!
-I can see a ball inside here.
-That's so close.
For the first round, from Takeshi's army,
the lord of the castle himself will fight.
What will happen?
YABUSAME
DIFFICULTY RATING: 200%
All right. Yabusame, first round.
Let's begin.
Good luck!
It's coming!
-It's a hit!
-You've got it!
Yeah!
It's coming again!
It's a hit!
That one hit the target!
-It hit again!
-You've got it!
It won't get in. Seriously?
THE ARMY FAILED
He failed?
-He failed?
-Oh no.
TAKESHI'S ARMY WINS
Lord Ennosuke, great job!
Seriously? So disappointing.
That was an onslaught from Lord Ennosuke.
Once the third shot hit,
he didn't lose the target.
A robust attack.
This one.
On the other hand,
the balls from the army...
One ball actually got in. So close.
-Oh dear.
-So close!
-He did well.
-One ball got in.
-Wow.
-He's amazing.
-Well done.
-Nice work.
-Lord Ennosuke is the winner!
-Yeah!
-Thanks.
-Yay!
Wonderful.
-What a shame. I'm so disappointed.
-I bet. What do you think of the rules?
It's so unfair. Very unfair.
Very unfair?
The last challenger from the army
is Katsumi Yamada's best student,
Yoshiyuki Yamamoto.
-If you hit it, you'll win. Good luck.
-Thank you.
The dream of getting the title
of Mr. Takeshi's Castle
was pursued by his mentor, Katsumi Yamada.
Now that Yamada is out,
his unfulfilled dream
has been entrusted
to his best student, Yamamoto.
Finally, please give him
a motivating and helpful piece of advice.
-You can do it! Let's do this!
-All right. I will do it!
WIFE
MARINA
Charge!
All right!
-Thank you.
-You can do it!
From Takeshi's army, it's Osamu Shitara.
I get anxious when it's my turn.
I've been watching their attacks,
and the ball hits this target.
The next one
is the guy from Black Tiger, right?
I'm scared.
But I'll beat him.
Takeshi's Castle
can't be brought down that easily.
-You're right.
-Sure.
Will the army pull off
a miraculous victory?
It's the final round of Yabusame.
Here comes the second round
of Yabusame.
Charge!
You got this!
-Keep shooting.
-Good!
You got this!
Good! Keep going!
You've got it!
You got this!
Good. You got it!
It's all right!
Did I get it?
THE ARMY FAILED
We won!
It didn't get in.
-Damn it!
-Oh no!
TAKESHI'S ARMY WINS
I'm so glad.
-You smashed the target!
-You did!
Before the game started,
Shitara was anxious.
He shot balls at the center of the target
and smashed it.
Takeshi's army defeated the opponents
and won a total victory.
-Well, well...
-A total victory!
Takeshi's army won!
We did it!
-Fireworks!
-Looks awesome!
-We never lose!
-But if I were a challenger,
I would go, "Damn it! There's no way
I could make it fit into that hole!"
Next, Takeshi is coming!
NEXT EPISODE,
ROBUST ATTACK AT TAKESHI'S MAIN CASTLE
The strongest army in history finally
launches an attack on Takeshi's Castle.
An elite group of challengers
selected from the three previous battles
will take on a more challenging game
in an attempt to bring down the castle.
The most powerful assassin is coming.
Hey, merman.
Well done.
WHAT IS CAPTAIN KIMURA UP TO...
THE ASSASSINS AT ENNOSUKE CASTLE
WATER MARSHAL, TOM BROWN
It's been a long time
since I've seen such a fun show.
-Everyone is pumped up.
-Yeah.
It's a show where you can feel the energy.
STRUGGLING WITH THE INCREDIBLE MACHINE,
YOSHIAKI UMEGAKI
WATER GUN
I can shoot quite far with this,
but I haven't used it.
HE WANTED TO USE THE WATER GUN
No time to use this.
I want to shoot someone too.
MERMAN, AUDREY KASUGA
The merman got her!
A GREAT JOB SINKING THE ARMY
ONE AFTER ANOTHER
He sank. Yes!
This gun's got some fire power.
BOWLING MONSTERS
HAMAGUCHI FAMILY
-This is the place for Dad and Kyoko.
-The place for us!
-You throw a ball and make them fall.
-Right.
-Number two and eight!
-Go and get it!
Go and get it!
SERIOUS MEETING AND PRACTICE
I used to watch this. It was fun.
THOUGHTS ABOUT THE SHOW
I'm on the show now.
It's like a dream, but it's real.
GOING ON A SHOOTING RAMPAGE!
Love, love, love!
It was so much fun.
Takeshi's Castle is fulfilling our dream.
-Let's say "Dream" 10 times.
-Okay.
Let's go.
Dream, dream, dream!
It's a dream!
-Love, love, love! Dream!
-All right!
THANK YOU FOR A GREAT JOB,
HAMAGUCHI FAMILY!
Thank you!