THIS PROGRAM WAS PRODUCED
UNDER THE SUPERVISION OF MEDICAL EXPERTS,
TAKING INTO CONSIDERATION THE HEALTH
AND SAFETY OF THE STAFF AND CONTESTANTS.
Gather round,
elite warriors!
THE YEAR 1986
Charge!
In 1986, a colossal battle broke loose.
THE IMPENETRABLE CASTLE
A castle so impenetrable,
only eight out of 127 battles
have ever seen its halls.
8 WINS, 118 LOSSES, 1 DRAW
WIN RATE 0.06%
That dreadful castle has reemerged
in the Land of the Rising Sun.
JAPAN
RESURRECTION
THE YEAR 2023
Charge!
Takeshi's Castle is back!
Fortified with extravagance and fortitude,
packed with new games,
it's the palace of your dreams!
WHO WILL EMERGE
AS THE BOLDEST WARRIOR?
NO TIME FOR FEAR
I'll bring justice upon you numbskulls!
Have a look and see for yourself.
TAKE NO PRISONERS
Victory is ours!
I'm gutted.
Tear it down
to take home...
ONE MILLION YEN
I will destroy you!
I made it!
Here we go!
Fall, fall till you can fall no further.
Struggle as you may,
he has you in the palm of his hand.
DANCE...
The man of the hour
that you've all waited for...
IN THE PALM OF HIS HAND
ARMY VS TAKESHI
Takeshi's Castle!
TAKESHI'S CASTLE
In the first monumental battle
in 34 years, 100 brave warriors
have been tasked with the mission
to tear down
three fortresses
that protect Takeshi's Castle.
The army's numbers dwindled
at the first fortress, Ueda Castle.
THE FIRST FORTRESS
UEDA CASTLE
In the end, they were left
with a frustrating defeat.
Victory is ours! We did it.
FAILED TO BEAT TAKESHI'S ARMY
CAPTAIN KIMURA DISAPPEARS
On top of that, Takeshi's army
has kidnapped Captain Kimura.
However, the army's fighting spirit
cannot be extinguished.
They've rounded up once again
and ready to conquer the second fortress.
THE BATTLES OF THE SECOND FORTRESS
Battles at the second fortress now begin
with the sound of the conch shell.
We opened auditions to the public,
out of which,
we chose 100 of the best.
Taking in the lessons learned
at Ueda Castle,
we gather participants
who are especially fit, from competitors
of the world renown Sasuke race
to pro wrestlers and Spartan racers.
What will become of them?
Meanwhile, Takeshi's Castle
has been moved closer
to the second fortress.
The formation for battle is now in place.
THE SECOND FORTRESS
NAOMI CASTLE
Here we are at the second fortress.
Let's greet the princess.
Sorry to keep you waiting, your highness.
LADY OF THE SECOND FORTRESS
NAOMI WATANABE
Come and get it.
-No, no.
-You're being reckless.
Princess, that's dangerous.
-I'm sure I was hit five or six times.
-My apologies.
The enemy is approaching.
-Are they close?
-Yes.
-An army of about 100 warriors.
-That's right.
-About 100? Not 100 exactly?
-That's correct.
We wanted exactly 100,
but people have lives.
NAOMI CASTLE
SEVEN FORTRESSES
Sometimes other things come up
and they have to cancel.
-What a real-life reason.
-So the numbers fluctuate.
I see.
So in conclusion, there is an army
of about 100 warriors approaching!
By the way, speaking of the count,
he's gone missing.
Missing?
-Yes.
-Oh, dear.
But we have an AI count
to help protect us.
-Shall we greet him?
-Yes, please.
Push.
Hey, what's up. So why did you reveal
that the army is an arbitrary number?
Well...
-Wow.
-It's better to be frank.
-Nowadays, people will fact-check us.
-True.
Since this is an AI, it can project
people other than the count, too.
-What's that?
-The AI is multifunctional?
-It can do many things.
-Is there someone you'd like to meet?
Really. Since this is a global broadcast,
I'd like to meet a foreign celebrity.
-Hi, Justin Bieber.
-Don't be silly. It's me, Justin.
-That sounds like Bobby Ologun.
-What's up, guys?
-No, it's me, Justin.
-No, you're Bobby.
-Let's turn him off.
-That's scary.
-How terrifying.
-Bobby must be his default character.
-Shall we get started?
-Yes, let's.
Could we have a word from you?
Listen up, army... I'll eviscerate you!
-This is great.
-What's with the face?
You look like a gritty hip-hop princess.
Princess of hip-hop.
What's this?
Hey, that's...
To Kimura
How dare you abandon your duties.
Could it be?
-He left me on read?
-That mouth.
I have no choice.
I guess it's my turn to take charge.
That voice.
Get back to basics.
The crowd is going wild.
Thank you for gathering,
my fearless warriors.
-I'm your captain, Hayato Tani.
-Captain!
Wow, it's him.
-It's Mr. Tani.
-Everyone used to imitate his "Charge!"
-He hasn't changed.
-Thank you.
Allow me to explain
for the younger Takeshi's Castle fans.
THE CAPTAIN
HAYATO TANI
This the legend who led the warriors
in the original broadcast.
Hayato Tani himself.
He's arrived today, fully prepared
to lead in Captain Kimura's absence.
The dreadful Count Takeshi
has currently gone missing.
Let's use that to settle this
34-year-old grudge.
-Look at them.
-I hope you all do your best.
-All of them look strong.
-Understood?
Our current mission
is to overthrow Naomi Castle,
that sits in front of Takeshi's Castle.
-You think they'll do it?
-I'm sure it won't be easy.
There will be challenges.
I hope you'll keep your wits about you.
Are you with me?
-Wow.
-It's Chiitan.
I'd like to take a moment
for introductions.
-I heard there's a Sasuke Jr. here?
-I'm here!
-Sasuke?
-Hi, I'm Sasuke Jr.
-There you are.
-Wow.
SASUKE CONQUEROR
YUSUKE MORIMOTO (30)
Yusuke Morimoto aka Sasuke Jr,
has won the race twice.
-He's so strong.
-What's your record?
-I've competed 15 times.
-And won every time?
I've won twice.
As the youngest person
to complete the course,
he earned his title of Sasuke Jr.
and is still an active competitor.
His name is Yusuke Morimoto.
Victory is ours!
Having been defeated
at the battle of Ueda Castle,
this time the army has gathered
superior warriors from Sasuke competitors.
The army even has competitors
from Spartan, the toughest race on earth,
as well as professional wrestlers
and exceptional athletes,
who are hell-bent
on avenging the previous army.
-That many athletes?
-They aren't playing around for this one.
I'd like to mark this 34 year gap
with the downfall of Takeshi's Castle
and we'll need all your help.
Our first challenge is The Border Wall.
THE BORDER WALL
DIFFICULTY RATING: 15%
COMIC DUO KITSUNE
HIROTSUGU OTSU &amp; KOSEI AWAJI
-It's the Kitsune duo.
-No one will get past us.
They're doing the fox dance.
Do your best, everyone.
-Charge!
-It's the OG "Charge!"
-Wow.
-Nice. It's lively.
The battle to conquer
the second fortress has begun.
Go, go, go!
COMIC DUO TOKYO HOTEISON
TAKERU &amp; SYOGO
-That speed.
-Look at how quick they are.
SPARTAN RACER
RYOTARO AIHARA (27)
-You're the first to arrive.
-Thank you.
-I wanted to beat the Sasuke champions.
-I see.
-I did it.
-Thank you.
SPARTAN RACERS TEAM
So this is the whole team?
You did great. Congrats.
REPORTERS - SANSHIRO
HIRONOBU KOMIYA &amp; SHUJI AIDA
-How was it?
-Cold-- I mean, warm.
FUTTSU POST OFFICE TEAM
SHUNSUKE KANEKO (40)
Proving their athletic capabilities,
the army clears the wall in no time.
DECATHLON RUNNER
HIROYOSHI USHIRO (27)
I didn't need the rope.
-They're spraying from that close?
-Everyone is determined
whether they're a prime athlete or not.
You get targeted with the hose
the longer it takes you to climb.
-Got it.
-And it becomes harder to climb.
-What a mess.
-The Samba guy that fell.
THREE MINUTES REMAINING
Help each other.
Those with an abundance of energy
help the others get over the wall.
With this momentum,
everyone might make it over the wall.
TEAM SASUKE
This was way easier than Sasuke.
IAIDO FIGHTER &amp; SPARTAN COACH
SHIHOMI SUEOKA &amp; MICHIKO SATO
-Piece of cake?
-Easy.
Determine to make them work for it,
Takeshi's army reveals another obstacle.
POWDER ATTACK
A new weapon, billowing clouds of powder
block the view ahead.
Powder Attack.
-It's such a simple name.
-Nothing clever about it.
TWO MINUTES REMAINING
This is relentless. What's happening?
The army doesn't give up easily.
They muster all their strength
and try to get everyone over the wall.
-Nice, you got this.
-This is sapping their energy.
-She went for it.
-She's soaking wet.
Amazing. I'm impressed.
MOM FRIENDS GROUP
KAMEZU
Everyone's happy
that their teammates made it.
TEAM YOUNG CEOS
TEAM SHOCHIKU GEINO TALENT AGENCY
We did it!
TEAM PRO WRESTLERS
TEAM EX CHEERLEADERS
TEAM OSAKA DRINKING BUDDIES
-I'm drenched.
-I'm pooped.
40 SECONDS LEFT
TWO WARRIORS REMAIN
With less than a minute left,
some warriors struggle to keep up
with the athletes of the group.
Oh, no, what are you going to do?
AIKIDO 2 DAN &amp; ENTREPRENEUR
KAZUNORI TAKISHIMA (46)
This is relentless!
-That looks rough.
-Climb-- I mean, make him fall.
-We should be rooting for him to fall.
-There's no time left.
20 SECONDS REMAINING
EGA-CHANNEL STAFF
THE BRIEF TROUPE L
-The Brief Troupe?
-He's on the staff at Ega-Channel.
-The Brief Troupe, okay.
-You got this.
That would be me, too.
10 SECONDS REMAINING
Go, keep going!
END OF BATTLE
They didn't make it.
TWO DROPOUTS
Unfortunately,
two warriors are out of the race.
-Only two? Most of them made it.
-Sadly, the army couldn't save everyone.
-You do judo?
-Aikido.
I'll throw them over my shoulder
on my way out.
-Could you just imagine that you did?
-I have, about five times.
Yes!
Hurrah!
And 111 warriors made it
over The Border Wall.
The road up ahead forks
towards future battles.
Time to head to the next fortress,
fearless army!
-Wow, awesome.
-What do you think so far, Princess?
-I got so excited.
-Me, too.
Seeing all of them trying their best.
-But only two people failed?
-We apologize for that.
-Most people are able to beat this level.
-I see.
-They tend to help each other as well.
-So it's a team event.
Right, so if you fail this event,
it might mean that no one likes you.
Those two are unpopular?
Shall we get to know
some of the most promising warriors?
We need to keep an eye
on this Sasuke Jr. fellow.
He's incredible.
The show, Sasuke, is as popular
as Takeshi's Castle worldwide.
And Sasuke Jr. has made a name
for himself as a legend.
-And now he's after Takeshi's Castle.
-Will we be okay?
-He's not to be underestimated.
-He's dangerous.
-Let's see what the AI count has to say.
-Okay.
What a great battle.
I feel that too many of them
have made it through this first battle.
But as you mentioned earlier,
comics that are unpopular here
don't make it in showbiz either.
Comedy is the business of serving people,
and the same can be said
for entrepreneurship.
It might be presumptuous to say this,
but people really show you
who they are in these situations.
-What wise words.
-We're in the business of people.
No one actually hates those two.
-Thank you, let's chat again soon.
-I look forward to it.
We do too.
-Today's Count Takeshi is kind.
-He is.
This episode, we have a new game
called Block Block.
WALK OVER ROTATING SHAPES
TO MAKE IT TO THE OTHER SIDE
What kind of game?
Apparently, we had to have
a custom motor made overseas
for this game.
-What?
-It's a motor that doesn't exist
in Japan and it had to be
custom ordered for this game.
We went overseas to make that happen.
That was the only way?
-It must be enormous.
-I guess.
Well then, let's have a look
at Block Block.
A completely new game that required
a special order of gigantic motors.
Not even Captain Tani could imagine
a game like this. What will happen?
Army, wonderful job making it over
The Border Wall.
You did it.
-"You did it."
-The battle ahead will be merciless.
This next game is called Block Block.
-That's huge. What's the scale?
-It's like nothing we've seen before.
I don't know anything about this.
Because Block Block is a new game
that was recently developed.
-I've never seen it.
-Well, it's brand new.
So I can't tell you much about it.
-They seem like they're having fun.
-But I have faith in you.
You're my most trustworthy warriors
and I hope
-you'll win and keep advancing.
-There are lots of women.
Understood?
BLOCK BLOCK
DIFFICULTY RATING: 89%
This will be interesting.
Hello, we, Tokyo Hoteison,
will be reporting on Block Block.
It's the same microphone
as Nobuaki Kakuda.
REPORTERS - TOKYO HOTEISON
TAKERU &amp; SYOGO
-Nice, Hoteison.
-Go!
IDOL CAFE ATTENDANT
YOYO
Here I go. This is scary!
That's huge.
-That's how big they are?
-So huge.
-It looks like a video game.
-I see why we needed special motors.
JUMP ACROSS ROTATING BLOCKS
AND GET TO THE OTHER SIDE
I'm scared!
-Impossible.
-It's too difficult.
It rotates toward you,
so you have to use momentum.
-That timing was off.
-You're right.
No, wrong timing.
-Totally wrong timing.
-Shouldn't have jumped then.
SHIMANE MOM FRIENDS GROUP
YOKO FUNAKOSHI (47)
-I'll do my best.
-The Moms Friends Group.
No, not there.
-You'll fall there.
-Totally wrong again.
-You're doing great.
-It's huge.
It must be hard to gauge from up there.
SILVER JEWELRY DESIGNER
HITOSHI KANNO (37)
Here I go.
Good luck.
-He makes silver jewelry.
-You got this. The timing is crucial.
-Timing-- wow.
-Wow. Run, run.
This is too hard.
-This is tough.
-He hit his head.
The warrior is here to get revenge.
HERE TO AVENGE HIS FATHER
KENGO EZAKI (40)
My father, Tatsunori, failed
the Strait of Gibraltar 34 years ago.
-Your father competed? He did?
-Yes, that's correct.
-I've come to avenge my father.
-I see.
-What a story.
-Ezaki's father competed
-at Takeshi's Castle 34 years ago.
-They look like twins.
Sadly, he was disqualified
at the Strait of Gibraltar.
So he fell in the net.
He'll compete wearing
the same festival robe
-that his father wore back then.
-Amazing.
We're the best. Ezaki family is on fire.
-You got this!
-Go, Dad!
-Be careful.
-Nice.
-Not so soon...
-But he's holding on.
-This is too complex.
-That's the trickiest part of it.
It's not a matter
of lack of determination.
Ezaki daringly faced the challenge
to avenge his father.
He was met with a frustrating fall
without making it to Strait of Gibraltar.
-Father and son alike.
-Next up...
OTTER FAIRY
CHIITAN
Chiitan, who fought valiantly
at Ueda Castle, is back for another round.
OTTER FAIRY
CHIITAN (ETERNALLY 0 YEARS OLD)
-You got this.
-Good luck, Chiitan. Go.
-Go, fairy Chiitan!
-No, pull them out.
-That's unsafe. This is dire.
-She's rushing. Pull her out quickly.
We will rescue Chiitan within seconds.
-You got this, keep going. They had that.
-Our next challenger is...
I don't think anyone will make it.
EX OLYMPIAN FIGURE SKATER
NARUMI TAKAHASHI
Narumi is a bona fide athlete
and doubles skater,
who represented Japan
in the 2014 Winter Olympics.
With friends from the same talent agency
in tow, she's stepping up to battle.
-Good luck. Make us proud.
-Sure. See you.
-Takahashi is such a bubbly personality.
-You're right, she's lively.
An Olympian is here to grace
the Takeshi's Castle stage. Yay!
-That's Sunshine Ikezaki's bit.
-You're right.
Charge!
-She looks so tiny.
-She's very calm.
-She must have strong legs. Go, go!
-I agree.
-You got it, stay calm. She's got this.
-That's how you do it.
-She waits for the moment.
-She's calm.
-Nice.
-She's got it. Go on, climb up!
-That was close.
-That block is impossible.
-That's really difficult.
-You can't beat it.
-An Olympian can't even do it.
-There's no way.
She was amazingly calm though.
Leave it to an Olympian to jump
gracefully onto the blocks.
But, even she struggled to get her leg
over this block and failed.
Takahashi could not beat the game.
Well, I didn't make it...
SOCHI OLYMPIC PAIR SKATER
NARUMI TAKAHASHI (30)
But, how did I do?
-Her eyes look wild.
-Well, what can I say...
The next group brought their whole gang.
-Nice to meet you.
-They're from Ega-Channel.
STAFF FROM A YOUTUBE FAVORITE
EGA-CHANNEL
The Brief Troupe is joining us from
the ultra-popular YouTube channel,
Ega-Channel.
I'll try my best. Here I go.
EGA-CHANNEL STAFF
BRIEF TROUPE M
You can do it!
The Brief Troupe are accustomed to putting
their bodies to the test
on their YouTube channel.
Hook your leg. Close but no cigar.
They displayed
surprisingly high physical abilities,
but were unable to get over the hurdle
of the blue plus sign.
You can't get a leg over it.
The following group is also a team act.
-What's that?
-This is a postal mark.
These five colleagues are best buds
-from the postal service in Futtsu, Chiba.
-They're close.
We're the most concerned about this guy.
FUTTSU POST OFFICE TEAM
TAKAO UCHIYAMA (42)
Look at this chubby, indulgent body.
Turn to the right and show them.
-He's sucking in his stomach.
-Stop trying to look good.
-Here I go.
-Good luck!
Get it, Ucchi. Come on, Takao Uchiyama!
-Here's comes Uchiyama.
-He's a big guy.
-No, Uchiyama...
-He's got bad knees.
-Too soon.
-I think he's got bad knees.
If you lose balance there,
you're done for.
-That's the wrong timing.
-They're having so much fun.
Dummy. What are you good for?
-He swallowed some water.
-He's in a rut.
He drank from the spring
of Mt. Midoriyama.
FUTTSU POST OFFICE TEAM
SHUNSUKE KANEKO (40)
-Good luck, Kaneko.
-Stay calm.
-Go, go, go.
-Run.
-Great!
-But he won't make it from there.
Oh no, oh no...
This is a difficult game.
-No one can get over the plus sign.
-It's an impossible task.
What's the best tactic?
They're correct,
the toughest challenge of Block Block
is trying to get over this blue plus sign.
Warriors fail one after the other,
unable to figure out how to conquer
this blue plus sign.
FUTTSU POST OFFICE TEAM
KAZUYUKI SHIRAI (32)
ENGLISH TEACHER FROM ENGLAND
JAMES PEPERA-HIBBERT (29)
MARKETING MANAGER FROM U.S.
GRANT SCHOLAR (31)
COMIC &amp; IMPERSONATOR
KOISHIDA JYUNICHI (41)
Koishida barely put up a fight.
I'm Hanna. I'll do my best.
IDOL GROUP KITTYCAT
HANNA YOSHIDA (14)
OWNER OF MATSUDA PLUMBING
DAISUKE MATSUDA (46)
HEAD OF CONSTRUCTION COMPLIANCE
MASAKI KATO (51)
TRADING BUSINESS FROM TAHITI
MATHIEU DOBEL (39)
What did you think?
It was cool, bro.
Your Japanese is so colloquial.
As the warriors continue to struggle,
here comes our next hero.
Jordan used to watch
Takeshi's Castle while in America.
He's hoping to win this game with legs
that were strengthened from surfing.
WORKS IN EXPORTS FROM THE U.S.
JORDAN ORIEN (28)
-What did he say? Kawa Burger?
-I'm not sure.
Don't do it that way.
Whoa, he did it.
-That requires strength.
-Wow.
-He might make it.
-Amazing.
-He made it.
-Wow!
-He might make he passed the plus sign.
-He's got this.
Wow.
-What happened?
-He didn't make it.
-He fell slowly. So slow.
-Impressive though.
He conquered the plus sign.
They end up figuring it out eventually.
Slowly but surely.
He's still hanging on.
-I failed.
-But you were close.
Though he couldn't complete the challenge,
Jordan made it past the blue plus sign
that was giving everyone problems.
It's an accomplishment
to make it that far.
-From the blue shape to the star...
-Some promising faces step up to the task.
Coming to test their astounding
physical abilities at Takeshi's Castle...
-Look at that endurance.
-...are the competitors from Sasuke,
hoping to make their mark
as the toughest army
-at Takeshi's Castle.
-They're so cool.
Here's the first challenger from Sasuke.
In Sasuke, we're able to do prior research
and face the challenge with a plan,
but that's not an option here
and we only have one shot.
So I'm a bit nervous.
CAR DESIGNER
NAOYUKI ARAKI (29)
First up is Naoyuki Araki,
who is a car designer
and has competed in Sasuke seven times.
As a car designer,
I've already pictured the path to victory.
Araki, we're counting on you!
Nice. You got it.
-Okay, nice.
-Keep it going.
-A car designer?
-Great jump.
-He's doing great.
-Good job.
-Has he figured it out?
-He's really fast.
-Look at him go.
-Wow, Araki.
-He keeps rolling.
-You got this.
-Come on, you got this.
-Oh, no, he's lagging.
-Oh, no...
-There he goes.
-That was amazing.
-He really tried.
-He was persistent.
-That's Sasuke.
-Seriously?
-The Sasuke team does good work.
For taking on this challenge
and giving it his all,
Araki will receive
the Fighting Spirit Award
and move onto the next stage.
We have the Fighting Spirit Award,
and it allows you to move onto
-the next stage even if you fail.
-I see.
KITAGAWA ELECTRONICS MANAGER
MASASHI HIOKI (41)
Our next challenger is...
-If I can do it, you can definitely do it.
-Okay.
You can count on Masashi Hioki to show you
how things are done in Sasuke.
He works as an electrician,
and as a father of three,
he is one of the best dads in Sasuke.
-Ready? Let's go!
-Once one person succeeds, it gets easier.
-How cute, he brought his family.
-They're always at his contests.
-So cute.
-That's a big family.
Charge!
-The cheerleaders are loud.
-You got this.
Those are soft like a sponge.
Nice, he might make it.
-He's got the touch. He's so calm.
-Hioki is great.
-He doesn't waste any energy.
-Right.
-Yamada seemed rushed.
-There he goes. He's got it.
He made it past the plus sign hurdle
in a breeze.
All that's left is to get over the star.
-Go! He can do it!
-Oh, no. Will he make it?
He made it! He did it!
He did it, awesome.
Great job, Hioki.
-He's a beast.
-He lives up to his reputation.
-Team Sasuke is impressive.
-They aren't your average Joes.
I did it. I'm ecstatic!
After calmly jumping past
the toughest shape in the lot,
he stayed grounded and raced
to the finish line in one fell swoop.
-Incredible.
-Hioki from Team Sasuke
is officially the first warrior
to beat Block Block.
-I did it.
-Yay!
-Wasn't that cool?
-It's was totally wild.
Congratulations, you did it!
-So cute.
-But then they wiped it off.
Following this success,
Team Sasuke continued to conquer.
Tada, a civil officer in Yamagata,
finished the course in the shortest time.
Wow.
Sato, the president of
the Japan Parkour Association followed.
The parkour guys would do it.
Kawaguchi from Team Sasuke
also completed the course,
-to add up to the team's multiple wins.
-Amazing.
Can they keep up this momentum?
Here's our last competitor.
I've beat Sasuke and now
I've come for Takeshi's Castle.
-Here he comes.
-It's that guy.
The man who conquered Sasuke twice,
it's Yusuke Morimoto aka Sasuke Jr.
He'll close out this event and hopefully
bring Team Sasuke closer to victory.
Beginning now, I, Shinya Sugiyama,
will be reporting on this event.
-He's dangerous.
-These blocks
appeared at the castle
as if came out from a video game.
Here to conquer it
is two-time Sasuke champion,
and an active competitor,
30-year-old, Yusuke Morimoto.
Here I go.
All right, you got this.
His teammates are voicing their support.
The event has begun for Sasuke Jr,
the undefeated champion.
From the red circle to the green triangle.
-He's unperturbed.
-Over the peak and onto the next.
And he jumps onto the blue plus sign.
It's no big deal for him.
He remains calm.
And next, he'll go for the yellow star.
-Taking no time to rest.
-Look at that speed.
Finishing like an action hero.
Conquering it in no time.
He completed Block Block in 22.08 seconds.
He barely broke a sweat.
Will Yusuke Morimoto be able
to conquer all of Takeshi's Castle?
Wow.
Including the award winner,
six warriors make it past this stage,
marking an overwhelming victory
for Team Sasuke.
Let's ride this momentum
and take down Naomi Castle.
So five players completed the task
and one received an award.
Team Sasuke are tough opponents,
aren't they, Princess?
You're right.
Hioki created a winning streak
by completing it first.
Once one person makes it, they all start
to figure out how to beat the game.
Everyone seems to be having so much fun.
-I liked that, too.
-They all seem to be.
They just seem elated to be there.
The Postal Service Team was so excited,
I barely understood what they said.
That guy was great.
I wish I knew how he got so confident.
-His energy was--
-He was on high octane.
The next game is called
The Daruma Falls Down.
MAKE IT THROUGH A MAZE WHILE
WEARING A DARUMA SUIT
A little birdie told me
that this game might be problematic.
-Problematic? In what way?
-How do you mean?
We have a warrior
that's a bit of a handful?
-How bad?
-Sounds scary. What do you mean?
We'll now catch up with the army
that went down the other fork in the road.
A fan favorite at Takeshi's Castle,
The Daruma Falls Down.
YOSHICHI SHIMADA
Back in the day, Shimada would play
the playground bully in this event.
But who will be our antagonist this time?
And what do they mean by "problematic"?
The Daruma fell down.
THE DARUMA FALLS DOWN
DIFFICULTY RATING: 90%
COMIC DUO SANSHIRO
HIRONOBU KOMIYA &amp; SHUJI AIDA
Let's now hear from some of our warriors.
-How does the costume feel?
-It's heavier than I thought.
-It's heavy.
-How are you with the heat?
-It's hot in here.
-Are you ready to get going?
-So you're telling us to hurry up.
-Seems like it.
-How do you think you'll do?
-I think I'll do well.
-Who did you bring with you today?
-My old cheerleading buddies.
-Hey, everyone. Are you ready?
-They seem tenacious.
FILMED IN AUGUST
It seems like you want me to move on.
-Those outfits seem uncomfortable.
-Let's see
what awaits in the battle ahead.
-Stay tuned.
-We're Sanshiro, the reporters.
Why did he wait to say that?
Let's see who in Takeshi's army
will be leading the defensive team.
Who will it be?
EX FREESTYLE WRESTLER
KYOKO HAMAGUCHI
It's Kyoko Hamaguchi.
-Kyoko!
-Are you ready?
Is she playing a deranged character
or is that how she actually is?
Fighting spirit, fighting spirit!
Fighting spirit!
-What is she doing?
-Let's go!
-Is this her usual shtick?
-I believe so.
THE FIRST ROUND
The first teams to take on the daruma are,
ex-cheerleaders from
Ritsumeikan University,
and the Mom Friends Group, Kamezu,
for a total of 10 warriors.
-Let's begin.
-Okay.
Try to get to the other side
without tripping.
Players can move when the target
has their back turned.
The daruma...
-fell down.
-Everyone looks so cute.
Oh, no...
FAILED
-Number one, you're out.
-It's the girl they interviewed.
The army lost one warrior,
but continues their steady pace.
They're getting pretty close.
There are still so many daruma left.
-Let's keep going. The daruma...
-What is happening?
-Has fall...
-Look, there are obstacles, too.
-You're right.
-Oh, I see them now.
-Fallen down.
-Oh, no.
-You can't step there. She moved.
-You're out!
-She's out?
-You fail if the target sees you moving.
-The daruma has...
-This is pretty demanding.
-It must be quite hard.
-I think so.
-This takes endurance.
-Fallen... down!
They're in each other's way.
FAILED
-No, there she goes.
-She can't stop.
So cute.
-You can't help yourself up.
-Look how far she went.
The daruma has fallen down.
FAILED
MOM FRIENDS GROUP
ROCCO
Oh, no.
-The daruma has...
-Are those rubber balls on the ground?
FAILED
-There she goes.
-She didn't see the obstacle.
Fallen down!
MOM FRIENDS GROUP
NICCO
-Nicco is out.
-How many people are left?
-The daruma has...
-The obstacles must be really challenging.
-Number two is pretty close. You got this.
-Fallen down.
-Nice.
-Well done.
-What's this?
-Are we having a stare down?
-What's happening?
-Let's see if I can make you laugh.
Hi! All right.
-I'm tickled.
-That isn't in the rule book.
-The daruma...
-Will our warriors
be able to withstand
Hamaguchi's stare downs?
Fallen down.
-She's so close.
-Can she resist laughing?
-That's unfair.
-Look away.
Somehow, Fujitaka resists laughing.
The daruma has fallen down!
Daruma number two wins!
FORMER RITSUMEIKAN CHEERLEADER
HARUNA FUJITAKA (24)
DAISUKE HIRANO (31)
Three warriors win the game
following the first win.
MOM FRIENDS GROUP
ITSUKO &amp; IKKO
This is absolutely a win.
-There's no denying it.
-Wasn't she moving?
We're on a roll with the first round,
four warriors have won.
Meanwhile, dark storms were brewing
-in Takeshi's Castle.
-What's at the castle?
Hey, Hamaguchi.
Why are you being so easy on the army?
You better crack down on them.
TAKESHI'S CASTLE IS FUMING!
The Castle is displeased and ready
to bring turmoil upon the battlefield.
The second round.
SON-IN-LAW OF A FORMER PRODUCER
KAZUSHI KATAKURA (40)
Katakura's father-in-law
is a former producer of Takeshi's Castle.
TAKESHI'S CASTLE MUSEUM ADMINISTRATOR
SATOSHI MAEJIMA (35)
And Maejima, the administrator
of Takeshi's Castle museum.
We also have
the Nakamise Barbaros Samba Team,
who is the reigning champion for
the most wins at Asakusa Samba Carnival.
How sexy.
Will their samba toned legs
carry them to victory?
The daruma has...
-Look at their cute head ornaments.
-Fallen down.
Number nine and four, you're out.
FAILED
-What? So strict.
-It's so sudden, too.
-Only the head ornament moved.
-What moved?
Following Takeshi's orders,
Hamaguchi makes the rules stricter.
But perhaps her barometer is too harsh.
Any slight movement will now
leave you disqualified.
-Are you serious? They bumped into me.
-This is too strict.
NAKAMISE BARBAROS SAMBA TEAM
TARO TSURUMI (43) &amp; NOBUE NASHIRO (53)
The daruma has... fallen... down.
-Number one, you're out.
-What? That's too harsh.
-This is all too sudden.
-Did they move?
NAKAMISE BARBAROS SAMBA TEAM
SATOMI HIRANO (45)
The warriors start dropping like flies
due to Hamaguchi's unreasonable ruling.
NAKAMISE BARBAROS SAMBA TEAM
NAOKO MINE (36)
She's strict.
This is so frustrating.
When finally,
Hamaguchi starts to run out of control.
What's happening?
-It's a samba rhythm.
-She's trying to get them to dance.
-Samba!
-Oh, no, they're moving.
-Don't move.
-Don't do it.
No. She's coming for you!
Samba! Sanshiro, you hear me? He's out.
FAILED
-Is this really happening?
-This is chaos.
-What? Can a battle be this dumb?
-Where is the logic?
NAKAMISE BARBAROS SAMBA TEAM
TAKE KAMIJO (43)
Using the rhythm of samba
to get people to move,
-Hamaguchi has become reckless.
-She's gone rogue.
THE SECOND ROUND
EVERYONE FAILED
-I'm happy.
-Thanks to Hamaguchi,
not a single warrior
made it through the round.
What were you thinking?
-I couldn't resist dancing.
-You couldn't resist?
Have you no self-control?
Well, Kyoko has good rhythm.
THE ARMY THAT PRIDES ITSELF
ON PHYSICAL STRENGTH
Hamaguchi didn't stop there.
One after another, these shining athletes
were caught in her schemes.
Off you go.
ADVENTURE RACER
JUNKO TOKUMOTO (34)
2022 WORLD KARATE CHAMPION
HOTAKA YOSHIZAWA (23)
SPARTAN RACER
RYUTARO AIHARA (27)
Even Aihara, who cleared the Border Wall
at top speed, was no match for her.
-And at last, the final round.
-They have their work cut out for them.
Coming up, we have the Pro Wrestlers Team
and the Young CEOs Team,
making a total of ten warriors.
They're the "young" CEOs?
The daruma has fallen down.
-In the back. That was obvious.
-Number eight, you're out.
As expected.
RECRUITING COMPANY CEO
RYOHEI SAKURAGI (44)
There you go.
Number five, you're out.
FAILED
This is very strict.
PRO WRESTLER
TOMOKI HATANO (24)
Are you out if you get bumped into?
-He can't stay?
-What?
-He's trying to resist.
-Number six.
IT COMPANY CEO
YASUYUKI HATTORI (46)
He can't be out yet.
FAILED
-No way!
-This isn't good.
Hang on. That's unfair.
-It's too strict.
-The daruma...
Is the army destined
for a merciless fate again?
One man decides to go out on a limb
with an idea.
...has fallen.
Something is fishy.
If you're plotting something,
I won't let anything slide
in this next round.
CONSULTING COMPANY CEO
RYOTA TSUJIMURA (41)
-I saw you wink at me.
-Did he?
-I see.
-You know what my Achilles' heel is.
-What's that?
-That's your weakness?
You're saying you can't resist a wink?
-Of course, I can't.
-Of course? Look at her.
Oh, dear.
-Look, she's becoming bashful.
-Oh, God.
Please do that again.
Look at her fidget.
-Focus, Hamaguchi.
-So cute.
She is a woman after all.
Her expression is so cute.
The daruma has... fallen down.
Number seven...
-Wait a second.
-He blew a kiss.
I'll let it slide.
-She's suddenly so girly.
-Only this time, okay?
-What's happening?
-The samba team will be mad.
-His flirtation trick worked like a charm.
-Daruma...
Now is the time to attack.
...has fallen down.
Here we go.
The daruma has... fallen down.
-He moved.
-He definitely did.
-Go! You got this.
-What's the verdict?
Congratulations.
You made it.
-Congrats?
-He moved though.
What's happening?
Tsujimura has clearly moving
when Hamaguchi turned around...
He would've been disqualified
in previous rounds.
But he receives special treatment
and wins.
I'm frustrated but that was a great round.
-What was that?
-Congratulations!
-Okay, boss.
-That wink saved you.
No need to charm the cameras now.
Hamaguchi did seem lonely
as you made it closer to the finish line.
-I felt lonely too.
-Shut up.
SEVEN WARRIORS REMAIN
Including the Fighting Spirit Award
recipients, seven warriors made the cut.
Finally, it's time
to bring down Naomi Castle!
Princess, what did you think?
-Hamaguchi was completely off the rails.
-I agree.
When she was strict, it was unreasonable.
When she wasn't, it was child's play.
Are we fine with how this game went?
I think this is the flavor
of Takeshi's Castle.
Okay, I see.
-Now, Princess.
-Yes.
-You've eliminated many warriors so far.
-You're right.
We feel bad for the army.
And we'd like to make up
for Hamaguchi's behavior.
We feel bad, so we're going
to host consolation games.
-I see.
-Would that be all right with you?
Of course. The more enemies, the merrier.
-I agree,
-At this stage,
we should help them out a little.
Let's take a look
at the consolation games.
Warriors who failed in battle
are randomly divided into three groups.
If they can complete a consolation game,
they get to return to the main battle.
-Yamamoto...
-Yes, Shingo Yamamoto, from Block Block.
You'll be competing in
You can't save the ball from 4 p.m.
-Un-ball-livable?
-Yes.
THE CONSOLATION GAMES
Un-ball-livable?
-Hope you're watching, Egashira.
-It's the Brief Troupe. Go.
EGA-CHANNEL STAFF
THE BRIEF TROUPE L
-You got this. Hurry, hurry.
-You won't make it at that speed.
He's running behind.
The ball is right there. He might make it.
-That was pointless.
-He's dived on his own will.
He was too slow on the steps.
SLIP-AND-SLIDE QUIZ
Then there's this game.
SAMURAI ROCK ORCHESTRA
YUME MASUDA (27)
I'll dodge the pond
and join my team in battle.
What kind of kiss is a "French kiss"?
-You got this.
-A, a light kiss.
That was the question?
-B, a passionate kiss.
-She's walking. I thought she might slide.
-That seems dangerous.
-Isn't it easier to slide down?
-She's agile.
-So flexible.
-Go.
-Oh no.
CORRECT ANSWER
B: A PASSIONATE KISS
-B is correct.
-Really?
-I thought it meant a light kiss.
-That was a tricky quiz.
EX NADESHIKO LEAGUE PLAYER
RAIMU SENGOKU (25)
Sengoku, who is an ex pro football player,
had to face a sumo wrestler.
-I don't like this.
-You got this.
Ready, start!
Takeshi's army wins.
She flew into the pond making
a dynamic arc. And for her bravery,
she earns the Fighting Spirit Award.
Right, this way.
Go right. To the right.
Nice teamwork.
Go right.
She's got this.
-Too bad.
-The ball has to stay in. It bounced.
-Wasn't that really close though?
-What a great shot.
I'll win this Slip-and-Slide Quiz.
SPARTAN RACER
MEGUMI TAKAGI (41)
Which object's name
originates from English?
A, Loofah. B, Okra.
Is it loofah? That's dangerous.
-How silly, she hit the middle pole.
-And her answer is wrong.
CORRECT ANSWER
B: OKRA
Don't they kind of look like trash
coming through a garbage chute?
That spout at the very end? Yeah.
I'll make it back to battle,
no matter what.
POSTAL WORKER THAT DRANK THE POND WATER
TAKAO UCHIYAMA (42)
-It's coming down the center.
-The center!
Now to the left. The left!
You dummy. What a dummy.
MOM FRIENDS GROUP
KAMEZU
TAKESHI'S ARMY
COMIC DUO TOM BROWN - MICHIO
CRAM SCHOOL INSTRUCTOR
KEITARO YAMAMOTO (30)
TAKESHI'S ARMY, COMIC DUO BAKAYOANATAWA
HIKARI "PHARAOH" HIRAI
FORMER IDOLING MEMBER
HITOMI SAKAI (33)
STUDENT &amp; FITNESS ENTHUSIAST
TAKARA MATSUDA (19)
TAKESHI'S ARMY - ACTRESS
AIKA YOKOTA
YOUNGEST SASUKE TEAM MEMBER
YUTA NAKAJIMA (14)
MOM FRIENDS GROUP
ITSUKO
She saved herself. She's playing defense.
IDOL CAFE ATTENDANT
YOYO
RETURN TO THE FRONT
-I pulled C.
-He's from the postal team.
TAKESHI'S ARMY - PRO WRESTLER
TOMOAKI HONMA
Never fear. You got this.
Ready, go!
-Honma is pretty strong.
-Oh, no.
-Oh, no, he slipped. Honma!
-This is unexpected.
-Resist the fall.
-Honma. No way!
The army wins!
-Why did we hire you for?
-He slipped.
RETURN TO THE FRONT
-Honma!
-He was so cute.
A pro wrestler shouldn't lose
in a straightforward battle like that.
-He totally slipped.
-He's not very loud,
so I had no clue what he was saying
as he fell into the pond.
WALK THE TIGHTROPE TO REACH THE OTHER SIDE
The next game is another fan favorite.
It's called the Strait of Gibraltar.
-This game is very famous.
-Is it?
OTTER FAIRY
CHIITAN (ETERNALLY 0 YEARS OLD)
Chiitan is in beast mode.
Chiitan!
Everyone is cheering for Chiitan.
Here we go.
-Well done, nice! Stay calm.
-You got this.
-Take this!
-Hang in there, Chiitan.
The water is aimed right at their face.
Slowly but surely, they're-- No!
Slowly but surely, she's-- No!
Chiitan!
-Chiitan, are you okay?
-Chiitan, thank you!
NEXT EPISODE,
THE FINAL BATTLE AT NAOMI CASTLE
Next episode,
the Strait of Gibraltar is back.
Can the army keep up their energy
and reach the final battle?
I feel bad for them.
Also...
Charge! I cheered on the army
with all my might,
but we lost so many warriors.
I've failed them.
Hi, Mr. Tani.
Come here.
Oh, it's you.
Spirit, spirit, spirit! Right?
You remembered me?
-You must stop.
-I've got you.
-What?
-I prefer this daddy.
CAPTAIN TANI HAS ALSO BEEN KIDNAPPED
CAN THE ARMY PREVAIL?
Wait! What's going on?
THE SECOND CASTLE, NAOMI CASTLE
BEHIND THE SCENES
THREE DAYS OF SHOOTING
WITH ABOUT 100 PEOPLE
I shaved my head
to look like Strong Kongo.
Here we go!
I'll solve this puzzle!
THE WARRIORS BECAME FAST FRIENDS
WITH FOLKS THEY'D JUST MET
STRENGTHENING THEIR BONDS
WHILE HELPING EACH OTHER OUT
I can't see it anymore.
This brings back memories.
Everything is built so well.
-Is it different from before?
-It's mostly the same.
THE CAPTAIN CONSULTED WITH THE ARMY
You have to jump on
before it straightens out again.
The last one was moving like this.
-So I think that's the trick.
-Can you even do that?
AND IN BETWEEN BATTLES,
THERE WAS REST AND RELAXATION
You're a Spartan racer?
It's the longest and toughest
obstacle course in the world.
What's an Adventure Race?
It's the toughest race in the world.
But the Spartan guys
said theirs was the toughest.
Adventure Racing is equally tough.
THE WARRIORS PERFORMED FOR EACH OTHER
AND SHARED THEIR COURAGE AND SPIRIT
AND THE BATTLES CONTINUE
Everyone gave it their all.
I saw the passion in your eyes
and I was touched.
Thank you.
Takeshi's Castle is the best!
Thank you!