THIS PROGRAM WAS PRODUCED
UNDER THE SUPERVISION OF MEDICAL EXPERTS,
TAKING INTO CONSIDERATION THE HEALTH
AND SAFETY OF THE STAFF AND CONTESTANTS.
Gather round,
elite warriors!
THE YEAR 1986
Charge!
In 1986, a colossal battle broke loose.
THE IMPENETRABLE CASTLE
A castle so impenetrable,
only eight out of 127 battles
have ever seen its halls.
8 WINS, 118 LOSSES, 1 DRAW
WIN RATE 0.06%
That dreadful castle has reemerged
in the Land of the Rising Sun.
JAPAN
RESURRECTION
THE YEAR 2023
Charge!
Takeshi's Castle is back!
Fortified with extravagance and fortitude,
packed with new games,
it's the palace of your dreams!
WHO WILL EMERGE
AS THE BOLDEST WARRIOR?
NO TIME FOR FEAR
I'll bring justice upon you numbskulls!
Have a look and see for yourself.
TAKE NO PRISONERS
Victory is ours!
I'm gutted!
Tear it down
to take home...
ONE MILLION YEN
I will destroy you!
I made it!
Here we go!
Fall, fall till you can fall no further.
Struggle as you may,
he has you in the palm of his hand.
DANCE...
The man of the hour
that you've all waited for...
IN THE PALM OF HIS HAND
ARMY VS TAKESHI
Takeshi's Castle!
TAKESHI'S CASTLE
An attack force
of 100 brave warriors has been sent
to bring down the first fortress,
Ueda Castle,
and its protector, Shinya Ueda.
In the 34 years since its last battle,
Takeshi's Castle
has strengthened its defenses
and started vanquishing warriors
one after the other.
Sixty warriors have survived
and passed the third fortress.
SURVIVORS
60 WARRIORS
The road ahead forks in two directions,
with more battles waiting ahead.
FIRST CASTLE
UEDA CASTLE
That's funny.
After this, I'd like to move on
to a new game
that was developed for this event.
-New game?
-Yes, we created new and dynamic games.
FIRST CASTLE LORD
SHINYA UEDA
Can't wait to show you.
OSAMU SHITARA - YUKI HIMURA
-Good.
-But our staff is cruel.
It's clear they don't want
anyone to succeed.
This show has always been that way.
Listen up, the next game is Strong Arms!
ARMY CAPTAIN
SUBARU KIMURA
I doubt you've ever seen or heard of it.
Don't be intimidated!
I believe in your abilities to succeed.
Let's begin! Charge!
There are more of them than before.
TAKESHI'S ARMY
NISHIKIGOI - HASEGAWA AND WATANABE
It's the Nishikigoi duo.
Listen, Army,
not a single one of you will pass!
You shall not pass.
With these handles, I'm in control.
Think again if you think
you'll make it through here.
Hey!
ROTATE CLOCKWISE
You broke it, dummy!
Hey, what are we going to do about this?
Breaking a set prop
is the biggest fear of young comedians.
STRONG ARMS
DIFFICULTY RATING: 92%
-I'll do my best!
-She's a narrator.
NARRATOR
SHIZUKA KAWANA
-You got this!
-Go for it!
Stay calm!
RULES
DODGE THE ARMS AND GET TO THE OTHER SIDE
-You got this!
-She's making it!
Jump over it. Jump!
-Go for it.
-That was dangerous. She's tough.
Can she keep moving forward like that?
-It pushed her back.
-It totally got her.
-That's not good.
-Jump over it!
She's got great balance!
-Go!
-Well done!
She needs to hurry.
The next arm is coming.
-Good.
-Get back up.
She keeps getting pushed back.
-Keep moving after you jump!
-Take your time.
There she goes. She went for it.
Once you lose your balance, you'll fall.
So true. It's difficult.
Takeshi, I'll try my best!
HOUSEWIFE
MASAKO TOMITA
She's back after 35 years.
-She's a careful woman.
-Good. Easy!
Don't grab the bar.
This one's very difficult.
-Easy!
-Don't grab the bar.
-Here he comes!
-It's Chiitan.
OTTER FAIRY
CHIITAN (ETERNALLY 0 YRS OLD)
What is that thing?
What is that?
-That's Chiitan.
-Chiitan? Okay.
-Chiitan!
-That's gonna be tough.
-Everyone's excited.
-They're pumped.
Keep your guard up!
-Chiitan!
-Follow the arms.
-He's doing great.
-So far, so good.
No, be careful.
His head is too big.
-You got this!
-Go, Chiitan!
-Look up.
-His head is a nuisance.
Man!
That was silly.
BOULDERING WALL FAIRY
BORUNEESAN (FOREVER 33)
-Here comes another one.
-It's Boruneesan.
It's another yuru-chara.
What's that konjac ghost looking thing?
Neither of them can see their footing.
-Great move.
-No...
Too bad.
It looks like no one can do it.
NARRATOR: JUN HATTORI
Suddenly, the Army gained
a powerful helper!
CELEBRITY IMPERSONATOR
JACKIE-CHAN
Jackie-chan, known for his impersonation
of Jackie Chan takes on the challenge.
-He's a very strong athlete.
-Full steam ahead!
-Good job!
-It's like watching a Jackie Chan movie.
Kind of, yes.
-Nice! What?
-What's he doing?
He was supposed to be a ringer,
but fell into the water
after the second arm.
No way!
Why did they even bother calling him?
-You'd think he would do well.
-Right.
DAI HIRAYAMA (31)
The warrior's brave attack continued.
IMARI HIRAOKA (12)
-That was dangerous.
-Watch out!
That was dangerous.
Meanwhile, Macaroni
a member of Sengoku Resistance
came close to winning.
Hey, fall in! Fall into the water!
SENGOKU RESISTANCE
MACARONI
Just fall in!
You're doing great! Good job!
-He's doing it!
-Careful!
No! That's not good!
He was one arm away from the goal.
That was so close.
I thought he was gonna make it!
That was a close call. He got way too far.
Things are getting hairy.
From now on, we'll use a new weapon.
BUBBLE MACHINE
We'll make it even harder for them
to make it across using this machine.
Things just got a lot trickier!
Damn you, Nishikigoi!
Our next challenger
is here looking for love.
-It's me. Here I go!
-It's Mayaya.
Go get 'em!
That's scary!
She's just looking for love.
LOOKING FOR MARRIAGE
MAYAYA (35)
Keep going, don't hold back!
Go!
-What happened?
-How did she...
Bubbles or not,
she lasted a mere six seconds.
Done way too soon.
Imoto, who came with her son,
has something to confess.
MOTHER &amp; SON DUO
KAORI (45) &amp; SAKURA IMOTO (13)
Captain Kimura, I love you!
BIG FAN OF CAPTAIN KIMURA - HOUSEWIFE
KAORI IMOTO (45)
-I heart you!
-Right back at you.
-Good job!
-It's an all-out attack!
Keep going!
-Defeat her!
-Jump over it!
-Go!
-Hang in there!
You're doing great!
No!
She fell.
Any parting words for the captain?
I love you, Captain!
Thank you! Thanks for trying your best!
Unafraid of the bubble machine's power,
the army charges forward!
HERE WITH MOTHER - 8TH GRADE
SAKURA IMOTO (13)
TV PERSONALITY
MIYU KANDA (25)
"TAKAGI BAKUFU" LEADER
ASUKA TAKAGI (29)
Welcome to Main Street in Hell.
Go! Get over the hump!
"TAKAGI BAKUFU" MEMBER
KENYA FURUKAWA (30)
DANCE LOVING DUO
AKINKO (32)
It was tough, wasn't it?
-I have no idea what just happened.
-Are you okay?
Next up, with an average age of 50,
is the Hibiya Horizontal Bar Club.
They're middle aged elites,
who work for major corporations.
HIBIYA HORIZONTAL BAR CLUB
I've already visualized
how we're gonna beat this game.
-We're absolutely ready.
-Yes.
I want to see them do well.
-I got this!
-Go for it, you 55-year-old.
HIBIYA HORIZONTAL BAR CLUB LEADER
TOSHITAKA HOSOI (55)
Go Hosoi, go!
The first one up is Hosoi,
who works for a foreign finance company.
-All right!
-Good job!
-Don't rush...
-No!
That ended too soon!
Why did he try to move so soon?
WHY DID HE TRY TO MOVE SO SOON?
Next up, Yoshio Yoda, an elite
from The University of Tokyo
and the oldest member of the team.
Move faster! Yes, he made it through.
His face is covered in bubbles.
-Nice, keep going!
-Come on!
-He's at the last arm!
-Look at him go.
What? Why did he fall?
-He was covered in bubbles.
-So close!
That's not good.
Yoda lost his vision
because of the bubbles.
He lost his balance
and fell in the final stretch.
The bubbles are working.
It's okay, we're doing better each round.
HIBIYA HORIZONTAL BAR CLUB
IPPEI SUYAMA (50)
Go, Team Hibiya!
Our third warrior, Suyama,
is a former elite diplomat.
Get past these bubbles if you can.
He's the same age as me.
-Try it.
-Hang in there. Nice.
-Wow! He's going for it!
-He passed the second arm.
-Keep going!
-He's one of the youngest in the club.
Get up! Get up and jump!
-Go!
-Jump over it!
-Come on, jump! Keep going!
-Almost there. Go!
He did it! He's doing it!
-He made it!
-Will he...
He did it!
-I did it!
-Nice job, Horizontal Bar Club.
-Well, look at that.
-Bubbles from head to toe.
He made it. Everyone is happy for him.
Take that!
-I did it!
-Great job!
-Aren't they his enemies?
-You're right.
-We're his enemies.
-They finally remembered.
He successfully made it over the third arm
that no one else had been able to clear.
At last, he's the first one
to clear the game.
He's our enemy,
but I'm happy he cleared it.
True, it feels nice.
-You're the first one to clear it.
-Really?
-Yes, you are.
-All right!
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
Even your enemies, the Nishikigoi,
were so happy, they high-fived you.
Follow his lead, everyone!
Make us proud, Marshall. You're our star.
Next up is the club's youngest member
and best athlete. Can he clear it?
-I'm afraid that they're gaining momentum.
-It's a problem.
-Let's stay on guard...
-Here he comes!
HIBIYA HORIZONTAL BAR CLUB
MARSHALL IKEDA (38)
-I'll do my best!
-Here he is.
Let's go!
-He's young.
-He's the youngest member.
Go, Marshall!
-Good pace.
-He started off...
-Wow!
-His movement is dynamic.
-It's like something out of a manga.
-Close call.
Nice, he's going to make it.
-The Horizontal Bar Club has great moves.
-He's gonna make it.
He's using the net to boost himself up.
Amazing.
Is he for real?
The Horizontal Bar Club is impressive.
Another one made it.
-Damn it, man!
-He beat us!
Let's keep up the good fight!
Tasked with following
those consecutive wins is this legend...
Here he comes.
A competitor
in the world-renowned show, Sasuke.
Katsumi Yamada, age 56,
is known as Mr. Sasuke
because he's been a contestant
since the show's first episode.
"MR. SASUKE" KATSUMI YAMADA
He arrived at Takeshi's Castle
carrying his historied reputation.
However, he failed to impress
at the Dragon God's Pond.
-He'll do better in Strong Arms.
-You think?
I'm challenging myself
to complete in all the games,
and show you every bit of what I can do.
It's meaningless
if I don't make it to the end.
He has no right to act so cool.
Yamada is set on winning
the title of Mr. Takeshi's Castle.
-His story can't end here.
-Good luck, Yamada.
MR. SASUKE
KATSUMI YAMADA (56)
He needs to redeem himself.
-Make sure he fails!
-Jump over them, Mister!
He has to win.
-Stay calm!
-He seems calm.
Go!
Jump over it!
Jump, now!
-Go for it!
-You can do it.
Hello!
No way!
That was the dumbest way
to go down. What was that?
That was awful. What was he thinking?
Why do we call him, "Mr. Sasuke"?
-That was awful!
-What happened, Yamada?
-No way!
-Why did he fall so soon?
-Can we see it again?
-It was just awful.
Mr. Sasuke tried to jump,
but couldn't find his footing.
He fell without ever getting
the chance to jump.
-Amazing.
-Man!
What went wrong, Legend?
-The bubbles...
-Yes?
The bubbles?
-...made things slippery.
-Obviously!
Bubbles are like that.
He's the worst!
The legend has failed,
but how about these guys?
The popular YouTube group, AUN.
Two out of their four team members
cleared Beach Boys and Girls.
Their physical abilities
are very promising.
They'll probably win the whole thing.
-They're strong contestants.
-They are.
ACROBAT YOUTUBERS
AUN - ACRE
-I'll show you how it's done!
-All right!
Acre!
First up is their leader,
who's been having a tough time.
Will he be able to redeem himself?
-He's the group's leader, right?
-Correct.
He's not that good.
ACROBAT YOUTUBERS
AUN - KANTA
-It's Kanta.
-I'll be the Team's first clear!
-Let's go, Kanta.
-Go, Kanta!
Next up is Kanta,
who has zero losses so far.
Wow!
-Great!
-Interesting choice.
-Well done, Kanta.
-Nice.
He's showing us some new tricks.
He's making good time.
-One more arm left.
-He'll make it.
-No...
-Wow.
-Well done!
-He made it happen.
Great. I think Kanta
should be their leader.
Don't say that.
-Nice!
-Great job, Kanta!
-He's excellent.
-Great.
-Clear!
-Well done, Kanta.
You made it look so easy,
like it was your daily commute.
That's a very short road.
No, this is not my commute.
In the end, five people beat Strong Arms,
and five received
the Fighting Spirit Award.
10 WARRIORS REMAIN
Five people made it.
Onto the next fortress, fearless Army.
Once again,
Yamada's performance was terrible.
You shouldn't talk down to him like that.
What has he accomplished?
In this one,
he just stood there, then he fell.
Wasn't that terrible?
Well, he's getting up there in age.
-It angers me.
-His body is deteriorating.
Don't compete then.
He's hilarious!
I have hope that he's gonna pull through.
That's why we keep giving him
the Fighting Spirit Award.
Haven't you given him too many chances?
Next up, a game as notorious
as the Dragon God's Pond,
"the Devil's Domain."
AVOID DEMON ATTACKS
AND MAKE IT THROUGH THE MAZE
This game has seen many iterations,
but what new traps will await this time?
Warriors, great job in making it this far.
Do you still have enough energy?
Yes!
Can you keep going?
Good. Now look,
the structure behind you
is the Devil's Domain.
It's time, attack the next fortress!
Yeah!
Great!
We're now at the Devil's Domain.
We, Nasunakanishi, will be reporting.
COMEDY DUO - NASUNAKANISHI
NAKANISHI &amp; NASU
Rumor is that there are
fierce demons living inside.
Scary.
PRO WRESTLERS
TOGI MAKABE &amp; TOMOAKI HONMA
-It's Makabe.
-Both Makabe and Honma are here.
COMEDIAN
YASUDA DAI CIRCUS - KUROCHAN
-Kurochan is here too.
-I'm gonna catch you! Beware!
NISHIKIGOI
MASAKI HASEGAWA &amp; TAKASHI WATANABE
-Hello!
-You're too noisy.
-Take that!
-Serves you right!
THE DEVIL'S DOMAIN
DIFFICULTY RATING 95%
Those are scary effects.
Time to defeat The Devil's Domain. Charge!
ROCKET NEWS 24 WRITER
HIDENORI YAMASHINA (48)
ENTRANCE - DEMONS - GOAL
GET THROUGH THE MAZE
WITHOUT ENCOUNTERING ANY DEMONS
That's bad. Run away!
DEMON VIEW CAMERA
He's doing well, but this corner...
That's awful.
-It's very disorienting in there.
-It really is.
Out you go!
They throw you into the pond too?
Let's see.
-I will conquer!
-It's the Rocket News guy.
There he goes.
Good luck!
ROCKET NEWS 24 - EDITOR-IN-CHIEF
GO HATORI (42)
He's good and very fast.
Wrong way.
-He did it to himself.
-Who was that?
GOPRO VIEW
-There's a random stranger in there.
-What happened back there?
-Well, there was this old guy
-who screamed at me.
-What do you mean?
I thought he was a demon,
then he yelled at me.
IF YOU RUN INTO HIM,
HE'LL YELL AT YOU
-He just started scolding me.
-And how did you feel?
I was dumbfounded.
I wasn't expecting it.
So, all he does is yell?
Parkour ninja might attack
with water balloons from above. Beware!
PARKOUR NINJA'S INTERFERE
BY LAUNCHING WATER BALLOONS
-The ninjas are the new obstacle, right?
-Hey!
A CHEERFUL PLANT ENGINEER
TOMONORI YUZAKI (46)
I will win no matter what!
Go get 'em.
-So, they just throw down water balloons?
-Right.
They got him.
Get out!
What a nice toss.
SWIMMING PRODUCER
MINA KOBAYASHI (30)
Comaneci, let's go!
She put her soul into that.
-Nice moves!
-Well done.
-She just has to outrun them... No!
-Watch out!
That was a good try.
-She fell from the momentum.
-Yes.
-It's a tough game.
-I'll try my best!
It really is.
Nurse Nakano received
the Fighting Spirit Award
for the bravery she showed
during Beach Boys and Girls.
Will she score big in the Devil's Domain?
-I remember her, she's the nurse.
-That's right.
NURSE
AOI NAKANO (29)
-No!
-That was terrible.
They got her really quickly.
Here, for your good work out there.
So long!
-He tossed her like garbage.
-He did.
-I'm hella pissed.
-Say that again.
I'm hella pissed.
-She's hella pissed!
-She said it so quietly.
Don't let the demon's attacks
ruin your game, Army!
Next up...
You're gonna run into one
-if there's that many.
-Definitely.
Cherry Yoshitake will get it done!
COMEDIAN
CHERRY YOSHITAKE (41)
Watch out... No!
Get out of here!
-That was too quick.
-He jumped in on his own.
He had a lot of energy, but he was
in and out in under four seconds.
Cherry's in a tough spot.
-He's absolutely useless.
-Come on!
This feels familiar...
-I'm ashamed of myself.
-No, don't say that.
As he should.
Next up, the Female College Student Team.
-We'll try our best!
-The Female College Student Team.
They're all friends
since elementary school, right?
I promise I'll get to the other end!
FEMALE COLLEGE STUDENT TEAM
MIRI KATO (21)
-Go get 'em, Katomi!
-Go, Katomi!
-They're hell-bent on finding you.
-I'd hate to be caught.
-No! Get away!
-Run away!
-She did it!
-Yes, that's the way!
She's getting away!
-Keep going!
-Go! No, they got her.
No, they got her!
She was so close!
Just one door away!
That's the worst.
-Yeah!
-Get out!
She's was right there.
Look at that.
The demons were onto her
but she ran away swiftly.
When they finally caught up to her,
the finish line
was just a stone's throw away.
What a shame!
How did I do? Did I get far?
-Yes, you were just one door away.
-Really? Just one door?
-Yes, you were so close.
-How frustrating!
When the target is a woman,
Kurochan can magically see through walls.
-I heard it's his special skill.
-That's not fair! He's the worst!
-I'll beat those demons!
-All right, here we go.
FEMALE COLLEGE STUDENT TEAM
EVE HANIUDA (22)
-That's not good.
-They're fast. Too fast.
The demons are too fast.
Your lips have turned blue.
You're a blue demon now,
let's get married!
-No, thank you.
-Don't you like me?
-Can I just...
-Wait, hold on!
-She's trying to escape.
-No, Kurochan.
Why did he fall too?
Hey, why did you drag me with you?
-What happened?
-Tell us, what's going on?
He asked me to marry him,
so I brought him down with me.
-You jumped into the water with him?
-Yes.
-What? Can you explain what happened?
-Tell us.
The staff's gonna get mad at me again!
The next team hails
from the Shonan region.
Two families brought together
by the mothers' friendship.
Kids, are you watching?
Daddy will try his best!
-He's a young father.
-Very young.
-Go get it!
-You got this!
SHONAN FAMILY BESTIES
TAKAAKI SUGIYAMA (41)
-Nice.
-They haven't found him yet.
-Look at that.
-He might actually make it.
-No!
-He was so close.
Too bad for you!
The next door was the exit.
-That's right.
-I made a big mistake.
-There was no way for me to slow down.
-I see.
SHONAN FAMILY BESTIES
MISATO SUZUKI (34)
I will avenge my family!
-You can do it, Misato!
-Why is she giggling?
She's from the Shonan Family team.
-She's good.
-That's an old trick to not get caught.
She's doing great.
No! They're gonna get you!
-Nice. Run away!
-She's starting to panic!
-She's in trouble.
-No, she ran into the scolding man!
That guy is the creepiest of them all.
-No, don't put that on me!
-They got her!
-That old guy is the scariest.
-Agreed.
He's a random guy out of nowhere.
Your pretty face is ruined.
-Oh, no, Shonan Family.
-Whoa, they threw her out.
You're done for.
The strongest athletes
almost make it to the finish line.
SLACKLINING WORLD CHAMPION
KOI OKAZAWA (13)
Even the pro slackline rider, Matsumoto,
was one door shy.
-He was so close.
-Nearly there!
-No one has made it.
-It's a tough one.
Perhaps it's time to call on the gods.
A young Shinto priest, Ikeno, who manages
three shrines will be put to the test.
A priest or a demon, who will win?
Let's go.
SHINTO PRIEST
YOSHIHIRO IKENO (27)
Here he comes.
Nice. He's doing great.
-He's fast paced. Will he make it?
-Nice. No, go around.
Hey, you. Wait.
-He made it.
-Wonderful. Well done.
-Way to go, priest.
-He knew where to go.
-Maybe god's will is real.
-Amazing job.
Well done. He was so calm.
What amazing luck.
The door he opened to escape a demon
was exactly the finish line.
And he just barely escaped another demon
coming in from the side.
Thus becoming the only person
to beat The Devil's Domain.
ONE WARRIOR REMAINS
-How cool. The lone winner.
-He is?
-Congratulations on your win.
-Thank you. I did it.
-You were very fast.
-Did you have amulets up your sleeve?
However, the real challenge
is making it to the final stage.
At this rate, the army will be wiped out.
It's been a tough fight.
Get him!
What the hell?
-We've got you now.
-Hold him down.
The demons got a hold of Captain Kimura...
and froze him in carbonite.
Why bother with these random storylines?
-I was--
-Lord Ueda, with this attack, the army
-won't be able to hold its ground.
-That's right.
We have their captain,
so the battle is ours now.
Serves you right.
Wait, I can't change characters quickly.
Don't drag me into this storyline.
An army without their captain
has no sense of direction.
-Was Kimura double-booked or something?
-No.
-That's not the reason.
-Not at all.
Let's see what AI count thinks about this.
-It's great that you've captured Kimura.
-Agreed.
-We've got him.
-Now the castle is safe.
Yes. But can we still host
the consolation games?
We want to see more.
You hear that? What do you think,
Ms. Momoi Kaori?
What do I think?
I can't be bothered with such a trivial--
What a bad impersonation. Who was that?
The ones he's not good at really stink.
CONSOLATION GAMES
REGISTER HERE
There are two fortresses remaining.
WIN ONE OF THREE GAMES
TO RETURN TO BATTLE
Consolation games are the last chance
for fallen warriors to return to battle.
Good luck.
The first consolation game is called
You Can't Save The Ball.
-I'll make miracles happen.
-Here's Rocket News.
ROCKET NEWS, EDITOR
MASANUKI SUNAKOMA (41)
This is good
since they're not good quizzers.
You're right. Hurry, hurry up.
Too slow. Like I said, too slow.
Those stairs must be taller than we think.
-They're pretty steep, too.
-You're right.
-Nice, it's right in the center.
-Go!
SENGOKU RESISTANCE
MARCO
Though he's the club leader,
Hosoi hasn't been able to contribute
to the team's success.
-Come on, leader.
-You got this.
HIBIYA HORIZONTAL BAR CLUB
TOSHITAKA HOSOI (55)
-He did it.
-Well done.
-The team must be elated.
-Yes! I passed!
RETURN TO THE FRONT
I did it!
-He's so happy. Did you see that?
-He made a comeback.
The next consolation game is called
Slip-and-Slide Quiz.
The quiz...
I'll win this round, no matter what!
Question, what color
is a giant panda's tail?
-Color of a panda's tail? Maybe white?
-A, white.
-B, black.
-Black or white...
-I think white.
-They're all the same?
TV PERSONALITY
MIYU KANDA (25)
-It was white.
-Oh, dear.
CORRECT ANSWER
A: WHITE
-It's not black?
-Nope. It's white.
-Which belongs to the dog family?
-Chiitan!
-A, cheetah. B, jackal.
-They look even dingier than before.
You got this, Chiitan.
-Chiitan is back in the game.
-So Chiitan had registered for it.
CORRECT ANSWER
B: JACKAL
Surprisingly,
Chiitan's trivia skills are strong.
RETURN TO THE FRONT
Chiitan is back in the game.
The last consolation game is called
Tug of War.
Here it comes.
-You got this.
-They're Sengoku...
-What was their name again?
-Sengoku Resistance.
Look, it's the AMA-WRES KYODAI.
Go for it!
Ready, go!
-This might be a good match.
-Those two are strong after all.
Winner, Takeshi's Army.
Ready, go.
In this game, your fate lies
in the opponent you draw.
COMPANY MANAGEMENT
TOMOYA NAKAMURA (45)
A weak opponent guarantees
your return to the frontline.
RETURN TO THE FRONT
TAKAGI BAKUFU LEADER
ASUKA TAKAGI (29)
But there were times the game
unfolded differently.
No... here he comes. It's Yokokawa.
Beware, the strength of a bodybuilder.
I feel bad,
so you ladies can work together.
-He gave them a leg up.
-Two women set up to the plate.
-Start!
-Come on, you got this.
They might do it.
-This is a good match.
-Come on, I'm rooting for the women.
-They couldn't make it.
-Winner, Takeshi's Army.
You liar!
FEMALE COLLEGE STUDENT TEAM
MIRI KATO (21)
The team's last chance to stay in the game
rests on their leader, Kato.
-Who will be her opponent?
-Go get them.
-It's sumo wrestlers.
-That's a tough opponent.
-You got this.
-What--
Come on all of you, together!
The whole team?
Is that okay?
This battle will be two on five.
What will happen?
They're not budging.
-Wait, they might make it.
-Go, go, go!
They did it.
The other guy just stood there.
RETURN TO THE FRONT
-That's great. Well done. They're back.
-Thanks a bunch.
With brilliant teamwork, the crew
makes it back to battle. Congrats.
Nice job.
Our 29 heroes head to the sixth fortress,
hopeful to make it to the final battle.
29 WARRIORS REMAIN
Next up, an old audience favorite,
Mushroom Plop.
HOLD ONTO THE MUSHROOM
AND LAND ONTO THE FLOATING ISLAND
To check how tough it is,
a warrior from Takeshi's Army
tested it out.
TEST PLAYER
YUKI HIMURA, BANANA MAN
-It's high up here.
-I went to test it.
-They had you do it?
-Yes, I tried it out.
This is way too high.
Here I go. Really?
So like this--
Seriously? I can't even grab hold of it.
How does everyone else do it?
Just grab it.
-Are you serious? Hold on.
-There's no way I can do this.
-You're supposed to test it.
-Sorry, I can't get up there.
-An apology is not enough.
-You were supposed to test it out.
What the hell was that?
Honestly, I'm not even sure
why they used this clip.
With my weight and weak grasping power,
it's impossible.
Is it that hard?
We've brought the actual mushroom
to the studio.
Your arms won't make it around,
so use this rope.
-Hold like that.
-Do you want to try?
-Be careful.
-Please do.
Amazing!
-See, I did it.
-You're amazing.
That just wasn't a good day
for you, right?
-You might be right.
-It'll work today.
Maybe use momentum
to get your legs around.
I'm hopeless.
-Terrible.
-I can't do it.
This level is called Mushroom or Splash.
How many warriors
do you think will succeed?
Release the mushroom at the right time.
Exactly.
Well, that's the kind of game it is.
MUSHROOM PLOP
DIFFICULTY RATING: 90%
BIG FAN OF CAPTAIN KIMURA, HOUSEWIFE
KAORU IMOTO (45)
This is impossible.
Right?
I'll try my best.
-At least she's not slipping.
-Wow.
HOLD THE MUSHROOM
AND LAND ON THE FLOATING ISLAND TO WIN
-She's hanging on.
-Amazing.
This looks impossible.
-Good try though.
-She was close.
This is a difficult game.
TAXI DRIVER / MODEL / ACTOR
DAI HIRAYAMA (31)
It's tough even without it rotating.
That's dangerous.
He landed on his face.
DANCE LOVING DUO
MAYAYA (35)
Once I grab you, I won't let go.
-It's Mayaya.
-She's got a tight grip, too.
She might make it.
She fell. There she goes.
It's hard to stay on
once it starts turning.
Mayaya, who is looking for love,
fell much before the target,
arms and legs flailing in all directions.
I'll try my best.
Good luck.
SHED TEARS AT THE POND
IMARI HIRAOKA (12)
Nice. Keep going.
-You got this. Look carefully.
-Go.
So close.
That was really close.
Her timing was perfect,
but her aim was too far to the right.
-True. That looks painful.
-She's flexible though.
I'll try my best.
-Good luck.
-Shizuka!
NARRATOR
SHIZUKA KAWANA
You can do it!
-It's going fast. She made it.
-She did it.
-No way. Will it count?
-Seriously?
Really?
Lord Ueda, we put some slime on it.
So you have no plans
of letting them succeed?
Awful.
The game that's tougher than it looks,
Mushroom or Splash.
It's even hard to stay
on the floating island.
Best of luck, army.
-How do you beat it?
-It's so difficult.
Now, two guys
from popular YouTuber, Aun team.
ACROBAT YOUTUBERS
AUN
I've yet to fail any game.
Surprisingly, Kanta has won
every stage so far.
Can he achieve a complete victory?
On the other hand,
I've failed at everything.
-But I've won every consolation game.
-That's because he's Ryu the Phoenix.
Ryu is like a phoenix rising from
the ashes at every consolation game.
Let's hope he passes this round.
He's their leader, but we might not
see much of him.
TAKESHI'S CASTLE
The sun has set, plunging the stage
into a mysterious atmosphere.
-It's nighttime.
-This makes it harder.
First up is Kanta who hasn't failed yet.
I won't be defeated by a mushroom!
-This guy is strong.
-Will he achieve total domination?
Get it.
As expected, it's too tough.
-He slipped right off.
-It's a tough one.
-It's not easy to land that.
-It looked so slippery.
He let go of the mushroom
a smidge too late.
The dream to win all levels
disappeared in one fell swoop.
-Takeshi's Castle isn't that easy.
-That's no surprise.
Ryu, you got this.
You can count on me!
The lucky guy who crawled back
from two consolation rounds, Ryu.
PHOENIX WITH 2 CONSOLATION GAME WINS
AUN: RYU
-Wow. Amazing.
-Whoa.
How did he do it?
-This is incredible!
-The Phoenix!
-He did it, wow.
-I didn't think anyone would make it.
Yes, Ryu!
-This is great.
-Well done.
-Did you see that?
-He's loving it.
AUN's phoenix has risen again
to become the first person
to win in Mushroom or Splash
and move onto the final stage.
PASSED THE FINAL BATTLE
BEFORE UEDA CASTLE
-That was great to see.
-He did it.
-Congrats.
-Thank you.
This is first official game that I won
and I couldn't be happier.
Who would you like to shoutout to?
Shoutout to Japan...
No, shoutout to people all over the world.
-You had to think about it?
-Why did he switch gears?
-Isn't this a lucky streak?
-It is. Hope to keep it going.
This is the radiologist, Matsumoto,
who was able to beat Strong Arms.
Will he succeed
in Mushroom or Splash, too?
-He cleared it.
-He sure did.
I won't fail!
RADIOLOGIST
TOSHIHIRO MATSUMOTO (34)
He might do it.
Got it.
-How did he do it?
-Wow.
He's right on target.
How did he not slip off?
-I made it!
-Incredible.
-That's amazing.
After landing, he almost slid off,
but managed to hold his ground.
-He almost fell.
-But he held on.
A momentous occasion of two winners
in a row. See you in the final battle.
PASSED THE FINAL BATTLE
BEFORE UEDA CASTLE
Hey, what's the deal?
The army is gaining in on us.
-I won't let them win any more battles.
-It's dire.
Take these additional rules.
We now have an added rule.
SMOKE MACHINE
You can barely see the floating island
through all that smoke.
Don't back down, fearless army.
Keep charging forward.
Why is the count suddenly so impatient?
Only two people passed the game.
He's ruthless.
Next up is Kato, the only warrior left
from the Female College Student Team.
-Good luck.
-I'll try my best.
-The island is hidden, right.
-It's terrible.
FEMALE COLLEGE STUDENT TEAM
MIRI KATO (21)
-Where is it?
-You can't see anything.
You got this.
Between the smoke and the lighting,
it's hard to gauge distance.
-That's too bad.
-How'd it go?
That smoke wasn't fair.
I couldn't see anything.
It obscured your vision.
-The smoke is too much.
-Even after this,
the Smoke Machine
continued to give the army a hard time.
-Why add it before the college girls?
-Yeah, why?
The difficulty rating
has dramatically increased.
One after another, the army
were plunged into defeat.
-It's unfair.
-The lighting is on, too.
Only two warriors have managed to win.
Not much of the army remains.
Look at all that smoke.
So close!
-But how will this man fare?
-Oh, yeah, this guy.
NO LOSSES SO FAR
WILL HE WIN THEM ALL?
Ikeno, the priest,
who has won all games so far.
Can he conquer Takeshi's Castle?
-He's amazing, isn't he?
-Yeah.
Here I go.
NO LOSSES SO FAR
SHINTO PRIEST, YOSHIHIRO IKENO (27)
-He failed.
-But he came close.
What a shame.
-He has lots of potential.
-Yes, he does.
It seems better to land on your back.
He let go just in time to land,
but landed in the water
due to too much momentum.
-Missed by a hair.
-He slipped.
But not all hope is lost.
HIBIYA HORIZONTAL BAR CLUB
Elite uncles with high potential,
the Hibiya Horizontal Bar Club.
Their strength is in their ability
to analyze their failures.
Not only did they enlist
their analytic flair to beat Strong Arms.
These heroes did it twice in a row.
They're our heroes.
This team really delivers.
We're finally utilizing
our full potential.
Your voice is ragged.
These guys are the athletes
and I'm the official cheerleader.
That's why my voice is ragged.
First up is team leader, Hosoi.
HIBIYA HORIZONTAL BAR CLUB LEADER
TOSHITAKA HOSOI (55)
-How do you stop with that momentum?
-You can't.
He managed to hit the target,
but couldn't stick the landing.
Is it better to jump from further ahead?
Next up is Suyama,
who was the first to win Strong Arms.
-You got this.
-You'll make it.
-Oh, no.
-No win this time...
You can do it, Marshall.
-What a shame. But he will.
-Marshall can do it.
Carrying the hopes of the team,
is Marshall Ikeda, the elite
who was born and raised in Canada
and speaks fluent English.
-Final stage, here I come.
-Marshall, Marshall!
The youngest star player. Will he make it?
There he goes.
Awesome!
Landing on your back is the key.
-You're right about that.
-Well done.
-How did he not slip?
-He's great.
-He did it!
-The Horizontal Bar Club is promising.
He jumped too late...
He made it, he did it!
I did it!
-He's the third one to win.
-I did it!
He quickly lifted his legs to keep
his balance just as he was about to fall.
He did do that.
He pulled through
and won his place in the final battle.
PASSED THE FINAL BATTLE
BEFORE UEDA CASTLE
-It's great, the guy before me cleared it.
-It's our guy.
-It's great.
-Right?
Our last warrior of the night is
Katsumi Yamada, aka Mr. Sasuke, 56.
He might put up a good fight after all.
He had high hopes of winning
the Mr. Takeshi's Castle title,
but his track record has suffered
not having a win since the Border Wall.
I keep falling but,
the Fighting Spirit Award has carried me.
So I hope to win
and have everyone congratulate me.
-Good luck!
-You got this!
Let's go!
Mr. Sasuke head to battle.
Yamada!
-Come on, Yamada, it's your last chance.
-He'll do it.
-I'll believe in him, too.
-He's Mr. Sasuke.
-Yamada!
Everyone is so excited.
I'm ready.
-Yamada!
Come on, hit the mark.
-Find the target.
-Wow!
Wow!
He couldn't stick it.
-He hasn't won a single game.
-No, he hasn't.
He hit the target in the middle.
It seemed like the perfect shot.
However...
Sadly, Mr. Sasuke slid overboard.
He's been falling in water all day.
-Not just here. All day.
-Sadly, he fell.
3 WARRIORS REMAIN
With three warriors remaining,
we now move on to the final battle.
We can stop calling Yamada back now.
We finally saw his final round.
I must say,
our staff is horrible
at gauging difficulty levels.
You're telling me they even put slime
on the floating island?
Lord Ueda, please keep your voice down.
It's supposed to be a secret.
When I went to test it,
the senior staff member
was tossing something like this.
I can't say for certain
whether it was slime or not.
There's no doubt about it.
-Anyhow, we have three warriors remaining.
-Amazing.
We'll fight them in the final round.
3-ON-3 FIGHT WITH THE LORDS
ARMY GETS A MILLION YEN IF THEY WIN
The three of us will fight them?
Yes, Lord Ueda,
you'll be in the final battle.
-It's a good number to battle with.
-That's right.
-Correct, our staff is very smart.
-Okay, I see.
Shall we say hello to the AI count
before the final battle?
-I thought there should be more slime.
-There was plenty.
-That's why he's the count.
-It wasn't enough?
You better win.
Three warriors made it to the end.
We'll be okay. Our staff doesn't want
to give a million yen to anyone.
Can we have a word of support, Mrs. Dewi?
I was playing a game
called Laugh or Splash.
I also played Sumo or Splash,
Calligraphy or Splash, splash, splash...
That's what I was doing with my time.
What horrible quality.
At this point, Count Takeshi
is simply having fun roasting people.
Let's do our best in this final battle.
Shall we get going?
All right, let's win.
The army is at a disadvantage
without their Captain Kimura.
Nonetheless, our heroes head to
the final battle ground, Ueda Castle.
The Lord will now make his appearance.
You already broke it.
He's already breaking things.
THE FIRST CASTLE'S LORD
SHINYA UEDA
I'll bring justice upon you fools.
-This lord is a little unhinged.
-See this.
Now it's just a dead weight.
I'll attack them by throwing this.
He's off his rocker.
Lord, Captain Kimura
is already our prisoner.
I've seen many props in my day,
but this has the least production value.
-Don't say that. Look there.
-Don't say it.
Look at the three warriors
just standing there, defenseless.
You fools.
-We have to say something back.
-Yes.
Tell them how you're all feeling.
You've made it this far.
-I'll do my best.
-Sounds good.
-I'll conquer this battle!
-Great.
I'll give it my all.
-There you go.
-Excellent.
-How about that?
-They're riled up.
-What do you think?
-They're no match for us.
-Then let's finish this swiftly.
-Not a problem.
YABUSAME
The final battle is called Yabusame.
HIT THE OPPONENT'S TARGET ON THE CARRIAGE
DRAW IF BOTH PLAYERS HIT
A warrior from each team rides a carriage,
but only the army's will pass by.
Shoot and aim for the target
on the opponents carriage.
The army wins if their ball makes it
into the red basket.
Takeshi's Army wins
if they hit the blue target.
But if both teams hit their target,
it's a draw and no points are granted.
Here comes the launching carriages.
-I like how flashy it is.
-Let's head over to it.
-Nice and flashy.
-Lord Ueda, you're up first.
I like it.
It kind of feels like I'm stepping into
-a Gundam robot or something.
-Yes. Because it has a cockpit.
The first warrior is...
Lucky boy, Ryu, from AUN. The phoenix who
keeps returning from consolation games.
He proved his athletic abilities
after beating the challenging game,
Mushroom or Splash.
I will win. No matter what.
We're honored that our teammate
is in the final battle.
-We are.
-I'm so proud of him.
I hope he brings us to victory.
The army's target is a hole
that's barely wide enough for the ball.
Can he bring down Takeshi's Army
in this unfavorable situation?
RYU VS SHINYA UEDA
Lord Ueda will face the army
in the first round.
What will happen?
YABUSAME
DIFFICULTY RATING: 200%
-Now for the final game, Yabusame.
-All right.
A SINGLE ARMY WIN EQUALS
THE ONE MILLION YEN PRIZE
Lord Ueda, beware.
Those are some tough warriors.
Leave it up to me.
-All I need is one shot.
-Sounds good.
Let's begin the first round.
Begin!
-You hit it!
-You got it!
-You got the target.
-See that.
-Damn it!
-Okay!
THE ARMY HAS FAILED
Is that game over?
Winner, Lord Ueda.
TAKESHI'S ARMY WINS
It happened so fast,
I don't know what happened.
Isn't it too difficult?
The army's ball came close to the target,
but didn't hit the bullseye.
In comparison, Lord Ueda
missed with the first five balls,
but hit the target
with the sixth and seventh.
Ryu, the army's first warrior,
is defeated.
DEFEAT
Was it hard?
Well, the carriage moves faster
than expected.
And the opponent's target is very small.
I hate to be the bearer of bad news,
but our team has been setup to dominate.
It happens so quickly.
Yesh, it happens so quickly.
I'll try to enjoy it.
Next up is Matsumoto, the radiologist.
He hasn't lost any game so far.
He is the best of the best.
A SINGLE ARMY WIN EQUALS
THE ONE MILLION YEN PRIZE
Yuki Himura will defend
Takeshi's Castle next.
I'm starting to feel nervous.
There's more pressure
because we have the advantage.
MATSUMOTO VS HIMURA
Can the army make a comeback?
Yabusame, round two.
-Let's begin.
-Go for it!
Begin!
-You got this.
-Good luck!
Go, shoot!
-Nailed it.
-You finally got it.
THE ARMY HAS FAILED
Hurrah!
TAKESHI'S ARMY WINS
-Good job, Himura.
-Thank you!
I got nervous because it took so long.
Himura aimed
without taking continuous shots.
He had already hit the target
on the third shot without realizing,
and hit it a second time
on the fifth shot, for good measure.
The army's first shot actually
hit the edge of the target.
It's true, the army had put up
a good fight.
Multiple shots reached the opponent's net.
One even made it inside.
It was a mere centimeters away
from the target.
-One of them hit the net?
-That was close.
I just barely made it out.
I didn't get hit by any.
My defense is flawless.
We have no means of defense.
Last up is Marshall Ikeda
from Hibiya Horizontal Bar Club.
-Do you want to switch?
-Your voice is ruined, but cheer for me.
He is the youngest
and the star player of the team,
who's won all battles except
the Dragon God's Pond.
The team's hopes for victory
ride on his shoulders.
We've seen the mistakes
of two other players.
I believe in him. He learns quickly.
What's your plan of attack?
I'll turn my weapon to 90 degrees
and keep shooting relentlessly
at the target.
-I see.
-All that's left is to pray.
A SINGLE ARMY WIN EQUALS
THE ONE MILLION YEN PRIZE
Osamu Shitara will defend
Takeshi's Castle.
The fate of Takeshi's Castle
is in my hands, so I can't lose.
-You can't.
-No.
IKEDA VS SHITARA
Can the army make a miracle comeback?
Yabusame, the final round.
-You're up for the final round, Shitara.
-Here we go!
-I'll finish this in one shot. No sweat.
-One shot?
Really? Can we give you fewer balls then?
No way.
-You better win.
-There's no way I'll lose.
-All right!
-Oh, no, I'm starting to get nervous.
-Let's begin the final round of Yabusame.
-All right!
-Good luck!
-You got this!
-Shoot!
-Keep going!
-Just keep shooting!
Shoot!
You used all the balls.
THE ARMY HAS FAILED
-Well done.
-You hit it a ton.
TAKESHI'S ARMY WINS
You got so many hits.
The army came close
but couldn't hit the opponents target.
Far from using a single attack,
Shitara attacked with consecutive shots.
With a total of eight hits,
the army has perished.
Hurrah!
You shot like you were in The Godfather.
-I had to make sure we won.
-It felt good though.
In conclusion, victory is ours!
TAKESHI'S ARMY WINS
-Wonderful.
-That was great.
What a great place Takeshi's Castle is.
To express my gratitude, I'll replace
my chainsaw from Amazon after this.
I want this game in Hibiya Park.
-They're about to redevelop the park.
-Let's go lobby.
Let's suggest it. We'll start a petition.
-We want this instead of our jungle gym.
-They can have them.
I can't believe
they let the army get that far.
Lord Ueda is spineless.
What? The captain has disappeared?
I have no choice.
I guess it's my turn to take charge.
NEXT EPISODE
MUSCLE HEADS ATTACK
The battle to overthrow
the second fortress begins.
An army with great physical strength,
from Sasuke competitors and athletes.
With so many winners,
they just might take Takeshi's Castle.
We did it!
I want to become Mr. Takeshi's Castle.
THE BATTLE OF KATSUMI YAMADA
BEHIND THE SCENES
HE ENCOURAGED EVERYONE
MORE THAN ANYONE ELSE
Rock, paper, scissors.
HE BOOSTED MORALE WITH UNMATCHED PASSION
Rock, paper, scissors. Yay!
Thank you. Hurrah!
Say cheese.
HE MADE MORE MEMORIES
THAN ANYONE ELSE
AND HELPED MORE PEOPLE
-Thank you.
-Did you make it?
Without Sasuke, I wouldn't be here.
Thank you very much.
BUT HE DIDN'T PERFORM
BETTER THAN EVERYONE ELSE
This is too pitiful.
What is there to prove
that I'm Mr. Sasuke?
Damn it...
THANK YOU, MR. SASUKE