Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Kazutoyo Koyabu
It's Koyabu
-Thank you very much
So let's get right to the point
Have any of you here ever had to fake something for a show since you entered the industry?
Yeah, faked a lot
The best time was with a psychic medium
Doing a show in a place where there are rumors of ghosts
It was said that there was a ghost in a phone booth there
So we went to the phone booth
Then came a sound of jingling bells
They said it was the spirit's voice
But I realized it was the psychic hitting the side of the phone booth with small stones
I've learned since then
Psychic programs are just lies
That's what they do
Recently, regulations in the TV industry have become more and more strict
Fake information in a literal sense has all but disappeared
So, today I bring this hypothesis about such fraud
Artists who are required to participate in misleading TV shows can't help helping the program
Has this been done before?
Yes, a similar theory was done two years ago
This time it is a comprehensive upgrade, single-cut verification
Will the performers risk their lives for the sake of the show and blatantly mislead
In this era of various rules and regulations
Do they dare to cross the red line of moral degradation?
Emotions are strangely high.
-Does it still exist?
This time, I want to reveal the truth in broad daylight
Why are you so angry all of a sudden?
-Yeah
To sum up, next we will verify the taboo of fraud
Also, for businesses that borrow performers' names
No matter how unpleasant the content, will they accept if the pay is high enough?
Artists who are required to participate in misleading TV shows can't help helping the program
First of all, the first difficulty level 1 target is
The embodiment of tenderness
Ganbare Luya's Yoshiko
The stage for this validation is
Yoshiko and Shouinji introduce the stores they frequent
The fradulent program is set up in such a way
Why would you want to hear about the stores frequented by these two people?
So, we took a look at the stores Yoshiko frequented beforehand, but
The trip was accidentally double booked
Suddenly, she's informed that one of the stores is reserved for Shouinji
And is unable to participate in the location recording
So, we want to talk a little bit about it.
-OK
Stores frequented by Shouinji
Originally, there was one that wasn't possible, but we repeatedly negotiated
It took a lot of effort to get permission
A tough situation to say no to
She's told that one of Shouinji's choices was difficult
The suggestion is to present it as a shop that Yoshiko often goes to
Making for an embarrassing request
The shop that Shouinji often goes to
Would it be okay to present it as one of the places you regularly frequent?
Eh, I see, I see
Although a little surprised
The offer is accepted smoothly
It'd turn out like this
So
This place's speciality is tomato noodles
Understood
Have you ever eaten tomato noodles?
Never, I have never eaten tomato noodles
To sum up, Yoshiko knows nothing
What to do?
And she's told this is a confidential matter known only to the producer
It happens
Shouinji doesn't know either?
-No
Ah, I see
With none of the staff supposedly informed
The location shoot begins
This is the guest who frequents this restaurant
Hello, everyone I'm Koyuki
※Koyuki - Japanese actress
Sorry, sorry
A little bit low energy
Tormented by guilt, right?
I'm Koyuki
Welcome, Koyuki
First of all, the opening shot in the vicinity of the restaurant
So the first spot
I'll ask Yoshiko-san to take us to the store she usually goes to
Ah it's stuck on top!
The name of Shouinji still remains on the signboard and is roughly covered with stickers.
A detailed operation
Please
No energy at all
Over there? This way?
No energy, no energy at all
Please
Next, Yoshiko leads the way to the restaurant
At the orders of the above
This is Ikejiri
Oh yes, it is Ikejiri
Searching desperately
Over there? This way or this way?
Desperately looking for tips from others
Realizing she forgot to consider which direction to head in
Yoshiko is unable to hide her wavering appearence
Who are you looking at?
So under the setting of going to a frequently visited place
The last thing that should have happened, happens
What?
Wow, loads of people!
They are going in the opposite direction
So, a way to turn around is needed
Is it on this road?
Right here
Wait a minute. Isn't this a convenience store?
Sorry
Joking, its actually over here
While being stupid, she turns around naturally
Very clever
Very skilled
Quick-witted!
Here, she tries had to remember the instructions show to her briefly
Finally, they arrive
Wow, this place looks great
-Yeah
This is it（DAIDAI）
After entering and sitting down
Soon, the recommended dish, tomato noodles, is served
But she's never had it
This is really delicious
When was the last time you ate it?
Recently...?
When unable to answer, just don't say anything
You have to say something!
Really should
Should answer straight away
To Yoshiko, who simply wants to escape
Next, enter the special recommendation!
She is continuously shown the former signs of Shouinji
Now...
The dishes supposedly recommended by Yoshiko will automatically appear
Eh? This!
Is it this?
-This is it
Is this a must order?
-Absolutely
The special recommended menu imposed on Yoshiko
Poor thing
With a load of chilli
What you see here is  punishment-level Mapo Tofu
Do you finish this every time?
Yes
-Really?
Scared by the special recommended menu that she has never had before
Yoshiko's expression continues to fade
No energy at all
Is this something that anyone can eat?
Can you?
No problem
I see, so you're good at eating spicy food?
Indeed
Wow... sorry, the smell is in my nose its choking me
Such a small voice
This is...
So, she eats the spicy food despite not actually being able to handle it
That's tough
How is it?
This is it, it's delicious!
So loud!
Really is
This is the taste!
Ah, its just...
Is it hot?
It's hot, of course!
She's angry!
Under such stimuli
Yoshiko becomes unable to hide her anger towards the staff
Its natural
Thus, we reveal the plan
Do you know what show this is?
I often visit the…
We're actually Wednesday Downtown
Embarrassed
Bastards!
A normal reaction
What did you think when you were asked to lie?
This is how TV is
The next target for difficulty level 2 is...
Lalande's Nishida
The setting we prepared for him this time is
What'll happen this time
-Yeah
A program like "Sunday Kitchen"
It is scheduled to air on Sunday morning
This time, we want to make use of your high-level cooking skills in comparison to other comedians
Wait a minute, we're doing that!?
I don't do much cooking
Ah... Is that right?
-Yes
This is tough
If you search for comedians skilled at cooking, your name comes up
Really? Let me see
For dessert and stuff
It comes up with Nishida
Huh?
So wrong
This isn't Lalande's Nishida, its Sekenshirazu's Nishida
So, this time, the setup is that the staff made a mistake
And mistook Lalande's Nishida for
Sekenshirazu's Nishida, who likes cooking
Sekenshirazu?
Also comedians
Another duo with a "Nishida"
I'm sorry, I don't really know many comedian duos
Its fine, its fine
In such a way, Nishida is mixed up with someone not even of the same gender
At this point, the proposal is put forward
Could you pretend to be good at cooking?
Just for this show, is that ok?
Definitely not
Oh, really?
It's a cooking program
It doesn't matter because you can just follow the teacher's instructions
-Yeah
Ok, well, I guess its fine
So
Let's spend a good time together by cooking
Feels real
Although not known for cooking, he wears the clothes of a chef
And the program quickly starts
In the pre-cooking talk section, we intentionally let the discussion end hastily
Today, the dish we're making together is Acqua pazza
Acqua pazza...?
A dish he has never heard of before
This time, they're making Acqua pazza, a dish with a very high threshold for novice cooks
An Italian fish stew
Doesn't understand a word of it
So, the materials in front of you can be used to your heart's content
Let's start cooking now!
Amazing...
He copies the process of the person next to him, beginning with washing his hands
Who am I, where am I, what am I doing, an empty brain
The amateur chef Nishida's fradulent battle begins
Unsurprisingly very unenthusiastic
If you lie, you'll lose energy, right?
Here, Nishida observes the taking of the main ingredient of Acqua pazza, snapper
But...
Okay, now what do we do?
Does Acqua pazza have to be made with snapper?
Or just any fish?
In such a way
He has no idea even what type of dish it is
Nishida, frozen in place, is overwhelmed by every move made
Poor thing
At this point
Can you make this dish with any kind of fish?
-Huh?
Can you make it with any kind of fish?
Oh, of course, in season fish is the best
So...
Instead of a big fish
He picks a small fish that looks easy to handle
But still doesn't know what to do
After that, in order not to miss the other's every move, he works at a sideways angle
But then, something unexpected happens
His view is blocked by the cameraman taking a close up of the food
He's unable to copy
Completely blocked
He moves immediately to try and change his view
However, he cannot escape the one-on-one camera coverage
He's doing nothing
Thus, he can only rely on hearing to cook
How can you cook by hearing?
Do you clean up as you go along?
Yes, it's usually done by the time the food is served
So, he also starts to clean up
And then, at the last minute...
He finally breaks through into the enemy's area
He's there, he's there, watching super closely
Done
The final result is revealed
Although not as good as the other person's dish...
It at least looks like something
You couldn't sell this
Here the truth is revealed
You've worked hard
-I have?
We are Wednesday Downtown
-Ah?
A sigh of relief
I was so scared, so scared
Great!
I've really never done this even once before
Acqua pazza, I thought it was pasta at first
I thought he was gonna make Italian...
But there was no pasta around anywhere
Finally, the verification of the difficulty level MAX
The target is
The goal is
The Mommy
I have a show to discuss with you
The MC of the show is Hamada
-Oh!
This time, it's a show where entertainers return to their hometown after a long time
The choice of Hamada as host doesn't match at all
A show full of warmth and fraudulence
There's one thing I'd like to discuss before we go on location
There's an issue with including family
Even if it's your own family, they can't be filmed because of restrictions
This is the setup
Oh, parents?
Going to shoot in homes now
It's tough because of coronavirus
So we need to discuss something
We'll prepare a detached house and pretend it's your old home
-Ok
And prepare a pair of extras to pretend to be your parents
For me?
A fake hometown and fake parents, Sakai's whole part will be completely fake
Unheard of super hardcore industry talk
The Mommy's two can't help but smile bitterly
You are called "Mommy" still, right?
Obviously called "Mommy" still ...
But my mother was on TV
There is a risk of exposure if someone sees and realizes
Yeah
Well, because it is a member of the general public, we can put a mosaic on the face
Ahhh I see
Indeed, if you put the mosaic on...
Is this kind of thing really possible?
Not the type to think to hard about something
The studio portion of the show will be recorded in three days
Hamada's people are aware
Hamada's name was brought up
This exterior part, if we don't do something about it...
-Wow, no...
Hamada's getting excited about the project
Hamada... I see....
Using MC Hamada as a strong backing
The staff pushes the messy negotiation forward hard
They'd definitely be afraid
They'd feel compelled to accept
I've heard that Hamada can be pretty scary
It seems that staff are afraid to disobey him
Indeed, that's right
So, if we refuse, it will cause a lot of trouble
Well, these things happen from time to time
Not even once has it been exposed
The TV industry is really like this
From time to time
Every now and then
Sometimes programs can't be completed without some trickery, so...
A reassuring image of an experienced fraud
Safe and secure
First, the fake parents are vetted
I want you to choose yourself
Like an audition?
And so, the director immediately calls in the extras
What can you say?
-Hey, wait a minute
I'm completely confused. What's going on now?
I... Anyway
-It's fake
Actually, it's not very important. It's just parents...
Yeah, and the mosaic, right?
It's just a report
This is airing in the daytime anyway
But this kind of thing usually gets exposed
No one will watch it
No way, Hamada's hosting it!
True
It's ok if we don't promote it... it's too late to pull out now
"If we don't promote it, we'll be able to get by without the fans noticing"
Says Sakai, who continues to talk to himself
At that moment
And so, the extras enter
Here are some alternate parents
You can choose the parents you like from them
Favorite parents?
Can we see the faces
So
Can I see? Sorry
Ah, similar
Ah, this one is pretty good
Surprisingly, he finds an extra who looks like his real mother
It feels like it will work.
-The same vibe...
But
And what about the father?
Father... is there only two choices for fathers?
How tall are you?
-179
Ah so tall, our family is very short
Is that so?
-I'm the tallest in our family
Well, if they are sitting down to shoot, it could be ok.
-Yes, indeed
Do some editing to adjust the height or something
Can you change height in post?
Can it be done?
Well...
I guess, post-editing, shrink him a little...
Then please choose one of these two
After being told that height can be adjusted by post-editing
The selection is complete
After which the "family" exchange information for 30 minutes
Finally, they visit Sakai's fake hometown
And a house studio prepared beforehand
Must be a weird mood in the car
Although it is a bit bad to say
Sometimes things like this are exposed
Has it happened?
Sometimes by other teams
-Hmm yes
If people like me that aren't used to it are involved then it could happen I guess
This will be very bad if it's exposed to Hamada, right?
If the forgery is exposed
No one on his side will tell him
It's been fine so far
In light of Hamada's dull senses, they were reassured
As long as you don't say anything yourself
It's something I'll take to my grave for sure.
-Thank you
Shortly after being reassured
So, here we are at...
The character's are wrong
The characters on the nameplate are wrong and the nameplate is just a piece of paper
Which shocks them both
What a crude forgery!
Is such a crude practice really possible?
However, everything that will be exposed will apparently not be shown
Believing this, they continue to shoot on location
It's too rough, right?
Ah, there's a dog
Yeah, did I not say?
Next is the Shiba Inu that he doesn't remember at all
His name is Genji.
-Genji?
Look, isn't he cute?
Because in shooting you can not simply muddle through
You have to get closer and get involved
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, it's because he's never met me before...
Scared of dogs
He's scary, sorry
That...
It's... it's been too long
Usually quiet?
Usually quiet, but there's a lot of people he doesn't know today
Nicely done
When a stranger calls a strange name, he will certainly bark
Genji（Real Name: Nana）
Uh... so
Can you take us to your room to have a look?
My room? No problem
Does he know where it is?
You can't get past it, can you?
Where is it?
-That one
Here
What?
I've missed this bag so much
Red schoolbag
Hey, what is this?
And so the shooting continued in the room full of traps
Opening the last room...
What's in there?
What room is this?
For some reason, its the waiting room at TBS with the leftover extras
That's weird. That's weird
Let them leave!
That now, this...
This room is a room that cannot be opened
Can't open?
-Can't be opened
Is it your parents room?
Parents... yes this is my parents room
My parents...
And so, the location shooting ended with the reunion of the impostor family
Well, thank you very much for giving birth to me
So embarrassing!
Wait, your mom is crying
Okay, OK, thank you all
With the finish, discussions about post-editing plans begin
It's a little bit confusing, some parts are too outrageous
The sailor suit uniform
How can that be dealt with?
Well, anyway, find a way to edit it
Sorry sorry sorry
What about your father's face?
I think its okay to not use the mosaic
No
-No?
The father is not so good
-Not so good?
Ok for the mom though?
No resemblance on the father's side
He's too tall
So much taller than my real father
What was said before about shrinking in post?
What is he saying?
If you can shrink him a lot...
At this point, we reveal the truth
What program were you told you were on today?
Today is "I'm Home, Mom"
In fact, this program is fake
Eh? Not "I'm Home, Mom"?
It's actually Wednesday Downtown
Eh? Wait a second...
Did you notice anything strange today?
Ah, seriously, this program faked too much
Saying "it's never been exposed once"
"Hamada's shows often have this kind of thing"
When the staff introduced themselves, they made it seem like they were professionals
Did you really believe that height can be modified in post?
Do I... I don't know so much about TV!
It's probably possible
You shouldn't ask us young artists who lack popularity to do this kind of thing
We'll really do anything we're told
In summary
They'll do anything
Seriously
Poor people!
How about it? What do you think?
Well, how to say...
The part of mankind called sin
These things happen
But this is could also be seen as being professional in a sense, right?
-That's true
Because it's to do with work, they take it seriously
The difference between professional and non-professional is here, right?
No, no, that's not the case
He's right
Look, now because of Youtube
The difference between professional and non-professional is a little unclear
Those who can fake are professionals, right?
That's not true, that's not true
I think if you look carefully, you can find some fakes on Youtube
But the last group of artists, The Mommy, had it tough
They were told it was Hamada's show...
Hamada is the kind of person who would say the VTR was boring
"You can fake it, but make it interesting for me"
That's not the case!
That's his motto!
What the hell? It's not!
Let's welcome the next presenter
No no no...
It's FUJIWARA!
So
Once performers become famous
They will get lots of offers for business opportunities
What type of things?
Eh?
Clothing
Certainly clothing
Food
Barbecue restaurants
Stuff like colored contact lenses too
Yeah, i'm involved in that
-Oh really
I'm working on colored contact lenses and western-style clothes
Oh yeah
Is that a serious project?
It's seriously being planned
I've attended meetings and stuff
Really?
-Yes
Seriously
Yes
-What?
Isn't there that type?
What?
Just use the name for endorsement and nothing else
-I guess
So, how about this
I bring you a theory about entertainer endorsement
It's this:
No matter how unpleasant the content, will entertainer's endorse anything if the pay is high enough?
I see
Your ex-wife made that milk tea shop
She didn't make it
She didn't?
If she did, i'd say "wow"
So weird
Do it then i'll spit out a "wow"
No matter how unpleasant the content, will entertainer's endorse anything if the pay is high enough?
The initial target is
Teshima Yu
Maybe
Initially, her agent tells her about a restaurant
But no details are known yet
There is a restaurant endorsement job coming up
For me？
-Yes
What type?
We will talk about the details gradually
It seems the owner is a big fan of yours
Quite convincing
He wants to work with you
Are there really such people?
They want to try it out
Probably a big pervert
Highly probable
It doesn't feel like an ordinary person
Really?
Like weird fetishes or something
"That kind of guy is either a pervert or has weird fetishes"
Teshima has a deep understanding
I think I must give people a dirty kind of impression
So i'd like a simple and fresh store
Somewhere where women can easily enter
She wants a refreshing place
However, the name of the restaurant is...
"Yakiniku Teshima"
I think I've seen it somewhere before
Will she lend her names depending on the amount of money?
This...
So, a few days later
Discussions with a fake agency
Getting to the point
About planning a restaurant, have you ever thought about what kind of restaurant you want to plan?
If I go out to eat
Almost all the restaurants I go to are barbecue restaurants.
-Yakiniku restaurants?
It would be nice to plan the type of restaurant I like
The thing she likes, by chance, is yakiniku
So, the store's name is firstly put forward
Teshima Yu Catering Plan
Turn to the first page first
Ahhhhh so good
-Yes
Simple and straightforward
"Yakiniku Teshima"
-Yes
That's not the name of the restaurant, is it?
That's the name of the restaurant?
Ah, the name of the restaurant?
How about Yakiniku Teshima Yu?
Is it OK?
How to say... no, I'm happy.
-Ok
Happy and a little shy
The feeling of happiness and shyness
It would happen
Although a little concerned about the name of the store, it passes
Have you ever thought about how to do a barbecue restaurant?
The kind where you can go with a little privacy
A store with a slightly dark feel
It's impossible for you to go to "Yakiniku Yu Teshima" in disguise
Please turn to the next page
It's the design of the store
-Wow
The picture is pretty cute
What about? How does it look and feel
-It's cute!
It's not too fashionable so it has a welcoming feeling
I really like the atmosphere
This A plan seems to be consistent with her thoughts
Of course, the main attraction is coming
Plan B.
-Wait. Oh, okay
This is the Teshima design
Is this the outside?
Yes, they are signs
Looks like its in Shin-Okubo
Hey, it's great
-Yes
This is inside? My photos
Yes
It's all Teshima Yu
"Delicious and cheap"
A and B are not at all similar
Yeah
It's a little unsettling, it looks a little like a adult store, maybe a bit confusing
She said it
A little rude
Could be a bit embarrassing for the owner
In other words, it's like a customs-free store
So it seems she wont choose B
The choice of A will use up a lot of the budget
-Hmmm
This is a question of endorsement fees or planning fees
If you choose A, you can get about 30000 yen a month
B will require less money spent on publicity
So for this one you can get 500,000 yen per month
A huge difference
A blatant demonstration of how the pay gap works
This one seems to be a bit more suitable for the masses
Hey, it's bad!
A is maybe a bit too higher class
She heard the fee
How about choosing A?
Slowly, she changes her choice with impossible reasons
The second one is not normal at all
After re-considering
If we go with plan A, people may think i'm getting too cocky
I know
Then how about going ahead with plan B?
It's cute
It has a good feeling
Teshima, who is easily and superficially obsessed with money
At this point, she is left alone with her agent
What will they say?
It would have been better to go with A
Indeed
But the pay is completely different
If we think about the future
It would be good for settling down
Yeah
After confirming Teshima's thoughts
A is much better
Next
About the background music in the restaurant
In the case of program A, it's jazz
Please listen
So sad!
But you do often hear this kind of music being played
At trendy barbecue places
It's very good. It's an immersive feeling
This is the other
Teshima Yu♪ Teshima Yu♪ Yakiniku Teshima Yu♪
Ju Ju Ju (the sound of barbecue) One piece into the soul♡
What do you like? Barbecued ribs?
Or me? ♪
Custom-made
Awful
Teshima Yu♪ Teshima Yu♪ Yakiniku Teshima Yu♪
Will this keep going?
Yes, it'll loop
"Or me?" Is that ok?
Do you care about the lyrics?
Yeah
It doesn't seem like the background music of a restaurant
"Or me"...
But of course, in terms of renumeration
Scheme A is only used as is, so you will not be paid
Scheme B will give you an extra 100,000 yen per month
Which is better A or B?
B
I already remember it, its catchy
Be strong!
The rhythm is good, don't you think?
How!?
You've got a good thing going
It's pleasant to listen to
600,000 yen now
After that
For social media, you'll get 10,000 yen every 1000 likes
200,000 yen when introducing the name of the store on a TV program
Downtown DX
Those two will roll with the topic
Yes, they answer people's questions. Both are very kind
As all of the unpleasant proposals are accepted, a feeling of freshness is long gone
It ends up with a large contract totaling 1.22 million yen per month
So, the truth is revealed
So embarrassing
What the hell?
I'm scared, what is it?
Th-that, what?
Something happened, right?
We are Wednesday Downtown
-Wow!
"No matter how unpleasant the content, will entertainer's endorse anything if the pay is high enough?"
if it's between 30,000 yen and 500,000 yen
You'd choose the 500,000 yen one, of course
Those signs
Those are used in the adult places, right?
And so, we know that Teshima is unfortunately not resistant to money
Next is an additional verificaiton
The target is
Nana Suzuki, who has ranked 1st in popularity lists before
She's risen?
I definitely wouldn't do it
I might
I still need to work harder
Yahagi~ Yahagi~
That would be even worse
I'd refuse that just out of embarrassment
Here, the plan is also discussed in advance
My favorite is yakiniku
The same as Teshima Yu, she hopes to run a yakiniku place
Please turn to the next page
"Yakiniku Nana Suzuki"
-Yes
Oh, yakiniku, i'm so happy!
Is the name of the restaurant "Yakiniku Suzuki Nana"?
Yes
-Awesome
That's great.
-What do you think?
How is it? It's clear and easy to understand
Store name tentatively adopted
Please turn to the next page
Super chic
-Thank you
Very fashionable
-Thanks
I like it
-The vibe?
Please turn to the next page
Another option has been prepared
Eh? What is this?
This is too much, right?
This is a design that completely highlights Nana Suzuki
It fits Teshima Yu's persona at least
I'm glad, but..
I feel a like it won't do so well
I think its a bit unapproachable
She said it
Indeed
Well, I think it will fail
Suzuki Nana shows clear disapproval of this look
A normal reaction
Regarding your fee
If Option A is used
It will use a lot of the budget
Yes, I understand
We can give you about 30,000 yen per month, 30,000 per store
The initial cost of B is not much
-Ok
So you can get 500,000 yen per month for this one
So much difference
Yes, every month
Is the difference really that big?
-Yes
After all, its a comprehensive use of your image and name
-I see
That's what it is
Ah, just give it a go!
That was fast
Super fast
But, the menu is cheap. If it's cheap and tasty, people will come in, right?
I think people will come
-Agreed
Said herself it looks like it will fail
After all, it is a ready-made store
I choose B
-Okay, I see
Thank you
Quick decision!
Next, the background music
Nana Suzuki♪ Nana Suzuki♪ Yakiniku Nana Suzuki♪
Ju Ju Ju (the sound of barbecue) One piece into the soul♡
Is it beef tongue you like? Grilled ribeye?
Or me?♪
Awesome
How about this one?
People eating will feel tired, right?
It's like one of those advertising trucks going around Shibuya
Correct answer
For Option A, you will not be paid monthly
Plan B will give you 100,000 yen per month
A big difference
Option B is more compatible with store B. I choose option B
-Got it
How about a discount when you play this music
-Good idea!
Personal proposal of a discount program
Suzuki ends up with a full package of 1.22 million yen per month
The truth is revealed
Whoa, what's going on!
How could she also do this
Thus we explain the project
So annoying!
Really, really annoying
What will people think of this?
What if my work is reduced?
How much work do you have now?
I can't make it work if I have less than I already do now
It is really unimaginable
In summary
The next challenge is Yakiniku Asahi Nao
What do you think?
-So scary
Can people change like this?
Is it possible to switch so easily?
Women of that rank...
At the stage of planning, wouldn't producers voice their opinions?
This is better and so on
Up until there i thought it was ok...
They wouldn't let their people just do whatever they want, right?
I guess
But how about if this kind of opportunity really came to you
Would you go along with it?
Honestly, Wednesday Downtown is a show that is using someone's name
Downtown's
Really?
Using the Downtown for fraudulent purposes
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03