Today's presenters are the same as last week
Please welcome, FUJIWARA
This is a continuation of last week
Today is also Kuro-chan's life on an uninhabited island
Firstly, a brief recap
A room was built on an uninhabited island
All of Kuro-chan's items were transported to it
After which the drunken Kuro-chan was also moved there
While there, if he collects 7 balls he can make a wish
Through a mixture of rock and tree climbing as well as swimming, Kuro-chan was able to finally collect all 7
So, ladies and gentlemen
What will happen next?
Being able to get home so quickly wouldn't be great
What other drama can unfold?
There's more
By the way, the balls are quite big, right?
So actually, he's entitled to him 3 wishes
What do you think Kuro-chan will wish for?
Maybe one of the girls from SUN TV
Possible, possible
Maybe his own show as reward for putting him through all of this
Since the Wednesday Downtown staff put him through so much
Thus
Got all 7!
Next I'm going to make my wish come true
I want to escape from here
Can you go back now?
Finally I can go back
It took Kuro-chan three days to finally collect all of the balls
I have collected 7 balls
Can I get my wish now?
Make my wish come true-
What's that sound?
Come back quickly! Come back quickly!
What's going on?
What?
Why is the drone coming?
Wait a minute... it shouldn't be a drone
What's going on?
Come on, say your wish.
I can grant you any 3 wishes
The drone speaks
It can talk?
Is the drone Shenlong!?
Because the balls are so big I can get three wishes?
I can say anything, right?
Then,
I want my own show!
You got it, Degawa
Impressive
Bingo!
Kuro-chan's first wish has nothing to do with the island
Surprisingly, it's his own show
Shouldn't he find a way to get back first?
Give me my own show!
I can't do that
Why?
That just wouldn't be possible
Can't I wish for anything?
I can't make that wish come true
No. What's with this lack of ability?
That's reasonable
Consistent
Why can't you do it?
Well, first let me go back to Tokyo
I want to go back to Tokyo
I can't do that
Why!?
I can't make that wish come true
No, wait a minute. What can you do?
That's a little pathetic
Come on, say your wish.
I've been saying it since a while ago
I want to leave this uninhabited island and go home
That...
Boat. Give me a boat
I see
It's amazing that this wish can be achieved!
Such a weird wish!
I've set up the boat on the beach
Boat by the sea. Where is it?
Shenlong's ability is limited, sorry
So, he begins searching along the coast
Finally
Wait a minute, is that it?
It's this one. It's this one
That's good
A small boat, I have a boat
I've got a boat! A boat!
But...
Wait!
There is no rowing thing!
Where's the rowing thing? Where's the rowing thing?
Where is the oar?
Hey
Why didn't you give me an oar?
I'll prepare an oar for you, then
Just one isn't enough, OK!?
I need two, a pair!
I understand
Fulfilling your second wish
Two oars for you
No! Wait a second!
So everyone, dragon humor, what do you think?
Hey, the oar is the second wish? Wait a minute!
And so, Kuro-chan uses up his second wish
The last wish is
In this case
I want to become a rich man
I want 1 billion. Give me 1 billion yen
There he goes
I can't do this
Why!?
Learn your lesson!
100 million, 100 million
I can't do this either
Isn't that bullshit?
Give it to me, I've been working so hard
1 million, 1 million, 1 million is doable, right?
Becoming less
Starting bargaining
1 million yen
I can't do this either
Why!?
What about 100,000? 100,000
So real
Ok, here you go
Is it possible?
Although i'm happy
So, goodbye.
Such a realistic amount
No, don't leave. Wait a minute
100,000 yen
100,000 is too little. 200,000!
10...wait a minute, wait a minute
It's come back
This is way worse that I expected
And so, he succeeds in obtaining:
A small boat, two oars and 100,000 yen
What the hell, fulfill your 3 wishes
Nothing was achieved
Unfulfilled wishes are piled up
What the hell!
Incompetent rage
Fuming inside the room
Unbelievable
That said, I'm going
You are responsible for putting the things in the room back for me!
Remember to put everything back!
Or i'll kill you!
Scary!
Angry Kuro-chan
There are too many killings declarations on this show
Ah, moving moving moving
I'm getting on, I'm getting on-
Bye bye, uninhabited island!
A successful escape from the uninhabited island
Is he rowing backward?
It's the other way around
Super tiring
It's too physically demanding. Life on an uninhabited island
With manual labor and unfulfilled wishes
He paddles for 3 hours towards the neighboring island
It took so long
Land, i've reached land
Pretty impressive
Finally
Dangerous
What's he up to?
Finally, i've arrived
The fall just now has a new meaning
Genius
After 56 hours, he steps onto occupied land again
I've arrived, i've arrived!
Then,
Where is this place?
This is Iejima's Bose in Hyogo Prefecture
Hyogo Prefecture?
He confirms the location
And boards a ferry to Himeji Port in Honshu
I took a cab because I had the money
Where is he going?
Please take me to Himeji Station
Are you an entertainer, sir?
Ah, for the moment, yes
You are an entertainer!
Yes
It's been a long time since I've talked to someone
I'm here, i'm here
Why should I use my own cash to go home?
I should absolutely let you pay for this
A rare return to Tokyo from the uninhabited island project with his own money
He's one of a kind
Returning to his real home again after 4 days
Great, but his stuff?
I don't think it's there yet.
-No, not arrived
But the room is cleaner.
-Yes, it's cleaner
Huh?
There's nothing left
Oh yeah, I haven't gotten my stuff back yet
Huh? Wait a minute, wait a minute
Eh? Eh? Wait, what's going on?
The refrigerator is missing
Eh? There's nothing left. Wait, what's going on?
Also...
The stuff here is missing too!
Scary
What should be here wasn't on the island, huh?
Why is it all gone?
Scary
There's nothing left. Back over here...
Huh?
100,000 yen
Ah, it's 100,000 yen
His wish
And then
What is it?
Another letter?
Congratulations on escaping from the uninhabited island
We would like to inform you of one thing
The house that Kuro-chan has lived in for 15 years is planned to be demolished
Eh?
This place...is going to be demolished?
Surprisingly learned from the show
No, why do you know?
Why do the staff know stuff that I don't?
Yes, so far we have used this site for many shoots
So this house is full of memories
After 63 years of existing, the decision was made to demolish the entire building
Residents were asked to move out by the end of August
So from tomorrow, we will start looking for a new home
Please have a good rest in your room today first
Looking for a new home?
Wait a minute, I do not understand this development, i'm not following
It's not over yet? Escaping from the island is not the end?
I do not understand ah... there's so much I don't understand
Where is my stuff? Where is the stuff from the other rooms?
Kuro-chan's belongings are being kept by the program team until he finds a new home
So, the island was just a prelude to Kuro-chan finding a new home
Hey, I didn't hear that the house was going to be demolished
It looks like there is still a lot of information for Kuro-chan to digest
For the time being, he heads to a convenience store that he has not visited for 4 days
Delicious~ So delicious!
He eats his favorite convenience store box lunch
And sleeps on the floor like this
Too tragic
What a day after coming back
Sleeping on the hard floor that night
He can sleep anywhere
So, a seamless transition from the uninhabited island to looking for a new home
This is the focus of the whole project
The program team has been one step ahead of Kuro-chan
We got the news that the residence will be demolished soon
So since everything needs to be moved out
We began to consider what to do
Which lead to this project
In a sense we're also doing him a favor
That's right.
-Helped him move
By the way, the two of us also accompanied him to find a new place
So folks, here comes the main event
So please continue to watch
Therefore, the day after returning home from the island
A weird way to wake up
Kuro-chan
Wow, what?
It's you two!
We're in
Coming in!
Wait why?
Wow - how clean it is!
Wait, why?
What? Why?
Why did you come in with the camera so naturally?
Wait a minute, what the hell is going on?
No need to keep playing up
This group of people
The same reaction every time
Okay, let's go
Let's go, Kuro-chan. Let's go
Wait a minute, I don't understand the situation at all
What is going on?
Looking for a new house, of course
What else could it be but this
Eh?
Come on
Eh? Really?
That hurts! Why did you hit me?
The building will be demolished
8 minutes walk from JR Shinagawa Station
Two-bedroom plus kitchen, rent 120,000 yen
Good location
For Kuro-chan, who has lived here for 15 years since arriving in Tokyo
This time, FUJIWARA decided to help him find a new house
So, the first house is
Over here
First of all, a house in Shinagawa Ward, where Kuro currently lives
Looks like a nice apartment
By the way, Fujimoto is the only one who has information on housing this time
Is this a public space? So narrow
Is it a parking lot?
There is such an area
Feels like something everyone can use together
This is not for everyone to use together
Eh? What the hell?
Eh?
-Eh?
This isn't communal?
No, this is a single house
Eh?
-Eh?
It's a lie, right?
-Must be, right?
This is a detached house
This is too big
This is a big deal for Kuro-chan!
Wait a minute, what's up with the detached building?
Please, please, please, please!
Wow, that's awesome!
Absolutely empty
Eh?
Ah, you thought it's an apartment?
No, this entrance is too big, right?
A big mansion!
I don't understand
That spotlight is outrageous
How fashionable!
No, no, no, no, no. Wait, wait, wait
This is great!
Wait a minute...wait a minute
Okay, first of all, this is the living room
No, no, no...Fujimoto!
Fujimoto!
This room is 45 mats
※1 mats = 1.62 square meters, so about 72.9 square meters in total
45 mats?
Yes
There's a heater over here
Heaters and other things have never been used
The house is 36 years-old
Unexpected...
It's an older building
The construction cost was 4.5 billion yen
4.5 billion?
A room like this
You can't stop yourself from laughing
This three-storey detached house has a total area of about 400 square meters
A 5LSDK mega house
Each room has ample amenities
Bathroom and toilet
It's not a matter of bath or no bath...
Wow, wow, wow, wow!
By the way, this should be introduced
Sauna room
Sauna?
Yes, you can have a steam
It's not even a simple sauna, it's impressive
Standard sauna room
A real sauna
This is not even a one-person sauna
Can fit a number of people
Eh, it's really impressive
Why are you locking up? Why lock me up?
Wait a minute. Open the door quickly
Open, open!
Don't do that kind of thing
Don't make such primitive jokes
It was not my intention
As for the uppermost third floor,
You can barbecue on the terrace
Are you kidding me? Are you kidding me?
The scenery is also great
Call all your comedian buddies to get together for a small bbq party
It'll surely be a mess in no time
I would never ask a comedian to come to my home
Troupe leader or something
I'd rather die than call him over
TKO's Kinoshita or something
※Due to Kuro-chan making fun of TKO's Kinoshita, Kinoshita angrily stomped on Kuro-chan's head backstage and then later abused him during a bout of drunkenness, which shocked Kuro-chan and led to him expressing his disgust for Kinoshita
I'd definitely be stomped on again
You won't get stomped on, it's okay
What's more,
He'll definitely be stomped on again
This is the maid's room
The maid's room? The maid?
Right
This place is exclusively for the maid
Lies!
-A bathtub?
A whole bathroom?
A complete package
The maids can live here comfortably
It's really something
This room is good
-Enough
It's enough for me to have such a room
After a look around the house
So, Kuro-chan, we've looked inside and outside of the house
What do you think is the approximate rent?
The rent for this place?
Looks so expensive
Monthly rent
Haranishi, you also think about it
How much is it?
800,000
Impossible
I don't think I can afford to rent it for 800,000
What about Haranishi?
It must be 2 million
Sorry, Kuro-chan, I think it must be around that
Not 2 million, right?
The rent for this residence is...
1.85 million yen ($13,600)
This is the price
So, to live or not to live?
I can't
So quick
It is impossible to live here
Don't back out and regret it later!
This one is eliminated straight away?
Don't say later that the previous building is better. Don't say such things
Eh?
After all, we're going to see a few more
Of course, we can't just view this one place
Well, let's keep it for now
Seriously?
Let's keep it for now
I can't stay here, I can't stay here
No, this one is kept for now
No, don't make the decision for me. I'm not keeping this place
Kept!
Eh?
The first ultra-luxury residence is kept for the time being
Kuro-chan is now looking at the second home
Over here
Not bad!
How does it look at first glance?
Looks good too, right?
Another detached building
A single-family house in Matsudo, Chiba Prefecture
We went to Matsudo
Smells like a new building
This way please
This is the open kitchen, which is integrated with the living room
A total of 16 mats
※25.9 square meters
4LDK two-story small building
A common family home
And then
Ah, not bad
5 years old, so it's a relatively new construction
Kuro-chan, how about this residence?
To be honest it feels like it'd be good to live in
Considering the future, getting married or getting a girlfriend or whatever
It should be a good choice
Right?
The only disadvantage is that it is a little bit far from the city center
The only downside is this
If you don't care too much then there's no downside
No problem
So it's time to guess the price
180,000
-A guess of 180,000
I think less than 200,000
Is it that low...it's a single family home?
I don't know, it could be more expensive
350,000
It's not that expensive, right?
The price of this residence is...
85,000 yen
So cheap!
85,000 yen, eh?
So cheap
85,000 yen?
Right? It's cheap
It's so cheap. It's cheaper than where you live now
Yeah, my current place costs 120,000.
-120,000
Is it too cheap? A little suspicious
Yes
This house is a murder house
Scary scary scary
Wait a minute. What's going on here?
Terrifying!
Hey wait wait wait wait
Terrible terrible, what happened?
Why did you bring me to this kind of place?
※According to the Internet, there are three possible incidents: ① a man killed himself after killing his brother-in-law ② someone beheaded their mother ③ a woman hanged herself in a closet and killed her son
I said I said I said why why why why
One second
It's scary
How did it happen?
What what what?
Don't ask
Stop being nosy
Wouldn't it be troublesome to live here?
Have you decided?
Decide what...
Will you keep it?
Just keep it
I'm not keeping it
Absolutely not. It feels like there will be something nasty coming with it
Don't say that something nasty will come with it
It will!
There's nothing
Did this happen long ago?
Well...
So curious, seriously!
If you hear such a thing you can't help but want to know
And so, the second place is not kept
The three then headed to...
A single house in Yugawara, Kanagawa Prefecture
Nice place
Single family home
It's a detached house and...
What's wrong?
What is this?
Isn't it a bit rundown?
It's got charm
-Eh?
This is called charm
Intriguing interior layout
Indeed
How about it?
This...
Did the last occupant run away in the night?
Yes
There is too much life in it
No, no, no
The occupant just left, right?
It's not the kind of place that says that
This side is full of garbage
Can really smell it
It's obviously the smell of dust
A two-level 2LDK small detached house with full amenities
The toothbrush can also be used
Ahhh, who used this!?
1, 2, 3, there are three people living here!
Since you're complaining so much
-What?
I'll tell you the best part
There's something good?
-Check this out
Over here
This side is still being cleaned up though
-Cleaning up?
It comes with this garden
-A garden?
A garden
It's about the size of a tennis court
This is that big?
He can take up gardening
You can turn it into a garden of your choice
Even this place with trees growing?
All of them are your own personal trees
Personal tree?
Personal tree
One more thing, Kuro-chan, please look over here
-What?
How about that?
-Really?
That right there is an orange
The oranges are said to be really delicious
From whom did you hear that?
Go and look
Orange? The real thing?
Can I walk on there?
Now he's definitely back from an uninhabited island
What the hell is this?
What's going on here?
Kuro-chan, you are even allowed to dig traps on this residence
It's a beautiful trap
I recommend this one!
Impossible to find
So, as this section is within the lease, the land offers ample opportunities for different shots
He let his guard down
It's the most suitable residence for outside scenes
Kuro-chan would definitely suffer here
This is dug way too big
The hollow inside is too big, right?
Incase you ran over there...
We had to consider all the circumstances beforehand
No, it's not okay. This is really bad, right?
And the house is not good at all
And it's as if the residents ran away halfway through their occupancy
Although their rent predictions are as shown
The correct answer is
0 yen
What is the deal with 0 yen?
-What is the situation
This house is used by the local community association
This is a house where you can move in for 0 yen if you become the house manager
Manager?
Must become the manager
What is the conditions, what responsibilities are involved
Community affairs are discussed in the living room about once or twice a month
So the administrator has the responsibility of managing the reservation and delivering keys
Isn't this something only the locals can do?
I hope that Kuro-chan will become a more prominent member of the local community
0 yen if you take the job?
-0 yen
0 yen is a big deal
So what to do?
-Free?
Yes, oh?
When it comes to free, a lot of complaints disappear
-Yes
No, there is a slight feeling of nostalgia about it
As soon as you hear 0 yen, you start thinking
You can retain 2 places at the same time!
Keep one. You can keep this one too
But this may also be good
You can also let people fall in the trap here when you hold the meetings
They'll be injured!
I don't think there are any young people in the community association
Therefore, the trap room with 0 yen rent is kept for now
Next is a house in Toshima Ward
It's already dark!
Because we had to travel from Matsudo
This is it
I'll introduce it from this side of the room
This side of the room
Ah, there's a bed
There's a bed
What's this?
Wait a minute. This is a room. Does that mean this is the first room?
Yes, this is the room
Not the first room, but the room
This room?
-Yes
No. Where's the bathroom?
-It's not here
Eh?
-Eh?
What?
It's a shared apartment
Shared apartment?
-Yes
That means there are shared bathrooms and toilets?
Yes, this is a six-story building with one room per person
A shared apartment with 36 people living in it currently
Girls too... in shared apartments, there are also girls, right?
Of course.
-Definitely!
Here's some good info
There are more than twenty married couples in this shared apartment
Eh? Love house?
What do you mean "love house"?
This is a shared living room with space for ten people to communicate and move around at the same time
There is also a standard gym
Wait, this is great, right?
The gym is so cool.
-Glamorous, isn't it?
Ah, there is also a piano
Do you know how to play?
I sometimes play "Merry Christmas Mr. Lawrence"
Oh really?
Surprised by this
Unique technique
I kind of forgot how to play it
Can you be a little more measured?
Either play badly or play well
I was about to say, "So this guy has that side," when you suddenly started playing badly
Later, the current residents were interviewed
Is it easy to get along with each other?
We are like a family
A family
-Family
Do you remember everyone's names?
Because there are names and nicknames, you make extra effort to remember
Everyone has nicknames?
When did you receive the nicknames?
The residents meeting
There's resident meetings?
First, potential nicknames are put forward then everyone votes
A voting system?
You all decide together?
As such, a nickname will be assigned to Kuro-chan, who may become a resident
Adventurer
Please tell us what you like to do and what you're interested in
Originally he wanted to become an idol
I was tricked into becoming a comedian
I also do rock climbing
And I have a Level 1 Dance Certificate
And am also a certified Aromatherapy Master
"Idol", not bad, right? You can be an idol here!
Since you wanted to become an idol before, right?
"Idol"
I am Idol-yo!
I'm super happy!
What the hell!?
Whoa, I didn't expect to have so much fun
-Welcome, welcome
What's your rent prediction for this shared apartment?
It's quite suitable for Kuro-chan, right?
Because it is communal,
I guess there are many people who live here to save money
80,000 yen
Wow, a good guess!
75,000 yen
So, here we go
-Please!
The rent here is...
115,000 yen
Unexpected
But isn't it nice? It even has a gym
Yeah but, going to the gym is not costly
So, Kuro-chan, what do you think of this place?
Keep!
Why?
Everyone here is very gentle and friendly
But its a gradual search
So i'd still like to consider other residences
Eh, more?
I mean, I finally found one that I like, so it makes me want to look at even more
Today, it took a whole day just to get to one
Number one and number two are absolutely impossible, right?
I don't know.
-I can't live there!
No, we don't know what you like, Kuro-chan
Keep? So which ones do you want to keep then?
The free one, and here
You're keeping the free one, you just can't let the free one go
I'm keeping the free one
And so, the search for Kuro-chan's new home enters a second day
Wow, what will happen?
Just came back from an uninhabited island the day before
Yes
And then immediately went on this location shoot?
What a mess
There's an "Adventurer" in the shared apartment
Kuro-chan is actually more like an adventurer
Shared apartments are not bad
Yeah shared apartments aren't bad
Yeah, I guess
But it'd be a bad choice for filming
Yeah
I don't live in Kasuga's apartment anymore
If Kuro's apartment is available to work with
It'd be a heavy blow to variety shows
A certain death
Especially for Wednesday Downtown
However, because Kuro-chan wanted to continue seeing more homes
The staff had to look for more
So after this, a week later,
Just as we were about to do some more viewings
Literally the day before
Kuro-chan got coronavirus
So we had to prepare to find other places after he had recovered
So it's not over yet?
How long will it take him to recover?
How long will it take?
Roughly
He should be out about now
Saying "out" is a bit...
He wasn't in prison
After the last episode - One month has passed
So, so...
It's FUJIWARA!
We are FUJIWARA!
Why did you come out?
To put an end to Kuro-chan's house search
I think we've had enough
Does it make sense to do it like this?
What are you talking about?
Therefore, one day in August, when Kuro-chan was successfully discharged from the hospital
So, this is the next day of house hunting
Great!
Day 2 day 2!
So excited!
I'm sorry for interrupting the shoot because of coronavirus
Really
It can't be helped...
It can't be helped
So, we've found a house you according to your wishes
-Really?
So please make a decision
He couldn't decide on a new home among the 4 residences he visited on the first day
And so, the first residence for this day was...
A 14th floor apartment in Chuo-ku
This is a decent place to live
Please come in, please come in
Ohhhh
Okay, okay, let's go
Please, please, please
Take a look
Ah, so spacious!
How about this place? It was built last year
-Last year?
A brand new apartment.
-Eh?
Suddenly a serious one
No, no, no...
You're helping me with this, you're helping me with this
The feeling of "let's stay here" came over me
Yeah, that's for sure
We can't take you everywhere of course
We also want you to make a decision quickly
Looks like it's for real this time, Kuro-chan
Just make a good decision
Did something happen here?
Not at all
-No?
Nothing
Age: one year and 6 months
A little larger than Kuro-chan's current residence
A 50 sqm 2LDK problem-free house
And it's brand new
Please look over there
-It's spacious
A walk-in closet
-It's super spacious
Is there any storage here?
What are you talking about? Can't you see?
The tone is so cold
I don't even know what he was asking
A house with plenty of storage
The rent is of concern
27... 8
28？
So, Kuro-chan, how much?
This is also an issue, I can't guess the price
220,000
220,000?
The rent for this residence is...
255,000 yen
Ah, so close
You are both very close
There is no reason to refuse a house like this
-So true
So...
I am interested in this residence
Please let me think about it a little more
That's the process, right?
That...
It feels like the first half and the second half are completely different
-Hmm
The time lapse is a bit long
I'm sorry
What was done on the first day of the shoot?
There was too much of a gap between then and now
I don't know what the reason is,
Why did you forget?
You know, the money issue...
A little indecisive about money, I guess
Scared by the prospect of doubling his current rent
Therefore, the residence here is kept for the time being
Next: Room 6
A three-story apartment in Shinagawa Ward
Here, oh
But the problem is the rent!
Eh-
Not bad
Here. It's spacious, isn't it?
Very spacious
Not bad, huh?
-It's not bad
28 years old, 87 square meters, 2SLDK house with roof terrace
There is a Japanese-style room
Japanese-style?
-A Japanese-style room
How to put it, the scent of tatami is good.
-Not bad, right?
In fact, check this out
This is a buried type furnace
Wow!
It's like a trap door
If this is it
-A feeling of the Showa era, right?
Nice!
Sitting next to the furnace with a girl
And then, what?
No, no, no. Shouldn't you be calling over the chief and HIRO instead?
Isn't that hell?
Why is it hell?
HIRO sweats from top to bottom all year long
With people like that putting their feet there
The chief would probably keel over
You can have a Yasuda Dai Circus meeting here, right?
No way
The chief will try and say something funny
Like he was pedaling his bike
He obviously doesn't know what is funny
He always says stuff like "it's been 20 years, let's take a bike trip" and other confusing things
I don't know what he's talking about
Sorry, it's my fault for bringing up the chief, I'm sorry
Then, in addition to the buried furnace and roof
There is one more thing to recommend about this
This part of the building is completely occupied by this place
So there is no next door neighbor
Just one place?
-Yes
Yes, a house that is suitable for entertainers
So how much is it?
About 340,000
340,000?
How is it worth so much?
280,000
Okay, lets see
Rent is 290,000
Almost
So close
10,000 difference
It feels like fate
So, what to do?
For this residence...
Enough...
Reserved!
Reserved
You've pretty much already said "this is the house", and yet there's still more
I don't think that was the tone he was trying to convey
That's what it meant
Isn't it more expensive than the first house?
Maybe a little expensive...
So you're not willing to live here, right?
But you always say something rash
-No, sorry
You can't live here
I do think it's good but,
You're going to run out of places to live!
The next one is the last one
Eh, the last one?
The next one is the last one.
-Didn't you say you've found a lot?
We barely saw any on the first day
Not that many!
So, the final residence in Kuro-chan's search for a new home is...
At last
Please enter
Excuse me
Ah, I see, I see
It's pretty good, right?
Yes, it is
Well, how can I put it?
How can I put it? It's a bit...
It feels like it's not the first time
Living room, dining room and kitchen
1LDK in Minato-ku, a 38 years old apartment
Doesn't it look a bit like your current house that'll be destroyed?
-Yes, it does
How to put it...
The size of the space is also similar, and the overall feeling is quite similar.
-Yes
It took a lot of effort to find this
I feel like I can live in it very comfortably
It's good, right?
-Yes, it is
The same as Kuro-chan's current house, a 4-story building without an elevator
And so, the rent
119,000 yen
It's below 120,000
-Eh?
And so, almost the same amount as his previous residence
Wow, what to do? This place is too good
Too good?
All the 7 residences we have seen
Think back over all of them again
Over the course of two days and viewing all kinds of houses, the one Kuro-chan chose as his new home is...
So Kuro-chan, which residence will you choose?
The residence I want to live in is...
Absolutely not!
Hurry up and choose, seriously
I know! Wait a minute!
I thought I would look at a few more
So Kuro-chan, which residence will you choose?
The residence I want to live in is...
The 290,000 residence
Is that so?
Yes!
The flat house
Yes, it's decided!
But you've been so concerned about rent
That place is twice as much as the place you live now
It is twice as much
What is the reason for this decision?
More rooms
Because there's no neighbors, there's no need to consider anyone else
This last place I was introduced to
Although it's similar to where I live now
It does feel nice
The rent is also low
So it does feel like a bit of a step up
But I also have the desire to live in a nicer place
We told you, right?
Eh?
From the very beginning
So after this, a formal residential lease agreement was signed
Finally, the moving day
The table should be...
The table should be set over here, right?
Yes, we provided new types of furniture suitable for the upgrade in house
Earned a lot out of it
Even the widely known bed
Was upgraded to a King Size Extra Large
That's good living
Because of the seawater or rain
When it was shipped back it was covered with sand
I was really disgusted
So he got a new one
So, after disposing of the furniture that received damage on the island, the move was complete
Right at this moment
It's going to get dirty soon, right?
The team has prepared a moving celebration for you
Moving celebration?
-Yes
What?
Please
Something to hang?
The gifts prepared by the program team for the new home are...
It's a camera
Camera? What for?
Why a camera? Why have a camera there?
To prepare for 24 hours 365 days of non-stop uninterrupted Kuro-chan life
For what? No need to...hey wait a minute
Are you really installing it? Wait a minute!
Due to disassembling and re-installing, hiding it would be to difficult
Sounds like he's talking about a hair transplant
And so, two cameras were installed in the living room and bedroom of this new home
Then,
Really? Is this happening?
Wait, so I don't have any room to escape?
Change my castle back. Get rid of them!
In the end, he chose the most spacious
Chose a house in Shinagawa Ward with a rent of 290,000 yen
Can't you just tell us the address?
We can't do that
And there are cameras
Not all rooms are equipped with it, right?
Of course
-Just the living room and bedroom
Even in the bedroom
I think it was installed
When Kuro-chan wants to do something, he has to go to another room
He'll have to do it in the buried furnace
This is worse than prison, right?
It's too messy, right?
A great thing has occurred
You should let the audience be able to watch it on their cell phones
If Kuro-chan agrees, it's okay, right?
Like that game SEAMAN, right?
Do you mean to go to raising?
Click the phone and a piece of bait will fall down
So how about it? Now
Now!
Want to see Kuro-chan?
There's a camera?
-Do you want to see it?
Let's see it
Of course you want to see!
Really?
Already a bit messy
It's a bit messy
Not at home
Isn't this for a pet?
What?
People who have pets usually install this kind of camera, right?
If you care about your pet
Could really give him stuff treats and stuff
So, let's take a look at the bedroom
Not there
He seems to be out now
Gone to work
-Work
A very precarious spot to place a box of paper, right on the edge
Right in the corner
Already jerked off a few times, right?
Incidentally, the places that Kuro-chan didn't choose
Apart rom the first residence
All of them are looking for occupants
All interested parties are welcome
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03
Eh?
Eh, what's this?
Wait wait wait wait
Eh, is this being filmed?
Eh, what's going on?
Eh, why? A live broadcast?
Wait a minute. What the hell? Hey, wait a minute
What's this? How are you doing this?
I've moved, yes