Edited by:
Not_BigM
Original subs by:
???
Please begin
This is my first time doing such a presentation
I'm a bit nervous....
Stop that!
I have a theory with me
The theory I bring to you this time is this....
The funny faces made by pretty girls are dull
I get that, I got the same thought as you
You get what I mean, right
Some amateur model post their funny face on their blog
and it's damn boring~~~
It is boring
Aren't their blog interesting?
None of them are interesting!
The boring blog is totally another different topic...
But they really are boring...
I see
For pretty girls, since they were small
They are more interested in how to look pretty
So there is no need for them to make actually funny faces
They're not interested in that, they don't do it
For others, the only way to get attention is to do funny faces
Therefore, the pretty girls won't be interesting at all
Wait, there must be some which are interesting
Absolutely not
It's like, I can't imagine she'd make such an ugly face given her cute look
Basically their funny face won't make people laugh
They get responses like "That's cute" or "Dare you to make yourself ugly"
Responses that make us feel like we are some fuckin weirdo
She's scary
We do funny faces only to make the atmosphere feel light
Your speech is full of bad intention...
Sorry, if I'm too over the top
If a pretty girl made funny faces that were better than mine...
That would be my hell
That would be a disgrace
Exactly!
That's understandable
Let's take Kakei as example, what do you think her funny faces would look like?
So Kakei's funny face in 3....2....1
That was quite funny, wasn't it?
That was a good one
Beyond expectation
Why did you purposely do a good one? It should have been a dull one
Just now, that one's level was quite high
I think I'll get hated because of this
Alright, how about Takahashi's funny face in 3...2...1....
That's a good one
There it is..the ugly one
That was like the mask my father use to wear...
Momotaro Zamurai
This is what we call a funny face!
You can ditch your announcer job now
No way, I'll remain as an announcer
Up next, we will find out if the funny faces made by pretty girls are really dull?
Wednesday Downtown
Now let's test the theory "The Funny faces made by pretty girls are dull"
We tested this at the Omotesando street, a street where many pretty girls appear
Excuse me, we are from TBS
First, we have this pretty girl
The beautiful 24 year old office lady
Do many people around you call you pretty?
No, they don't
Don't lie
But you must be quite popular?
No, not at all
She is humble, but when we asked her to show us her ICON on LINE....
We found the sign of a pretty girl,
a good looking photo taken by her as her ICON
For those who are not popular, or think that they are not good looking, their ICON would normally be...
Dogs
Cats
Childhood photo
This is a prejudice....
Can you give us your best shot at making a funny face?
Funny face?
So, are the funny faces made by a pretty girl really dull?
Now that's a dull one
This one is really dull
It looks dull from any point of view
The lowest level of funny face
Next up is this girl
She's cute
A 20 year old undergraduate who is working part time at a cafe
Do people around you call you pretty?
No, they don't
Stop lying to us!
I wish they called me that
However, her LINE ICON is still....
No doubt, the sign of pretty girl, her own portrait
You need confidence
to use that
If someone is really not that good-looking
They're ICON should be them on top of a world heritage
Enough with this explanation
Can you give us your best shot at making a funny face?
Seriously!?
And her funny face is....
Her funny face was so dull and it makes people feel like asking "Do you know what they mean by funny face?"
Next is this girl
A pretty18 year old undergraduate
People around you call you pretty, right?
Erm...I've no idea...
Does anyone say you looks like a celebrity?
Well... Hashimoto Kanna
It's not important whether you look like her or not...
And the old man that slowly passes behind her is also not important
Her LINE ICON is this...
A photo that brings up her appearance up by using her friends
Her funny face is...
Again, a dull one...
Next is this girl
A pretty girl that looks like Haruna Kojima from AKB48
Instead of funny, this one looks more adorable
We continued the test and found all the funny faces by pretty girls are dull
No one is interesting
Next is this pretty girl
A 24 year old undergraduate who uses a posed look for her LINE ICON
Finally, an acceptable funny face
Quite a surprise for us to get an unexpected funny face
And then this 24 year old pretty girl
Seems like there are some pretty girls that can do a moderately funny face
But as a whole, the funny faces by pretty girls are mostly dull
What about this talent who seems quite good at doing funny face?
Sorry to disturb
It's Wednesday Downtown
What..what...what??
A talent that's active in variety show, Nana Suzuki, who can be considered as pretty
This may be a bit sudden
Please give us a funny face in 3...2...1...
Now!? No way. Wait...what's this about?
She didn't do it immediately
This is sudden
Wait a sec, I need a certain angle
An angle?
To make a funny face
You need to take the shot from a low angle, is that okay?
She concerns about the quality of her funny face more than the making of funny face
That's what we call a pro
Please shoot it properly
This is a bit hard for video
Manager, please check for me too
3...2...1...
She's a fool
She indeed is a good variety show talent
What did she mean by
"manager, please
check for me too?"
She had shown us the pro-like funny face
Did you shoot it properly?
Yes we did
Really?
Then, that's fine
Next we have her...
Good morning
It's Wednesday Downtown
What?
Kikuchi Ami
This time were doing something on funny faces, do you mind?
What do you mean by that?
Please make a funny face for us
A funny face? Now?
Are you kidding?
Let's do this
Now?
3....2....1....
I can't....wait, I can't make it
Can you take it from this position?
From below
As expected
How is this?
It's a bit different, right?
Can you show me the screen?
This is just cute...what should I do?
What is she talking about?
It just look cute...what should I do?
That's not cute at all!
She tried not to leave any cuteness
Just like Nana, she looked at the quality of a funny face, instead of doing it in a cute way
She can also be considered as a pro
So, how about this person?
The one who represented Japan for Miss International Beauty Pageant 2014
The top class beauty in Japan
She represented Japan?
Hongo Lila
Indeed that was a hot topic back then
That's a surprise
We want you to make a funny face for us
Funny face...is that fine?
Funny face?
Although she's a pretty, there's potential within her
Could she give us a nice one?
Let's find out
I'll try to make it
You will?
She's has the strength
of a Yokozuna
3....2....1....
Now we know that basically, the funny faces made by pretty girls are dull