Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let's get on with our first presenter please
Who is it, is there anyone there?
It's FUJIWARA!
Hello everyone, we're FUJIWARA
I know you, i've seen you guys on TV
It's... Genki Haranishi!
Correct
-And poor thing Fujimoto
Who are you saying is a poor little thing? In what way am I a poor little thing!?
Matsumoto is crying
-Why are you crying?
Why is Matsumoto crying?
I can't believe they forced themselves to be on a variety show
Whose forcing themselves!?
So you are forcing yourself to come
-I didn't force myself
I'll start then
-Let's start. Let's start
This time is a long-waited Kuro-chan project
Really looking forward to
-I've been waiting for a long time
When Kuro-chan gets drunk and falls asleep he just doesn't get up, right?
Yes, it has happened before
So this time, we took the drunken Kuro-chan to a great place
What more is there to do?
I thought last time's flower field would be the end of it
※OA：20191030
What does everyone think the place is?
Inside a grave
The staff here would do such a thing, right?
Put him in a coffin
-Then let's state the answer, ready?
The project we brought this time, is this:
Kuro-chan: Living on a deserted island with a single room
Single room?
Please allow me to explain
First a room the same size as Kuro-chan's was built on a deserted island
Then, all of his stuff was moved to it
Everything
-Yes
Then the drunken Kuro-chan is moved to the room on the island
When he wakes up and walks out of his room, he realizes his home is now a uninhabited island
I see
Can this be done?
What do you think, Degawa?
No no no, how would you react
Thinking you'd left civilization
Not knowing what to do, it'd be really painful
You couldn't speak, you'd be speechless?
-It's difficult to understand the situation
Yes
Because the rooms are exactly the same
But since he's Kuro-chan, the first thing he'll do is probably look for Mother Kuro
First make contact
Kuro-chan: Living on a deserted island with a single room
And so...
"The Spirit of Kansai Gyaru"
This time we invited Kuro-chan, who has performed PCR testing, to participate in a fake program on SUN TV
※Kuro-chan was diagnosed with covid on July 18 and was discharged on July 29
We called him to a place in Kansai
Let's get hyped together!
And took advantage of this time to remove all the things from his room
The stains on the bed are awful
Take away all the garbage too?
Then we loaded all the luggage onto the truck and drove west
The staff really work hard
The destination is an uninhabited island floating on the Seto Inland Sea
Its name - Black Island (Kuroshima)
The name is a perfect match
Half a day was spent making the island hut
And all the luggage was moved from Tokyo
Thus, a complete reproduction of Kuro-chan's room
This camera view
-Exactly the same!
So, on an uninhabited island 500km away from Tokyo
The moving of Kuron-chan's room is complete
But tenant knew nothing about the matter...
Cheers~
I'm really worried about after this~
At this time, he was unaware that something worth worrying about was actually in progress
He's really aiding the preparation
As usual, Kuro-chan is instructed to drink one glass after another to begin with
With a guy in the park...
Wait!
Ah~ I really can't
Really can't do this kind of thing!
Wait, wait
Can't stop drinking?
He's in a really good mood
After listening to the Kansai gyaru girls' unadulterated conversation, he gets more excited and drinks even faster
Put down your hand holding the glass
It's everyone's fault that I have to keep drinking
Oops I said~
Everyone is so cute~ really!
Excuse me, staff members
SUN TV is the best!
His rolling drunken eyes
And then...
Terrible
Sexual harassment occurs through a barrier
Two hours after shooting began...
Uh
Kansai
The spirit of Kansai's gyarus...
SUNTV uh ah…
As usual, he went to sleep after getting drunk
This is still work, right?
Finally...
As expected
Everything is now ready
After all, there is a lot to drink
Usually a show would never hire him again
Regarding Kuro-chan
We all know that he is not easily woken up once he drinks
As this time he is on a bot, he wears noise-canceling headphones
And is then taken to the port in a drowsy state
After all, it's not far from Kansai
And so, he departs with the rising sun
The departure location is quite
At least put him in a better place
And arrives on an uninhabited island while still asleep
And then...
Gently chucked onto the bed
He is smoothly returned to his own bed
Faced with "waking up and finding out that he's now on an uninhabited island"
He undergoes an experience that is possibly the first of its kind in history
What will Kuro-chan do?
The room is decorated exactly the same
He sleeps for two hours in his Kuro Room on Kuro Island
Finally...
You'd surely panic
He has arisen
No doubts about the room
Probably thought someone sent him home
But after all, this is SUN TV
I've forgotten about how they do things in Kansai
But in this case, Kuro-chan did not feel any sense of dissonance
It looks like he forgot
Amazing! Tweeted instantly
First, the usual good morning tweet
Hmm...
Eh?
At this point, Kuro-chan finally realizes something
He was recording a program in Kansai, but doesn't know how he got home
Are doubts setting in?
But...
Hmm...
Ah...uurrr...
It's the hangover that's more taxing
Five minutes after waking up
In order to go to the toilet, Kuro-chan finally gets up and walks to the door
Just how will he react?
Not much of a reaction
You'd surely react like this
Opening the door to what should be the kitchen
Such a long silence!
There's now a sea in front of you
Faced with this shocking sight...
Eh？
Can't even stand up
He can't help but have weak legs
Finally said something
Eh!?
Hey, where's this, hey? Wha...
Eh? Eh?
Wait, what's going on here?
What's happening?
Where!?
WHERE!?
Wait a second. What's going on? What's going on?
This is my home, right?
Eh? What the hell is going on!?
Wait, I really don't understand what is happening
Why is my house here? Why is it here? It's not even my home, right?
But this is my home
What the hell?
After this, he continued to wander between the beach and the hut for ten minutes
This is Wednesday Downtown, right? It must be Wednesday Downtown!
How else could this happen? It's not in a dream
It isn't a dream, right?
Only this show, right?
You're pretty much only on this show, right?
Kuro-chan gradually comes to understand the situation
Hey! There's staff here, right? Staff!?
I said come out! I don't understand what's going on!
Although Kuro-chan shouts at the staff with all his might...
What's that? A drone?
What the hell? A drones flying over
This time, no staff will appear
Instead, with the use of this drone,
And the numerous cameras set up on the island
Kuro-chan's life on this uninhabited island will be recorded
And so,
Eh!? What is it? It looks like something is dangling
Can I take it off?
What is this?
Kuro-chan's room has been transported to an uninhabited island
There is a camera in the box next to the room, please film yourself
What!? This is an uninhabited island!?
What the hell's up with this teleportation!?
It also says "Please film yourself".
So how do I get back?
Kuro-chan seems to have many questions
What the hell is this place?
What the heck are you doing?
First things first: head protection measures
And defecation
Do I really have to film?
And what is this thing, it goes on the head?
I don't need to. I'm not doing it
Despite his protests, he nonetheless beings to film
No, this...how the hell did it happen?
It's really the same as my house, really
It is my usual home
This is the jungle, right?
The window opens to a jungle
Although it's my home
Once you open the door... the sea is there!
Sea?
Isn't this like a portal?
This is an uninhabited island, right? Can I even leave?
Can I just escape?
Actually, I just saw another house
So if I want to escape, they can probably tell me how, right?
In fact, this uninhabited island is about 1km to the next manned island
Is it possible?
Could swim there with a little effort
And so...
Ta da~
I'll use this to escape
I'll use the breaststroke to swim to the land
He's using his own personal items
-Yes
I'm off then, let's go!
The destination is over there
So, Kuro-chan's uninhabited island escape challenge begins
But this is the Seto Inland Sea after all
The wind and waves shouldn't be too strong
But...
Oh
Huh? The waves are a little big. Eh?
Ah...it's not the same as a swimming pool
The wind is too strong, and the waves are too strong, why!?
How can it be the same as a swimming pool
After 20 minutes of continuous drifting on the tide
Rubber ring... the rubber ring is floating away
A great pity, his escape ends in failure
Just used up his energy
Impossible, how the hell can I swim there
Wasn't it your idea?
What the hell? Seriously
Are you mocking me?
It's mocking you
What's that?
The mocked Kuro-chan seems to have found something
What is this?
A bowling ball  on top of a cushion
What is this? The hole...
There are four holes?
This ball is a hint, right?
After all, it's too suspicious
Ah
What does east-west, north-south mean?
This hole is...
East, West, North, South... is that instructions to go to a certain place?
Or am I supposed to stuff something into this hole?
There's a piece of paper next to it
Open it quickly and read it
It's a scroll, isn't this a bit too depressing?
In fact, this scroll shows...
This is a map, right?
The four-hole bowling ball was found here
Does that mean there are hints in all these starred places?
If I collect these, is there a way to escape?
I'm home
There are four holes
And it was on this cushion, right?
Eh, no way!
It can't be that fantastical, surely!
Dragon balls?
One, two, three... one, two, three, four
※One, two, three, four: In the Japanese comic book Dragon Ball, the seven Dragon Balls are pronounced 1234567 in Chinese.
Is this the four star ball?
Hey, wait a minute, I remember this from dragon ball
There are seven of them, right?
It's a lie! It's a lie!
A total of seven markers
Is it the same as the seven dragon balls?
Will the dragon appear?
Really? Will the dragon grant my wish?
That's right, if he collects all seven bowling balls on the island, his wish will come true
It is an adventure-based escape project
The adventure is about to begin. It's about to begin!
Let's go and embark on an adventure!
I will definitely collect all of them!
And so, Kuro-chan's incredible adventure is about to begin
What does everyone think?
When Kuro-chan first opened his door there was no response
Yes, indeed, indeed
You're exactly right
I've been screwed with similarly in the past, when I came home and opened the door,
All of my stuff was gone, and the place was turned into Hawaii
Turned into Hawaii?
-The reverse
The reverse version, the room was filled with real sand
There was a big sun umbrella and the ground was full of crabs roaming around
So I know that, in this type of situation, it's really impossible to react straight away
I was completely speechless. I couldn't even say something like "It's Hawaii!"
It is impossible to say anything
You freeze up
You freeze up, so Kuro-chan's reaction is very real
First of all, this
Here
It's right next to the house, so it should be right around here
And so, Kuro-chan begins searching the beach area next to the hut
On the map it seems to be a bit more ahead
Probably around here?
This vicinity?
Despite searching, he's unable to find anything resembling a bowling ball
This is the place drawn on the map, but I can't seem to find anything
So, he abandons the beach area for now
This is where I'm going now, this rocky area
These are gloves I didn't hesitate to buy at a Visual Kei shop
As long as you wear these gloves, your strength will increase many times
Wish~
※Wish" and "ZKY" are the comedian DIAGO's jokes
ZKY
Where is it? Is it near there?
I'll climb up and see
What exactly does ZKY mean?
We'll get the ball and dream together
Wish Wish Wish~
Facing the craggy cliffs, Kuro-chan performs with surprising ease
Yes, in fact...
Climbing practice, lemme do it! Facing this wall, I've gotta get over it!
This is definitely a lie
Kuro-chan has faced this wall head on with sincerity, now i'm a professional rock climber!
Definitely just for show
It's a lie
There's no wall that I can't climb!
Thanks to an interest in rock climbing, Kuro-chan has faced the difficulties of rock climbing on a regular basis
So, the flat rock face is smoothly climbed
That's scary!
After all, there is no safety harness either
Nothing here?
After reaching an altitude of 15 meters...
Ah...
Dangerous!
It's too dangerous. The rock is so fragile
The rocks are loose here
That was close, this rock is soft
Give me a minute, the rocks are falling
Kuro-chan enters an area of unstable rock, and then...
Damn it!
Hey, it's scary. Is it all this type of stone up here?
One wrong step and he risks falling, but...
Kuro-chan is surmounting the difficulties in front of him!
Told you it was a lie
Use all your strength to knock down the wall!!! Justice is power!!!!
After all, there's safety measures in a place like that
Ah, almost there! Made it! Made it!
And so, Kuro-chan successfully conquers the rock wall with all his might
Wow, here comes the ramp
Finally...
Ah, I've found it
I found it. It's that one, right?
The color is orange. I found it!
I've found the ball!
After a lot of effort, he's finally found the ball
Found it, found it, found it!
But from here is the most difficult part
The rocks will crack here, staff!
Staff!
Staff! Save me!
No one's coming to save you
Staff, you're watching, right?
Staff, i'm serious
Staff~
Unfortunately, Kano Eiko's soulful cry cannot reach the staff
They've also got matching gloves
The result: he must rely on his own strength...
I'm there!
Ah, it's over there
Scary
-Super scary
Got it!
I got the ball!!!
This is so scary!
,I have now found two, which means...
,I need to find five more, right?
,Correct
,The sun has begun to set already
,I guess I can't finish it today
,How many days will this take?
,Eh... I'm scared!
,Do I have to get food myself?
,Yeah, really
,Yes, usually this kind of location shoot on an uninhabited island involves...
,Getting food from nature
,Either collecting fruit from the trees
,Or going fishing to get food
,However, as this time, an entire room was transported over
,Will there be some in the room?
,Ah, i've got water
,Cup noodles
,Ah so many treasures, there are many
,But there's no gas!
,Beer, I also have beer
,For once, messy bad habits actually turn out to be beneficial
,And whiskey
,This was a gift
,Small quantities of food has been gathered
,And so, in the end
,So much!
,It's great to have a whole room transported over
,This level of plentiful bounty
,Is rarely seen on a desert island
,This guy loves Gummi
,Also all grape flavor, why?
,I'm ready to eat then
,Dinner preparation
,I worked way too hard today
,So,
,Surrounding collected branches with stones
,I can't believe it!
,Luckily there are
,The smoke is so big, my eyes hurt
,He boils water in a pot
,The fun of the uninhabited island has been halved
,Too well-equipped
,Ah, how there are bugs, ah~
,Too normal, should go and catch some fish or something
,I'm having a beer!
,He's also having a beer
I'm exhausted
,Cheers~
,Cup noodles plus 2 cans of beer
,A fulfilling solo-camp
,This doesn't feel like a deserted island
,Next
Eh?
,Eh, there is actually signal here?
,Even though it's an uninhabited island?
,Kurojima
,A Kuro island...
,You really found one...
,And so
Hello?
,Mother? It's me
,He reports to his mother what has transpired
,So basically...
,The one who hates me most is Kuro-chan's mother
,※Kuro-chan's parents said in the show (O.A. 210113 39:03) that they hate Fujimoto
,My whole room was transported to an uninhabited island
,You're lying aren't you
,I'm not lying
,A careful explanation of an impossible situation
,It must be Wednesday
,He still hasn't been told it's a tv show
,So weird, so funny!
,It's not funny, seriously!
,You can do it, Akihito!
,You must be drunk again
,What the hell!
,It seems like the mother, like the son,
,Is also the type that doesn't stop drinking until becoming unconscious
,This is a good trait to inherit
,Nothing to do today so i'm going to sleep, sleep
,And so
,An early beddtime at 9:30 p.m
,The second day on an uninhabited island
,Morni-morning puri puri princess---♪
,Oh that's a good one!
,It's better to target these three today, right?
,Today, Kuro-chan's goal is...
,The three balls along the beach as shown in the picture
So,
,So scary!
,Where's the ball?
,This is an adventure, right?
,Embarking on a path without a road
,By the way,
,On this island, except for the hut area
,There are no flat places
,If it was anyone other than me they'd be hurt!
,Between the craggy cliffs that still fill one's vision
,Kuro-chan has to keep going up and down the face
,I've been walking for an hour
,It's been two and a half hours since he left
Ah
,Eh, is it not here?
,This sea cove
,This must be it
,Arrived at last
,The location of this ball appears to be somewhere in this cove
,Ah, that's the one, right?
Ball!
,That orange thing must be the one
,You wouldn't wanna go down
So
,Perfect
,If you put this tube above the surface you can breathe
,Like a member of a criminal organization carrying out the orders of a high-level boss
,He becomes the silent twin killers: Kuro-chan
,Actually, this tube that Kuro-chan is carrying
,A CPAP, a device that assists breathing during sleep
,He uses this instead of diving snorkel to dive into the water
,What is the result?
,Would this work?
,No point at all, right?
,It's gone in!
,To be expected
,What's wrong?
,How did all the water get into my nose?
,Of course it would
,CPAP Operations: Ended
,By the way,
,Although the position of the ball is not very deep
,A bowling ball submerged in water
,Is very hard to retrieve
,Looks too heavy
,So slippery
,As it has a fair amount of weight
,It will immediately slip if not grasped firmly
,You can do it!
,There are only two holes
,How can this be caught?
,You guys are doing it on purpose, right?
,Get it! Get it!
,Ah, it really slips out
,So close!
Seriously!
,So, he keeps on trying
,For 30 minutes
,At last...
,Got it! Got it!
,Finally got the third ball
,I thought I was going to die
,Immediately afterwards,
,Kuro-chan continues along a path without a road
,I'll bring the watch with me
,Eh? This must be it!
,Ah there it is!
,He arrives at the cave where the fourth ball resides
,After hurrying into the hole
,It stinks...
,I didn't brush my teeth
,But it's not my teeth
,Your teeth must smell pretty bad too
,Actually, this cave
,Because of the alternating high tide and low tide is always shady and dry
,It stinks!
,It emits a strong stench like food waste
,This island is awesome, how did this form in such a way
,Kuro island
,The island is really as the name suggests
,He is forced to bear the stench
,And finally retrieves the fourth ball
,There is only one goal left for the rest of the day
,This one is going to be a problem
,Once the sun goes down, nothing can be done
,The time now is 4:00 p.m.
,You can do it!
,If the sun goes down
,Being unable to return to the hut is a possibility
,So he must hurry
,So fast!
,You can do it!
,Finally
,Eh?
,Wait, wait, wait, wait!
,Isn't this an island itself?
,Finally
,The island off-land where the fifth ball sleeps appears
,It's too deep, isn't it?
,This is not the same level as the place where the ball was sunk just now
,The sea must be crossed
,To reach the island where the fifth ball sleeps
,Specifically, 50 meters of the rapid tide must be traversed
,It is impossible to come back like this
,Just go for it, right?
,Not even one staff member came out
So,
,So deep, so deep
,The life preserver was lost on the first day, right?
,Although his physical strength is heavily depleted
,Kuro-chan is determined to jump into the depths of the water
,Do not underestimate the breaststroke!
Damn
,While filling a stomach with water
,He swims against the tide for 15 minutes
,Awesome
,At last
,He arrives at the island
,I'm here!
,I...
,I am...
,Kurokawa Akito!
,That's right!
,Climbing onto the island! I'm on the island!
,Scared me to death, scared me to death, scared me to death!!!
,Swimming over
,Swam over... although I was afraid I still persevered
,Really scared me, too scared
,I was really scared to death
,How many times are you going to say it
,If I was in danger on the way would you save me?
,Someone would surely have to save me
,You'll come to my rescue, right?
,Mummy
,I'm really tried
,Ok we get it, get on with it
,I'm 44 years old in the summer, and i'm really tried
,Akihito will try to keep going, Mummy!
,Desperately trying to show his effort
,I'm not feeling a sense of danger at all ah
,While continuing to stumble around
,The sunset is drawing near
,No, where is it?
,If the sun sets it'd be super scary
,I've come this far, I have to find it
,The search lasts for 30 minutes
,Ah, there it is!
,Placing it somewhere like this is bullying
,Found it!
,And so
,Today, Kuro-chan retrieved a total of three balls
,But...
,Must get back before sunset
,It is the journey home that is the hardest
,Submerged in the water
,So heavy
,This is the same as the death penalty, holding such a heavy thing
,That's the second lot
,There's one more but I couldn't carry it
,It takes two trips to finally get all 3 balls back
,So tired...
,Later,
,I'm starting!
,Like a manual laborer he wolfs down his instant noodles
,And today also sleeps like a corpse
,It is the morning of the third day of life on an uninhabited island
,Morning, morning, holiday land~ Aloha Oye - - - - - -♪
,After posting a tweet implying he is on an island
,I need to have a wash
,The 3-days without a bath Kuro-chan
,Decides to go to the sea for a little dip
,Drones don't come over, okay?
,That's enough, right?
,I'm going to wash now
,No need to film
,After three days
,This man has transformed into the lord of the island
,Ah so cold!
,Is that little pot necessary?
,Small pots are still necessary, right?
,Wouldn't jumping into the water be enough?
,Because there is no body wash
,He decides to use shaving cream instead
,Ah, this sizzling sensation feels really good
,With shaving in mind
,He then gives his head hair a quick once over
,Don't shoot this
,Terrifying
,That's awful
,Hurry up and go, will you?
,Get lost!
,You don't see this kind of image on variety shows much, right?
,Demanding someone gets off his island
,As if he were completely indigenous
,Kuro-chan's Kuro Island
,It's kind of awesome
,It's your own island!
,It's so refreshing after washing
,Breakfast, hat about breakfast?
,It's already the third day
,The food is almost gone
,Shall I just eat a can?
,Ah...
,I have to go back today
,So i'll find the two remaining balls
,I'll eat the seafood flavored noodles too
,I can't stand it, I want to eat
,Is it okay?
,Think about it Kuro-chan
,If I keep dawdling like this I'll waste a few more days
,Seafood goes best with the sea
And so,
,The end of the line
,So good
,The last pack of instant noodles is finished
,Along with canned sardines
,I'm full
,Towards the sleeping 6th ball
,He heads into the forest
,I'm off
,Ah it's a bit wet
,Ah, it's raining
,It's raining a lot!
,No more motivation!
,Ah, an umbrella
,Great, thank god for the umbrella
,A rare view on an uninhabited island:
,A scene of someone walking into the forest with an umbrella
,Wait a minute, is this okay?
,This rain is a bit scary
,Is a typhoon coming?
,In fact, this day...
,Had the biggest rainfall of the year
,What a sudden downpour this is
,It's really coming down hard
,Braving the heavy rain
,In a forest the size of Tokyo Dome 2
,He searches for an hour
,Ah, there's an orange thing!
,Ah, it's a ball. There's a ball
,A ball is found in a 5m high tree
,Put in such a nasty place
,I found it, I found it
,This must be a bit scary
,Do I have no choice but to climb?
,Making preparations
,He hatches a plan to climb up halfway and poke the ball
,The trunk of the tree is wet
,It's okay, he's an experienced rock climber
,Experienced my ass!
-He's really experienced!
,But...
,The rain-soaked tree trunk proves very slippery
,So it's tough to climb up
,Nonetheless, he struggles for 15 minutes
,Damn
,He hasn't moved at all
,Hey wait a minute!
,Although he was able to climb up
,He unfortunately loses the critical stick
,Ah the stick!
,But there's no turning back
,Indeed
,So, he chooses to climb up a bit more
,Pretty smart
,You'd have to!
,That's enough
To reach
,Just push it
One, two, ah
,Success!
,Be careful!
,Dangerous, dangerous
,I'm like wax from a candle
And so,
,Mummy!
,I will succeed as long as I don't give up
,Okay, enough
,You used to say, Mum...
,Again, as per usual
,He talks to his mum for a while
,I really hate having to listen to this
,Finally,
,The one on the beach
,Ah he's angry
,Where exactly is it?
,I kind of want to try it too
,Try what
,What exactly?
,Which part?
,This kind of uninhabited island shoot
-Hey, are you serious?
,I'd like to try it out for a little while
,Then let's get started!
,Soon when you leave you may find your home isn't there anymore
,What remains is...
,The one he's been looking for since day one
,But has yet to locate
,The ball on the beach
,But I've been searching for it for the past three days
,Where is it?
,Why can't I find it?
,Why isn't it here?
,Eh, maybe it's smaller than the rest?
,Could it be translucent
,I can't see it. Is it camouflaged?
,No way!
,Why is the last ball so weird?
,The staff of this program really loves to make things difficult
,Like making stuff invisible
,Could it be in the sky...
,If not in the sky...
,Is it buried in the ground?
,Correct answer
,Buried?
,That's it, that's it, isn't it!
,These people would definitely do this sort of thing
,And so,
,Guessing correctly, Kuro-chan begins digging
,Hellish
,Where is it?
,With a tone like "Where is Panama?"
,He keeps digging
,Where is it? Where is it?
,Kotouge's line!
,Where is Panama?
,You actually know this
Kotouge's line!
,"Where's Panama?", right?
,Where the hell is it?
,Do I have to dig all of this?
,While complaining
,He digs for a whole hour
,Ah, i'm at my limit
,The depth is not known either
,My back hurts
,At last
,Kuro-chan is out of strength
,This kid really likes that small pot
,I can't use my hands anymore
,No more grip strength
,Kuro-chan begins to concede defeat
,However,
,But I still have to dig!
,If I give up here, it's all a waste
,Don't admit defeat!
,Try harder!
,I've gotta make it to the end!
,Mum and Dad always told me
,Never to give up half way
,After two years as a repeater, I ended up in a junior college
,Dad's clothes are very impressive
,And withdrew again from school without permission
,That exaggerated Takeshi Kitano shirt
,I never lived up to anyone's expectations
,But Mum and Dad
,No matter what happened
,They never gave up on me
,I have always been a willful and careless person
,He's like a criminal
,How can I repay my parents?
,Stop asking for money every month
,I have to reassure them and put them at ease
,I am now going to start changing now
,If I don't change now, there's no point
,I think this is my last chance
,With gratitude to his parents
,Kuro-chan continues to dig the sand with his family's pot
,At last
,Ahhhhhhhhhh
,There it is. There it is
,It's there!
,It's really buried here
,Mum and Dad, I tried hard!
,I found it! I found it!
,I've been looking for such a long time
,I really suffered
,And so, he has finally collected all 7 balls
,He's talking to the ball
,The last ball
,All 7 are together
,The only thing left to do next is to grant my wish
,I need to escape from here
,With this, will Kuro-chan finally be able to escape Kuro island?
,What fate awaits him?
,What does everyone think?
,A cliffhanger ending is it?
,How do you all feel about this
,Really feel a sense of majesty about it
,But not at all moved by it
,Why not? Not even just a little bit?
,Really not moved in the slightest
,Maybe just a tiny bit?
,What aspect is supposed to move me?
,Where is the emotion?
,You're doing "Where is Panama?" again
,After watching it, I think
,Make sure you have a small pot
,You can do anything!
,It's useless isn't it?
,You can wash your body and dig in the sand or something.
-No use at all
,It can also cook instant noodles
,There is no need for it. Surely using your hands to dig is faster
,Everyone is thinking this is coming to an end, right?
,Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03
,But it's still early
-Is this just the beginning?
,What else is there to drag on for so long
,There's more content to come
,So we have to wait until next week?
,Yes, it will be continued next week
,Next week is also a special hour of Kuro-chan
What's this?
,What awaits Kuro-chan
Eh, is it not over yet?
,This unbelievable journey of adventure
,Don't miss it!