This is Suiyōbi no Downtown.
Welcome everyone
Hamada Masatoshi
(Downtown)
Fujimoto Miki
Gotō Terumoto
(Football Hour)
Matsumoto Hitoshi
(Downtown)
Shibuya Nagisa
So let's begin.
Our first presenter...
will enter now. Come in!
(Matsumoto) Are they coming?
Yes, it's Koyabu Kazutoyo
Presenter:
Koyabu Kazutoyo
So then everyone
The Yoshimoto giant ('kyojin')
No,
there's already an actual Kyojin
All Kyojin
It's not me. Well, then...
I'm annoyed
You're back on track
Today we have the annual favorite
What I've brought with me today is this:
The 7th Annual Lyric Changing Tournament
Yes, it's the one that's
always extremely funny every time
And once again the jury is changing
The jury for the 7th tournament is University of Tokyo students
Elementary
school students
Gyaru
High school
boys
girls
Middle
school students
Rookie
comedians
Uni. of Tokyo
students
Ah, I see
Tokyo University. It's going to be hard
It's a different angle
They're the one who never messed
around in class
That's biased
They don't know the difference between
what's funny and what's not
Biased
Don't you think?
#
Elementary school students
Middle school students
High school girls
High school boys
Gyaru
Rookie comedians
The annual favorite.
This year we're doing the 7th...
Lyric Changing Tournament
Tonight we've once again gathered 8 groups of singing comedians
1st Tournament Winners
Doburock
Staff) The jury this time is current Tokyo Uni students
Well, here we are
Tokyo University Students? They're mostly virgins, right?
That's rude
Koga Ken
I've been doing funny songs for a long time
I have to try to win in one shot here
My material's in a bit of a quiz style. Something you need to think about
So I might just have a chance this time
Razor Ramon RG
Once again I've made the lyrics about a heavyweight
Yuriyan Retriever
Well they're studious people so
I think it'd be better to make the song more intellectual
Yasei Bakudan Cookie!
I think I can come up with ideas you won't find in the brain of Tokyo University student
I think I'll go with just a little science and math
Iron Head
There's a contest in Kansai called "The King of the Song Contest"
We've been in it 4 times at most
So we were probably invited because of that. We're very confident
4th & 6th Tournament Winner
Hollywood Zakoshishō
Hello
Air! Shooo!
3rd victory
Doburock
Hollywood
Zakoshishō
Iron Head
Koga Ken
Razor
Ramon RG
Yasei Bakudan
Cookie!
Yuriyan
Retriever
In all, 8 groups entered.
From the first round to final,
they will switch lyrics for the 3 assigned songs.
This time, the decision will be made by
51 students currently enrolled at Tokyo University
Who on earth will match with the students' taste and be victorious?
Also...
Theory: The make-your-grandkid-laugh
challenge where the grandkid doesn't laugh at all. A painful reverse prank
And then...
Theory: Even 'The Touch' do some solo gigs
★Subbed by fmck fansubs★
reddit.com/u/fmckfansubs
patreon.com/fmck
Doburock
Hollywood
Zakoshishō
Iron Head
Koga Ken
Razor
Ramon RG
Yasei Bakudan
Cookie!
Yuriyan
Retriever
The Lyric Changing Tournament.
The first assigned song is...
Usseewa ("Annoying")
♫ Huh? You're annoying, annoying
It became a hot topic
with its aggressive lyrics
A big hit from the first half of 2021
Ado's "Usseewa"
How will the 8 groups change this song?
♫ There's no problem
Doburock    VS.    Koga Ken
Round 1
Match 1
First, Doburock
(Eguchi) Music, start!
I'm going to show my dick to my partner
♫ Huh?
It's small, small, small!
If it were a battery it'd be AA-sized
No! It's big, big, big
When it matters, it's D-sized
Well it's true that the size may be AA but
It's super powerful and long-lasting
In terms of type, it's alkaline, not manganese!
Doburock    VS.    Koga Ken
Round 1
Match 1
Up against Doburock, it's Koga Ken
What's right is
What's that?
♫ Huh?
Annoying, annoying
More than you thought,
Don't hold back,
You don't understand
Annoying, annoying
Judgement
With both songs finished, it's time for...
The 51 Tokyo Uni students were asked to vote for the funnier song, with the song receiving most votes winning
Let's see how the Tokyo Uni students judged this battle
Round 1, match 1
Here's the result:
Unai Risa
(TBS Announcer)
Doburock
Koga Ken
Doburock-san get 44 votes
and Koga Ken gets 7 votes
Advancing to the semi-final is Doburock-san
So few...
Thank you very much
As we thought...
You're Tokyo Uni students so batteries
They're smart
I think it was a good idea to
include elements of physics and engineering
2nd-year student
Human Sciences III
Q. What did you find
funny about Doburock?
Well, it was...
Using AA batteries as a metaphor in a dirty joke
It was like the slang my friends use
It was kind of silly, and it made me laugh
All our hard work paid off
Because the truth is, you know, it's not AA-sized
That's not the point
Doburock
Hollywood
Zakoshishō
Iron Head
Koga Ken
Razor
Ramon RG
Yasei Bakudan
Cookie!
Yuriyan
Retriever
Lyric Changing Tournament
Next...
Razor Ramon RG    VS.
Round 1
Match 2
First up, Razor Ramon RG
There's one thing Beat Takashi's been doing lately
And I'd like to sing about it.
Music, start!
What's Beat Takeshi has been doing lately? I'll tell you now
His belt's high, high, high
It's higher than you thought
High, high, high
It's probably near his nipples
If you want to make your legs look longer
Put the belt high, high, high
It'll keep your balls stable. There's no problem
Right?
That wig should be a bit better
The wig's all unkempt
Razor Ramon RG    VS.
Round 1
Match 2
Up against RG is SAKURAI
Paper
Paper Rock
Paper Rock Paper
Paper Rock Paper Rock
♫ Huh?
My opponent, opponent, opponent
When he uses scissors, it's 2 wins, 2 losses
When he uses paper, it's 2 draws, 2 losses
Ah... Thumb, middle finger, ring finger, little finger
Are the fingers you don't use when twirling around a dragonfly's eyes
TL note: Apparently a way to catch dragonflies is to make them dizzy by spinning your finger around their eyes
Thanks
Who will the winner be?
Razor Ramon RG
RG-san got 40 votes
And SAKURAI-san got 11 votes
Advancing to the semi-finals is RG-san
Doburock
Hollywood
Zakoshishō
Iron Head
Koga Ken
Razor
Ramon RG
Yasei Bakudan
Cookie!
Yuriyan
Retriever
Next in the
Lyric Changing Tournament...
Round 1
Match 3
Yuriyan Retriever    VS.    Yasei Bakudan Cookie!
First up, it's Yuriyan Retriever
Music, start!
I cut my nails, cut my hair, cut ties with you
Cut the ties, but don't cut the dollars!
♫ Huh?
Annoying, annoying, annoying. You really are
You're so annoying
You're the annoying one! What are you on about?
What are you saying? It's you
It's you who's annoying
Annoying, annoying
You're the one being annoying
What are you saying? It's you
Oh, is it? Is it? Is it?
What?  Seriously, that's enough
You're the annoying one
That's enough
Yay
Round 1
Match 3
Yuriyan Retriever    VS.    Yasei Bakudan Cookie!
Up against Yuriyan,
it's Cookie!
The strongest from America
I'll show you what that is
♫ Huh?
Fat arms, arms, arms
Scott Norton's the strongest
Jura- Jura- Jurassic Bomb
If you eat it, you're done
Ah, Roppongi Ibis Hotel's computer room suits you well
Chōshū, Kensuke, Hase Hiroshi
Newton will be standing no matter what move you use
Yes, thank you.
Yes, thank you, thank you
Thank you
In a contest to change Usseewa's lyrics,
Yuriyan mostly just said "Ussee"
And Cookie! sang about Scott Norton, leaving the audience behind as usual
He just couldn't stop himself
It's a sickness
Who will the winner be?
Yasie Bakudan Cookie!
Yuriyan Retriever
Yuriyan Retriever-san got 28 votes
and Cookie!-san got 23
Yuriyan-san progresses to the semi-finals.
Congratulations.
(Yuriyan) Thank you very much
You didn't change the lyrics
I did change them
No, you didn't. It was all 'ussee ussee'
I did
I changed them so much
I did change the lyrics
You're colluding with the students
You don't know Scott Norton?
He'll kill you all
Idiot. They're a national treasure
You'd be the dead one
1st-year student
Natural Sciences III
Q. What did you find funny
about Yuriyan Retriever?
It was very Yuriyan-like
It was funny how it defied the common wisdom of lyric changing
You did it for her, Suiyoubi
You've been working in the shadows
Is it Yoshimoto? Yoshimoto told you to let Yuriyan win
What the hell's going on?
I'll kill you
(Matsumoto) Don't say that
Doburock
Hollywood
Zakoshishō
Iron Head
Koga Ken
Razor
Ramon RG
Yasei Bakudan
Cookie!
Yuriyan
Retriever
Next on the Lyric Changing Tournament
Iron Head       VS.   Hollywood Zakoshishō
Round 1
Match 4
First up, it's Iron Head
I'll work part-time, save up money
cut back on food expenses, and buy a moped
♫ Huh?
No socializing or studying, just the moped
Work hard, live frugally
I'll be sitting astride a moped
Ah, I think. That mediocre exhaust sound
Even if I don't have insurance, there's no problem
You've got to have insurance!
Iron Head       VS.   Hollywood Zakoshishō
Round 1
Match 4
And up against Iron Head is...
the winner from last time,
Hollywood Zakoshishō
Hello, I'm Ikari Gendō
Alright... Music, start!
Shinji Shinji Shinji, pilot the Eva!
♫ Huh?
Shinji Shinji Shinji, are you going to pilot the Eva or not?
Let's clear this up
If you won't pilot the Eva, go home
Ahh, Fuyutsuki too. Ride the Eva, ride it, ride it
Shinji Shinji Shinji
All according to Seele's scenario
That is all
Who will the winner be?
Hollywood Zakoshishō
Iron Head
Iron Head-san, 9 votes
Hollywood Zakoshishō-san, 42 votes
Progressing to the semi-finals is
Hollywood Zakoshishō-san!
Pilot the Eva!
Well, it was an easy win
The first one, like that
I've won twice, right?
I showed them what a winner looks like
Huh?
I never expected someone else to have glowing eyes
'Usseewa'
Doburock
Hollywood
Zakoshishō
Iron Head
Koga Ken
Razor
Ramon RG
Yasei Bakudan
Cookie!
Yuriyan
Retriever
In the Lyric Changing Tournament
For the next round, here's the song we're using
I'm in the stars tonight
♬～Cos ah ah
Reaching Number 1 on the U.S. Billboard charts
A big hit from South Korea
BTS' 'Dynamite'
How will the 4 semi-finalists change its lyrics?
Doburock    VS.   Razor Ramon RG
Semi-final
Match 1
First, Doburock
I'm a
I'm a te-
I'm a te- te-
I'm a te- te- te-
I'm a te- te- te- te-
I'm a te- te- te- te- testicle
Te-
Te- te-
Te- te- te-
Te- te- te- te-
Te- te- te- te- testicle
Right or left? Which testicle are you?
I'm a left testicle
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no
What's the matter?
I've made a huge mistake
I'm actually a right testicle
They're backwards?
Doburock    VS.   Razor Ramon RG
Semi-final
Match 1
And up against Doburock,
Razor Ramon RG
There's one thing Summers-san have been doing lately
And I'd like to sing about it.
Music, start!
What Sum- Sum- Summers-san have been doing
What Summers-san have been doing, I'll want to say
What Summers-san have been doing, starting now
Their pants are super wide
Sum-um-um-um-ummer's pants are super wide
Sum-um-um-ummer, both of them have super wide pants
I'll tell you something else Summer-san have been doing
They keep wearing tight jackets
Who's going to be the first to advance to the final?
Here's the result:
Doburock
Razor Ramon RG
Doburock-san get 31 votes
RG-san gets 20 votes
Progressing to the final is Doburock-san
Thank you very much
We did it! Thank you very much
Thank you very much. Phew!
Well, um...
It's because everyone sees us the other way around
So that's...
It's like "which one's on the right?", isn't it?
I think Summers-san probably wear Red Wing shoes
Today, unfortunately, I wore Timberlands
Tokyo Uni students notice such things, right?
Doburock
Hollywood
Zakoshishō
Iron Head
Koga Ken
Razor
Ramon RG
Yasei Bakudan
Cookie!
Yuriyan
Retriever
Next in the Lyric Changing Tournament...
Semi-final
Match 2
Yuriyan Retriever       VS.   Hollywood Zakoshishō
First, it's Yuriyan Retriever
I've got one thing
I've got one thing on my mind
The dust in every house...
It's gray...
It's gray... but why?
Even if there are no gray things in the room
It's gray...
It's gray... but why?
Semi-final
Match 2
Yuriyan Retriever       VS.   Hollywood Zakoshishō
Up against Yuriyan, it's Hollywood Zakoshishō
Hanmakanma Ambaramba
Hanmakanma
Hanmakanma Hanmakanma
Ambarakamba Ambarakambara Hanmakanma
I know how you feel, I know how you feel
Hanmakanma. That was Furuhata
(Zakoshishō) I know how you feel
Who will win this battle and face Doburock in the final?
Hollywood Zakoshishō
Yuriyan Retriever
Yuriyan-san: 10 votes,
Hollywood Zakoshishō-san: 41 votes
The finalist is Zakoshishō-san!
Yes, yes. I knew it
I knew Tokyo students would get it
On the other hand, Yuriyan-san, what happened?
I'm documenting this
Scary
It's scary
So scary...
('Kongo' means 'later')
I'll use it as a reference video, kongo
Kongo
Republic of the Congo
Republic of the Congo? What republic?
This is so stupid
What are you filming?
Don't film like that
I'm going to use it for next time, for myself
That's nice
Weren't you like "let's kiss" when we were waiting for the results?
I wanted to kiss you, yes
What's that about?
I wanted to kiss when the curtains opened
'Usseewa'
Doburock
Hollywood
Zakoshishō
Iron Head
Koga Ken
Razor
Ramon RG
Yasei Bakudan
Cookie!
Yuriyan
Retriever
So, our finalists are
these two groups
And our last song is...
♫ We are...
'Homura'
The theme song from the
number-1 grossing film in Japan,
'Demon Slayer'...
LiSA's 'Homura'
Doburock
Hollywood Zakoshishō
The two finalists that will be competing...
Runner-up
Winner
are the same as in last year's final
1st Tournament Winners
Doburock
4th & 6th Tournament Winner
Hollywood Zakoshishō
Final
VS.
Will they be able to redeem
themselves from last time?
First, it's Doburock
Fish ball soup,
Fish ball soup, Dumpling soup,
Fish ball soup, Dumpling soup, Pork soup,
Fish ball soup, Dumpling soup, Pork soup, Rice cracker soup
The most erotic soup is
The most erotic soup is nameko soup
TL Note: The word for soup (shiru) also means bodily secretion and nameko is a type of mushroom
Nameko soup, Nameko soup
But on other hand the least erotic soup is...
Sumashi soup
TL Note: A kind of clear soup. 'Sumashi' also means uptight/prude
or serious (like the face he's making now)
1st Tournament Winners
Doburock
4th & 6th Tournament Winner
Hollywood Zakoshishō
Final
VS.
Up against Doboroku...
It's Hollywood Zakoshishō,
whose 3rd victory is at stake
Chanchakachan Chanchakachan
Chanchakachan Chakachan
Chanchakachanchanchachanchan
Damn it, Da-damn it!
Chanchakachan Chanchakachan
Chakachakchaka, Damn it!
Damn it,
Damn it, Damn it,
Damn it, Damn it, Da-damn it!!
I thought it was air
I thought it was air but it was ice!
I thought it was air but it was ice! Damn it!
With dicks, testicles, and nameko soup, all of Dobrock's lyrics were all in the same dirty-joke style
On the other hand...
Zakoshishō continued to attack with his unchanging style while introducing new material
So which side will come out on top?
In the Lyric Changing Tournament
Here are the results of the final match:
Doburock
Hollywood Zakoshishō
Doburock-san, 17 votes
Hollywood Zakoshishō-san,
34 votes. Which means...
Zakoshishō-san is the winner!
I did it!
(Fujimoto) It feels like if
you play fairly, it's not enough
I did it!
This is just...
Victory 3!
Yeah, really
This is unprecedented
Seriously, it's the exact same result as last year
Exactly the same
Damn... it's really frustrating
What is it?
We did everything we could in this tournament
We did, really
I'm probably more passionate about this than any other contest
What we'll be doing for the next year
Is checking all of the shows Zakoshishō appears on
Who's going to beat me?
Who's going to beat me? I'm waiting!
Huh? Yeah
Doburock
Hollywood
Zakoshishō
Iron Head
Koga Ken
Razor
Ramon RG
Yasei Bakudan
Cookie!
Yuriyan
Retriever
7th Lyric Changing Tournament
Winner: Hollywood Zakoshishō
(2 years in a row, for the 3rd time)
And with that...
the winner of the 7th Lyric Changing Tournament
is once again Hollywood Zakoshishō
Doburock
Hollywood
Zakoshishō
Iron Head
Koga Ken
Razor
Ramon RG
Yasei Bakudan
Cookie!
Yuriyan
Retriever
Right?
Again?
He was a huge hit
with the Tokyo students, wasn't he?
I think it's because Tokyo students
spend all their time thinking too much
His stuff is really about nothing, isn't it?
Amazing
I really loved Doburock-san's
'Te-te-te-testicle' from the semifinals
You do?
Hey
I knew it when you became a mother
These two were laughing
so much at the testicles
Doburock-san had
dirty jokes but...
They didn't sound dirty
(Shibuya) It was like they were
dirty jokes girls can laugh at too
I think it was great
There's shades of dirtiness
There's shades? Really?
Yeah, it went down well
Everyone's Theories
Next, introducing and
verifying various theories...
Everyone's Theories
Everyone's Theories
Tonight's presenters are...
It's FUJIWARA!
Presenters:
Haranishi Takayuki / Fujimoto Toshifumi
Yes, we're here, we're on TV!
Well then everyone...
What kind of person was your grandpa?
My grandpa got stomach cancer,
had his whole stomach taken out,
and I remember he lost loads of weight
You don't have to tell us that
It's okay. It's...
Mikitty
Mikitty is cracking up
I couldn't help but laugh
It's like 'why is she saying that?'
Because everyone loses
weight if that happens
Today we've brought you a theory related to grandpas and their grandkids
Here it is!
Theory: The make-your-grandkid-laugh
challenge where the grandkid doesn't laugh at all. A painful reverse prank
We're trying to have fun on this show
so why make such a painful theory?
Matsumoto-san, have you ever seen your mother try to make your daughter laugh?
I've never seen her laugh that much
How about yours, Gotō?
My dad, when his grandkid, my son, comes
is like "Ah, here you are!"
and then goes straight to his room
What's that? Why?
Theory: The make-your-grandkid-laugh
challenge where the grandkid doesn't laugh at all. A painful reverse prank
And so, we invited grandpa comedians with grandkids to this fake project
The first:
Hello
Gushiken Yōkō
Staff) Do you think you'll be able to make your grandkid laugh?
Of course I will
Without a doubt, she'll laugh I think
Gushiken's granddaughter is...
Gushiken Kanna-chan
Staff) Is your granddad usually funny?
Yes
Staff) He makes you laugh?
Staff) What kind of things does he do?
Funny faces
Staff) Today, if you make her laugh
Staff) we'll give Kanna-chan a product she wants as a gift
Yes, yes
Woah, she'd love that
But on the other hand, we also told Kanna-chan...
Staff) What do you want most of all now?
Sweets Recipe
Card game
What she wants
(Staff) Sweets Recipe
Staff) If you don't laugh once, we'll give it to you
I'll do my best not to laugh
So, both of them think she won't get the
present if she fails the challenge but...
Izakaya - Asakusa Ichimon
Actually, she'll get the present no matter what
in this super heartwarming project
So both of them don't know that
It can only end happily
Kanna!
Kanna! Long time no see
Sorry, I need to go to the bathroom
Kan... long time no see
When he's alone with his grandchild...
the investigation begins
His first tactic is...
I've got loads of funny glasses
I'll use a variety of glasses
I'm thinking it'll be quite funny, you know?
Earlier, these I...
I got some new glasses I want to show you
I'll put on the new ones for you...
I'm thinking I'll go with the ones that are cute
I've bought a few kinds
Look down, look down
How are these?
Bad?
Why are they bad?
They're not cute?
The first pair of glasses falls flat
If my granddad did this I'd laugh
(Gotō) Yeah
I know, right?
Next...
What about these?
Are they cute?
Gushiken lands a clean right jab
TL note: Gushiken is an ex-boxer,
hence all the boxing metaphors
Kanna-chan looks like she's about to laugh
That's not even his intention
And then...
Gushiken throws out a barrage of blows
as though this is the critical moment
His desperate attack continues but
Kanna-chan somehow
manages to endure it
And then...
I'm Butada the Pig-Man!
But Butada the Pig-Man...
Simply falls flat
This is high quality stuff!
Gushiken-san must be shocked
Give me a moment
Grandpa will show you something funnier
One moment
Gushiken's next tactic is...
Chocopla
With the T written on it
Staff) The TT brothers one?
TT brothers
I've seen her laugh at it
Using Kanna's favorite, the TT brothers,
he goes for the win
You can look now!
T!
Hey! T
Gushiken unleashes the TT brothers
combined with Butada the Pig-Man
Here's one!
T!
TT TT T
Upside down
Upside down T
Flipped...
Here's one!
TL note: This is the kanji for his first name, Yōkō
Yōkō
T...
And so...
Prank Reveal
(↑an impressionist)
to a Gushiken who's doing so much at once that he looks like Dancing Tanimura ...
we reveal the prank
Staff) Gushiken-san, it's over
Staff) You didn't make her laugh
She wasn't herself...
Staff) So we'll give you this "Recipe Card"
Congratulations
To Kanna-chan...
He's become like "Ashita no Joe"
Staff) We told her if you don't laugh, you'll get a present
You said she'd get it if she laughed, to me
You said she'd get it if she laughed
That's why I was trying so hard
You were laughing inside, weren't you?
You can laugh now at the end
She laughed
She laughed!
Be quiet!
'Be quiet'...
Next, our second granddad is...
That's the spirit!
Hey!
Animal Hamaguchi
Staff) How are you going to make him laugh?
Staff) Do you have a plan?
'Did it make them laugh?' and 'Is it popular?' are the kind of things I research every day
So leave it to me
For some reason, Animal's tone
is more serious than usual
What he wants
Game
And once again
Hamaguchi Kyōtarō-kun
once he's alone with his grandchild
the investigation starts
What do you want to do in the future?
Ah.. umm..
Work for a sporting goods manufacturer
Sporting goods manufacturer?
Yeah
Well there'll be a lot of challenges but
Kyōtarō, overcome them
and make your dream come true!
Yeah
Grandpa's going to give you
some encouragement now
Alright
Let's go, Kyōtarō!
Ready, start...
Go go go go go
Go go go go go!!
Hey hey hey
Hey hey hey!!!
(exhales)
Kyōtarō, today...
The chanting fell flat but
Animal continues like it was nothing
And then...
Yes, Kyōtarō
Kyōtarō, do you remember?
Yeah
At Sensō-ji there's that statue of Kannon-sama
There, when you were 18 months old...
The wig that once got instant laughs...
got no reaction at all, so...
he hurriedly changes direction to telling anecdotes
There were visitors everywhere
In front of the visitors, you know?
And after that...
Ai Ai Aiai Aiai
Aiai Aiai...
Apart from the wig, Animal continues acting how he usually does
Aiai Aiai
Aiaiai
He isn't even holding any laughter in
So, because both of them couldn't make their grandchild laugh...
We're doing an additional investigation with non-celebrities
Pe! Kato-chan pe!
How about this face?
No good?
But these also ended in victory for the grandchild
(retching)
Kato-chan's no good?
Granddad, hello
But among them...
There was this granddad too...
Alright! Which one...
1 2 3 Go!
Then...
Daaa
Oh?
Alright!
Next, grandpa's bringing his friend here
And then...
Ryōta! It's grandpa's friend. 1 2 3
I'm Bellytarō!
What?!
Hehehe
And so, in the make-your-grandkid laugh challenge, the sole winner was Bellytarō
Investigation Result
Bellytarō
Yes, congratulations!
The winner was Bellytarō-san
In the case of Hamaguchi-san,
his grandson...
Wasn't holding anything back at all
Animal-san
chanted "Go!" 10 times
To make his grandkid laugh
But they often do that same
chant of 'Go!' at athletic ceremonies
Does that mean they're trying to laugh too?
That's right
Today, we have one more
Gotō, today you on here as a solo act,
without your partner, right?
How often do you appear solo instead of as a duo?
I appear solo about 60 to 70% of the time
I don't think it's more than 70%
Downtown-san,
are you about half-half?
Hamada-san does loads of solo gigs
I think so
Hamada-san
I see you doing them all the time
I don't
I always see you on "Tonight on TBS"
(sings) You know, that advert?
(Haranishi) I like the background music
I always see you on there
So then, today...
we've brought you a theory
related to solo gigs
Here it is!
Theory: Even 'The Touch' do some solo gigs
The Touch
They do? Really?
Definitely not
How about it? Have you
ever worked with only Kazuya?
I don't remember!
For them, definitely not
No way
Have you ever wanted to?
It's not that I want to...
The Touch
You've never felt like
working with Kazuya?
How about you, Gotō?
They can't
They're a package deal. They can't appear solo
Theory: Even 'The Touch' do some solo gigs
And so...
The Touch
Twin comedians
Hello
When we asked them about the work they've been doing recently...
Investigation programs, right?
Yes
As you'd expect since we're twins with the same body and lifestyle
Takuya will for example eat spicy food
Kazuya will live normally
To see what happens
Because we've always done lots of experiments
They call us 'guinea pig comedians' at the office
It seems that, as twin comedians, experiment shows are their primary source of jobs but...
Staff) By the way, do you do any solo gigs?
I did Ametalk! solo for example, as a sweet-loving comedian
Yeah
As expected...
They do sometimes do solo gigs
We were in our 3 or 4th year then
Even if we were on a show, it was just for a gag
We mostly would just do "Wait Wait Wait" or "Out-of-Body Experience"
Going there alone meant you couldn't do anything
It's like your only weapon, being a twin, is blocked
It's like you're just an ornament on the stage
Staff) By the way, why did Takuya-san do that solo gig?
Yes?
The program makers thought it'd be funny if only one of us appeared
Both of us love sweets so...
Our manager was  like
'Well, it might as well be you because you're older'
It was age-based for some reason
There was no good reason
Similarly, for Kazuya...
"Impossible!" Episode 4
He appeared alone on a late-night
anthology drama called "Impossible!"
He was specially selected to appear in a tricky role as a stupid cat burglar who gets stuck in a washing machine
Was it like "We need a small, fat, dull middle aged-man"
"Let's use either one of The Touch"?
That's right
Here too, it seems either would've been fine
Staff) So what do you two think of solo gigs?
Umm...
About 10 years into our career, our chief manager told us
"It'd be good if you two started doing more solo gigs now"
We're firmly against it
Not everyone has to be like Osugi-and-Piko-san
And that's all because of the trauma from 'Ametalk!'
Ametalk!
Lincoln
FLASH coverage (2008)
Impossible! ep. 6 (2010)
Small Powerhouse (2011)
Itoda Project ~Rakugo~ (2011)
Magic Knight (2014)
Dr. Nurse Aid (2014)
Family of 25 years (2017)
Kazuya, 6 roles
Magazine
TV
Web
SPA! coverage (2009)
Impossible! ep. 4 (2010)
Small Powerhouse (2011)
Passionate Gym Meet (2012)
Dramatic Kansai (2015)
A Certain Capitol (2016)
TV
Magazine
Web
Live
Movie
TV
On Stage
Takuya, 9 roles
The Touch's solo gigs by year (2003 to 2021)
The two of them...
in the 18 years
they've been active...
have done this many solo
gigs:
Takuya, 9 roles;
Kazuya, 6 roles
And after the last in 2017...
They haven't done any
solo gigs at all
Only Takuya's been on Lincoln
You're right
Dai Taku
Dr. Heinrich
Harapeko Twins
Yoshida-tachi
At this point, we investigated other
twin comedians who don't seem like they'd do solo gigs
Kōhei
Older
Brother
Yoshida-tachi
Younger
Brother
Yūhei
When it comes to the manzai artists, Yoshida-tachi...
Older brother Yuūhei: 4th place
Younger brother Kōhei: Didn't qualify
Yoshimoto Ugly Ranking 2019
Older brother Yūhei alone
was selected as an Ugly Comedian
and appeared solo at the event
As for the competitive eater Youtubers,
the Harapeko Twins...
Ako
Competitive eating YouTubers
Harapeko Twins
Kako
Older
sister
Younger
Kako
Older
sister
Because only one
competitive eater could appear
older sister Kako
appeared alone on a gourmet show
And comedian twins Dai Taku and Dr. Heinrich also
Dai Taku
Dr. Heinrich
have experience working solo in live performances and reenactments
Among these famous twins...
How about the ones you'd least expect to have solo gigs?
Kin is 100 100
Gin's also 100 100
Call Duskin on 100 100
Duskin
Free
Trial campaign for new customers
For both the happy and the sad
Kanie Gin
Legendary twins
Narita Kin
The legend celebrity twins
that debuted at 100,
Kin-san Gin-san
However...
Tetsuya-san, I won't die
Surprisingly, we found a solo appearance by Gin-san
Kin isn't here. I'm very sorry
No, no, it's fine
That's totally fine
What do you mean?
Kin-san had gotten a
fish bone stuck in her throat
so had to miss the shoot
So, it was due to a health problem but
Even Kin-san Gin-san had a solo gig
Yes, that's how it was
(Staff) I see
Yes
Staff) OK, thank you
Staff) Now, could you move to the other seat please
Sure
(Gotō) Huh?
Huh?
(Shibuya) Huh? Huh?
Staff) Thanks. Now, let's do the same questions again
Got it
(Gotō) Huh? I'm scared
And so...
Investigation Result
The Touch appeared solo
for this segment too
I'm annoyed!
That's cute
Do you understand what happened?
I get it
I'm annoyed!!
You thought it was The Touch
talking for the whole thing
I didn't notice at all
Nothing seemed odd
Wow, it's kind of scary
So that's why they seemed a bit odd,
like they had no energy
Because they couldn't interact
(Gotō) They couldn't have a conversation
That's right
I definitely thought you'd notice since their moles are in different places
How would we know that?
I was really nervous
I thought they looked too similar.
They don't look that alike
Which of them was it?
It was Takuya
(Fujimoto) The older one
It was the older brother?
Yes, it was the older one, obviously
No, no, no
What was the aim here?
(Fujimoto) Exactly
So we could be like
"The Touch DO have a solo gig"
But now doesn't this raise the question...
Do twins really exist?
(Gotō) I'm scared
That's scary, stop
★Subbed by fmck fansubs★
reddit.com/u/fmckfansubs
patreon.com/fmck
Next week, a 90 minute extended special
I'm so scared, my head hurts
Theories so scary they'll make your head hurt
You don't have to do it
to know it's difficult
and theories anyone can see are difficult. Also...
Who could make that funny?
A theory that seems
impossible to make funny
A special set of theories,
for this year's last broadcast
This'll be hard, for us too
A scandal...