Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
It's Jinnai Tomonori!
Yes, it's me
So, this time I've brought an annual project
The 8th Best Lyrics Adaptation Championship
Here we go
Is it the 8th edition already?
It's the 8th year, the 8th edition
This is much more anticipated than other competitions
In the 6th and 7th, Hollywood Zakoshi dominated
Impressive
He's obviously good, but I don't remember it
Indeed
-Only remember watching it
But this time the judges have also changed
The jury for the 8th edition is senior citizens
The age has gone up again
Seniors over 75 years old are the judges
That's...
Is this so Hollywood Zakoshi doesn't win again?
If its the same as before he'll just win again
How dare you admit it?
No, he is still able to win!
Just like Ernesto Hoost
-Indeed, indeed.
The Annual Competition
Celebrating its 8th edition this year
The Best Adaptation Lyrics Tournament
Tonight, a new group of eight singing comedians assemble
This time the judges are senior citizens
Senior citizens?
I feel like older people will laugh if they're encouraged to
More-so than young people
The elderly may laugh at those who sing well
They definitely prefer people who can sing well, so I'm really in the running
I have a very powerful secret strategy
If you curry favor with them, it's possible to win by a large margin
Really?
They are my most important target audience
I originally became a comedian in order to make older people laugh
Already bullshit.
-Already lying!
Right in the center of the bullseye
I often consider whether I can capture the hearts of that age group of viewers
I also adapt lyrics to sing to senior citizens
For example, Hibari Misora
"Ahhhhh, the flow of water, help me"
It can be triggered at once
I actually did not want to become a parody artist
Actually, I wanted to be a lyric rewriter
So I'm planning to debut today
Hey, how come no one has been able to defeat me?
You guys, come out!
Gos Gos Gos Gos
Huh?
The above 8 are the participants
From the first round to the final round, they will adapt the lyrics of three designated songs
The judges are...
51 seniors aged 75 or older
The oldest age is 88 years old
Who will be able to capture the hearts of the older people to win the title?
And!
Kuro-chan's new serialization project begins after a 3 year absence
I don't understand, what is this?
This Wednesday, right?
The Best Adaptation Lyrics Tournament
First, the matchup for the first round is:
♬ We are in the third year of high school~
The song selection is suitable for the elderly
Released about 60 years ago
♬ Although we're going to go our separate ways~
With a cumulative circulation of 2.3 million copies
♬But we are brothers forever ~
Kazuo Funaki's debut song "Senior year of high school"
How will the 8 contestants adapt the lyrics of the song?
Round 1, Game 1
A guitarist battle
Old and new generation dueling
♬ With a red shoulder, I'm 60 years old
♬ I can't remember the names of the people
♬ Ahhhhhhh~ Who is this person?
♬  I have an impression of his face, should be an acquaintance
♬ Now I remember
♬ It's my brother
Slow and clear
Surprisingly quite honest
Using a silver-haired approach
He wins the laughter of the elderly
Now the challenger
Can he do it?
Vocal YU-KI Dancer SAM
♬ ETSU and CHIHARU DJ KOO
They won't get it
All members of the band TRF formed by Tetsuya Komuro
♬ Ahhhhhhhh~ The TRF that everyone knows
We don't all know it!
♬ Now only DJ KOO is still lively
This one's lost, right?
Not known
♬ Only KOO is still lively
That's not good.
-No, it's not
They don't get it
Both sides have finished singing
When it comes to the judging session
51 seniors press the button of the side they find interesting
The winner is determined by the number of votes cast
You didn't press the wrong button, did you?
Please forgive them for that
How will the elders judge this matchup?
Round 1, Game 1
The results are as follows
Tatsuo Kamon with 49 votes
Shinichi, 2 votes
So the confirmed semi-finalist is Tatsuo Kamon
Congratulations
-Thank you
Just 2 votes...?
Q.What did you like about Tatsuo Kamon?
I heard myself in his songs and it felt interesting
The 2nd one i'm a bit unsure what he was singing about
Mask, mask!
Next in The Best Adapted Lyrics Tournament is...
Round 1, Game 2
First is Razor Ramon RG
I am from North Island Music Office
My name is Ooe Yutaka
Very similar
So, music start!
♬ The black part takes up most of the eye
I don't know which way I'm looking
♬ Ahhh~ black eyes~ black eyes~ almost black eyes~
♬ The eyes always feel like I've seen
♬ The eyes of the great white shark that attacks humans
What will happen?
RG uses a secret strategy of black eye color pupils to win or lose
He is competing with the three-time champion, the Hollywood Zakoshi
Good luck
♬ Ambala Kambara Hangma Kangma
This is bad
-Risky
♬ Dongdonglong Bobolong Hangma Kangma
Champion
-Why sing this?
It's not very good, is it?
♬ Hey ~ I'm Jinsaburo Furuhata
♬ Can you wait? Hangma Kangma Hangma Kangma
It's not even an adaptation of lyrics anymore, right?
♬ I've noticed the atmosphere here
Just end it
♬ Hangma Kangma I am Furuhata
What will happen?
Very good, very good!
It's an even match.
-What will be the result?
Neither side of the audience seemed to be immersed
The outcome of this matchup is...
RG 14 votes, Zakoshi 37 votes
So the semi-finalist is Hollywood Zakoshi
He's surprised
Congratulations
-Thanks
You're scary, your eyes
The eyes are really scary, if you look close
The black eye is too big, it's too much
My name is Ooe Yutaka
Q. What did you like about Zakoshi?
Although I do not understand what he was singing
He spoke very clearly, that was good
Ooe, I didn't understanding what he was singing
A little scary...
I see.
-The eyes!
Too bad
That guy, it's not funny enough to please the audience
It's a shame, isn't it? That guy
I still need to continue to sharpen
And send songs across the country
It's Ooe
Next in the Best Adapted Lyrics Tournament is...
Round 1, Match 3
First is Chance Oshiro
♬ Red F1 car Michael Schumacher
♬ Got knocked down~
♬ Ahhhhhhhh~ 3 months to heal
♬ Immediately rejuvenated
♬ Jumping and skipping
♬ My wife also jumped out
It suddenly became very Chance
Why're they not the same size
Subtle Sizing
Competing with Chance is
DobuRock
♬ Giant zucchini Put it in your pocket
♬ I was walking on the road and was seen
♬ Ahhhhhhh~ It's really big!
♬ No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. This is zucchini
♬ What? It's a cucumber!
♬ No, no, no, no, no, it's zucchini
What's going to happen?
-But still...
Which side will emerge victorious?
Chance Oshiro 24 votes
DobuRock 27 votes
Just about won
So the semi-finalist is DobuRock, congratulations!
Thank you all
You are really still in your prime, I can be sure of that
Great!
It's too bad, just a few votes
I really wanted to perform the next one
I was going to sing a song by Ueto
I want to perform it so badly
Next in the Best Adapted Lyrics Tournament is
Round 1, Game 4
First, Michiko Shimizu
I am Miwa Miroku
Music Start
*Refers to the two flavors of Marumo Ramen from Toyo Fisheries
♬ Red fox and green civet
♬ I am Miwa
{The song "ヨイトマケの唄" was written and composed by Akihiro Miwa in 1966, and refers to the old days when a heavy hammer was pulled down to strengthen the foundation
♬ Ahhhhhhhhh~ Song of the Heavy Hammerers
♬ For the sake of my father ouch yah yah yah
{These two lines are the first two lines of the above song, and "えんやこら" is the shout of a hard worker pulling a rope with a heavy hammer.
♬ For mother's sake ouch yah yah yah
♬ Thank you for listening!
Michiko Shimizu has captured the hearts of older people with her beautiful imitation
Does Cookie have any chance of winning?
Hello everyone
It's great to see everyone's spirit
Hello, ladies and gentlemen!
How is your health?
He's starting like this
You have also been sitting for a long time, right?
Please bear with us again
It's like a warm-up session
In fact, I was brought up by the older generation, so I like you all
Then please listen. Thank you all
♬ The tall man standing in the red corner
{Alexey Ignashov: The Russian grappler known as the "Eastern European Red Scorpion" is best known for his knee strikes
♬ Red Scorpion Star Alexei Ignashov
♬ If you don't suppress it, knee knee knee and send you a knee
It's falling apart so fast
♬ Ah ah ah ah ah ah ~ broken jaw hard work
♬ Fleeing, but Ignashov is right behind him
♬ Even if you look backward, you will be wrapped around the front knee knee
Cookie first uses sweet words to make them let down their guard
Then uses a K-1 boxer to attack the elderly
Who will win?
Michiko Shimizu 37 votes
Cookie 14 votes
Congratulations to Michiko Shimizu for advancing to the semi-finals!
Even if you make that face
Pay attention to your attitude
I said so many kind words
Why? Isn't this the K-1 generation?
Of course not, no matter how you think
Never seen K-1?
Thank you for your hard work
What "hard work", it didn't go as planned
Kazuyoshi Ishii, the founder of the world-famous kickboxing tournament K-1
You told me they were all relatives of Director Ishii
Didn't you say this was a meeting of relatives of Director Ishii?
In such a way you'd win?
Of course i'd win, you bastard
It's Ignashov
He's got a ruthless knee
It's the same as a poison needle
The Best Adapted Lyrics Tournament
The next song designated for the semi-finals is this one
♬ Work your way up
The #1 Billboard global hit
♬ Hope not to shed tears
Sakamoto's "Walk with your head held high"
What kind of adapted lyrics will the four groups of semi-finalists bring?
Semi-final match 1, first of all, Tatsuo Kamon
♬ Look down and walk
♬ In order not to trip and fall
♬ Loose here and there
♬ This night, the urine also leaked
Singing slowly and clearly
Against Tatsuo Kamon is
Hollywood Zakoshi
Start!
♬ 46.3 million yen
♬ The grant was transferred by mistake
{A famous scene after Sho Taguchi, an employee of Abukicho, was charged for mistakenly giving 46.3 million yen in benefits to a family and was released on bail
♬ The wind was so strong that all the hair blew to the front
Who will actually be the first to advance to the final?
The results are as follows
Tatsuo Kamon 45 points
Zakoshi 6 points
So the finalist is Kamon, Congratulations!
He's very strong
No. Do they not watch the news?
I also deliberately chose the news that people of this age would know
This is not completely unfunny
The Best Adapted Lyrics Tournament
Next is the 2nd game of the semi-finals
First is DobuRock
♬ Plucked the wrist hair and ate it
♬ Chest hair can also eat Oh
♬ Chest hair and so on do not eat it
♬ I want to eat calf hair
I see
-Not a dirty joke
Playing against DobuRock is
Michiko Shimizu
♬ Hello, I'm Tetsuko Kuroyanagi
♬ What about the song "Walk with your head held high"?
*The song's lyricist, composer and singer respectively
♬ by Mr. Rokusuke, Mr. Nakamura, Mr. Ku Sakamoto
♬ A popular song composed by this trio
♬ Everyone, in order to go forward with their heads held high, health is still very important
♬ To this end, the most important thing
♬ It's a generic drug
{A commercial for a generic drug from Towa Pharmaceuticals
♬ Tohwa Pharmaceuticals
Powerful keywords
-The response is quite good
Not quite dirty DobuRock and
and Michiko Shimizu, who doesn't really adapt songs
Who will win the showdown and advance to the final?
DobuRock 15votes
Michiko Shimizu 36 votes
The finalist is Michiko Shimizu
When talking about eating wrist hair
I thought, "Oh, this is not good"
"I'm not supposed to talk about this"
So, these are the two players who advanced to the final
Next, the final assigned track is
♬ Both of them closed the door
Released in 1971. A big hit of the Showa era
♬ Both of them erased each other's names
♬ At that time, you will think of something to say, right?
"Until the day we meet again" by Kisehiko Ozaki
The two who are over 60 years old rightfully advance
Which one will win the title with this tune?
The Best Lyrics Adaptation Championship Finals
First is Kamon
♬ Until the day we meet again, my partner will go first
♬ Although I'm still sad, I feel like I've let go of a heavy burden
♬ Never have to take care of him again and go on a trip with a companion
♬ A lonely wife should live a long life, right?
Both sides will win for the first time no matter who wins
Next is Michiko Shimizu
♬ I am Setouchi
♬ Welcome to all of you who have come all the way here
♬ What about the song "Until the day we meet again"?
♬ It's a very famous song
It's not an adaptation of a song at all
♬ It's a song about the separation of men and women
♬ But when it comes to the real most important difference
♬ Actually, it's the separation from life
♬ You may be approaching that moment
When the funeral takes place, the staff will securely close the coffin door
♬ And then, although the name will be eliminated, you will get the precepts
♬ And at that time, what did Lord Buddha say?
♬ In order for that day to come, we must actively survive
♬ It's a song like this
♬ Thank you for listening
If she wins this...
After all, it is a song adaptation tournament
Both sides clung to seniors in 3 games
Who will achieve the final victory?
The results are:
Kamon 32 votes, Shimizu 19 votes
So the winner is Kamon Tatsuo. Congratulations!
Kamon, How do you feel now?
Next, I will focus on this age group and continue to sing
Although it's a shame
I never thought I would make it this far
Already very happy
To sum up, the winner of the 8th Best Lyrics Adaptation Tournament is Kamon Tatsuo
Okay, so the 8th winner is Kamon Tatsuo
Ah, that...
He was good, and superior to the rest
But there are also various interludes
Everyone was interesting in their own way
Only Shinichi was not good
That guy is going to hang his head in shame
Neither the elderly nor us were feeling it
We should understand at the very least
True
This time I found that the judges to be quite unique
But no foreigners has been invited to be a judges
-Yes.
Maybe at some point
But no matter what age you are, domestic or foreign
Everyone will feel that Shinichi is not interesting
All eyes on him will not be moved
Judges?
The eyes of the judges on him?
What is that all about?
Let's welcome the next presenter
Ahhh
Yes, its Fujiwara
Just Fujimon?
Just Fujimon
It's here, everyone
What?
The long-awaited Kuro-chan project
Great!
-The worst
Don't say "the worst"
The coexistence of "great" and "the worst"
Polarization
-Is everything okay?
So, please take a look
-Okay
Beautifully done
Standing there are 9 ladies in dresses
Eh?
Here we go again
What's going on?
A familiar opening
Such a loud echo, what is this?
Where is this? Where am I? A building?
What?
It's so spacious, isn't it? Where is this?
What a big echo
Have we arrived?
Hey, are we there yet?
So, Kuro-chan
Don't say the same as Agnes Chan
Nobody said anything
What?
Please take off the blindfold
No one said anything at all
I took it off!
Eh?
What's this?
What... women?
"Women"
I don't get it. What is this?
It's Wednesday, right?
It's Wednesday... right?
He's scared
So, do you ladies want to ask Kuro-chan anything?
I do
Are there any girls among us that you like?
What?
Any I like?
-Yes
Well... you're all cute
Seriously, everyone is so cute
Ah, of course, Nami who asked the question
Ah, I'm Mina
It's hopeless.
-How can he get both characters wrong
Ah...
He misread it
So do any of you like me?
Eh?
What do you mean?
Everyone?
Really?
-How is it possible?
Eh?
I really like you
What is this? Wait!
Can't figure it out
I don't understand. I've never met such a person
This is Wednesday, right?
All the ladies here like Kuro-chan
Really?
-How is it possible?
Eventually you will choose one of them to confess to
The goal is to become a couple
You all just raised your hands, it's not a lie, right?
You all raised your hands but expressing love is not so simple
Like shouting "yes"
He's really looking after himself
Yes
It's like this
Still a bit quiet...
What's wrong with this guy?
Raise your hand if you like Kuro-chan
I do
It can be done, can't it?
I can't watch
-The light in the eyes
Ah
So, is this the result of Wedneday's call for "people that like Kuro-chan?"
Yes
Did you collect them?
In April a notice was sent out to recruit
There was such a thing.
-That's right
Do you really like me?
Yes
Can you find so many?
Great, not just a random girlfriend
What the hell are you looking for?
So, Kuro-chan
-Yes
Please change into clothes that match the ladies
Wait for me!
OK
Such a quick attitude change
We know they all like him
It's Kuro-chan
What?
This expression is really bad
Just go!
-Indeed
Awesome, what is this?
-There are so many
Everyone is so cute
Yes, they are very beautiful
MONSTER LOVE
What's this?
So, Kuro-chan's new project has officially begun
First MONSTER HOUSE, then MONSTER IDOL
After 3 years the third edition of the MONSTER series is here
In April this year, the program team recruited women who really like Kuro-chan
Yes, it took a lot of time to prepare, but finally the project has begun
Really?
-There's a lot of them
But this time it all involves girls who say they like him
Kuro-chan can build upon his past experiences, right?
If this project is to see Kuro-chan find happiness
I don't want to see it.
-Sometimes it's good to have something like this
Is it that simple?
I understand people may feel a bit conflicted
Kuro-chan's dirty side comes out really quickly
-Super quick!
With people that like him
-He'll be unrestrained
That's what I want to see
Will we be able to see it?
-It's already on display!
Enough is enough
It's already showing a bit
I just want to watch and despise him at the same time
The last wave when leaving the room
The waving action is disgusting, so disgusting
Just want to see this
Okay, folks, let's get on with it, please
Hello everyone
Cute!
Cute?
Thank you big ~heart~yo~
Everyone's Kuro-chan has appeared
I'm coming to the heart~yo, I'm coming to the heart~yo
So smug
With "heart" at the end of his words, it means he is in a good mood
I changed into formal wear to match everyone
What do you think of Kuro-chan?
So handsome
The tie suits you
-Oh, it's nice
I do not hate this kind of complement ~heart~yo~
What's wrong with this guy?
-I can't watch
Here we go. One, two, cheers.
-Cheers!
Meeting everyone, the mood is so good!
Ok ok, ba-bu!
So interesting
What's so interesting?
Here we go. "Interesting" Cheers!
"Interesting", it's just not at all
I always follow him online
He is better in person than I thought, really handsome
Seriously?
Sincerely?
He's cuter than I thought, like a mascot
Really?
Not at all, okay?
I already thought he is very handsome
Really?
But he's more handsome than I realized
Seriously?
He's becoming more and more attractive
Genuinely?
I've never experienced this feeling of being a king before
Finally, Wednesday is doing something good for me
This time if it really becomes...
I have a 10-year window, 10 years
I'll really be dating
You've all prepared so much
No matter what, I have to seriously decide
If I can't find someone here, I won't be able to find anyone in life
Manly
Do you guys have any preferences? Its important to know
Everyone's fetishes are different
What about you, Mana?
This sitting position...
I like sound
The voice
I like hands
I like older men
The age difference with Kuro-chan is the one I like the most
Everyone's very direct
What about Kuro-chan?
I like to see the food in a girl's mouth when she eats
That's very chic
The mouth
I want to see it
But who~ but who~
Awful!
I want to see Richi who's covering her face with champagne
Poor thing
-She's been chosen
Want to see it?
-I want to see it~
What to do?
Want to see it~
Which should I eat?
She's happy to be chosen
She loves it
Wait, I'll choose, which one to choose...
There are too many to choose from
So cute
So disgusting
Like this?
Will it go in?
Open your mouth
It's too big!
It's all in~
Amazing!
Disgusting, disgusting
Disgusting
Open your mouth, open your mouth, open your mouth
His eyes are shining!
I can't see it at all. Open wider, copy me!
I see a little bit of it
Wait, I'll return the gift, i'll return the gift
Do you need to do it too?
Here
What?
Foreign objects mixed in
What does "foreign matter mixed in" mean?
Not visible at all
-Not visible
What is this image?
I'm super excited
The climax is coming
The pinnacle, this is the pinnacle
Showing me her mouth
I saw what others usually don't
This person is hopeless
So, I exploded with happiness
The mouth is superb
I really like this kind of mutual thing
I'm really amazed
So disgusting. Is he serious?
In my heart, I just felt "ugh!"
a 40 year-old doing this sort of thing
It's really disgusting to me
Who wants to see inside the mouth of some old dude?
Cheers!
Worry about your status
Worry
There are fake ones among them
I might've drunk too much today
Next, Kuro-chan chatted with the girls individually in order
I am a dental assistant by profession
So although I really like Kuro-chan
I still think its important to pay attention to the taste of your mouth and the alignment of your teeth.
-Yes yes yes
Yes, from a professional point of view.
-It's something I focus on
Can you help me check the taste of my mouth?
Breathe for me.
-Is that okay?
It's gotta stink
No smell at all
It stinks! It stinks!
Just a few fillings
It was seen, really
There's a few caps, but they're fine
It's totally acceptable for me to fall in love
This girl is so skilled
I was so happy that you didn't duck when I breathed
Good talker
I don't dislike you at all
To confirm, is that the first time you showed someone the food in your mouth?
First time in my life
Definitely the first time
What a stupid question
Sorry, but that's what fetishes are for
If its for the person I like then its fine
It's amazing, it's really amazing, seriously
What the hell?
Oh no, seriously!
Ri, I like you
A confession!
I'm happy to hear it
Everyone will hear the same thing
Sorry, I'm too happy so I got drunk
When I heard about this project, I thought
Once I'm in a relationship, I won't stop at just dating
What are you talking about?
I'm thinking about marriage
-Yes
I also want to get married to Kuro-chan
Too fast, right?
No, wait, how? I seem to have an answer...
So quick!
Miku, what type of girl are you?
You know, the color of your hair, what is this style?
Normally it wouldn't be so done up
But I heard you like pink
I dyed it pink, but the color kind of disappeared
Was the change made for me?
I came here to marry you
Is there such a person?
Ah~, Mi, I'm going to protect you
I'm protecting you now
I hope you will protect me
What the hell?
How... how should I put it...
It's like, "this might be love"
So annoying
After this also
I have 24-hour surveillance at home, do you mind?
Do not care at all, let them look
Let them watch us fool around
The one-on-one chats with Kuro-chan to find a new girlfriend after a long absence of 10 years
I hope you can teach me a lot of things
What do you want me to teach you?
You asked me to teach you
I didn't say it
So close!
Talking to me so closely, I really felt sick
This is someone's real feelings
He really thinks of himself as a handsome man, really stupid
Now Kuro-chan must announce the first batch of unsuccessful hopefuls
2 of 9 will be eliminated
It's about time. How are you feeling, Kuro-chan?
I'm torn, but after talking to everyone fully, I have a firm answer
So, Kuro-chan, please tap the shoulders of the girls you would like to stay
Qualified
Thank you
Crying!
So happy?
Tears of joy?
I don't know, what if it's an act?
Next, please select the second person
Kuro-chan, please make your choice
Looked inside her mouth after all
Likes this girl
Qualified
Thank you
Afterwards
Qualified
-Thank you
Finally these three remain
Kuro-chan, please select the last person
Eliminating 2 people
OK
Not nervous at all
Mami, you've passed. Congratulations.
-Thanks
Above is Kuro-chan's ranking
I feel that Mana and Momo genuinely liked me
But they're not really my type
So I eliminated them
There's something I need to tell you.
-Something to tell me?
In fact, not everyone here likes Kuro-chan
See?
-It's true
Now he knows
Eh, what do you mean?
Of course there are also some that like you
But a few are just pretending to like you
What? This is so not necessary!
It is
What'd be the point if they all like you?
So, as some girls have been included to pretend to like him
Can Kuro-chan find a girl who really likes him and get a girlfriend after 10 years?
What is the purpose of this?
So, what about the 2 people eliminated today?
Which side are those 2 people on?
They were both pretending
No way, absolutely no way!
It can't be true, seriously!
That's awful
I was lying, sorry
Pretending to like Kuro-chan is a bit too tiring
To be honest there is nothing that I like about him
Understandable
Really?
-Really
Wait a minute
Women are scary
He was fooled
I felt so guilty after eliminating them because I really thought they liked me
So that means you can't tell
Wait
If those 2 people are fake...
It feels like everyone is fake now
Seriously?
What is this line?
Now, the remaining members will start living with Kuro-chan
The setting is once again Okinawa
Cheers!
I am trying to get married!
I'm not playing around
Can I kiss you?
I hope you only like me
I like you the most!
What the hell?
I don't trust the girl who likes me
What?
What's up with this secrecy?
This is not a simple love project at all!
That's for sure.
-Not everyone wants to make good memories with that lowly man
We don't know how many are sincere
-Correct
There are a few people who are lying, but we don't know who
-Yeah
But 3rd place Risa is lying, right?
Risa?
After all, its impossible to believe that Kuro-chan's mouth doesn't stink
Who knows? I've never smelled it either
It stinks
It definitely stinks, doesn't it?
-It stinks
You haven't smelled it either
It just stinks
It can't stink 24 hours a day
I don't know why i'm sticking up for Kuro-chan
Are they crying because they're happy or because they want out?
-Yes, yes, yes
It could be either
It's unclear what the tears are expressing
Maybe it's acting, maybe it's true
It's scary
Michopa you can't stand him, but you're also curious, right?
-No, no, no.
To see what'll happen
I don't care about his love life at all
I just want him to be cheated
Kuro-chan looks happy right now
But also a little suspicious
I hope the program team quickly torture him to death
That's too much!
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03