Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Today is an extra-long episode
Is it really good to add time for this?
It's good
Shortening its seems more appropriate
Let's welcome the next presenter
That's the one, right?
It's Fujiwara!
Don't enter like Junji Takada
Today is a special episode
I'm going for it
You know what I mean
3 2 1
Not a theory!
How can we all say it together?
So hard to guess
You know it all, right?
It's this
MONSTER LOVE
I'm looking forward to it!
Very happy
This is the only project today!
Just this one
A very popular project!
Honestly, I really enjoy watching it
I'm just watching this and The 13 Lords of the Shogun
These two
They don't match
What else will be broken after breaking the cookies?
Nothing else
Here's a brief review
Kuro-chan has been living lives in Okinawa with a mix of women who like him and are just pretending to like him
Later, he found out that the ones pretending are doing it in the hopes of becoming idols
The three remaining individuals have now formed an idol group
The song is also very good
The song is so funky!
-Have you heard it already?
It's a popular type of song
I don't get it.
-Very trendy
So, although 3 people have debuted together
This project is, in the end, a love project for Kuro-chan
Indeed
So he'll now date each of them
Then confess to one of them
There is still 1 woman left that likes him
Michopa, what's up with that expression of yours?
Always this expression
What?
The difference with him is too large
Do you want to keep the persona?
It's ok to admit you like watching it
Yeah, Michopa
-There's no need to hide it
Be honest with yourself, you love to watch it
No, no, no
So let's get started, guys.
-Let's go!
Please take a look at the finale of Monster Love
It's fashionable!
-Yokohama?
I'm already pissed off just looking at him
Aki-kun!
I've been waiting for you.
-Miku
What do you want to do today?
Let's go to the planetarium
Oh, so romantic!
Well, i've always wanted to go
Let's hurry up and get over there.
-Go?
Let's go
It's here
Oooh wow, hand in hand
Wow, awesome!
Maybe Miku actually likes him?
Well, it seems pretty fashionable so i've always wanted to come
The most natural
Miku is very aggressive
Oh, awesome!
Did you forget about me, Miku?
I haven't forgotten
Really?
Yes, all I think about is Aki-kun every day
Holding hands?
I haven't seen a single person since I got back to Tokyo and I'm so lonely
So powerful
I'm the one who's lonely!
Finally we can date
If she's a fake then she's pretty impressive
I'd be surprised if she's lying
I like you
Me too
Now is the closest
So peaceful
Finally we can date
I'll fill up on happiness with Aki-kun while I can
What?
Then I also
If this is acting it's really good
It's really awesome
You can use my arm as a pillow
Really? I'm so happy
Really?
Is this real?
I've always wanted that
Is that Kuro-chan?
No, it's a full moon
I've always wanted to do the same
So close, so close, so close
Stop it!
Miku
This sound, why do you need to gasp
So powerful
Impressive
So happy
So erotic, really
Were you aroused?
Super aroused! Seriously
What a dirty room!
Straight up seducing me
Where is this place?
Pretty snazzy, huh?
-Yeah.
I wanted to come here, so I made a reservation
It's great
Cheers
Why does it have to be so fashionable?
Drinking a lot!
Tastes good
Yummy
But what I'm a little concerned about is
I haven't asked about Miku's previous relationships
What kind of love have you had before?
He cares
Hmm...
A little embarrassed to say
Almost all of the people I dated before were...
I got cheated on
Eh, why?
I guess my presence became too normal
So going after others was more exciting
The back of his head is really interesting
How did you find out he was cheating on you?
I had a bit of suspicion
But at that time I wanted to believe him
Don't eat pizza now!
Don't eat pizza!
Eating and drinking pizza
I guess he thought he wouldn't be shown
Don't eat it now!
-Listen well
Everyone thinks so...
He sent message saying, "I'm looking forward to tomorrow," but it was for someone else
I replied "Huh? We aren't meeting tomorrow, this is Miku..." like this
Don't eat it!
I realized becuase of this mistake
Also got a fork in his other hand
Probably underestimated me
At least look at her face
I'm not like that
-Yeah
Just had to say it
If I go out with Miku, I won't cheat
Has to say it
-Who'd want to cheat with you?
True
I know
Miku
Don't touch her!
Touching people without moving
Like you
Are you drunk? Your face is hot!
So happy, really happy
Soft and sticky, really cute
Smells so good
-Eh, it smells good?
Yeah
Like
Good morning
-Good morning, Mina
It's been a long time.
-Yeah
Today, because Kuro-chan said he likes "rock climbing"
I want to go to the place where you can do it
Have you ever done it?
-No
Bowling
Want to use the bowling pin?
Will it be hard?
Where is the bowling pin?
Ah, this is quite difficult
It's pretty scary
He does this a lot
-Really?
Seems so hard
Huh?
Wait, wait, wait
So high! Wait!
Ah wait, no
No rope
Mina wants to try it.
-Want to try?
Then you try
I'll do it, then
It's not that easy!
Cute
Put your hands here, your feet are free, right?
Seems pretty good at it
She's young, after all
Can you do it?
Eh? Eh?
Whoa, Mina is so good at this
Aren't I good? I guess I'm good at it
She's shown him up
Smiling as she went, so much energy!
So dirty!
Where does he usually sleep?
I was really happy!
Looks great
-Yeah
So fashionable, I want to take pictures
It'd be a shame not to
Let's take as shot together
Shoot
So natual
Ok, cheese!
Let's eat
So cute!
Have you joined any club activities?
Disney Club
Disney Club?
-Yeah
We all go to Disneyland together
And watch movies and stuff
What is the ratio of male to female students?
Uh, probably more men, I guess?
They're trying to pick up girls?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
What would you do if you got hit on?
Getting worried
What are you talking about?
"I like Kuro-chan"
Will you say it? Will you say you like me?
-Is it better to keep it a secret?
That's fine, then
Is that OK?
So cute
Ginza
Kuro-chan
Ah Richi
It's been a long time since I've seen you.
-Long time no see
Where are we going?
There is a place I want to take Kuro-chan to
Hey wait, you brought a lot of things?
For the sauna
Wait, wait, wait, wait, you should have told me earlier
-Let's go to the sauna
You should have told me, I haven't brought anything
Sauna?
This place?
-Yeah
Going in together?
Super trendy, huh?
Not together, surely?
Very clean
You went to a sauna with Shoji, didn't you?
Rock bath
Oh, so awesome.
-Awesome!
Kind of nervous right, in this sort sauna with an erotic vibe
-Erotic sauna
I'll go change. See you later
Richi are you still not ready? So hot!
So hot, so hot on the back
I've been waiting for a long time.
-Richi
Ah
Different from usual
Stop staring!
Really?
Oh, awesome!
Indeed
It's like this...
No problem, right?
This sporty vibe is awesome
What "no problem"?
Really suits you
Ah, it's hot!
Wow, awesome
So, Richi, are you competing?
To go out first
Go out?
Who can stay longer?
That's right!
Ah, yes, yes, I got it wrong
Why do I have to say it again? Richi
You said it as if the first one out wins
Ah no no
The winner must fulfill one request
Absolutely cannot lose
Is that okay?
-Yes
That's it then
Shall we start right away?
Richi, start!
Okay, here we go
Ah, Richi, your face is sweating more than your body?
Wow, really?
-Yeah
Kuro-chan is so excited
I'm look forward to your makeup running
Why?
What'll it look like?
So disgusting
So hot, so hot...
What are you looking forward to?
It's not working anymore, right?
Hurry up and get out!
So hot, so hot...
Such a classic play
It's...it's not working. It's not working
Like the old skit from The Drifters
It's hot! It's hot!
This is what you do as a comedian
Win!
Richi laughs very happily
I didn't see that kind of smile in Okinawa
Seeing Richi smiling so happily
Made me like her even more
The sauna is great
Yes, so happy-
We have a bet, right?
-What?
Hmm?
Well, what did you say?
Eh?
Don't you remember?
What?
The winner gets one request
Have you thought about it already?
I have always wanted to ask you for something
Me?
-Yes, a request
Request... i'll do whatever I can
You have a request for Kuro-chan?
I want to know your contact information
Ah, yes
Then let's trade.
-Oh, that's great
Great!
Can I have the queen's
Let's send messages every day!
-Hmm
Queen?
Then, Richi, grill to your heart's content.
-Awesome
Wow, look's great!
He's watching!
-Her mouth
Mmmm, so soft
Is he looking inside again?
He's looking
Pretending to be eating, but actually peeking
Eating with Richi makes the food even more delicious
Yeah, everything's delicious if you eat with someone you like
You're a good talker!
Has Richi taken classes recently?
Singing
And dance with everyone
How to put it? The last time I saw you
The recording?
-Yeah
I was just focused on producing
That day was super scary
Scary?
The feeling of "Producer Kuro-chan"
Kuro-chan-san
Don't say it like Ms. Agnes Chan
It was that kind of feeling
Ignored
So I was very nervous before the meeting today
Completely ignored
Right now, completely
I just want to find the girl who liked me in Okinawa
I really like Richi
But the thought of you saying "like" to everyone is...
Yeah, he's said it to everyone
Feels kind of weightless
It doesn't have any weight?
-Yeah
If Kuro-chan likes everyone
And you've said "I genuinely want to find someone and be together with them"
Does that mean that you'd go out with anyone
No
To think that two people other than me would also date Kuro-chan like this
It's even more intense than that
It's a bit worrying
Clinging to each other at the planetarium
I want to know who you care about the most
Thinking about it
It's really Richi
Really
It's hard to say
Really?
This guy is a liar!
Richi is not lying either, right?
No lies!
I believe in you!
A very angry face
Trust me
Ah, it's burnt. It's burnt
Now you've dated all 3 people
When will you confess?
About this
I've narrowed it down to 2 people
2 people?
Yeah
There's 1 person that is a wrong choice
But I haven't decided who to choose between the other two
I want to go out with these 2 people again
Then I can decide, is that OK?
Understood
By the way, who is the one who is eliminated?
Mina
Mina?
-Yes
If she is sincere, this is the end of the project
No problem. Absolutely not. Absolutely not
The other 2 people are genuine
I'll tell you now, then
Mina
Lied
I knew it, that one...
So scary
So close, so close...
I'm sorry, I'm a little...
I don't know if i'm happy or not, but I'm sorry
Didn't like her?
I've been lying
At that time in Okinawa
The buffalo time?
We were very close
Always holding hands
It was kind of...
Super... disgusting
That was close. That was close
If we hadn't dated, I would have thought it was Mina
That liked me
Is that right?
Dating is critical, absolutely
That... sorry
Please let me go on a real date with Miku and Richi!
Therefore, Mina is eliminated
What?
So, the remaining choices for Kuro-chan are Richi and Miku
He guessed correctly
Impressive
Or he actually saw through...
-Yeah
Awesome
Mina was pretending
Buffalo experience
Buffalo experience... no no
A buffalo experience would be pulling a cart while on all fours
This is called a buffalo experience
What they did was a buffalo ride
It's not right
Yeah...
-Do we have to do this again?
That's not right...sorry
-I've learned
Please heat up the atmosphere at once
-No, no, no
So who, out of Richi and Miku, is sincere?
The planetarium
That part was quite impressive
So I think its Miku
Quite intimate
It's hard to fake it...
-It can't be acting, right?
I think it is impossible to act it
So, you think Miku is sincere
I think it's Miku
It should be Miku, right?
But the kiss...
Richi
Miku just kissed him on the cheek
Richi actually kissed him
But either way they're both very hardworking
Don't say hardworking
It is hard work, though
But its to debut as an idol
They'll do anything
So bad, don't say that
No, not that they would do anything
Is that what being an idol is about?
No, no, no, it was to shut him up
I don't think so
Are all idols like this?
-To shut him up
What?
What he said is obvious
It's so comfortable.
-The view is great too
What do you think?
Delicious
That's good. Give me a bite too
Ok
Eat up!
Don't breathe!
It's delicious!
It's obviously a matcha cake, but the cheese flavor is also very strong
Yes, it is obviously a matcha cake, but the cheese flavor is also very strong
It also has the flavor of Richi~
He's mocking her
A cold smile
It also has the taste of Kuro-chan
Yes? Really?
Wait!
Are you thinking "what do I say now?"
Must be
A loss for words
After adding you on LINE, I'm super happy every day.
-Right?
Send LINE every day
Didn't Michopa announce her marriage?
At that time I was very shocked
We talked on LINE
-Yes
Do you remember?
I said "One less competitor"
You replied "great"
Seeing this reply
I decided that afterwards I liked Richopa instead of Michopa
Don't use my name to name someone else
Thanks to Richopa, I'm so energetic now
Richi may think this is just for the cameras
That I say these things
But I really mean everything I say
Really
I've been watching Wednesday Downtown
It's strange for me to say this
But i'm glad you liked me because of watching me
I really like Kuro-chan
And not just because of the program
So really
Now Kuro-chan is in front of me
I feel like i'm in a dream
You did love projects in the past
And have been pranked so many times
Every time I look watch, I think "I want to make him happy"
So this time
Very heartfelt
What?
So this time it is up to me to put an end to those pranks and make Kuro-chan happy
Awesome
Not even a single tear came out
Will this be the end of it?
What is this?
She's laughing
You're so caring, I've obviously been making you cry
Is she moved or just finds it funny?
If you say so, if you are not sincere, I will really storm out
If it's all a lie, i'll really storm out
"I'll really storm out"
Ah, sorry Richi, I forgot
I forgot this is about time together with Richi
Because Richi said, "I want a gift" in the past
I bought something
That face
Can I add one more request?
Add another one?
-Yeah
I want something I can carry with me
A gift from Kuro-chan
Jewelry?
No, anything is fine
Really, just something small is fine
That will make me think of Kuro-chan
Something that will make me feel like you're with me
I kept my promise!
What?
What a beautiful box
A present
A necklace
Eh?
An hourglass necklace
Why an hourglass?
That's good
Is it good?
For example, if you're angry
Or have a bad day
Can't wear this
No matter what, you can always go back
That's the meaning
That's true
Not happy at all
Also, later on
There may be quarrels and many things will happen
But, no matter what, we can always go back and return to the two people who like each other the most
We can fall in love again
-Yeah
Good taste
So happy
I especially like the park
It's more fun to come with you
Aki-kun, you said you wanted to eat my bento
So I made one
This girl is very much like true love
So cute!
Handmade bento
Happy, I'm so happy!
It might not taste good, though
Awesome
Cute, super cute!
This is painted on the cling film
-That's right
Small octopus sausage!
-Yes
I want to put MIKU's love into my body
Please put it in
What is this? Oh, plum?
-Yeah
Do you need to be so shocked?
Delicious
Due to plum
It's good.
-Great!
Do I have something stuck here?
Nothing is stuck, okay?
Stop it, please, it's disgusting
Take it off!
I can taste the taste of Miku's hands!
Everyone please watch quietly
"I can taste the taste of Miku's hands!"
He's playing dumb
In fact, there is nothing
I can taste the taste of Miku's hands!
Tasted Miku's hands!
Very funny
She's laughing
So cute
Laughing though, right?
So happy, this is happiness, right?
If they like each other, then its ok, right?
I have something I want to ask
If they like each other...
-That's right
My principle is not to fall in love with idols
He's said it before
If I ask you not to be an idol, will you give it up?
Yes, what are you going to do?
I'll give up if you want me to
Thank you
Don't laugh, Matsumoto
You're not supposed to laugh at this part
Then I'm relieved
Great!
I really can't fall in love with idols
I can't lie to myself
I like you
So I just want you to be mine alone
Ok
Isn't it better to support her dream?
I like your honesty
Impressive
Miku Miku
Then you'll be just mine
-Yes
Gross
I already am
Me too
Its love, right?
That hurts!
Ouch!
What?
Who?
You scared me to death
-Long time no see
Long time no see indeed
What did you just do? It hurts!
How are you? It's been a long time.
-Yes, i'm good
I need your help buying something
What? So sudden?
Have you got a girl you like again?
Bingo
Want to buy another pendant box?
I'm not buying that.
-You're not?
Come, come, let's go
Please, help me choose
Just follow the trend of this action down
Hello
The seniors
The MONSTER IDOL members
AiKA·THE·SPY
KAEDE PHOENiX
NAO·OF·NAO
First meeting
We are Mameshiba no Taigun
I really like you
Really? That's a great thing to say
-Really?
Always listening and singing your songs
So happy
So nervous
So cute
So happy
Today is the first meeting
A little nervous
Everyone is so cute
You are especially cute
Have you all been tortured by Kuro-chan?
All victims
We have had a lot of interactions with him
Good way to put it
Do you the 3 of you really like Kuro-cha?
Some do
Do you all know?
No
-You don't?
Really?
By the way, does his mouth stink?
What a question?
Really stinks
It stinks, doesn't it?
Seems like I'm the only one who thinks it stinks
If it stinks, say it stinks
You really don't think it stinks?
Doesn't stink at all...
Did you get up close?
-Yes
I kissed his face
A shriek of terror
Kissed his face?
Eh? The mouth... not there, right?
I have
Mouth-to-mouth? Mouth-to-mouth?
They're all so surprised
Unimaginable
-Yeah
Was it difficult?
Difficult
"Was it difficult?"
But it might also be because you like him
-Yeah
Really? I'm so curious
Here here here
Engagement rings
What kind of girl is she?
Want to see?
-Yes
Her
And her
And? What?
2 people again?
Don't say "again."
-Two people again?
I'm torn.
-What about the ring?
You buying two?
No, no, it's for one person
They are quite familiar with each other
Yes, indeed. Kicked him when she saw him
What to do, seriously
Who should I give it to?
Which one do you think is better?
-I like this 310,000 one
※Just under $2500
Why? Why this?
Because it's shiny
Yes, 319,000 yen
Okay, then I've decided
It's expensive
I want the simple one
※Just over $2600
It's 340,000
Are you not satisfied?
You were the one who said you wanted my advice
This is the case, the final decision needs to be made by me
So which girl are you giving it to?
Have you decided?
I haven't decided yet
To be honest, I'm struggling
Have you decided who to confess your love to?
So dirty
Yes, i've decided
But it is difficult
I've been wondering who's real and who's not
But ultimately I have not decided by this standard
What do you mean?
I still want to choose to confess to the girl I like the most from the bottom of my heart
So, if she doesn't really like me after confession
I won't regret it either
I may have liked one more from the start
But I want them to know my true feelings
And for them to become my girlfriend
I see
An hourglass necklace
That can be reversed
Mikitty doesn't seem to like the necklace very much
It's a bit lame, isn't it?
No, no
Someone must like it
It's not the necklace's fault
Saying "you can turn back time" is the most lame thing
It's still lame!
No, I'm talking about Kuro-chan's taste.
-Yes, yes, yes
The girl made bento, I think maybe they were in Odaiba?
Them eating bento together, it really felt like love
It was tough to see anything else
But it's possible that the bento was prepared by the staff.
-No way!
Can you quit it with that sort of thing!?
Doing such a cute little rice ball, would such a nice thing come to this mind of this program's staff?
What?
But after all, it's handmade, so, when you compare the two, Miku is more attentive.
-True
This girl, the one that got the hourglass
-Richi
Just receiving
Maybe its not good to say it, but she didn't give anything
The girl did not do anything
-She did
Maybe that's a bad thing to say.
-Indeed
But I think it's good for Kuro-chan to choose the girl he likes
That's was good point at the end.
-That's the only thing that's good
I seem to be a little nervous
So much has happened
To be honest, I didn't want to say this but...
I am grateful to the program team
If the program team did not give me this opportunity
I may have never had the chance to find a girlfriend
It's thanks to Wednesday that i've been able to meet a girl I really like
Truthfully, I really appreciate it
No, no, we also hope you can confess and find a girlfriend successfully
So, Miku and Richi are both waiting for Kuro-chan
He'll choose one
Who will Kuro-chan meet?
A little nervous
Is it Miku?
I think it'll be Miku, seems that way
Hasn't his mouth been stinking for a bit too long?
From the start with Mameshiba no Taigun
The stench is very persistent
So, be careful
-I'm off
Go!
Go for it!
Wearing a hat now
Who was chosen?
Who is it?
I see...
-Richi
Did you wait long, cold?
You came
-Sorry
I thought you would go to Miku
Crying
Why? Why do you think so?
So happy
Poor thing
Miku, Kuro-chan went to Richi
Ok... ok
Ok
So that's it...
I don't understand, can't tell if its real or not
Both crying
Would you cry if you're lying?
Nothing can be done
I've worked hard
What does it mean?
I'm a little late
Sorry if it's cold
What are you talking about?
It's okay
She's wearing the necklace
Richi, are you happy to be an idol?
I'm happy
You're happy?
-Yeah
What are you practicing?
I see them both every day
We danced, practiced singing, ate together, and had a lot of fun
Wow, really wearing that lame thing
Not lame at all
All getting acquainted.
-Yeah
By the way, does you actually like Kuro-chan?
Does she?
In terms of Kuro-chan...
We've only known each other for 2 months
But it seems we have known each other for a long time
We have known each other since a long time ago
I feel so too
But for me
I've seen you on TV since about 5 years ago
At that time, I thought that you might live near me
And then every day, every day, I thought
Maybe I'll see Kuro-chan when I go out
Seems pretty real
So I was happy going out everyday
I've been excited to go out every day for the past 5 years
Looking forward to meeting Kuro-chan
Really?
That's how I suddenly found myself liking you
In my heart you have been by my side for 5 years
Really?
It started so long ago.
-Yes
So, that we can meet and talk like this
It always feels so incredible to me
Every time I meet with you, it feels like a dream
Do you really like Kuro-chan?
I do not really like Kuro-chan
That means...
Great acting
So you've been lying the whole time?
Yes, I've been lying
What's up with this kid!?
You've become an idol.
-Yeah
Her acting skills are too strong, right?
So why did you insist on lying?
That's amazing.
-Acting skills are too good
Initially the goal was to become an idol after being confessed to by Kuro-chan
So I've been trying to get Kuro-chan to confess to me as a goal
So I worked hard to reach this goal until the end
She's worked hard
I was determined to stay until the end to let Kuro-chan confess to me
I worked hard for my goal
That means
May I tell you what I think?
Yes
Richi, 2 months ago, you were 1 of 9 girls
From the very beginning I thought you were so cute
You reluctantly showed me the inside of your mouth
Made you feel embarrassed
After going to Okinawa to buy groceries, you said you didn't want me to think of you as a casual woman
It made me think "I want to protect you"
Since then, I thought about you a lot
Can't help but laugh at that line
I came here today
It's not to know if you really like me or if you're lying
Why I came...
True feelings
I am a person who always makes the wrong choice
My decisions never lead to anything good
I was nice to a girl, but she dumped me
But I now believe that this love of mine is real
I came here because of genuine feelings
You said you like me, and I really like you
This like of mine, this love
Don't laugh!
This is my final love
A little too long
Although I have no self-confidence
Say you like her, confess already!
Although I say a lot and get carried away
I still haven't had a girlfriend in ten years
I also almost do not know how to fall in love
I
The one in front of me, Richi, I like
If you are willing to accept this kind of me
Coming
-Here we go
Please go out with me
Please
She likes him, right?
Kuro-chan
First of all, thank you for your confession
What's going on?
But I want to confirm one thing
Confirm?
Do you have to give up being an idol to go out with Kuro-chan?
Here it is. Here's the problem
Eh...
Although I signed up because I like you
Eh?
I ended up becoming a member of the group
I've been surrounded by girls who wanted to become idols
I know they all took this opportunity very seriously
I feel bad for them that I am the one able to debut as an idol
So I decided to make a serious effort to be recognized by everyone
I've held on to the determination to practice being an idol with everyone
This is a good thing
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
-So
I want to be like you said, 3 people trying to work towards becoming leading idols
I want to work towards this goal
So I want to continue to be an idol
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Wait...wait...what's going on?
Wait, can I confirm?
Do you like me, or have you been lying?
I signed up because I like you
Do you want to fall in love with Kuro-chan?
I really like him
Wait, wait, wait, why are you crying? Why are you crying?
Wait wait wait Richi, calm down, calm down
Tell yourself that!
Richi
I signed up because I like you
But I also always wanted to become an idol
Wait, wait, wait!
Although the plan was different, we are now idols
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Suddenly... Richi, wait, that
Are you thinking straight right now?
Speak for yourself!
Cursing himself
You liked me from the beginning, right?
Yes
If you like me then that's enough
I know it's fun to be an idol
I know working hard will make you happy
But your fondness for me is true love, right?
You've worked hard because you like me, right?
Yes
Think about your first thoughts, your first feelings
Hey, staff, what's going on here?
Indeed, there is nothing wrong with it
Does this make sense?
It's weird!
She signed up because she liked me but this is the result? Do you think it is reasonable?
Don't you think it's outrageous?
Absolutely unreasonable
I can't do this
I came to erase the memories of heartache
Say something!
"Say something"
-There is nothing to say
Impossible to say
Richi this is wrong, its wrong
This, this, this
Scary
I bought a ring
This one I bought is the most expensive
I really like you
The price doesn't matter
I bought such an expensive one so that it can be used as a wedding ring
It cost 340,000. 340,000!
What are you saying it!
Much better than in MONSTER IDOL and MONSTER HOUSE
This love is completely different
That was like puppy love
With Richi...
I can't live without you
I understand, I understand, I know you have a dream
I, I really like you
Richi
You said it, you said it
It was you who said you didn't want to see me in pain
Can't stand to see it
That's why I said "I want to make you happy" in the cafe
Didn't you say so, Richi?
I took it all seriously
Don't give up
You're all I have. That's what I've always thought
I really I ah I really
Talking nonsense
I really love Richi
Now it's time to get down to business
Richi
Eh...
How...
How... how... how to do it?
He's broken
Scary!
I really like... you
He's broken!
He's starting to laugh now
Parts are dropping out now
Richi
Being an idol, or me, I want you to think clearly about which one you want
So scary
Really, I'm like a clown
Emotions are out of control
I have never liked a person so much
The more I like someone, the more timid I become. I'm scared
I don't know what to do anymore
Because it's you I like so much
I've never liked anyone this much
Please give me a chance, Richi!
Let me confess once more
Think back again
It's gone on long enough
Turn the hourglass of the necklace upside down once more
Here we go. Here comes the role of necklaces
Turning back the clock
-Turn back the clock
Let me confess once again
You are the only one in my eyes
You are the only one I like
With me, such a lame me
Please take this. Go out with me
Please
Please, Richi
Sorry, I'm so torn
Kuro-chan
Please go out with me
Seriously?
Really?
Really? Richi?
Think again!
-No, no, no
You're not lying to me, are you?
Don't! Refuse!
Please go out with me
Richi
No, right?
RICHI says "Please go out with me, sorry I'm so torn"
Calm down!
-Richi, calm down
Sorry
Richi, think again, Richi!
Are you sure its okay?
Sorry to make you cry
I will always cherish you
What are you doing?
Scary scary scary
Nothing like each other
They like each other!
It's horrible
No, no, no. So scary.
Look at Richi's expression
I'm not letting go
Coming again
-From below again
Another kiss from below
-It's coming again. It's coming again
Here we go!
How many times do you want to kiss. Hey, hey, hey
-No, no, no, no
Still sticking out the tongue, also sticking out the tongue
Look, look, look, look.
-It's too hard on my eye
Don't do it
RICHI is so happy!
-Enough, enough!
You're mine. You're mine, Richi
Really?
Michopa, look at Kuro-chan's great expression!
Richi, let me put the ring on your finger.
-Ok
Seriously?
-Yes
Probably also very torn
The engagement ring is on the left hand. We're saving it for the wedding.
-Yes
Please give me your right hand
So cute, so beautiful
It suits you
Show me
So great
So beautiful
So happy
I've cried over so many things
I love you
Not finished
Too much!
Looks so happy
I did it!
Yes, 3rd time's the charm!
Too good, too good, Richi, Richi
Looks so happy
You are mine
So cute
It's so cute, Richi
You are mine!
I'll never let you go
Enough already!
I was so panicked for a moment
I thought you didn't want me anymore
You're not going to change your mind again, are you?
No
Ah the sound!
My mouth doesn't stink, right?
It stinks a bit
Spoken with great affection
Enough!
It doesn't stink!
Everyone
-Really?
It went well
-In summary, Kuro-chan and Richi are together
That's great
-Congratulations!
Well, good for them
They've got everyone's blessing, right?
Hamada's volume was really loud at the moment of confirming the relationship
"Eh!?"
Exceeded the volume of the "here are the results"
It's really bigger than the "here are the results"
It's the first time I've heard it louder than "here are the results"
No, no, no.
-It was surprising
Really surprising
I really thought it would not work
Kuro-chan's expressions were very interesting
Too much kissing too
The kissing was too much
What was your reaction when kissing
From below
What was everyone's reaction? Unpleasant?
These two
Mikitty, Michopa and Hamada
They kissed a little too much, right...
-It was too much
My stomach's hurting watching it
But its been a long road for him
It's emotional that it's over right?
Because the kisser is ugly, you don't want to see the kiss scene
Now it is better not to say such things
It's not that kind of time anymore
-It's not those times anymore
But after the confession...
If Kuro-chan is a handsome man, you'd love watching it
But immediately after the successful confession, kissed
So you're all disgusted
That reflects badly on your worldview!
What a pain
You're all out of touch with the times
It has nothing to do with whether Kuro-chan is ugly or not
Personality
-Yes
Seeing Kuro-chan like this
It has nothing to do with whether he is a handsome man
He just has a bad personality
The bottom of the bottom of the bottom of garbage men
Why is this happy ending getting such a bad response?
The kiss at the beginning is not even a kiss
Just biting lips, its gross
Like a unicorn sucking on the sap
Just say sucking the sap
That's not going to happen, is it?
Will the hourglass necklace be sold out from tomorrow?
This is going to sell out!
-No way
The same model as Kuro-chan's
-No way!
Its sold out on Amazon
Please buy it as soon as possible
Production has been stopped.
-Production has not stopped
This Christmas, get the hourglass necklace as Kuro-chan for a gift
So, everyone has said so much already
Let's have them both come out
The couple, Kuro-chan and Richi, please come out
Congratulations
Congratulation
-Congratulations to everyone!
Congratulations
-Thank you all
Is it true?
It's true.
-It's true
That's great.
-That's great, Kuro-chan
Really good
Although it's great
Do the women have to say such things?
It's too much, isn't it?
-It's true, Hamada too
No, you kissed too much
Because I liked her so much, I just wanted to make sure
Do you think it's OK?
I was very happy
Really?
Richi, what do you think about what Mikitty just said?
It's really outrageous.
-It's too much, right?
Didn't think they'd come out
What a mess!
Mikitty, please apologize to Richi
Apologize. Apologize to her first
No, I'd rather bend than break
You've gone too far
I don't want to apologize against my will
What do you think?
I think it's too much...
It's too much, isn't it?
It's really too much
"Richopa"
Not happy to be called that, right?
I really think of you as my greatest love rival
No, no, you don't have to
Then you win!
Michopa also has her eyes on Kuro-chan
Michopa has lost
Don't say it, give me a break!
You guys are good together. Really.
-Michopa, Michopa, Michopa. Sorry
It's like a wedding reception!
Don't you have anything to ask?
How many dates have you had together since?
Because it cannot be exposed
So, we have to keep it secret until the show airs.
-Keep it a secret
We haven't met up in public
That means you went to Kuro-chan's dirty place?
It's not dirty, it's just a lot of stuff
It's just messy
She'll help with the cleaning, right?
From now on
There will be various considerations and countermeasures, right?
Did you go?
-Did you go to Kuro-chan's?
Yes, I've been there.
-You've been
After all, we are dating
Stayed over?
Not yet?
-Of course she has
Of course
Because we're dating!
Indeed
It's normal
Normal
Do you still think it's okay after going through all this?
Yes, I like him even more
Would you break up afterwards?
What do you mean, Matsumoto?
And this...?
This?
This thing
It's okay to be with this thing after this experience?
Yes
Because the Wednesday team installed something in the bedroom and living room
Camera, right?
24-hour surveillance cameras
It's still there
So while I was thinking about alternatives
But I think the first time must also be in bed
What are you talking about...
-But the room has...
24-hour surveillance cameras
So I used tape to wrap the camera in a towel
And that's how the night went
After all, you're a couple
Indeed
After this episode airs, you'll start dating normally?
Of course, we'll be dating like crazy
Is it okay to be his girlfriend?
It's okay to be pelted with stones, right?
Remember to bring a helmet
Even when walking outside there will be no pelting, it's fine
Richi, do you know who the culprit of the cookie incident was?
No, I don't know
That episode hasn't been broadcast yet
Didn't say?
What do you mean you didn't say? That thing that everyone...
The culprit who smashed the cookies to pieces was
The Okinawa incident
-It's nobody's fault. It's nobody's fault
I don't know
Even if we find the culprit, what can we do?
We went through it all together, everyone was sad
No, the culprit has been found
As a producer, these things happen
No, we know who the culprit is
You know best who the culprit is
The day of the broadcast will also be exposed
Eventually it will be exposed
You'd better be honest with Richi
The culprit who smashed the cookies to pieces was
The offender is
Miku
Hey! What a piece of crap
You're such a piece of crap
Too disgusting
Didn't Miku make it?
It wasn't
Don't lose your memory without permission!
Do you really want it to be revealed?
You have to say it
There are many complex reasons for that incident
I did it
Eh...
I did it. Oh, it was me
So shocked
Totally stunned
The hot love has been dunked in cold water
Lying to you, lying to you, lying to you
It's not a lie!
It was hard at that time, wasn't it?
Very difficult
No, no, no
Made you look bad
Made her look bad!
Don't make people cry!
But Richi is super cute when she cries
No, don't say that either
Because they are a couple
Isn't Richi going to quit the group?
Yes, that's right
What do you think, Richi?
I did come to this project at the beginning because I like Kuro-chan
This goal or this dream has been achieved
This point has been accepted
So I'm quitting
Want to quit?
-Yes
If not
It would be hard to get support as an idol while being Kuro-chan's girlfriend, right?
That's what Kuro-chan thinks, right? That's what idols are all about
I am trying to support her
But idol's can't fall in love, this is an important thing
So I weighed it out and wanted her to be my girlfriend instead
So since Kuro-chan has a girlfriend now
You are retiring from the entertainment industry
Why? It's not right. It's not right
You need to retire
Don't say its great and it's a relief, Michopa
Not so
Not quitting?
Not quitting
I will continue as a member of Yasuda Dai Circus
And incidentally, I'd like to mention
We have a video of Richi talking to the other two members about this
Being confessed to by Kuro-chan
We've decided to date
Because of that choice, I can't continue with you
Take a break?
-Yes
This kid is amazing
Take a break
That...
There is something I must report to the two of you
What... what... is it bad?
Being confessed to by Kuro-chan
We've decided to date
I didn't know!
So Richi is the one that really liked Kuro-chan?
I thought it was Miku
No, I thought it was either of you
Really?
It was close. Almost got stolen
Do you guys really think Kuro-chan is disgusting?
Uh...
My comments in the interviews were always "disgusting"
I said "I'm trying so hard to act"
I kissed him on the cheek
You're really strong. You don't even like him.
-And slept next to him
I slept on his arm
The person that likes him is still here, you know
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry
Does Richi hate me a little?
Really super annoying
You'd surely hate it, right? Doing those things to the person you like...
Super jealous... I might be the most jealous of you
Going after him in front of me the whole time
It was impressive
This girl is really impressive
So, do you want to continue your idol career?
I kept thinking about it when I was confessed to
Ultimately, I chose Kuro-chan
Really...?
So I can't continue with the both of you
Really? Decided?
Was it your decision?
Or was it a decision made only after being told by Kuro-chan?
Kuro-chan kept saying "I won't date an idol"
So this was the basis of the decision
I think the final decision was Richi's
But I think we need Richi
If Kuro-chan confessed to me
Although this is not a good approach
Richi would have been able to stay in the group
This is a huge opportunity
And you've worked hard for this opportunity
But I've given it a lot of thought
Although only for a short period of time
Being with the two of you
I've really been happy every day
Its thanks to the two of you that i've been able to work so hard
It's hard to say but...
Really thanks for everything
Sad, right
-Sad but it ended well, at least
That's what happened
So, you two really are a couple
Congratulations
Thank you
Kuro-chan's love is even stronger now
Kuro-chan is crying
I've just realized this sort of thing happened
I didn't even know these three had talked about such topics
This is the first time you saw it?
I feel that I have brought a lot of pressure to these 3 people
That's true
You have put pressure on all the people of Japan
It's not just about putting pressure on these 3 people
More than 3 people?
It is these 3 people who suffer the most
Then, let's talk about this directly
Eh?
Let's get these two out on stage too
You fooled me!
What a great actor.
-Strong
These 2 people worked hard to the end
It's hard, isn't it?
The buffalo, at that time
Buffalo
Holding hands...
Buffalo experience
No, no, no
A buffalo experience is being on all fours dragging a plow
The time you rode in the buffalo cart?
At that time, we were holding hands
Indeed
-Very close
I felt sick to my stomach
I can't believe you just said that
Richi likes me
She likes me
Miku really worked hard!
Can you cry on command?
Tears were shed at once
As a child, I was a child actor for a while
Make an effort and you can cry
Thinking about Kuro-chan makes it easy to cry?
No not at all
What was on your mind when you cried?
Thinking of something like the death of grandpa
What dead grandpa?
Thinking of your grandpa can make you cry the most?
You had to think about grandpa a lot
I put my grandfather's memories over here
Scary!
They all really want Richi to stay in the group, right?
Really want her to stay
Want to go on as 3 people
She was able to capture Kuro-chan's heart so well
That means you have the potential to be an idol, right?
Indeed, can capture the fans' hearts too
That's right, it's definitely possible
High potential
Now it's a 2-person team. What should they do, Kuro-chan?
Well, I also think just 2 people is not enough
So we can host some auditions
No, don't do it without permission
Why?
What is it? What is it?
Downtown, can't I advertise here?
On this show
How about it?
That's kinda annoying
Why? No its not, right?
I didn't expect Matsumoto to be so reluctant
Please, please, please!
RICHI, help me out
-Why are you asking Richi?
This group has nothing to do with her
It's true.
-Because she's my girlfriend
Ok its fine then I guess
There you go.
-Good
Please apply for the auditions!
There we go
Okay, thanks
I didn't get cold feet, I just said the usual thing
We know
No one said anything
You didn't play dumb either
No, I'm not playing dumb
Because no one will laugh
It hurts to hear you say that
Wow, so boring
Really unfunny
Super unfunny
No one laughed
How do you feel about your unfunny boyfriend?
That's too harsh to ask
Unfunny boyfriend
Use the hourglass to rewind time a bit
Rewind the time to the point where it wasn't lame
Rewind it quickly
Safe. We've gone back
It's not safe at all
What a convenient necklace
Although originally it was supposed to be these three
The group will soon appear on the CDTV Special New Year Live Live special
Awesome!
Gaining momentum quickly!
Just two people?
No, Richi's idol activities have also been extended
She will be a member until that point
Three people are needed
-Great!
So, this is the end of Kuro-chan's love story
Yes, thank you all
Your love story ending means...
Officially graduating from Wednesday Downtown
Graduation?
-Yeah
Why? Why?
I'm not graduating, the relationship has nothing to do with it
Because
No one is interested in your happiness
Matsumoto! How could you?
As Matsumoto said
Messing up my private life?
Can't you mess up my private life?
Don't you hate it? Being filmed by the camera all the time
The cameras installed in your place have all been removed
No, no, no. Please put them back
Definitely better with a camera
It's not better, Richi will come round
It's okay, it's okay
It's okay to be seen, right~?
It's not okay.
-Definitely don't want to be filmed
Richi, lets have hot pot
Here's to Richi and Kuro-chan's first dinner at home
Let me see your mouth
Richi, lets have hot pot
It's off, look!
Very impressive, right? Be careful
It is a compatible umbrella
Like
Sucked in, sucked in!
Get on with it
It's done!
So here's to RICHI and Kuro's first dinner at home
-Cheers!
It's so hot, it's hard to put your mouth down, help me blow
You ate it!
It's delicious
Let me see your mouth
Open up a bit
More, more, more
I see it, I see it
Nice, nice!
Bedtime, bedtime!
Couple's clothes now
Yes, it's the same
I've really needed a pair of good pajamas, now i've got them!
The pajamas are so cute
Try the hood
So cute!
Eh? Super cute, right?
Your's also has ears
Cute
We should always be together!
Richi, let's sleep
So soft, so soft
Sort~
Smells so good!
Are you wearing perfume?
-No
You know, i'm not actually Kuro-chan, I'm Bear-chan
One word makes a difference
So happy
-So happy
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03