Okay everyone, let's begin!
Tonight, as our presenters, we'll be having these gentlemen.
Welcome!
Woah, so many!
It's Tamura Kenji, Chocolate Planet, and Kasuga!
TOOS!
Hey that was funny, do it again!
TOOOS!
That's pretty good!
Yeah, that's really funny.
Really funny.
Okay but did anybody even notice Kenji go cha~?
Wait, you didn't hear me?
It was right in the center! A center-cha.
Wow, you really cha-ed, huh.
Okay, let's get on with it.
Yes, that's right.
Okay everybody, it's what you've been waiting for...
It's an "everybody's theory" special.
Okay, who are we starting with?
I'll go first.
A real star duo.
Thank you.
Okay, so the theory we've chosen this time is this.
Even if you're at home alone, if somebody knocks on the door while you're on the toilet, you'll end up saying "I'm in here!"
No way, right? If you were alone?
Wouldn't you be too terrified?
You would, right?
Yeah, but before the fear sets in...
You'd reply by reflex.
Yeah, exactly.
I see. So it's fear versus reflex.
What do you think?
Well if it were a person's voice, I'd be scared, but I wonder if you could reply to a knock with a knock.
You might just reply with a knock.
It would only be really scary knowing for sure there's a person there.
A theory that says: even if you're at home alone, if somebody knocks on the door while you're on the toilet, you'll say "I'm in here!"
Kawai from Einstein.
A hidden camera has been placed in his home while he's living alone.
30 minutes pass until the time comes.
While Kawai enters the bathroom...
A staff member hiding on his balcony comes in.
Woah, that startled me!
Huh?
He locked it!
He didn't say "I'm here."
Since he didn't seem to be coming out, let's try it once more.
Woah!
What's going on?
It's Wednesday Downtown.
You can't do shit like this...
Die. Die, die, die, for real.
I really can't do this.
Do you know the line between right and wrong?
In conclusion, they didn't know.
In the end, he didn't say it.
Fear won.
Of course it would!
He locked the door so fast.
That would be so scary.
Okay, moving on.
Here's the next theory we've chosen for today.
No matter how unpalatable the food, if you were on a streak catching marshmallows in your mouth, you'd eat it
The targets this time were called in under the pretenses of a challenge.
Nadaru, from Colocolo Chittychitty Peppers.
How are you feeling?
Well, we've done it live once before.
He doesn't remember at all.
Quit similing at me.
The unpalatable thing Nishino will be throwing is...
Hornet larvae
Wow, he's good.
I didn't think he'd be this good at it.
Nadaru smoothly catches a number of marshmallows.
He keeps sticking his hand out.
He looks like Itsugi Hiroshi.
Did he notice it?
He ate it.
Larva
Marshmallow
Yuck.
He feels something is off, but he continues...
In total, three larvae entered his mouth
And now, to reveal the prank...
You put some wet thing in there.
Thanks for your work today.
I think I saw something funny.
What's all this?
What did you do?
Did you notice anything unusual?
Yeah, there was some kind of wet marshmallow
Yeah, the wet marshmallow!
What the hell did you do here?
Some wet marshmallow...
What's the prank?
What did you do with it?
Did you eat it?
Hold on, what?
The theory is that if you're catching marshmallows, you'd eat whatever nasty stuff that gets thrown in.
Here's what it was.
It was larvae??
Stag beetle larvae.
No, not stag beetle. Hornet larvae.
Oh, it was only hornet larvae.
Huh?
Wait, that's your reaction?
You're relieved?
As a kid I used to be fed hornet larvae.
By who?
My dad.
I always said that I didn't want to eat it
But at least it's not from a stag beetle
Chocolate Planet's selection from everybody's theories.
Moving on, we have...
Among the names of elementary schools and middle schools, the word "east" is particularly common
We'll take a look at the kanto region, and count up schools with "north," "south," "east," and "west" in their name.
Starting at the fourth most frequent, we have...
North, at 163 schools.
In third place...
West, at 213 schools.
In second place...
South, at 247 schools.
In the end, "east" was indeed the most frequent.
Now, according to our researchers, the reasoning for this was...
a mystery.
What are they on about?
East was most common.
If you're sitting in a sauna, you should be able to eat scalding foods with no problem.
Cause you'd already feel hot all over.
For our challengers this time, we have this pair, regulars of the show by now.
They're both mostly able to handle the temperature of the food under normal conditions.
The person who enters the sauna is decided by rock-paper-scissors.
Abarareru-kun's sauna is set to 99ºC.
Ikezaki's room, right outside, is 25ºC.
Two pieces left!
I think I can do it
However, Ikezaki's already down to his last egg.
Okay, I'm done! I'm done!
That's hot!
The air in here is unreal!
Being inside the sauna...
was the food any less hot?
No, of course it was hot!
The next theory from Chocolate Planet is...
If you put your pants on while the hem is sewn shut, you'll fall down
Yeah, of course you would.
Just outside our last location, we find Ikezaki again...
Right, that's what would happen.
The last theory chosen by Chocolate Planet today is...
Kids who complete a bike tour across Japan during their summer vacation would grow up to be splendid adults
This time our subjects are brothers who completed a bike tour of Japan in the summer of 1997.
The brothers started in Ashiya, Hyogo prefecture.
In 44 days, they completed a tour of Japan.
In total, they biked approximately 3,300 kilometers.
Furthermore...
They raised money for the Great Hanshin earthquake.
Participating in activities across the country, they helped with recovery from the earthquake...
In total, they raised nearly three million yen in contributions from Hyogo prefecture.
Surely, they would go on to be splendid people.
The phrasing here is scary...
It really is.
Are they gonna turn out OK?
Pleased to meet you.
Here's the older brother, Masamichi, who's now 34 years old.
At present, what is it that you do?
Currently, I do work related to the Guinness World Records.
He works for the Guinness World Records in Japan, spending his days alongside people who challenge the human limits.
So what about the younger brother, then?
He must be the bad one.
What I'd really like to do is support the people who endeavor.
I think it's a job that I can do to give back.
I'd say it's my calling.
And what is it that your brother is doing now?
Currently my brother's living in America...
and he's working for Apple.
In conclusion: they really became splendid adults.
So, Fujimon, what did you think?
How about that theory about schools with "east" in their name?
What was that?
Yeah, tell us what you thought about that one.
Well, uh...
Who cares?
No, wasn't it amazing?
There were twice as many with "east" than "north."
No, but...
You're messing with me.
You seemed to be most interested in that theory.
No, but I wasn't.
Was "east" in the name of the school you attended?
Well in high school it was, yeah, but...
Why would I have any reason to care about that?
Yeah, but in the end, "east" was the most popular.
What do you make of that?
It was clearly the most popular. By far.
Right, going off of that.
You're killing me.
I can't stand this.
Up next, everybody's theories, as chosen by Kasuga.
Okay, here are the theories we're doing today.
A theory that states the oldest property available for rent must be from the Edo period.
Really?
Well there's a lot of old buildings, you know.
I happen to have lived in one for twenty years myself, "Mutsumi-sou."
The building was made in 1966. A 55-year old building from the Showa era.
So if we hit the maximum age, it could be from the Edo period, right?
But you don't mean a sort of cultural building...
No, I mean a place you can actually live.
A theory that states the oldest property available for rent must be from the Edo period.
First, we'll look at the oldest property available for rent in Tokyo.
A run-down part of the Bunkyo ward.
This property here was built...103 years ago.
1919 (Taisho year 8).
A building that survived the Great Kanto earthquake and Tokyo firebombing.
It remains a property for people to rent.
For the curious, we'll take a look inside.
It's pretty nice.
The inside's nice, yeah.
Although it's been renovated several times, the space remains intact.
Currently, the rent for the property is 120,000 yen.
(approx. $1080 USD)
If you had been paying that for 103 years, the total would be 143,820,000 yen.
(Approx. $1.3M USD)
We talked to the current renters about their experience.
It gets super cold.
The temperatures...
Numbingly cold in the winter, and really hot in the summer.
The walls are super thin so we really hear the neighbors.
That's not so great.
Next, we'll expand our search to include the whole country.
In Fukuchiyama, Kyoto, we came across an even older building.
A detached house, currently seeking renters.
127 sq. meters, 6 rooms excluding dining and kitchen.
It may need some remodeling, but the rent is 50,000 yen.
(Approx. $450 US)
What's with those four adjacent "Japanese-style rooms"?
It was built 127 years ago.
Meiji 27. (1894)
Moving on, we have a detatched house in Yamazoe village, Yamabe, Nara prefecture.
204 sq. m, with 6 rooms excluding dining and kitchen.
The rent here is also 50,000 yen.
The kitchen reflects the time in which it was built, with a kamado wood-burning stove.
In the bathroom, there's a goemon-style bath, still functional.
Now, to reveal the age...
I'm afraid we only have one method to prove it, but...
It goes back 153 years ago.
The first year of the Meiji era [1872].
With a house available dating back to Meiji year 1, finding a house from the edo period was all but confirmed...
In what year do you the building was actually erected?
I think it would've been the end of the Edo period.
I can't be totally sure of it though...
With this, the theory is nearly proved.
But if we continue our investigation...
In Kamigyo ward of Kyoto, we found an unusually old building.
The property has a narrow frontage, and a long entryway.
In the past, taxes were applied to the frontage, so...
it was built to be narrow.
In the Edo period, there was a "frontage tax."
It seems that this sort of long, narrow property was typical of the era.
As for the building's age...
I've been told it was built 350 years ago.
Although there aren't documents confirming it, stories dating the building have been passed along.
Stories of a building from 1670...
We're renting and currently seeking tenants.
What's the rent?
80,000 yen.
The bathrooms have been recently renovated...
But you can really feel the age of the place through its still-functional well.
In conclusion: those interested should inquire.
Fujimon, your thoughts?
Well, I mean...
For the bathroom there, I think I would have preferred it in its original state, you know...
You'd take as it was, huh.
Are all the comments you make going to be that gloomy?
So strict!
Soooo strict.
Everyone's theories, as selected by Kasuga. Next up, we have...
If elementary schools kids asked Jimmy Onishi, "Jimmy, are you getting any?" he'd be so surprised that he couldn't reply.
Note: I'm not familiar with this gag— I'm pretty sure it's a dirty joke though...
Hello! This is Jimmy Onishi.
Today I'm here at the Edo Tokyo Museum.
We brought out Jimmy to a fake TV shoot.
Ok, all set.
We're gonna make arrangements to go in now, so please wait here for a bit.
Once he thinks the camera's stopped rolling...
Jimmy, are you getting any?
Sure ain't!
Damn, he's good.
Everyone's theories, as selected by Kasuga. Up next...
Somewhere, there must be a pair of sisters like Maya and Meena, where the elder dances and the younger tells fortunes.
In the RPG Dragon Quest IV, you encounter the Mahabala sisters, Maya and Meena.
Could there really be a pair of sisters living the same way?
For efficiency's sake, we'll start by approaching a fortune-teller.
I can't think of anybody here matching that description at present.
I'm afraid nobody comes to mind.
There was something like that in Dragon Quest, wasn't there?
I'm acquainted with a number of fortune tellers, but...
I can't think of anybody that fits the bill.
But among those we asked...
I myself am a fortune teller, and my younger sister is a dancer...
but I guess that's the opposite?
We found the inverse of the Mahabala sisters, with a fortune-telling elder sister and a dancing younger sister.
She's been in America, belly dancing in New York...
They were spot-on with the dancing and fortune-telling, but unfortunately in the wrong order...
Who cares if it's the wrong order?
But when we continued on with our search...
We came across a promising lead in Yokohama's Chinatown.
Welcome. A pleasure to meet you.
This is Ms. Hoshi, a fortune teller at the Four Pillars of Destiny.
We've heard that your sister is a dancer. Is that right?
My sister's practiced traditional Japanese dance since she was a girl.
The older sister is a practitioner of Japanese dance— that is to say, she's a dancer.
With this, we've found the real-world incarnation of Maya and Meena.
Have you been told before that you're just like Maya and Meena?
And who would they be?
Is it some kind of legendary tale?
Yeah, something like that.
Everybody's theories, as chosen by Kasuga. Up next...
When talking about Yasu from Zun, for some reason you always have to include the "from"
Can you do one more?
Hell yeah I can!
They really got some use out of this spot, huh.
We're gonna show you some pictures of comedians, so...
Tell us the name of their duo and then their own name.
Okay, got it.
Downtown, Hamada Masatoshi.
Audrey, Kasuga.
Panther, Ogata.
Viking, Kotoge.
Saraba Seishun no Hikari, Morita.
Zun's...Yasu-san.
Everybody's theories, as chosen by Kasuga. Up next...
It can't be possible to lap up water faster than a dog
What, you mean like licking it?
I'm pretty good at licking though.
Here we have Kuro-chan, a man confident in his tongue capabilities...
By the way, if you lose, you'll get a few electric shocks
Wait, what?
Looks like the dog's thirsty too
Quit moaning.
He got it all.
No way!
He's going "woof."
Wait, hold on!
Oh, he's woofing.
It's really not working.
Everybody's theories, as selected by Kasuga. Lastly, we have...
Safety shoes really are safe.
So, to test the theory out...
Ow, ouch!
After his competition, we brought him out again as a subject.
The theory you'll be testing this time is "safety shoes really are safe."
Safety shoes are safe?
We'll be using steel-toe boots, standard-issue safety shoes.
For some reason I've always thought safety shoes were cool, so I've worn them before, but...
You mean you wore them in private?
Yeah.
Look at those nips.
They're pretty hard, huh
The experienced Kuro-chan prepares for action...
First...
Hey wait, this is pretty heavy...
LEVEL ONE: BOWLING BALL
You're gonna take that and drop it on your boots.
By myself?
Yeah.
Is it really gonna be OK?
Look, this is only level one, so try to hurry up.
Wait, how many times am I doing this?
It's an everybody's theories special, so it keeps a quick pace.
Oh, so it's a quickie.
Doesn't hurt at all.
Then why'd he cry out?
LEVEL TWO: HAMMER
Could you put your foot on that?
I actually felt that one, though.
More than that bowling ball earlier.
Did it hurt?
No, it didn't.
Oh, that's good.
Let's do the next one, then.
Wait, what?
Hold up, hold up!
LEVEL THREE: CAR
I thought I was gonna be run over.
Yeah. So next...
Don't "yeah" me.
The car's gonna run over you.
You're gonna run over them?!
Yeah
Am I gonna be OK?
Is he OK?
Is he or isn't he?
Are you OK?
It ran over you?
It ran over me...
I'm fine!
Ooh, I tricked you!
Trickuro-chan!
Trickuro-chan.
He really said Trickuro-chan.
Moving on...
LEVEL FOUR: TRUCK
This is level four.
Come on, no way.
There's no way you can do that!
No, really, come on!
There's just no way.
We've already reached the max for what I can do.
Do you really mean you can't?
Like, for TV reasons? Or you really just can't?
There's no way I can!
No, but like, Kuro-chan, you really really can't?
No, I can't!
We'll end the human experimentation here for now.
We'll continue with a raw egg.
I guess they'll put it inside the boot.
Oh, they put it inside?
Hey...
You shoulda brought this out sooner.
That was scary.
If you had this before you should've brought it out.
This might be even scarier than last time
The result?
Here I go.
Oh shit!
It's super broken!
That's scary!
The whole theory's scary!
In conclusion: there are limits to the safety of safety shoes.
So that's it.
You know, we almost ended off on the wrong foot there.
I mean he was only considering it, but...
If he actually went for it, we'd be finished.
Scary.
Maybe it was his animal instincts.
Up next: everybody's theories, selected by Tamuken.
Okay everyone, I'll be the last to present today.
To start off, please take a look here.
So I'm hearing some surprise, but you know who this is, right?
It's Bit, right?
The impersonator?
Yes, exactly.
Today, we've brought you a theory regarding this Bit Takeshi.
Here it is.
If shown a caricature of Bit Takeshi and asked who it is, not a single person would reply "Bit Takeshi"
Huh, I guess not.
Nobody would know who Bit Takeshi is.
Even among comedians, that would be tough...
If shown a caricature of Bit Takeshi and asked who it is, not a single person would reply "Bit Takeshi"
The entertainment industry's hit rock bottom.
Booby-traps battle royale!
Bit Takeshi's been playing Beat Takeshi alone for 42 years.
I guess there is a resemblance, huh.
He looks more like the old Beat Takeshi.
And now, we present what must be the world's first caricature of Bit Takeshi.
But if we take a look at it compared to a caricature of Beat Takeshi...
Indeed, if you look closely, you can see the difference.
Will anybody be able to correctly name the caricature?
We're going to show you some caricatures, so please identify them for us.
Sanma-san.
Tamori-san.
Beat Takeshi.
Why would Bit belong in the same group?
With those three back to back, of course they'd say that...
They may have been suggesting "Beat" a little too much, but...
They were.
Indeed, nobody said that it was Bit Takeshi.
And after that...
Beat Takeshi.
As expected, it's nothing but "Beat Takeshi."
However...
I think it can be done correctly, but...
When you've got the big three all lined up and expect us to guess that it's "Bit Takeshi"...
That's playing dirty.
He makes a good point...
We'll try testing if people can guess it based on Bit's picture alone.
Beat Takeshi.
Takeshi Kitano.
Beat Takeshi.        Beat-san.
Beat-san?
In the end, out of a hundred people, zero answered "Bit Takeshi."
However, it's possible that for lay people, Bit is simply not familiar enough.
So we conducted an additional investigation among comedians familiar with Bit.
First, we have...
Somebody who's worked closely with Bit over the years, Haraguchi Akimasa.
We called him in to a fake business meeting.
Would you mind if we asked a few questions for a survey on caricatures?
The result...
Sanma-san.
Tamori-san.
Takeshi-san.
Takeshi who?
Beat Takeshi.
Wrong.
Huh?
The correct answer was Bit Takeshi.
In the end, he didn't answer "Bit" either.
Incidentially, here's one of Beat Takeshi.
Ohhh, I see.
Actually, yeah...that was pretty rude of me.
They're totally different.
I feel kinda embarassed.
* Sokkuri Kan-kisara is an event held at a pub full of lookalike entertainers. Vermont Hideki was originally imitating Hideki Saijo (see his Vermont Curry commerical)
Up next is a longtime friend of Bit and a regular of the Kisara*, Vermont Hideki.
Hideki's really not looking the part.
Let's begin.
Could you bring it closer? My eyesight's really bad.
Ah, Sanma-san.
Tamori, isn't it.
Ah, it's Takeshi.
Takeshi who?
Beat Takeshi-san.
Next is a friend of both Bit and Beat, Matsumura Fumihiro.
Akashiya Sanma-san.
Tamori-san.
Kitano Takeshi-san.
Incorrect.
Huh?
Then who?
Ah, Bit Takeshi.
In the end, he too was unable to reach the answer straightaway.
I mean...there's something about him that looks...
too poor to be Takeshi-san.
Up next, a junior to Bit before making it big...
Audrey's Kasuga.
Oh really!
Sanma-san.
Tamori-san.
He'll know.
Takeshi-san.
Takeshi who?
Hm? Beat Takeshi-san.
Your final answer, once more, please.
Beat Takeshi-san.
Incorrect.
Huh?
Ah, Kitano Takeshi-san.
Incorrect.
Huh? But that's Takeshi-san, isn't it?
The correct answer was Bit Takeshi.
Oh, come on.
That can't be Bit.
Takeshi Kitano...
Is this one here.
Actually, yeah. When you line them up like that...
I feel bad about it.
You say "actually" like it was obvious.
Among comedians who know Bit well, zero were able to identify him straightaway.
For our final subject, we'll test Bit himself.
If he can't get it right either, our theory is as good as proven.
That's, y'know...
Sanma-chan.
Makin' it easy, huh.
Tamori.
Huh?
That's...me?
Or who I'm impersonating, I guess?
I guess it's who I'm impersonating, so...
Beat Takeshi-san.
Your final answer once again, please.
Incorrect.
It's...
me?
In conclusion: Bit Takeshi is the first to achieve total victory in a "zero people" theory.
We did it!
Finally!
Even though we've been doing these "zero people" theories all along...
This is a first?
It is, thanks to Bit.
But it wasn't a very close match.
We kinda knew what would happen.
And the way it was done wasn't that fair.
In that order, right?
The big three.
Right, so that's Bit's fault, isn't it.
No, no, no.
You're really not that funny today, huh.
Everybody's theories, as selected by Tamuken. Up next, we have...
If you've been locked in a room, after checking the lock once, you wouldn't notice if it were unlocked afterwords
The set up is as follows...
A victim has been locked in the room...
Please remove your eye mask.
Mantenro's Ootoni.
He kinda got big, huh.
Huh?
What's up with the coat?
What's going on?
Not thinking he has to do anything in particular, ten minutes pass by.
And then...
He realizes that he's been locked in.
'scuse me!
15 minutes after being in the room, the door is quietly unlocked.
'scuse me.
That's interesting.
Is anybody there?
This is bad.
Indeed, he did not notice the door being suddenly unlocked.
And just like that, four hours pass by.
Huh?
I'm really not allowed to leave at all?
He really has no idea what this is all about.
What's the meaning of this?
Really, what is this...
He notices.
Is it okay if I leave?
What's this about?
I mean, what?
What is this?
I'm coming out.
Everybody's theories, selected by Tamuken.
Four hours, huh.
Up next is...
At the sushi restaurant in Japan furthest from the ocean, the freshness should be a concern.
First, let's locate the sushi restaurant furthest from the ocean.
According to geographical research, the furthest location is at this point in Saku, Nagano.
And in this part of Saku, there are approximately 20 sushi restaurants.
Among them, the closest restaurant we found was...
this 57-year old establishment, Miyako Sushi.
Ah, welcome.
It would seem that this is the furthest sushi restaurant in Japan from the ocean...
Yes, I'm aware.
Moving along, to get to the point...
Sorry to be rude, but is the freshness a concern?
- It's not a problem.
That is rude.
From both Toyosu and Niigata...
we get fish coming in every day.
Since we're right in the middle, we actually have supply from both directions.
In conclusion, the freshness wasn't a concern at all.
Everybody's theories, selected by Tamuken. Up next...
If a child wearing Hotei-print clothes were to get lost at a shopping mall, he could be found by intercom with the message "calling for the child wearing Hotei-print clothes..."
** The Hotei-print (hoteigara) is the signature design of rock musician Hotei Tomoyasu.
This time, our theory will be tested by a three-year old kitted out in Hotei-print.
We'll have him play a lost child in the shopping mall here.
Excuse me!
I have a lost child here...
What sort of announcement will be made?
Next, the supervisor is called in.
Let's see how the announcement is made by a staff member who isn't aware of our theory.
The result...
Calling all customers...
Just now, at our entrance, a lost child was reported.
The child is a boy about five years old...
wearing black and white leopard-print jersey.
Would the customer responsible for this child...
please make their way to the main entrance.
Everyone's theories, as selected by Tamuken. Lastly...
When talking about Yasu from Zun, for some reason you always have to include the "from"
~Part Two~
Downtown, Hamada.
Audrey...
Kasuga.
Cocorico...
Kondo.
Zenko-Ji...
Baldy.
Salaryman...
Yamada.
Shoten...
* Shoten - classic rakugo TV program
Katsura.
That's enough.
In conclusion, Jimmy hardly knows the names of any comedians at all.
Kinda pisses you off.
I think we need a new referee.
Fujimon, going back to that place far from the water...
What did you make of the freshness proposition?
Come on, I mean...
The whole country's pretty connected...
and it has been for a while, yeah?
Even if...
Even if it's being delivered, it's gonna come pretty quick.
Right, but y'know, actually, there was delivery from both parts of the country, right?
What do you make of that?
Oh yeah but actually it was delivery on—
both of the–
killl meeeeee.
Gimme a damn break.
But if they've been around for 57 years already, it must've been pretty tough in the old days...
Yeah, that's true. 57 years ago...
Well, it's...
news to me.
Come on, even Kanda-san noticed.
Get it together, man.