Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let's get on with our first presenter please
Jinnai Tomonori!
Do you all remember the suspicious person who appeared in the "live broadcast"?
I do
-That was fun
For this supposed live broadcast
Yoshimura did very well
His popularity rose
-He was on network news
Yoshimura received great acclaim
This revealed that experience helps
As Abareru and Ogata both got into a little panic
Maybe they didn't perform well because they're not senior enough
-That's it!
So, this time, i've brought the following theory
If a suspicious person interrupts a live broadcast, an experienced announcer can handle it perfectly
I see. How will veterans deal with it
After this, veteran announcer vs. suspicious passersby
Also
I got married at the age of 16
Another collection of families with a small age gap
The 2nd 4 Generation Relay Competition
Then, when getting hit by a colorless stinky air cannon while being criticized
You won't mention the stench
If a suspicious person interrupts a live broadcast, an experienced announcer can handle it perfectly
What kind of people will do it?
Let's see who it is
This time we set up a supposed live broadcast
And invited experienced craftsmen with more than 30 years of experience
To cover a BBQ venue in Saitama for a fictional program
Seems legitimate
During the live broadcast, the suspicious passerby will pay a visit
Of course, this time, the actor who was previously well-received for his role as a suspicious character, is back again
This is the case. The first target is Akihiro Yoshimura, 44th year of the Era.
You got a great guy!
Yoshimura has been on air every week for ten years
※A long-running Japanese variety show broadcast on TBS from 11:45 to 12:54 every Sunday since October 6, 1985
How will he handle the situation?
The live broadcast begins
This time we have Mr. Akihiro Yoshimura, come on out, Mr. Yoshimura~
Hello, I'm Akihiro Yoshimura!
It's really nice to have a BBQ in spring
So today, we came to the BBQ site in Saitama, Arima Gorge
At this point in the broadcast, we get the guy out as soon as possible
Feels stable
He's worthy!
In this new green period of the coming summer
BBQ in spring like this
It may not have much to do with summer...
Are you OK?
We're live right now!
Brother. Brother.
-Is it okay?
So today we come to interview people who are interested in fishing...
To interview rainbow trout fishermen
Brother, what are you doing here...are you here to fish?
Brother, brother, are you fishing...
Did you come to fish?
Fishing, fishing
Brother... brother let's fish
Brother, let's fish, come on
With the sudden intrusion, although there is a moment of timidity
He quickly recovers and continues the live coverage
And
There are still a lot of fishermen, let's turn back a little to see
There is a foot bath
Because there are very few people today, you can soak your feet for a little rest
Look this way next
Great, great, too impressive
So cool!
There may be those who come fishing without their equipment
There are also BBQ sets full sets can be rented
The cost of a set (half day) is 2500 yen and 3700 yen a day
People with no rod and bait can also come here to rent
In such a way, he throws the topic to distant building facilities
To cleverly lead the camera to the place where the crazy guy isn't
A skill that only veterans possess
Worthy of a veteran
Afterwards, as usual, after properly handling this pestering guy
Then we will introduce you to the BBQ venue afterwards
I'll take you back to the studio for now.
-Thank you
Easy to get around him
Reducing the impact to a minimum with this wonderful performance, the camera goes back to the studio
After that, he continued to report cheerfully without showing any sense of surprise
This is a staff problem
-The staff should have gone to stop it
The next step is to escalate the crazy level
What exactly will happen?
There are young people fishing here
They're taking a break for a while
Do you guys have any fishing experience in the sea, river or something like that?
No.
-No?
But most people would have been to the fishing pond, right?
I haven't been there either.
-It's also not common anymore
Wait a minute, brother, brother...
There are rainbow trout here, right?
Are you all right, brother?
Brother...
You're not a zombie either, okay?
Brother, move slightly to the side... just stay there for a bit
I'm so sorry!
From the river, a wet zombie appears and its still greeted with a smile
So here we reveal the project
May I ask what program you thought you were invited to today?
Eh... Uncle Broadcast
It's actually Wednesday Downtown
Eh?
That's why a guy like that came?
-Yes
You guys are skilled
Terrific
I'm impressed
Even went in the water
It's so cold
The next target is
32 years experience, Kikuhime Hayashiya
Same as my rakugo
She's a woman
Kikuhime who was active as an announcer on TBS's information program "Just" in the first half of the 2000s
※"Just" was broadcast live on TBS Life from September 28, 1998 to March 25, 2005 in the afternoon on weekdays
A woman
Let's get started
Could be a little scared
This is the lake called Lake Naguri
It may sound shocking to hear the name of autumn chestnut
What? Hello, brother?
Would you like to present for us?
It's very sudden but sorry. Are you here to play too?
You are also here, it's a little... sorry... so suddenly
And then around here, there's also boating in this lake
Hasn't changed her face yet
There are also places to fish
In autumn, you can also enjoy the beautiful maple leaves here
What a great place!
So let's take a look at this side again
There seems to be a visitor who is having a good time
For the sudden arrival of the crazy guy
This one also continues without the slightest panic
How many people came together today?
-5 people or so
Did you fish often?
-My supervisor is more...
Ah, this is your boss.
-Yes, for now
Do you fish often?
There are no opportunities after work
Wow, wet, why are you wet this time?
Wait a minute, that... Why are you wet this time?
You don't seem to be catching much fish here, so I'll come back when you get some
Some uneasiness is felt about the river appearence
Next
It's okay, because the climate is great. It's very pleasant
Being able to do it under the blue sky is also one of the joys of BBQ
From my perspective as an older woman, I like it
It's cool and you don't sweat
All equipment can be rented here
I like it, so I suggest you try it too!
Surely an instinctive reaction would manifest slightly?
Ultimately, she ends up in a scary situation live
We are actually Wednesday Downtown
My favorite show!
I love it!
Despite saying this, she failed to realise
What kind of theory do you think this is?
What theory?
It's your favorite program, after all
Joints and such? Eh what what what? Joints?
What joints?
That... the knee joint
What theory?
You don't even know this show, right?
Bone joint?
Definitely doesn't know the program
Regardless of whether they're funny or not, veteran broadcasters are undoubtedly skilled like the theory suggests
Don't say stuff like "regardless of whether they're funny or not"
The next target is...
Hi~ I'm Nakamura!
Known as TVchampion's former announcer
※TVchampion was a variety show broadcast on TV Tokyo every Thursday from 19:30 to 20:50 from April 16, 1992 to September 21, 2006
Yuki Nakamura with 45 years of experience
Today we came to Arima Valley
It takes about an hour and a half to get here by car from Tokyo
That...can...can reach
Possibly because he hasn't been on TV for too long
Nakamura stumbles even without obstacles
Don't say such things
So we get things moving
The maple leaves in autumn are really...
The tourists coming for a walk also... should be a lot
Hey, hey, wait a little bit!
We... we're on the air now!
Where did you come from today?
Wait a minute, wait a minute...
It is obvious that the unexpected appearance of unexpected and suspicious people is a surprise
Rainbow trout can be caught here!
Are you going to follow me all the time?
Because we are live a lot of things will happen
Eh, this customer seems to be particularly fond of the camera
Please go to the side... just a little bit
It's a completely incoherent
The river appearance is also a mess
Give me a break!
Always in a state of handicap, the broadcast ends
After that the fourth target is
Mr. Chin with 33 years of experience
A veteran broadcaster who is known for his door-to-door visits to outside locations
How will he deal with it?
You can also see maple leaves here in autumn
It's a great place to get away from it all
So today, sir, sorry, thank you
Today ah, let's see...
Sir, sorry...
No problem?
-Yes.
Excuse me, sir, what's wrong with you? I'm sorry
Today, let's see how happy the spring BBQ is!
I would like to introduce you to
I'm sorry, but we're shooting now
Treating suspicious people with a smile
Mr. Chin, who speaks to others while looking them in the eye
But after that
Sir, I know, what is wrong with you?
What are you doing here? What's going on? Is there a problem?
I'm sorry...
Busy with the crazy guy, the broadcast is neglected
At this moment the broadcast goes back to the studio
To let the staff intervene to get rid of the crazy guy
Then
Sir, what's wrong with you?
What's going on? What's wrong? It's okay?
Very kind
Don't be  too rough with him
Mr. Chin, more concerned about the man than the flow of the broadcast, is thrown off slightly
A nice guy
I can tell that this is a kind person...
And
It's great to catch two of them!
For newbies
What? What?
What's going on? What on earthl?
Come on up! Let's get you up!
What is going on?
That towel, towel towel towel
He's too nice!
I'm sorry, you were shocked, right?
I was shocked too
Alongside helping the crazy guy
He also doesn't forget the subject of the interview
Aside from being a broadcaster, he is an excellent human being
It's really comfortable to be in nature
Indeed, you will also want to jump into the water
Because it's comfortable. It's comfortable, right?
You'll want to jump in... don't jump is fine too
It's okay not to dive
This kid is so excited!
In a state where even Chin can't do anything
We reveal the truth
Afterwards
That person is from Wednesday Downtown?
I'm really sorry
He is a well-mannered person
No this is great!
I wanna cry
I was also moved to tears because you are so gentle
Well, that's great
What the hell, really?
An unexpected and heart-warming scene
The final target is
The oldest, 79-year-old Eiji Bando
...apologizing just now
Sorry for wearing the Lions hat
※The Lions refer to the Saitama Seibu Lions, a team in the Pacific League of Nippon Professional Baseball.
That kind of thing is fine
Did something happen?
-Sorry, a little...
What's wrong?
-That's a little...
Because it is a live broadcast, sorry
Although this part has unfolded similarly so far
It feels like something bad is going to happen
Raise it a little. Raise it a little
It's good to shoot here
Caught! Great!
You guys keep up the good work!
Sorry
Pushed away
Slightly pushed away
Because it's live
Just pushed him
BBQ is fully available here, and is waiting for your reservation
Pushed away hard
The forced removal of a suspicious person causing trouble constantly
Tough to shoot
And
As we need to prepare a little now
Let's go back to the studio please
-Okay thanks
Later, we will introduce more beautiful places, please look forward to it!
Broadcast back to the studio
Damn, I'm scared
Can this be broadcast?
This is something that can't be broadcast, right?
Just watch for the time being
In summary
It seems like some parts of this wont make it to broadcast
It can't be helped
I'm thinking the whole of the last part will have to be cut
I'm sure there's some discussions going on about compliance
Matsumoto, what do you think?
-About what?
Please comment on Bando's part first
I think it was spiritually invigorating
It won't be forgotten
We've once again witnessed the spirit of Showa-era men that had been forgotten
They have to find a way to make the show work
Bando was the only one to not interact with the guy
Because he thought he was trying to cause trouble on purpose
He was pretty cool
How about we just don't say the name "Bando" in the clip
Everyone will still know!
Just write "Some Old Man"
Or refer to him as just A
It was a shocking sight wasn't it
Can you do this to him?
The voice is so obviously his!
I feel like covering the eyes will work
And make the name A or B or something like that
So everyone please look forward to the eventual broadcast
I'm scared it'll get cut
Yeah but this show is so stupid
Let's welcome the next presenter
Hello everyone
It's Shimofuri!
This time, we are not bringing a theory but a project
Really?
-Yes.
I hope its something heart-warming
True
I hope this next segment will be aired in its entirety
It should be
Please offset the bad vibes
What we have brought is this:
The 2nd 4 Generation Relay Competition
Oh yeah
Previously we had a children Mothers Grandmothers and Great-grandmothers relay race
How about this, the family aspect is heart-warming, right?
Yes, warm
Just a little relay race...
It has nothing to do with the relay race, right?
No, no, no. Relay is also very good
Are relay races really heartwarming?
It can be a chance for family bonding
Can just a little bit of heartwarming content fill the hole we have now?
Well, the last part was a bit much
The 2nd 4 Generation Relay Competition
This time, we decided the order as children to great-grandmothers for the race
First of all, we came to this store in Asahi City, Chiba Prefecture
The four families in the first group of the competition are
Hello
The Yoshida Family
Firstly, Nana, a 23-year-old mother of two, introduces her family
So young!
This is the great-great-grandmother
92 years-old
Yes
Very energetic!
Oh - really? Thank you!
This family has five generations together
The eldest daughter is Nana and the youngest is Yui
She is the child of a boyfriend I dated in her second year of high school
This year she's five years old
Are you married now?
No
After saying "I want to have a baby", I said "Let's break up then" and then we broke up
Don't say that in front of the children!
The day after the breakup, he got a new girlfriend
Great-great-grandma is laughing!
Nana, who gave birth to her eldest daughter unmarried at the age of 18 in her senior year of high school
Different biological fathers
Married to another man at the age of 19 and gave birth to Yuato, three years later she divorced
So, Nana's mother
This is my mom Asami
Asami, grandmother of two at the age of 44
Are you married, Asami?
No...
Ah, grandma too...
-Yeah
Divorced once?
-Yes
Great-great-grandmother's going again
This is not the funny part!
What happened?
The discussion of divorce hit the funny bone?
I'm sorry I laughed out loud
Tears are coming out of my eyes
The Yoshida family, including the great-grandmother who has no history of divorce
Each of the five generations in the same family had their first born very early
（Great-great-grandmother）20-years old
（Great-grand mother）Also 20-years old
(Grandmother) Also 20 years old
(Mother) 17 years old
Pretty much as close as possible
The Yoshida family, which has been passing down the family line with high frequency, will have these four people out on the relay
Next is Osaka Prefecture
The second group of four families participating in the competition are
Hello
The Murakami Family
Mom, Rinka, 20, and only daughter, Sera, 2
This is my mother Ayano
Grandma Setsuko
Sister Misaki
Sister Kia
Was Sera born when you were 18?
Marriage necessitated by an unplanned pregnancy
Marriage necessitated by an unplanned pregnancy~
Are you still married?
Now it's... over
Is it always like this?
She got pregnant with Sera during the second year of high school
A year after the senior year, she gave birth to a child and got divorced just 2 years after
Similarly, her mother Ayano, is also
Are you married now?
At the moment, nothing
Divorced once?
-Yes
Eh? Everyone laughed out loud!
It's fine
But when pressed by the staff who noticed something different
In fact, she's been divorced twice
Slow down when you lie
It's hard to admit
The Murakami family also face the topic of divorce with a smile and cheerfulness
Great-grandmother Setsuko, who has also been divorced twice, is 69 years old
Grandma is in high demand now
She recently dated and broke up with a 72-year-old guy
Really?
Setsuko has recently broken up with her boyfriend 3 times
How did they meet?
He picked me up while shopping in the supermarket
Then we went to karaoke
Too frivolous? Is it okay to say?
She's already very frivolous
Who are you talking about? Tanaka
Tanaka?
Do you know about Tanaka?
He took me to Disneyland
Tanaka's treat
These 4 members will participate in the relay race
Next up is Hiroshima Prefecture
The 3rd family in the competition is
Hello
The Noike family, the 35-year old mother Akane
Then let's introduce the family
This is the eldest son
Eh, son?
16 years old
Have you ever been told "your mother is so young"?
It is often said
I was told "Your mom is super cute" the other day
This is the second son Keiji
This is the third son Taizan
Fourth child and fifth child
A mother with a lot of children
He's my first husband's child
The rest are my current husband's
Divorced three years after giving birth to the eldest son at the age of 19
2 years later, she remarried her current husband, Masao
And they had four children
Masao's children start with the second child
After divulging the fact that only the eldest son's father is different
The children are embarrassed
They didn't know their father's aren't the same
I see...
Really?
She's gonna bring this up now?
Are you making it public now?
Thought it was a good opportunity
I'm nervous
After disclosing the secret to the four children without any reservation
This is not the time for a relay
We return to introducing the family
This is Mom Ayumi - 53 years old
This is Ayumi, who has five grandchildren at the age of 53
Initially married at the age of 16
It wasn't marriage for necessity?
No
The dowry was paid and the marriage ceremony took place in a normal manner
The ultra-rare model of getting married without being pregnant
What is this BGM?
Then at the age of 18, she gave birth to Akane
This one too
While together they had three children, but their marriage lasted only 10 years
This is my daughter
After that year, she remarried and had a daughter, Aoi, with her current husband
The age difference between her and her eldest daughter Akane is 20 years
In other words
She's my aunt
The aunt is younger than the nephew
And then there is...
Kazuko, 78 years old
Great-grandmother feels uneasy about running because of her advanced age
He's in athletics
How long can you do the 100 metres in?
12.4 seconds or so
So fast!
So the first participant is super fast and the last batter is the oldest of all
Thus, the following family members will participate in the relay race
The fourth group is also from Osaka Prefecture
The first person will have a big lead, right?
The Yamaoka family
Pregnant at age 18 and born at age 19
This is Churisa's mother, Mika-san
I was 16 when I got pregnant and gave birth at 17
Surrounded by super opposition
Looks like a bad girl
My relationship with my mother was very bad at that time
Probably all are
Really?
Yes
And this is Mika's mother, who is now very close to her
How old are you?
The Yamaoka family has a unique quality
Dad and mom always stick together, they're super in love
They're always together
Even if Dad goes to adult places
Mum will go too
Also known as "fancy" places
Eh?
"I'd like to go to the fancy place..." or something like that
"Be careful"
You really don't care
It's better than him having a mistress, right?
Eh, you also go together?
Yes, outside
Eh, it's not outside, it's in a hotel...
Ah, hotel?
I book a room
You wait behind the glass...
Yes yes yes
What kind of quarrel is this?
The Yamaoka family, which has nothing to hide, has no divorces
A Super Successful Family
So the relay race is these 4 people
And
Hello!
The Takahashi family here is also a 4 generation family
In a beautiful living room
There are beautiful mothers
Have you ever been divorced?
Never had one. The family is complete
This is the beautiful family's composition
These four members of the Takahashi family will participate in the competition
Takahashi family, let's do it!
Oh!
The former winners great-grandmother's foot makes them unable to participate
An unexpected medical suspension
Also
Because I can't shut my business
The five-generation Yoshida family  will not be able to participate
Sorry about that
So this time the relay will be carried out by these four
4 generations relay!
Thank you for having us!
It will be the same as last time
Half laps of a 150m track will take place in this order
Toward surpassing the Japanese record of 1:25 of the previously relay
So, everything is ready
First runners are Ryuya 1 year old, Seiya 2 years old, Yui 3 years old
There is also the 16 year old member of the track and field club, Itsuki
Which family will win in the end?
Seriously...
Families comprised of different generations will compete in a relay race
Who will be the winner?
All in position. Ready
The Noike family shoots out ahead
And in the blink of an eye, the 16-year-old hands over the baton to his 35-year-old mother
An overwhelming lead
Can the Noike family maintain their lead?
The gap with the second place is now more than half a lap
At this time the 3 year old finely hands over the baton to her mother
The Noike family on the other hand have completed passing the baton to the 53-year old grandmother
Who will be the first to pass the baton out of Seiya and Ryuya?
So heart-warming!
It's really heartwarming
At this time, the baton of the Noike family is handed over to the 78-year-old great-grandmother
Shockingly she's walking!
Although the first batter is 16 years old, the last batter is a senior, can she keep up the pace?
At this time the Murakami family hands its baton over to the 45-year-old grandmother
The Noike family is walking to the finish!
In second-place, the Takahashi family hands over the baton to their 75-year-old great-grandmother
While the Noike family is still walking!
So white
Catching up!
Pretty fast!
The gap is gradually narrowing
Can it be reversed?
Ah, so powerful, so powerful
Second place is visible!
The Noike family are the winners!
Not much difference with the second place
So cute
Hydrating so fast
By the way, the time of the winning family was 1 second longer than that of the previous winner
Thus, the crown stays where it is
Just one second!
Only 1 second difference
You used the family composition chart again for this
Yes, the family composition chart
They said a lot of weird stuff
Super messy
How can I say it? Families that are not bound by the marriage system
Very cheerful
Lots of independent women
Very strong indeed.
-Very strong
Quite powerful
We are looking for many more families with four generations together
So if you think you can win, please contact our team
Better be quick
Indeed
If you don't do it early, the last generation will be...
Next is everybody's theories
Tonight's presenter is
Tamura Kenji!
Previously we tested an air cannon with colorless air
Everyone remembers, right?
That was funny.
-Interesting
This program struck gold with this
It was something that had never been done before
This time
We've added the air cannon element to a popular segment of this program
Oh
The theory is:
When getting hit by a colorless stinky air cannon while being criticized, you won't mention the stench
What a mess
There is no reason for people to have to be scolded
There is no reason for people to have to smell something bad
I'm curious about that stench
What kind of smell is it? What the hell is it?
It's a smell that doesn't exist in this world
When getting hit by a colorless stinky air cannon while being criticized, you won't mention the stench
This time, we recruited seniors and juniors from all walks of life
However, when it comes to the power of the air cannon
It's unavoidable, right?
Oh wow, it stinks...
This guy-
I'm sorry...
As before, the setup is conducted in secret
Such a powerful stench
And colorless
First of all, the first group is rehearsing in a small theater
Of course the target knows nothing
So, the lecture beings instantly
You're doing badly so you must be looking down at me or the play
I don't get it
And you say that you want to be an actor
I really think you are very childish
If the rehearsal is bad then the actual performance will be even worse
Nothing good will happen
If you don't work hard its impossible
Once the target is suitably depressed
The air cannon is launched for condolences
Why do you have to use the air cannon to condole someone?
What will happen?
Are you motivated?
What's going on?
She swung away
Next
Is there something wrong?
Nothing. Sorry
It really stinks!
She didn't shout "it stinks!"
Same after this
How about it? What do you think?
Stop screwing around
What's going on? What is it?
What is it?
Totally unfocused!
Do you have something to say?
She does have something to say
But its tough to rule out the possibility that the seniors are emitting the stench
What? What's wrong?
A hellish experience
We revealed the truth now
Shocking
What is this? What's going on?
Does it stink?
It stinks
What is the smell? Will it cling to me?
It stinks!
Next are male actors
This group also starts the lecture immediately
You want to be a lead actor?
I'd love to
Or don't you want to?
-I do
Your voice is too small to hear
I want to be the lead actor!
Do you understand what I'm saying?
What do you want to become?
You want to be the lead actor, right?
-I want to be the lead actor
If you want to be the lead actor, say it louder!
I want to be the lead actor!
Oh oh, a little louder
I want to be the lead actor
Then do it!
It's not like that, Hamada
At the moment when the target is about to cry for real
Condolences are sent from the air cannon
Don't, he's crying
Do you understand?
He touches his nose to mask his disgust
What a roundabout tactic!
It's not like touching your nose is ever a good thing
And he doesn't say "it stinks"
The same is true for the following target
Thank you for your magnificent words!
Yeah, sorry
Patience
Next
Everyone will put up with it
Oh my God, don't do this
He breathed in
He's using his strength
Obviously it stinks
What an expression
You have a strange look on your face. What's wrong?
-Nothing
Patience
The next verification is on an imitation artist
Hamada is very fond of this kind of thing, right?
He loves to watch people smell stinky things
You've never smelled Hamada's farts, have you?
They're incredible, a PM level of 3.5
Next, condolences to the parody artist with the air cannon
There is no way to talk about this
It can only be posted on social media
Do you have a new gag?
-No
What?
There are so many TV programs nowadays
Trends change so quickly
Are you aware?
-Yes, I am
You notice but you're not coming up with any new gags?
At the pain point of the lecture
The next segment shows
To be able to come to such an excellent place today
Thanks, I'm Ayase
Music Start
Sorry, my throat is a little...
My voice is a bit stranined
She blames it on her throat
Next up
sa'TOSHI
Very similar
All laughing
Not good, it's coming!
What a mess, 3 hits!
Until here
Most people believe that the stench is caused by the fart of the seniors
So the situation of not being able to say stink continues to develop
Among them
What do you think?
What is your personal opinion?
If I'm late, I'll keep the rest of the company waiting
I'm trying hard to go to bed early, but haven't started acting yet
It's not right for me to do so
Are you listening to me?
Stinks
He said it!
He said it
Later
Why do you keep touching your face, are you looking down on me?
No, something stinks
It's a little hard to talk
I don't feel well
I want to go to the toilet
Why do you want to go to the bathroom when someone's talking to you
Tummy is a little upset
A junior who wants to get out quickly even by lying
Next
You're too stalkerish when you're drunk
This is the iron rule of hosts, right?
"Don't drink it yourself, let the guests drink it"
Why can't you help it?
What a scene!
-What is this scenario?
What's going on?
In summary
air cannons should be used carefully in larger spaces
So interesting!
The kid that said "stinks" so directly was great
Yes.
-A no nonsense man
Kids today are like that, right?
-Yeah.
Should do it to someone like Jimmy who is super sensitive
Yeah!
Don't you want to see Jimmy's reaction?
-Yeah
A little stink and he'll
-He'll probably throw up
Probably will throw up
Let's see
Using the frequency of a Taiko drummer to launch is good
Because of this, Jimmy's version has been recorded
And will be released soon
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03