Welcome to Wednesday Downtown
Let's get on with our first presenter please
It's Chocolate Planet!
It's Chocolate Planets!
Yes indeed, we are Chocolate Planets, thank you for having us
Thank you, thank you
So, although it may be asking too much,
Everyone please look here
-What what what
Does everyone know what this is?
It's a deep-sea monkfish
That's right, a deep-sea monkfish
Do you know the characteristics of this fish?
It has a glowing light
Do you know why it glows?
Because they want to attract other small fish to them
-That's right
Deep-sea monkfish glow from the top of their heads to feed on the small fish that are attracted to it
This time we bring you a theory about deep-sea monkfish
This is it:
Deep-sea monkfish traps also work for humans
Wait a minute, I'm a little confused about what you mean
What is it? Give me an example
Well, it glows, right?
And fish are attracted to it, right?
Then the deep-sea monkfish eats them
"Does this apply to humans as well?" That's it
Does this apply to humans?
-In humans, that is...
The kid on that side, you speak first
That means I'm not very credible, right?
Let the planets speak
I am the planet
-That is, the monkfish will glow
There's a light, right?
Then humans come along
And then they are preyed upon
Preyed upon...?
-Can it eat humans?
Is the trap for humans also light?
It's light, it's light
That is, whether deep-sea monkfish can prey on humans
That's all.
I was just asking what everyone thinks, so I raised this question
Are you okay? Were you uncomfortable just now?
No discomfort, no discomfort-
-Instead...
We are just wondering why they can't understand
What don't you understand?
I want to watch the VTR at home, is that OK?
Why does it have to be like this?
Coming up, the horror of the deep-sea monkfish prank!
What's that?
Also, we have...
No-one can tell who you are if you're wrapped in 10 rubber bands
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU!?
And, "If the person who is pranked pisses themselves...
The instigator's face will instantly turn serious"
And, the "No couples sleep in bunk beds" verification!
Verify that the deep-sea monkfish's trap also works for humans
This time the stage is this warehouse
First, we contacted the targets under the guise of a fake program
Then suddenly let the venue expereince a blackout
At this time, the deep-sea monkfish machine hidden behind the wall of boxes appears,
Illuminated only by the tip of its tentacle
If the target is attracted, it will be preyed upon instantly
Ah I see
First of all, the first target
Nishimura
-Yeah
Viking's Nishimura
He's completely unaware that on the other side of the wall, there is a giant deep-sea fish
Nishimura is confirming the playing cards that will supposedly be used in the next challenge
What the hell?
Just when he is, for some reason, checking the smell of the cards...
Suddenly...
Whoa scary
Pretty scary!
Can't see anything at all
A power outage!
Why just this reaction?
Not even a sound
Not making a single sound is pretty impressive
If it was me I'd probably be more afraid
Then the staff wearing night vision goggles quietly remove the wall
Deep Sea State
-Deep Sea State, absolutely
In the darkness, within the deep sea setting, a deep-sea monkfish appears
It's pitch black
Really dark, can't even see the monkfish itself
Nishimura can't see anything
The camera is really powerful isn't it
What the hell?
He's finally speaking
The reaction to the power outage was rather uneventful
Indeed
Here it is
Here we go
-It's bright!
A single light in a sea darkness
Incidentally, the view that Nishimura saw was this
And then...
Hey...
I'm sure you'd go closer
He's leaning over!
Nishimura is slowly drawn to the light
So interesting
You're really good at leaning over!
Once you get close...
-That's all it takes
It's ready to eat, right?
And then...
And then...?
Feeding begins immediately
How does it hunt?
Ah, what, what, ah
I'm scared!
What is this?
This is how it happens
That's how it happens
Next...
Ah~ so cold
Ah~ slippery and slimy
The digestive juices enter
Ah~ so slimy
What is this, feels smelly and sticky and smelly
Any more?
Back into the light
It's a turd
-Yeah, a turd
Excreted through the anus
What's the deal?
It's been excreted!
What do you think just happened?
-Hey, what are you talking about?
What do you think is going on here?
-What?
Seriously, what?
Firstly, you are on Wednesday Downtown
Eh…？
What...what is this? What theory?
What theory? It's a theory right?
What...what? What is this thing?
"The deep-sea monkfish trap also applies to humans"
A deep sea monkfish is that monkfish...
The one at the bottom of the sea?
-Yes, the slimy one.
Ah this ah ah um
Ah——
The glowing one?
-Yes.
The one with the thing is the deep-sea monkfish?
-That's right.
That's the deep-sea monkfish ?
-Correct
The light?
-Indeed
It leads things toward it
After I got close, my feet got stuck and it moved
Yes, that was it eating
-So I was eaten, right?
Ah, I was in it's stomach. This is gastric juice, right?
You understand so fast!
Then I've been digested
-Correct
In the darkness, if light appears then you feel safer
There's no one that wouldn't take the bait
Ah, isn't this the deep-sea monkfish?
Didn't see it before
Wa--!
This, this, this, this!
This is how I was staring at it just now
No one can escape from this, can they
Impossible to escape from
This is an awesome theory!
The deep-sea monkfish is awesome!
Super interesting
I want to go home straight away,
And look up "deep-sea monkfish" in the encyclopedia
Regardless of whether it works for humans
Or whether it is even possible to avoid it
The deep-sea monkfish device is chilling!
It's really interesting when leaning over
The second target is...
Please sit here for a moment, I'll call the director
Ah~ Shiraki
It's Ah~ Shiraki
The candle's flame
She practices the scenes of a fake script with great care despite the messy outfit
And despite the messy outfit, she is very careful regarding hygiene
Ah~ Shiraki
She may be more wary
The scallops are about to be preyed upon
And then...
Wah!
Scary, isn't it?
Excuse me!?
You'd most likely say that at least
This is the normal reaction, right?
Excuse me--!?
But its probably better not to move
I'm scared!
Scary, scary, scary, scary, scary!
It's scary, isn't it?
Excuse me!?
Scary, scary, scary!
Something seems to be coming...
Different to Nishimura, the sensitive to sounds and movement man and woman
Excuse me!?
I am night blind, I can't see anything!
Night blindness isn't the problem
Is there anyone there?
What?
The light is on
And so...
You would lean toward it
-Yeah
While treading carefully, she walks ahead
It's really impossible to see anything
Can't see anything at all
Can't see what's in front of her
Slowly moving towards the light
Leaning over!
Excuse me!?
She's still relying on that
This one also, unsurprisingly, went onto the tongue of the monkfish
Still a bit further, still a bit further
The feeding begins
Is it time to begin?
So scary... scary ah ah ah ah what is this!?
Eaten
What's going on? Scary!
What's the deal?
Scary!
How do you feel?
It's scary
It's a prank, right? A prank?
And so, we divulge the theory...
Ah——
Do you know the deep-sea monkfish?
-I've heard of it
Uses this to lure
Ah this is a universal object is it?
I just normally...
Went in the direction of the light
Incidentally, how do you feel about this lubricant?
This is the first time I've used it
It's good stuff
First use
I think I understand the type of people who like this...
What are you talking about?
I see. Is there anything else you want to say? Any more questions?
The rest of what I want to say...
Will appear after the commercial break
I'm sorry...
Start with "Sorry"
Shouldn't end with "Sorry"
The next target of the deep-sea monkfish prank is...
Mou Chugakusei (Already a high school student)
What will happen?
Ah!
Ara?
Are?
After darkness descends
The wall is moved as before
And the deep-sea monkfish debuts
Excuse me!?
And then, this time too
Getting closer
Excuse me!?
Definitely closer than before
Then, as he is already in range...
Yeah
Because the light is on
Wait...
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts
More digestive juices were put in this time
And then,
No! What? Why?
What is this...
Because of the darkness, I've been feeling nothing but fear
We are from Wednesday Downtown
-EH?
Wednessy?
What is Wednessy?
Deep-sea monkfish prank?
Ah, really, it's a deep-sea monkfish lamp
The design is so good its a pity you can't see it in the darkness
Is that the point?
I was really attracted to this orange light
Only this orange light could be relied upon to move forward
Indeed
Is there anything else you would like to say?
Ah~ actually, I was really looking forward to doing the show I thought I was here for
"The support group is here today, too"
"For the sake of everyone, let's go..." or something like that...
It's self-made
Yeah it's self-made
Next up...
Hasegawa
No problem, right?
Excuse me!?
You're not doing anything weird, are you?
Anyone there?
Everyone says "Excuse me!?"
Ahhh!
The power is out
As always, this time too
Looks like a different person
His expression is so stupid
Is anyone there?
Does look stupid
-Yeah
Drawn by the only bright light in the darkness
Wow!
And then...
You see, looks so stupid
Bad, bad, bad
It's pouring!
The quantity is very good
Ah, so that's what happened, I was eaten
-That's right
So that's how it is
Next time I'll eat instead!
And so, the final individual is...
M-1 Champion
Sakai
This guy is pretty weird
His use of words might be pretty bad
Indeed, he must be eaten
Eh? Excuse me--!?
This is really what a bad guy looks like
The power is out
This guy doesn't even look frightened
It seems to have tripped
You'd usually scream a little, right?
Failing to spot the light, he wanders around for 3 minutes
He pisses me off!
Why can't he find it?
Finally...
I don't really understand either
It's so dark maybe he can't see it
What's that?
And then...
Hey--
What happened all of a sudden?
The panic is starting
Restlessness
Dangerous!
What what what what?
Ahhhh, ahhhh, snake, snake, snake, snake!
Still hasn't figured it out
Snakes?
Wait, there are snakes ah
Not snakes!
Why?
Actually, it's not snakes but digestive juices
And then...
What, what, what, what, what?
This time is based on the concept that the gastric juices will digest the clothes
Additional elements on top of the original
What the hell is that
This is "the trap of the deep-sea monkfish applies to humans as well"
The one just now
Like an orange ball
-Light
I was very restless and moved closer to the light
And I was eaten
Because it was the only one that lit up...
And then, because I was eaten, I was digested in the stomach
That's why it's so sticky
Huh?
To sum up
The trap of deep-sea monkfish is inescapable
Awesome
That's awesome
-So that's what it was all about
What does everyone think?
In short, 100% of the people were lured
Very impressive
Monkfish are doing some amazing things at the bottom of the sea
So this is probably how it happens to all the fish that are preyed upon
No idea what's going on
That works for fish
But it won't work for comedians again
Indeed
After this broadcast
However,
After watching it, even if...
How about changing this part?
The light part?
Replace it with something like putting a colored thing in a place where there's nothing else
But then...
It's not a deep-sea monkfish
So strict!
Let's welcome the next presenter
What?
Who is it?
Ah
It's Tamura Kenji!
Thank you for having me
Thanks for coming
This time i've brought
A theory about rubber bands
This is it:
A person with 10 rubber bands stretched over their face cannot be recognized
Eh?
Frequently featured in shows
Is seeing many rubber bands can be stretched onto the face in 1 minute
Stuff like a Guinness World Record challenge
Pretty common, right?
Has anyone here done it?
I've done it
-Yeah
The face is deformed after putting it on, right?
It's super deformed!
So,
With about 10 rubber bands, no one will be able to recognize the person
Can 10 be done?
So, let's verify it now
Right now?
-Yes
The set has already been prepared
Please move over there for the on-site verification
Team Quiz - Who is the Person Disguised by Rubber Bands?
This time, the teams are divided into Matsumoto and Hamada teams
The theory will be tested in the form of a quiz
Also on this side is the comedian that will never turn down any work...
Flirty comedian Fujimoto
Be careful of your choice of words
What do you mean by flirty comedian?
Matsumoto team's rubber bands
One team will be presented with other team's rubber band-tied face
And will be able to confer with each other
Up to 20 rubber bands can be used
If you succeed in making your opponent guess incorrectly,
The number of rubber bands used subtracted from 20 is the score
However, if the other team gets it right, they get zero points
So if you can't guess with 5 bands, you get 15 points
Ah it's this type of rule
I don't understand at all
You 'aint your standard idiot!
Can't help it, too old
He's already the age where his driver's license will be cancelled
Who are you talking about, idiot?
It's still too early for that
Who's gonna confuse the acceleration for brake?
So, for the first round of rubber bands tied to the guest,
Both of the participants are male
I see
We have A or B
So i'll ask Matsumoto and Hamada to choose
Which one?
Either is fine
Let the other side choose?
No problem
B
You're choosing B?
-Yes
Don't let each other see
So each has decided their respective guests
Got a good one
We don't
The next two teams move quickly backstage
And are given rubber bands
Where are the features of the face...
Nose...
It's the nose
The eyes have to be strained and deformed
-The eyes are still...
Lift the nose up or pull it down?
It's better to put it up
-Put it up
The first to attack is Hamada's team
And Matsumoto's team guesses
Yes, ready to go
Hamada's team used how many rubber bands
So few
A very light touch
So let's begin
Hamada's team... OPEN!
So hard
-Who is this?
This is just 8?
Ah, this...
This is...
The amount is low
It's tough
-Let's discuss it
Is this really just with 8?
Yes
-Yes
This is awesome!
We did it!
We're in trouble
-This person's original foundation is too tough
We did it in such a short time!
I know the answer and still can't even see it!
Fujimon you know loads of people!
No idea at all
There is no such person!
Very good
Well, well, well
-That's a win
No clue at all
May I speak?
Not a formal answer
-Not a formal answer
FUNKY's Kato?
No, it's not right
Would he come here?
Can he do this?
He's not lacking work, right?
-I couldn't say
How about Takahashi?
COWCOW's
Tada?
Ah, Tada?
No
With the rubber bands it does look similar
Yes
Have to rewind
You have to imagine what it was like before the rubber bands were put on
It's almost time
It's kind of close
Okay, okay, that's him. That's it
Do you have an answer?
Suddenly it came to me
Are you ready? Team Matsumoto, please give your answer
Miyashita Kusanagi's Miyashita
Miyashita
Miyashita Kusanagi's Miyashita, did you guess correctly?
Now let's have the guest remove the rubber bands
Eh? I don't know
A face like this with just 8
This this this
I can't see it now
Then please take off the rubber bands
-Who are you?
Who the hell are you?
Hmmm
It's a big change
Did we get it right?
No? Who is it?
Still don't know yet, ah don't know yet
Who?
The correct answer is Miyashita Kusanagi's Miyashita
Great!
Matsumoto's team answered correctly
Barely got it right
So close!
Awesome
That's right
Guessed correctly
That's awesome!
Guessed it right!
You were right!
When I first saw it, I really couldn't tell
Miyashita, how did the rubber bands feel?
Being constricted by the rubber bands is surprisingly painful
But in comparison to the rubber band,
Backstage, Hamada said "Don't move"
And at the same time hit me here, which was much more painful
My apologies
Hold still!
So Hamada, who started the game, did not receive any points
So, Matsumoto's team
How many rubber bands did you use?
An aggressive approach
Of course we're going to attack
Yes
So, Matsumoto's team... OPEN!
Eh?
Very good
Who is this!?
You're a little too close!
Just stand there!
Don't go any further!
This is not good. This is not good
Who is this guy?
Please keep your face close
Is he a grandpa?
There is no sense of freshness
-No sense of fresh meat
This... this thing...
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU!?
Yes!
-Don't do that
Don't describe people like that!
Yes!
Seems to be completely unclear
This is a grandpa, right?
No, I think he may not be that old
Not that old?
-Seriously?
That's what i'm thinking
Guess someone at least
This is not good
Just now she said...
Please hurry up!
I guess it's pretty similar
Quite similar
Go for it
There is nothing else
-Nothing else
Okay?
I really can't tell
I can't recognize them!
So, Hamada's team, please state your answer
Lasher!
Itamae
-Itamae
Seriously unrecognizable
Are you sure?
I can't tell
-I don't really recognize them, but...
Okay, please come to the front and take off the rubber bands
That...
Hey, who's that!?
Guessed right
The hair really is the main feature
Just looking at the face isn't enough
I didn't expect you to guess correctly
Honestly, couldn't you guys guess quicker!?
Seriously, you can't guess a bit quicker!?
I'm really sorry
-It's Lasher Itamae!
Awesome
Hamada's team answered correctly
-They didn't give up
So impressive!
I couldn't do it too harshly
But I did think "the face could be more taut"
But I really couldn't do it
No, it's not a big deal
It's fine to do anything to him
-No, no it's not
Don't point like that
So, both sides answered correctly in the first round
So neither side scored points
Can we see it now?
You can see it
Guests for the second round for both sides are women
After selecting,
The same process as before takes place back stage
This is very good
-Further up
That's perfect
I can't tell
-I can't tell either
That's it, let's do it
-We'll win, we'll win
So, Hamada's team guesses first in the second round
How many bands?
More than the theory!?
Still very much on the offensive
Yes, a little bit, but I still want to win
-Really making it difficult
OK OK OK
Then, please get ready...
Matsumoto's team... OPEN!
Eh?
-Very good
Don't cross the line, don't cross the line
Very good
So that's how it is
This...
-I can't tell
The skin still looks good
The skin is good
-The skin is very good
Age can't be discerned
But the skin is nice
The mouth may be a feature
Mouth... where have I seen this type of mouth before...
Please don't think about it
This is a comedian, right?
Has the feeling of a comedian
The eyebrows also haven't moved much
So, it's almost time to answer
Go fo it, that's it
Please, Hamada
Do Hamada's team have an answer?
-Do you have an answer?
Was it Hamada that said it?
Not quite sure though...
Then, let's hear from Hamada's team
Enoue
-Yes
Enou
-Nietzsche's
Ah~
That means it's not right
Can we try again?
Really!
You've shown your hand?
-What is all this?
What a bore!
No, why are you dancing!?
So strange!
Let's dance, everybody!
Let's all dance!
What a botch!
Who the hell is it?
-Please can the guest come to the front
Who is this?
Have you met her?
You must've
Really?
Hamada-san hasn't?
No, no, I'm sure we've met her before
Really?
-Yes, i'm sure of it
Can the guest please remove the rubber band
-Who is this?
I really can't tell
The face is all puffed up
Looks a lot like my friend's wife
How is that possible
So, the correct answer is Papa's Ai Nappu
Ai Nappu
It's Papa's Ai Nappu
How is this possible to recognize
Great!
So, Matsumoto's team used 11 rubber bands
And scored 9 points
Yes, yes!
Matsumoto's final score was 9 points
How many rubber bands did Hamada use?
-How many did we use?
If Matsumoto's team is not correct either,
The score will be 9-10, and Hamada's team will win
How will it end?
Eh? It's tough!
Eh?
Very good, very good
You really did it!
I can't even recognize it
I think your team's gonna guess wrong
I forgot who it was
This isn't a comedian, right?
No, it feels like someone that has their eyebrows done nicely
Like maybe Inoue Sakura
Inoue Sakura
Looking at it, i'm struck by the beautiful eyebrows
Is it Tomoko Kaneda?
Or is the skin a little too good?
The makeup looks different
Makeup!
The makeup isn't the same?
The makeup is very well done
Great eyeliner, seriously
It's almost done, isn't it?
Eh? I don't know
Is it Nora?
-Nora?
No it can't be, is that Nora?
Nora or Remi, choose one!
Totally different, right?
Don't just consider people named Hirano!
Then let's say Nora
-Nora
Then, Mastumoto's team, your answer please!
Nora Hirano
-Norora Hirano...Nora
What are you saying?
Is it the right answer?
Please come forward
Huh?
-No way
Not at all!
Who are you!?
Today's clothes are really good
Who is this?
This type of clothing...
Who the hell is it?
-Even looking at the clothes I can't tell
Please remove the rubber bands
Ann Lewis?
Will Hamada's team end up winning?
-Looks like Yukihina
No way!
Is this your first job?
That's awesome!
-Hey!
Who the hell is it?
Eh, eh?
Hey, is it that person?
Eh?
I'm Nishiyama Moshi
-Eh~?
The answer is Nishiyama Moshi
Yeah!!!
No, no, no
This is really...
-Good!
Wrong answer!
Can't you choose your work?
-Can't you guess?
So, Hamada's team wins
Yes!
OK OK
Awesome!
No, the only reason they won is because of Hamada's sadistic streak, right?
He was obsessed with pulling the upper lip upward
If you can achieve this level of effect it'd be good
To the top
Stop, pull up and stop
So it can be said that people who have 10 rubber bands on their faces are unrecognizable, right?
Yes, it is
It's proven
This is the proof
We won!
-Verification over!
Thank you very much for your assistance!
Next introduces and tests the theories of people throughout the globe
Tonight's presenters are...
Fujiwara!
-Thank you for having us
We're gonna do it!
I'm going hard today
-Going for it!
Thank you for having us
I have a question for everyone
When was the last time everyone pissed themselves?
It wasn't very long ago for me
Sometimes it feels like it if you haven't pissed very carefully
Yes indeed
-It happens
What about you, Nami?
-Probably about 5 years ago for me
Not that long ago
-So you can leak too?
I was holding it and shaking on the way home from the parking lot
I was struggling with the key to open the door then I just suddenly relaxed
It all came out
-All of it?
Not a drop left?
-Yes
You just couldn't hold it anymore
If you just let half of it out it doesn't help
So if someone knew an acquaintance pissed their pants, how would they react?
It depends on the character of the other party, but they probably wouldn't react too strongly
Right?
-That's most likely the case
So, this time we bring you a theory related to urination
This is it:
If the person who receives a "happy surprise" pisses themselves, the instigator's face will instantly turn serious
What the heck?
If it was a dog it'd be understandable
-That's true
It's normal for dogs to do that
-Indeed
Well, we have already verified it so let's take a look at the VTR
If the person receiving a "happy surprise" pisses themselves, the instigator's face will instantly turn serious
This time the participants thought they'd be appearing on "Surprise Meeting Between Ordinary People and Idols"
A "We'll Make Your Dreams Come True SP"-style program
This teenager will be so happy to see his idol that he pisses himself
The verification target is...
Fuwa's here!
Fuwa
She herself is no stranger to laughing so much that she leaks
Therefore, a perfect candidate in regard to both popularity and urination
The teenager isn't expecting to see you today
He's completely unaware that his wish is going to be fulfilled
Ah ~ this is a gonna be a happy surprise!
Are they here now?
-Not yet, they will be shortly
Tell me when they come, then, I'm too loud
After a fake opening
It's finally time to meet
Thank you for being here
-Thank you for having me
Fuwa will appear from behind during the interview
The standard surprise process
What will happen?
Thank you for your continued encouragement!
Whether on TV or on youtube, you are always entertaining
I really like you
So please meet with me, please!
Good morning-pi! I'm Fuwa!
Ah!
Eh?
Eh? Wait a second...
Even Fuwa has...?
Eh?
Eh? Wait a second...
It would be like this
Should change faces...
Eh? Hey this is a leak...
Maintaining the atmosphere as much as possible
Hey, wait, you're leaking?
Joyful in the face of urination
As expected, Fuwa shows a serious expression for a moment
No wonder
-Human nature
Wait, I have a change of shorts. Wait for me
Eh? What should I do?
Do you have pants? Can you change your pants again?
I didn't bring any with me...
-You didn't bring any?
I should have some, wait a second
Eh? Wait, what should I do, this will be weird, right?
You can't cut for a moment, can you? What should I do
So gentle!
Fuwa is so gentle!
While considering the editing problem, the happy teenager is led to the bathroom
She lends him her own shorts
Is his mother here?
His dad was here
-Dad?
And also...
Did you wipe it? Why not? Unbelievable!
Why is no one wiping it
No toilet paper or something?
Use some paper towels to wipe it
Urine on the floor
If you wipe it when it's dry it'll still smell
Sprinkle some of this
As expected of someone with experience of incontinence
She looks like she is used to it and even directs the cleaning of the urine on site
And then
We can't do another surprise, right?
He's already met you now
Just focus on the upper part of the body, because the pants changed
Just use the top half of the shot
The leak is treated as if it never  happened, and instructions are given to the editor
Just start with his happy expression after seeing me and cut it
Very good, it suits you, it suits you!
Pretty good
Ver good, and it's okay, don't worry about it, I leak too
We are the Leaky Pee Alliance
-Yeah
At school you can tell your classmates that "Fuwa and I are pee-pee allies"
So gentle!
And so, the truth is revealed
This is not the "Happy Surprise" crew
Hey, what? No way!
What do you think it is?
Eh? WedDown?
-Yes
Eh--?
You're a spy of WedDown!? Are you kidding me?
Ah right
Just now I put on a really happy performance
In fact, I was terrified
I thought to myself, "No way!"
In summary, people who have experienced it themselves are very gentle
So everyone, what do you think?
I'm sure it'd be like that!
Indeed, it would be like that, the normal human reaction
Fuwa is still very impressive
-Very gentle
She also took the editing into consideration
What exactly were we supposed to learn through this theory though?
The matter of urine leakage is damaging to the atmosphere
Time and space seem to freeze for a moment
And also that when meeting fans you should prepare an extra pair of pants
That's not necessary
We also have another theory for you today
Have you ever slept in a bunk bed?
I did, when I was a kid
Yeah?
-It was a bunk bed
How about Matsumoto-san?
-I never have
Not with your brother?
-No
Ones with a top and bottom bunk
-I said no already!
I'm scared
You've said it so many times already
Ask me again, maybe something will come back to me
Did you and your brother sleep in a bunk bed
-I already said NO!
What do you want from me?
Why did I have to ask again?
Anyway, this time we bring you a theory related to bunk beds
It is this:
There are no couples that sleep in bunk beds
What is it?
-We have bunk beds in our house
No way, that'd make the hypothesis instantly incorrect
Yes
-A ready-made example
Really?
Right now?
-Now
Do you sleep on the top or bottom?
We have two bunk beds in our house
I sleep on the top bunk, my son sleeps on the bottom bunk
And with the other, my daughter sleeps on the top bunk and my husband sleeps on the bottom bunk
It isn't that two adults sleep on the same bunk bed
-Yes
That's fine then
It's because my daughter prefers bunk beds
Two bunk beds in the same room?
-Yeah
Is your home an army dormitory!?
With an officer shouting "Get UP!!"
Didn't Hamada sleep on a five-tier bed during high school?
What's a five-tier bed, a bunk bed is just top and bottom
What sort of bed is a five-tier bed!?
You can jump from the top and parachute down like a solider
And mess people up
-Sounds like something out of Ashita no Joe
No couples sleep in bunk beds
When it comes to bunk beds, they are usually used by two brothers
Or in student dormitories, which gives the impression that they are mostly used just for children
That's the image that usually comes to mind
-Yeah, yeah
So, are there any adults using bunk beds?
First, we enquired with a bedding store
Then searched on SNS
The survey found...
This 44-year-old woman who currently lives in Fukushima Prefecture
I started sleeping on this bunk bed about 4 years ago
Usually I sleep underneath and my mother sleeps on top
Mom?
Surprisingly, a mother and daughter aged 44 and 73 use a bunk bed
The mom doesn't sleep below?
-You'd think that'd be better
That's quite tough
So we asked them to show us how it looks
Is it more comfortable to sleep on the top or the bottom bunk?
The top bunk is hotter in summer
Although the top bunk is for adults
I always worry about whether she's going to fall out
To be honest, I don't recommend it
So, why are these two adults sleeping in a bunk bed?
To save space in the bedroom
Originally, I wanted to my son and I to use the bunk bed
To begin with my son slept on the top bunk
But as he grew up, it switched to my mother
My son now sleeps on the floor here
So adding the 16-year-old son, it's like this
Three people sharing one bedroom
The next person is an adult who sleeps on a bunk bed
This 21-year-old woman currently lives in Tokyo
I sleep on the top bunk and my grandmother sleeps on the bottom bunk
For about 12 years since elementary school, I've slept in the bunk bed with my grandmother
What are you laughing at?
Now one is 21 and one is 77
You're so noisy
-What are you laughing at?
How does it feel to sleep here?
-Very comfortable
What's so funny about this
And,
I have three brothers
In the opposite room is my mother and two brothers in a three-tier bed
Three-tier bed!?
-I've never heard of one!
Three-tier bed?
-That's right
My two sons and I sleep in this three-tier bed
The top is the second eldest, the middle is me, and the bottom is the third eldest
The bottom pulls out
So you pull it out when it's time to sleep?
-Yes, yes
At first, my three sons slept here
But since my oldest son is no longer at home, I sleep in the middle
The second eldest is 26, I'm 49, and the third eldest is 24
We are all adults now
Everyone is an adult
Total age: 197 years
Spread across a total of five beds
Why add the years together
Although several groups of adults sleeping in bunk beds were found
Are there really no couples?
Oh yeah...
-The main topic
However, suddenly
The next group of adults that sleep in bunk beds are...
What is this image!?
This 36-year-old woman who lives in Akita Prefecture
How do you use this bunk bed when you sleep?
I sleep on the bottom and my husband sleeps on the top
To sum up, finally
We found a bunk bed couple
By the way, the way they fall asleep is a bit strange
The orientation of their heads is not the same
But the man is very happy with the current bunk bed state
He peeks from above to see if I'm awake
And seems very happy when he does it
I think the person who invented the bunk bed is really too awesome
But, why did you decide to use this bed?
We took it over because originally it was for our children
Every day they fought about who would sleep on the top bunk
I'll sleep on top!
-Today is my turn!
Is this footage necessary?
Concerning who sleeps on the top bunk, they often pulled and shoved each other next to the ladder
Not needed, not needed, we all understand
This makes it very easy to understand
And also the one in the lower bunk kicks the one above from below
To make it more visually appealing, the VTR was prepared for the audience
It's good to have such things to be able to understand
What are you doing!?
I see
Day and night the siblings argued endlessly
So there was an upward kick
Yes, yes, much easier to understand with the VTR
That's enough you two!
If this continues, then father and I will sleep on the bunk bed!
That's right, didn't she just say that?
So that's it!
Wait a minute, what is this?
And so, the two adults slept on the bunk bed while the children slept on the floor
In all of the current findings
Every family originally bought the bunk beds for their children
Apart from this couple, who now live in Tokyo
Soon after the wedding I asked for a bunk bed
I think it's reasonable for us not to interfere with each other
Since my wife requested it, I had to accept
In summary, there are two types of couples
There are then
Couples sleeping in bunk beds
It's not a big deal,
But the VTR recreation...
It didn't have much content
It's not so much a matter of it not having much content, more that it wasn't necessary
Not needed, not needed
Seriously what the hell, that VTR was so annoying
Wait, what was so annoying about it?
We shot the VTR in order to make the audience understand the situation more clearly
I don't think the audience for this show is expecting that kind of VTR
Explanations for layman aren't clear though
No, they said it quite clearly
It was exactly the same as the picture I had in my head
Comedians have more imagination though
-Yes that's true
The average person has nothing in their head
-Yes, better brains
What a waste!
-The picture doesn't immediately come to mind
Not everyone can do it
Has our program's staff been replaced?
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03