Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let's get on with our first presenter please
It's Jinnai Tomonori
Soh, the project I brought is...
"Soh"?
Not so, but soh?
So
Let's get to this, this time the theory I bring you is this
6th No matter who views these comedians' funniest moments, they'll find them interesting
This is it
This is the 6th edition
Yes, the 6th edition so it has become a regular project
What do you think about this, Matsumoto?
I'm sure there will be many editions of this
Since its focusing on old footage
It doesn't cost anything at all
Just spending a little
How much?
6th No matter who views these comedians' funniest moments, they'll find them interesting
First of all, Oda
This one is more than 20 years old
But I still get a great feeling when watching it
Higashino's project of wrestling with idols
Carrie
Throwing female idols around, kicking them
It's pretty tough to do
At one point, Higashino, who had unilaterally suppressed the idol, was attacked
The referee was Hamada, who was fanning the flames
He incited the idol to get fired up
As a result, Higashino was beaten
Lets see his reaction
This is not the kind of response you can make when asked to
Its a one-time miraculous reaction
What?
This is Idol vs. Higashino: The shocking ending
So nostalgic
That's right, this one
This idol is very strong
Starting from here
Strangled
Yes, it starts here
Awesome
I remember
Throwing up!
This
This expression and...
I couldn't believe my eyes...
Not sure its a performance, rewind and watch it again
Really throwing up
I can't get over it
Watching this as a student left me with a strong impression
Oda's funniest moment: Higashino throwing up
And kicked down into it
Kicked into his own vomit
Next is Knights' Hanagawa
Senba Kitcho's press conference, which caused an uproar more than 10 years ago
The boss's pauses, intonation, timing and facial expressions
There are also serious ones
It's all textbook
His most interesting moment is from 10 years ago
A press conference for Senba Kitcho, a high-class restaurant that became a sensation in 2007 because of the food falsification issue
It's like a skit
When answering a reporter's question, the owner's wife whispered instructions to the son who answered the questions
Known as the whispering boss lady
So this is it!
You don't know it?
Its difficult to perfect pauses like this in skits
Especially for current affairs manzai
There will be times when I can't write
And when reading again, i'm forced to go back and reflect
Its kind of like musicians going back to listen to The Beatles
If you can't decide, go back to Senba Kitcho to reflect
A textbook example, this press conference
So, what was the reason for the change in the labeling?
That...
Louder
Looking into each other's eyes
We had a weak awareness of compliance
The shot is also interesting
That is, there is no subjective sense of trying to deceive consumers, right?
No
Say "we didn't think"
Thought people couldn't hear
We didn't think
He said it
And made a statement
to avoid responsibility
Too funny
The cameraman is hesitating
We didn't know what we were talking about
This must be a first
I'm really sorry
It's interesting no matter how many times I watch it
And with the mother-son relationship, it's even better...
It's probably always like this with them
Telling the child "don't do this"
It reveals some of the normality of mother-son relationships
The son would normally say "enough"
But couldn't say it because he's at a press conference
Plus the son's expressions make it all the more interesting
By the way, the Senba Kitcho name has now been abandoned
Instead, they have opened a store called "Yuki" in Kitashinchi
Apparently, the boss's wife occasionally appears in the restaurant
If you go there, you may meet her
Next is Mouchu Gakusei
A few years ago, I happened to see it on TV
The ranking of Yoshimoto artists
A program like "Personal Information Disclosure Yoshimoto Ranking
It was a live show
Diane's Tsuda was very impressive
It was revealed that the staff said a lot of bad things about Tsuda
Lots of examples
Tsuda's response was very impressive
His rebuke was really powerful
So much so that I couldn't go to sleep afterwards
It was just replaying in my mind over and over
Here is Tsuda's rebuke
Photography assistant in her 20s
As usual, he didn't talk at all during a food location shoot
But he was super loud when eating pasta
Don't say "as usual"!
Oi! Assistant photographer, don't say "as usual"!
"As usual!"
I think this reaction is really strong
"As usual"!
He also ate a lot of bread
What's wrong with that?
What's wrong with eating bread?
Why can't you eat bread?
Eating bread is a good thing, right?
Eating bread is a good thing!
Eating bread is good, what the hell!?
He's given reasons
You ate a lot
What's wrong with that?
Did I eat it all? Eat the whole store?
Ah, I still remember it very well
I especially remember it when i'm ill
It helps me recover
The legendary line "What's wrong with eating bread?"
I probably won't be able to sleep tonight either
Its stamped to the inside of my eyelids
The moment that Mouchu Gakusei likes the most
Tsuda's bread-related criticism
What's wrong with eating bread?
Next is Kawahara
His choice must be weird
Utsunomiya's new comedy
Although a junior
The name is wrong
On Instagram or something
She did something
Made something
It was really interesting
Or maybe infuriating
Irritatingly funny
What do you mean?
The video of Utsunomiya
What is this
This is it
What the hell?
What's she spending a long time doing?
What is it?
I see
It fits in
It's really interesting
Awesome
So surreal
Because it's Kawahara!
The excitement of not knowing what's happening
Then she put in a mushroom
This point is pretty common
Not very common
Everyone would put in a mushroom in
But after that...
She looks at the camera
The last laugh
I don't understand the feelings
Wondering about the emotions is interesting
Putting mushrooms in is something that probably everyone has done
Did you see it?
Hama-chan...Hama-chan, did you see it?
Don't say Hama-chan
Did you see it, Hama-chan?
Then watch 1 more time... please play it 1 more time
He saw it!
Hosting is a big headache
Next is Minamikawa
Two years ago, Shochiku had a 1 minute video
It came from a competition which was voted on
Because it is something that can be done at home
And because they were all comedians
They involved parody skits
But among them was Iwami
She is a 48 year old entertainer
This senpai did something that made people wonder, "Hey, why did you do this?
With the words  "Residential Area Stairway Challenge", it begins
They couldn't leave their building
So, this 48-year-old woman
She went from the 4th floor down to the 1st floor of her building
She did a challenge to get down the stairs in 40 seconds
For what? Who would do this?
The reasons for this are unknown
Why would you shoot this?
You can't even hear what's being said
The image is also very confusing
As a comedia with 20 years of experience
Its a bit of a clumsy performance
It would be interesting to include all of them
This was played on my web show
Really for only hardcore comedy fans
And it created a small-scale sensation
The "Residential Area Stairway Challenge" begins
Hello, I'm Iwami, and I'm here for the project "Kakuza at Home"
※Kakuza is a theater located in Dotonbori, Osaka.
I'm going to do the "Residential Area Stairway Challenge"
Nice piano
I am now on the 4th floor
The light is still flickering after being replaced
Why?
I want to go down the stairs from the 4th floor to the 1st floor in 40 seconds
Fix it!
The biggest challenge is on the 2nd floor
Because a man on the 2nd floor has left his door open
Can't hear it at all
I have to get through there fast
So, the "Residential Area Stairway Challenge" begins!
The middle-aged woman is going down the stairs
Causing trouble
What kind of challenge is this?
Ah, the door is open
Did it. Easy pass
The "Residential Area Stairway Challenge" was a success!
It's so confusing...
No matter how many times I look at it its still good
The meaning is indeed unclear
At the start, the light is flickering
So why shoot there?
Wouldn't starting from the door be better?
Why start by wearing shoes?
Having a good laugh
There's a door open on the 2nd floor?
That doesn't really matter
Why not find out why its open afterwards
The guy who lives there said "electromagnetic waves can't be dissipated" so he kept the door open
So many points
Then Iwami
Lived there for 40 years, been downstairs every day for 40 years...
It's so long, this commentary
5 seconds to get down the stairs in elementary school
What are you laughing at?
"When I was in elementary school, I could get down the stairs in 5 seconds by centrifugal force"
So much to say!
Minamikawa's favorite moment
Combining multiple factors in a residential area down stairs challenge
Watching it again
The full version again
Did it. Easy pass
The "Residential Area Stairway Challenge" was a success!
Okay, that's it
Impressive, didn't even say how long it took her
The results were not revealed
-It only would've taken a few seconds
It might've been longer
What do you think, Meruru?
So that's where "whispering boss lady" came from
I've heard people say it, but I didn't know what it referred to
I always thought it was a folktale
So it really happened!
Speaking of Tsuda
On Owarai no Hino
That part I really liked...
"Goigoisu"
Super funny
-It's really funny
What?
Actually, it's not funny at all
On the contrary
Let's welcome the next presenter
It's Fujwara!
Enough
Next is not a theory but instead a project we've all been waiting for
MONSTER LOVE
Looking forward to it
This time, it's the 4th installment of Kuro's love project
I really like this project.
-Really?
I watched it beforehand and watched each part twice
I love it so much, its so good
But what do women think of this project?
What do you think, Meruru
I also watched it
I told everyone I "watched it for work reasons"
Don't want others to think it's what I want to see
No, it's not
I felt ashamed
It's okay to watch for non-work reasons
Its necessary to watch in advance
So, here's what's happened so far
Kuro-chan and the women recruited by the program who like Kuro-chan started living together in Okinawa
Among them are people just pretending to like Kuro-chan
Last time, Kuro-chan mistook Risa, who really liked him, for a pretender and eliminated her
Yes.
-What a shame
You are really...
That scene was really great
A great scene
Then after the elimination
Richi kissed Kuro-chan after discussing whether his mouths stink or not
-A great scene
That part when they were talking about if his mouth stinks
-Back and forth
The psychological warfare of breath holding
What?
It's a psychological war of smell
I was in the dressing room of TBS once
There were several female make-up artists around
Everyone's hands stopped moving
So it'll stop
So a lot of people must be happy to see this
What?
CPAP
-Treatment of apnea
Who?
It's a good thing she didn't laugh out loud
Indeed
Aki-kun
Wake up~
-Miku
Good morning
Darth Vader!
What's going on?
This is CPAP, because of apnea
※Continuous positive airway pressure ventilation system
Oh I see
Not "Oh I see"
There are other things you should ask, right?
Oh I see
I've made breakfast. Want to join me?
Of course
Then I'll wait for you in the dining room
Ok
Seems like an act
I'm in a good mood this morning
An angry expression
Just the two of them
Looks delicious!
Great!
You went to culinary school?
Yes, I trained as a pastry chef
So I've been trying to get Kuro-chan to eat freshly made food
Thought I'd bake some cookies if I had time today
Will you eat them if I do?
Absolutely.
-Really?
Then I'll make more
I'm gonna get fat
You're fat enough already
Can you accompany me to the place I want to go later today?
There is a place I've always wanted to go with you, just the two of us
You've become so aggressive
So embarrassing
What's wrong with this guy?
Good morning
Handsome man's lines
It's early
Thank you for the food
I'll go first
The atmosphere is a bit weird
Where are you going?
They'd surely ask
Miku has somewhere she wants to go
Yes
-I'll leave you to it
The atmosphere is tense!
Bye-bye
See you later
I'll go first
Obvious expressions
A date?
It's a date, right?
So uncomfortable. She's so aggressive
I told you, we don't need this
Its needed!
Ah its starting
That's enough!
So cute
Everyone is so cute
Don't smell it. Don't smell it
So trendy
We're here?
-Here?
Yes, here
The place I've always wanted to come with Aki-kun
You wanted to come here?
-Yes!
Up here?
-Up here
Glasses?
Super beautiful!
Super beautiful
That's awesome!
You wanted to come here, right?
She said it already!
I wanted to see this view with Aki-kun
This bell
It is said that if you ring it with your lover, you will be happy together
So I want to do it with you
"With your lover" means we're already lovers?
Is it ok to be lovers?
Well, lets do it together then
Is that a yes, then?
Didn't say yes, just said ring the bell
Let's start 3 2 1
It rang!
It's ringing!
No shit!
-It will definitely ring!
It's ringing!
You rang it!
So happy
I am also happy
Ah, they sell local specialties.
-Oh, really?
That was dangerous, just then
And pendants
Thought something was gonna happen
They're heart-shaped
Oh, really?
So cute
There are 2 in a box, shall we buy a pair?
1 for 1?
-Yes
Ok
It's a beautiful day
The sea can be seen so clearly
Want to sit here?
Yeah
We've sat down.
-Yeah
"We've sat down"
The view in front is super beautiful!
I wanted to have a good conversation in a place where I can relax
I'm glad to finally have some time
You stare at me like this
It makes my heart burn
It's burning?
-Yeah
So powerful, such powerful words
Can that burn my heart too?
Ah, the other way around?
I thought it was already burning~
I want it to be a bit more intense
If this was a performance you'd laugh out loud
Feel it?
Impressive
I've received a lot of Miku's love
You got it?
I got it
But I can't just focus on Miku completely.
-Yeah
If I only talk to Miku
The others will start to be biased toward you
Because I know that women's jealousy is very scary
What do you know about it?
It's like a big deal
So although I like you a lot
I can't be alone with you everyday
Everyone is very nice, all very lovely
And Aki-kun has to choose one
It must be very difficult
It's not easy!
Such an angry expression
Don't use that expression
Because I am considering very sincerely, so it is very difficult
Eh, are your eyes moist?
It's hard to see Aki-kun feel bad, it makes me feel bad too
I'm sorry, i'm very happy to be with you
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry
Well... I hope you can rely on me more
His brain is messed up
Give me a hug
Come on
Super aggressive
For men, this isn't unbearable
Where are you looking?
Moist eyes looking to the distance
I like you so much
I like you most in the world
That's not good
Do not maintain this distance
After that, you can pamper me
Is that okay?
-Yes
I'll pamper you, then
I can be pampered at any time
You are so gentle to me, despite there being no exclusivity...
Wouldn't you like to have me all to yourself?
It is Aki-kun's decision who to choose
How dare you say that!
The lines of the flirtatious man
In Aki-kun's mind, there are many girls
But as long as you come back to me
I'm fine with it
Sorry
It's also tough for you, right? Sorry
So I'm not the only one under pressure!
I can't watch it!
How dare you say such things!
But yesterday you chose me
I'll make a deal with you
I will pamper you, and Mike will pamper me
-Yeah
This expression
After that, we can have dinner with other girls and go play together
But I believe you will come back to me in the end
Quite heartfelt
Feels like the real thing
Trust me.
-Ok
Trust me~
-He'll surely betray her
What a great day!
What the hell?
So happy
The opposite of a great day
What a great day!
Anti-great day
Kuro-chan
Who is it?
Good morning
What's going on?
So rare
You slept a long time, right?
The first time?
I'm sorry for sleeping for a long time
Your room has a lot of plastic bottles and a variety of things, right?
It's all been revealed!
I can stretch my legs to sleep in between things
So some say
Seems a lot like Kuro-chan
It's pretty good to have similarities
Pretty good? You're weird
But what's wrong?
Oh... the buffalo
There are places to experience buffalos
What does it mean to experience buffalos
Here?
-In Okinawa
Really?
Can we go together?
Here we go again
Shall we go?
-Let's go
Go on, go on
A buffalo experience surely is plowing a field or something
Enough, you're so annoying!
We get it!
What do you mean experience buffalos
He said it last time
Right at the ass
Ah, it's moving, it's moving
Its horns are impressive
I heard that you eat chocolate while you sleep
Holding hands
Eat chocolate in bed with your eyes closed like this...
Eh, you wouldn't?
No, it's strange
You can try it. You can try it
Not "you can try", its a unique skill
Not much of a good vibe going on
When I got up, I found chocolate all over my back...
-That's not good
So happy
Ah, thank you
So big
So much meat
Looks delicious
Yummy, yummy!
It's super delicious!
-Super delicious
Ah, you're making mini ramen!
I'm eating it like that
Yes
So youthful
This is how it's done.
-It's so cute!
Can I put green onions too?
Please put in the green onion too
Here we go then
Delicious
Seems very natural!
Are you happy with me?
Very happy
Aren't you happy now?
Super happy
-Happy, right?
To be honest, today is probably the funnest time i've had
Look, you're saying it again
Rapidly heating up
Surprisingly, you like that type of girl
I do!
I really do!
I feel like I can see something I haven't seen before
I thought I was teaching her, but I actually learned a lot
She's more youthful than me, much moreso
So if such a girl says stuff like this to me its hard not to be affected
Okay
Mina
-Impressive!
Heating up rapidly, but only just now
When you see her, it makes you feel like the others are acting.
-That's right
Mina is quite natural
She's natural but not as aggressive
But she's going for it now because she thinks "they're all getting closer"
What do you think, Meruru?
I'm most unsure about Miku
Seeing Kuro-chan so closely he also seems pretty serious
Indeed, it must be tough not to laugh when seeing his CPAP
Isn't that too strange?
"Because I have apnea." "Oh I see", that was it
So true
Very shocking!
She should have asked more
The person you like wears something like that
I have doubts
-Because of that?
Yeah
Ah, making a snack
She's making her move
Heart-shaped
Ok
I'm back
Welcome back
Ah, great. Baked cookies for me?
Yes, I made cookies for Blackie while I was waiting.
-Well done
Can I have a piece?
Its just finished, wait for it to cool down
By the way, we
Bought fireworks
Great!
Looks fun
Whoever's goes out first loses!
What?
What a boring rule
So fast, so fast, so fast!
Ri's is so fast
Don't you have any originality?
It's really fun!
How has living together been?
Every day goes by so fast
We went to a lot of places, aquariums and so on
And had fun at the beach
Flew away
The one who was flung away
To be honest, I'm happy
Being with everyone like this
You say you like me
I hope that lasts forever
It's tough to think people will still be eliminated
Although we are rivals, everyone has a good relationship
It would be nice if we could continue to be together
Oh, I'm so happy.
-Yes
5 people doing fireworks together
Ah yes, didn't you bake cookies?
Let's eat
Miku made them
I'm so happy!
-So happy!
It's cooled down
I want to eat it
Eh?
What?
They're all broken...
Someone's up to something
Why?
What is this twist?
A new genre
I put them here
Why is it like this?
Someone is angry?
Did someone accidentally knock it off?
Someone must have done it on purpose
No
I didn't come down from the room
Jealousy
It looks suspicious. At first glance, Richi is the most suspicious
Why is it broken like this?
This expression...
Eh? Who did it? No way...
No, everyone came with great anticipation
Eh? Who did this?
I want to stop and take notes
Want to review again
Definitely not me
We went on several dates
Spent a lot of time together
Although looking at you guys like this I've always been jealous
She cries all the time!
I would never do such a thing...
But now you suspect me again
And you'll stick up for Miku
The relationship between you two will deepen further
More difficulties...
So who did it?
I think it was Miku
Baked it herself, smashed it herself?
Miku?
I think she broke it herself
I see
To make someone a villain
I also think it was Miku
You think so?
Yeah
I'm sorry. I'm sorry
I know it's hard for you too
I didn't expect the blame to be placed on you
What is this plot?
A sudden twist
Crying!
Surely not, why would you do such a thing
Although not me, but I do not want to suspect others
The good girl routine
Really?
Not resolved yet?
Tough
A lot of things happened just now
But I still want to rank properly
What'll happen?
The person's name who isn't called will have to say goodbye
Will the first place change this time?
1st place is
Richi
He trusts her
2nd place is
It'll be impressive if Miku isn't included
Will he eliminate her?
Miku
She fell in the rankings
The ranking has changed
Will she come forward?
In 3rd place...
For the person whose name isn't called, its goodbye
Hamada, what do you think of Mina?
Don't you think it's a little too natural?
Don't even use honorifics
You care about that?
-Courtesy?!
Mami, who was active at the beach
And Mina whose first date resulted in a rapid increase of good feelings
3rd place is
Who?
Who will be eliminated
Mina
She's eliminated
Today we are saying goodbye to Mami
Ok
If it's related to what just happened, I'd like you to reconsider
If not, I can accept it
Because there is no way for me to trust Kuro-chan
So I think it's better to cut it off here
So?
By the way, do you really like me?
No I don't
What a reaction!
So you don't like me?
No
Didn't you cry at the beginning when you were finally chosen?
-Yes.
Mami, you've passed. Congratulations
Fake tears?
The tears were not fake...
I was happy to be chosen
Regardless of whether I had feelings for you
Straightforward
Ruthlessly heartfelt
This time with Kuro-chan, i've really hated it
So blunt
Thank you
Thank you?
Please come back.
-Okay
Didn't drag it out
Wants to end it quickly, after all
Can't help it
"Please come back"
She said, "I don't like Kuro-chan at all"
And is she angry?
Very angry
And also said she hated out time together
Super scary
Why should...
It is obvious that I was cheated, why are you angry at me?
Luckily I eliminated her
If I had been more active
Maybe it won't be so
I never thought it would end this way
Hmm?
Because I thought by getting to this point I could become an idol
What is the story behind this
Very reluctant
What's going on, idol?
Good morning, everyone!
Good morning
I am Watanabe, the president of WACK
It was about this?
This time we called everyone over
Some of you may want to be idols, and some of you don't
This selection session
Is judged by "being liked by Kuro-chan"
Yes, MONSTER LOVE, without the knowledge of Kuro-chan
Was a simultaneous love project and idol audition
So that's the reason!
I get it now
Except for those who really like Kuro-chan
The others are audition participants who want to become idols
No point otherwise
Kuro-chan once also said
"If I can't get one person to like me"
"I can't get many people to like me"
I also agree with this statement
I hope everyone will work hard
Ok
And I hope that you will try to capture Kuro-chan's heart
So that's it!
Ok
This is the real theme
This time it's down to three people
-Yes
A lot has happened today too
A lot of things?
For example, the cookie incident
Ah, the cookie incident
That was me
That's scary!
Eh?
Well, I broke the cookies
Why would you do such a thing?
Why?
If it's just eating cookies
Everyone will say "tastes good" and nothing more
So by breaking them
I get to see how they'll respond
How will the one I like act?
Awesome
So I heard everyone's heartfelt words
Good thing I did
Oh my, it was amazing
I never thought it would be so effective
Very successful
So scary
Okay
So, everyone
Wait a minute wait a minute wait a minute
When he said "it was me" just now
I really wanted the CPAP
You don't need it, right?
Apnea?
My breathing was suspended
Scared to death!
I was really shocked
Everyone was shocked!
When the girls were arguing Kuro-chan's face was expressionless
Now when you think about it, it's super scary
Rewind, please look at his expression
There are girls crying
If I watch it at home
I eat after watching Wednesday Downtown
We eat late
I probably wouldn't be able to eat
You can still eat, right?
I rarely skip dinner
Cold all over
Can't sleep
This project is poisonous
There was also other stuff
"Eh, be an idol?" That was pretty shocking, wasn't it
What is this?
To become an idol, you have to make Kuro-chan like you
So all the people eliminated who don't like him
They shed tears for the path of the idol
After that, came a stronger dose of poison
It was very painful at the end
Doesn't like anything about him
"I've hated it"
You hated it?
Then said "thank you"
"Please come back"
"Please come back." "Thank you."
It's Kuro-chan's fault they wont become an idol
I wanna watch it all back from the first one
The meaning of the words has all changed
Very interesting. Every sentence
Indeed
So, there are two parts left
This is it for today?
That's it for today. But there's two more parts
Its the end of the day and we're going home?
-That's it
I feel so uncomfortable
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03