MC Hamada Masatoshi
(Downtown)
Hello everyone!
This is Suiyoubi no Downtown.
Bakarhythm
Konda Haruna
(Harisenbon)
Matsumoto Hitoshi
(Downtown)
Shigemori Satomi
(All) Hello!
Our first presenter
will come out now.
Presenter
Jinnai Tomonori
It's Jinnai Tomonori-san!
So everyone,
People who use Kansai-ben
despite not being from Kansai
Have you seen any?
Ah yes. Aren't there a lot of workers at Yoshimoto like that?
(Haruna) They use Kansai-ben
Ahh..
My manager who used to represent me
would always use Kansai-ben
I thought he might be from there but
he was from Chiba.
(Haruna) It is unpleasant
That's kind of gross
Bakarhythm, how about you?
When I was young,
a director at the time
despite not being a native
often spoke in Kansai-ben
so when I'd tell him my jokes, he'd say
(In Kansai-ben) That's funny!
<That's annoying
Ah, someone like that
I felt like my joke was being tainted
What are you talking about?
And with that,
I bring to you now:
Kansai Werewolf
Kansai Werewolf.
What does that mean?
Does everyone know
the Werewolf game?
A game where players are divided citizens and werewolves, and have to guess who the werewolves are
Werewolf game
Yep
You have citizens and wolves.
Everyone talks and tries
to figure out who the wolves are.
Kansai-ben version of that:
This time we have the
Find the fake Kansai natives
I see
After this...
Out of a group of people not known
for being from Kansai...
Who are the fake Kansai natives!?
we find out who's just pretending
(In Kansai-ben) I'm old Osaka
Then, at the convenience store...
No Plastic Bag Shopping Challenge
I can't believe how effective this is
And...
Is the portable shrine boil
disappearing because of Coronavirus?
Kansai Werewolf
Everyone, welcome to Kansai Werewolf.
Gamemaster
Jinnai Tomonori
Out of the 8 people here, 5 are from Kansai,
but not generally known for being so.
Hidden Kansai Natives.
The remaining 3 have no
connection at all to Kansai
but are pretending they're from there. fake Kansai natives.
Akira 100%
Hayashiya Pei
Inamura Ami
Jimon Terakado
Kawasaki Mayo
Watanabe Yōchi
Ôsawa Akane
Ōhashi Miho
The Kansai Werewolf players...
are these 8 people:
Of those 5 are really
from Kansai but
fake Kansai natives.
the remaining 3 are
The 3 fake Kansai natives
know who the other fakes are.
So, it's the first day
and it's elimination meeting time.
Detect the fake Kansai Natives using Kansai-ben intonation
Elimination meeting
Please try to find who the
fake Kansai natives are.
Let's begin.
Day 1
Elimination meeting
(In Kansai-ben)
I'm Terakado Jimon.
That's a bit too much isn't it?
What are you saying?
I'm definitely a Kansai native and
Jimon-san you don't seem like one at all.
Definitely not!
Just so you know, my accent is old Osaka
"washi"... ha ha ha
It's even old in Osaka. So young people there--
How many years ago was it?
It's been about 30 or 40 years.
The words have changed so much.
His Kansai-ben's awful.
Is he really from there?
Jinnai also doesn't know who the fake Kansai natives are
When I debuted in Tokyo, you had to speak Tokyo-ben
Well, I agree with that.
45 years ago when I came to Tokyo,
speaking Kansai-ben was unacceptable.
For your image.
That's right.
After people like Sanma-san appeared,
Kansai-ben quickly became acceptable.
That's right.
So we were trained...
"Ah, Kansai-ben? No, no, no"
Jimon-san you don't really need an image like that do you?
Huh?
Why are you criticizing me?
It feels like I'm being criticized. Why?
Isn't his intonation strange?
Weren't you using Tokyo words too?
Well, of course. I've been in Tokyo for 45 years.
Mayo-san doesn't strike me as a
native but his Kansai-ben is good
Jimon-san, you're very suspicious.
Huh?
Very suspicious.
People from Kansai don't speak slowly like that!
It's more energetic.
There aren't many people there like you.
After graduating middle school, I spent about 30 years as a battlefield cameraman.
So I've lived all over the world.
I knew about that but...
My Japanese has become
My Japanese has become strange, hasn't it?
I see. That's right.
I don't know about Watanabe-san.
Akira-san
Akira's suspicious
Akira-san doesn't do Kansai-style comedy, right?
You're usually naked, right?
Comedians from Kansai don't do stuff like that
I'm from Shiga. My father...
Huh? Say that again.
Shiga
Why don't you use Kansai-ben if you're from Shiga?
I moved to Saitama in the first year of middle school
Since then it's been like 35 years, hasn't it?
I've been here ever since then.
When I trained to be an actor, I also had my intonation corrected
Is that so?
I love Chaplin
If he's fake, he's good
1 minute remaining
OK everyone, 1 minute left
My elementary school teacher was Fujiyama Kanbi
So I'm deeply Osakan
The accent is totally different to Jimon-san's
Osaka baseball ground is nearby.
I've been going there since before
Nomura started at the Nankai Hawks.
Ah!
Wow!
So Osakan.
Appearance-wise you're the most
suspicious but I trust you the most.
Do you normally use Kansai-ben when performing?
When I'm in Osaka, to an extent
Why don't you use it when you're in Tokyo?
Flowery Tokyo-ben seems... n-natural
Suspicious!
What's that?
That's really suspicious
Day 1 complete
OK everyone
It's elimination time
Could all players please
select one player who they think
is a fake Kansai native.
These two are both suspicious
I can't decide
Jimon-san is the only suspicious one
It has to be Jimon-san
Voting is complete
Let's see who voted for who
Jimon-san thinks the fake Kansai native is...
Watanabe Yōichi
Without a doubt!
He hasn't spoken any proper Kansai-ben at all
Well... you haven't been speaking it either.
Huh?
Watanabe-san didn't speak in Kansai-ben.
That he didn't use it →
makes me suspicious.
I see. I see.
And Watanabe Yōichi-san
thinks the fake Kansai native is...
Terakado Jimon
The first word
out of your mouth was in Tokyo-ben.
Well.. I dunno. It might be a bluff.
There are all sorts of things
that are easy to say in a show like this.
But you shouldn't judge
someone for something so simple.
He's annoyed, isn't he?
Very suspicious.
All the remaining players
voted for these two.
Hayashiya Pei...
voted for Watanabe Yōichi.
However...
The remaining 5 all voted for Jimon.
Which means...
Jimon-san has been eliminated.
With 6 votes against him,
No way!
You're not going to air this, are you?
What the hell is going on here?
Day 1's elimination is Terakado Jimon.
Note: The other players can't hear this
I don't know either.
Well, shall we find out?
Here's the big reveal.
JImon-san, are you a fake Kansai native?
Or, are you actually from Kansai?
I'm from Kansai.
Huh?
From Hyogo.
I'm from there too, you know.
Kawanishi.
Kawanishi?
And I went to elementary school in Minō.
You'd go to Osaka?
Yes, to Osaka.
So, how come your Kansai-ben is so crappy?
Until when?
My 5th year of elementary school.
My whole childhood was in Osaka.
Then after I became an adult,
I returned a lot to Osaka for work too.
The truth is I've spent a long time there.
But you don't speak in Osaka-ben at all?
After I debuted with Dachō Club, I stopped needing it
Ryūhei-san is from Kansai, right?
Dachō Club
Ueshima Ryūhei
Yes, totally.
He also sounds fake when he uses it.
I knew about Ryū-chan but...
Yeah.
I didn't know about Jimon.
Can you say 'what the hell!' in Kansai-ben for us?
What the hell!
That's really awful.
And so, the remaining members are
are these 7.
And in Kansai Werewolf,
Just like in
the original,
A team wins by eliminating all of the opposing team's players.
OK everyone, it's day 2.
If this were the normal game, after elimination
a citizen would be eaten by a werewolf but
an upstanding Kansai citizen would never eat or get eaten by someone, so
for this game we have no such rule.
So, let's start the elimination meeting.
Day 2 begins
Can I say something?
Inamura-san hasn't said anything since we began
It wasn't on purpose.
I originally came here in the 5th year of elementary school
That's young.
So it hardly comes out at all.
What kind of situations do you use it in?
TL note: obaa-chan = grandmother
With my western... obaa
It's like something from
"Once upon a time in Japan"
So how would you speak to your western obaa?
I need someone to play her...
Pei-san
Could you be my obaa?
H-how would you like me to do it?
"How would you like me to do it?" is..
Like you're on the phone with her.
Obaa, how are you?
I'm good! How are you?
Ah... I'm [in KSB] fine!
"Fine"?
Suspicious.
There's something strange about Akira-san too
[in KSB] Really?
No, no. I'm good at Kansai-ben.
You're good but there's something off about it
Well it could be because he's from Shiga
Shiga and east of Biwa lake. It's really rural
But I also don't have that
impression of Ōhashi either...
1 minute remaining
Are you from Osaka?
Hyogo.
Do you normally speak in Kansai-ben?
When I'm working with Yoshimoto, lots of the staff are from Kansai,
so even the meetings will be in Kansai-ben.
That's when a little slips out.
Even though I trying to suppress it.
Ah... natural!
You're very Tokyo.
Watanabe-san, you're barely Kansai.
I feel like I'm losing the words...
Hahaha
Well.. it's bad already now...
I've been here in Tokyo since I came here at 13,
I've been married to a foreigner for 30 years.
But I still haven't forgotten it!
Well he's the same as me.
Even if the accent doesn't
come out, he's from Osaka
When they talk slowly you can't tell
You can't
Day 2 complete
It's elmination meeting time.
Who could it be?
Could all players please vote
for who they think...
is the fake Kansai native.
Voting is complete
Ōhashi-san thinks the fake Kansai native is...
Inamura Ami
Yes.
She may be from the west, but I feel like it's more Kyushu or Okinawa
Calling her obaa-chan "obaa",
I've never really heard that in Kansai
We don't say it
Next, Watanabe Ryōichi votes for...
Ōhashi Miho
Definitely.
Your native language is Tokyo-ben. Using your announcer skills, you speak Kansai-ben.
Your roots are in Tokyo.
Can he say all that off-the-cuff?
I know
All the remaining
players
a single person
voted for
That is...
Watanabe Yōichi
Therefore...
Watanabe Ryōichi-san
has been eliminated.
Watanabe-san, are you a fake Kansai native?
I'm a fake Kansai native.
By the way, where are you from?
Shizuoka
Shizuoka?
With that...
out of the remaining players,
2 are fake Kansai natives.
Day 3 begins
(Kawashima)
I have a question for everyone.
What did you think when you first came to Tokyo?
As you'd expect, the cars and buildings are so cool..
A bit different from Osaka. More refined.
Akira-san, how about you?
The udon soup was really dark I thought
It's different, right?
Something good's coming
It's a bit too cliched
That's suspicious
Akane-chan, how long has it been?
After graduating middle school.
People from Osaka, even if they don't have to, live hard and fast, don't they?
Haha, I know. Always..
People from Tokyo choose a goal and work towards it
Now this is Osaka-ben! She has to be from Osaka.
I came to Tokyo and the first thing I noticed was how many convenience stores there were,
So I'd think "ah, this is paradise!" in my day-to-day life.
The intonation is a bit...
it's totally weird, right?
You know, Inamura Ami-chan's Kansai-ben...
It's suspicious!
It's become Jimon-ized
It's bad, right?
Day 3 complete
At the end of the 3rd day, the person who received the most votes was...
Caught out by her intonation,
it's Inamura Ami.
So...
Inamura Ami has
been elimnated.
I'm a fake Kansai native!
Ami-chan, where are you from?
Tokyo
Totally!
At the end of the 3rd day,
there remains one more fake Kansai native.
Who is the remaining fake Kansai native?
If they can discover who it is,
the Kansai citizens will win but...
who on Earth could it be?
Day 4 begins
So. you know. I'll be straight..
I'm honestly thinking Akira-san is a little strange...
I thought so too at the start
Yes
But, his intonation on one thing changed my mind
He pronounced Biwa lake "Biwa lake"
(changing his intonation)
I'm thinking he's really from Kansai...
Am I being tricked?
No, no, no
So? That's what I'm thinking
But Mayo-san..
in this episode you've seemed like someone from Kansai at times
but you're an actor, aren't you?
So if you've had accent training for a role,
you'll be able to speak it perfectly.
Wait a second! I..
I'm a Kansai native! In every respect.
That's been bothering me from the start
If he's a fake I can't tell at all. Really.
You've been using standard Japanese with some Kansai-ben sprinkled in,
like someone who puts on a Kansai-ben accent when saying the word "Kansai".
(partly in KSB) Really?
It's not like that at all.
That "Really?" is a bit strange too.
We'd say it all in Kansai-ben.
You thought about the "really?" too much,
so your next sentence came out completely Kanto-ben, right?
Not at all.
He's good but the small details are wrong
I really really am from Shiga though!
Day 4 complete
"Shiga"
I don't know...
Do people from Shiga
pronounce it "Shiga"?
Mayo votes for Hayashiya Pei...
On day 4, Kawasaki
and Akira 100% for
Ōsawa Akane.
Then...
The last 3 all voted
for the same person.
Akira 100%
So, on day 4
the person to be eliminated...
is Akira 100%-san!
If Akira 100% is a fake Kansai native, the Kansai citizen team will win
Is he?
I'm a fake Kansai native.
(Ōhashi) We did it!
That means the Kansai citizens win.
Kansai citizen victory
The fake Kansai natives in this game were...
Akira 100%-san
Watanabe Ryōichi-san, and
Inamura Ami-san.
Huh? Jimon-san
So the first person everyone chose,
Terakado Jimon, is a fully-fledged Kansai native
Exactly!
He was the worst of all
So, to conclude, Jimon-san,
what did you think of Kansai Werewolf?
I'm exhausted
And with that, the first
game of Kansai Werewolf
results in a citizens' victory
So as we expected, people from Kansai can tell when someone is faking
But, for me, Akira...
Can you?
Ah, which part?
he fooled me quite a bit
Definitely...
the way he said "Biwa lake"
(changing intonation)
When he said "Biwa lake" instead of "Biwa lake"
From Shiga
Miyagawa Daisuke
(with Kansai-ben intonation)
Daisuke says it "Biwa", doesn't he?
So I thought it might be a Shiga thing
Yeah, he does
From Hyogo
Terakado JImon
Downtown-san, did you know that
Jimon-san is from Kansai?
I did
No I didn't
Dachō Club has 2 people from Kansai in it
That's right
From Hyogo
Ueshima Ryūhei
From Okinawa
Higo Katsuhiro
Jimon-san,
at this point,
can we revoke his right to call himself one?
Definitely
Our next presenters will come out now
Presenters
Kazuya Shimasa/Yashiki Hirosama
(New York)
It's New York!
Thank you
New York, right?
So...
From last July, plastic bags have had a fee
Ah, yes
If you bring your own,
you can use that but...
when you don't, how much do you carry without a bag?
As long as I can carry it in one hand
Because I want to take my key out when I get home
One hand full is enough
(Shimasa) I see
I know
Today we bring you a
theory related to that fee
Here it is
The most one can carry home from the convenience store without a bag is 10,000 yen's worth of products
Oh..
Yep
(Haruna) It's quite a lot. 10,000 yen
Can you hold that much?
It really is
I've worked at one before so I know.
Things like chargers and cosmetics...
They sell things which
are small but expensive.
Ah... I see, I see
If you buy things like that then maybe...
TBS Announcer
Yamamoto Rina
No plastic bag shopping battle!
Alco & Peace
Hiroku Yūki / Sakai Kenta
Matenro:
Anthony / Ōtoni
Onigoe Tomahawk
Sakai Ryōta / Kin-chan
Carrying things today will be people who we think would have an advantage:
Big-bodied entertainers
These 3 large entertainer
teams will battle it out
Without putting the products they buy at the convenience store into a bag,
each must
Transport the goods 10m in their hands
GOAL
The team who spends the most wins
In a task like this teamwork is important
We get along well but...
these guys probably don't.
Yes we do
We get along great
We're
childhood friends
We never talk at all backstage
Are you still trying to?
No one who wants to do that
Showa-era entertainers, right?
Our first challengers are:
Anthony
Matenrou
Ōtoni
Let's go!
Ah, what to choose?
This is hard
I just want to eat a bento. I'm hungry
(Ōtoni) Bentos are bulky
Wait
It's totally fine
I guess
But we can only buy one
Rule: Only one of each product may be purchased
One of each type?
(Staff) one bento only
Rule: For every product purchased but left behind, there is a 1000 yen fine
Also, regardless of whether it is put in the basket...
for each item not carried back
a penalty of 1,000 yen will be imposed.
Therefore...
Buying while predicting how much they can carry
... is important here.
This is a battle of money, right?
Even if we buy loads of small cheap stuff, it's no good
We should buy everything expensive
Let's do it
Expensive is expensive, whatever it is
Woah woah woah
This is great
Electric shaver
Isn't this expensive?
Put anything over 1,000 yen in
I found something amazing
What is it?
Y-shirt
(Anthony) We're getting that for sure
This will be no problem at all
By the way, even though they're expensive,
Prepaid cards are forbidden.
The same goes for things like reusable bags:
Products that were made to carry things are also forbidden
Look at these earphones!
Wow wow wow
Earphones
It's great here
There's a thermometer here too
Body thermometer
A USB cable...
And there's a cable here
USB cable
Put all the USB stuff in
USB drive
(Anthony) Put it all in
Ah, wow a mobile battery pack
Mobile battery
(Ōtoni)
This tie is expensive too
Necktie
Will this be OK?
Razors
Razor blade pack
Yes, it's OK. Don't even think about it
They're putting in loads of things over 1,000 yen in
After spending 10 minutes
choosing products in the everyday life section...
Oh, let's finish with a fruit sandwich!
Fruit sandwich
You just want to eat it!
Mixed fruit sandwich
One of these
Can we finish now?
OK, we can
This has to be the limit
This is the maximum limit
Let's go pay
Shopping complete
Hold on, now it's spread it all out like this...
it's looking harder to carry.
Do you need a plastic bag?
Honestly, yes
In charge of carrying  for Manterou will be Anthony
This is unbelievably easy
Isn't it? We could've bought more
You're carrying it all in one hand, Anthony
We miscalculated
After they misjudge Anthony's capacity, he is left with an empty right hand.
This is the worst
(Yamamoto) Here they come
So much spare capacity
This is so bad
I underestimated myself
This is really the worst
So easy
We're done
Just your left hand
He's only using one hand
The goal's here!
Put it on here to finish
We're done!
Wow that's amazing...
To carry all that in just one hand!
We miscalculated
You could've carried twice as much
(Anthony) I could've
We seriously screwed up
Necktie
Y-shirt
Electric shaver
Shoes
Battery
Gift bag
Foundation
USB drive
Lingerie
Supplements
Extension cord
Bath towel
Razor blades
Cotton pads
Mobile battery
Thermometer
USB cable
Earphones
Umbrella
Fruit sandwich
Bento
Blu-ray discs
Lightbulb
Nail clippers
Brush
Earplug
Flashlight
Manterou was able
to carry a total of...
items
yen
Our next challengers are:
Kin-chan
Onigoe Tomahawk
Sakai Ryōta
Good morning
Everyday goods?
Stuff like batteries
Yes, yes, yes
Something light and kind of expensive
Look!
Body thermometer
It's almost exactly the same
They've arrived at that corner, haven't they?
Guess so...
Now I'm thinking, if it's all
too small I won't be able to carry it
Yeah
So what if we put it on something bigger?
Something like a large slab
How's this?
2000 yen
Nappies
As a platform
Yes, sure
We can put loads on this foundation
I see
That would've worked
And then...
Loaf of bread
Another foundation?
Let's do it
After adding bread
to their foundations...
This foundation's expensive
Foundation
(Kin-chan) Put it in
(Sakai) Shall we get the lipstick too?
Lipstick
(Sakai) Put that in too
The fragrance is good too
Fragrance spray
Can we get both these steaks?
They're different things, yes
Chicken steak
Hamburg steak
Kyu-chan cucumbers!
Pickled vegetables
They add their last product...
Here you go
Shopping complete
Let's start with the foundations
I'm worried about the bread
With the foundations constructed...
They start placing products on them
Then...
OK OK OK…
They attach small items to Kin-chan's curly hair
However...
No, I can't hold more
I can't put this on?
That's what I'm saying
We'll get penalties for these...
Penalty x 9
(Kin-chan) It's all the stuff you
added at the end
Ryo-chan, open the door!
Alright, let's go Kin-chan
(Ōtoni) Can he do it?
OK OK
Incredible
(Sakai) Ok, let's go Kin-chan
He's doing it!
Wow
(Anthony) Here he comes
(Yamamoto) Hang in there!
Can you see where you're going?
Just about
This way
Where?
Right, right, right
Looking good
OK!
Seriously
That was great.
(Yamamoto) Well done!
Earplugs
T-shirt
Lingerie
Cotton pads
Mobile battery
Earphones
Soluble fiber
Hairbands
Candy
Hairpins
Shaving foam
Lip cream
Mints
USB drive
USB cable
Sweet chestnuts
Mechanical pencil
Fragrance spray
Foundation
Support brace
Razor blades
Bath towel
Lipstick
Cigarettes
Nappies
Bread
Cup yakisoba
Blu-ray discs
Cheese
Body wash
Tongue brush
Medical spray
Mouth gel
Brush
Supplements
Kitchen bleach
Y-shirt
Air freshener
Denture cleaner
Lighter
Towel
Thermometer
Batteries
Shoes
Sake
Snacks
Ice cream
Electric shaver
Drastically exceeding Manterou's total,
items
they were able to carry...
yen
Body lotion
Biscuits
Hamburg steak
Cup ramen
Chicken steak
Energy drink
Pickles
Can of beer
Chocolate
But, what effect will the penalty of 9,000 yen have on their score?
Alco & Peace
Hirako Yūki
Sakai Kenta
The final challengers are:
Let's go
I'd rather die than lose this
Then, Hirako discovers something...
How about that?
What if we use it as a base?
Box of cakes
With this as a base and a frame too...
We can make a big square thing like Jenga
Similar to Onigoe, they choose the...
Pedestal strategy
And then...
Cane
How about something like this?
With this and
an umbrella we can build a frame
Sounds good
That'll work
It'll be sturdy
It will
Right?
Combining the cane and umbrella
They invent an improved base
Clever
So clever
Let's start with the biggest first
Jenga-style
Like this? Is that OK?
OK
Yeah
I think it will
Wow, this will totally work
Ah, this is a good shape
Interesting
Ice cream
Nice
We can play with this
What?
Interesting
Yep, we can play with it
Then, after that,
Yokan
(jellied bean paste)
Having chosen mainly
square products...
they finish shopping.
Donuts
Yes, just a bit more
I think he's scared
(Ōtoni) Wow, amazing
It's really stable
(Ōtoni) Really great
It's the best
It's so stable
He's not going to drop a thing
No problem at all
Beautiful
(Yamamoto) You can put it down like that
It's like a piece of art
(Yamamoto) Magnificent!
Wow!
(Yamamoto) Well done!
<That is so good
The number of products may not be the best, but in terms of art...
They're stacked beautifully
We're different to the crude people at Yoshimoto
Stop it with that
I want you to see it
With three very different ways of carrying things, what will the final result be?
Alco & Peace
Matenrou
Onigoe
Tomahawk
(Yamomoto) All together, go!
Alco & Peace
Matenrou
Onigoe Tomahawk
How much?
(Yamamoto) Matenrou got 50,774 yen,
Onigoe got 54,244 yen,
and Alco & Peace 55,351 yen.
(Anthony) Unexpectedly close
Seriously?!
So close!
If it weren't for the penalty...
It's because of that
Now we're going to have another round
Huh?
Second round?
We're adding an "open one item" rule now
For round two...
Added rule: one product can be opened
The type of product they choose to open and hold other products with is key to winning
First in this round is Mantenrou
who came last in round 1.
Using one hand with this open...
Ah, actually
This is too easy
What will they open?
It's this
This
Opened item:
Umbrella
An umbrella
We'll open the umbrella
and put things in
This is good, right?
Here it is
We can put so much in this!
Seriously
So..
This will work
Things that are as light and expensive as possible
Umeboshi for 400 yen
Ah this is best
Umeboshi
Umeboshi for 400 yen is best
The best?
Is he an idiot or something?
Having chosen...
Lightweight and high value goods
they start putting them in them umbrella
Go! Put it in!
There must be 30kg here
Alright
Look at this
Over here, look
where I'm looking
Can we load it up again?
(Staff) Sure
Dropping things inside the store is allowed
so after devising a new way of carrying things...
they repack and try again.
Can I fit?
This is the most it can open
(Ōtoni) You can do it!
Ah wow, it's holding it, it's holding it
(Yamamoto) You mustn't drop it
now, Anthony-san!
It's so far
My arms!
Impressive
Keep going!
Ah, phew!
OK
I can't lift my arms at all
(Yamamoto) Well done!
We did it!
After that, Matenrou's score is
Total:
items
yen
Added to their score from round 1,
their total is 132,222 yen and they provisionally move to 1st place.
Next, Onigoe Tomahawk's attempt
Which item did they open?
Go straight forward
I can't see ahead at all
<Wow, here they come
Go right and stay level
(Yamamoto) He can't see ahead at all
Forward, forward...
Go straight ahead
(Yamamoto) Slowly slowly
Yes, they used a t-shirt
Opened item: T-shirt
By tying the sleeves and blocking the neck hole with a box of rice crackers
Onigoe made a large bag
We could've put more in
There's so much space in here
Straight, straight
Aaah, I can't
Forward, no, no, forward
You can do it, you can do it
A bit more!
Forward, forward
(Yamamoto) One more meter
OK OK OK…
This is OK
(Anthony) Yay!
OK
We did it
(Yamamoto) Wow, amazing
With this strategy, this has become an unexpectedly physical challenge
Onigoe's score is...
Total:
items
yen
Their grand total is 122,414 yen
so they fail to surpass Matenrou.
Last is Alco & Peace
In round one they took pride in carrying things gracefully...
So, what kind of item did they open?
It's fine.
There's more than enough width.
< There he is
<Wow, here he comes
Duct tape?
Ah..
Wow!
Yes, they opened
duct tape
Opened item: duct tape
They combined products
into easy-to-carry shapes
and even wrapped some around his body
to reduce the burden on his arms.
(Yamamoto) Wow
<He's coming out
Ah, we dropped one
(Kin-chan) We dropped one
Leave it, leave it behind
Skin lotion
It's super stable
(Various) He's got room to spare!
(Yamamoto) Amazing
Ahhhh...
Alright!
(Yamamoto) Well done!
<Great
Total:
items
yen
I can't believe you used such a dirty tactic
We were humans carrying things
You're not a human anymore!
This is a convenience man!
Alco & Peace
Matenrou
Onigoe Tomahawk
The final result is as follows:
The winners are Alco & Peace!
Everyone, what did you think?
Well, compared to how excited the participants got...
We in the studio did not get as excited
I don't know but
The viewing figures for children will be really good
Haruna-san, what did you think?
Well, you know,
Maybe one round was enough
Hey!
I got a bit excited
Shigemori-san, you?
At the end when they used the duct tape
Oh, really?
it was like "oh, you can do that!"
It was like a Eureka moment
That's good
Well, the rating figures for kids will indeed be good
32, right?
32?
Next...
Everyone's Theories
Investigating various popular topics and theories sent in by viewers
Tonight's presenter is...
Presenter
Tamura Kenji
Yes, it's Tamura Kenji-san!
What happened?
What's the commotion?
It seems we're waiting for Tamuken
Ummm, ah..
I've forgotten my notebook
He always has it
Yeah
So I thought...
let's see if I can manage without it
What are you saying?
Ah, but, it probably would've been better to go get it...
They'll give it to you from here
Please don't be angry at me later
They won't be
Sorry, I'm really sorry
What's going on?
OK, everyone,
(mispronouncing gozonji as goronji) \nDo you know mikoshi dako?
"Goronji"?
Please, get it together
Mikoshi dako?
(Lit: "Portable shrine octopus")
Do you know what mikoshi dako is?
If you carry a portable
shrine like this,
That's right
a bump forms on your shoulder.
Is there anyone here who's seen one?
Ah, I haven't
I've seen people with it on TV
It's a pretty big bump, right?
The shape changes.
Recently, there haven't been many festivals, right?
Ah, yes, because of coronavirus
Ahh..
So what I bring you today is this:
Are people with mikoshi dako losing them because of coronavirus?
I don't know about this
In the last 2 years?
Yes
They haven't carried them on their shoulders for two whole years
You know, they've always done it
so when they can't..
they go rogue.
They have secret festivals
Don't you think?
Right
Huh?
and law-evading mikoshi
Law-evading mikoshi…
They'll do it...
In the shadows...
Right
Is all this hopeless stuff written in your notebook?
You brought it here especially for us?
All of it
It's all written there?
So what Tamuken was saying just now weren't his own words, right?
Law-evading...
Of course not
Law-evading mikoshi?
"Law-evading mikoshi"
is written right here
Wow it is
It's stupid, isn't it?
Well then sorry
"Law-evading mikoshi" is here
They made you say it
But actually I...
Approved it and decided to say it
I'm responsible too
Well yeah, you could've left it out
However,
the law-evading mikoshi...
I liked it and I wanted to say it
You liked it
Are people with mikoshi dako losing them because of coronavirus?
Due to coronavirus, festivals all over the country were cancelled
Kanda festival cancelled
Mikoshi togyo
cancelled for
first time in 74 years
Yamahoko Junko
cancelled for
first time in 58 years
For two years the
mikoshi haven't appeared
Have the mikoshi dako of those who held them disappeared too?
The first person we visit is
(Staff) Nice to meet you
Nice to meet you
With 10 years' experience
carrying mikoshi, Sekido-san
Prior to coronavirus, he did it every month
Here's his mikoshi dako from 3 years ago...
3 years ago
WIth one on his shoulder
and one on his neck, his is the
2-boil type
What has happened to it?
(staff) Wow
Here's my right shoulder
(Staff) It's huge
Thank you very much
Totally still there
Hasn't it grown?
(Haruna) It's gotten bigger
It's growing
3 years
ago
Now
It isn't smaller at all
(Staff) Ever thought about removing it?
Not once
My wife hates it
(Staff) So she wants you to have it removed?
Yes. As you'd expect, she seems embarrassed
But I'm proud of it
It's been like having a medal
To be honest I'd like the left one to be bigger.
I'm a bit ashamed of it at the moment
(Staff) How do you mean "ashamed"?
It's like "this guy only carries it on one side!"
"He hasn't got one on the left at all!"
So I want to grow the left one to show people I can hold it on both sides
(Staff) Are there any advantages to having it?
Shoulder bags fit it perfectly
I think it's convenient
Next is...
(Staff) Hello
Hello
Clearly a southpaw, it's...
Yamawaki-san
years'
experience
(Staff) How many times a year would you do it?
Well, around 70 times
(Staff) Would you tour the country?
Just around Kanto
2 years
ago
It was this big 2 years ago but now...
Let's see
(Staff) Ahh
Here it is
(Staff) Incredible
It's smaller now but it'll get bigger when the season starts
(Staff) How much has it shrunk?
About 1.5 to 2cm
2 years
ago
Now
It's definitely gotten smaller but...
it's not disappeared.
When I was in hospital due to an accident,
the doctor asked me if I wanted the
hematoma on my shoulder removed.
"No", I said, "without this I can't carry the mikoshi"
(Staff) Without that...?
It'd hurt
This stops it hurting
This fits perfectly now, doesn't it?
(Staff) It's like a cushion
Yes, it's like there's a cushion inside it
(Staff) How has it helped you in your daily life?
Shoulder bags don't slide off at all
That's enough
They fit perfectly in my shoulder here
Everyone'll say that
Next, in possesion of his own mikoshi...
Ichihara-san
years'
experience
Could you show it to us?
Sure
2 years
ago
Now
His hasn't changed size
in the last two years either
I used to work in sales
It was hard to take time off on weekends with festivals
So because I wanted to do this,
I changed jobs and did something else
(Staff) You moved jobs for mikoshi?
I did
(Staff) Has having one helped you in any way?
For example, in my room when there's nothing to lean on
If I'm sitting down like this, it's a perfect pillow
(Staff) I see
Also, when holding a ba--
This man, who wouldn't look out of place with a cane, has one too
Fujimori-san
years'
experience
(Staff) It's totally different
From the front...
Oh, cool!
Wow!
Possibly useful on planes, it's the
Neck pillow type
Watanabe-san
years'
experience
It's like this
Well, to be honest,
When people who don't do festivals see it, they definitely wonder what it is
I think the size probably hasn't changed that much
5 years ago
It's like a boob
In terms of cup size, I'd say it's a C-cup
I'm often told that at least
That being said, it's not like it has a pointed tip
Ozawa-san
years'
experience
There are
mikoshi-carrying
women too
(Staff)
Where is it?
This is the boil
(Staff) It's a bit hollow
3 years ago
It hasn't gotten smaller
Now
Kondō-san
years'
experience
And here is the
"Little Kiyohara"-type
And from the back...
These are my C-cups
"Middle Kiyohara"-type
Miura-san
years'
experience
(Staff) Wow
(Staff) You have 2?
And behind there's...
(Staff) Behind? How do you mean?
(Staff) Oh, cool
Really cool
Kōchi-san
years'
experience
Next, someone whose
head seems to be sinking
into their body...
A "Younger Toguro"-pattern mikoshi dako
(Staff) Wow, cool
It's just like an octopus
(Staff) Have they gotten smaller?
It feels to me like they haven't
(Staff) So they're not going to change?
No they're not
Watanabe-san
years'
experience
And this is Watanabe-san
(Staff) Woah
(Staff) What's going on here?
From the back, it's just like the character for mountain (山)
(Staff) Are there any ways in which you've found having them useful?
Shoulder ba--
Result: We look forward to them holding the mikoshi next year
What did you think?
Wow
It was not what I expected
It was pretty impressive, right?
I want them put on us too
(Haruna) On that drawing
(Bakarhythm) MIkoshi dako
No, no
You don't hold mikoshi, do you?
You earn those from
carrying mikoshi
A lucky charm
As a lucky charm
And you're holding up Mt Fuji
Because the comedy world is resting on your backs?
You'll get comedy mikoshi dako
Great
It was better than I'd imagined
Panelist Theory
investigation Special
★Subbed by fmck fansubs★
reddit.com/u/fmckfansubs
patreon.com/fmck
Next week..
'When peeing in the mens' toilets,
everyone can see you from outside' theory
We air theories given
by panelists in the opening
And investigate a selection of them
If Downtown were young now,
they wouldn't be this popular