Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Savannah's Takahashi!
Isn't this everyone's favorite Takahashi?
-Everyone loves him
There's no such thing
But it's not right to say "no such thing"
So
We have previously verified that it is easy to leave an artist alone on location
Did it several times
-3 times
Panther's Ogata
-Yes
Tram?
On the other side of the road crossing was the film crew
When the tram passed, the people were gone
Most unpleasant
This time, we bring you a spin on this idea
The theory i've brought is this:
Waking up in the morning at your travel destination to find everyone else missing is quite sad
I'm going to cry. I'm going to cry.
-It's hard to top
What else do you need to say?
This time the person is left behind on a private trip
I see
Imagine getting up in the morning and finding yourself alone
What would you think?
Well, you'd call someone, right?
You'd call
First you'd call them
What do you think, Cookie?
I'd think, "No, I'll just keep waiting"
Just wait?
Wait until my flesh disappears
Only the skeleton remains
This is my fault, I shouldn't have asked you
Sorry, sorry
Waking up in the morning at your travel destination to find everyone else missing is quite sad
So sad
First of all, the first scene is camping
This is a bit scary
The target is
Incidentally, this time not only the camping partners who came together are missing
All the camping supplies except for the tent that he is sleeping in are also taken away
The setting is to wake up in the morning and find themselves completely alone
Cheers!
It's great!
The long-awaited camping trip of the Ogata Army begins
Has something interesting happened to you recently?
In fact, 2~3 months ago I went on a trip
Commandante Ishii, KAZMA and I, and Attack Nishimoto
We booked random accommodation
This will do, right?
And went to a hot spring
Unbelievably, Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi was there
The real guy!
That's awesome.
-Is that true?
Don't give me an unexpectedly surprising story!
He was there for his health
That's for sure
It seems that the lower half of his body is also quite strong
To be honest, I forgot to look at his knob
Show me. That's the most important thing, right, you guy?
Forgot to look at the knob...
I'd love to hear what kind of knob he has
-Right?
A million unexpected Nagabuchi anecdotes got the group all excited
They did not go to sleep until 2:00 am
Good night
-Goodnight
Thank you for your hard work
So, 3 hours later
Oh, who's out there?
In order not to wake him up
Ogata slowly starts to crawl out
Impressive, he's out
Then the two people in the next tent get up quietly
And quickly began to retreat
If you don't put it all away, it's not funny
Then, the other tent is carried away untouched
So lonely
Perfect!
Preparation work completed
Waking up would be scary
The next step is just to wait for him to wake up
Ogata looks like he's been up all night
However, after an hour and a half there is no sign of him waking up
The time came at 6:50
What will be the reaction?
It's almost 7:00
Looks so sleepy
Eyes swollen like copper bells
This is not the face of the setter
The alarm clock will go off
Here is the perfect opportunity
This will definitely wake him up
If not?
We go home
Seriously?
Ah, he's up
He's up, he's up, he's up, he's up
Finally, he wakes up
He first notices the person next to him is gone
Probably dumbfounded
Of course you'd react like this
You'd look beside you
All silent
No one at all
Ahhhh or something like that
Single camping
Why're you looking again?
No, we aren't there
Hey, why is there no one here?
You think they'll be there if you look again?
Really double-checking
We're not there, how can we be there?
The campsite has been searched for all the way back and forth
Of course, there is no sign of anyone
After all, even the tent is gone
Ogata!
Later, he tries calling Ogata's phone
Definitely won't answer
Why... ah...
What the hell did I do?
Thinks he did something wrong
Did I say something that excessive?
He thinks he's been left behind because of a slip of the tongue...
Sorry about that
Then... disillusioned
For some reason he lies on the river bank for more than 30 minutes in anger
This was followed by...
Pushing against a tree stump
And bathing in the river with his clothes on
It seems to be quite enjoyable
Ah-
Head buried in the tent and shouting
All kinds of peculiar behavior
Scary
This solo camping lasted for three hours
At last, he begins putting things in order
And packs the tent away
To leave the campground
For the taxi that he calls
The program team sent a pre-prepared vehicle
One-person camping?
No, originally four people came together
I don't know why the other 3 people are missing in the morning
Eh? Eh?
They seem to have gone back
Not only are the people gone, but the camping tools are also gone
I am really too miserable
30 minutes to the nearest station
Then
Ah, Ogata!
What is this all about?
No, no. What is this?
What's wrong with you? What's wrong?
No, not what?
Sorry sorry sorry
Eh? Hey, seriously?
Really, what's this?
No, that...
-Huh?
Because you were still sleeping
No, no, don't leave me behind
Hey, seriously, what are you...?
-No, no, no. You were still sleeping
Still sleeping, what the hell!?
I told you to get up.
-No, no, you're confused
You wouldn't wake up
Seriously, why are you drinking coke?
Are you guys sightseeing?
We've been walking around
-It's true...
As the emotional state prevails
The reveal the truth
Oh, whoa, strange guys are coming...
We explained the project to him
I first thought "we did have a barbecue yesterday, right?"
Thought you were dreaming?
-I did, really
Thought maybe you'd actually come alone.
-Really thought so
So, next
We verify using added dream elements
This time the target is Alco&Peace Sakai's junior
Computer Universe's Hasshi Happy
What the hell kind of name is that?
This time not only will all the fellow members disappear
Don't know a single one of them
Even the hotel staff and residents will disappear
Thus, an occult element is added
What will happen?
Eh?
Whoa
Super cool!
They enjoy the first day at the spa
And have a late 1:00AM bedtime
Best day ever
5:30
The same as before
Without waking the target
Everyone leaves the room
They must be nervous, right? iIt's over if they wake them up
Indeed
This time the target's cell phone is taken
As is his luggage
Yes, yes, it is better to go straight like this
Then, while the trapped people successfully exit
All the residents in the hotel also disappear
Preparation work completed
Oh he's up
He's getting up
He's realized
The phone...is gone
If the phone is there, there's a solution
However, it's not just his cell phone
His companions and luggage are all missing
What'll be the reaction?
Sensing the situation
Eh? Where...
Eh?
You'd have this reaction
A little panic
Computer Universe
Panicking, he leaves the room
The places he visits are
The lobby on the 1st floor
Wow, that's scary
Anyone?
And, of course, there's no one
Completely gone
He's making that kind of sound
Didn't expect this
There's no one there
A super fast runner
Super funny
Anyone?
Wow...what?
Ahhh
Anyone? Anyone?
Not good
Going crazy
Ahhh
Why is there no one there?
Excuse me, is anyone there?
You're not going to cry, are you?
Anyone?
Wow, it's over...
It's over
Not a single person? Anyone?
Anyone?
Ugh...
It's like "Calling for Love in the Center of the World"
Anyone?
Really like a movie
It's a little scary if there is no one at the front desk
Ahhh, no one
No one
Nobody...
"Somebody help me!"
Anyone?
Ah, it's over
Not a single person
What's going on?
Ah, there is no water...
This is just a coincidence
Ahhhhh
I can't do this
I can't do this anymore
Ah, someone help!
Somebody!
That's a little scary
Surely scary
Out again
He's outside
Looking for a car?
Oh wow, that's scary
That's scary
The cars are gone too
Yesterday it was full of cars
It's really like the end of the world...
For a first time prank
He's been gifted with a luxury experience
His belt is gone too
His clothes are open!
Wow someone's there
Finally met someone
Ah someone's there!
Are you from here?
Uh-huh... that way... right over there
What's going on? What happened?
Is this place open?
Hasn't been open for ages
It was popular in the bubble era
The setup is revealed
The hotel is long since abandoned
I came to stay here yesterday
Where...here?
-Yes
Good acting!
You can't get in, right? Isn't it locked?
No, you can, we got it
Can you come here for a moment?
It's still open
He's grabbing him!
I'm from the area, there hasn't been anyone here for 10 years...
I've got goose bumps
What? What?
Wait, so afraid, so afraid, so afraid
Look, there are lights on
It's weird
Come and see, come and see, please
Is there a renovation team coming?
Why are you still so concerned about not wanting to show your body?
No, I'm staying here
Eh?
I also had a drink
Also went to the bath
Eh?
Really, I'm not lying
You see, not a single car
Please don't say it again
Already convinced of the setting
He brings an older man, an actor, with him
And returns to his room
However, there is one last step here
Wait ah ah so scared
There are people!
Someone's in there
Wait, wow, I'm scared
Who is it? Whoa!
What's up? What's going on?
Because it is a hotel where time has stopped for decades
The other 3 people who came with him are already old men
A puzzling setting
What the hell is this!?
Can't figure it out anymore
Is it time travel?
So
What's going on? What's wrong with you?
Are you...Ochiai-san?
-I'm Ochiai
You too?
Sakai...
Are you okay?
This...
He has gradually begun to accept the fantastical setting
What a simple person
So, the truth is revealed
Scared the hell out of me!
Ahhh, Sakai, Sakai is really...
That what really... really... really...
What happened to you?
Ochiai is balding
No that's not it
That's not the point
What were you doing!?
I thought I had come to another world
Genuinely believed it
In summary
Sadness is no longer the point
So that's it
If this setting continues to develop
You could do a real long story with it
A long-form trick
All the way up until the old men compete in the M-1 tournament
Still gonna compete in M-1?
The second half is so strong
The tent one is all but forgotten
Please don't forget that part
Especially the story of meeting Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi with his own eyes by chance
Let's welcome the next presenter
Who is it?
Here we go. It's Super-Sasaguaiko-Machine
Hello everyone
It's been a long time
Long time no see
Has it been 2 years or 3 years?
It's been 3 years since I saw you
What was the last one that you came with?
-What theory?
This is a sequel to that theory
Do you remember what the theory was?
It seems to be related to professional wrestling, right?
Was it!?
What are you doing?
That's definitely it!
I remember that one most clearly
I remember Maeda
Ah, Maeda's speech problem, right?
-Yes, yes
By the way, Maeda is doing a talk show with Fujinami Tatsuo today
He's not coming, don't worry
Maeda's not coming here
Yes, I can confirm he wont be coming
I see
The theory I brought this time is
The 2nd Teaching Women How to do a Figure-Four Leglock Over the Phone
It was done
Do you remember?
-It's been done
How does it work?
I'll briefly review the highlights from last time to illustrate
Please take a look
The last time was 3 years ago
First, Keiji Muto
Then Genichiro Tenryu
Then Liger
Legendary wrestlers
These three challenged this theory
Tenryu was successful
As was Liger
But Muto failed
A big failure
That's what happened
Sure enough, it's hard to call and teach women the tricks of professional wrestling
How about the fact that it is difficult to describe wrestling in words?
If you can use the phone, teach women to use the skills
It actually can be done
And this led to a moving sense of triumph
A huge accomplishment
However, it is a bit realistic to say that
The job wrestling industry we work in
Has many secrets
It's a contact sport after all
-That's for sure
In these 2 years, because of coronavirus
We have had a tough time
So, professional wrestling making phone calls
Phone calls about wrestling
A new industry has potentially emerged
Phone work about wrestling?
Do not say it as if it really happened
It sounds a bit like a wrestling job
One more thing
Muto Keiji announced his retirement in the spring of 2023 next year
Therefore, Muto-san's sure-fire leg-lock technique
It is unsure whether or not it will be inherited by someone
It is also very important for Muto
So, if we don't teach the technique
Worst case scenario, his retirement may have to be postponed
I'm a little worried about this
No, no, no
So, how did it turn out?
Please take a look at the VTR
The 2nd Teaching Women How to do a Figure-Four Leglock Over the Phone
So
Scared me!
Cell phones are handed to the two ELF's members who know nothing
The person on this phone will give you instructions
I hope you will act according to the instructions and achieve success
Oh.
-Huh?
The content of the instructions...of course
The figure four leglock
Hold the other's legs in place like the number 4
A representative skill of pro wrestlers
So, of course, the person who comes to teach this skill is
The master of the leg lock
Without further ado
It's been a long time since I've used this kind of phone
Whoa!
Why did you get scared?
Hello
-Hello?
I am a professional wrestler Muto
Eh, really?
It's ELF's Arakawa, isn't it?
-Yes
So, please do as I say
So we can complete the move
Do you understand?
-Okay
Because there is a time limit and it must be completed within the time limit
If we don't start soon
Ok
Can Haru and Arakawa stand facing each other?
Face to face
Is it okay for Haru to lie on her back on the spot?
Haru, can you lie on your back?
She down?
So fast
Yes, lying down
Well, it's a little difficult from here, Arakawa
-Okay
Put your right foot between Haru's legs
The left foot on the outside.
-No instructions for me?
It in there?
In there?
-Yes
Then
Put Haru's left leg...
-Left leg
Muto can't see that's why this is difficult, right?
Can't understand, yes, yes
What's the best way to say it...
Forbidden to use specific instructions
Move Arakawa's legs
Put Haru's left leg...
Cross over
Sit down while passing it through
Haru's left leg must be bent over
Okay, I'm done folding
It's folded, right?
What happened? I was folded
This is instead...
Haru's right leg, below the knee of the right leg
From the top of Arakawa's crotch up to her navel
Completely incomprehensible
Is this clear?
A little pain
It will hurt. It will hurt
Wrestling moves are meant to hurt
Is this right?
Asking "Is this right?", I can't see it either
The right foot is inbetween my navel and crotch
Do you have a referee there?
-There's a referee
Is that a completion?
The referee has the final say
NO
-NO？
Fight
-Fight？
It's a "NO"
Then...then let's move it back
The last action you performed
-Yes
Haru's right leg straightened
Left leg bent up
-Bent
Grab the ankle
Put your ankle below the thigh
"On your thighs"... so that's it?
So that's how it is, huh?
And then? And then what?
Pain, pain, what?
And then? Where do I put my legs in?
The right foot in the triangle of the hole
Ah right leg ah OKOK wait a minute
Let me put my foot under your ass. Under your ass
Scary, why're you so suddenly excited!?
Then, Arakawa, sit down
It's not that way, is it?
It's this way, right?
-It hurts like hell
Haru has a leg that is straight, right?
Haru's right leg
Straighten the leg. Straighten the leg
Yank it to the top of your own waist
She'll hurt a bit
Girls are softer though, so it's okay
The right leg is now on the top
I am lying down
The leg that is bent should be on top of the leg that is straight
Toes on top
Finally, the left leg should be on the toes
The left leg should be pressed on that
Wait, wait, wait
Haru, come under my knee please
Can you press down?
-You have to press down?
Knee, control with the knee
It will be very painful so be gentle
-It hurts!
Wait, that hurts.
-Is it okay? Referee
Ask the referees
-OK
Yes!
Ah, I'm exhausted...
Can retire now
The Muto-ELF combination took 4 minutes 52 seconds to successfully complete the move
Superb competition
The next challengers are...
Good Morning
-Good morning
This program's idol group
Two members of Mameshiba no Taigun
The skill to be challenged is...
Difficult!
The anaconda vice
Wrists and neck are clamped in a death grip
The original move of Tenzan Hiyoshi
Therefore, Tenzan will explain the move
Hey, it's coming. Then I'll answer it
Ah... hello
Hello~
Sorry, I'm Tenzan Hiroyoshi
Cute
I am a professional wrestler
It's Aika, right?
Yes, I'm Aika The Spy
Okay, next
I'm going to say this move
Is Miyuki there?
-She's next to me
Seems so suspicious!
-Very true
Miyuki, can you lie on your back, Miyuki?
Scary looking but softly spoken
Akin to some new type of telephone fraud, Tenzan explains
Aika should be pressing against Miyuki's upper body
Like that?
Ah, I've done it
Although I can't see
Please grab her right wrist
Grab the right wrist with the left hand, right?
-Yes, yes, yes
And then, just like this, press on her
Pull hard in the direction of Miyuki's feet
Hand clenched like you're trying to break her neck
Does it feel like the neck is going to break?
-Stop! It hurts!
It hurts, Aika, Aika
It hurts!
-How about the referee?
No? Give up?
OK
OK!
Ah, OK Come on, it's good
What are you talking about?
Tenzan and Mameshiba no Taigun perfectly complete the move in 3 minutes and 49 seconds
"OK Come on" is good
The final challengers are...
Good morning
Oda Ueda
These two are challenged with the skill of...
While clamping one of the opponent's legs
Lock the face upwards as much as possible
STF - The step-over toehold with face-lock
This looks so hard
The person in charge of explaining the technique is the creator, Chono Masahino
I am Chono
Good morning
First, please put the opponent down
Please let her lie down
This way
She down?
Okay, already lying down
Then, Ueda is lying down... what're you called again?
So noisy
I'm Oda
-Oda
Oda, please lift up Ueda's legs
But in fact, the original version is not two legs
Instead, only one leg is lifted to turn the person over
That's the beginning of this technique
So
We aren't at the XXX
Wednesday... this isn't what I expected of Wednesday
Please take the left leg as the axis to turn the person over
Is that so?
Ah it hurts, it's gonna break!
Accidentally said two legs
Ow ow ow, stop!
Already doing it wrong?
And
Oda is lying face down, right?
Oda is now sitting and has always been
Eh? Sitting?
What's Udea doing now? Lying down, right?
Oda is sitting, Ueda is lying down
Sorry, the name is a little difficult to distinguish
Ah, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, what...
You're doing it to Ueda, right?
-Yes
There's no time for that, Chono
Oda, please put your legs between her legs
Oda uses her own legs...?
Both legs clamped
No longer has anything to do with Ueda
Then the middle of the leg
The leg of Oda... ah not Oda, that...
What does the leg look like now?
The legs are...
What's Oda's leg doing?
Oda is currently sitting
Ah...
-Yes
Just can't get Ueda's name out
Sitting? Wait... sitting...
Already confused
Wait a minute wait a minute
The caller is panicking
Oda is down...facing downward and lying down?
Oda is still sitting, hasn't changed.
-Eh? Sitting?
Eh, is Ueda lying face down?
She's lying face up
Ah that's no good
Already in a state of affairs where the name and situation are confused
Chono, time up
Is this considered a failure?
It's time to judge
Whose fault is this?
Instead of saying who... it's time
GOD DAMN!
Okay, OK, thank you very much
In summary
GOD DAMN!
What's this?
The verification result is "God Damn!" what does it mean?
What a terrible ending
"Okay, OK", don't show us the place where his fire is extinguished
Malicious editing
However, it's confusing via phone, right?
Yes, you can't see each other at all
If such a tradition existed, it would probably be very popular
Store managers calling to send vulgar instructions to women...
It's like remote health care
Matsumoto, it could really be done
Don't fan the flames!
Should we try a crowdfunding campaign?
Next is everyone's theories
It's Fujiwara!
They always do this "so that's it~" type line
But then they never do it here
We can't do that
We're not being paid enough
I don't want to hear that
Yes, there's no way to cash in
It may be a bit sudden. Do you know the program "Home Alone"?
You know that, don't you?
This time we bring a theory related to this
There is at least one lone store in every industry
What industry?
In the case of stores, do public restrooms count?
It would be strange to count that
Not really
Who pays money for public toilets?
So that's it~
So that's how it is, so that's how it is
Thank you
His old age is super obvious!
-Thank you
White hair has spread upward
More and more... eroded.
-The amount is becoming more
I'll become all white at some point, please look forward to it
There is at least one lone store in every industry
First of all
The Lone Restaurant
This store is located in Kiwa-cho, Kumano City, Mie Prefecture
At a glance, only this store seems to be located away from the hustle and bustle of the place
As a restaurant there is no more inconvenient location than this
So, we took a bus from the nearest station and walked along the mountain road for 1.5 hours
After getting off the bus, you have to walk along the road with almost no street lights for about 10 minutes
Also gotta walk!?
Is this really the right path?
At first it was a bit hard to believe that there was really a restaurant here
Unbelievable.
-Is it really a restaurant?
Not at all, right?
So sudden
But there is
This is the Lone Restaurant
The name is Mizuwari
These people must have been drinking and driving, right?
No no
They'll call a chauffeur to pick them up.
-Really?
Hurry in and see...
Looks busy
Just the right amount of business
Why did you open a restaurant in the deep mountains?
If it is opened in a place where people live
If the door opens and closes, the karaoke sound will be heard outside
In the city its okay, but countryside people go to bed early
I think sooner or later we'd receive complaints
Indeed, if it is in a quiet street
The sound from this house would be quite attention-grabbing
Next is the lone vintage store
This store is located in Tahito-cho, Iwaki City, Fukushima Prefecture
30 minutes drive from the nearest station in the direction of the mountain road
Through the woods
This is General Store Tabi
American workwear-based vintage store
And a buyer's store dealing in vintage goods
Originally I didn't want to open a store
I wanted to have a garage where I can park a bus
Then how did it become a store?
Because I have a bunch of vintage clothing myself
For the sake of display, I wanted to hang them all up
Acquaintances or friends who come often said they wanted stuff
So it became a store
Next is the Lone Pachinko Shop
This store is located in Kanzu Island, Izu Islands, Tokyo
Population is about 1800 people
An island where most of the islanders are engaged in fishing
30 minutes drive from Kanzu Island Airport
In the village's periphery is a solitary presence
What's there
There's one!
The only pachinko parlor on the island, Oasis
Let's take a look
Wow I can't believe it!
Today the customers
Are just one
Why open in such an isolated place?
A pachinko store itself should be opened in a more prosperous place
But if you open in the center of the island
It'll be easy for people's wives to see them playing there
So it happened like this because of that
If you open in a quiet place, customers have less attention on them
This is the reason to exist on an isolated island
Moved here 20 years ago
If the sky is clear, fishermen are out at sea to work
If so, its complete empty
The business is barely viable
Next is the Lone Inn
Located in Toga Village, Nanto City, Toyama Prefecture
Surrounded by mountains and lakes
No other buildings are visible at all
Supreme solitude
The only way to get to the hotel is by boat
A 30-minute boat ride in a green landscape
After boarding the private dock
You reach the Omaki Onsen Inn
Originally there was a village near here
But due to the construction of the dam it was flooded
So, only the hot spring hotel has been preserved
It's pretty hard to get here, isn't it?
What is the approximate number of guests?
We've been featured in many mystery tv dramas
So guests come now and then
An isolated location
A perfect setting for a murder
It's easy to kill people
Not easy to be noticed
It has become a popular secret place to stay for those inclined
The only thing is, as a place to stay, there are no roads around it
In addition to the place where you live, you can not get out at all
Next is the Lone Hotel
Located in Genkai-cho, Higashi Matsuura Sur, Saga Prefecture
This store is also completely unconnected to the local community
A place that cannot be reached by land
Therefore, the owner has to go to the port to meet the customers who have made reservations
It is physically impossible to have guests just coming to eat
So, a 10-minute sea cruise by shuttle boat
Opened in a place surrounded by sea and mountains
The placed is called Gyosanjin
Both owners are fishermen
Because he wanted to eat freshly caught fish
He opened this restaurant next to his house 14 years ago
It's a lot of trouble to come here
Can guests come?
Saturday and Sunday, there is no way this year
Day and night are fully booked
Weekends are already full up until next March
All working days before November are also full
Super popular
A super popular restaurant that even the regional Michelin guide has introduced
Do celebrities come to eat privately?
Yes
Like who?
*Carlos Ghosn: Former CEO of Nissan, who was arrested by Japanese police in 2018 on suspicion of huge financial crimes Absconded to Lebanon in late 2019
Carlos Ghosn
Last is the Lone Batting Practice Centre
Really?
Located in Kumano-cho, Aki-gun, Hiroshima
Leaving the city from the nearest station
Its a 15 minute drive along the mountain road
This facility with a huge parking lot is
Aki Batting Center
We asked the hammer-throwing turtle owner from Mario about the business
The turtle that can throw a lot of hammers
Do customers come in large numbers?
Usually 0, but at most 7~8 people
There are only about 20 people at most on weekends
By the way, there was only one customer on this day
Is it sustainable?
The debt is astronomical, so it is difficult to maintain
How much is it?
All together about 300 million
Eh...
In addition to this batting practice center
Do you have another job?
No
In summary
We found some
What else is there to say
Hamada was very interested in the lonely restaurant just now
Have an opinion or something?
What're you saying?
Isn't it a restaurant?
So what?
To drink
Well, it's all watered down (Mizuwari)
What?
Super watered down
That's no good
No, its almost water
You can't!
There's water (mizu) in watered down, its fine
That's not right!
It's water, its the same
It's not a restaurant!
They have a driver, dont worry
A lone driver
"I'm going to have a drink."
"You come and pick me up later"
An older woman
Yes, call the woman
She has sons
So it's like this
Yes, yes, that's right
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03