Welcome to Wednesday Downtown
Thank you
OK
Lets get on with it
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
It's Ooki
Thanks for having me
Good eveni-mi
Ah, good eveni-mi
It's been a long time since I've heard it said
It's been a long time since anyone has said it to me
It's been a long time!
It's been a long time
I proposed a theory 7 years ago
Does anyone else remember?
Ah, I remember
I remember it too
There has been some similar to it
Yes, there has
Finding out whether certain people are still alive
Yes, you remember
What was it?
There are people that saw the living Tokugawa Keiki that are still alive
It turned out to be true
Indeed, it was quite interesting
So, theories related to people who have seen things like this
This time, i've brought another
This is it
There are people that saw the real Hachiko that are still alive
Ah, that's awesome!
Really?
It's Hachiko!
How long ago was it?
Hachiko died in 1935
Showa year 10
About 87 years ago
It was the Showa era?
As they'd have to be about 4 or 5 years-old to remember
The people likely to have seen Hachiko would have to be 90 and upwards
It's still very possible
-Indeed
I see
-That's it
What do you think, Shigemori? Do you know anything about Hachiko?
It's the dog that Takamori Saigo had, right?
No, it's not
-Is that wrong?
Completely incorrect
-Really?
That dog was called "Tsun"
I don't know then
I'm really sorry. Please don't ask me anything else today
Shibuya's Hachiko, you really don't know it?
Ah, I've seen the statue of Hachiko in Shibuya many times
That's a statue
-Yes, yes
It's based on a real dog
Really?
There are people that saw the real Hachiko that are still alive
Hachiko appeared at Shibuya Station in the early Showa period
At that time, Shibuya was served by the Yamanote Line and above-ground trains
Tokyo Metropolitan Electricity Tamagawa Train Interchange
And had various stores around the station
That's impressive
It has existed from the early Showa period when Hachiko was alive until now
There is even a store in front of the Shibuya Yagyu exit that is still there
Shibuya Nishimura Fruit Bar
Oh that is there
We're looking for someone who has seen Hachiko in person
This store was opened in January of Showa 10
Hachiko died in the spring of the same year
It was established basically in the last few months of Hachiko's life
Our store does have some connection to Hachiko though
My grandmother said, "I fed Hachiko"
My father said, "I remember it was a very big dog, it walked slowly along the road."
I've heard them say this
Although the bronze statue in the shape of a small dog
Hachiko was actually an Akita, a large breed of dog
It's not completely accurate
At that time in the alley where Central Avenue is currently,
There were many yakitori stores opening one after another
When Hachiko approached
Drunken guests would feed it with leftover chicken
I've heard them talk about it
Unfortunately, both of these people have since passed away
Is there anyone from this area in that period still alive?
-I'm not sure
If they were alive, they would be 95 years old or older now
At that time, the Chamber of Commerce was in the shopping street
But I don't think it's easy to go access to now
Next up
Operating in Shibuya since the Taisho era,
Fresh Fish Shop: Fish Power
Yes, I've heard about Hachiko from my grandmother who has passed away
My grandmother once said, "I saw Hachiko with my own eyes."
She said on the night we watched the movie about it
It was so memorable
That movie was
"The Story of Hachiko" which was released in 1987
After watching the film, he was moved by his grandmother who told of seeing the living Hachiko with her own eyes
He said, "Hachiko was great, he came here every day, what a great dog."
There were yakitori shops around the station
He went there everyday
People eating there would feed him with bits of it
After the last train, the stores closed
Then Hachiko went home
I heard that every day he did the same thing
Stop talking about it
Now that I think about it
I'm not sure if it's true or not
Definitely fake
So, Hachiko's main purpose
Was it to wait for the master, or for scraps of chicken?
It's for the master!
Wait a minute. Wait a minute
Just think of it as waiting for the master
Even the owner of the old store that has been opened until today
Doesn't know if any of the people who saw Hachiko in person are still alive
Next, we asked nursing homes and day care facilities around Shibuya
I remember a few years ago there seemed to be some
But now it seems there aren't any left
People who saw the dog must be 90 years old or older
We asked about 20 people here
No of them saw Hachiko in person
It seems it's not that easy to find
However, after talking to elderly people living in Shibuya...
How Shibuya used to be is surprising
This is what this elderly woman, who has lived in Shibuya Kamiyama-cho since she was 3 years old, had to say
My home was completely burned down during the war
Small houses were built on the ruins
The market in front of the station was very impressive
Shibuya burned to the ground when Tokyo was bombed
After the war, crowds gathered in front of Shibuya Station due to the expanding market
Now the Central Street side, the General Store Street side...
There are many small shops
Suspicious items were sold in bulk over there
Suspicious items
Six years after the end of the war
With the gradual revival of Shibuya, something appeared
An amusement park opened on the roof of the East Hall in Toyoko
A small cable car was built at the time of the opening of the West Pavilion
Cable car?
-Yes
A cable car connecting the two East and Cross Halls
A photo at the time shows it
The two sections separated by the station
Had a cable car connecting the rooftop amusement park as an amusement facility
It started operating in 1951, but only for a year and a half
In addition, there was...
What did you do for a living?
I'm a Geisha, I'm still in the business
Even now
Koito, who started as a Geisha at the age of 20 in the streets of Shibuya, is now 93 years old
Was there Geisha in Shibuya?
There used to be about 100
But now there are only four
-4?
Four
From the Taisho to Showa era
Maruyama-cho in Shibuya had many Geisha
At its peak, there were more than 100 Geisha
Later the stores were closed
And then they became love hotels
But the stores didn't directly change into love hotels
All along the Yamanote Line is the Hanayagi Street
Were there hundreds of people everywhere?
-Yes, yes
There was one near every station, like Shinjuku
But now it is in decline
There is only one left
Is it here in Shibuya?
-Yes
Although we gained a lot of interesting information related to Shibuya
We had still not found anyone who had seen Hachiko
Pretty difficult
Next, we located a researcher at the Shibuya City Museum of Localities, which is the most knowledgable of Hachiko
We enquired with Matsui
Hachiko was born in November of the 12th year of the Taisho era.
The following year, in January of Taisho 13, he was brought to Shibuya for breeding
The owner was from Tokyo Imperial University
Professor Eizaburo Ueno
But Professor Ueno died just one year later
After the death of Dr. Ueno
The story is, Hachiko went to Shibuya every day
Published in a Showa 7 newspaper
"The big dog in front of Shibuya Station waiting for its deceased owner."
Everyone knew this story
"What a faithful dog", everyone thought
After 7 years of continuous waiting for the owner, Hachiko had received coverage
And became a popular star at Shibuya Station in one fell swoop
The day after the story was published
In order to touch the head of Hachiko, schoolchildren formed a long line
His popularity was high
In front of the station, "Hachiko rice" and "Hachiko pancakes" appeared
There was a wide range of goods named after Hachiko
Until the death of Hachiko in Showa 10
Shibuya Station "Hachiko Fever" lasted for three years
An especially surprising pice of information pertains to the bronze statue of Hachiko
When was the bronze statue built?
A year before the death of Hachiko
It was completed before the death of Hachiko?
-Yes
Before passing away
Yes, newspapers state that Hachiko himself was at the unveiling of the statue
Attended in person
An accomplishment most people, except dictators, are unlikely to experience
A celebration of his life while he was still alive
This statement is too...
We are searching for surviving people who have seen Hachiko in person
Are there any still alive in 2022?
I think there is
But it'll be tough to find
I personally know the son of the veterinarian who treated Hachiko
I asked him a lot of questions about Hachiko
But he passed away in December of last year
From our museum's perspective, we would very much like to find someone who is still alive
I'd like to ask them about Hachiko, but it's getting harder and harder
Even after becoming world-famous, Hachiko still came to Shibuya Station almost every day for 3 years
So there must have been many witnesses
Thus, we continued our investigation for three weeks
And finally got some valuable information
The words "It is possible that I saw Hachiko with my own eyes"
We travelled to Narita City in Chiba Prefecture to meet an elderly person
Where did you live in Shibuya at that time?
About 2-3 minutes walk from the station
In front of my house was the head office of Tokyu
There was a long row of wooden buildings
We're looking for someone who saw Hachiko in person
Yes, I saw him
He was very large
Success!
Finally, a person who saw Hachiko has been found
Said so readily
When I was about 4 years old
In front of my house, my father said, "Hachiko is coming"
Looking out from inside the store, he passed by in a whoosh
I just saw him like this
Makino, whose home was a hardware store
Saw Hachiko walk past the store, though only for a moment
He really did go there every day
I heard that Hachiko was always around the station
At that time, there was so many food stalls in front of the station
She's definitely gonna tell this story again
People drinking there would throw chicken or bones or something to him
Can we stop talking about yakitori?
I've heard Hachiko ate this sort of stuff a lot
It seems that this is indeed true
And another...
I saw Hachiko crossing the street at the Yamanote Line
While looking out of the train
Saw Hachiko outside?
Kuroi, from a train, saw Hachiko crossing the street
Eyewitnesses are suddenly appearing
First he looked left, and then looked right, and then crossed the road
What a great laugh!
I saw this
And this lady who used to visit Shibuya Station at that time
I was born in Showa 3
Hachiko died in Showa 10, right?
Yes
I can still remember things very clearly from when I was 7 years old
It was at the ticket gate
He was hanging around
Just kept turning around
Was it common for Hachiko to be at Shibuya Station at that time?
Yes, lots of people went over to pat him on the head
He was a very calm dog
Pale yellow
How can I put it? He wasn't that good-looking
And...
Ah, professor!
This Shibuya-born inventor
What?
Have you ever seen Hachiko with your own eyes?
-Yes
I am now considered to be a long-term experienced individual
Seriously!?
I created this "Long Experience Platform"
The most important is that the narrator of history
I've witnessed a lot of events over the years
※A failed mutiny that occurred in Japan on February 26, 1936, in which some young officers of the Imperial Army led more than 1,000 soldiers to assassinate the "unificationists" and opponents of the government and senior members of the military, and the coup was eventually crushed.
For example, the February 26th Incident
Machine gun teams lined up on the street in what is now Harajuku
Although we are also interested in the February 26th Incident
We would most like to ask about Hachiko
-Yes, Hachiko
Lying there, sleeping
Baaaaa, lying there as if asleep
No "barking" at all
No response
Just waiting there for his master patiently, same as is known
Also, there is Daigo, who likes dogs
I'd like to ask you about Hachiko
-Hachiko, a very loyal dog, right?
Have you seen him with your own eyes?
-Well, when I was in kindergarten,
I lived in Osaki at the time.
I used to get the Yamanote Line at Shibuya
At the ticket gate outside, Hachiko was there
I used to go and pat him on the head
You patted him?
-Yes, I did
Touched Hachiko!
I was in kindergarten so him and me had the same eye-level
Not only seeing him, we also found people who have touched Hachiko with their own hands
Awesome!
Not only that, but we also found genuine footage of Hachiko
Please watch this rare footage
Faithful Dog Hachiko
Yakitori!
Is that him?
He's huge!
You also came to see the dog that moves people?
Why are you touching the dog? Come here
Why should only teachers should come here?
This is the real Hachiko
And a little off-topic
When I was walking near Sakuranagi on a quiet road
Across the street came a man of my age now
He said, "My mother fed Hachiko," and I was shocked to hear that
The left ear was folded
It's true
And "my mother sewed it"
The tip of the ear was broken when he returned from a fight outside
She did the stitching, but because it was done by an amateur,
After the injury it wasn't restored to its original state, it remained in this folded state
This is what I heard
You just came across this person?
Yes, I was surprised to come across this information completely by chance
To sum up
There are plenty of people still alive that saw Hachiko
Impressive
There's still some people that saw him
Quite a lot this time
Wasn't he in a movie?
He acted in Showa 9
-Indeed in a movie
"It Started in the Alps released in Showa 9
But he was really big
-Really big!
Very impressive
But there were many derogatory statements
About Hachiko...
Not loyal to his master but just wants to eat chicken, right?
I guess so
And that one...
Bronze statue built before death 'like a dictator"
It's better not to say this sort of thing
"Surprisingly dirty"
-Yeah, yeah, yeah
We don't need this kind of information
The old man sitting on his doorstep at the end
Was he waiting for his mother to get back?
He's not the kind of grandpa who waits for people on the side of the road
Let's welcome the next presenter
It's FUJIWARA!
Thank you
-Thank you
Previously, there was a project that had junior comedians performing
And FUJIWARA's Haranishi made it very awkward for them by saying "I have a similar joke, are you copying me"?
We had a project like this.
-Do you remember?
Haranishi was shown a segment by a junior comedian and improvised a similar segment
Then, he made it difficult for them by attempting to prevent them from performing it
As a result, basically all of the junior comedians' sketches were successfully suppressed
Originally, it was just a joke
Indeed, but after I met one of the juniors
He said he never performed the joke after that
I don't know but i'm still feeling weird about it
-It obviously wouldn't be performed again
So this time, we've come up with another diabolical theory
It's hard to overcome a senpai who insists on playing the same character as you and says "I did it before you"
Certainly difficult
And so, the first test subject invited to a fake shoot was
Thank you for having me
With three years of experience: Yasuko
Yasuko
I was a self-defense officer
Last year, she became popular with her Self Defense Force persona
The one who is going to make things difficult for her this time is
Thank you for having me
With 20 years of experience: Texas
So experienced!
Self-defense force after all
-Looks the part
Like Yasuko, he was also a former member of the Land Self-Defense Force
A pioneer of self-defense comedy
Looks very convincing
Next
Documentary skit
Wow, I forgot the lines. What was it?
We let Yasuko, who is yet to shoot,
And Texas, who just finished filming, meet in the lounge
Wow
-Good morning
Good morning
Texas?
-Yeah, it's me
Wow!
Thank you, Yasu
Thanks for your hard work
-Thank you for your hard work
I'm sorry
-No
We're meeting for the first time, right?
-Wow, wow
First time meeting, excuse me, excuse me
I'm really, really sorry. I'm really sorry
I've always wanted to meet you
No, no, I don't dare
I always follow you on TV
No need to be so polite. Sit down, sit down
Oops, no
Yasuko is very frightened to meet her senpai for the first time
Yasuko is usually like this
Must be scary
How many years have you been doing this?
Just two years so far
1 term?
-Yes
The conversation between the two naturally comes to the Self Defense Force
What rifles did you use?
Type 89 Rifle
-89 ah
Did you use 64?
-Yes
Wow!
What are you talking about?
-I don't understand
Have you ever thrown a hand grenade?
I have
You can't throw it without an order?
-Yes
That must be tough
-Yes it is
First, we let the two happily talk about the self-defense force
And then, the difficult challenge begins
I don't mean anything by this but
Our two personas are really pretty similar, aren't they
Starting with clothing
Oh I don't mean anything weird by it
-Yes
As an unexpected attack is unleashed
Yasu can't help but suddenly sit up straight
And then
After all, it was me who started using the Self Defense Force persona first!
Here we go
There is indeed a bit of similarity... regarding this
By the way
Can you stop using the Self Defense Force persona in the future?
Self-defense force persona...waaaa
What do you think?
Waaaaaa... how...
I'll stop being a self-defense comedian
Yasuko chooses to give up the self-defense force persona after a painful internal struggle
Really?
Can you really?
The orders of commanding officers must be absolutely obeyed
If you want to wear camouflage, then I won't wear it anymore
You are not in the service now
Really, sir, your orders are absolutely correct
Then I'll...waa waaa ehhhhh ummm
Yasuko painfully decides to give up her persona to the other side
What a face
In future we can still coexist in separate domains
Thank you for giving me this opportunity
No, no, I'm the one who should be thanking you
OK, "yes, sir!"
What's going on?
Out of respect for her superior, she decides to relinquish elements of the Self Defense Force
Do you have a favorite camouflage style?
I like the blue camouflage of the Maritime Self-Defense Force
So you can wear blue camouflage?
Fiiiine
Regarding the five different kinds of crawling
The first four are one's that i'll use from now on
No problem at all
Waaaaa! I don't know
Eh? Is it okay or not?
No problem
It's okay?
-Yes
After that, all kinds of unequal treaties were decided upon, from the one-shot technique to the way of speaking
Yasuko literally always dresses like this
What is this?
What are you going to do if you don't work as a SDF comedian anymore?
I'm SONY, so I'll go naked
Cover here with a pan
Isn't that also plagiarism?
Ah, is it plagiarism? Wow, I'm sorry
I... i'll wear a loin cloth, loin cloth...
And swallow fire
What the hell?
The next target is
Excuse me. Good morning
I'm Elf Arakawa, thanks for having me
With six years of experience: Elf Arakawa
Happiness~
She is now gaining popularity as a gyaru comedian
The one who will make things difficult for her is...
Is this joke bad?
A gyaru comedian with 11 years of experience: U-BEAM☆
These two are also meeting for the first time
And so the challenge begins
How can I put it?
Some seniors often tell me that our two personas collide
Seniors said that?
-Yes
It's a clash, right?
In terms of the gyaru persona then I guess there is a bit of a clash
I also often feel, like, "aren't I the one that started it?"
Have you ever considered giving up being a gyaru comedian?
This...no longer a gyaru comedian?
Are you being serious about this right now?
It's serious!
Yeah
I think... the entertainment business is a place where losing is tantamount to dying
But I just want to do the same thing as U-BEAM by chance
So if personas are colliding, perhaps this could just be seen as a healthy competitive relationship
Like, I don't want to lose to you but I don't mean any offense by that
Hmm...
I'm sorry if you see it that way, but I can't give up
Very bold
-Arakawa, right?
Faced with the unreasonable difficulty of trying to monopolize the gyaru persona that is not exclusive to anyone
Arakawa decisively refuses the request with careful expressions
Thus, U-BEAM ☆, the senpai, counters
Do you have any signature joke?
First of all, I usually open by saying "Yay!", right?
When I see your "Yay!" I have the feeling of "Wow, so similar"
Isn't that how you lot all say hello?
-Yes
The topic shifts to accusations of joke stealing
I might also say "Happiness" and "Hashtag"
I also do, how should I put it...
To make things difficult for the other party, U-BEAM ☆ starts to improvise and create a joke that clashes with the other's
And so
"From Happiness to Loneliness, Bring the Chef out!"
I have a joke like this
-No way!
And,
Also "Storm Crying Wailing"
I have "Wailing in Moderation"
-Really?
The quality of jokes is significantly lower than the other's
It's improvised after all
What about "pretending to apologize but actually showing off Chanel"?
"Thank you-Chanel!"
No way...
U-BEAM☆ holds on tightly
And so, Arakawa, who had been very strong before...
I'm really sorry about this
I feel like we both can't get away with "Chanel"
I won't touch "Chanel"
-Really?
Yes
"The best good, GUCCI" is okay?
This seems more interesting
What the hell is interesting?
Chanel becomes exclusive as the other is allowed to change to Gucci
What are you talking about?
And so, the truth is revealed
I'm afraid, I'm afraid
This is Wednesday Downtown
No way!
The whole time I kept thinking "please let this be a prank!"
U-BEAM☆ that was really messed up
You must've thought I'm awful
It sucked, seriously, what a shitty person!
No question!
I'd definitely think that
And so, the last target is...
Hello, I'm JP, a parody comedian, thank you for having me
With sixteen years of experience: JP
Appearing on Wide na Show as Matsumoto recently helped boost his popularity significantly
He is ranked top amongst all Matsumoto Hitoshi impersonators
The one who has come to make things difficult for him is...
Thank you for having me
With 30 years of imitation experience as Downstutowntsu's Matsumoto Hitoshi
Not at all alike
Do you have confidence?
Not really, but I I I I will work hard will work hard
It's true that... yes, people with a long history... are long... yes
His speech is so wasteful
These two met once ten years ago
How did it go?
Good Morning
-Good morning
What's going on?
It's been a long time, please let me know your contact information
I'm not being rude, am I?
I don't even know how to get anything up on my phone
-Really?
Yes, basically, I let my wife or Hamada do it when he's around
Who?
His partner, right?
Downstutowntsu's
The two reunited Matsumotos have a nice chat
Can you show me Matsumoto's laugh?
Ah a laugh
Really similar
The pose is also similar
I'll mimic the laugh too
The quality...
-Terrible
A low-quality Matsumoto
Begins using his seniority to be unkind
Will it work?
Go ahead
-How should I put it? The imitation of Matsumoto
If I tell JP directly, if it's okay, don't do the imitation
Saying it in person, what will happen?
Ah... eh... what do you mean?
Do you want me to talk to Matsumoto?
No, no, it's me telling you
If its okay to stop doing it, like this...
What if I told him in person?
What do you mean?
What's he talking about?
Uh... what are we talking about? I'm sorry
I forgot what we were talking about
It's a long, complicated sentence like a Kamaitachi skit
Matsumoto Hitoshi isn't getting his point across at all
His conversation skills...
To put it bluntly, can you not...
-Please tell me, tell me
What?
Can you stop imitating Matsumoto?
Should have just said that to begin
-Yeah
Don't do it... eh, now?
-Yes
I value the viewers' opinions
If people like to see it, then I want to keep doing it
Reluctant to give up?
-Reluctant to give up
JP politely expresses that he will continue to imitate Matsumoto
Matsumoto continues to express himself
JP, i'm just telling you here
I have Matsumoto's contact info
-Is that so?
I personally feel that Matsumoto actually acknowledges me more
That's for sure. I don't think there's anything wrong with that
Definitely not so
Implicitly revealing to the other party that Matsumoto is more accepting of him
How dare you say that!
Hamada is also very good to me
The actual Hamada?
-Of course
He's saying he is supported by Downtown
Wow
Showing off his good friendship with Hamada
And stressing the superiority of using real hair instead of a wig
How to say
If you can give it up then I will also be happy
What kind of tone is this?
Yes, I understand
To be honest, I do it because I really like Matsumoto
Also note the Kansai accent
The fact that I am able to do this today, my own efforts don't even account for 0.1%
Its all thanks to the help and support of Matsumoto
It's all really due to Matsumoto
If that...
If possible
Sorry, I'm getting a little carried away
I feel a lot of emotions inside, sorry
Let me think about it
I'm really sorry
What a face that was
Please let me continue...
What an expression
Excuse me
You're not the real person you know
I sincerely ask you to let me continue to imitate Matsumoto in the future
Facing JP's plea with tears in his eyes
Please let me imitate Matsumoto, please!
Ok
Inexplicably, one impersonator allows another impersonator's impersonation
Who the hell are you?
The main purpose seems to have changed
Here the truth is revealed
Who are you?
-He's Hitoshi!
Why do you get to make the decision
Why does he decide on my behalf?
That... no... that...
Sorry, I have to put the wig on
JP thought it was the fake segment for an online show
But we informed him it was actually Wednesday Downtown
Seriously!?
No way!
Great!
Thank god!
I thought...
I'm so happy
-I was having a tough time too
I really thought I couldn't do it
Impressive
I'm sorry. I'm sorry
I've made it this far...
I thought I was going to lose everything
To sum up
Losing one's persona can be so painful that one cries out in pain
Impressive
An impressive VTR
-How was it?
I didn't expect Matsumoto to cry at the end
I also didn't expect to see such a thing unfold
How do you feel about JP?
His love and respect for you overflowed on the screen
He is a good guy, so I guess its too be expected of him
Compared to him, Hitoshi is really...
-It's true
Looking at him pisses me off
He's become more and more unlike you in recent years
A number of unexplained phenomena have occurred
I'd like to see the real Matsumoto giving Hitoshi a hard time
If you gave me the chance I wouldn't stop!
Saying anything is incredibly fair
Next is everybody's theories
Tonight's presenters are
Onigoe Tomahawk
-Thanks for having us
Anti-social, anti-social people
-No no no
Without further ado, this time we bring you a hypothesis related to one of Yoshimoto Kogyo's senior members
Please have a look
There are no young comedians who know the real name of Honkon
Probably not
He was using his  real name until the end of "Gottsu ee Kanji"
Then changed it to his stage name
Changed to Honkon?
-Yes
How long has it been since he changed to Honkon
25 years
By the way, Iizuka, do you Honkon's real name?
Well, I watched Gottsu Ee Kanji
It's Kurano, right?
Yes, his first name is Kurano
Matsumoto certainly knows, right?
No, my memory is a little hazy
Takahiro
We're not really sure
What?
You're asking the question but you don't know?
I'm sorry
Originally the group was called Hong Kong Macau
The group disbanded, leaving only Hong Kong
For some reason people started calling him Honkon Honkon
So that's where he got his stage name I guess
Yes
There are no young comedians who know the real name of Honkon
To verify, young comedians who debuted after Honkon's name change were tested
First
Good morning
Debuting just six years ago, The Mummy
Please listen to the question
-Ok
Question?
Who is this?
Hello
-Hello
Honkon？
Correct
Yes
-Yes
Have you ever worked with Honkon?
We worked with him twice in Osaka
What impression did you have of him
He wears glasses backstage
When reading the newspaper or something, it's kind of scary
He's a very nice guy though
Please listen to another question
What is Honkon's real name?
This is a bit...
Honkon's real name?
He has a pretty unique and interesting name
It's more of a beautiful name
What is it...
It's more like a handsome man's name, right?
Nakayauchi Mao
Is that a handsome man?
Incorrect
As expected, they don't know
Too tough
Next is Hanako Kikuta, who has experience in co-starring with a different agency
What impression do you have of him
He sometimes... makes political statements
This is what has happened recently
A little... a little scary
Is that okay? He won't be mad will he?
So, what is Honkon's real name?
Eh? Honkon's?
What was it? I should know
What is it?
It has "Kura" in it
Kurama Toshikazu
No? Who knows?
The next question is a junior comedian who belongs to the same agency as Honkon
"Kura" was right at least
And is also a regular on "Marco Pololi"
Must know then
What is Honkon's real name?
Kurano...
Kurano Yoichi
Wrong?
But we really...
I haven't been a regular member for six months
We're not that close, really
Excuse!
Is that the issue?
The next challenger is...
Miki should know, right?
Not only do we often meet on shows, we also perform at the Lumine Theater once a month
We're often together in the green room
Wait, what? What? So scary!
I'm scared of...
I don't really want to talk about Honkon
This is the most unacceptable
Still
-What's wrong?
He's been angry with me several times
I did indeed do something wrong
Said my greeting was too shallow
-Too shallow?
Greeting was too shallow?
He told me "say good morning properly!"
"Saying "morning" isn't good enough"
"Look down and say "good morning" properly!"
"What you're doing isn't a real greeting"
He got angry at the show's celebration party, where Higashino and all the staff were present
I also had a meal with him at Lumine once
Honkon asked, "What are you going to eat?
"Soba noodles"
"Oh really?" "Yes."
"Is it good?" "Yes."
He scolded me, saying, "don't you wanna have a conversation!?"
Don't want to
I was shouted at for not wanting to start a conversation over lunch
-I've been shouted at a few times for the same thing
Doesn't want to
"Say something!"
And he'd tell me "don't answer so boringly"
As we now know that Miki and Honkon are very close, let's get to the point
Known
What is Honkon's full name
Really?
-See!
Honestly, I might actually know
After all, you'd definitely know important senior comedians
You know?
-Yes
Seriously, I can't think of even a single character
It is similar to Honkon?
I'm not saying anything
-Can't think of a single character
Forget about the validity of this theory or anything
Not being able to answer is very rude to Honkon
Homma... Homma Daisuke?
Too much
That was very rude
-This is gonna be bad
Can I say it?
-Please do
Kurano Takahiro
Correct
Very good
Its Kurano!
Everyone is so rude
Regarding Gottsu Ee Kanji, people always think of Downtown, Imada and Higashino
These main characters
Ah wait what i'm saying is too much....
I don't really understand what he's getting at
To sum up
Honkon's going to shout at everyone
I'm sorry
-This is bad
If Honkon sees this he'll be angry
He watches all shows
-Literally everything
You are the ones who brought this theory
We haven't met him yet
If possible, I hope to reach the end of my career without meeting Honkon
No way, you haven't met at all?
-No, not at all
Really?
-Not at all
Really!?
Many young comedians have warned us over the years to be careful
We also watched Honkon when we were young
But why are Downtown's henchmen still held in such high regard?
Shut up!
That's scary!
This should absolutely never be said!
Hamada, this is the guy that said it
Even juniors wouldn't dare say such a thing!
I'm sorry, this guy is really...
We are currently recruiting women who really like Kuro-chan
Although the planned program is not yet confirmed
The specific plan will be determined according to the situation of the recruited people
Please go to the program website to state your interest!
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03