Hello everyone, welcome to Wednesday's Downtown!
Here we go - our first presenter is this person!
Who is it?
It's Cunning Takeyama!
As an entertainer...
...what do you think is the thing you need be most careful of?
The most?
Affairs?
Yeah, affairs.
Pictoral magazines.
If we put those together, any kind of scandal.
I have an experience from eleven years ago.
My picture was put in a magazine...
...and that caused quite a hassle.
During those times as soon as you hear about a scandal...
...your mind just goes blank.
I heard about my scandal right before a quiz show on NHK.
I couldn't answer a single question that night.
My emotions were all over the place.
I know that feeling.
When I see an unfamiliar, important-looking guy like a chief manager...
...roaming around set, I think to myself "something definiely happened."
After this there's definitely going to be something.
And so this is the theory I have brought today.
Theory: Even if your manager told you "a scandalous article about you will come out tomorrow,"
...a professional would finish their job for the day without showing any signs of the upcoming issues.
I see.
If you're a professional...
...your personal scandal has nothing to do with the job.
So they should just push through.
If I was informed of a scandal right before coming here...
...I can't just mope around while I'm here.
But you couldn't answer questions at the quiz show!
I was truly so shocked!
Even now I barely remember anything about the show!
Also:
Today we investigate the theory: Even if your manager tells you "a scandalous article will come out about you tomorrow,"...
...a professional would finish their job for the day without showing any signs of the upcoming issues.
Today's targets: KoroChiki's Nadal, Panther's Ogata, and Yasumura.
We had them come in for a fake to show to determine who the most useless entertainer is.
Please take the lead since you're the eldest.
Actually, I'll take the lead.
In that case, I can lead!
I can lead too!
In that case, I will lead!
By all means, please!
What the hell, man?!
All three started the gig with high energy levels.
Today we've prepared the same scandal article for each of them.
We will tell them one at a time over the course of the gig.
While the staff "get ready," the comedians wait in the green room.
First we target this man.
Manager: We need to talk.
It can't be here?
We escort him to another room to tell him about the article.
Sorry, umm...
...around the end of last year, did you go out drinking with some girls?
The end of last year?
It was right around December...
I actually haven't been out drinking with girls.
Well, it's about this, and they've also taken pictures.
And the picture shown to Nadal is:
Nadal: Accusations of drinking with underage high school girls.
An article with bad implications.
What is this?
What the hell is this?
Underage?
Yes, the investigation for this theory began months ago in December.
End of year party... it's been a great year!
At an end-of-year party with close friends...
Good evening.
Wow, she is Jitsukata's type of girl.
Nadal's friend brought her female friend, who brought her friend to the party...
...to set up the female actresses.
This is bad.
From the girls' perspective this
party would be such a letdown.
As soon as they all have a drink, the setup is complete.
By the way, the girl drinking next to Nadal is the "underage" girl for the sake of the investigation.
Jitsukata brought them.
I'm pretty sure I confirmed with them.
How old are you?
TN: Legal drinking age in Japan is 20.
I'm 22.
I just turned 20.
20? Are you sure you're not 19?
I'm 20!
I beg of you, seriously.
We're really toeing the line here.
It's so real.
Indeed - if I get caught with drinking with an underage girl...
I properly asked if she was over 20.
This is his fault.
This is @#$%&*!
This guy's messed up in the head.
This guy is seriously messed up.  He's deranged.
People from Shibuya are generally deranged.
People from Tokyo are messed in the head.
All these deranged people gathered and created this deranged city.
That's the reason drugs are spreading through Tokyo.
That's why I don't like Tokyo.
There are only these psycho guys.
I've never met a proper guy here, seriously.
For some reason, Nadal's anger was directed at Tokyo in general.
And then...
I knew this would happen if I ever did something like this.
Using my joke like "yabbeezo!" ("that's pretty bad").
Like, "he went for the underage girl."
"He went for the underage girl, yabbeezo."
The way they write this pisses me off.
I only have these dirty jokes.
I only have jokes they can easily make puns out of.
I don't have any pop.
He kept saying it wasn't his fault.
In the article there are accusations of sexual harrassment.
I don't remember.
I legit don't remember.
Did you say any of these things?
Is there a chance you said these things?
No, no - I didn't say that.
I might have asked about the last time she got busy.
Marin, you're seriously in danger though.
It seems like guys would target you with your vibe.
Have any guys recently invited you...
...to have a one-night stand?  When's the last time?
No comment!
Marin-chan, you can whisper - just tell me when you last did it.
But it wasn't like...
..."when did you do it last?" in a harrassing way.
It was more like, "when's the last time you did it?"
There was more pop to it.  I was saying it as a joke.
I don't know how the manager isn't laughing.
She went for it pretty recently!
Let me ask Yasumura-san for advice.
No, hold on...
It's still very raw information.
So, please keep it a secret from those two, and don't tell your wife either.
This is rough...
Please keep it to yourself for now.
I can't work like this.
The thing Nadal was most worried about with the article release was:
You know how I have those commercials? What's happening there?
Umm...for now...
Wait a minute...no no no no no no...
This is awful!
Crap crap crap crap...
A TV commercial that was just recently confirmed.
Is the commercial gone?
Judging from the way things are going, it will probably be scrapped.
My head hurts...
I have a stomachache.
Also the gig you are doing right now...
...it might get shelved too.
But we can't tell other people...
...so for now please continue working normally.
My commercial...
What is going on?
This is awful.
Yeah, well...
We gotta cover this up.
Covering it up is a bit...
We need to cover it up, otherwise these guys just do as they please.
The drinks...I paid for those!
Yeah...
Wait, actually it was Hikaru.
Nadal would do anything to keep his commercial...
...demanding that they cover up the article somehow.
This guy... seriously.
Please cover it up.
We can't let these guys walk all over us.
Yoshimoto as a company isn't being taken seriously.
They're thinking they can cash in on us.
This is seriously so wrong.  It's messed up.
Well, the article is actually coming out...
Cover it up...just this once.
I was really looking forward to it.
Well that doesn't change that it's getting published.
Could you...take this seriously?
I've got it.
This is the worst.
Crap, I don't feel good.
The news hit Nadal both physically and mentally.
Staff: Excuse me.
Back to the show.
Let's see how he's doing.
Let's go!
Yep.
His energy level is perfect!
Compared to the other two who came through with their usual high energy levels...
...Nadal has completely toned down since the opening shot.
The next thing these three are going to do today...
...super spicy dandan noodle challenge.
Okay, let's go!
That looks spicy!
So... spicy...!
Nadal, on the other hand...
It hurts!
I can't eat this...
He took the first bite...
We've gotta finish this - we're the stars of the show!
We're the regulars!
Let's do this!
We'll do our best!
Let's go.
Nadal knows that the pilot episode won't even air.
Next to the two who went to war with their spicy dishes...
...he was just drinking water the whole time.
This can't be done...
When two of them finished their bowls, the filming for this segment was over.
You weren't eating at all!
You didn't eat anything!
Following Nadal...
At this point we tell Yasamura about the article.
Umm...
...this article was just sent to me.
18 years old... high school girl...
This is awful.
Oh that's spicy.
"Accusations against Yasamura are as follows:"
I mean, I asked her age and she said she was 20.
How old are you?
BON THE WORLD
(comedian)
I'm 20.
So young!
LLR
Tomohoro Ito
Trendy Angel
Takashi
Isn't it scary?
I almost want to check her license or something.
Is this a crime?
This is horrible.
I have to go to court and stuff, right?
There were also allegations of sexual harassment.
Sexual harassment?
Yasumura-san, are you drunk already?
I'm not drunk.
He's drunk.
Oh, he's drunk!
"He showed me his nipple, which I didn't want to see..."
"...and coerced me to touch it with my glass, as if to say 'cheers!'"
Oh yeah, I guess I did that.
Y... You did that?
I did show her my nipple.
What the hell, man?
From the top!
That's so nasty!
Nipple cheers!
That's cold!
This party went full-throttle on the sexual harassment.
However, once the girls left...
This...is Marin-chan's?
Marin-chan and Mao-chan.
This is Marin-chan's.
This is bad.
This shot glass has a higher percentage.
He's really doing it.
It feels like we've seen this somewhere else.
He's disgusting.
Do you mind if I go to the bathroom?
No, not at all.
If this is real then this is quite...
Well, at this point I would get fired, right?
I'm not sure that you would get fired...
Worst case I'm getting fired.  I mean...
99% chance I'm getting fired.
Right now we're confirming if everything is real...
...talking to the other people who were there, so...
...so, for now, please continue.
Continue like this?
I had to confirm the details with you as soon as possible.
So I had to tell you now.
Can I really work in this state?
With Yasumura mentally preparing to retire, we continue filming.
We find ourselves in a situation where two of three are not all there.
Let's see how it goes.
Okay!
What's next?
Where did Yasumura's energy from earlier go?
On the other hand, perhaps with the passage of time...
...Nadal's energy has partially recovered.
The next segment for these three to partake in is...
...to ask women around Venus Fort who the #1 man they want to sleep with is.
Wait a minute!
If I got a vote from such a cutie, I'd be so happy!
Hold on...
We're matching!  It's the turtleneck!
Just 30 minutes ago Yasumura had a vibrant energy.
Now he doesn't crack a single joke.
Additionally...
From time to time we could see he was consumed in his own thoughts.
And now we tell Ogata...
...who has been carrying the session with his high energy...
...about the article coming out tomorrow.
If this comes out, its over.
Here we tell Ogata about the article.
If this comes out, it's over.
Drinking with someone underage...
They wrote "say 'no, thank you' to alcohol."
They're using my joke as a pun.
It's over for me.
It's over if this is released.
This girl is 18 years old?
She's 18.
Didn't they look quite young?
No...I mean...
...young?  It looked like she had white hairs.
As if you'd drink with someone like that!
Kind of like white hairs...
Hmm...
Her skin didn't look very nice, either.
It wasn't nice.
Oh, and one more point:
Eh? What?
Here.
The borderline sexual harassment...
Did that really happen?
I don't think I did anything that was borderline sexual harassment...
I swear I didn't do anything!
I have a wife and kids.
I have 33 years left on my mortgage.
Do you think I would do something like that?
I'm not trying to accuse you.
...but right now, Yoshimoto can't deal with ANY lies.
Understood.
I mean, if you lie about something like this...
Yeah.
Can you clarify what is true and what isn't?
I did say "I'd tap that."
You said that?
I said it as a joke.
Man it's fun to go out drinking with some ladies.
I'd tap that!
I'd tap thaaaat!
What about her hair?
Did you smell it?
Yes, I think I smelled it.
In reality, Ogata didn't even touch their hair - let alone smell it.
For some reason he confessed to a crime he didn't commit.
Perhaps other false confessions come from being in this type of high-pressure situation.
Is it wrong to smell their hair?
Why? Is there a law?
If someone feels harassed...
...that's already sexual harassment.
By the way, what he actually did do once the girls left was...
(The actress' chopsticks)
May I?
Hey, stop it with those kind of jokes.
Wait, what? Eh? Eh? Eh?
He's taking it home.
Feels like we've seen this before, too.
Wait a minute, help me out here.
I'm not sure to what extent I can help, but...
...the article is being published.
I mean, there's really nothing I can do at this point, is there?
Perhaps he felt there was no way out of this situation.
At this moment...
Are all the other comedians being exposed too?
We should cover their faces.
If the story is coming out
anyway I'll take the fall.
We would all be screwed,
that's not necessary.
After that display of loyalty...
...we sent Ogata back on set to continue filming for today's gig.
And then...
Such a somber vibe!
The green room was like a funeral.
Let's take a look at the shoot where all the stars believe it will be shelved.
Please begin in 5...4...3...2...
It's completely different!
Two hours ago they started with so much energy.
Everyone's demeanor has calmed so much...
...it's like we're seeing a different show.
Ogata was hit particularly hard with the news.
So we're competing to see who can find as many good things about Venus Fort.
You can walk around freely and we'll share our answers later.
Let's go!
It looks like tears could stream down his face at any moment.
This is the worst.
And now...a segment with a forturne teller to see who has the best luck.
From here forward...what is going to happen...
...in terms of a career change?
Career change?
Yeah, I want to hear about a career change and whatnot.
Yeah.
Like, not as a comedian?
Yeah, I want to hear about non-entertainment stuff too.
Also, my kids...will I stop being able to see them?
What happened to you?
His thoughts are completely consumed by the scandal.
Did you see anything about me losing job opportunities?
No no no no...
Really? I'm talking comedy jobs.
Yeah, nothing like that.
So if I work hard, everything will go well?
It will.
That gave me some energy.
This is going to come true, right?
You're not energetic at all!
Is it really going to come true?
You're scary!
Are you sure?
At this point they have wrapped up filming for the day.
As the three of them were set to leave the building...
...we set up a fake journalist to ambush them.
How will they react?
Good evening, excuse me...
This is in regards to the underage drinking accusations.
Can these allegations be considered factual?
I apologize.
So you admit it? We can consider it the truth?
I'm sorry.
I mean...I didn't know about it...I'm sorry.
Do you feel bad for what you've done?
I mean... I...um...
Yes...um...
Yes.
I should have asked them properly.
Eh?
I'm sorry.
Is it Ogata? Who is it?
Is it Ogata?
It's me.
What? Me too.
They told me about that, too.
Wait, what?  Yasumura-san, too?
They told me a girl I had drinks with...
My manager told me between segments.
They said I sexually harassed them.
They accused me, too.
Oh, this is the exact same.
You can go, man.  We'll take care of this.
It happened to me, too.
Eh? What's going on?
Wait a second...
What's going on?
It's me...
Wait a minute, what...
Here we step in to reveal the prank.
Oh, we got pranked!
Thank god, I'm so relieved!
I'm so glad!  This was a lie, right?
That was close!
It's not getting published, right?
Oh god, that's a relief!
I thought it was over.
What kind of feeling is this?
Staff: Do you know what show this is?
Eh...Dokkiri Grand Prix wouldn't do anything this messed up...
No, they wouldn't.
Wednesday Downtown.
That's correct.
The script said "Other TV Station!"
Are you allowed to do this?! I should sue you guys!
Let's sue them!
That is so wrong.
The script said !@#$
But I'm so relieved...
Seriously, so relieved.
I seriously thought I would have to get a divorce.
Staff: All's well that ends well, right?
But that was a close one.
If I was pressured more, I might have gone for it.
What?
You would have gone for it?
Yeah?
In conclusion, it was good they didn't go for it.
That was amazing!
All three of them got down in the dumps!
I don't want any of the viewers at home to be confused.
Those three did nothing wrong...
...and this show is seriously messed up.
They asked for their age, and didn't do anything bad.
It's a great educational video.
Even as a joke, licking the chopsticks...
...and doing this with the cup...
...that's seriously gross.
Do you guys do that?
Every comedian does that.
That's not true.
There's no reason to do that.
People who do that all become comedians.
Did you do that?!
Of course not!
Hamada-san definitely does it.
Does everyone do the "nipple cheers" as well?
That one was invented by Hamada.
What the hell?!
Hamada is the originator.