SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
fB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TRANSLATION BY SHION
TYPESET BY SHION & KEDOMAS
EDIT & QC BY KEDOMAS
Here's our next presenter, please come in
It's him!
Presenter:
Kasuga Toshiaki
(from Audrey)
m 0 0 l -30 0 l -30 30 l 30 30 l 30 0 l 0 0
It's Kasuga Toshiaki
Toos!
Alright, today I want to show you---
Already? It's too early
I don't want to waste time
Have you ever experienced a booby-trap?
Oh yes
- Booby-traps...
He really started already...
- That's right
'Cause I want to show you the VTR
Booby-traps? I think Tanaka had
Oh yeah, I've fell down in like 10 of those
That's a fair bunch
How about you, Matsushino?
- Never
Oh, never before?
- No
How about you, Downtown?
I don't think we haven't, right?
- Yeah, i guess so...
Most likely yes
- I think so too
Alright, about the booby-traps...
They're fun to watch, right?
- They are
It's fun to see them work
So, here's the theory I've brought with me today
Booby-traps Battle Royale
"Booby-traps Battle Royale"
What's this about?
It's basically a booby-trap-your-opponent game
You have some booby-traps yourself
And you have to lead your opponents inside them
Yes, it requires strategy
To a degree
- Sounds fun
It's also about psychological warfare​
- I see...
But it's not a theory at all
Well, yeah, it's not
It's fine, we don't need them
Are we done with theories?
Yes, today it's not a theory
10:06 A.M.
Good morning
Akemi Matsuno
Anzen Manzai
Miyazon
Mari Yaguchi
Trendy Angel
Takashi
Viking
Kotohge Eiji
Step forward and form a line
We tricked them into thinking
this was a camping episode
Get closer
Professor Kitano
(Beat Takeshi)
It's Takeshi...
- Where...?
What's going on?!
- What the--?
What was that?
Wait, what's that?
- Listen
The entertainment industry has hit rock bottom
Wha-?
What are you talking about?
- That's why...
Wait a second, this is getting scary
That's why I thought of this game
Booby-trap Battle Royale
What?!
- What the hell?
text
Give me a break!
Who are thos--- aaah!!
So goddamn loud!
This is scary!
I'll have you booby-trap each other
Booby-trap each other...?
- W-wait
Boobie-trap battle until only one will be left!!
On today's plan, only one of them will be left
It's time for Booby-trap Battle Royale
This is incredible...
Each one of them knows two trap locations
There's a total of 10 holes dug up in this camping site
Each member knows the location of two of them
A psychological game about luring your opponents
It's a psychological game in which you have
to lead your opponent inside your own trap
Cookhouse
Kotohge
Matsuno
Miyazon
Takashi
Yaguchi
Their holes have been chosen by lottery, here they are
They all receive a map with their own holes
And they received a map
which only shows their two holes
I think that... this one must be my hole
So you fell inside your own hole, huh...
That's a shame
No, Matsuno, you don't have to dig it yourself
Are you sure about...
I g-g-g--gg-guess so?
They're already there?
- Yeah, I think so
An idiot shouldn't speak with another idiot!
Are the holes in there already?
- Yes, they are
Tracking their own traps
They all went to check their own booby-traps' location
Booby-trap Battle Royale: start
11:16 A.M.
And now the game finally begins
Alright guys, now go get ready for lunch
Sure
- Got it
Should we walk this close to each other?
- Well, there could be a trap...
11:16 A.M. - Going to the cookhouse to prepare lunch
Oh, that's right
- This looks like one     - Watch out
Hey look, there's... like, over there...
- What's going on?
There's some kind of flower, let's go see it
- A flower?
We should eat first...
Come on, it's Spring
Let's go see the flower sprouts
Flower gazing?
That's right, flower gazing
But lunch...
We gotta make it first
She's just revealing her moves
- Right...
What Matsuno is plotting is...
How can I put it...
Cookhouse
Current location
Matsuno
Objective
She sucks so bad!
This way!
Matsuno? You suck at this
- What?
No way we're falling for that
There's a trap over there, right?
No, that's not...
- Already?
Her plan failed because of her poor acting
Her plan to lure them failed because of her poor acting
Oh boy...
Cookhouse
Current location
Matsuno
Objective
She only revealed where her trap was
In the end, she only let them know where her trap is
That was too quick, Matsuno
This is the cooking area
Cookhouse
How nice, it's all set up
Come on, let's get ready
11:21 A.M. - Time to start the barbecue
Again?!
There she goes again
Matsuno..?
She's so bad at this!
Where are you going?
We gotta get ready
We gotta set everything up, right?
Matsuno's trap
- She sucks so bad...
I mean, it's so obvious
You're really bad at this, Matsuno
Come on, let's get ready
Alright, let's get ready then
Cookhouse
Matsuno
They all know there's another hole nearby
Another poor act reveals her second hole
Current location
But...
Matsuno's trap
This is incredible
We gotta move this
Over there
But...
Let's take this thing over there
Why...?
Where are you trying to go?
Come on, I'm not scheming anything! Let's go
What are you--
- It's heavy
Let's just move it ov---
How could he fell for that?
Whaaat?!
"What" my ass, it was so obvious
So quick
- That can't be
It was crystal clear
Was it?
- Of course
Your act sucked the whole time, Matsuno
Yeah, I was like "it's here, isn't it"?
Miyazon eliminated after 7 in-game minutes
[4 people left]
Her acting was poor, but one person didn't notice it
And so, Miyazon drops out
I really had no idea
Defeated contestants monitoring space
How come everybody knew that?
As expected from Miyazon
They regain composure and start the barbecue
Back to the camp, they're getting the bbq ready
And then...
Everything ok in there?
Takashi alone leaves the cooking area
Takashi leaves the area alone
Oh, hey Takashi
He pays a visit to the eliminated Miyazon
He goes to see the eliminated Miyazon
I was worried about you so I came here
Why, thank you
You know, just that...
Miyazon is
looking for something
And while exchanging a casual conversation...
Look, a dog
Takashi takes something out from his backpack
A dog? Where?
Creepy...
Over there?
He just stole his booby-traps
I'm going to avenge you, Miyazon
Right?
Takashi!!
He's clever
See ya later
No way!
- He stole it
He's so dumb he didn't even realize it
He stole Miyazon's map
He successfully stole Miyazon's map
Miyazon
Miyazon's booby-traps: GET
And he managed to steal the holes
near the logs and in front of the dog house
Takashi-san... We can't start the fire
- Sorry
- Huh?
We really can't
- Not even a spark
Charcoal​ won't do it
- What do we need?
Some wood or something
- You think so?
A chance to lead them in towards the new area
Here comes his chance to lead them
towards the logs area trap
Current location
Miyazon
Whoa, he's evil
Oh, isn't that a firewood pile?
Logs
Miyazon's trap
It is
- You're right
Aren't those too much?
There's actual firewood!
Want me to go get them?
Yeah, please
Yaguchi is lead by Takashi to go get the logs
Tricked by Takashi, Yaguchi goes towards the logs
Miyazon's trap
She's stepping aside...
Grab some logs, will you?
- Please
Sure
- Looks safe enough...
Safe
She's safe
Maybe she sensed something,
But Yaguchi chose to grab the farthest ones,
instead of the closest ones
She grabs the farthest ones
Oh boy, I'm scared!
And in that moment...
- That's too much sauce...
Hey guys!
Huh?!
Good morning, folks!
It's your partner
Hi guys, do you have any trouble with anything?
- Nishimura, why are you...?
You... need help?
- What's going on?
Why is him here?
11:44 A.M. - Nishimura (Viking) enters the camp site
We have a guest acting as their camping teacher
It's Nishimura (Viking),
the comedian who loves camping the most!
Number 1 camping-loving comedian!
I didn't know that
What's with the military?
They're visiting us
It's nothing, don't worry about them
- Yeah, let them be
- Why is him here?
You ok with the fire?
Let me just...
What is that?!
- Stop it, we don't need this
I never saw that in my life!
- The hell is that?!
It's a fire breather
- What?!
Don't worry, we're good
- It's fine
It's lit
- Enough with that
It's lit, see?
He doesn't know anything
This man doesn't know anything, but they can use him
To make him go around to check suspicious spots
They can use him
to check suspicious areas
But they don't want him to fall into one of their own traps
He could fall into your own trap
A complex man
That's what Nishimura is: a complex being
Delicious!
- I told you!
- Very good!
It's good
What the hell is this? It's so thick.
It's my personal fork
- Tastes good
This is pretty good!
It's very good
Really, really good
Your fork is amazing!
The hell is he eatin'?!
12:38 P.M. - Free time
After the barbecue, they have some free time
They all decided to pick their favorite object
and playin the field
It's pretty wide around the dogs' spot
Maybe that area should do it, is there any other wide field?
You sure? Looks narrow to me
- It's not really the best spot
There are too many trees, they'll get in our way
Let's go over there that spot
But there are trees in there too
Are there? Really?
How about that place?
- Yeah, that spot is pretty wide
- Here?
Choosing the right place while suspecting each other
The four are trying to find the right spot,
while suspecting each other
Take an advantageous position
They want to lead them near to their traps' area
Overdo it, and you'll be exposed
But if they're too open about it, they might reveal their place
So they keep on questioning each other
- How about this spot? Pretty wide, huh?
Isn't this spot good?
Let's do it here, then
- Sure
Why are you all so hesitant to choose a spot...?
'Cause we want a wide spot
- That's it
This spot is good, let's play here
As a result of their debate,
which even Nishimura felt it was strange,
They chose a place near Kotohge's trap
Current location
Kotohge
Will Kotohge make the most out of this chance?
Wanna play some baseball?
- Oh, nice idea
I'll be the pitcher
The pitcher?
The pitcher
Who's the batter?
One of the girls?
Please, Matsuno, you go first
Alright, Yaguchi-chan, or anyone, it's fine
Sure
I'll guard the base
Isn't that a little suspect?
Over there, over there
I'll be the pitcher
Kotohge's trap
Right there, yeah
That should do it
Yaguchi is lead by Kotohge right in front of the trap
Yaguchi is lead by Kotohge right in front of his trap
Right in front of it
Can I? Shoot it back over there
Here I go
Here
Oh shoot
Sorry about that
Ah, so she has to go get it...
Kotohge's trap
Wait
We still have some balls here, it's fine
Don't worry
There's still more
Other balls?
Yeah, right here
Oh shit, sorry!
Kotohge's trap
You have more?
I don't
What just happened?!
He's clever
What's this?!
He's good
She totally fell for it
Oh?
You got me!
What are you doing?
You set it up so naturally!
He has no clue
What...
That was mine
Nishimura is so clueless!
Such a nice trap, well done
He's like "what's going on?"
Does that mean, you planned to make me the batter all along?
That's right, that's my hole after all
"My hole"?
What's "my hole"?
"My hole"...
His presence is such a burden!
Yaguchi eliminated after 1 hour and 35 minutes
[3 people left]
Yaguchi got caught up in Kotohge's plan and is eliminated
She completely disappeared
Kotohge is really good at this
The other three contestants and Nishimura
Current position
Miyazon
Yaguchi
Are close to the holes of the two eliminated
It's full of holes in there
This field is swarming with traps
Yaguchan can't take part in this anymore?
That's right
What's with this rule? Hahaha
Eh? No more baseball?
Yeah, that's it
After seeing Yaguchi in that state...
He still believes they're doing a camping episode
He still thinks this episode is about camping
Nishimura is a freak
Really...
Miyazon's trap
What's that? There's two of them, so cute!
He then proceeds to walk near a trap
Incredibly close to a trap
Wanna play frisbee? Or badminton?
"So cute", he said...
Let's play frisbee
Frisbee
- Sure
Let's go
I'm really good at frisbee
Is that so?
Throw it over there...
What the hell is going on...
Booby-traps are really fun!
He completely disappeared
Why is there a pitfall in here?
He hasn't realized it yet!
Come on!
Who was it?!
Hey, hey!
It's one of the staff
It can happen, alright
Who was it?!
Are you kidding me?
Makes sense
Who was it?
That's a tv show for you
It can happen
Who was it?!
The staff isn't immune to traps
A cameraman fell into a trap?
This is incredible
- Yeah...
A cameraman fell down?
Are you kidding me?
What the hell?
I'm amazed
We are in the middle of a trap rush
It's a rush, a rush
Why is there a pitfall in this place?
It's a booby-trap rush
All in the same place?
Is this "my hole"?
No, that's not your hole
But you said "my hole" before
Cameraman
Eliminated after 1 hour and 39 minutes:
Nishimura
[3 people left]
After Nishimura,
The cameraman is eliminated
The game isn't progressing at all
- It says "cameraman"
- A lot is going on
Only people unrelated to the game are falling down
It's a total mess
It's a complete mess
Oh my...
Now that Yaguchi and Miyazon are out...
We don't know where their holes are...
Right...
I used both my holes, I don't have any more
- We don't know
staff) Maybe you shouldn't have say that aloud...
-He's right
- Exactly
- Right
Kotohge ended up revealing he ran out of holes
Kotohge revealed he doesn't have holes anymore
Nishimura may be an idiot,
But so is Kotohge
By the way, Matsuno is an idiot too
- Come on...
And the same goes for Miyazon
Come on!
Matsuno hasn't accomplished anything yet!
I shouldn't have said it when Yaguchi fell down my trap
A man without any holes is going somewhere...
The place where this man who lost all his holes is going to...
I'm sneaking into Yaguchi's bag, it feels exciting
Makes sense
Yaguchi's map: GET
And so, he steals Yaguchi's map from her bag
That's a basic move
Now he's got some holes
Miyazon
Yaguchi
One of them is the one Nishimura fell in
Yaguchi's booby-trap: GET
But he got the other one inside the tent, he's got a chance
And his plan is the following...
His trump card: baseball plan
It's his trump card again: playing baseball
Again?
He aims for a strike-and-miss by Matsuno to lead her inside the tent
He wants Matsuno to miss the ball,
so he can lead her inside the tent
However...
Here goes!
Whoa! Nice!
That was incredible!
That was impressive!
She hit it perfectly and sent it back
She striked it back at him
Well, she's an athlete after all
And not only once...
She's incredible!
Why are you hitting it?
"Why are you hitting it"?
Matsuno shows an unexpected talent
An incredible baseball talent
That's something
But...
Where is it?
It went inside
Oh shi-
No you didn't!
Come on!
Oh man!
Come on!!
You should have expected it
Hey you! Come on!
The hell is this?!
Matsuno eliminated after 2 hour and 8 minutes
[2 people left]
With Matsuno gone,
From now on is a 1-vs-1 match between Kotohge and Takashi
Come on!
I know for sure you don't have any more traps
I'm not sure about that
There are only Miyazon and Matsuno's trap, 1 of each
And Matsuno, yeah
And two of mine
You have two of them?!
That's right
You still have two?!
Yep
Cookhouse
Kotohge
Matsuno
Miyazon
Takashi
Yaguchi
With this, if we exclude Matsuno's trap
Everyone
knows
about
this one
which everyone got right at the beginning, there are only 3 traps left
Kotohge doesn't have his traps anymore
But he wants to know where Miyazon's trap is
Miyazon
I can still get Miyazon's trap
But actually, that trap too
He knows where it is
Is controlled by Takashi, who got it at the beginning,
so it's actually 3 vs 0 traps
Kotohge's situation is tragic, but...
Kotohge's situation is desperate
What will happen?
Here
Oh, thank you
You poured that much?
You ever saw anyone drinking that much tea before?
Well, we moved a lot...
Now that it's 1 vs 1, there's not much action
It's hard to have some action now that they're only two
And so, this situation of stall goes on
What are they going to do?
What the? What if they don't do anything?
It's gonna get dark!
2:46 P.M. - 3 hours and 30 minutes since the game started
I have no clue where your traps are...
It's gonna take a while
They examine each other's movements
Exploring the field while checking each other out
While they go around to explore some more
But then...
I'm making a quick toilet break
Really, I gotta go
Kotohge moves towards the toilet
Kotohge is going where the toilet is
This is scary...
This place is fine, no wonder
Yeah it's fine, thankfully
That one's out of order
Hey, you can't use that, it's out of order
- That's so suspicious
- Sounds fishy
Hey, you can't use that, it's out of order
But it says it's out of order...
Unbelievable!
He did it!
I see, so Takashi knew it...
Of course he did
Huh? Kotohge?
No way!
I've waited all the time for you to pee!
That's why I poured you that much tea!
Now I understand!
It makes sense
I told you we should get a break for that
Also, I'm the one who wrote "out of order"
Eh?! This guy...
I had no idea!
"Out of order"
Are you kidding me?!
Honestly, I was ready to wait up to two hours
Man...
That's impressive...
Game over
Time: P.M. 2:53
Winner: Takashi
He's so sly!
Really
I see
And that was it
I still don't get what's the point of Nishimura
Really, what's his deal?
They said they could "use him somehow"
But he fell down so quickly, so...
Even the cameraman
Yeah, that's true
I've never seen someone from the staff falling down a booby-trap
Yeah, me neither
What do you think about it, YOU?
- Well...
After the first half, it kind of... well, sucked
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
fB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TRANSLATION BY SHION
TYPESET BY SHION & KEDOMAS
EDIT & QC BY KEDOMAS
He walked away quicker than I expected
Yeah, I thought he would have been slower