Timers: IngloriousBee, ShiratoHaki, Riddell, Phantom Translators: Natsume, Hikarii, Royaltree, Jump4r, Zebestt, Xueshi
m 0 0  l 1800 0  1800 140  0 140
WDT Project
Welcome to Wednesday Downtown everybody!
This is our first person, please enter !
Please welcome Kazuhiro Ozawa !
Happy to be here
This time, I have a theory, but
before it, please take a look at this.
This T-shirt..
Do you know what kind of T-shirt it is?
What kind?
It's Clash right?
"The Clash" is a band
A band right?
A band from London right?
One of London's three biggest punk bands, "The Clash"
I really like these "The Clash" band T-shirts.
One day, one of my juniors was wearing a Clash T-shirt,
I was really happy.
I asked him "Do you like Joe Strummer? Have you heard of him?"
He was a member right?
Then,
And then he asked me : "Who is Joe Strummer?"
Joe Strummer is the vocalist of The Clash.
The main?
Indeed
It's like someone wearing a Downtown T-shirt without knowing who Matsumoto is.
Oh I see
I don't know whether there is a Downtown T shirt or not
For example yeah
So for kids who are out of order
I brought today the theory that will strike the final blow on them
Please
Asking people wearing band T shirt in town if they know the intro song of the band and if they can not answer, the T-shirt is confiscated and they can't complain.
I see
Although it is strict, it's not that I don't understand it
So like "You know about them?"
Exactly
Let's wear a Downtown t-shirt and do a kidnapping joke material quiz !
But, there is no Downtown T shirt !
Really ?
After this, people in the street wearing band T shirts taking the intro quiz
Moreover,
The older you get, the shorter a day seems (Theory)
Get out of the room after exactly 24 hours
Why some people wear sunglasses in the middle of the night
The question of the fear of the number 4 in Japan's buildings
Verifying the theory of people wearing band T shirt in town and if you can not answer the band's intro quiz
the T-shirt is confiscated and you can't complain.
Therefore, starting the investigation.
Then, immediately
Nirvana T-shirt discovered
Because of the charisma
I don't know about that
Excuse me
It's for TBS television
We would like to do an interview
Yes
Is it ok if we ask you one or two questions?
Sure
Here is the question :
What is the title of this song ?
It's the most famous one
He doesn't know at all
It just started though
Maybe he doesn't know about Nirvana
Does he know it or not?
Answer !
No, I don't know it
This is like doing "Linda Linda" by Blue Hearts
Oh really?
You don't know at all?
I really don't know
What do you know about the T-shirt you are wearing ?
Oh this one?
Nirabana
Hm? One more time
He doesn't even know Nirvana
I bought it because of the design and cause a lot of hip-hop artists seem to wear it
And now, explaining the project
It's a bit embarrassing, isn't it ? Hahaha
It is of no use to confiscate it
We felt sorry for him being embarrassed so we exempt him
Nirabana
And then,
Nirvana's Vocalist Kurt Cobain T-shirt
With that said...
I don't know at all
I don't know
I really don't know
You don't know at all?
Another fail
Who ? Whose is this song?
Whose is this song?
Could you please turn around?
Eh, is this person singing?
This one ? Is the singer this person?
Eh, so this it?
This is wrong
So I was wearing it without knowing
People from the countryside who don't know Kurt Cobain
Where did you buy it?
At the local Uniqlo
And you don't know what kind of person he is?
I have no clue
Yes, from now on I'll remember it
With this, I'll remember
And then,
Guns N' Roses
I know this name
You should know it
Have you heard this before?
No, I haven't
So why are ya wearing it?
Is it Guns?
Guns N' Roses
I know the name, but
I have never heard the song itself.
Because this is from a brand I like
that's the only reason I bought it
It's not because I especially like Guns N Roses
I see
Next one is..
Iron Maiden
You know a lot of them
It's because I like Hard Rock
Really?
Yeah it's true
I don't know
Is it famous?
It is.
John Lennon
For that kind of high tempo?
Seriously
It seems unexpected
Even though a lot of people are wearing band t-shirt
Someone who knows the song doesn't show up
Among them
This time, an artist from Japan : E.YAZAWA
If you don't know this
If you're not a fan, you don't wear it
After this, we are going to Diamond Moon
the shop.
Parent and child go to a E.YAZAWA specialist shop.
Even the kid's cap is E.YAZAWA
They are expected to be able to answer
For sure
It is also the most famous one
Even I could answer
Did you get it ?
Intro..
I don't know.
Unexpected incorrect answer
The title is [Don't stop, Ha Ha]
Aaa
Now that you said it
I don't really listen to this one
Next one is
Rolling Stones T-shirt
Please give the title
Correct
Do you like it?
I really like it, please look at this
Discovery of a true fan wearing a band T-shirt.
Furthermore,
It's Guns
The Shanananani~ song
Rock'n Roll Radio
I know it
This is from Metallica, Enter Sandman
From the album Jazz, Bicycle Race
As expected, real fans give correct answers immediately
Only 5 people gave the correct answer
Red Hot Chili Peppers ?
Gins..
Guns
Looks like "Guns Nose"
Guns...
Guns N' Rosie
It's Guns N' Roses !
Guns N' Roses
This guy? That's his?
I forgot...
Only people who do not even know the artist, the band or the song.
Intro Correct Rate, 5 / 51 [10%]
Then, there is no longer band T-shirts, but
How about T-shirts often seen in town ?
Che Guevara
There are a lot
Was there ever a time where you groveled in front of someone?
Probably not
This time we conduct a separate interview
involving those wearing Che Guevara T-shirts
Maybe then I would have done dogeza
The following day, we asked them to come into the studio wearing the same clothes.
He's looks so wary
It is pretty suspicious
Please have a seat
Wow
excuse me...
Gotta be uncomfortable.
It's scary, huh?
Scary, isn't it?
A Guevara T-shirt...
Incredible
Same shirt again
There's a lot on that one
Same shirt.
It's a colorful one
It appears they realize they're all wearing Che Guevara.
With that said, what awaits the unsuspecting four
is a Guevara Quiz which starts now
If they like him they should be able to answer
They should
Let's start with the first question
What is the name of the person who is pictured on everyone's T-shirt?
That's obvious
There might be some weird ones
Some might've bought it for the design
Everyone, please reveal your answers on the board
All right, we have them all
Well then
"GEvera?"
Hirose, could you please read your answer to us?
GEvera is kind of...
Chu Gevera
Once more please
Of course, the correct answer is...
Che Guevara
Che Guevara (duh)
It's Che Guevara
Che Guevara
It's hard to pronounce, heh
The pronunciation?
Don't you think so?
He said it
Can I just go home?
You can't yet
But I reaaally want to go home
We continued on with the Guevara Quiz.
"Can I go home"?
This guy is impossible!
And so the results are as follows
- Argentina
(Where was Che Guevara born?)
- Bolivia
(Where was his place of death?)
That's impressive
- Cigar
(What is Che Guevara's favorite item on the battlefield that was also used as insect repellent?)
- Nikon
(What brand is Che Guevara's favorite camera?)
All correct!
Unbelievable
Having answered all questions regarding Che Guevara correctly, he attains victory
Dang, he the real deal
I'm incredibly happy
Lastly, Hirose
Yeah......
What are your thoughts on today's quiz?
I'll never wear this T-shirt again in my life
Hmph
With that said, it is advisable to know what is written/drawn on your own T-shirt
I see
Wow
Those were the results, but...
it seems like the older people wore it because they liked it and the younger people wore it for fashion.
It was sad for that kid. He won't be able to wear that.
"GE-GEvera"
- Guevera isn't it?
In exchange, the show should've given him a t-shirt.
Maybe a Wednesday Downtown t-shirt.
Oh, right. Something like that.
Want to make one?
A Wednesday Downtown T-shirt
Except this show could end at any time and it wouldn't be surprising.
I don't want it to end.
Is that so?
On the edge
So unstable
Let's move onto the next presenter - this person!
Please welcome Viking's Kotoge!
Are you a senior citizen?
No, not at all!
You're mistaken.
I'm wrong?
You asked so kindly.
Are you young?
I'm young, I'm young, yes.
You forgot your bolo tie.
Nah, I'm not old-- I'm not an old man!
Not an old man?
- A bolo tie is an old man's accessory.
Right now I'm 40. I don't wear bolo ties.
Isn't 40 kind of an old man?
40 isn't really. It's middle-aged.
How old are you Matsumoto-san?
I'm 52
THAT'S OLD!!
You're an old fart!!
Well, yeah. I'm an old man ain't I!
Exactly!
Among this group, you two are closest to death.
What the hell are you saying
We're like right there
That's right. You guys already have one foot in the grave.
And so, as you get older haven't you thought "The days are getting shorter!"
It is fast!
Isn't it?
Definitely
It flies by
This is what the older generations say so
this time what I have to present is this!
Theory : The older you get the shorter a day feels
This is totally the case
That's hard to measure, isn't it?
Exactly, that's why this time, in order to do so
We had various entertainers go into prefab rooms, where they couldn't see outside...
and asked them to come out in exactly 24 hours!
Based on their own timing!
Is that possible?
With no signs of time.
Like, "I think it's been around 24 hours..." is what...
There's nothing, right?
There's nothing.
No windows.
And when they come out, they should come out starting with the oldest....is the theory.
I see
The older you get, the shorter the days feel theory test commences.
With that said, this time we have boxes where one cannot see outside.
We'll have 4 entertainers, from different age groups, enter...
and instruct them to come out when they think 24 hours have passed.
If this theory holds true, they should come out starting with the oldest.
The participants were non-busy entertainers whose schedules were open for 24 hours.
Don't say "non-busy".
First is...
representing 20s, Zawachin.
I didn't know.
20s.
Next, representing 60s, is...
Lou Oshiba.
And since our oldest participant is to be in their 80s...
80s?
and since many entertainers in their 80s are superstars...
Yeah, that's true.
We had this person come.
Who?
Assisted us in our 10x Quiz, extra, Yoshiyuki Yamada-san.
This is also called a knee.
Since the participant representing 40s was late...
Where could he be?
the three go ahead and standby in their rooms.
What's with the 40 y/o being late?
Aah~ I'm worried.
What's up with that?
First, I'm going to change.
Oh they have a fridge.
Yes, yes, it's furnished inside.
Since tonight is just an observation of time. Bringing in personal items is allowed.
Meals can also be eaten at any time they want.
That makes sense.
Coming in 10 minutes after the three.
There he is.
Really?
So it's this guy.
Turning 40 this year, Yasuda Dai Circus' Kuro-chan.
There he is.
He only appears on these things.
As usual, only Kuro-chan isn't explained anything.
Man, this guy's so easy.
For real, so easy!
With everyone gathered now. At 0:00AM the test starts.
He's the easiest the get.
So...now that it's started...
because there's no clock...
to gain an idea of what time it is...
drawing a picture is good.
Ahh~ what should I do~
Not used to not having a phone.
It's gotta be boring.
Well, it would be boring.
Right, no smartphone.
No TV, either.
Can't play with your phone.
A ukiyo-e book.
He went for his ukiyo-e book first.
Since everyone brought in personal items, they start killing time, except...
Kuro-chan, who knows nothing.
Tell him!
He doesn't even know if he can take off the mask.
A room!
Well, you're not wrong.
Is there a simpler answer?
Eh? What is this?
He doesn't know anything.
Rule?
This is where finds out.
Leave this room in exactly 24 hours.
What do you mean? What do you mean?
That would happen.
What do you mean by "exactly"?
I can't tell what time it is!
Looks to be a little agitated...
Are you testing how good a human's internal clock is?
With his instincts, he roughly figures out the experiment.
You catch on quick!
He was looking directly into the camera.
What's with this guy?
It is now, 1:00AM. An hour since the start of the test.
"Is that all?"
Slee~py
Probably 30 minutes have gone by.
40 minutes, 30 minutes.
Now, since the start...
it feels like an hour or so has gone by. Lemme jot it down.
I don't think it's been 2 hours yet.
Maybe 1 hour has gone by though.
You're not even looking at your ukiyo-e book.
It's been about one hu-h
One hour...
Stop smacking your lips
I think about one hour has passed,
Let's make a mark.
So that's how he's gonna do it
So far, everyone is still accurate in their timing.
Smart
Still a long time left
2 AM, 2 hours since the start
True
How will they tell time when they're sleeping?
What time is it?
I wanna play with my phone
The struggles of youth
maybe 2.5 - 3 hours have passed
Well, it's time to turn in.
Why are you drinking?
Tomorrow I'll wake up at around 6 or 7 AM.
Because my body is used to that right now.
If he sticks to his usual routine
Believing that his body knows when to wake up
It'll be easy to tell
Lou retires.
Hmmm
I see
And then
80 year old Yamada retires.
Beer as well?
Yeah, I'm a little worried.
The way he put his hands...
oh, double ones
What the hell is he doing?
Current time is 3 AM
Everyone's probably asleep now.
It's probably just me still up
Is he dead?
Dude there's a futon
No, I didn't mean "ehh"
I was dreaming
I was dreaming just now
Even though I wasn't sleeping
Disgusting, sleep-talking
That's scary
If I sleep, I probably won't remember what time it is.
Scary
However...
What a disgusting sound.
This guy is filthy
At 4:00, losing to his drowsiness, Kuro retires.
Afterwards, Zawachin also retires.
4 hours since the beginning
Everyone has fallen asleep, but the clock still continues.
The first to awaken is...
Lou Ooshiba
I think it's sometime between 8 and 9
His internal clock is probably off after getting up
Let's go with 8:30
Lou currently thinks it's 8:30
but it's actually only 6:00
I see
Here we have a substantial time difference.
Our next contestant to wake up is...
Zawachin
It's maybe 12:00? Let's write that down.
No way you slept that long
But actually, it's still only 8:00
Does the human internal clock misalign once we go to sleep?
However, what about the most apprehensive Kuro
What a weird way to get up
9:00
Maybe 9:30?
Somehow, he got the time just right.
Isn't that amazing?
Only 2 minutes off!
Hella correct!
He's really taking it easy
Isn't that bad?
At this time, everyone passes time in their own way
I'm getting a bit anxious
Yeah same
the 4 members waiting for the 24 hours to pass.
Oh it's nice they have a TV
What the hell is he doing?
3-4-5
What's so interesting about that?
What's the principle here?
4-4-5
That's so scary
This is bad
Is he ok? still alive?
The first person to come out is...
Eh.. Someone's already out?
Isn't he early?
What? It's the 60's Lou Ooshiba
Yeah he's early
And with that, unfortunately, the theory has been proven false.
I just thought that now would be a good time
The resulting time is...
2:00 PM?
An amazing 9 hours short
An amazing feat
Am I first?
I see
I think my stubble was getting to a good point
So I thought maybe 24 hours had passed.
Oh my god right, yup
Amazing
And then, 10 minutes later.
Who? Ah Zawachin
What? Zawachin also leaves her room.
15 hours?
How unfortunate
Only 15 hours have passed?
That's scary
really scary
Wild
I get that feeling
Our remaining members are 40's representative Kuro
1-2-3
And 80's representative Yamada
Is Yamada OK?
He seriously might be dead
Which will leave closer to 24 hours?
Is this really about the internal clock?
Is there something after this?
Right, he doesn't know about this?
After this is the main part?
We've tricked him too much
That's true
They really won't answer me
Kuro is anxious without knowing the full story
Oh he's alive
He sleeps alot
Sleeping for 9 hours, Yamada gets up at 11:00 AM
Passing time by tracing Ukiyo-e art
That's a tasteful way to kill time
And afterwards goes to sleep again
I really don't get it
What is this? Tell me!
I have no info!
How scary
He's only had himself until now right
No way he can laugh in that room
Both parties continue to kill time...
Then..
Ok, goodbye, it has been exactly
24 hours. I'm leaving in accordance to the rules!
I'm leaving!
I left!
Shouldn't Yamada hear that?
Kuro decides to leave first
It's because he doesn't understand anything
The resulting time is...
Nicely done
Does this mean I'm wrong?
Without context, his reaction is pretty weak.
With a error within 46 minutes, an amazing record
Eh, what's going  on here?
Like seriously what is this?
We're finished here.
No, I don't understand
I really don't
And finally, the last to come out
I'm glad he's still alive
80's representative, Yamada
Wow that's amazing
The resulting time is?
35 hours?
An incredible 11 hours over!
Amazing
You've gotta be kidding
Wow...
This is incredible
The poor staff members
I actually thought I was still early...
Right...
With that, it turns out that the speed at which a day passes has nothing to do with age.
I see, they're unrelated...
But the fact that Kuro had no information and was still the most accurate is amazing.
Very true
Kuro-chan's trust was just amazing
But he's lost his trust in people
Right
The people who did that was "Wednesday Downtown" though
That's true
Mhmm
I think Zawachin would have had a different result if she had her phone.
I have the feeling that she would have been more accurate if she were playing with her phone.
But a phone is essentially a clock so...
That's true...
What are you talking about
Sorry, my bad
Ah, wait, is there something in your ear?
Ear monitor?
Maybe from... Daikichi!
She has some backup with her retorts
That makes me a bit worried
Moving on, we're introducing theories from around the world in "Everyone's Theory" corner.
Tonight's presenter is...
Koyabu Kazutoyo
Thanks for having me
Chairman
Thanks
The bags under your eyes are fricking crazy today
I was free yesterday, that might be it
I didn't do jack yesterday
Let's move on to the theory I've brought for you today. Here it is!
Theory: The people who wear giant sunglasses at night can't have a valid reason other than being a superstar
Aw that's a bit...
There are alot of normal people who do that
Yes there are
If it were midday, you'd have plenty of reasons like UV rays or protecting your eyes in general
That I can get
They're called SUN glasses
They're for the SUN
At night there's NO SUN
Sunglasses at night feels a bit, you know...
Superstars putting giant ones on to not get recognised, that I get as well, but...
...when you're not even a superstar...
...and the sun isn't even out...
...wearing these giant, dark sunglasses...
...why the hell are you walking around like that at night?!
We thought there were people who thought this way...
Motoki-san were there people wearing sunglasses at night at the baseball stadium?
There aren't really no...
There are people who put on paint under their eyes though...
That's for a day game
And that's also me right now too...
After this, a search for sunglasses at night
We're investigating the theory that The people who wear giant sunglasses at night can't have a valid reason other than being a superstar
That means a search for sunglasses at night in the city
And then...
There definitely are some
We've found someone...
...who even has the vibe of a celebrity
Sorry
We're from TBS Television
...this might be rude but are you in showbiz by any chance?
Yes I am, got found out...
Somehow, she actually was famous
However...
Are you a model?
(Note : OL stands for office-lady, which basically means she does office work)
I'm an OL*
Oh you're an OL...
It was just a joke...
The hell is this girl!?
You're wearing sunglasses even though it's night out so we thought you might be famous...
Oh gawd I hate that. This was about me? Not him?
That's like uh the worst
By the way why are you wearing sunglasses?
I haven't got makeup on
To hide your no makeup face
Next we have this person
We thought you might be famous so...
That's completely wrong though...
By the way why are you wearing sunglasses even though it's night out?
There's a rumour going around that if you see my eyes you get pregnant
Theory : If you see my eyes, you'll get pregnant
There's no reason to write that out!
You're always wearing them?
Always always yes...
Even inside my house...
...Since everybody'll get pregnant...
...I can't take that responsibility
It was new kind of dad joke
It's for fashion right?
Next...
Are you in showbiz?
No I'm not no...
Why are you wearing sunglasses at night?
This guy's funny as hell!
Why I wonder? For my getup you know...
It's a side-job right?
Yep
A side-job?
I'm a host
He was a host that's in a band during the day
And also...
We both have regular customers so...
...if we're found out it'll affect our income
And it's okay to put you on TV?
After that, we talked with alot of people with sunglasses...
...we couldn't even meet a cheap artist, let alone superstars
However,
Is it possible that you're in the entertainment business?
I'm not, but am I not kinda though?
I'm a rapper
Your name?
I go by "Chanmina"
Actually this lady, was part of a show that Koyabu was the MC of...
She started out as a high-school rapper...
...she's known with the youngsters
Why are you wearing sunglasses at night?
I get secretly filmed alot like...
..."Chanmina was there" and stuff
There was a time where my eyes looked really ugly
It's because of that, yeah
It wasn't about fans recognizing her and being annoying
It's about not being filmed ugly
Also, this woman too
I rap, yeah
It was Fuziko-san,
from a group called "S7ick chicks" (Slick Chicks)
I have work with an entertainer tomorrow
It's dissing an entertainer
Female rappers all wear sunglasses at night, we got that but...
We haven't met a single superstar
It's TBS TV but...
Are you an entertainer?
Uhm, why? Am I?
You're not in showbiz?
I'm not an entertainer
What's the instrument inside the box?
It's a tenor saxophone
So you're a sax player
Yeah I am
Have you put out any CDs or something similar?
Of course
How many was it?
About 14 of them
I'm very sorry for my rudeness
Actually, this person was given the "Japan Jazz Award"...
...The tenor sax player Imazu Masato
So you were kind of a superstar in the Jazz world?
No, that's a long time ago though
It was 1989
After that,
We're from TBS TV but,
Is it possible that you're in entertainment?
Oh me?
I'm not really in the industry, but I do "entertain"
This is a Saijou Hideki impersonator...
...called Vermont Hideki
Here I have make up but, uhm...
*Note : Kanpeki means perfect
...it's like "Hideki Kanpekii*"
Did that just fail?
If that gag has failed, I go...
*Note : Sangeki - Fail/Tragedy
..."Hideki Sangekii*"
If I'm being called to try more I do...
He turns his switch on really quickly
You don't have to say "sudden"
And the next person we've approached is...
This woman wearing the biggest sunglasses we've encountered today
Are you in showbiz?
Yes I am
Your name?
Vanilla
I'm a plastic surgery model
This investigation has shown that,
Actually alot of entertainers appear to wear sunglasses at night
And even within those...
Excuse me
We're from TBS TV but...
Okay
...is it possible that you're a famous person?
No that's not true, you're not from TBS are you?
No no no
No way you're from TBS
Um, it's TBS TV
What are you doing here??
I'm scared...
We're asking people wearing sunglasses at night if-
I'm not in entertainment as per se...
But I do do theater on stage
Since I'm a singer
I sing songs yeah
You're not in the entertainment business but
I'm not darling no, I'm an artist
A-HHAHA oh ho
Cuz' that's different, isn't it?
She was not a beekeeper, but a singer
Nobody said anything about a beekeeper though
She was really giving off a star-vibe but
Have we met a real superstar?
Darling is this...
Darling this isn't filming now is it?
That's no good, I'm, you know, on...
...I do work with Yamamoto Linda and others so...
...I can't have my face shown
However, it was OK to put it in a brochure...
...for publicity for an upcoming concert
Stop that
Like this..
...We've seen it somewhere before zamasu.
The person who said "Zamasu" right..
Right?
By the way this lady is a chanson singer called Shimazu Tomoko
A genuine singer
Come over to the Mitsukoshi Theater, darling,
On the 18th
Uh ha ha ha - I'm completely not though...
By the way, usually
Do you use the word "zamasu"?
I do say "zamasu" yes
But if my husband saw-
With that, We found a "New zamasu" unexpectedly
Where the hell did we land at?
It's completely wrong
What happened here?
The worst thing about this show
You're looking for sunglasses at the start
And in the end you've found new "zamasu"
Why the hell would I care about that?!
Cut that out!
Isn't this a little too full of itself?
Too full?
Even in stores,
Placing the name of the owner as the store name
the owner will most likely be too full of themselves
Yeah,that does happen
The expression that they get too full of themselves is a bit
Cheerful and jovial types too
Those that come forward
Unexpectedly are my hated types
Continuing this, I would like to present my theory. \nThis time the theory I brought is:
Theory : 'In Japanese buildings, the number '4' is overly cared for'
How about it? Isn't it time for someone to call upon this?
Uwahh, its the number '4'
Like house numbers
Right
Room numbers like '444'
Sometimes room numbers like '104' are missing in Japanese condos
That does exist
But for baseball players, '4' might be given to a player
'4' might be given to a player
But the number '42' is hated by everyone
42 =  (Death)
But there are foreigners as well
Well, for foreigners
Jacky Robinson took the number '42'
and wore the same jacket
Where everyone took on the same jersey
as Jacky Robinson such cases do exist
Itou-san, what are your thoughts about '4'?
I like the number '4' the most
the number?
Whereas on the other hand, everyone else
kinda of hated it, therefore wanting to be unique, I liked the number '4'
Intentionally
Uwah, here comes death, Don't you consider that?
I think of it as shiawase(Happiness) Shi ('4') in that case
Ehhh,1,2,3
'4'
She's really fourth
Great luck
is that right?
'In Japanese buildings, the number '4' is overly cared for' Theory
Lets begin with hospitals which detest the imagery of death
At this Aichi Medical University Hospital
Fourth level's 42
Cutting out only the '42' room
The connotation of '42' and death
is what we are trying to actively avoid
It's a common occurrence in hospitals to remove the room '42'
However at Hitachi Medical Center,
We go by 401,402,403,skipping 404 , next is 405
For entire floors,the room number '4' does not appear
Furthermore,
Even in the medical examination rooms,the number '4' is avoided
Inspection rooms too are removed from the number '4'
X-rays rooms too are distanced away from '4'
Wow, they really thoroughly removed '4's
Changing rooms which are unrelated are also not spared too
'4' has been purged
Wow, that's a really complete deletion of '4'
That was a hospital which was thoroughly aware and considerate of  the effects of '4'
Next up, at the kisshoCAREN Inn
'4' too is something they are overly concerned with
Rooms ending with '4' are disposed of without a doubt
The entire 4th floor
has been removed from the plane of existence
Was there supposed to have a 4th floor?
Even in the elevator, the number '4' is missing
The floor number right after 3 is not '4' but 5
Even in the employee only elevator and locker room
there is no number '4'
In the entire building, there is no trace left of '4'
When they overdo it like this, it brings attention to the fact, there is no '4' around
An Inn which is totally frightened by the numeric '4'
Following that, In miyako-jima
A condo which is overly concerned with '4'
5th floor over here we call it 5th floor instead
Doors closing
There is only 5
Yeah there is only 5th floor
Announcer: This is the 4th floor
Wait up, wait up, one moment please
On top the number is displayed as '4' but below
where the buttons are displayed, it is '5' instead
He has pressed the 5th floor but,
Announcer: This is the 4th floor
The announcer is saying that it is the 4th floor
ending in a nonsensical mess
so which is which?
The person might think not yet and not get off the lift
For example
here's the key to 503 and hands it off to them
And when they go up, they will definitely hear that this is the 4th floor from the announcer
Then where exactly is the 5th floor?Above this?
Over here, we have more upper levels
The announcer says [This is the 5th floor]
Confusing
Overly complicated
Due to budget constraints, we were only able to do it to that extent
On to Car plate numbers
Taking into consideration of the whole nation
As long as you don't deliberately apply
The above two numbers will not be chosen for your carplate number
This has already been decided by the Ministry of Land, Infrastructure and transport
Just because of the connection to the number 4
Even when we take a look overseas
China similar to Japan, the number 4 sounds exactly the same as the character death
Having the same pronunciation in China, the number '4' is also shunned upon
In this Chinese style Las Vegas hotel,
The floors 40 ~ 49 are gone
Whereas in the west, '13' is considered to be unlucky and eschewed
Similarly the practice of omission of '4' inauspicious digits in Japan, the number 13 is avoided in certain buildings
Up to now, we have shown many places in Japan which put up great efforts to escape '4'
However..
There exist certain industries which purposely utilise '4'
I can understand the sentiments behind preserving this part of Japanese heritage too but..
Don't you think we have been going overboard?
There exist certain industries which purposely utilise '4'
and They are Funeral services companies
Centrally located in the Chiba prefecture, 54 funeral services owned by this certain company
Their telephone numbers all end with '4444'
We can easily imagine the number '4' with the kanji
Furthermore, the pioneer of this '4444' trend is
Continuing the trade since Edo period, this 8th generation funeral service company president
Simply put, its the most efficient way to invoke connections with death
In morgues which don't have telephone directories, to make it easy for people to look up, '4444' was used
Since I was small, I helped out my family business and eventually inherited it
There is really no interesting tidbit or story behind it
just a way of how to win over our competitors and get our pay from their inheritance tax
There exists funeral services ending with 4242 extension as well
Is that so...
Those are indeed the points to be taken into consideration
When you think about the phrase 'shi ni', isn't it weird?
I can understand their apprehension if it is 'shi nu' (To die)
Isn't 'shi ni' just half-hearted in terms of expression? (To death)
So how do y'all feel?
Kind of like shinimasen (Won't die)
Indeed now that you pointed it out
Check out our Facebook and Website for more Wednesday Downtown! This video was subbed by a community run project called the Wednesday Downtown project. Thanks for watching!
m 0 0  l 1800 0  1800 158  0 158
In our next episode we attempt the bunt homerun
Against a pitching machine at 300km/h
Theory :'On SNS, the one determined to be cuter is the one who uses it as the profile picture'
To show the best version of myself
Slowly drawing the details
Furthermore
Can you play the telephone game using different genres?
We have a quiz for Nagano on Christian Riese Lassen
I have memories of seeing this piece of art before
Who best understands their working tool?
This is my best partner