Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Ok ok, i've been paid so i'll be serious
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Bakarhythm!
Hello everyone, i'm Bakarhythm
I'll get right to the point
Currently in the variety industry there are many comedy contests
Such as "M-1", "R-1", "King of Conte", "THE W"
They are usually classified into types of segment, number of people, gender etc
This time I bring a new type of competition
Are there any others that can be done?
It is this
30-1 Competition
This is a competition for short segments of 30 seconds or less
-So short
As long as it is less than 30 seconds, any type of segment is fine
Its not classified by type but instead time
A new perspective
I hope we can hold it every year from now on
If the winner becomes popular after the championship, this may really happen in the future
Has anyone become famous from Wednesday Downtown?
Isn't there that dog thing?
Mameshiba something, right?
Yes, yes.
-Please remember it properly
Apparently Downtown is doing well from this show
Is that what you think?
So, from the 656 groups that signed up
40 groups were strictly selected to participate in the official competition
The official competition is divided into 5 groups performing segments through video
The five winning teams from each group will enter the final
These five distinguished guests, led by Hitoshi Matsumoto, are the judges
Who will be able to become the king of the first generation of the 30-1 competition?
30-1 Grand Prix starts first with the A group
1st is Chocolate Planet
They are coming to participate too!?
Thirty-sixth
All Japan Powerlifting Championships North Kanto Preliminary
m 0 0 l 0 177 l 995 177 l 995 0
It's okay, it's okay. You can do it. Be confident
Go on, go on
Let everyone see the results of your training
Go, go, go!
Good good
Lift it! Lift it!
Try again next year
-Yes!
Oh come on!
Be serious
I didn't expect them to do such a standard one
2nd is PlusMinus' Iwahashi
Can't do Do Re Mi song
♪Do is swallowing acorns
♪Re Is scratching a Lexus
※Mixi: Japan's once popular social networking site is now in decline
♪Mi is time to start playing Mixi
♪Fa is getting flesh caught in the zipper
♪So is messily spreading mincemeat
♪Ra is dressing naked people
♪Si is kicking a deer
♪Let's all sing together
3rd is Double Art
Ah, it's Mi! It's definitely Mi!
Wow, I'm so excited to seem them in a place like this!
I wonder if I can go up and say hello
I might not have another chance, I better say hello
Excuse me, can I shake your hand?
I'm sorry. Thank you
So, are you Mi?
I am Fa
-How are you Fa?
A one-joke one
4th is WesP
From now on, I will use this shirt to become a bunny girl
Music start
Good expression
I can't understand this guy's expression
5th is Nelsons
Very famous
Really? What a great lineup
You dog is so cute!
-Thanks
Wow your dog is very cute it
-Thank you
Let it come and play with mine
Sir, your dog isn't here
When did it happen?
-I don't know
When did it disappear?
Why didn't you notice?
Because I'm an idiot
Did you leave it at home?
My partner is at home, let me ask
Hello? Yeah, that's great. Bye then
That's great.
-Is everything ok?
Tonight is hamburger!
That doesn't matter at all!
Bye!
Great!
A proper skit!
Lots of parts to it
6th is Westland
A man who can use qigong
I participated in swimming training classes as a child
But my speed was really not fast enough so I gave up after a while
I started playing soccer again instead
I played pretty well at first
Event dream of entering the J League and going overseas to participate in the World Cup and so on
This guy is awesome!
It was an honor to work with my teammates
Great nose
Now there are more and more children who do not exercise much
Please make sure they take part in sports and sweat a lot
Thank you
It's so hard to choose!
7th is Nana Magari
You
Want to buy this for 20,000?
What is this?
This is a fictional dirty joke: GINMO
GINMO, what is this fictional thing?
How is it? Isn't it very colorful?
I don't know
Come on, buy it.
-I don't want it
You won't lose out.
-I said no!
Wait a minute...
This guy... is married!?
8th is Kimura Family
The Kimura family decided on tonight's meal
Tomatoes, scallops, and red peppers
Italian fish and shellfish risotto tonight
What is this?
First of all, these eight from group A
Pretty good group
Oh, by the way, Bakarhythm will also participate in the decision-making process
1 2 3 4 5 people will participate
We do to?
-Yes
Do we have to choose?
That easily?
If they're low quality, we can easily decide
Feels quite tough
-The level is very high
Sorry, but please choose the most interesting group from the 8 groups just now
How do you all feel? Considering the time is only 30 seconds, this is still...
They really did great
-Yeah
All the way from serious to messy.
There were many very complete segments
So who is the winner of group A?
Please show your cards together!
Nana Magari, Nana Magari, Iwahashi, Westland, Iwahashi
Split votes
-Split votes
In this case, Jinnai will decide
I see, i'm good to decide
Iwahashi or Nana Magari
I was hesitating between the two groups
-Oh, yeah?
I see
Can I say it already?
-No problem
PlusMinus' Iwahashi
Iwahashi, I see
Matsumoto, why did you choose Iwahashi?
Well, he lasted the whole 30 seconds, he's really interesting
The amount of things included was also a lot
-I see
Ijiin also chose Iwahashi
If the end is not so sharp it'll affect the overall segment
But in the end... is it ok to comment so seriously?
I feel like i'm under a lot of pressure
Of course you should comment seriously
They all signed up to do this
What about you? Is it because of the similarity to your own work?
No, no, although there's a sense of it
I just thought it was really interesting!
Yeah, the last line was really funny
And, after all, this is the only star born from Wednesday Downtown
Tooth Princess
The first combination that relies on Wednesday Downtown
Bakarhythm also went for Nana Magari
-Yeah
They started with a disgusting beginning and ended with a cool ending
I see
This contrast is great
So, the winner from group A is
PlusMinus' Iwahashi
So formal
Next is group B
9th is Tokyo Dynamite
This lineup is quite impressive
Welcome
Beef stew
Bread or rice
Bread
Beef stew still not ready?
Sorry, our family is in the real estate business.
-You should have told me earlier
These two are really messing around
10th is ZAZY
You are awesome!
Your nostrils are so big
Yes, I have big nostrils, after all I
Zucchini!
Plug plug
Zucchini plug plug plug
Yes, winter melon
Please go out with me
Why why?
Don't say it twice!
That's where the sashimi goes!
What is this?
It's the same as usual
11th is Manzara Demone
Is this your first time stealing?
-Yes
Take everything out.
-Okay
Eh, what happened? How did you put it in?
Sorry, also
More? The paper bag is all wrinkled.
-I'm sorry
Why? Why are there still things inside?
I also stole a pre-charge card, i'll return it to you
You also stole a prepaid card?
Eh, why so many?
I don't know what's going on.
-I'm sorry. I'm really sorry
It's my first time.
-You're lying!
Liar!
12th is Inu
No need to be polite today. Drink as much as you like
Thank you boss
Please let me pour your drink too.
-Thank you
So, cheers!
Get out of here!!
I see
13th is Takeo
Sato, you didn't work at an izakaya, did you?
-Yes, I did
But you're great, you'll be a manager soon
Ahem. Thank you
What's wrong? A cold?
It's okay. I'll be fine if I take my medication.
-Really?
Be careful not to catch a cold, what with the recent weather and all
I'm fine
You're fired
People who snort medicine through the nose will all be dismissed
What are you doing?
No 14th is Koide
I want to show you my collection of musician publicity photos
This is KAN
Next is Oe Sendi
And finally, Toshinobu Kubota
I'm Toshinobu!
This guy is playing around
Why did you call him here?
15th is Mochu Gakusei
Come see the barrel museum
Barrels
Yeah, barrels
Thank you all
That's it? Wow
Nothing at the end
18th is Jizonshin
Welcome
Elementary school students don't usually buy water
Elementary school students don't usually buy water at the convenience store
How much is your monthly allowance?
300 yen
You have to use a third of it to buy water?
You will kill people in the future
Wow, a tough choice
Indeed
It's a difficult group, isn't it?
This group is very difficult
Please vote
There are many combinations I still want to see. I still have many more I want to see
So, among these players, which group will be the winner of group B?
Have you written it? Please raise your cards together
Inu, Inu, Takeo, Tokyo Dynamite, Jizonshin
The decision is made
-Inu wins!
You have chosen Inu
Yes, the content is very simple, but the point was great
Jizonshin was close
Coo went for Jizonshin
-Yeah
Sort of speaks to my heart
I also want to make such a fashionable sketch
I have great respect for them
Very interesting
Jinnai went for Takeo
I still want to see them
You can't take medicine from the nose
Absolutely not!
But I did hesitate for a moment. Inu was also good
Even just mentioning their names in this way is a very good thing for them
But in the end, Inu got two votes
So the winner of group B is Inu
Interesting
So awesome!
Next is group C
17th is Jeradon
Hey, where did you take the princess?
That woman, I tied her to the top of the tower
What did you do? How is the princess breathing?
The oxygen there is probably only enough for the average human to last an hour
You can't go past without defeating both of us
What are you going to do?
Why're you the one that's responsible for speaking?
Indeed
Fun
18th is Oswald
Thanks, we're Oswald
I want to buy an expensive thing
There are two choices, and I'm still debating which one to buy
I see, you are hesitating between what?
I'm thinking of buying a road bike.
-That kind of good bike
Or buy a golden retriever?
-That kind of big dog
Yes, yes, yes, which one do you think is better?
This really depends on the purpose
Depending on the purpose I may be able to give an immediate answer
The purpose of course is transport
Then buy a road bike
19th is Makino
※The costume here is from the 2013 Japanese drama "The Sea Maid" in which Amano Aki is the female lead
Hello, I'm Amano Aki
Doing this now!?
Hello everyone, I'm the sea girl
What? I'm not a real sea woman
JEJEJEJE
※JE (じぇ) is the dialect of Kitasanriku, where Amano Aki is from, and is often mentioned in the drama
No, I caught sea urchins. Look!
Ah, I also have sea urchins in my clothes
No, this is my furry
It feels so long!
20th is TEAM Kondo
Congratulations on your marriage!
Here's a song for you, Butterfly by KAELA KIMURA
I'm sorry, I accidentally played the entrance song of Choushu
Let me try again
I really like Choushu
What's with the pause at the end
21st is Raichou
Gymnastic wear gymnastic wear
What can be done in gymnastic wear
Just turn up the ribbon, just turn up the ribbon
Turned into handcuffs for arresting prisoners
7:47 pm Arrested for being too old-fashioned
A bit of a mouthful, right?
Anything can be done with gymnastic wear
22nd is Mayurika
Damn, this kind of place opened an interior decoration store
Wow, what is this? So strange
What is this, what is this decorative item?
Look at this pose
You can't hit a ball that far away
There is a switch, ah what is this?
It is a humidifier
23rd is Okami
I didn't want to kill you. It's all your fault
Who is it?
They're in, what should I do?
Hello, we're ChallengeJoy
※ChallengeJoy: Japanese detergent brand, this is a parody of a commercial that lets housewives experience the effects of detergent
You've come at a bad time
Very bad timing indeed
24th is Kintaro
Only 8 years
The talented child singer from the country next door
It's really not the same level!
※Original Song: Korean Nursery Rhyme "Bo Bo Song"
This is the level I expected at the beginning
A real mix
The level is slightly lower
Yes
An easier choice
Then please vote
Have you written it? Then please show your cards together
Jeradon, Jeradon, Jeradon, Kintaro, Jeradon
I see
Matsumoto chose Kintaro
Its Kintaro
I can watch it for two hours straight
Funny indeed
Very funny
Jeradon, I know
That is actually the beginning of a longer sketch
It is part of a sketch
Originally part of the a longer one
Bakarhythm also selected Jeradon
Yes, the explosive ending was very strong
So that's how it is
Same with Coo?
I hesitated choosing Raichou
Raichou, you were on the fence about Raichou?
Raichou (thunderbirds) don't hesitate, right?
Only Jeradon and Raichou for me
Raichou is very powerful, the gymnastics clothes
Makino even managed to make 30 seconds feel long
Felt like 4 minutes
30-1 Grand Prix
Next is group D
25th is Warafuji Naruo
It's so stupid
You wont qualify!
You will be disqualified this way
You're doped up, aren't you?
What the hell! Just get out!
Hahahaha no i'm not
What are you laughing at?
That's not doping
Isn't it?
This is just taping
Shouldn't have said it
26th is Razor Ramon RG
As expected
It should be a good fit
Question for Takushi Arisawa, the WedDownKing
Super Hard!
Down…
It's too fast! Takushi Arisawa
Please tell us your answer
Okay, the answer is miso
Beautiful!
What is the seasoning in the miso that Downtown probably drinks in the morning?
Miso Beautiful! That's it!
Quick answer. Impeccable. Takushi Arisawa!
27th is Daishizen
Mini skit
American father on a yacht trying to get his adolescent son to talk about his troubles
Shota, why don't you try to steer too?
Eh, can I?
You're my son. You can do it.
-Yes!
Aaaah!
Heheh, you are too far to the right
Are you going to drive to the Atlantic Ocean?
I heard you don't get a seat on the school bus, what happened?
It was about that?
And a special ride on a yacht
28th is President of Japan
We have a transfer student coming in today
I'm Nishihara from Koumei High School, thank you
Why did you bring your own entrance song?
29th is Robin Foot
Are you all right, sir?
Ahhh sorry about that
I heard that there was a robbery?
I told them I didn't have my wallet, and they stripped me all over
Okay, I'll write a statement. Can you describe what was taken?
Sunglasses
Mask
Trenchcoat
Those things
Ah, just three things?
Yes
Just took those three things?
-Yes
Then we'll have to write another statement. Is that okay?
20th is Zigzagziggy
The pitcher throws the first pitch!
Ohhhh, it's a dead ball!
Eh?
Eh??
It hurts! You're... stop...it hurts!!!
Why?
Why... it hurts!
Wait... is anyone there?
Why are you doing this? Stop it!
I'm a center fielder!
That expression
31st is Matsumoto Club
♪Some women's underwear fell on the roadside
♪While caring about the eyes of others, picking up
♪Underwear, picked up
♪So it was actually a hair band
♪Hair band
32nd is Hoko
This guy is also a veteran
In your mind, you must have the concept of "that thing looks like this" to imitate
After all, to imitate is to be the same
The important thing is whether it resembles the concept in your head
We will now move closer to that "concept"
Now this is the hairstyle of the fat girl in Doraemon
I see
Wow, this is too hard to judge
The quality increased again
Although it is indeed difficult to judge, but please write down your choice
So, who will be able to enter the final?
Okay, please show together!
Wow, President of Japan got three votes
So, they are the confirmed finalist
Ijiin-san, what was behind your choice?
I would like to see more
-Yeah
I feel like I want to see more of this series
-Yes
Very admirable
Coo, you chose Daishizen?
Yes, because of the explosion at the end to get a laugh that I chose them
The three remaining people all chose the same person
Jinnai, you chose President of Japan?
Well, they were holding it in, and I was wondering where the hell it was going to explode?
But in the end, it was more normal than expected
-So that's it
Sure enough, the entrance song is still very funny
Does Matsumoto feel the same way?
There is a great sense of tension in the 30 seconds
I thought the music would be played after
What do you think?
They make you think the student's reveal will be the funny part
But in fact the joke is actually the song
It contains a slight reversal
-Indeed
It's fun.
-Got it
In a nutshell
President of Japan is advancing from group D to the final!
Will the members of each group deviate too much from each other?
True
Really true
If these guys are all in the same group they'd probably do something better
That's true.
-Two or three of these groups are estimated to be in the final
They just happened to be divided into groups like this
30-1 Grand Prix
Next is group E
33rd is Stamina Bread
Thank You House from 10 yen
What the hell is "Thank You House"? Never heard of it?
There's loads of coins
If it's only 10 yen, its ok to try it once
Thank you house...
Thanks
This guy's making an easy living!
34th is Moriya Biyori
My clothes have been hidden!
It was definitely that guy who did it!
What kind of bullying is this?
Time...
It's almost time for the show!
It is obviously public assault
I've already been interviewed by "Erotic Continent"
Really can't find it
35th is Robert
Tokyo sure is prosperous!
Hey, I'm in TV production
Oh no an industry person
The baldness of your forehead is incredible
Soon there will be a camera crew passing by. Can you please give way?
-A camera crew?
Eh, what are you shooting? It's awesome! Tokyo is really something!
Who will it be? Any star?
And then there's the fact that I've lived in this neighborhood
Here's the point. Here's the point.
-What the hell kind of star is this?
I can't even understand what he's saying
Hello, I'm Washio.
-I'm being pestered
So it's called Washio...
36th is Rainbow
Short skit
Alumni Association
Long time no see
Huh? Ta-chan?
Junko, you haven't changed at all since then
Ta-chan you seem to be a little fat, right?
Hahahaha, you sure are rude
This kid
Don't do that
No one will act like they did in those days, ok?
What're you talking about?
Not like that!
37th is Ultra Boogies
Ultra Boogies' new sports program
Foul, foul!
PT PT？
Penalty, ok penalty
Penalty ok?
-ok
10 9 8 7…3 2 1
It's over
12 tissues
11 tissues
Yes!
38th is SHIOMARIACHI
SHIOMARIACHI's ultra-short start!
Ah, this is not the New Year's greeting certificate
It says, "Happy New Year, please teach me more this year"
The top has a New Year's atmosphere
Wait a minute, take a closer look
Its actually Heineken beer bottles
Awesome!
Ah isn't this mahjong?
One two three
Four five six
Seven, eight ... hey isn't this the FILA logo?
39th is Chance Oshiro
He's here!
Luciano Pavarotti awakens after being bitten by a dog
40th is G Takashi
Antonio Inoki in a money transfer fraud
Hey, hey...hey, hey, hey!
It's me it's me
It's me, it's me, it's me!
Who is it? Who is it?
Who are you?
Ogawa, Fujita, Choushu?
Who is it?
I need money
Sorry money
Here a pun with money hahaha
Pay the money!
41st is DobuRock
Takei Sou who can beat any animal
I can make love in the face of any animal
Then watch me practice make love with a lion
If it is a lion, a little distance from it
First do a few fake movements
If it bites fiercely
Grab the mane with one hand
Block its movements
One headbutt
After feeling its resistance weakened
Make love！
A scary sound
It's over really fast!
Incidentally
The last group, DobuRock
Due to the content
I don't know if it can be broadcast
So you can't vote for them
I see, its not in there
Yes, the staff just wanted you to see it
That's right, that sketch is a big problem
I see
Yes, so it can't be broadcast
That's XXXX!
So please vote for group E
Almost done?
So, please publish the results together
Ah, Chance got three votes
Jinnai, you chose Robert?
I really want to continue to see Robert
I see
Ijiin you went with Chance
I think his personal aura is enough to last for 30 seconds
He also brought a good sketch
Matsumoto, you also chose him
Yes I did
If the dog was dirty and looked like it had a disease, the effect might be better
The dog was a bit too clean
A little clean.
-Yes, it is
What do you think, Baka?
Chance is very interesting
I don't know what to think of it but its still good
Ok
The winner of group E is Chance!
So, these five progress from the group stages
Who will win overall?
These are the finalists
What do you think?
Very impressive
Everyone who got through are strong figures
-Indeed
Impressive that Inu can be with the others, right?
-Really is
Now that I look at it, I think Iwahashi was the wrong choice
It is true that Iwahashi stands out among these people
That is the case
After all, we don't know who we will choose after
But, either way, he's the finalist of group a you selected
Okay, now it's finally time for the final!
First, the finalist of the first group is
PlusMinus' Iwahashi
Breaking a clarinet
My favorite clarinet
A clarinet handed down from my father
Knowing that it is very important
It's messed up, it doesn't make a sound
What to do, what to do?
Really shouldn't have chose him
He should not have been chosen.
-Very true
I made a mistake.
-It was a mistake
Next is
Inu
Short sketch: Gym
Let's do a few sets for the abs first
I don't know if I can finish it
It's time to start!
One!
-Uhhhhh...
You can do it!
I can't do it
I can't do it!
How can I do it?
Your arms are open, if you close them, it will be easier
What's the position?
You see your armpits are open
Just a bit more...
Oh oh, it worked!
Success...
What the hell?
Next is
Jeradon
You're a tough talker
But there's no way out
Come out, Ibiru!
What the hell is this guy?
Is it time for dinner?
-Wha?
I'll leave it to you, Ibiru
I'm starting
-No!
Are you okay?
Eh?
I'm actualy an FBI agent
Isn't this too complicated?
Next is
President of Japan
Towel
Surprisingly, went for the head
Fifth is
Chance Oshiro
The Terminator
I am Taro Aso
Are you kidding me?
He's joking around
It's over. It's over
You guys picked them all
These guys...
I didn't know it'd turn out like this
First of all, Iwahashi was really not the right choice
So please, everyone...
-Wait a second
This is the final, right?
It's the final, right?
-Yes, it is
I really want to choose again
Want to change the group
It would be nice to be able to start over from A
So, finally the first 30-1 champion is about to be decided
It's too hard.
-Please take your time to think about it
Okay please write down your choice
It's too hard to choose...
What will be the result?
So let's start announcing
The final selection, please show all together!
President of Japan
Inu
So, the winner of the first 30-1 Grand Prix is
President of Japan!
Matsumoto, you chose President of Japan
I considered comprehensively
From the overall viewpoint, I chose based on an overall assessment
President of Japan came first
-So that's how it is
Well, they were very bold
Jinnai, you chose the same?
President of Japan in 30 seconds is really interesting
Their choice of focus is also interesting
Baka, you also chose President of Japan
Yes, they also chose a different type of segment for the second one than the first
This point is also worthy of evaluation
Ijiin you though Inu should be the winner
Yes, originally
I thought it'd be between Iwahashi and Oshiro
I didn't expect them to fall off so quickly...
But both were good at using the last 5 seconds of time
This sense of atmosphere is very cleverly rendered
So I think it is very good
Coo you chose Inu too
Yes, but I was also thinking about President of Japan
Inu's good at making you guess what'll happen
But Oshiro is too weird, right?
Who would end with a parody of Aso Taro?
Too weird
Yes, there are obviously many other options
The last thing he did was to reference Aso Taro. Who would do such a thing?
Wrapped up like that
Now I'm annoyed for having said a dirty dog toy would've been better
This is not a problem at all
Who cares if it's dirty or not!
How do you feel after the competition, Baka?
I really think this competition is very good
Lots of people will reflect afterwards due to it being the first time
They'll understand a lot more
There must be a lot that weren't broadcast, right?
-Yes
Oh, that's true
There are 35 groups that did not air
Then the possibility that many interesting ones weren't shown
-Indeed
Is it possible to see one we didn't watch?
-Yeah
Don't you want to see it? Raichou...
Forget Raichou!
This is the last group you want to see, right?
The second skit of Raichou?
Good morning
-Good morning
Huh?
What?
Isn't this 300,000?.
-A scam, right?
What the hell?
-Congratulations
Congratulations?
Eh, what're we getting paid for?
Isn't there anything to do with the number 30?
-30?
30...
Eh, do you know what it is?
I might know.
-What is it?
I really don't know anything to do with the number 30
Isn't it that one?
Eh, is it okay for me to say it?
Is it Wednesday Downtown?
Yes!
-Oh-oh!
30-second segment
-Oh really?
Eh, so the result is... right?
Congratulations, you won the 30-1 Grand Prix
Eh!!!
-Awesome!
It's a lie, right?
Eh, we won, right?
-Yes
And that's the prize money for the contest, right?
And it's our first time on Wednesday...
Eh, it was actually a serious competition, huh?
That was really a contest... huh?
No, I just thought...
Chance Oshiro did it too.
-Yes
Something seems weird
I thought we were invited to do something that was pranking him...
No, it's not.
-Oh oh no ah
We beter take Chance Oshiro out to dinner then
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03