Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
It's Razor Ramon
Early summer foo~!
It's so noisy!
-Early summer
Yes, cheers to the season
So who do you think is the strongest duo in terms of strength in the entertainment industry?
Duo?
A two-person duo that have the best strength
Strong physique, Onigoe Tomahawk or something
Sei sei sei Not bad
These two have also done professional wrestling
-Yes
You should also be very strong
We've done professional wrestling. We're confident
Today we bring you this project to determine who is the strongest
Double sumo wrestling strongest duo decision tournament
Double Sumo
-Double Sumo
A 2-on-2 two-man sumo tournament
Simultaneous competition
4 people at the same time
You need to use your head too.
-Yes
The schedule for this competition is as follows
Onigoe and Matenrou
Matenrou
They look strong
Very large
And very heavy
Timon D also looks very strong
There are threes?
For the 3-people groups 2 people are selected to participate
Mama Tarte, the one on the right, is it muscle or just flab
Mama Tarte are very big
Aren't Mama Tarte dead?
So fast?
There's no such theory, right?
VTR playback!
You didn't say "foo!"?
-Sei
I see
Double sumo wrestling strongest duo decision tournament
This time, we invited 8 groups of artists with excellent physical and motor nerves
All look very strong
For a Special 2-on-2 tournament
To decide on the strongest group
The 1st match of the preliminary round was
Onigoe Tomahawk
Not only do both of them weigh more than 100kg
Sakai also joined the judo division during his high school years
And Kin-chan weighed 100kg in elementary school
Often see this photo
A super heavyweight combination that is very suitable for sumo wrestling
Do you know how many years we have argued comedically
We also have physical attacks when we quarrel
We've been sparring for decades
So we are the most suited to sumo
Even if i'm fighting Honkon, i'll go for it
You shut up
The other side is
Matenrou
Anthony is okay
The problem is Ontony
183cm 128kg Anthony has a professional level physique
And agile Ontony, they make up Matenrou
To be honest I don't think I will lose
I started eating a lot of meals 1 week ago
Weight gain of 7 to 8kg
They're small fry, small fry
They don't matter
Although we're the same generation
Their bad in sumo and comedy contests
The time has finally come for me to become the No.1 in the world of comedians
Onigoe Tomahawk and Matenrou showdown
What was the result?
So, the contest starts now!
The teamwork that you don't see in ordinary sumo can be the key to victory or defeat
The first is the Onigoe Tomahawk against Matenrou
Although there is almost no difference in the total weight of the 2 groups
Will the winner be Onigoe, both of whom are over 100kg
Or Matenrou with their giant and smaller combo
What happened?
Start!
Both sides are rushing up
Instantly all 4 are huddled together
Now it is a 1 vs 1 situation
Ontony is down
Immediately after Anthony was also dejected
Matenrou have been taken down without damage
Onigoe Tomahawk are the winners!
From the start, Onigoe quickly rushed Anthony
But Ontony forced his way in
And the situation became 1-on-1
Afterwards, the sumo wrestling was performed separately
Onigoe finished with a 2:0 win
We were going to start by targeting Kin-chan
But it's hard to stay on track
Seeing your partner down
Thinking about it being 1 on 2
Its difficult not to lose at that point
After the preliminary round, I want to tell the others
It definitely wont go as smoothly as planned
No, it won't
Absolutely not
Next is the 2nd game of the preliminary round
First of all
Timon D
Good physique
Timon D, elite sportsmen from a prestigious high school baseball team
The strongest pitcher in the entertainment industry who was discovered by professional baseball, Takahishi
And Maeda, who won the first place in the nation in physical strength test in high school
The strongest combination of physical ability
No matter what the project is, Takahishi is always throwing things
Yes
Throwing coconuts, throwing barrels, throwing hammers
And today is...
Throwing people out
The other side is
Daishizen
Looks strong too
Pretty heavy, huh?
Cooking?
Weighing more than 100kg, but also can dance breakdance, Shin-chan
And Roger, who has practiced Ryukyu karate
The combination of flexible giant men
Impressive
Yesterday, for sumo, to become a little stronger
※Shishoku hot pot is mainly the hot pot eaten by Japanese sumo wrestlers.
I ate cheese and tomato fondue
Assorted hot pot
No matter who the opponent is
I will do my best
Roger
-Hmm?
You can do it with effort
Do not say Timon D's line
Preliminary Round Match #2 Timon D vs. Daishizen
Coming from a prestigious college baseball school, Jimi High School
Timon D, whose physical abilities have been recognized
And in terms of the weight advantage: Daishizen
What happened?
Start!
Here we go. Takahashi is the first to pull away
Maeda tightly grasps his opponent
And Shin-chan takes his opponent from behind
It's become 2 on 2
Timon D together
Timon D launches an attack
They're out!
Maeda fell out first
Then wrapped around the neck to drop the opponent
Out!
Timon D gets the win
This is a good one.
-Very interesting
So strong
This is the number one sports entertainer
Completely demonstrates his physical ability
Timon D's Takahishi did not grapple with his opponent
Instead, he shielded his partner Maeda from behind
So the back was attacked and temporarily in crisis
Lastly, he used the weight of his opponent to cause a fall
Finally, victory!
The third match of the preliminary round was a matchup between 3-person teams
So interesting
First of all
Nelsons
Have you decided who will participate?
Me and Wada
Because he has a tattoo
Tattoo on the waist
-Its not there anymore
It's okay not to say
Can't take off
-Can't take it off
No, I can
The Nelsons are two experienced wrestlers
In the Beijing Olympics I made it to the final selection
Very impressive
My experience is significant
Maybe it's a little strange to say that about yourself
But we should be the most promising to win the championship
The other side is
Babylon
Who's participating?
I definitely want to do it
I have the power to destroy the opponent
Pretty awesome!
What are you talking about?
No, no, no, it must be me.
-What?
After that, an audition was held within the group
The second contestant is 180cm 120kg giant man Chiba
He and Nori, whose hobby is to bodybuilding and fighting, are going to the preliminary round together
We are all powerful
Indeed, we are a threesome full of power
Our skits also use power to obtain laughter
To be honest with you, Babylon is just a warm-up
I'm using these muscles to compete
Just for today's practice
Preliminary Round Match 3 Nelsons vs Babylon
The Nelsons, both of whom have wrestling experience and intend to use it as a weapon
Nori, who has honed his tackling experience in fitness and rugby
Plus the giant man of Babylon: Chiba
What will happen?
Start!
It's on. First, it's a 1-on-1 situation
Coming around behind him and taking his legs out
Only Nori is left
He's tripped and put down
Nelsons get the win
Not bad for having wrestling experience
Nothing to do with muscle
Quite impressive!
Babylon's 2 members failed to resist at all
Nelsons Aoyama first uses the push-pull arm technique to turn behind him
And a one-legged takedown to take out Chiba in seconds
Wadaban also put Nori down with a foot hold
A complete victory over Babylon
Winning is not a problem at all
Nori's muscles are just for show
Not real muscle
Indeed
Ah
Don't be angry Nori
Want to do it again
No more
Next is the 4th game of the preliminary round
First of all
Razor Ramon
Good body
Older age
Yes, much older
Salt foo～
OK
Razor Ramon who met as pro wrestling students
After joining the comedy world
They've continued to work as comedians and professional wrestlers
Tell us who you have fought with
Akebono, Abdullah the Butcher, Tiger Jeet Singh
Genichiro Tenryu, Scott Norton, Giant Silver
Fought with many giant wrestlers
Is there a 2m tall one today?
The other side is
Mama Tarte
178kg
Sorry, Marjorie
Ma, sorry
The exercise experience is 0 but the weight is the heaviest in the competition
The 178kg giant man Otsuru has a sumo level physique
Kashiwara looks small but weighs 83kg
Combined weight: 261kg
I've never fully utilized the strength of 178kg
Using this power may cause tragedy
So i'll use 80% of my force to fight
We have undergone a lot of hardships
Had his head bust open by Tiger Jeet Singh
What a "sei!"
Preliminary Round Match #4 Razor Ramon vs. Mama Tarte
Seeing this huge body caused a lot of noise in the room
Both joined professional wrestling clubs during their college years
Razor Ramon, a solid middle pairing
Against Mama Tarte, the heaviest overall weight in the tournament
The weight difference between the 2 combinations is almost 100kg
What'll happen?
Start!
It's begun!
The two sides rush each other
2 are pushed out
What is this?
2 people rushed in
And 2 were pushed out
Mama Tarte is too strong
Two out simultaneously
This is really "sei"
Mama Tarte gets the win
Razor Ramon together prove useless
2 pushed out together
A total shock
Despite being at a 1 vs. 2 disadvantage
He still knocked out both
178kg monster Otsuru
This is my power...
Don't seem to be aware of the strength
We went according to plan
2 people attack Otsuru first
But 178kg is really "sei"
-"sei"
How many times do you have to say it?
From here, the best pair of sumo wrestlers will enter the semi-finals
The 1st match was
Sorry for losing in the preliminary round
Using power to push down the giant man Anthony
The duo of over 100kg, Onigoe Tomahawk
Against Timon D, the first artist in the sport with outstanding physical ability
Who will be able to advance to the final?
The match is about to start
Start!
Onigoe start by targeting Takahishi first
Takahishi is out!
Now its Sakai and Maeda's one-on-one
Maeda's tries to throw his opponent out from the waste
Maeda forces a throw!
Strong core strength
Awesome awesome
Timon D gets the win
But
At this point the deputy referee approaches the playing field
Eh?
Foul?
What's going on here?
Investigating
A disagreement
Referee disagrees
So strict
Need to see a replay to decide
Take a look at the replay
Is it out of bounds?
The foot looks out of bounds
What will be the verdict?
Winner Onigoe Tomahawk
The referees have re-ruled
Onigoe Tomahawk reverses the win
Is it necessary to be so strict?
Maeda's foot stepped outside the field a little bit
Very strict
Very interesting!
Next is the 2nd game of the semi-finals
The victory went to the Nelsons who won the match with their magnificent wrestling skills
They will be facing Mama Tarte's monster Otsuru
Who will be the winner of the match?
This is a duel of skill and power
Who will win?
Start!
It's begun!
One is out first
Then it's a 2 on 1 leg lift out
Aoyama alone takes down 2 people in seconds
Nelsons get the win
Otsuru, who was defeated without being able to use his power, has this look on his face
Aoyama takes out one in seconds
Then rushed up from the side to hold and push out Otsuru
Very weak
Otsuru
Yes...
I don't know why I grew so fat
Not for this, I'm sure
Just as planned
I wanted to defeat them as soon as possible
Wada said he'd hold out.
-Yes...
You were holding out, right?
No, actually...
When Aoyama went to attack Otsuru
I though I better back away
Then I was straight out of bounds
Foot out of bounds
Now the final
Onigoe Tomahawk vs Nelsons
Who will be the winner?
The final match is Onigoe Tomahawk vs Nelsons
Is the name Aoyama?
Although you seem to have been a wrestler
You're a comedian, right?
Do some enjoyable wrestling!
Beating you is enough
The comedian who didn't succeed when he should have, right?
Think about yourself!
Stop it
Psychological warfare
The junior Onigoe Tomahawk against the senior Nelsons
A 4-person showdown!
What will happen?
Start!
It's on. It's 1 on 1
Aoyama and Sakai twist together head to head
Both want to drop each other
Aoyama pushes out his opponent!
Kin-chan is still left!
Aoyama is watching from the side, forming a 2 vs 1 situation
Wada throws hard
Nelsons get a nice win over Onigoe Tomahawk
Very frustrating
Sakai is too strong
Several times I wanted to press him down
But I finally got him out
Honestly, I didn't want to lose
Couldn't get a hold
What?
Unhappy?
Especially unhappy
But this game does not end here
What's going on?
Eh?
Please welcome these 2 people to the stage
Who?
Forget this!
It's Yunbo Dump
He's called cashew?
Yes, after the victory Nelsons will go against Yunbo Dump
The one who wins this match is the real king of double sumo
Yunbo Dump, a duo of 2 people over 130kg
Cashew participated in the sumo wrestling national competition during his high school years
He was also selected by the sumo wrestling world and is one of the strongest wrestlers in the entertainment industry
All out attack
This is a problem, we knew nothing about this
But the hopes of all those who have competed
Are my power to defeat you
Nelsons against Yunbo Dump
Who will be the real king?
Nelsons
Yunbo Dump
Nelsons who are good at wrestling
Versus the heaviest group in the entertainment industry, Yunbo Dump with 263kg
What will happen?
Start!
It's on!
Cashew... ah out
Then Fujiwara pushes his opponent out
He's out, and then Fujiwara pushes his opponent out
The referee awards Yunbo Dump the win
The comedians are all standing up
Eh, Yunbo Dump？
Body...
This is determined by the video
Eh, who won?
Watch the replay
Note the 2 people behind
Hands on the ground! Hands on the ground!
Did you put your hand down?
Look at the fingertips
There's dirt
Hands covered in dirt
Referee misjudgment: the winner is Nelsons
Great!
A lot of twists and turns
Nelsons, who won over Yunbo Dump, are now declared victorious
Nelsons
Wada bringing down Cashew
Was a big help
Is your forehead cut?
No its not
Not cut
-It's turning red
It's not that easy for me to get hurt
In summary
Nelsons were the first sumo wrestling kings
What do you all think?
Well...
Why are you both the presenters?
Gliding across the floor
That was really a monster
Both pushed out at the same time
So everyone should praise the Nelsons, who beat the monsters
We paved the way for the battle against the monster Otsuru
Then Aoyama took over
We started this story
This was pretty interesting
I also want to see who's the worst
I think Karateka should be the weakest
I see
But that's just one person so...
That's exactly what I mean
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
It's Chocolate Planet
It's chocolate.
-We are Chocolate Planet
It's Choco-chan!
The only person who can call us "Choco-chan" is Master Nishikawa Kiyoshi
Basically they're ChocoPla, right?
So without further ado, this time we bring you the second edition of a certain theory
The 2nd "Make your Partner Do a Double-take" Competition
This was interesting last time
Have you ever done a double-take?
Have you, Kanda?
Once I saw a homeless person, probably on their first day living on the street
A very young person
Who started putting things on the ground
Starting the day?
-Yes, then they went...
I did a double-take
"Okay, let's do it" means
-Well, that's probably what it means.
They put something on the floor and did this action
How can you be so sure its their first day?
The 2nd "Make your Partner Do a Double-take" Competition
Quite difficult, right?
This time, we let these four construct a scene that you can't help but look twice at
And set up their respective partners
So, the first challenger was
Nishkikoi's Watanabe
Each group prepares 2 kinds of scenes
Please describe the first scenario
It's "the staff has long fingers"
What?
Long fingers... that's it
Super long
So creepy!
That's good
Would you only look twice at it?
Taking the cup is good
This began with taking a mold
Realistic!
To make the fingers 1.5 times longer
Impressive
Can you touch your hair up a little?
At first glance, you might not notice
That's awesome. Good job
That's good
Acting instructions are given by Watanabe himself
Ah, really well done!
The thumb is also long
Hasegawa comes to a discussion meeting for a fake program
This time you are invited to participate in a special program of "Health Survey of Entertainers"
No suspicion at all
Quickly...
It's just a physical test in a studio for entertainers who don't lead a regular life
Then you will get the health diagnosis results
After this result
So long
-So realistic!
Didn't notice
Hasn't seen it yet
Although it should be in his field of view
After 5 minutes of not noticing it at all
At this point
Can you stroke your hair a little?
Stroke your hair to show your fingers
Very conspicuous
I presume you haven't jumped continuously for a long time
No not at all
It's been a long time since I've done it
But in spite of this he also did not notice
Can you scratch your head with your index finger?
Before, I would just make some rice and buy some side dishes at the supermarket
Later
There you go!
When you're busy, it's tough
This is a success, right? Definitely a double-take
So, a double-take was successfully induced
Then
A typical example
You'd become very concerned
Yes, you'd care a lot
After all, we saw it once
Always watching
Final Total: 13 glances
Therefore, Watanabe's first time was a perfect success
Next is
Korokoro Chikichiki Peppers Nishino's challenge
The first one is
Posters for TKO Kinoshita's radio program are posted in the hallway
Nadal has been a bit down on Kinoshita until now
The reaction of "how is it possible?"
Therefore
"TKO Kinoshita's Tonight is also a KO"
Just right, how to say, it feels cheap
Because he'll pass the corner here
He'll be able to see it in plain view
The poster is set up in two places in the corridor of the radio station where it will be easily visible
What will happen?
Here we go, here we go
Look! Look!
Looking at the various posters
He's looking, do a double-take, quick!
Although he looked...
He stared at it but just once
After finding the poster, his eyes did not move at all
It even held his attention as he turned the corner
Instead of looking back, he stared
It's okay. There's another one. There's another one
Then
He's looking, he's looking
Kinoshita's still working?
Eh? The audacity
The "audacity" is a bit too...
I didn't expect Nadal to despise Kinoshita even more than I thought
Therefore, Nishino's first effort ended in failure
The next one is President of Japan's Tsuji
The arrangement is
As soon as he enters the building, he will surely go for a shit
So by the time he's ready to go to the bathroom, the bathroom will be in the process of being cleaned
Then the cleaners will come out
A lot of people will come out
Can he make his partner do a double-take by drawing on his daily habits?
What will happen?
Good Morning
-Good morning
Lots of luggage!
Can I go to the bathroom first?
-Yes, no problem
Out to the left
Just as predicted
Just like Tsuji's information, he went to the toilet immediately after arriving
Usually, he goes there after putting his stuff down
It's really the same as usual
Is it working?
-You want to use the toilet?
Yes
-We're almost done. Please wait a moment
Ok, got it
He's looking, he's looking!
Can't take his eyes off of it
He's looking
He's watching, right?
Looking at each person once
Then
Ah he looked!
This is a double-take, right?
Although the battle line is a little long
He just about did a double-take
So, the final challenger is Chocolate Planet's Nagata
When it comes to me, it must be a small prop
This time, i'm ready to use my best working chip bag sealer
Is this a masterpiece?
-Yes, my best work
The setup is that the chip bag sealer will be sold in large electrical stores
It'll be on display when he's on location
After a quick glance, he'll do a double-take
That's it, right?
The price is also to ensure a double-take
In this way, Nagata completed the setup himself
Also did the outer packaging
Very real
Dondake!
So loud!
He'll definitely say "don't!"
-Don't!
They're really a duo
I knew for sure he'd do it once
Why say this at the start?
Don't say that. It's hard work
Then
Coming
Finally, he comes to the area where chip bag sealer are sold
Eh, what is this?
Staring
Keeps staring at it
Panasonic...
I think he is now in a completely unknown state
This location shoot can no longer continue, right?
So, the result at the end of round 1 is shown in the figure
Round 2, because it doesn't matter even if it is found to be a trick
The setting will become more daring
First, Nishkikoi's Watanabe
What's the 2nd one?
"Radio Exercises Masanori Dance"
When Masanori passes by
People will be doing radio exercises
The radio exercise they'll do is the "Masanori dance" that Masanori always does
In this way, i'm sure he'll do a double-take
Walking on the road near my hometown
A grandmother passed by and it looked like something came out of her mouth
I thought "what?" and looked again, she spat out her dentures and put them back in
Couldn't help but look again
"Radio Exercises Masanori Dance"
Keep going down there
-Okay, got it
The first is to extend the hands from the top to the front
Here we go!
Here we go, here we go
Hand and foot movement
Cross your wrists
Super unnatural
Did you notice?
Noticed?
Mouth is always open
Lean your hands to your face and head, dumb movement
Suspicious
What a face
Turn your neck
Once again, hand and foot movements
This is what you will do every day
What's this expression, he's also looking back
Becoming restless, right?
Open, close
He's stopped
Always watching
Open, close
One more time, turn your neck
This isn't a double-take
This is staring
Still greeting them
Afternoon
What greeting?
Masanori!
Noticed quite quickly
No, no, because I know this set of movements
Did you think there was anything else strange today?
It's that one, right?
A woman with long fingers
That one was pretty much a double-take
Really?
-Yes
Therefore, Nishkikoi is 1 win and 1 loss
Next
Let a fan approach Nadal
Then say, "can we take a picture together?
After the contact
After a dozen meters after the place appeared exactly the same female appears
They're twins
After the girl says, "thank you for your hard work"
The next one will appear
What'll happen?
This should be an easy one
Here we go
Sorry.
-What is it?
Are you Nadal?
-Yes, I'm Nadal
I am a huge fan
-Thank you
If you can, can we take a picture together?
-Yes
Thank you so much!
Very well played
I'll take it then
Cheese!
Very irritating
Ah, super happy, also did the action
Thank you. I will support you
OKOKOK now...
He did a double-take
A nice double-take
This is indeed a double-take
Confirming the first person after seeing the second
A beautiful double-take
What what what?
"Make your partner do a double-take"
Yeah, I think I probably did
Had a good look back
A very nice double-take
-Looked back several times
Did you think it was teleportation?
Who would possibly think that?
-What then?
I thought it was someone wearing the same clothes
But you thought something was weird, so you did a double-take, right?
Don't think I'll fall for anything
Who the hell would think of teleportation?
Next
Does this feel out of place?
-It does seem weird
I knew it!
Who wants to listen to that?
So, the next one is the second round of President of Japan's Tsuji
"In the lounge, the manager is eating charcoal grilled meat."
If it's just the manager, they might comment
But if they're eating with someone who looks like a producer
Maybe you'd do a double-take instead
The scenario looks like this
In order to keep the charcoal stove from being seen immediately
The players are told where to stand specifically
This is it
I see
What will happen?
Good morning
Please come in
I'm director Kimura
This time it's TBS...
This is a double-take, right?
Probably holding in a laugh
Is it a double-take?
I'm director Kimura
Looked first
This time it's TBS...
Then looked again
It would make you laugh
He's laughing
Then, after the subject of the meeting leaves the room
What will be said?
Sorry, I'm a little late to say hello
I am from President of Japan
Ah, hello
This is the producer, Yoshida
Ah hello
Just kinda...
I think maybe the smoke is not really going out
So, we reveal the truth here
What are you doing?
I don't get it, huh?
What do you think?
I thought these two are completely crazy
So, the President of Japan succeeded twice in a row
And finally...
The person working at a Turkish kebab store
Is Dennis's Yukio
Instead of greeting customers, they look at their phones instead
A very idle Turkish kebab store clerk
Is it weird?
-It's not weird at all
It feels like it would be a good match
What'll happen in the end
Too integrated into the environment
Here we go, here we go, here we go
Nervous
Will feel "huh? right?
Here we go. Here we go
Ah, didn't notice
Ah, he's gone
That's too bad!
0 views
Hello
What is this? Seriously
Just notice!
What?
It's the "make your partner do a double-take" tournament
Ah, that
Did you ever feel like doing a double-take?
The potato chip bag sealer, right?
One more place.
-Really? No way!
If you use your special ability, you can see it right now
When it comes to my special abilities...
Is there a comedian around?
There is
-No way
It's over, I didn't realize
He is super good at spotting comedians on the street
Let's go back.
-Eh, no way!
Go back a bit
Eh, no way!
Didn't notice at all?
Didn't notice
And then there is...
When you get to the computer area
Why? He fits in too much
Go back
Eh? Eh?
Yukio's already done a double-take
Go back a bit
Eh?
Eh? What?
Wow, I'm sorry
In Summary
The only pair that didn't do a double-take is Chocolate Planet
That's funny
That's the result
Why does this program let the worst performing people host?
The same with Razor just now
-I'm not sure
It was already decided.
-We didn't expect it either
Yukio really fit into the scene
In fact, when waiting
2 customers actually came to try and buy something
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03