Timers: SaltPacket, ShadowMagic, Jump4r Translators: Saalow, CatZombies, Jump4r, Otviss
m 0 0  l 1800 0  1800 140  0 140
WDT Project
It's time for Wednesday Downtown! Thanks for tuning in.
Let's kick it off!
Let's welcome our first presenter. Here she is!
What's up!!
It's Haruna Ai!
Thanks for having me!
Thanks so much, everyone.
Well, if it isn't Hamada's side piece.
Is that true?
Yeah, she's Hamada's woman.
What the hell... she's a dude!
How lovely.
They get along a little too well, I think.
I'm just saying. It's suspicious.
No, no, no, no.
What I've brought with me this time
Is a theory concerning cosmetic surgery.
I've noticed something about today's panel.
All of you have double-eyelids, right?
Am I correct?
That seems about right.
If it's not a problem... would anyone here mind being picked on?
...about our eyes, yes?
There's no way anyone will volunteer for that.
If you'd all please direct your attention to the monitor...
Ugh, it's me!
That's me!
Oh wow, that's...
What a little cutie!
Hamada-san...
This is from when he broke out of boarding school!
You're right!
I've seen this photo before.
And he's got single lids...
Yes! He's single-lidded here.
Yeah!
And now...?
No, you're wrong!
This is a bit suspect, isn't it?
I didn't get anything done to my eyes.
Why would you do something so ineffective?
I didn't!
Hold on a bit. Is it alright if I take a look?
Let me see.
You're too close!
Could you close your eyes?
They're totally banging.
Are they...?
What the hell...
What are you even doing!
What are they doing??
What exactly is this that you're doing?
How did your eyelids get like that, then?
Hell if I know!
Age. It's age.
Ahh.
It's the skin sagging down.
The hell's this got to do with your theory?
That's right! Here's the theory I've brought with me this week:
Nobody's Had Their Double Lids Surgically Changed to Single Lids
Ohh! I see.
That's right. This is the reverse of the norm.
I see, yeah.
After the break: double lids to single lids, we ask the pros about unusual surgeries!
And a program first: The REAL Prank!
I'm with "Weekly Girls' Gossip"...
Scandal Leak! This comedian thinks he's being pranked.
It's real.
...but it's 100% true! How will he react?
Plus, a "Comedians who are bad at improv are funnier when they're drunk" theory
Followed by a trip to see if there's such a thing as a rest area that doesn't sell soft-serve!
Has this strange corrective surgery ever been performed?
We investigate.
Double-eyelid surgery is among the most common cosmetic procedures, however
oh god!!
Could it be that there are those out there who've had the reverse?
stop it with that picture
And so begins our survey of outpatient plastic surgery clinics.
god I hate that photo
what's with all the fans?
First to respond to our inquiry was this clinic in Roppongi.
Dr. Kamakura, a plastic surgeon with 18 years experience, answers.
Have you ever performed a double-to-single eyelid surgery?
I have not, no.
ah, bummer
Not a single person?
Not a single person.
I'm actually not sure I could do such a procedure.
that's true
It would be quite difficult and take a very steady hand.
is that right?
Academically speaking, that's not a procedure commonly taught.
Conversely, the single-to-double procedure is very simple.
For this doctor, no such thing.
And what's more, the surgery has a very high level of difficulty.
But since we're already here, we asked Dr. Kamakura a few more questions.
Doctor, among the surgeries you have performed,
Has there ever been a time where you've thought "this sure is rare"?
Rare surgeries... let's see...
There was one patient who wanted a "butt chin".
This was a male patient of mine.
Rare Cosmetic Surgery File 1: Butt Chin
not quite to that extent...
surely that's exaggerated?
that's...
"I want to look like a Hollywood star!"
This is the request patients often make.
But how does one go about creating a Butt Chin in the first place?
Specifically what that entails is an injection of Hyaluronic acid to split the chin.
We leave the center alone while adding fillers to the left and right, and there you have it.
Hyaluronic acid is absorbed back into the body after a period of time,
I see, so it's temporary
So the cosmetic benefits only last about a year.
I didn't know that was a thing
Is that so?
Yes.
But that's not the only unusual surgery he's performed...
This was a female patient I had,
She had very slim calves,
And she wanted them a bit more shapely, similar to the shape of a fish carrying eggs.
Rare Cosmetic Surgery File 2: Pregnant Fish Calves
you can get that done?
Since this was a slim person who wanted to gain weight,
Instead of liposuction, the more common procedure,
What this surgery called for was the introduction of fat to the body.
I've experience dealing with requests like those.
There's certainly an air of "what a waste" with such surgeries.
Next to respond was this Shinjuku clinic.
Dr. Yamamoto, in practice for 24 years, answers.
there's a lot of hot plastic surgeons
No, I've never performed that surgery.
What about your colleagues?
No, not among the surgeons I know.
Is that so?
-Yes.
There's no strong leads to be found,
But what about other rare cosmetic surgeries?
rare surgeries?
There was a gentleman with a tattoo on his, uh, manhood.
The tattoo was of his ex-girlfriend's name.
He got it there?
The tattoo was in English.
I think it said "EMIKO"...
Normally this tattoo wouldn't be visible,
"When I get aroused I can see the full text, and I don't like that" was the claim.
that's something else
"I'd like you to remove my ex-girlfriend's name."
sounds painful!
That's the surgery I was tasked with.
Rare Cosmetic Surgery File 3: Ex-GF EMIKO-ectomy.
that's enough!
So normally, he couldn't see it, right?
That's correct.
Under normal circumstances, the penis is collapsed similar to an accordion,
And the lettering of the tattoo shrinks with the skin.
So in that instance, the tattoo would look like a black splotch.
no...
that's crazy
It would probably look something like this.
not necessary!
I don't need the visual!
like that, huh?
he already described it
Moving on to our next doctor...
No, I've never had a patient undergo that procedure.
We're unable to get any info on double-to-single eyelid surgery,
nothing!
But what of Dr. Maruyama's other procedures?
There was a male patient of mine who wanted his nipples removed.
what? why?
"My nipples..."
removed...?
"I want my nipples gone," that was the request.
how?
what does that mean?
Wait... what exactly do you mean?
So, basically,
The issue he had was that his nipples would get erect and become visible, even under a shirt.
There are quite a few people out there who are self-conscious about that.
Rare Cosmetic Surgery File 4: Nipple Removal
how is it done?
What exactly does that surgery entail?
The first step is to remove the very top of the nipple.
After that, I remove the rest of the nipple, leaving the areola.
Then I take the bit I sliced off at first and graft that onto the areola.
Oh, I get it!
It's not like they're totally removed, right?
When viewed from the front, the nipple appears normal.
But from the side, there's no obvious erection going on.
A lot of very stylish people request that.
"I don't like the way it looks under my shirt," for example.
to get surgery for that reason... wow
Other fashionable plastic surgeries include...
There was a patient whose hobby was running.
And so to prevent irritation during a run,
This patient requested a scrotal-reduction surgery.
what?
Scrotal...?
"I'd like a sportier vibe," was what he said.
Wh... What in the world?
"A sportier vibe...?"
A sportier vibe?
He asked that I make it smaller, more compact.
sporty??
Rare Cosmetic Surgery File 5: Scrotal Sportification
I don't get it!!
I made an incision,
And stretched the skin back to reduce its size.
It turned out very well, actually. Looked great too.
"You really helped me out!" was what he told me after.
So he was happy with it.
"you really helped me out!"
Yes.
"helped him out..."
We continue in our investigation.
It's very common for Chinese patients to come to Japan for cosmetic surgery.
"Fukumimi," or puffy, long earlobes,
Are a sign of wealth among Chinese people.
What I do is inject Hyaluronic acid into the earlobe and make it bigger that way.
Rare Cosmetic Surgery File 6:
Earlobe Enlargement for Chinese People
Furthermore...
A patient of mine requested that his genital size be reduced.
that's possible?
He's been my only patient so far to have such a procedure.
why...?
Rare Cosmetic Surgery File 7: Genital Reduction
what the hell kind of...
In this case, the patient got married,
the banana...
And his wife had been very suspicious that he was unfaithful.
Her doubts were so strong,
"If you make it smaller,"
"...I won't need to worry anymore" is what she told him.
there's no way...
"So could you make it smaller and shorter?"
That was the specific request.
that is so screwed up
How big did he want it?
what's the point in that?
Well... the size of an elementary schooler's.
The remaining would be the same size as a grade schooler's.
poor guy!
I guess you can...
what? that's possible??
Among the strangest plastic surgeries so far...
absolutely absurd
...we find this case.
We're looking to see if anyone has gotten double-to-single lid surgery.
There is someone who wants a double to single eyelid surgery.
There is?
Yes.
At last, we've discovered our original objective, a single eyelid surgery.
Is that so?
That's right!
Really?
Finally found one.
Futhermore,
There IS someone
We have the surgery scheduled soon.
One's coming up.
Oh, I see.
Surprisingly, he's preparing to do the surgery in two weeks.
Perfect timing.
I see.
Then, we receive permission from the doctor to interview the patient.
I dunno, I wonder
The next day, we hear their story.
Hello.
Thanks for working with us.
This is the Chinese woman receiving the double to single eyelid surgery.
Ah, Ryuu.
Ryuu In, 34 years old.
Ryuu, what for?
They're really defined.
Her eyelids are distinctly double, however
Lovely double eyelids.
What's the story behind you getting the double to single eyelid surgery?
Okay, okay.
Because originally I had single eyelids.
Eh?
Originally, I had single eyelids.
What the heck is this?
She wants to reverse it?
15... around 16 years old I think.
Before I came to Japan, my mom said
"In Japan, lots of people have single eyelids so
when you go to Japan, wouldn't it be good to have double eyelids?"
"Let's do it." I said and I had it done.
This time's surgery is on
her surgically made double eyelids that her mother recommended 18 years prior.
They will be returned to their original single eyelid form.
What is she gonna do?
But why the heck did she decide to have this surgery?
One thing is everyone says "You had surgery, huh."
Oh, it looks too obvious?
I'm often found out.
"You've had surgery on your eyes." for example.
It's a little unpleasent...
One reason is that the surgery done in China is rough.
The fact she had surgery is quickly revealed to those around her.
Is that so?
She doesn't like it, huh
Then another reason is
Thinking back to when I was small, I really think that, "It was better like that, huh."
She came to think that she liked it better when it was natural.
Single eyelids are cute, too
One week later. Surgery day.
What are they going to do for filming?
Long time no see.
It's been one week, huh.
That's right. Today I have a slight surgery.
We inquire what her state of mind is right before surgery.
For Koreans, everyone has single eyelids, right?
I think that's nice.
Ah right, like K-pop.
You're not worried at all?
No, I'm alright.
The cosmetic surgery that Ryuu will receive is as follows.
First, an incision is made along the double eyelid line from the previous surgery.
The eyelid is then opened.
The thread that creates the double eyelid is removed.
There's a thread inside?
The stitches in the hypodermis under the fold are removed.
That's rough.
The eyelid is then sewn back up.
With that, the surgery finally begins.
Ah, this is amazing!
This is amazing.
Then, after one hour, the surgery is over.
Is the result like before,
with clear single eyelids returned?
Thanks for coming.
After the single eyelid surgery, has Ryuu
been returned to single eyelids like before?
Thanks for coming.
It's so swollen that we can't tell at all.
That's surprising.
But that's right after.
Needs a little time.
You can't really tell...
It's so swollen.
Still, there is a fresh scar.
At present, it became an even more distinct double eyelid.
Yeah, I see I see
Right, since we're trying to forcefully revert the incisions to make them double
Well, it should get better within two months.
The doctor did a really good job
It's even more of a double eyelid than before.
It's even more.
But it does take two months.
One month later.
Only one month after surgery, this is Ryuu.
Since we're reverting back, it's more swollen for now
They're still swollen but the progress is good.
We have no choice but to wait a little longer.
That said, they should be healed by the time this airs.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Yes?
So why did we air this so soon?
No, but really in order to broadcast it, Ryuu was really...
No, no, no, no.
If that's the case, wait until after one or two months.
That's right.
When this is airing, they'll insert footage of it.
Yeah, exactly.
We'll show everyone how the single eyelids look after waiting two months.
Are we in such a rush?
On that note,
Two months after surgery, this is what Ryuu now looks like.
The swelling has gone down but it now looks more like a natural double eyelid.
The swelling has gone down and
it still didn't turn into single eyelids.
In comparison to the surgery I had done in China, I think it's a lot better.
However according to the doctor, Ryuu is the slow healing type and going forward they will become proper single eyelids.
Let's move on to our next presenter
Savanna's Takahashi
When you think of "Wednesday Downtown"
you think of the many "Pranks" you have performed
From Hamada's beloved "A person is there" series
to the "Scolding" series
We have assaulted many people with our plans
But within that...
we have discovered a brand new concept
within the world of pranks here today
Really?
That hasn't been done before?
That has definitely not been done before
That I haven't even heard of
I see
And that is this...
Real Prank
What the hell? What do you mean?
What do you mean by that?
Just from the title it's a bit much right?
It really is
When you think of a prank reveal, what kind of things come to mind?
Concerning the image
The sign comes out
The sign comes out right!
Everyone's seen that sign come out that says "Prank Success"
When that comes out you realized that you've been pranked
Like "Oh man!"
Like "Ahh, it was a prank!"
That's right
Depending on the circumstances, you'd be like "Aw man that was a prank?"
That's the feeling you get right?
This time, on that sign
Instead of "Prank Success", we put...
"Real"
"Real"?
What is this??
I don't understand what you mean by this at all
With all the things happening around you
In the moment you think that it's a prank
We reveal that it's real
The fact that everything is real
is what we will convey with that sign
So, for this theory, the Wednesday Downtown staff have taken a special route
to do research on several tabloids
Scary!
We were able to successfully obtain
an upcoming article containing personal gossip on a certain celebrity
That's really amazing!
What do you mean?
And that person will get hit with the "truth"
It's actually real?
Yes it is
I see, so you make them think that a scandal is going to be released
then when they're thinking "oh this must be a prank"
That it must be a prank right
It's Real!
That's terrifying
In order for this plan to succeed
we needed real, unearthed celebrity gossip
So with that...
Research was performed on several weekly publications
From Weekly Girls' came an article that they planned to write soon about a certain star
That celebrity is...
Sanshirou's Komiya
Oh wait, will it leak?
With that, during early May
A reporter from Weekly Girls' has prepared to ambush Komiya, as he's about to appear on a show
We were also given permission to film at the scene
Hello Komiya, nice to meet you I'm from Weekly Girls' Magazine
Ahh, this feeling sucks...
Komiya. You had said earlier that you "like cabarets"
It seems like lately you've been having a lot of fun around the countryside
Do you remember?
Eh? Wait? What?
You went to Atami sometime around March correct?
Yeah...
You did, correct
How did it go? Regarding your pick-up style
Wherever you went
Saying things like "Come and play with me in Tokyo", "I'll pay for your travel"
Did it go well?
I never said..
Oh really, I've heard some things here and there about it
Here and there?
The article being released is...
About Komiya flirting and messing around in Atami
Do you have a card?
Oh yes yes, please
I apologize
Suddenly stopping you like this
I have a show now
Oh are you busy now?
I've got a new joke to do so...
Oh... is that so
I can't feel bad for you in this situation
Who cares
Since it's a new joke, we'll back off
This is regarding Atami?
Yes, regarding Atami
What is this? Are you planning to publish this?
Well, yeah we did have that intention
Eh? This is kind of scary...
Komiya becomes startled by the sudden direct interview
But Komiya does remember doing what the reporter is saying?
He did actually go to Atami
Excuse me, I have to contact my manager
Oh, is that so?
And my new joke...
And my legs hurt
This should be your new joke
"new joke" and "my legs hurt"
Komiya tries to escape the reporter with some puzzling excuses
Is this going to be published?
We have plans...
What are you going to drop?
Just stuff like the answers you give us..
Well, was there anyone you made fall for you?
No, the girls were just doing their jobs
Is that right
But is there anyone you're still being contacted by?
Being contacted by? Contacted?
I don't think so, I haven't met anyone either
So the Ogikubo* girl didn't work out either
*Ogikubo is a town outside of Tokyo
Didn't work out... did I contact her?
Ehhh? That's scary!
I think Noda contacted her though...
He sold him out!
This guy!
She said "I got a message from Komiya" though...
Through line?
Yeah, with Line.
I don't use Line though
Oh, via mail then
Mail?
She got several messages from you saying
"I'm nearby so let's hang out" is what she said
What about that? Did it go well?
No...
Ahh, I'm sorry, apologies for interrupting you
Thank you very much!
He's sulking
He's sulking so bad
There's small grains of truth here, but this is his first ambush
Still not knowing whether this situation is real...
He stares at the business card he received
They're taking pics
Hurry up, you got a new joke to do
And your legs hurt...
Of course, he has the memory of doing this
He's still looking at the card...
He rationally takes in the situation
Blatantly hangs his head
Afterwards
He reports the details to his manager
You did go right?
To the cabaret club
Yeah, I did end up going
With the shock of knowing that the article is going to be released
We end this day here
The day after the magazine's assault.
Komiya is called out to the office to discuss the facts regarding the article
This is pretty heavy
We also contacted the office beforehand
and had them set up some hidden cameras
This is an amazing prank
Basically, the article will publish
Probably around next week it seems
When did you go to Atami?
Well, sometime around last month?
Noda-san, and... just you two?
On vacation?
So you traveled, and at night, you went to the clubs?
That's right
Noda said that he wanted to go
Oh, Noda said he wanted to go?
Yeah
He's like a child
The reporter said
You met a woman in Ogikubo
and exchanged contact info?
That was Noda
He's been bringing up Noda a lot
He's really selling him out
Noda exchanged the contact info?
Noda probably traded numbers
And when we usually go to Kouenji
Noda probably contacted her
Repeatedly selling out his senior comedian, Onigashima's Aiamu Noda
Komiya tries to save himself, however...
In these days
And even an issue involving a woman, this article...
if it releases
Things would not be looking very good
If there were more extreme acts done
You could lose some commercial jobs or sponsors
And you might not be able to
perform on some of your regular shows
I see
Just doing the late night shows is fine though
No, that's not good...
Not allowed even though it's late night...
"Late night only is ok"...
If you could do this in moderation...
Being scorned with a rational argument
Komiya can only bow his head
However, the manager leaves his seat...
But all I did was go...
That's right
He's single too
I just went to a store
He's really saying a lot
Is it really that big a deal?
How does everyone else avoid this in life?
I didn't do anything
Why is he talking to himself out loud like that?
Talking to himself in a matter of fact tone
His anxiousness explodes
And then...
Aida usually goes to cabaret clubs more than myself
And he goes to visit prostitutes as well
He talks a lot
He snitches on his partner's unrelated nighttime activities
In terms of popularity
he has less so nothing's been said
Aida uses me as a shield
It's best to tell Tomita that as well
Basically, the article will publish around next week
so please prepare yourself for that
With that part being real, he feels down
From here, in order to prepare for the "Real" reveal
With the help of actors, we'll make him think the article will not release, and this is a TV prank
and he will become more relaxed
I see...
The first part of the "Maybe this is a prank" block
An interview which reeks of lies, from a show that reeks of more lies
This show is called "Cupid's Love Talk"
Cupid's Love Talk...
Yes
Everytime we bring a guest to the studio
and we solve some love problems
on this talk variety show
Ok
We'll be asking you a few questions
so we're pleased to be working with you
This was supposed to be an interview about romance, however...
It's common to go out to the countryside
When you visit the countryside, do you like to play around?
Well, you see...
I go to the onsen, the cabaret clubs, and the like
Do you like cabaret clubs?
I guess so, it's nice to go when you want to drink with women
For sure, you must be popular when you go there right?
I mean, you're famous...
I'm thinking that's all "Business Talk" though...
Ah, is that so?
What do you like specifically about the clubs?
I don't like them that much, but I don't...
With that, Komiya has found the connection with the "prank"
And gives an "I'm saved" expression
And then
Ah, camera!
He's looking for the camera!
He surveys his surroundings
Camera found
And then...
a smile
So straightforward
Now that he's under the impression that this is a "Scandal Release Prank"
Finally, the man Komiya will suspect as a prank instigator
Onigashima's Aiamu Noda invites him to dinner
giving off the feel that the prank reveal will happen soon
The way he sat like he's going to
leave soon is pretty suspicious
And then...
What? What is it?
He's searching
What are you peeking at?
C'mon, I've had enough of this
What?
Nevermind
"I already know so hurry up and reveal the prank", he feels
And after that...
Do you know something
I do not know what you are talking about
About the Atami thing
What Atami thing?
A woman seemed to leak something...
Eh? Uhhh... eh?
Eh? What's that?
She is... did...
leaked...
I got ambushed
Ehhhh...
What, why are you laughing?
What is it?
With Noda's naturally atrocious acting
Komiya's suspicions have been confirmed
With that...
From now, we enter the main portion of the plan
Finally, we present the "Truth"
Woah!
To Komiya, who thinks this is all a prank
Finally, we present the "Truth"
Oh!
You surprised me
He looks pretty relieved
As the staff storm the room with cameras
He gives a "Yup, it's a prank" grimace
How're you feeling?
Is it normal to ask that now?
I'm sorry, I have to apologize
I really think that I already know...
He's not very good at lying
"I'm sorry for figuring out the prank early"
He apologizes, gazing from his pedestal
But really he's a man who's figured out nothing
By the way, umm...
What is it?
He's just holding the sign
It's like that right?
Regarding the "Komiya was going to Atami's cabaret clubs
and was playing around" thing
Wasn't there talk of an article being released?
That talk, in fact is...
A prank?
It's real
Real?
Real.
Hold on, what do you mean?
It will release?
It will
The article will release in the Weekly Girls' publication
Hold on a minute...
Hold on... what do you mean by...
What do you mean "real"?
What's this...
It's real.
Sucks right?
We just came today to convey to you the truth that the article will release
I'm not caught up in a prank right?
You're not, this is all real
What, if it's real, that's no good!
What do you mean 'real'
Normally you'd say "It was a prank"
But it's not
What do you mean "real"? The article will release?
Uhh, what about that reporter?
He's real
Huh? What??
Cause it's real
You're saying "real", what do you mean "real"??
I don't get the trick
Wait, where does it start being real?
I'll say it again
The story that you were messing around in Atami cabaret clubs
Will release
and the main office's anger is also real
Wait, isn't that bad?
I don't understand anything, what does this mean?
I've never seen a sign like that
saying "real"
normally it's "Prank" right?
Like we said, this isn't a prank
What the hell!
We used the normal prank format to come and reveal the truth to you
No no that's not needed
Are there pranks that leave this shitty of an aftertaste?
This isn't a prank
No, you say "It was a prank"
I'd say "Oh, thank god", and we'd have a few drinks. That's a prank.
What is this "real"
This isn't a prank
Saying it's not a prank would be fine if you were to put it a little more gently!
Normally you should be releasing this more secretively
A bunch of people will see this (article)
A bunch of people are gonna watch this
Hold on, my head is spinning...
I don't wanna go home... hold on...
Ehh, this is real?
What am I even saying "This is real?"
And with that, everything is real
This article was actually released correct?
Yes
When this airs
This gossip article about Komiya in Weekly Girls' will already be out.
This article isn't a big deal though right?
Yeah it really isn't
It doesn't really matter
Komiya's evilness has seeped out...
It really has
I think Komiya did a great job though
That satisfied look when Komiya looks for and finds the camera
Even when he realized that
He must have thought "I can't reveal that I know, because I'm a comedian"
Ahh, like "I wonder if this might be a prank"
So he has to play along with what he thinks is a prank, with that huge smile on his face
He really is THE HUMAN
I wonder what his new joke was...
What the heck was that brand new joke he had that day?
Next, we test various theories from around the world.
The Viewers' Theory Corner
Tonight's presenters are:
It's Miki~
Thank you.
Today we've come here but, um~
Yes.
"We've come here" you said.
Saying you came here, it's work!
We're nervous, right?
What are you nervous about?
No, no, no. It's our first time here...
It's fine, "We came here."
We actually did come here.
We came here today.
We took a plane to come here.
We've come here today.
What is this speech?
It's impossible to recover from this speech.
Mastumoto-san.
Yes?
On the IPPON Grand Prix show,
Yes, the oogiri-style improv show.
There you watch various people, but
when you're watching, what makes you say "This guy is good."?
Surprisingly when it comes to manzai,
the straight man seems to be more fitting right?
I see.
Suprisingly.
You prefer the straight man more than the funny man.
I can't say unconditionally, but surprisingly it's sometimes like that.
So, it's sometimes like that.
Is that so.
Like Football Hour's Gotou-san...
Therefore...
Sorry, you two were talking at the same time.
Calm down!
I'm not the Eight-Eared Prince Shoutoku...
You can hear two people, right?
You can hear two people, separately.
This time, we have a theory that even comedians bad at improv can become funny.
This is what we've selected.
Here it is.
Theory: "Comedians who are bad at improv are funnier when they're drunk."
Ah, I get it.
They're better if they're drunk.
That's right.
Let's investigate the theory: "Comedians who are bad at improv are funnier when they're drunk."
Dining-with-strangers Queen Challenge. Yay~!
It's Amaki Jun.
This time, while filming a fake program,
I feel bad for them
these comedians bad at improv will have fun drinking.
For saying "they're bad at improv"
Otake huh...
Tooth!
That's a strong start.
Once they've had plenty to drink,
they'll receive their improv challenge.
Ah, that's the good stuff.
That's good!
They pound glass after glass.
They may be bad at improv but these three are good at drinking.
Then.
Fukuoka.
Nagasaki.
Yamagata.
They continue drinking for three hours.
Amazing.
Amazing, 12 drinks.
They've become completely dead drunk.
Hmm, I want to go a trip, just the two of us.
For our main purpose, we move to the TBS studios.
There's a strange atmosphere.
On this improv set, we'll test our theory.
So sudden.
Open this, open this.
Heigh-ho.
Huh?
Wait a minute, what's this?
I've been waiting for you.
No, no. Everyone's been waiting.
What do you mean?
Alright.
What is this? What, what?
No, no, no.
What? What? What's this?
We've already started.
What? What? What? What's this?
No, no.
They're incredible.
What, what? Wait a minute.
Kasuga, please sit.
For now, sit down. Ok.
I don't know.
Wait, wait, wait.
That's enough.
Ah, that's good. You turned out great
That's good.
Abareru-kun, thanks.
This is really bad.
You guys are Wednesday Downtown.
Wait, wait, wait.
What? Kawashima-san,
Wait a minute! What, what, what?
Have a look.
It's everyone's favorite.
What, what, what?
Hmmm, college girls.
So much work for Kawashima-san
Sit, you! Quick.
Hurry up and sit, you.
Well then, what theory is it?
Ah, answering a quiz, something about answering a quiz while drunk.
Ah, I see.
About boisterously answering the quiz.
That's why we're drunk.
Let's do some improv!
What did you say?
"Let's do some improv!"
Why would we improv? There's no way
Astute!
Eh?
Today's investigation is:
"Comedians that are bad at improv are funnier when they're drunk."
Seriously?!.. wa-wait, wait.
Thank you.
Could you be quiet a little
Eh, do improv right now? In this state?
Yes, everyone's energetic improv.
This is a show right now?
You already know that.
Your-
It's Wednesday.
Wednesday.
Kawashima will judge when their improv answers are funny.
Too hard!
Will they really be funnier when drunk?
Dead drunk improv start.
Well, let's get started.
The first question is:
What's the stage name of the sumo wrestler who went 10 years without a win and retired?
This is a good one, huh?
This is too sudden
Ah, he's quick.
Quick.
The stage name.
Which one? This one? This one?
I'll go, I'll go. I've got it. I've got it.
Alright, Otake-san. Let's see.
Looking forward to it.
I'M DONE!
Ok.
The sumo wrestler's stage name?
Sweet shrimp.
Ah~ close. Good point though.
Why is it no good?
If it was the character for "shrimp" you would've been fine
I see
So it's about that
The hell is this diligence
Well, cause I'm your senior
Okay Abareru-kun!
Tell us the name of the wrestler!
Stoic
Ah I get it
Got one!
Kasuga-san, let's go
The name of the wrestler who didn't even win once
Osumo-chan!
That wasn't it
Go for it Otake-san!
Vinegar
Yeah that's good!
Was it Su(Vinegar)?
Okay you got it.
That made me happy
With an answer he could not have provided if he was sober
Otake splendidly gets a point
Are they still making him drink?
Onto the next theme...
What was the message Momotaro sent to the demons before going to the demon island?
Have a think
This is getting messed up.
Does he think that's some kind of ultra miracle water?
They're really picking up the pace now
Huh? To the demon island?
He goes there right?
You must get this
Got it!
Go for it Kasuga-san!
Do you have space for 4 people today?
Yay!!
Yeah that's good
Kasuga, who is only slightly drunk
Gets a point with a genuine answer
That's kind of embarrassing
If Downtown were to change their name to ___ &____ what would be it be?
It's gotta be this...
Alright Abareru-kun, what would be their new name?
"The Blonde Yakuzas"
Are you alright?
You happy with that one?
You sure that was it?
It's a buzzer for me
This dude is just...
His face is turning pale
What would Downtown change their name to?
"Gangster organization"
Are you ok?
He's drunk!
When they watch this live, they're gonna be furious at you, you know
He's drinking alcohol
No uh, it can't be helped
You were like that stupid Amuro Ray guy
Otake-san, what would be downtown's new name?
It's cause they're two different characters alright?
The breast meat & the thigh meat
That one was funny
Yeah it was
The breast meat and
The thigh meat yeah
Cause they're playing separate characters
Who would be someone unexpected to have released a nude photo book?
Next one could be funny
Okay okay!
Come on, let's go one by one
Huh? Whatcha say?
What did you say again?
Check by yourself please
Otake is gone
Ok, go ahead
Issei Sakamoto
This was wrong huh?
It is wet instead
Sorry, I'm gonna go take a leak
Are you going to go pee?
Sorry
I'll do this one too
That was close
What's up with you anyway?
Well, I'm not drunk so
Give us one, we're drunk so give us an example.
Please give us one example
I'm just saying he should have one
Instead of only us giving you answers
What would you write if it was you?
Yeah we want a hint from you
Provide us an example
He ain't gonna give us a hint guys
No he'll give us something more like "This answer is the correct one"
You're the improv legend
I'm not a legend
You've never failed with improv
That's right
Expect, we're being serious
I have to be serious okay?
Reina from Max
I had to be serious
That was very good
We got the correct answer!
As you can see, here are the points so far
They are having a blast
And now, the last question
What would be a comedian with the nickname "A stupid ass without a punchline"?
What did you say?
Kasuga-san, go for it
A stupid ass without a punchline is Chiemi Blouson
It's the alcohol talking
A bell is no good
Give me the buzzer
Okay, that's good is it?
Yup yup yup
Kasuga-san
Who would be a stupid ass without a punchline?
* A respected TV-presenter and actor
Hide-chan (Hideyuki Nakayama)*
You okay?
Wow... that's
He's drunk
This is really bad
Are you alright?
You've got courage for sure
There are many Hide-chans
He's way too drunk now
Well, you wrote "chan" so...
My Hide-chan is not the one everyone else thinks it is
When you get the bell it goes straight to air you know.
No no no
In conclusion, when you drink alcohol you dare to say more
Just terrible
It was pretty funny though
This was bad
We just want you to understand that they were drinking
They were not serious
It's because it was improv
Exactly exactly
Well of course...
That's why
we don't think downtown is a gangster organization
No that's fine
cause we actually are so
No no we're not
We have another one
So people who have been to a highway...
Highway?
Been to..
I'm pretty certain there are people who have been to highways
What are you on about?
Going there...
You mean more like people who has been on them right?
Correct
People who have been on them
Exactly, that
There are service areas
And you go to them right...?
Stopped at one!
Yeah I've stopped at one.
Right?
There's lots of food at these service areas
Any classic foods you think of?
I wonder...
Corn dog
Corn dog!
Potacon!
Potacon!?
It's bacon inside potatoes that's on a stick
We're asking about staples though
They have them around
Everyone is confused
We're only on #2, don't throw a special ones
Melon pan
Ah I see
Exactly
Soft serve
Right!
We have a strong image of them
Soft serve at service areas
Cause they are everywhere
Yeah I guess we do
This is the theory
Theory: There's no service area that doesn't sell soft serve
They have them everywhere don't they?
Exactly
Theory: There's no service area that doesn't sell soft serve
How will this go?
And so:
I'm sure they all have it
Here are the people who will help us with the verification this time!
Thank you very much!
Okatsu loves these
In addition to soft serve, we're also investigating the classic corn dog and melon pan
The three participants
will visit each of the service areas along the Tomei Expressway
Wow this is tough
They will then check if these three items are sold
What do you guys think will be the best?
I'm thinking the corn dogs
And you?
I think soft serve
The wishes of the participants decides who is in charge of what item
The winner is whoever has bought their respective item until the last stop
In other words, if the item isn't sold, you drop out
We drop out?
Correct
So if you picked an item that's available everywhere
you get to be on TV for longer am I right?
Exactly
And with that,
we're off to our first stop: Kouhoku parking area
You're married right?
Yes I am.
He has a daughter as well
She's 5 years old
5?
Oh I see
She does ballet, gymnastics and judo.
Ballet and judo are opposites!
On Saturdays mornings she has ballet and judo in the evenings
That was apparently very funny
While the bus is running, have arrive at the first location, Kouhoku Parking Area
We're expecting to find them aren't we?
No one's dropping out on the first stop
The investigation begins
Yes, investigation just begun
And without delay
There's one immediately!
A bakery!
There's melon pan, huh
Found it!
Yay!
I got a brioche melon pan
This is a good sign
They have them
I'm a bit anxious...
There's a...
Shonan gold!
Ah, it exists
They have it!
Hokkaido Soft Serve
Of course they have it
Look below it please
Corn dog for 250 yen
We go it!
Yay!
Soft serve and corn dog gets cleared right away
That looks delicious!
Here we go!
Oh they eat it?
They gotta eat it?
Delishhh!
This gotta be tough
The deliciousness is in the yokozuna class
It's a fusion of delicious and a Hak...
Next they will be arriving at the "Ebina Service Area"
That was sad
It can't be helped
Morita clears his right away with the famous Ebina melon pan
We sold 27,000 of these in two days
You sold 27,000!?
That's amazing
The number of sales has been certified by the Guinness World Records
And then,
A Yubari melon one right?
They have corn dogs!
Yahoo!
Yay!
They had all of them
They complete all of the three items this time as well
This is tough
How's the world class taste?
Yeah it's really different than the last one
How is it different?
It's more delicious
I mean I say delicious but...
It's strange that it doesn't really go all the way in
Um... It's really delicious
deliiiirious
However something's strange with Morita
They didn't even ask why he said that.
Are you full?
Yeah I'm getting there
A feeling of fullness seems to have hit him
Well I guess so
Incidentally, This time we introduce a rule that the person must finish the product
This'll make you full for sure
And at our third stop, Nakai Parking Area
We struck a double!
Corn dog
And soft serve
Yay!
Immediately!
We did it!
While Tsuneda and Akatsu found theirs smoothly...
Uh the melon pan's gotta be inside for sure
Morita goes inside the shop for his search
That's rough
That's right
At that point
Uh!
Aah aah!
Oh no its wrong. This is Anpan
You gotta be kidding me
Custard... Cream...
Cream pan... Cream pan...
Don't have them already?
What about the outside?
Unfortunately, They didn't sell any
Ah I see...
Great work!
No way!
You're kidding me!
You've dropped out.
No way. I can't believe it
Is it ok if I'm in the car chatting?
Please go home
And with that, on the third Nakai parking area stop, Melon pan Morita drops out quickly
Haha, Melon pan Morita
And so,
Yup I'm feeling it
Don't you think we can exchange just once?
No
Ok...
Delition!
They gotta be full
Kakuryuu?
That's right
It's going very well for out two contestants
Sorrie
Haha sorrie
Is he alright?
It seems like he's approaching his full stomach limit
Well of course
Ice cream seems like the toughest one
At which point, at the 7th spot, Ashitaka Parking Area
The second person to drop out is:
Do you have corn dogs?
No we don't.
Huh?
You serious?
Didn't have any huh
This for real?
You were right about the soft serve
Okatsu san...
Indeed
You've dropped out
Really?
I can't believe it
And with that,
Corn dog Okatsu drops out
Soft serve Tsuneda is left alone
We've arrived at our 8th stop, Fujikawa service area
Fujikawa
As expected, they found soft serve here as well
They have them everywhere
I guess so
Right
Somehow he manages to finish it
There aren't any places that don't have them
Without failure, the service areas keep selling and he keeps eating
It's been 9 hours since the start of the recording and he's completed 10 soft serves
9 hours!
This has been a big
time waster for me
Tsuneda realizes that
even if he wins it will still be a waste
And so,
We've arrived at our 11th stop, Ogasa parking area
Around here is pretty dark now...
Yeah it's dark, it's already evening
Are you sure they have it?
Let's have it
Let's have it..
You seem tired
No no
Hmm?
The search begins promptly inside the shop as usual
But they can't quite find it
Do you perhaps have soft serve?
Sorry, we don't do soft serve here
Really?
Which means... this is the end
Can't be real
Really!?
Yes
They don't
right
have it
correct
If I may, why don't you sell any here?
Uhm well,
we used to sell it before
Because of various circumstances...
Since February this year, sorry
Well that's it then. There are shops that don't have it
Tsuneda, this is the championship
We did it...
Unwittingly, if it wasn't for Ogasa parking area,
they would have sold it all the way until Sakurajima service area in Kagoshima prefecture.
So they do it sell it everywhere
Yes
So that was the result!
If you guys called them beforehand he could've finished it
That's right but...
If we did we'd all be very sorry for Tsuneda-san
He'd have to eat sooo much soft serve
What did you think? Nimura-san.
I mean there are a lot of different flavors depending on where you get it.
It was fun
Right?
If we could try them all together sometime that would be great. Ok so that's it!
That was us from "Viewers' Theory Corner"
That was such a forced ending!
Check out our Facebook and Website for more Wednesday Downtown! This video was subbed by a community run project called the Wednesday Downtown project. Thanks for watching!
m 0 0  l 1800 0  1800 158  0 158
Next week: Real Life JoJo Transmission Tower returns!
In the ruins of a mountain
No what is this
You can't escape unless you lure in a substitute
So I'm camping right now
A tribute to ever-growing harshness and betrayal of human life
And also,
Are there people who actually call themselves breast maniacs!?