This is Suiyoubi no Downtown
Welcome everyone!
MC: Hamada Masatoshi
(Downtown)
Hori Miona
Matsumoto Hitoshi
(Downtown)
Ogi Hiroaki
(Ogi Yahagi)
Ōkubo Kayoko
(Oasiz)
So let's begin. Here's the first presenter!
Come in!
It's Fujimon!
Yes, yes. Hello, hello
Presenter:
Fujimoto Toshifumi
(FUJIWARA)
Hello everyone!
Fujimonty, isn't it?
Fujimonty
What's Fujimonty?
So everyone, I know it's out of the blue but→
have you seen any people who have had plastic surgery?
There are, yes
Well, there are some
There are but you
wouldn't tell the person
Of course you can't say "ah, you've had surgery" and point it out to them
No, you can't
You can't say that for sure
It's too hard
Of course not
So with that,
here's the theory I've brought here today:
Theory: If a female celebrity you haven't seen for a long time has had loads of plastic surgery, it's hard to point it out
You made it that hard?
(Ōkubo) Someone they
haven't seen in a while
Maybe someone like
Hamada-san could say it jokingly
No, I don't think I would
Really?
Once when I was on a shoot with Ogi,
There was one person
there who'd had it done
I think I know who you mean
Who?
It has to be that shoot
Right
And when that person wasn't around,
Ogi came up to me and said →
"Jeez..."
"They were so different, I laughed"
But I don't think they heard him
There were a few people there.
That person was so bad
They'd done it that much?
Yes, so much.
Even Fujimoto-san was laughing
I didn't laugh!
I kept in, unlike Ogi
Isn't "keeping it in" strange too?
Coming up...
When a female celebrity with makeup in the style of plastic surgery appears,
How will the comedians react?
And then...
Unsuccessful comedians face off!
Who's the best at taking bentos from backstage home?
★Subbed by fmck fansubs★
reddit.com/u/fmckfansubs
patreon.com/fmck
Theory: If a female celebrity you haven't seen for a long time has had loads of plastic surgery, it's hard to point it out
So, our first targets are...
Alright!
It's Tokyo Shopping Street Tour!
Daian
Tsuda Atsuhiro
Yūsuke
And the person who'll be our plant,
Nīyama Chiharu
the first female celebrity we
haven't seen in a while...
We give Nīyama a makeover
using special makeup in the style of plastic surgery
She'll appear midway through as a guest
in Daian's fake town-exploration shoot
Itadakimasu
Hot!
This would really burn me
Do it! You got so far already
After they've roamed around a little,
at last...
We send in the plastic surgery monster
And we haven't told Daian about the guest,
so it will be a surprise appearance
It says we've got a special guest who comes to this restaurant often when they're in Togoshi Ginza
Oh? It's Nīyama Chiharu-san?
Wow, really? Come in!
Seriously?
Hello
Hello! I'm looking forward to working with you today. I'm Nīyama Chiharu
Eye bags
Lips
We've added as much volume
as possible to her eye bags and lips
An extremely gaudy plastic face
This is Daian's
reaction to seeing it
Hello. How do you do?
Hello
All their excitement's gone
Nice to meet you.
Yes, I'm excited
They don't know what to do
We're Daian. Pleased to meet you
As expected, they can feel something's wrong
but they didn't say anything
Then...
Do you come to this area often?
From the time I debuted, my office has been in Meguro so...
So I've spent time walking and eating in these streets
He can't even look at her face
I haven't been able to do it recently of course
Yūsuke's not looking anymore
But I'm hoping we'll be able to do it again soon
He will
If he looks, he'll laugh
That's true
I think so
(Nīyama) So I can go with my
daughter and teach her the custom
This is not good
He's looking at her from the side!
It's just too perfect
How old are you now...
I'm 40
Wow!
You don't look it. Really, you haven't changed at all
Oh, really?
You haven't changed at all
It's clear that isn't that the case
Tsuda tells a lie he didn't have to tell
And then...
Staff) Alright, it's OK. We're done at this restaurant
Staff) Daian, could you two wait here for a little while?
We let Daian have some alone time...
You seriously...
You're so bad
It's so bad
Did she just do it?
Because she's still not used to it
Everyone's finding out soon if that's the case
Everyone will know
Seriously, it's like Angelina Jolie
She got Angelina Jolie lips
It's like Obake no Q-Tarō, isn't it?
The lips, really
Can she really change that much?
She used to be cute, before
Seems she's been through a lot
They're getting excited talking about her plastic surgery in secret
Ogi was like this too
Totally,
I remember
I know
You were like this, Ogi
And then when filming restarts...
the group go to a Korean food restaurant recommended by their special guest
And then...
Staff) Sorry, we need to fix your makeup Nīyama-san
They fix the makeup on her bulging lips
Seeing this, Daian...
can't stand it and start to laugh
Then when she accentuates
her mouth while eating...
He laughed!
She's going to notice
He's just laughing
She can't blow
I'd laugh if I were them
Nīyama's doing it
She's making them laugh
(Ogi) It looks like it
Honestly
Nīyama-san, need any water?
(Nīyama) I'm fine, thank you
It's really good. Wow
(Yūsuke) Like, the flavor is...
This is hopeless
Tsuda...
Isn't he bad?
Why so much...
He's out of control
Nīyama-san overdid it
Because Nīyama-san
can't see her own face, right?
She can't, and she's
trying to make them laugh
It's her fault too
A mosquito stung me
What time of the year do mosquitoes sting you?
Today's the coldest day in 20 years
Why did a mosquito...
(Tsuda) What's up with this guy?
Why at a Korean restaurant...
They're trying to make it about something else
Yeah
Like 'look, we're laughing
at something else!'
Why did a mosquito sting you? This guy...
They try to fake it but...
for some reason the plastic surgery makes them crack up and they can't stop laughing
Manager
Then, in the car on the way to their next location
She was different when she was on TV a year or two ago
Isn't anyone she knows saying anything?
Like her makeup artist or manager
Well I guess it's hard to tell someone that
Can they say it casually?
Even if they do...
That might be OK
She might say something like "Sure"
No but it's... What should we do?
We're not going to say, are we?
Although they considered pointing it out...
in the end Daian did not bring up the surgery all day
But they might as well have
Right? Since they laughed so hard
And after the segment with Nīyama is over...
and Daian are alone,
it's time for the...
Prank Reveal
Staff) How was today?
I want to come here again
It was fun, wasn't it?
Staff) Is there anything on your mind about today?
Those lips were incredible...
Staff) Honestly, what did you think when you saw them?
I was surprised. Like...
But you hear about people doing stuff like that sometimes
You can't mention it
Staff) By the way
Staff) This show isn't "Tokyo Shopping Street Tour"
Huh?
I see
(Yūsuke) What do you mean?
Like a psychopath. Scary
Suiyoubi no Downtown, right?
So...
I heard all of it
You laughed too much! From the start
Theory: If a female celebrity you haven't seen for a long time has had loads of plastic surgery, it's hard to point it out
What is this?
It's just your lips, right?
It's not just my lips!
Your eyelids are so weird
Yes, yes
Under them?
That's right. The puffy eye bags that are trendy now
Cheekbones too?
No, these are all mine
Ah...
Ah... sorry...
(Nīyama) You're just insulting me now
And so, our next targets are...
Hello! We're Ginshari!
Ginshari
Hashimoto Nao
Unagi Kazuhiro
We've arrived
Yes we have
And the person who'll be our plant,
Anzai Hiroko
the second female celebrity we
haven't seen in a while...
A special guest
I didn't know
I'm nervous
Well then, shall we call her in?
It's Anzai Hiroko-san! Please come in
Hello
Hello, welcome, thank you for coming
Anzai-san
Hello, I'm Anzai Hiroko
This time, we've increased
the level of surgery
Eye
bags
Lips
Surgery Level
As well as her lips and eye bags,
Nose bridge
we've Avatar-ized her nose
Hello. Seriously?
Seriously? Seriously?
Hello!
Hello, welcome, thank you for coming
Hello, thank you.
I'm Anzai Hiroko
His face now
They can't hold it in
It's coming out
Look at Hashimoto
No, she's my age
Seriously?
Ah, I'm happy. Thank you
From gravure, right?
I knew this would be funny
Manager
And, like before,
when Anzai and the staff leave them alone...
Do you remember how her face used to look?
Back then? I do but...
She was in her teens then, wasn't she?
Well, that...
Like it's...
I don't even know if I can look properly
She's so different compared to back then
I don't mean anything bad by it but...
It's like Kaiji
You can't tell her that
I definitely won't
As expected her new face is a hot topic
But they don't seem to be mentioning it to her so...
I just love Korea
I go there all the time
What do you go there for? The food?
For the food and for beauty
Ah, beauty too
For things like Yomogi steaming, right?
That's right, that's right
For perspiration
The one that that goes up your butt?
Yeah, yeah. Like that
With the words "Korea" and "beauty",
we hinted at
plastic surgery but...
They didn't bite
Manager
However, when they're alone again
To tell you the truth, I don't even know if it's her
No, it's her. It is.
That's her voice. It's fine
I didn't really know her voice
Her voice is just like that...
Because I mostly know her from photos
She hasn't changed that drastically, has she?
She has, you know. She's changed too much...
Isn't it just a little?
It's not a little. It's not
She's a totally different person
That being said, I don't really mind
Yes, yes
In the end, it's all about whether she's happy with it or not
I guess
Hashimoto is a progressive comedian, respectful of diversity
So once again, the shoot ends without surgery being mentioned
(Staff) "Tokyo Shopping Street Tour"
isn't the name of this show
Prank Reveal
Wait a moment. Seriously
I think there's only one show it could be
Suiyoubi?
What else?
Woah, hold on a minute. This is so bad
It has to be Anzai-san
Theory: If a female celebrity you haven't seen for a long time has had loads of plastic surgery, it's hard to point it out
So after she explains today's
theory to them...
There's no way we could
It's impossible
What kind of theory is this?
It's obviously impossible, right?
Why didn't you mention it?
Huh, so you're really her?
I am
You are... Sorry, sorry
Huh, so it's okay to tell you that?
That you've done loads of surgery
So you're going public about it?
Unagi thinks the plastic surgery is real
And our last targets are...
It's Tokyo Shopping Street Tour!
Yay!
Hamaie Ryūichi
Kamaitachi
Yamauchi Kenji
And our plant is...
Nīyama Chiharu, with even
more plasticity
Nīyama Chiharu-san? Come in!
We haven't met before
That's right
(Nīyama) Hello
Hello
Nīyama Chiharu-san? Come in!
We haven't met before
That's right
Hello
Nice to meet you. I'm looking forward to today
This time, in addition to her eyes and lips,
Eye
bags
Lips
Surgery Level
we've given her a prosthetic nose too
Nose
(Nīyama) Hello!
Come in, Nīyama Chiharu-san!
(Nīyama) Ah, that's right
We haven't met before
(Nīyama) Ah, hello
Hello
Nice to meet you.
I'm looking forward to today
Yamauchi.. Ah, Hamaie's laughing. Stop!
Hamaie-san
Stop it Hamaie
I'm so happy
That's right, we haven't met before
I come here fairly often
(Yamauchi) Ah, we don't...
Hamaie has to stop
Hamaie's laughing, seriously
He can't do that
(Yamauchi) We weren't expecting it but
our first shoot was in Togoshi Ginza.
Out of Tokyo's shopping streets...
He's become like Furuhata
TL Note: Musician Furuhata Ninzaburō poses like that
it's the shopping street we know best.
(Nīyama) Ah
He is
Yamauchi's very good
Huh, Hamaie-san, are you okay? What happened?
I'm fine. Excuse me
Faced with this deadly weapon,
right from the start, Hamaie can't stop laughing
And then...
There's a Korean restaurant nearby
The gomtang soup there is really good
What's "gomtang"?
I've heard of it
It's full of collagen
So it makes you plump and soft
You definitely seem plump
Really? Yesterday I had some actually
So if you eat that your skin fills up
Like jelly
Just like how Korean cosmetics contain capsaicin to make your lips swollen
They really are
Huh? I'm so happy. Is that a compliment?
(Nīyama) It's really popular now
They're really plump
Although he doesn't use
the term 'plastic surgery'...
Yamauchi boldy mentions her lips
And then...
Have you changed your makeup?
My makeup...
As I approached my 40s,
I've started using nothing but drug store makeup that doesn't cost a lot
thinking it'd be good to make a change
Today it's all drug store makeup
(Nīyama) Yes
Plump... They're so plump
Like, compared to how I remember you, they're so plump
Ah, really?
The drug store
Halfway through! There's no coffee left
Yes, it's that good
It has to be something special to do that
Once again, Nīyama and the staff leave them alone
Her face is weird
Manager
I almost made a joke about it
Thinking it was a joke where a fake person comes out
Like I was going to say "Who are you?"
I was about to say "you're fake, right"
That was really close
And can you stop with all that beauty talk?
Like how you were talking about how plump her lips are
Well there are people who like that kind of thing
I guess so, sure
Fat lips must be fashionable
Although...
Nīyama Chiharu-san probably thinks it's a good idea
Manager) Probably
So we shouldn't really worry about it
Kamaichi say if she's okay with it,
the outside world shouldn't complain
However...
Were you popular? In your schooldays
In school but also...
Recently men have been checking me out even more than back then
I think
Wow! This is going to give my skin a boost
It's boosted plenty already
It is?
Yeah
Isn't it already the best already now?
It's good now?
It's not good to boost it too much
Now's already enough
If you become even more attractive than this,
everyone will look at you too much
So now's a good time to stop
Really?
Seriously, right now, this is enough
You're beautiful
(Nīyama) Really?
"You shouldn't get more surgery", they tell her in a roundabout way
Is she trying to get them even puffier?
It seems so
She's had her lips done
Ah, definitely
She's totally different
Her nose's different too
Now I look at it, it seems so
Horipro will have to stop her, right?
TL Note: Talent agency
Ah but she herself said she's good now
She did. Because...
It's like manzai. Sometimes you end up having no idea what's going on
You try to keep fixing it
And it stops being funny
So you fix it and fix it and you don't know what's funny anymore
One month before M-1?
Around then
That time?
We fixed it too much and didn't know
Nīyama-san's now a month before M-1
Prank Reveal
Staff) Good work
Ah, the lips
It has to be the lips
Not just them. Everything, right?
You're the Wednesday people, aren't you?
Staff) Are you sure?
It definitely feels like it
Staff) What do you think the theory is?
"Nīyama Chiharu's had surgery"
It wouldn't be so simple
As before, Nīyama explains the theory
Theory: If a female celebrity you haven't seen for a long time has had loads of plastic surgery, it's hard to point it out
It is
But that's not a theory
That's hard to do
You knew before investigating, surely
We're not going to say "You've had surgery!"
Only an outsider would say such a thing
So, the result is:
People are free to have surgery and it's not something to point out
(Ogi) Great
Wow, amazing
Well...
It was done perfectly
Right?
And it looked so good too
The surgery
Yeah
And Anzai Hiroko-san...
What an excellent choice
Really,
it seemed so plausible
Like if Anzai Hiroko-san
did have surgery...
"That'd be her face"
if she were to get surgery
Daian laughed the most, right?
That was terrible
Right
Tsuda was so bad
Tsuda was, really.
And the inside of his mouth...
Even though it was full,
he burst out laughing
You could see everything inside
He went that far
despite being on camera
If we were to progress it a bit further...
We could give them 3 nostrils
Like what would people do then?
They'd probably say in that case
They'd say something
(Ogi) They'd say something
They would
Well...
What would they say?
Huh...
Huh... What happened?
Here's our next presenters.
Come in!
Yes, it's Shizzle!
Presenters:
Ikeda Kazuma / Murakami Jun
(Shizzle)
Thank you, hello.
We're Shizzle!
Long time no see, Shizzle
For our segment today,
everyone...
Do you eat the bentos in the green room?
Yes
I do sometimes
Yeah, I do
And Hori-san,
how about...
Taking a bento from there home?
Really?!
Yes, I do
Ah, really?
Huh?
Three meals a day isn't enough so...
Huh?!
I eat about 5 or 6
Just like Rickson Gracie
Oh, really?
Breathing?
Can you do that cool breathing?
(Ogi) Rickson's breathing
She can't
She probably doesn't know who he is
I definitely don't take them home
Ogi, do you take them home?
Definitely
Definitely?
It's just embarrassing
First of all, the act of taking one
home is embarassing
It's not embarrassing
Such a simple reason
But it's unseemly,
carrying it around
Well, sure. Put it in a bag
And I don't think of them
as being left over
I think of them as being for the crew
Fantastic
So taking them is wrong
I see
Today,
we bring you a theory
related to those bentos
Here it is
Yes!
Unsuccessful Comedian Competition:
The battle to decide the King of the Taking Bentos from Backstage Home
(Ōkubo) Oh no!
I don't like this
Oh, sounds funny
You know, young comedians
with no money
will surely take home
not just 1 or 2
I see
but a large amount of bentos
There's a tendency, yes
Today we'll find out who's the best at it
By the way, what about you?
The truth is, Ikeda here...
Yes
You?
has a bit of a habit of taking them home
Yes. Well, however...
I've only found out now that this is an "unsuccessful comedian battle"
Ah, they got you, did they?
I'd understand if it were "not successful"
but "unsuccessful" is a bit...
It's like "in the future too"
It's true
This is the first I've seen of it
Unsuccessful Comedian Competition:
The battle to decide the King of the Taking Bentos from Backstage Home
For this, we surveyed comedians and managers from each office
to find comedians with a habit of taking bentos home. Of those with the most votes, 7 have been entered into the competition
The first is...
Hey
Hi
Target:
Shizzle
Ikeda Kazuma
Nominator:
Shizzle
Murakami Jun
I've never seen him not take catering or bentos home so...
In 18 years
As soon as Ikeda enters the green room...
Hey, wait a moment. What's this?
Huh, what's all this?
There are bentos
Don't you wish they'd told us?
I ate before coming here, unfortunately
They don't usually but still...
Today, we've invited the comedians to a fake segment in
the show "Dream East-West Gag Battle"
and prepared this room as green room for the VTR material
Because it's a large-scale special program,
the bentos are numerous and luxurious
Maisen
Mini burger
Sandwich
Origin Bento
Torikyū
Tsutaya
Furthermore...
Oh, it's just us?
We're last so it seems people were taking turns in here
Ah, really?
Yes, this is a green room that comedians shooting material take turns using
And they're the last ones
G Takashi
Shiomariachi
Shizzle
TEAM Kondō
Perfect conditions for taking bentos home
At this point, Ikeda...
Do you have something like a bag...
(Staff) One moment, yes
Ah, is it alright?
Sorry to trouble you, thank you
He orders a bag
from the program staff
A bag? They're not even free anymore
It's that...
I came here with a small bag
I can't fit so much. What should I do?
Huh, what's this? It's so good
It's because it's a new year special
Great. So that's why?
Then...
Better than Messi?
What... ...dding ...ally
TL Note: He's only saying some of the words
What... kidd...
Thank you very much
After they've finished shooting material...
Murakami leaves the green room first
and starts monitoring in another room
Then...
He's standing there so much
He keeps looking and looking
Because he's alone
He's already taken 2
Oh, he's stacking them up
First he secures 2 of the
popular Torikyū bentos
Torikyū (Karaage Bento)
Torikyū (Special Bento)
And then...
he puts that bag in his rucksack
He travels by motorbike
Right now he's planning, in his head
So Ikeda can't carry things in his hands
Next...
4 Maisen
Maisen
(pork fillet cutlet sandwich)
(shrimp cutlet sandwich)
and then...
another 2 Torikyū
Torikyū (Karaage Bento)
Torikyū (Special Bento)
Woah... This is offensive
*tuts*
He tutted! What was it for? What?
"It doesn't fit"
He then fills the empty space
with snacks and cup ramen
Prices are based on our research
Choco pie
Jagarico (chips)
Cup ramen
Cup soup
Once his rucksack is full...
he reluctantly leaves the green room
So here's the...
Prank Reveal
This is embarrassing
I don't like this kind of thing
Evening
Good evening
Good evening. Can we go inside for a minute?
Eh, what is this?
Ikeda's eyes are like those of a frightened shoplifter
Definitely
No no
Just like he's a shoplifter
We know already
I stole nothing!
Could you please unpack your bag?
Woah... no.. woah
Could you please unpack your bag? Come on
I know what you're thinking
Ah, look how full it is
Wow... this... it's so bad
It's really bad isn't it?
Incredible!
Oh man, it's going to be so bad when my dad sees this
Here's a mini ramen
Even though he told me to stop doing stuff like this
Mini ramen, yes
Ikeda's haul consisted of:
Bento
Cutlet sandwich
Mini burger
Cup ramen
Snacks
Drinks
Total items
Cup ramens
with snacks and cans of juice,
and 4 Maisen with 4 Torikyū.
A total of 6,758 yen.
I was going to tell my wife about this on LINE
Like "I've hit the jackpot today"
Our next target is...
Target:
Makino Suteteko
Please don't forget me!
Hip hip hip!
It's hip hop!
The person nominating her is her kōhai
from the same office,
Nominator:
Ishide Nanako
She never doesn't take something home
Whenever I've been able to work with her,
Suteteko-san's always taken something home
So, after returning from shooting material...
Suteteko changes her clothes and then...
Looks like it
She's free to take anything
She knows what to do
As expected, she first takes
2 easy-to-carry Torikyū Bentos
Torikyū (Karaage Bento)
Torikyū (Special Bento)
Look how big her bag is
Unsuccessful comedians have
big bags, don't they?
And then...
She's still going?
Yes, yes
Looks like it
Maisen (mini burger)
2 Maisen mini burgers,
and 2 cutlet sandwiches.
And then...
Maisen
(pork fillet cutlet sandwich)
(shrimp cutlet sandwich)
2 of the industry favorite
Tsutaya bento
Tsutaya (Seaweed bento)
Carrying them 2 at a time
for some reason,
Origin (makunouchi)
Origin (seaweed)
She puts a total of
10 products in her rucksack
And then...
She rummages through the snacks too
She looks bad with her mask
I don't know why but it looks bad
And how she's speechless too
Appro
Baum-roll
Choco pie
Jagarico
Kabukiage
Le Monde
She's selective
Her rucksack's about to burst
And then finally...
No way. Stop already!
Cup ramen
She adds a cup ramen
With enough food on her back to last her a week if she got lost in the mountains,
she escapes the green room half running
Prank Reveal
Huh?
You dropped your tea
Suteteko-san!
Suteteko-san
Nana-chan!
You took quite a look didn't you, Suteteko-san?
No but this is really...
Yes, well, could you just take out...
No but it's...
It's...
Ah, look at this
What is this? It's like a goody bag
Suteteko's total is an astonishing 43 items
Bento
Cutlet sandwich
Mini burger
Cup ramen
Snacks
Drinks
Total items
for a score of 9,229 yen,
beating Ikeda's.
(Ishide) I said take it all out,
didn't I, Suteteko-san?
Well, actually...
The truth is I wanted to take so much more
So why did you stop?
Well, if I'd been carrying stuff in both my hands,→
wouldn't it have looked weird? I came here carrying nothing
Next, it's...
(singing theme song to Jaws)
Woah, an Indian!
Target:
Impossible
Hiru-chan
One time he took like five bentos home,
Nominator:
Impossible
Eiji
with the aim of rationing them out over a week
but he ate them all in a single day
When Hiru-chan
returns to the green room,
he takes out his clothes to make an empty bag
With a hat like a criminal
He's thinking about how to pack it all
Definitely. He's good at this
Tsutaya (Seaweed bento)
It's not
Yeah, it's not his first time
Like a convenience store clerk
Then he balances the bentos'
positions to destroy the evidence
So he knows he's doing wrong, then
Cup soup
It's scary how he's saying nothing
Can of coffee
Can of juice
Ah, wait, wait
Prank Reveal
Do you have a moment?
Huh?
Don't say 'huh?'. Just empty the bag, please
What? It's just clothes...
Look! Look!
Just clothes
He's covered it. Woah
It's just clothes
It's just clo...
I thought something was wrong
Wow!
Seriously? Huh? How embarrassing
He had 10 bentos
in his bag but
Bento
Cutlet sandwich
Cup ramen
Snacks
Drinks
Total items
Hiru-chan's total is 9,060 yen
just about losing out
to Suteteko
I'm embarrassed
You've been in the industry for 17 years already
Yeah
Even a young comedian wouldn't do this, really
I was planning to party for three days and three nights
Next...
You don't need that
you idiot
Someone who's lately been working
mainly as a garbage worker...
Target:
Machine Guns
Takizawa Shūichi
Nominator:
Machine Guns
Nishihori Ryō
Takizawa's obsession with free stuff is amazing
He derives the greatest pleasure in not having to spend a dime
So it's not that he has no money but he wants to profit
Let's see...
Thank you very much!
We're done
Without hesitation
Wow!
The moment they return
to the green room,
Can of coffee
he springs smoothly into action,
putting 5 canned coffees
into his rucksack.
It's like he's tidying up
It is like he's tidying up, isn't it?
Like a garbage worker
Then, Nishihori exits the room
leaving him alone...
He's eating
That's another bag, the stomach
Can of juice
He did it, he did it
All of them!
Scary
Can of juice
Amazing
He's doing it while eating
He's looking outside occasionally
Ah, this is good
He's not doing it while eating
but rather eating while doing it
I don't like how he's doing it
It's amazing how he can hold three of them
Can of coffee
He occasionally interrupts his work to eat...
He's not going for the bentos at all though
Yes, how come?
He's looking outside so much
One after another, with a practiced hand.
he cleans up the catering in an organized fashion
Perhaps if I were there he wouldn't go this far
Maybe I make him self conscious
Next, Takizawa takes this out of his rucksack...
A spare bag dedicated to carrying things home
Torikyū (Karaage Bento)
Torikyū (Special Bento)
He puts 6 Torikyū bentos in all at once
And then...
With the skill of a trader
It is like a trader, really
he takes a total of 10 Maisen
shrimp cutlet and pork fillet
cutlet sandwiches
Maisen
(pork fillet cutlet sandwich)
(shrimp cutlet sandwich)
For sure
This wouldn't be possible for a beginner
He puts 5 Tsutaya bentos
into his second carrying-home bag
Tsutaya (Seaweed bento)
In just 6 minutes
he cleans up almost all the catering that was in the green room and finishes
Then...
He checks the perimeter and exits the room
Prank Reveal
You did it
Huh, what?
Where are you running off to?
What? What? What?
The one on your back too
This...
Yes, you
What is it I've done?
It's not like I've done anything wrong
There's nothing bad about it
That's why I knew you'd do it
In fact, you did better than I could have imagined
Huh, what? Is everyone angry at me?
Are you angry?
We're not angry
Everyone's scared
What's this?
No, no
I got these from the office so they're unrelated to this
What did you get?
It's full of tissues
Wait, you got all these tissues from the office?
They had spare...
Hey, this is just the office supply
No, no, no, it's not
"I haven't done anything wrong", he says
but for some reason Takizawa can't stop sweating
The things he took home
from the green room
Bento
Cutlet sandwich
Cup ramen
Snacks
Total items
totaled an extrodinary 19,147 yen.
The fourth player to finish,
he holds a decisive lead
What would you do with all this? You couldn't have eaten it
Well, um...
Well for example, if it's hijiki, I'll collect the hijiki, from each of them
And then freeze it
You open them all
I open them, disassemble, if it's hijiki collect the hijiki,
put it in Tupperware, and freeze it for later
Then it's always ready. I just nuke it
It's not really "always ready"
Staff) You were amazingly fast at putting the cans in
Yeah
I thought since no one's here, I-I-I-I'll do it while I can
Staff) You don't like being seen?
Well, as you'd expect, if I get told off,
it's a little uncomfortable, isn't it?
Yes, yes
It is
Next, the fifth target is...
Target:
Miura Mild
Can you do that
kind of thing at karaoke?
Nominator:
Oideyasu Oda
When we go do a performance
he'll take home a huge amount of water
But all he took was...
2 Torikyū and 2 water
Bento
Drinks
Total items
totaling 1,706 yen.
Wait wait wait
This isn't funny at all!
No, it's so bad. No no no
Hey everyone, let's beat him up
Hold on. Did I do anything wrong here?
Then...
Target:
Minamikawa
Someone else who's
said to have a habit of
taking a lot of water home...
Nominator:
Ojin Osborn
Shinomiya Akira
Result: the joke bombed
It bombed?
Yes
Bento
Snacks
Drinks
Total items
Why? When did it happen?
So what was the right answer? To take loads home?
If you'd put loads in, we'd be laughing so hard
Who would do that?
And so our 7th and last target is...
Target:
Thank you very much.
I'm AMEMIYA.
Nominator:
Viking
Nishimura Mizuki
We work out of the same office
and have the same manager
It seems he's got a dedicated carrying-home bag
Plus, once he was taking so much
that when he got home he found
he'd taken someone's half-eaten food
Could AMEMIYA beat Takizawa's score of 19,147 yen?
This won't be easy
with a score like that
Target:
Our last challenger is...
There it is!
It's huge, isn't it?
Wow
This is possible
"This is possible" he said
What's possible?
For this man, everything's possible.
He takes...
Tsutaya (Seaweed bento)
6 Tsutaya,
6 Torikyū,
Torikyū (Karaage Bento)
Torikyū (Special Bento)
and 10 Maisen,
Maisen
(pork fillet cutlet sandwich)
(shrimp cutlet sandwich)
leaving none of them behind.
He's carrying them from the bottom?
It's pretty heavy
And then...
He's still going?
I guess we'll see
Maisen (mini burger)
Then he takes all 20 of the
mini burgers Takizawa left alone
That's enough now. That's enough
But that won't stop AMEMIYA
who puts snacks into the remaining space in his bag
Finally, he takes some waters...
and, unbelievably...
puts them into his guitar case.
After stripping the room bare of its catering,
AMEMIYA leaves the green room with a huge amount of luggage
Prank Reveal
Hey, AME-chan!
Good evening
What are you doing?
What's that?
Now hold on a minute. What is this?
This is pretty terrible
Terrible?
AMEMIYA managed to get 132 items
Bento
Cutlet sandwich
Mini burgers
Cup ramen
Snacks
Drinks
Total items
with a total of 27,208 yen
greatly surpassing
Takizawa's score.
I guess I just had an urge to take it
Seriously. Also, um...
I'll be honest. This is kind of like my appearance fee
No, this isn't included
Well, basically, TV doesn't pay that much, does it?
Really AME-chan?
As someone from the same office, I'm embarressed
There's no one who takes this much
Well today I kinda...
I got a bit greedy
(Nishimura) That much?
And so, the winner is...
Green room catering take home ranking
Takizawa Shūichi (Machine Guns)
Makino Suteteko
Hiru-chan (Impossible)
Ikeda Kazuma (Shizzle)
Miura Mild
Minamikawa
AMEMIYA, who took home everything except for some canned drinks and 1 bento
(Ogi) Amazing
Amazing
Machine Guns -
Takizawa Shūichi
Makino Suteteko
Impossible -
Hiru-chan
Shizzle -
Ikeda Kazuma
Miura Mild
Miamikawa
I didn't think he could
beat Takizawa
20,000…
That's true
He's quite successful,
surprisingly
Isn't he? Relatively
He's ranked highly
That's right, yes
Well, that's
a bit surprising
But it's not like it's...
wrong
It was very thief-like
Well...
They're not violating
any rules, right?
I see
(Ogi) Really?
It's just bad manners
And manners depend
on the individual, sometimes
(Ogi) So it's a moral thing?
Don't cover for him so much
(Ikeda) Morals differ by person
Ōkubo-san
She is
You've been looking repulsed for a while
That's not...
You looked totally different before the VTR
(Ogi) I don't think it's that different
It's like I've seen a nasty face
If we checked it on an infrared camera his eyes would be glowing
Really?
★Subbed by fmck fansubs★
reddit.com/u/fmckfansubs
patreon.com/fmck
♫ I cut my nails, cut my hair
Next week, the 7th
Lyric Changing Tournament takes place
Popular comedians' changed lyrics
are graded by
University of Tokyo students
♫ If you take it, you're done
Also, the make-your-grandkid-laugh
championship
where the grandkids don't laugh.
A painful reverse-prank
Go! Go! Go! Go!
And we investigate whether
TL Note: Twin comedians
The Touch do solo gigs