Welcome to Wednesday Downtown
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Jinnai Tomonori
Always here
Okay, so what about this time?
I've brought a theory about love that's rarely seen on this show
This is it:
Among the people you know, if you confess in the order of how much you like them, and you'll find someone within 100 people, no matter who you are
What do you think, Matsumoto?
What'll happen with this I wonder
It's not about just finding anyone
You shouldn't treat love like a game?
No, definitely not
Otomo, what do you think of this project?
I think it is feasible
Isn't there a lot of couples in this world?
They can't all be each other's number one so...
Indeed, it must happen
Is it a male chasing female or female chasing male?
I think there'll be a big difference
If it's a woman after a man, I think it's quite feasible
Indeed, it's entirely possible
To be honest, this is usually how I do it
You go in an order?
Among the people you know, if you confess in the order of how much you like them, and you'll find someone within 100 people, no matter who you are
What'll happen?
This'll make hearts beat
The person who challenges this project today is
Who is this?
papa Hoshino Disco, 31 years old
Don't know him
Appearing as a finalist in King of Conte and R-1 Powerful artist
King of Conte?
- Really?
Hamada, he was on your show!
You remember?
Yes, yes, his song is very good
Recently, his single has been gaining attention as well
This song is indeed very popular
I've gone about six or seven years without a girlfriend
I've had no opportunities to meet anyone recently
So far, he's dated two women
Isn't he cute?
The three years between the ages of 21 and 24 and the second year of middle school, respectively
Dating in the second year of middle school is so early
I was just thinking that if I could use the power of variety shows
When you find a girlfriend, it's good
Wow, it's really a bit like a documentary
At the same time, I received a request from this show
So, he was given a week to think carefully about who he wanted to date
The day of confession has finally arrived
I am fully prepared
Still nervous though
But I'm determined to confess from now until I succeed
So, the women Hoshino wants to date
1st is
Actress Hinako Sakurai
No, no, no, no. This is not a serious choice, right?
The one he chose was actress Hinako Sakurai
It'd be strange to omit such a choice I guess
We've acted together before
We spent about a month together, including practice
No, no, no, no.
I feel we had a good thing going
It'd be weird to not include her, then
Although I also think it is probably impossible
If he likes her then yeah
But, I guess I still want to use this program to take the chance
Just give it a go
So, we bypassed the agency and contacted her directly
I'm so nervous
Straight up?
Hello?
-Hello?
Hello, huh?
-Uh, that...
I am papa's Hoshino Disco
Ah!
Is it okay to talk on the phone right now? Are you busy?
This is definitely not going to work
Ah, well...that... I'm practicing today too
Definitely can't get this nervous
It's that musical practice
Ah, practicing for the musical...
Yes. What can I do for you?
Ah, that... I'm just now...
How can I put it?
I just kind of wanted to call you
So I'm calling you
A bit scary...
Ah, okay
That, uh, that...
Gonna confess directly?
We've acted together on the stage, right?
I think... I like you a lot
Wow, scary
It's scary to confess to Sakurai
Hm
I think you're a very nice person
So, if possible, uh...
Would you go out with me?
Ah, I think you are a very nice person too
But how can I say it? I just see you as a friend, Hoshino
In other words...
Yeah, as expected
Well... ah, so that's how it is, huh?
But I'm happy that you confessed your feelings to me.
-Well...
If you don't mind, you can come and see my musical
More?
Ah, indeed
This isn't an announcement!
There will be a show in Tokyo from the 16th, if you can arrange it
I'll be sure to come
-Yes, yes, yes.
A new way to advertise!
It's over
When I was rejected, I was more upset than I thought.
I see
Change the mood quickly
Now i'll just focus on the memory of being invited to a musical
Next, the 2nd woman he wants to go out with
Needs to pick up the mood
2nd is Tomite Ami
Look, here we go again
What's going on?
Another female actress
Hoshino sets a high difficulty level from the outset
This is not possible
You suddenly say you want to be in a relationship with me
It's so sudden, I don't know you at all
-Yes, I see
If that's all you need to do, it'd be easy!
Third is...
The comedian Miku
A single comedian, Miku
Oh, third place
What are you doing right now?
So disgusting, this kind of question
Ah, I'm at home now
-Ah, you're at home... resting?
Yes
-Oh, I see
Later, can we meet up?
Oh, the method of confession has changed
Eh... is there something wrong?
No its nothing bad
So, for the third, she's asked to meet near TBS to confess in person
That... well...
-What's this?
I'm recording a show right now. Is that okay?
-It's okay
I asked you to come here today
Because... I like you
-Thank you
Will you go out with me?
Ah... eh? Is that how you feel about me?
That type of feeling, yeah
Ah... yeah
I'm sorry.
-Oh, is that the answer?
Ah...
It's hard to continue after being rejected
Then
I only know you as a comedian
It's starting to get serious
So because of that, it's a little bit...
The selection is becoming more realistic
But I really hate men who are weaker than me
I've only worked with you, outside of work, and in the future...
His choices are still a bit far off
It's a bit of an excuse if I tell you that I want to focus on my work right now, but...
A bit detached
Ah... I see
A writer?
Would you be willing to go out with me?
What crap are you spewing? I'll beat you up
So harsh
"I'll beat you up"...
Do you have a boyfriend now?
Ah...yes...yes
Eh? You have a boyfriend?
She's his senior after all
And so, from his first confession in a decade
Hoshino is rejected by 9 people in 4 hours
I'm a little tired of this project
How many times do I have to be rejected...
So, he's given a little break to adjust his mental state
Yeah, you'd be sad
I'd like to call Nyan's Miyuki
The tenth?
When we drank together, I was impressed by how strong she is
So uncouth!
It was a cute contrast
She's really a "10th person" kind of level
By the tenth person, the difference in quality is pretty big
You do want to go out with her, don't you?
-Yes
Despite being a surprising choice, he seems sincere
So, they agreed to meet
After waiting for 30 minutes
Sorry, you've worked hard.
-Thank you for your hard work
Ah, what's up?
-Although there are cameras..
Is it a big show?
-Does it matter?
He quickly gets to the point
Miyuki... I... like you... yeah
I see...
Please go out with me
Sorry, I can't
Eh, you can't?
-No, I'm sorry. I'm really sorry
You're not my type.
-I see
What type of people do you like?
A little more macho, I guess
That type, but you're....
Hoshino, the unmanly man, sinks
So, next is the eleventh
An old hometown senpai called Yuka
Yes, a good choice
A normal person?
-Well, yeah
At this stage, the first normal person arrives
She was one year ahead of me in the basketball team in high school
Our families have been close since I was in elementary school, so we were very close
I often visited her home to play
He'll be really sad if this one doesn't go well
I liked her very much at that time
Yeah this'll be a bad one
But I don't think my feelings ever reached her
He's already been rejected 10 times though so that should ease it a bit
Maybe now it'll get through
You say that, but this is the 11th place
Yeah
To be honest, I didn't have much hope for the higher ranked people
I just wanted to challenge myself
From now on, its more personal
And so, confessions for more realistic candidates begin
An odd sounding statement
Hello
-Hello
Long time no speak
-Long time no speak
I've seen you on TV a lot
Ah, really? You've been watching?
I'm watching, I'm watching
-I'm happy to hear it
A good vibe
How have you been doing?
Maybe...
I'm married now
Ah!
-Didn't know?
Married already!?
Married already?
-Yes, already married
You're already married?
-Yes, I am
Is that your child I can hear?
-Yes
Eh!?
Confess!
That's not good. It's not that kind of project
But she sounds happy. That's great
It's 7:00 p.m., and six hours have passed since the first confession
Six hours is more than enough to destroy the nerves
The 12th woman is now arriving at TBS
Tsukakoshi, a junior who he used to work with
Sorry, there are cameras
How have you been?
Not bad, you've been busy, i've been watching you
Thank you. What are you working on now?
Now I am working as a designer
And so, after a little bit of pleasantries
Sometimes I think, it'd be nice to have a girlfriend
Thinking such thoughts
Go for it then
That is true
Seems ok?
Tsukakoshi, what do you think?
Eh, wait a minute, why so suddenly...
No, well, its that...
I'm single currently, i'm not sure about you...
At the moment?
Now, I have someone I'm dating
And so, moving on to 13
Yes, Ito Chinami
She is now working as a professional gamer
She's the person I have the best relationship with
Should meet often then
I've maintained a good relationship with her for a long time
Due to not wanting to ruin their friendship, until now
A realistic candidate?
Her name was not even mentioned up until this point
I think she's the one that suits me the most
A serious choice at 13
This is what I think
And so, a meeting is organized with the 13th person
The fourth meeting at this spot of the day
What are you doing?
-This is a bit weird
Good evening
-Good evening
Sorry about the cameras
Seems like a good relationship
It's been a long time since we've seen each other, so I'm still a little nervous
It's true that we haven't seen each other for a long time, we haven't met up
We often game together
But we haven't chatted much during
Yes that's how its been recently
Said to be his best relationship with a woman
The atmosphere is certainly the best so far
What will happen?
Yes, yes, recently, we often play games together, right?
I really think we are very close friends
But... is it possible...
But I think there's a sense of adoration
Do you mean from me?
-Me
We are great friends
But actually, I have the feeling of "like"
I have been thinking about this very carefully
Is this a bit too direct?
Could it be "like"?
"Could it be like"? Is that a question?
No, I mean, its "like"
So
If you are willing...
From now on, can we play games together as lovers?
Eh... dating ...dating is...
When we game together, although we've had a lot of interaction
We haven't switched from communication mode to lover mode
Ah, indeed, indeed.
-The communication...
Just between friends
What about game mode?
So if you take this into consideration
There has been a game mode
If you can show more sincerity, it is not impossible...
So it's not hopeless then
Of course
I have a chance?
Its too sudden now
But there are a lot of aspects I like about you
Us being in a serious relationship together
It is not impossible to imagine, but
You haven't even invited me on a date yet
Nor have I been invited to dinner with this in mind
So to suddenly say "let's be together" is kind of suspicious
Like, are you serious?
True
Ah... yeah
Do you get what i'm saying
-Yeah, I get it
I think what you said is completely correct
He's like Kuro-chan
It's impossible to just say yes on the spot
Now its like "if you could..." kind of thing
-It's not there yet
Not  yet, that sorta thing
But a good vibe nonetheless
I get it
As she couldn't give an immediate answer today, so
Here, with the 13th place...
Not a complete success
What are you feeling right now?
Her words are still ringing in my ears
Sure enough, we should date first
If you don't meet a few times before confessing your love, it doesn't make much sense to agree
Didn't Kuro-chan do the same?
Really, I'm speechless
It really happened
It makes me feel even more that she is a wonderful person
A very thoughtful person
So, as Ito only gave him a tentative answer
As he still hasn't found a girlfriend, we continue the plan
Still more?
If we can start with friends
-Ah start with being friends, right?
It's a bit, well, if you're dating, you're a little too eager, or, how to say, you're a little...
Yeah I see
That's what everyone says
The 16th place female is
pon loop's AMI
The male/female group, pon loop's AMI
We have been doing live shows together for about 3 years
Pretty good relationship
He likes female comedians
She is always full of energy and cheerful
I think being with her would make anyone more energetic
She also works at a ramen shop in Akasaka
Become cheerful
So, he contacts the person he deems to be a suitable match
You're living with Miyuki, right?
Yes, we live together
Has she come back?
Yes, she has come back
This is great
Oh, did she mention anything about me?
Something about Disco?
-Yeah
If she didn't say anything, don't worry about it at all
No, nothing special. I didn't talk to her after she got back
I've been busy doing my taxes
Doing your taxes so you've been too busy too talk
Yes, yes, yes
-Ah OK OK
I'm a bit pressed for time, the day after tomorrow is the deadline
It's 10:00 p.m. and because it's late
This time, we went to where the woman lives to confess
It's very late!
Why is it a shrine?
Ah
-Eh?
Ah, Ami.
You're here?
Wha...
What are you holding in your hand?
I just got back from the laundromat
The clothes just finished drying
It was drying
-Ah, sorry
What's wrong? Is something wrong?
There's one thing. It's urgent. I have to talk to you
There's something I wanted to say in person
Disbandment?
-Not a disbandment thing
I guess the opposite of disbandment
Eh!? I see. You wanna form a duo?
Not really, but close I guess
Form a trio?
What's up with this kid?
AMI, who is always cheerful, seems like the sun to me
Being together would be like being healed
-Eh? What do you mean?
Please, go out with me!
-Eh!?
Eh?
-That's pretty much it. That's why I called you out
Feels pretty good
Eh, did you hear something, from somewhere?
Eh? What?
Eh, like what?
Did you hear something from Miyuki?
Eh, no, I haven't heard anything, but...
You didn't hear anything, right?
From Miyuki
-No
Eh?
-Eh?
What is going on now, what's happening?
Well, then it doesn't matter, i'll tell you
Oh, please do
That, actually...
I once talked to Miyuki about how I like you
Eh!?
That's why she was surprised
Here comes the biggest shock of the day!
Really?
Eh, what to do...
What's with this development?
It's inexplicable.
-It's really inexplicable
Really unbelievable...
-Seriously!?
So now, although she said she likes him
Hoshino, up until this point, hasn't actually said "please go out with me"
Oh oh, I see...
Why? Well, the answer is surely because of the 13th choice, Chinami
Chinami said she wanted to go on a date first.
-It's true
He's so popular all of a sudden, he's got so many choices
However, it's still not a sure thing with her though, right?
It's not a sure thing
-But it is with Ami, right?
Ami likes him, for sure
For Ami of pon loop, Hoshino is his first choice, right?
Indeed, seemingly the highest ranked person
Well, then isn't Ami the best choice?
-AMI is a good choice
So you think its best to choose Ami?
Yes, I think maybe its best
Now we understand Miyuki more as well
Indeed, the reason behind her actions are clear
It's true, there's was sense of deliberate indifference and rejection
When she got home, she probably didn't say anything about it on purpose
Ah, she didn't want Hoshino's rating to go down.
-Ah, I'm so excited
This character relationship chart is impressive
It's already movie-quality, and the trailer for the movie was released this summer
Can we watch it again from the beginning?
-What are you talking about!?
So, a week after the shoot
I've thought a lot about it since then
I want to go on a date with Chinami and confess again
Ami is very important to me as a fellow comedian
Obviously likes her
So Ami has lost
So, Ami is informed of his decision
Well, although we're not dating, I think it's good to get everything out in the open
Now I feel a sense of release, it was very exciting
After i've confessed, I feel pretty comfortable
So, Hoshino, who wanted to reaffirm his feelings for Chinami
Oh
-Sorry I'm late
You're here
-I kept you waiting
Finding gaps between each other's work commitments
2 weeks later
Finally, it's time to confess again
Really... I... Chinami... I like you
Please go out with me
We went out to dinner a few times to see how things would go
I can't say yes to a relationship
I don't feel much of a spark from you
Have to decide after the date
This is important
I'd like to still be friends, in this way i'm sure we'll be happy
But I'm really happy to know how you feel, thank you
You already knew, right?
Thank you
And so, Hoshino's courtship is over
Do you have any plans to confess to Ami again?
Ah, in terms of her I think...
It's best to leave it as it is
But... the one who was rejected by Hoshino...
Poor thing!
She hasn't given up
Disco did not prove or disprove this theory
So can I have a go at it?
I would love to have a boyfriend, really
From the bottom of my heart
So the pon loop's Ami
Her 100 man confession battle will be shown in the near future!
Let's welcome the next presenter
Kamaitachi!
Although a bit sudden, do you remember this previous project?
Two people compete in a fake match against each other
-There was such a thing
A matchup in which both sides are instructed to lose before the match
This time brings another form of this duel
The theory this time is:
Both sides are extremely angry
What does this mean?
The two people involved are told separately that they are the ones pranking the other person
They're told to be very angry to the other
I see
But the other person does not know that the other person is also a setter
So they are also trying to make the other person really angry
Both sides
-Yes
The most entertaining two-sided anger
What will happen this way?
The initial target is the two people who immediately come to mind when it comes to quarreling: Onigoe Tomahawk
These two have perfected the art of arguing
We want you to do it
-Okay
The "Real Angry Man" setter
-Ok
I don't know how far I'll go if I'm really angry
A bloodbath is possible
Is this okay?
By the way, have you had any real fights lately?
About two months ago
This was a while ago
If we really fight, seriously, please come to call it off
Considering those involved
A real fight may develop
These two men are deeply disturbed by this potential result
So this time it is
How many times can you say "kora!" in 30 minutes?
Like Chosho, right?
"What the hell are you looking at?" That sort of "kora!", right?
A fake project with a challenge of how many times you can say "kora" in a real fight in 30 minutes
Like there would be such a show
-Yeah
Chair Kick
Grab
Kneel
Oi! (Kora)
Table Slap
Water
By the way, the reward point system is as follows
Very game-like
So, the two sides who are really angry with each other start
What a ranking system
I've been waiting for you for a long time
I've been waiting for almost 30 minutes.
-Is it that long?
Waited for about 30 minutes
You should have said something!
-No, no, no...
Very good approach
Using a partner's tardiness as a reason to fight
Sakai begins a resourceful battle strategy
What's that, witty?
What is this?
This is how your company does it, right?
I get it
-What do you get!?
This is a prank, right?
What?
Unbelievably, he pretends to have realized he is being pranked, although that is actually the case
Very clever approach
So, getting too close to the truth
It's gotten complicated
Kin who is shaken by the thought of being exposed
Is this going to work?
You went to a meeting before this, didn't you
No, no, I didn't
You surely did, super suspicious
Oi! (Kora!)
What the hell are you doing?
Oi!
-What the hell? Oi! What the hell, you bastard?
What do you think, you're trying to prank me, aren't you!
I've said no!
As expected, the two earn points by fighting
By naturally adding "kora!" into their conversation
You're the one doing it, you bastard!
Don't be ridiculous!
Next
Your angry look is very suspicious!
Splashed!
Your angry look is too suspicious!
Drank it already
Your acting sucks!
It's you!
Can't fight back
Despite starting quickly
As quarrels are a common occurrence
Neither side genuinely realizes the other is the setter
It happens too regularly for them
Next
Get down on your knees
Let go of me!
You're the one who should let go of my hand.
-Let go of me!
Then let go together
Ah, are you kidding?
Move your hands!
Seriously stop it!
You're still grabbing me!
Upon finally letting go
Both look on nervously
And so it went on for 15 minutes
Half time
Oi!
Aren't you bored with this?
-You're the one that should be bored!
You're boring!
-Oi!
What are you doing?
What's this for?
Disgusting disgusting disgusting disgusting disgusting
This is so long
They've been informed that this will light up when there's 5 minutes left
And that the word "octopus" is now activated
So, the "octopus" bonus round begins
Oi oi oi oi oi oi oi oi!
Octopus, octopus, octopus!
Octopus! Oi!
At this point
Ah, you really
Earned a lot!
What's all this?
With Kin's impressive octopus streak
Finally, the fact that somethings up becomes apparent
What was that just now, octopus?
Octopus! Octopus! Octopus! Octopus! Octopus! Octopus! Octopus! Octopus!
But the situation continues regardless
Octopus! Shut up!
So, high-speed declarations of "octopus!" continue until the time is up
It ended up feeling wrong
Octopus octopus octopus
-Shut up, shut up, shut up
Octopus! Octopus! Octopus! Octopus! Octopus! Octopus! Octopus! Octopus! Octopus!
Wait a minute
What is this?
-It's not right...
Who was the setter
Me
-No, I was
The point at which this guy kept saying the same words as me
I knew something was off
What do you think this program is?
Chidori's special program, right?
It seems like XX and XX
-No.
Uh...
Theory, theory? Theory?
-Correct
But generally speaking TBS isn't allowed to lie and say its another channel, right?
Can it pretend to be XX
I guess XX wouldn't be so aggressive
Wednesday Downtown
It can pretend to be another station's program without any permission?
This is like illegally downloading porn
Next is FUJIWARA
In the same way, both are called in advance
Haranishi made his head look like that?
And thus, the two-side angry meeting starts
Both sides are white
Your new hair, have you had any comments?
Great reviews!
Good reviews?
Yes, people say I look much younger
Using Haranishi's image change as a pretext
Fujimoto begins
On this point
It'd be better if you paid attention to your appearance
What do you mean by appearance?
It's hard to get hair that people think is good
But do you think its enough?
Take this wrinkle line for example
Don't you care for your skin? Oi!
To not get that thing
That's a strange way to put it, right?
Skin care I definitely won't do it, never will
Don't you care for your skin?
An unexpected skin care "kora!"
Two words that definitely do not go together
Skin care and "kora!"
With a contradictory sense
It's too suspicious
It's gradually starting to heat up
You're the guy who doesn't do anything every day
Oi oi oi oi listen listen listen listen
Let's talk about appearance
Either wrinkly or smooth
What kind of thing do the audience want to see more?
That is, I know more about skin care
Can't you listen to me?
What do you think?
What should I go and buy?
Buy hyaluronic acid
Minor verbal altercations continue
How thoughtful!
Since we're talking about this
As soon as summer comes, you always wear shorts
Wear what?
Don't wear that stuff!
Why not?
Too much leg hair!
-Eh?
Too much leg hair
And so, the venting from boredom continues
While talking on the phone with family
Can you stop using a Tokyo accent?
Seems natural
What the hell?
Don't cut your nails in the break room!
In the lounge you sit like a woman!
So what? Its comfortable
It's disgusting, right in front of us...
Sitting in front of me like that, you are too disgusting
I sit like that at home too, what's wrong?
-That's none of my business!
You don't blow your nose when you have a cold!
The snot is just always leaking out
Ordinary people blow their nose
But you're always just sniffing it in
So what!?
Or you just stick your finger in your nostril
What kind of action is that?
What's wrong with not being able to blow your nose
Who the hell can't blow their nose!?
It's a health problem!
It is not a physical thing, just blow a nose!
Just practice at it
Practice at blowing it!
I'm sick of seeing it
Is that a thing to practice?
Spare me of it!
I said I can't blow my nose
Try it now, there's some tissues
What is this argument?
Really can't blow it
You're not doing it right.
-What's wrong?
Press one nostril and blow
There's nothing up there now
Oi oi oi oi!
-What is it?
Try it!
-Oi, what?
What? Oi!
-Oi!
You copying me?
-Oi oi oi oi!
Copying me!
And so, "octopus" bonus round begins
Octopus!
Time is up
The truth is revealed
Thank you for your hard work
This is a prank
Eh, what? I'm a little confused confused confused
The setter for the prank was
Me... me, right?
Eh?
What is it? What's going on?
So we explained the project to them
By the middle, i'd forgotten I was the setter
I just didn't want to lose the argument
I definitely won't lose
I also really felt that I could not lose
The final goal is the combination Plus Minus
This is gonna be bad, isn't it
-Yes, it is
You won the Manzai Talent Award, right?
Thank you
The youngest recipient of the award, right?
Downtown also won the award, right?
At a a younger age than us
Well we are better, right?
And so, Plus Minus
And so, the two-side angry Plus Minus meeting starts
We get this close to each other
And say stuff like "die!" to each other
I'm a little scared
We occasionally argue
Fighting each other... its likely it'll happen
Really?
This has nothing to do with the prank
Its excessive today
Doesn't get points for this, right?
What's too much, who are you to judge?
So noisy since the morning
What the hell are you talking about? "so noisy since morning"?
What? Oi!
Ugly!
You're the ugly one, right?
How you look is the definition of ugly
Your face looks like its melting
It doesn't look like it's melting
What "it doesn't look like its melting", you just copy and don't even think of anything
What do you ever say thats new?
Your face is sagging
You talk so much crap!
Ah, the water!
Quick progression
It is indeed quite real
43 this year
Stop this, what're you doing?
-You started it!
You're so full of crap
It's baffling
Ah? Oi! What? Oi!
Who are you saying "oi" (kora) to?
I'm saying it, oi!
Who're you looking at and saying that?
You think you're right about everything, don't you?
I don't think so, you do!
That's what you think
No I don't!
You think that way, hey, hey, hey, hey, dumbass!
-What's this nonsense?
You know, you stink
You're the one that stinks!
You do!
It's obviously you who stinks!
Both sides are talking a lot
In this room
Listen to me!
I'm the one talking now. Oi!
I'm letting you!
I'm talking here, why the hell are you interrupting, oi, you bastard!
Look really quite real
I'm telling you to pay attention!
What i'm saying to you is important, understand?
Outsiders won't be saying this stuff, get it?
Don't say it then!
What the hell is wrong with you?
As a result, Iwahashi takes his partner down smoothly
Iwahashi's behavior is so scary
Stop! Oi!
What are you doing! Oi, idiot!
Never seen such a quarrel
Let go!
Dammit!
43 year olds
Biting!
I can't believe he's biting him
What the hell is going on?
Get out
Get out of here! Oi, get the hell out of here!
Only halfway
At this time
What the hell are you doing?
Give me back my 2000 yen!
Huh?
2000 yen
I don't know anything about that
What 2000 yen?
M-1's registration fee of 2000 yen, give it back
2018 and 17
That's a lie!
Give me back both!
And so, they start to bring up old things as an excuse to continue to fight
Give me back my 2000 yen!
I don't have 2000!
Don't say such ridiculous things!
I'll give it to you!
Don't throw money!
Pick it up!
Such a smooth movement
Iwahashi starts attacking with a strange sleeper technique
No points!
Why are you using such techniques?
What the hell are you doing today?
It's you!
Why are you running your mouth so much today?
You're so noisy, i've put up with you long enough!
Oi!
I'm always holding back what I want to say
Baldy, oi!
10 minutes to go
You're really at fault!
You never do any jokes for me!
How many jokes do you have?
Only me? I'm always giving you jokes!
Only the master and Freiza!
No, you've had loads
"Kill you", just that
You've said loads!
Iwahashi, I'll kill you!
You are so irritating
So painful
Look, dumbass
It hurts to watch
I can't talk to you properly
It is impossible to talk to you
Here comes the sleeping technique
Immediately strangled
After fighting they go back to their seats
Ow ow ow ow
You don't get points this way!
No points for biting
"Octopus" bonus round
Since there's cameras they always return to their seats
Octopus, you octopus!
What octopus?
You're an octopus
Octopus
-What octopus?
Get bangs
Get a handful of curly bangs!
Octopus
-You think you're Choshu?
Oh interesting, no I don't
I don't know
Octopus! Oi!
-Seriously, your face is sagging
You'd score 70 points for your imitation
Getting points!
What the hell are you doing?
Disgusting, so noisy!
Again with this technique
What are you doing?
Finally the time is up
The truth is revealed
These two people are idiots, right?
This is a prank
Eh?
That's right. You're surprised
Its a prank
But i'm the setter
Eh, what's going on here?
This is Wednesday Downtown
Great!
Weird to say "great"
It's finally here!
This is Wed Down!
Ma-chan, Hama-chan!
They'll be angry
You should be happy too!
It's so weird, I'm already confused
In summary, the scores for all are as follows
The winner of the feeder challenge is Sakai of Onigoe Tomahawk
I see
Plus Minus really started complaining to each other in the middle
Usually, biting occurs
Nothing can be done about it
When I went to the lounge, I once heard Kanemitsu screaming
I ran over and saw Iwaashi holding him and biting his head
It can does happen
-Then there's nothing to be done about it
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03