Our next presenter is this fine fellow. Come on out!
It's Tamura Kenji!
Thank you for having me.
From today forward, especially for Wednesday Downtown...
...we will be starting a brand new project.
Why'd no one tell me?
So to kick things off, let's take a look.
Sometime in August.
I seriously had no idea.
They're cute!
So many cute girls.
Sixteen girls brought together for a reason unbeknownst to them.
They don't even know?
They don't know what they're in for.
Here he comes!
I'm so happy!
With hands like that,
it can only be him.
Kuro-kawa has arrived.
What's he gotta
do with them?
Wait, wait...
Eh? What's going on?
I can hear lots of voices.
Eh? Who's there?
There's chicks?
Why say it like that?!
Huh?
Just say "girls"!
Wait, are there lots of chicks here?
"Chicks" again!
What an idiot.
Eh? What's going on?
They gave me something.
Feels like there's a stand.
Ow!
What'd he even hit?
Eh? Am I OK to take this off?
Who is it?
Who's that?  Who's that?
Are you ok to just take it off?
Uwahhhh...what's this?!
What is this?
Is this a dating series?
We don't know anything about this either.
Her face...
You don't know?
So does that mean...I have to whittle 16 down to 1?
Eh? We'll be living together?
Living together...
He says it like he
wouldn't want it.
It's going to be the
same again this year.
This?
The monster is
out, after all.
What is it?
You know, on the
inside he's over the
moon about this.
"These sixteen girls before you are aiming to become idols."
"You, Kuro-chan, are tasked with selecting the members..."
"...and producing your own idol group."
You know this guy
is gonna fall for them.
This is bad.
A producer?
You want to be idols?
You can tell he's
really happy.
He's so happy.
Yes.
You can tell he's
holding back.
It's 'cause he
loves idols.
He's not troubled by
this at all.
I look forward to working with you.
So I really have to decide?
You can see right
through him!  Look
how happy he is!
I mean, it says right here "select the members."
Well...that means the examination has already started.
We've already begun.
What the hell is
he on about?
So this is the power dynamic.  I understand.
Wow, he's really
full of it.
I understand my problem.  Yeah.
Whoa, whoa, look
at his face!
Yeah...
It got all dark.
I'm already scared.
I'm scared, but I
can't look away.
T/N: Kuro-chan's last series was "Monster House", a parody of the reality show "Terrace House".
"Monster Idol?!"
And so with that...
Is this allowed?
For him to...
I know he's your favorite, Hamada.
No, no, no, no...
Now, Kuro-chan really does love idols.
He knows every little detail, doesn't he?
Literally everything. Any live show he goes to...
...he takes his notebook, and writes every single thing down.
Creepy.  That's just creepy.
So that's why, this time, Kuro-chan will be becoming an idol producer.
He'll be producing?
He'll be producing.
Just watching this creeped me out.
He's putting on this concerned and troubled face...
...but you can tell he's incredibly happy.
This is impossible.
Tsu-chan, surely you've had auditions?
I've had auditions, sure, but we were just...
It's like that, I guess.
Imagine having Kuro-chan as a producer.
I assume that it was left out that they would be produced by Kuro-chan.
Exactly.  The sixteen hopefuls were only told...
...that this was an idol audition for TV.
We didn't tell them it was Wednesday Downtown.
So that what those sixteen knew when applying.
And that's all they knew.
If you told them that Kuro-chan would be the producer...
...I think a lot of them would have just quit.
You think so?
If we told them they can just leave when they want...
...there wouldn't be anyone left.
He'd be there alone.
But Shigemori, you went to an audition that changed your life.
Yeah, I did.  But I wouldn't want to be in their shoes.
But, they know if they leave...
...they're giving up the chance to appear on primetime TV.
So I think that itself is big motivation to stay.
In order to break into the entertainment industry...
...they know they'll be liked by perverts and bad people.
That's not the case at all!
Wait wait wait wait, that isn't the case at all!
Did you just come here to be liked by perverts?!
Hypothetically!  Just hypothetically!
She's not talking about herself!  It's just her experience!
Yeah, yeah, exactly!
This girl's an idiot.
Coming next: Monster Idol's first screening process begins.
No, this is just...
Here, Kuro-chan will be told his task again - in greater detail.
My name is Watanabe.  I'm a WACK representative who manages groups like BiSH.
Of course, I know who you are.
Yes.
So this guy is
pretty well know.
Wait, is this for real?!
It is, yes.
WACK, the company that produces BiSH and other idol groups...
...is managed by this man - Watanabe Junnosuke.
In this series, the members that Kuro-chan chooses...
...will debut under WACK.
By the way...
...in terms of the songs, the lyrics, the choreography...
...everything will be left to you to decide, Kuro-chan.
Is he for real?
Eh, me?
Yes.
I've never done anything like this before.
That's ok, we'll be here to support you.
So if that's the case, then...
...I can basically create my kind of dream idol group?
Exactly, yes.
The day is already flying by, and you still have 16 girls, right?
I'm going to need you to get that 16 down to just eight.
Eh? Today?
Yes.
No, no ... isn't that too fast?
That's quick!
So, I have these cards for you to give to the girls you want to keep.
These cards allow them to continue.
Today there's eight.
For the first stage of the audition...
This is going really quick.
...the girls will go through a vocal check and some appeal time.
Using these two tests he must halve the group from 16 to just eight.
I've just wondered...
...these idols I'm making...are they allowed to have relationships?
I will leave that to you to decide.
For me to decide... OK.
Scary! He's so scary!
What's with that face?
He pisses me off.
Sorry about the delay.
He's so full of himself!
Walking around like he owns the place!
So, with all that...
...I now fully understand the complete power that I wield.
So if you don't appeal to me, it's no good.
Yes.
So if you can't make me like you...
If you can't do that, then, of course, no one else will love you either.
The hell is he...?
Think of me as someone you need to like you.
So, if any of you can't get through to that person...
...there's no way you'll be able to fulfill the needs of anyone.
I can say that without any doubt.
Is that ok?
Is it really ok?
The hell is he saying?
This isn't a game.
Please do your very best to make me, the one with all the power, like you.
Complete compliance.
Gotta appeal to him,
don't they?
Yes.
Is it OK if I have a brief moment?
Why is he laughing?
Let's talk about the next task.
I think I'd like to move on to the next thing.
You've got no hair!
Among them...
What hair are you moving?!
Baldy.
Eh? Thank you very much!
You've passed.
Aika
That was quick.
How do you feel? You passed.
Eh...I'm super happy!
Thank you so much.
Do you know why I picked you?
What the...?
No... I don't know why.
It's because... you're cute.
Straight to the point.
Thank you so much.
Are you happy?
I'm super happy.
The hell?
What's up with
this guy?
Have you started to like me?  Just a bit?
Yeah, I really like you.
That's nice.
And with that, Aika has become the first successful candidate...
Why is this so gross?
..with only seven spaces remaining.
This is amazing. I
expected nothing less.
Continuing on...
Oh, she's good.  She's good.
Hanae
Checking out their vocals...
Nao
Yuzu
How was that?  Did you sing with all your might?
Risa
I sang with all my might, for if I didn't I would live to regret it.
How much, out of 100%?
I feel it was 100%.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
What the hell is he
talking about?!
She said "I feel like", which means she wasn't singing at 100%.
With all sixteen candidates having their vocals checked...
...they move on to appeal time.
So, everyone... we've come together once again.
How does it feel? When you change locations, your feelings change too.
Ah, I can tell you're pretty nervous.
And I think that's just fine.
I really wish they'd tell him to shut up, just once.
With Aika already chosen, the
rest are split into three groups of five.
Aika
Akane
Hanae
Hinata
Kaede
Kana
Marika
Misuzu
Miyuki
Nao
Natsuko
Risa
Ryou
Sumire
Yuri
Yuzu
Starting with the first team...
What should we toast to?
What would you normally say at a time like this?
Well, I'll go.
You'll start, Nao-chan?
Yes.
Nao
Cheers to Kuro-chan!
Aww thanks, cheers!
Also I'm not Agnes-chan, so Kuro-chan is fine.
Cheers!
Agnes-chan?
So...do any of you do any cute poses?
Any poses to show off your cuteness?
Are you already doing yours, Miyuki?
Miyuki
That's nice, but hold on.
Let me go in for a closer look.
This is embarassing...
Why are you looking down now?
Did you get embarrassed?
Ryou
The other girls continue to try and appeal to Kuro-chan.
Nao
Marika
So what's about you, Kaide?
Kaede
My cheeks are really soft.
Your cheeks are soft?
Yes they are.
Ah, they really do look super squishy!
They're super squishy!
This is my cutest feature.
May I? I'm kind of curious now.
He's gonna do it?
Sure.
He's gonna touch her?!
Well he's curious.
He's touching her!
He's touching her
really close.
It's like he's gonna
kiss her.
Yeah.
What are you doing?!
That's enough!
Just feeling this one side...I can't tell if anything's different.
Can I feel both at the same time?
Yeah.
Gross gross gross!
They're nice.
No, they're really nice.
They're soft.  They're really soft!
You've got something great there.
What the hell is this?!
So, Kaide... would you care to join me over here for a little chat?
OK.
The hell is he doing?!
Right here.
Excuse me.
It's like that, isn't it? You can't fully be yourself in a big group of people.
This is just too much!
You're in a hostess club, dude!
Kaide
How do you really feel?
I'm actually a pretty shy person.
So, for me, personally, it's easier to talk when it's one-on-one.
Wait, do you have a bit of an accent?
I'm from Hokkaido.
You're from Hokkaido.
Yes.
Honestly, you know...
Kaede-chan, you know, I actually, um... I think you're really great.
Thank you so much.
Honestly, Kaede-chan, I really like you.
He touched her!
Ah, I like you too.
Really?
I knew it.
Yes.
I knew this would happen.
What do you think of me?
I think you're...definitely different from how you are on TV.
You seem really kind.
I think the way you think and speak those ideas is amazing.
I thought, "he really thinks things through and comes up with the right answer."
You know, honestly, even if this was a completely different idol group...
Why is he touching her?
I, too, wouldn't be taking this seriously so far.
But I'm creating my dream idol group, after all.
Why did he touch her?
You know, so I can't do this half-heartedly.
If it was ok for me to do this half-heartedly...
I seriously don't think it'd end well.
Right.
Look, he's touching
her the whole time!
So, let's say...
...we both like each other and were to go on a date.
Where would you want to go?
Umm...
I want to ride on a Ferris wheel.
Ah, nice!
I like Ferris wheels too.
They're so fun.
Yeah.
You know, really... I really... um...
You may be shy...
Hasn't he heard
of personal space?
...but no matter what happens, I'll protect you.
There it is!
Thank you so much.
His usual, "I'll
protect you."
About Kaide-chan... of course she's cute. Yeah.
She's cute, and she let me pinch her cheeks.
When I said, "I like you"...
...Kaide-chan responded with a strong "I like you."
Kaide-chan will definitely pass.
This project has already started.
It's only because
she wants to pass.
In this series I want to create idols.
That's the name
of the game.
But I also want a girlfriend.
That isn't the purpose of this.
Nao
There's actually something I've been wondering about.
You listened to me sing in the examination, right?
You spoke to every single person.
Kurochan-san spoke to every single person except me.
You didn't say anything to me.
As soon as I finished singing, all you said was "thank you."
And that was it, wasn't it.
I don't know if I come across as cold...
But I'm actually really interested in Nao-chan.
Really? How interested in me are you?
To be completely honest... the most.
Really?
Yep.
You're not lying to me?
Does it look like I'm lying to you?
Yeah... well...
Nao-chan, actually I... like you the most.
Nao-chan, do you like me?
Yes, I really like you.
No, no, you're
meant to be an idol!
He was just so close!
Right here... his face was right here.
Yeah, yeah, that's it.
When he held my hand, I just...
She was creeped
out by him.
When he held my hand, I just...
...I just thought, "What? What are you doing at this time of day?"
...about halfway through him talking.
Are you quitting?  You should probably quit.
But I knew it wouldn't help me advance if I refused him.
So I thought I didn't really have much choice.
This one's strong.
Miyuki
The next candidate was so nervous...
...she was moved to tears during appeal time.
She's really crying.
Look, I will protect you.
There it is again!
Yes, please protect me.
I wonder what's wrong.
No, I really will protect you.
So, please, just do your best, in your own way.
He's crying too!
Yes, I'll do my best.
They're crying together!
You have a tear.
Stop it! Stop it now!
This is just...
Ryou
The remaining candidates all get a one-on-one appeal time with Kuro-chan.
Marika
He spoke privately
to all of them?!
That's crazy!
Group 1's assessment time is over.
Staff: You've now seen all five of this group.
Staff: How would you rank them?
For me, Nao is number one.
Kaede is number two.
Third is Miyuki, I guess.
The girl who cried.
Number four is Ryou.
So number five is Marika.
Staff: In regards to Kaede-chan and Nao-chan...
Staff: ...you told both of them that you "like" them.
Staff: If they weren't here to become idols...
Staff: ...would you be
interested in them in a romantic way?
Yeah, well...
"Yeah, well..."
...I have fallen for them a little bit.
No, no, no, no, no.
Yeah...
The successful candidates from
the first group are announced.
That was quick!
So, I will now announce who's passed.
Miyuki, you've passed.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
But how will she
cope with all the
embarrassing stuff?
My thoughts exactly.
Kaede-chan, you've passed.
Yes.
Thank you so much.
Congratulations.
These are the successful candidates for today.
But why has Nao, who was ranked so highly, been eliminated?
But, after this, there will be another chance for you.
So, please return to the others.
Thank you very much.
What does that
even mean?
Why didn't he
pick Nao?
Staff: Good work.
Good work.
Staff: It's a shame you didn't make it.
Yes.
I talked to him seriously about how much I want this.
And he said, "I know how you feel."
But he ranked her
number one.
So I'm thinking he didn't understand me.
I am feeling a little bit betrayed...to be honest.
Of course you'd
feel that way.
I am feeling a little bit betrayed...to be honest.
Akane
Hanae
Hinata
Kana
Misuzu
Natsuko
Risa
Sumire
Yuri
Yuzu
And so he also makes his selections from groups two and three.
This makes seven successful candidates in total.
Aika     Kaede     Miyuki   Misuzu     Kana     Hinata     Hanae
Which means there is still one place open.
What will happen?
Aika     Kaede     Miyuki   Misuzu     Kana     Hinata     Hanae
These are the seven girls that Kuro-chan has chosen so far.
Which means there is one more place open.
This is painful to do, but I can only choose one of you to go forward.
This is just...
And that person is...
Nao-chan.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Why not just
pick her earlier?
Nao-chan, please step forward.
Yes.
Nine hours earlier...
Staff: So far, you've already made the first cuts.
Yeah, and you know...
...I'm not going to hold back now.
I want to have my proper explanation right at the end.
But I already gave away the first one.
Thank you so much.
You've passed.
Thank you so much!
Kuro-chan gave away the first card right off the bat.
The real reason for that was...
Seated next to her was Nao. She was the one I was interested in.
Staff: Oh, really?
Yes.
Staff: But you didn't give it to her.
I didn't.
You know...
Such a creepy face.
Basically, I wanted to see her cry.
Huh?
I wanted to see her so relieved that she was moved to tears.
Nao-chan, how do you feel being the last person to pass?
My life is on the line, so I'll work hard.
She is seriously crying!
It's just as he thought!
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Just as expected, she really cried.
No, I saw those tears, I really did.
And they weren't super beautiful tears either.  They were real.
But seriously, she really cried how I thought she would.
It gave me goosebumps.
If she had just passed normally...
She wouldn't really think that much about me, would she?
This way she'd be wondering, "why didn't he pick me?"
She'd be thinking more and more about me.
Then she'd start liking me more and more, right?
She'll like me more and more, and all those emotions will flow out.
In the form of that final tear.
This way she'll like me a dozen times more.
And with that, the first audition for Monster Idol is complete, with these eight members.
You eight will be going on to the training camp.
I think I chose the best members, if I do say so myself.
You know, this isn't just a one day thing.
At the training camp we'll be living together, so I can see your bad sides.
They'd think, "we have to unite and work together wherever we are."
That's one of the many things idols have to be capable of.
I have high expectations for the training camp.
So, let's take the idol world by storm!
The stage is set in Okinawa.
What the hell?!
I want to pass.
What?! What?! What?!
He's touching this
girl again!
I hate liars the most.
Seriously, what
is he doing?!
I like you the most.
This is amazing!
So fun!
The person who will be leaving us tonight is...
What the hell was that?
What the hell.
What kind of company are you running?
He's proper mad!
Seriously, what is that guy doing?
Well, towards the end I was thinking...
...he may be able to pull off making an idol group, but...
...he's way too fast.
He is going quick!
He is blazing through!
It was like that from the start!
I thought it was going to end in that silence...
...but then suddenly that girl is shrieking "aaaah!"
Who was that?
What even was that?
Was something stuck down their throat?
Are you saying someone was choking her?
So what kind of company is this "WACK"?
They have groups like "BiSH".
They create a somewhat different kind of idol.
They get to be their real selves, right?
So, do you think having a group produced by Kuro-chan...
...is the kind of thing WACK does?
It saddens me to say, but you would be correct.
Is that so?
Shigemori, what did you think of it?
Once you get over the cringeyness of it...
Well...it....
...it's the best.
It became the opposite?!
It comes full circle.
Once you're over it, you have the feeling of euphoria.
Exactly! It made me want to watch even more!
Even though it's so bad?
It's just so fun!  It's the best!
Subtitles by WACKisIDOL.