Hello, Bananaman~
I've wanted to meet you!
You surprised me! - Hello!
You were on Tantei Knight Scoop, right?
I heard about it from Takeyama-san.
- You startled me!
We were able to see Tantei Knight Scoop live!
We're really glad.
- I'm happy for you!
I heard from Takeyama-san that you had a really great time.
In the end, everyone was moved to tears!
I love the director â¤
Your dream came true!
22 / 05 / 2017
Broadcast
During the broadcast the other day...
I can see it!
- You can?
The entrance to the ABC building.
Let's go!
We love Tantei Knight Scoop.
And we've seen lots of episodes.
And we want to see them ...  live?
We want to see them live.
They ask directly
To see a taping live
It's no use.
They didn't get to attend a taping.
But...!
Now it would seem that after this broadcast aired, Tantei Kight Scoop was flooded with requests asking them to let them see a taping.
And they fulfilled this request, so they were able to see the show live. - Ah, I see!
What's that? Tokyo Banana [they make cream cakes] ?
You went and bought this just for us!
- Because we're Bananaman after all!
They brought us Tokyo Banana!
I never thought we would get something from you!
What do you think of this studio? [compared to Tantei Knight Scoop]
- It's completely different, isn't it?
Pretty small!
Small?
These are our outfits!
- You're embarrassing us!
I'm sure they've never had a Detective like this!
This is simply the latest fashion trend in Japan.
Definitely not, no way!
Eeeehm~
- No way, he's lying!
But, Tantei Knight Scoop is Number 1.
"Why did you come to Japan" is Number 2!
Ah, I'm glad about that. Thank you!