Subtitles: Zurui
Isn't there anyone that can help??
It's a hero!
"Small..."
I'm sorry...
THE SIDE OF JUSTICE
I got here before you
You're Hamada-kun, right?
- Yes
Do you remember me?
- No...
Just as I thought... you don't
Well...
This afternoon, you
called my justice "small"
I almost cried
By looking at me now...
what do you think?
Am I small?
I'm not small, right?
Not small, but...
"BI"... say it
"BI"
Say it! "BI"
Say it!
Say it with me!
"BI"... "BIG", right??
I just wanted you to understand
I came here because
it was bothering me
I just wanted you to understand that!
- Yes I do
But, I wonder why you
called me "small"?
Well... you we're small...
How did you determine...
Damn, this thing is irritating!
How did you determine
that I was "small"?
- How...
You compared me to the monster, right?
- Yes...
But, don't you think that's strange?
You were comparing
me to the monster...
But what if there was no monster?
If I was there alone, you would
definitely call me "big", right?
- Yes
Isn't that true?
That's why it's strange
You made up your mind on your own,
what size I was, either big or small
Makes me want to cry
Yes...
A big apple or a small watermelon...
I wonder which one is "big"??
Do you understand?
- Yes...
That's the part I really
wanted to make clear
Yes...
Anyway, do you know my name?
No... I don't
What do you think it is?
"something-man"
Just like I thought...
Damn, this thing is cold!
Just as I thought...
You think I am a hero
like Ultra-man, right?
- Yes...
No, I'm not!
I'm Kamen Rider Z!
Ultra-man can change in size, right?
He can grow...
- Yes
But when I change,
I stay the same size!
I am big for a Kamen Rider!
I want you to understand that
- I understand
Even if I fight with a monster
there is no comparison
Because of my size, the
monster wants to fight me
But, I don't run
Don't you think that's impressive?!
I just want you to know
- I'm sorry
Now do you understand?
Well, I said all that I wanted to say
But it still feels like it's not enough...
You're Hamada-kun, right?
- Yes
Do you have something
that you use up?
Huh?
Something that you use up
I'll say it clearly, "money!"
Isn't money great?
I don't really need money, but...
You hurt my feelings, so...
I want you to take a risk too
I was wondering if you
could give me some money?
Sorry
Can you hurry?
I really don't have much on me...
That's fine, whatever you got
Are you sure?
Pay me enough to
make yourself feel bad
I only have coins...
Coins for me is really small money...
Oh ok...
Ok, I won't hold back and accept this
Well, I'll be going
- Ok
Don't tell anyone about this
He's big, but a small human being