COCORICO Channel (COCORICO Channel)
(COCORICO Channel)
Hey, Mike.
What will you do
if you  hear
rat‐tat‐tat at the door
and
"Can you let me come in?"
of stranger?
I will not let him so.
Why?
Because he may be
a robber who pretended to be in trouble.
So I'll not open the door.
That may be possible,
so you mustn't do.
Yeah.
Well.
What will you do
if you may have seen him before?
I will not open the door, too.
Why?
Because I might have seen him
on wanted poster.
That may be possible,
so you mustn't do.
Yeah.
Well,
What will you do if he is uncle Tom who is a kind baker?
I will not open.
Why?
Because he may become robber unexpectedly
even if he is always kind.
"Why has such gentle man done such thing?"
We often heard such thing, right?
Yes.
Well,
what will you do if he is Mr. Brown at your school?
I will not open the door.
Why?
I just don't like him.
What a simple sense!
It's important in your life.
Yes.
Well,
what will you do if it is a hungry squirrel in forest?
I will not open.
Why?
Because
such thing happens
only at fairy tale.
I've never seen or heard about such squirrel.
So I'll not open.
Yes.
It's scary if a squirrel knock the door
and talk to us,
right?
Yes.
Well,
what will you do if he is your grandfather?
My
grandfather?
Yes.
I'll not open.
Why?
Because there's not my grandfather lives here.
Hey, did you see his face?
No-no-no-no.
What's that atmosphere?
Oh, no. How scary!
Oh, my goodness.
What's that atmosphere?
He played with scare intentionally, right?
No-no. It's you.
You asked me scary thing, huh?
It's so scary.
It's completely horrible story.
He said "there's not my grandfather lives here".
That's because you said...
Stop.
you asked it.
But he is right.
Although I'm like old,
I'm not his grandfather
but his father.
So I told you
"there's not my grandfather lives here".
But how scary atmosphere did you make?
I've just told you
there wasn't grandfather here.
I told you clearly.
How horrible story this is!
I really told you clearly.
It was like horror movie, right?
It's scary.
Hey, stop saying strange thing, huh!
What has happened then?
I, by myself, thought
"Did I do anything strange?".
Stop.
What was that pause?
It's scary, right?
It's really scary, right?
No-no-no-no.
But,
you may think "How old is he?",
right?
Hey, it's none of your business.
This is makeup for today's performance.
"There's not grandfather in my home"!
I told you clearly!
How scary!
Stop it now.
No, it's really scary.
Don't make me surprised.
Oh, my goodness.
Don't make fun of me, huh!
Hello, it's "Pizza Italiano".
Hey, it's pizza delivery.
Yes, we've ordered it.
We ordered 2 pizzas.
It's pizza delivery.
It's pizza delivery
though we were talking about stranger.
We ordered pizza
few minutes ago.
Don't make me surprise!
It's just pizza delivery.
There're our medium and large pizzas.
What a good timing.
I thought it was stranger
just like we've talked about now because
it was possible.
It may be possible
like some movies.
And it may be possible
also in TV dramas.
I'm so surprised.
It's pizza delivery though.
And although we wanted only one pizza,
he ordered two.
Both large and medium size.
No-no-no-no.
I can eat up whole of pizza though it's so large.
You know large size pizza at this shop is so large, right?
Large size pizza at this shop is so large.
Now, let's take our pizzas.
I'm going, too.
Oh.
Oh, no!
We got pizzas!
That sound was of falling pizza.
Look this large pizza!
It's larger as I imaged.
How large it is!
It's too large.
And I've told you we couldn't eat up all.
The sound of pizza falling
is so similar to someone's falling down.
And it was good timing.
It's too large size pizza.
Isn't it too large?
So I've told you we couldn't eat up all.
I'll eat remained pizza next day.
I think it's not enough to eat up in 2 days.
I like remained pizza more than just delivered.
Don't say like about curry and rice.
Don't say like...
I like remained pizza more than just delivered.
It's large pizza.
Too large pizza.
Anyone wants to eat?
I'm following large pizza.
Too large pizza.
Oh, no.
Stop following me.
Behind large pizza.
Oh, no. Stop chasing me!
Now, I'm chasing you.
I'm chasing medium pizza.
Oh, no. I'm followed.
I'm chased by large pizza.
Please subscribe! (Please subscribe!)
(Please subscribe!)