Surprisingly enough, people other than the Owarai talents speak of Documental
Saying that it's hilarious, which really surprises me
To be honest, this is definitely not something classy
What surprised me was that Rola said she wants to join
What on earth are you thinking?
And she says "I can handle it"
We've been constantly adding some minor changes to each season
Point System
Zombie System
and that variation seems to be working well
So this time, we will add another new rule too
A new experiment
You can ask someone for help
so an outsider will blend into the group
Helper System
Well, it could be a stray dog, if you like
Did you tell them about the new rule?
Yes I told them
But maybe all of them would ask for help,
and maybe some would say it's not necessary
So the number of helpers will be kept as a secret
The desired "ending"
I'm looking forward to see an instant defeat
Instant may sound too fast
But having the contest to end in a couple of hours
never happened before right?
It's the same as boxing,
first round knockout is much to be desired
Arising in the pandemonium,
is the improvisation of group owarai
While these 10 contestants are enemies to each other,
but it's actually a team play as well,
you can't just be disturbing others,
so this really makes me think that,
Owarai is gathered with a group of gentlemen
Well, gentlemen are showing their dicks
but still, showed in a gentle way
as a gentleman, as a nobleman
Towards the 5th contest
It's just interesting
I'm doing a TV show about Oogiri
as well as shows like Suberanai Hanashi
I'm also the judge for Konto
and I can totally see that people have different strengths
and the players that suits Documental is gradually taking shape
I hope to see a champion contest soon
Yesterday, I've been watering the plants in my garden
and I got panicked when it iced up this morning
But I was told that they will be fine.
This taught me a lesson about the toughness of plants
That being said, I would like to offer you an invitation
Could you prepare one million yen
and gather at a designated location?
I shall reinitiate Documental
I have prepared a reward of 10 million yen for the winner
Of course, participation is voluntary
For those of you who wish to participate
I shall inform you of the time and location
Awaiting your reply
I hope the steps of Spring will bring luck to you
Sincerely, Matsumoto Hitoshi
THE PARTICIPATING COMEDIANS ENTER
That's a big bag
I'm the first one?
Am I the first one?
Akiyama is like a regular member now
Nothing has changed in this room
Well, only this room
I'm Akiyama Ryuji from the group Robert
It's time to win the prize
Excuse me
What's happening?
I remember this envelope
Will you accept it for the 3rd time?
This is exactly the same envelope right?
So as the way you come in and hand me the letter
Akiyama is really an all-round player
And he suits Documental perfectly
It should be no surprise if he wins this time
I personally find his scene
with Kendo Kobayashi very impressive
It was hilarious
That was not planned at all
I was just acting as the massage girl that I know
I seriously didn't expect
my private activities to help out
The chubby imitation creator
But that's still not enough
So I'll take it to the next level this time
Instead of just sticking to the
usual patterns in previous seasons
or just following others blindly
I want to fight with originality
I have that same feeling again
I hope this will be interesting,
even to the comedians that are not participating
Everything is exactly the same,
including the interior
Here he comes
It's his first time to join
Really?
-Akiyama
-For real?
I'm Takahashi from Savanna
I brought in one million yen
and I wanna take home ten million
-Hello     -Hi
Me?
Why would Matsumoto choose to invite me?
Takahashi is more of an intellectual type
Instead of using his body,
He may possibly play the game
with a little bit of cunning
and choose to keep a distance instead
The Super Flatterer talent
People always say that
there's a constant smirk on my face
When I was a student,
some gangsters asked me "what are you laughing at?"
and I got into trouble for 3 times
"What are you laughing at"
Does this count as laughing?
Yes
It does?
Absolutely
What about this?
That's out
Out?
I have to judge this fairly
or else that's another Fujimon incident
they say "Matsumoto is being too nice to Fujimon"
No way!
Wow, Takahashi-san
So that's how it goes
Normally, you should be able to
imagine the victory for a competition
Not at all for this
So to be honest,
I don't think I'm gonna get the 10 million
This is blowing my mind
I can't imagine how Takahashi-san
will be like in this contest at all
Good morning
-Gosh, this is amazing
-Didn't expect this coming
Each of the three is different from the other two
Hello, I'm Kano Eikoh from Maseki Geinosha
Wait a second, is this...
This is awesome
I do think he is interesting
Well, he himself probably won't admit that
He's funny for being absent-minded
What does Documental means to you?
It's a Dohyō
*Dohyō is the ring in which sumo wrestling bouts are held
It's a clash between comedians
It's a clash between weapons
Wait, Sumo don't use weapons...
It's actually a battlefield, please let me change it
The narcissist prank victim
But surprisingly, Eikoh may possibly
be the aggressive player in these times
Although it won't be interesting at all
But those dull moment may instead become his weapon
Although I've joined many talk shows
but most of the time I was tongue-tied or making mistakes,
which ends up with some unexpected laughter
Those laughter were never meant to be there
So this time, I want to make
other comedians laugh with my own gags
I won none of the awards all this time
This is true for the R-1 contest too
Wait a second...
I actually won once in Tsuruko-san's radio show
Yeah I did...
but there's only 3 contestants
We haven't met since you've returned right?
*Eikoh has been in a scandal for cheating with 6 girls
Let me think...
Yeah, we didnt
Aren't those lines on your cheek becoming deeper?
Yeah...
My face is getting hollow
Well, that scandal must be stressing him out
Really?
Well yeah, this guest must be surprising
I'm Jinnai Tomonori
I really want to go home, even now.
-Hello     -Hi
Ahh...so here it comes
-Will you accept it?     -Of course
You'll need to prepare one million yen
It's not about the one million
I don't want to join even if you pay me one million
This is gonna be interesting
He's good at making fun of others
So I think he will be doing a good job
Mister One-man
One thing that I worry about Jinnai is that
he's not interesting at all when it comes to Oogiri
I don't have my own gags,
and I can't make people laugh all of a sudden
I'm not the striker who scores goals
and here comes the police car again
When we had dinner together at the end of last year
We talked about whether to join Documental,
if it ever invites us right?
Yeah, we did we did
-I said I'll definitely deny it
-Yeah you did
Basically, I'm here without any weapons
So I'm aiming for a counter attack instead
Who else is coming?
There's 6 more people
This is amazing
No one is really out of space this time right?
What a long stick
-This is the best stage man     -I know
-Really?     -Wow, amazing members
He's terrified
This shows someone's personality
Well, I see
You do feel anxious though
-Good morning     -Good morning
Here comes the champion of King of Konto
I'm Yamauchi Kenji from Kamaitachi
I'm the champion of King of Konto in 2017, which is said to be the best contest ever
-Here it comes!     -Here it comes
I will accept it
I could see this coming,
as I've been working so hard
If I'm the contestant,
I won't want Yamauchi to be here
This guy doesn't really laughs at all,
and he turns on you with a poker face
His face itself is unfair
An unfair face
The ever-victorious Konto man
He's one of the potential winners
-What do you think?     -Just go
Would you pay me half of it?
Then repay me 5 million if you win
Well, I'll pay for it, no problem
-It's just a verbal promise anyway
-Why did you add that man
This year is really important to us
So I'm seriously aiming to win
-Is this your first time     -Yes it is
But I've been watching this
-You've been watching this show?     -Yes
I'm very greedy
I want to make people laugh to tears,
get them to think that I'm amazing
and win the 10 million all at a time
Is the one million in that bag?
Yeah it's in here
It has been really difficult for me to fund this
But you've got the prize from King of Konto isn't it?
-There was no more left
-You used them all?
I gave it to my parents and repaid my debts
So not much was left
I tried to borrow it from Yoshimoto finance,
but they refused me
-They didn't lend you any?     -Yes
It sounds like a giant is coming
-For real?     -Really?
-Jinnai is here too
-We just hung out recently right
-What are those words? (on his chest)
-Is the red panda still standing up?
Is this for real?
Hello, I'm the fantasista of owarai, Tamura Kenji.
Ciao
Please have a look
Here it comes
I actually think this suits Tamura very well
I've always suggested to invite him
He's the one that can deal with
dullness the most within today's members
He is really strong in this sense
-Kansai's side business king
-Try to ask him about virtual currency
Well, the Industrial Revolution in human history
this changed the use of horses to cars
and this boosted our productivity
which is one giant leap for mankind
The same thing is happening in the world of virtual money.
This is a revolution.
He's basically a slave to money
I bet he wants the 10 million more than anyone else
People seem to only recognize me
as the owner of a BBQ restaurant, or as an entrepreneur
and I want to make them think
"No, no, no, Tamura Kenji is a comedian"
When I was young,
I used to ignore all of the audiences
And only focused on making other comedians laugh
If I could take back those feelings
Maybe I would be able to win the contest
This is your first show after the scandal too right
What scandal?
-Both of you have been in a scandal
-Eh, you too?
No, I have never been in a scandal
-What are you talking about?
-So that's not a scandal?
No it's not a scandal
I just had food poisoning
The restaurant is in a scandal though
-Really?     -This scares me!
Wow, Tamura is here!
You've been on this show right
Jinnai, you cut you hair?
Well, I do cut my hair
-This is amazing!     -Give me a break!
Hello, I'm Kendo Kobayashi
People call me Kobaken
Excuse me? What are you doing here?
I'm looking for some interesting happenings
on the love hotel street
Jinnai, Kenkoba and Tamuken
were actually in the same comedy class
It's exciting to see these three comedians
gathering in the same space
But Kenkoba has been on Documental for a several times
So he might think that "this is my place" against the other two
The man of tenor eros
I realized that it's impossible to win with the tactics last time
there is still something left there for me to do
I really regret for not being able to ejaculate last time
I really regret about it
Last time, I was actually trying
to be interesting instead of winning
But this time,
instead of being interesting, I prefer winning
And instead of winning, I prefer ejaculating
If Jinnai starts doing some kinky things like we did before,
I'll literally cry if this happens
Laugh dude, just laugh
Because he came this far without doing all those shits
So it must be hilarious if Jinnai happens to do it
Those glasses are not fair
Ok ok, don't be scared man
This is becoming a classmates gathering
Almost everyone from our class is here
There's 3 of them here
Hello, I'm Hollywood Zakoshisyoh
-Hello     -Yes?
Invitation from Documental?
Oh, so it's finally here
Well, I probably won't be able to hold back my laughter
He has a unique conception of world
So maybe he's the one to win the contest
But it's gonna be horrible
if he's my daughter's boyfriend
A man with 2 trillion imitations
The king of sloppiness
Wow it's Eikoh-chan!
Your voice is so loud
Of course I am
The 4 people from NSC11th class
-You are happy right?     -Yes I am
There's no broadcasting code right?
Then I am the man!
Some contestants are aggressive
and some are not right?
Some of them do nothing
and simply hold back their laughters
I feel like "what are you doing here?"
Let me show you guys what to do on Documental
I am the true Documental!
I'll show you the max Zakoshisyoh
It's not even 10% when I'm on TV shows
This is what you call "crazy"
This is who you call a "lunatic"
I feel like winning as you're here
Why man! I'm definitely not going to laugh
I think everyone will be surprised to see this guest
He came with nothing, nothing!
This can't be true!
Is this a classmates gathering
Yeah, I know
Why would you accept it?
Hi, I'm Chihara Jr.
So I'm finally invited to the show
-Hello, excuse me     -Yes?
The contestants will all be people I know right
Well, what would be happenning
I have no idea what Junior should be doing too
To be honest,
I thought I'm irrelevant with this kind of shows
The logical minded veteran
-Give me a break, I can't do this man
Some people are actually introverts when they are off the stage
That being said, I wonder how Junior will be doing
I'm personally interested to see a different Junior,
even if he loses the contest
I came here without bringing anything
I try to keep my mind blank
There's nothing I can do about it anyway
I don't have any interesting gags
and I really dislike parties with a lot of people
My social life is extremely shorter than others
I'm primary school level when it comes to socializing
So I'm curious to see how far I'll go too
Kanoh-chan
As the last person comes in,
the atmosphere is probably gonna change completely
Here he comes...wait she?
He shouldn't be a female,
so maybe he just became a female?
This is horrible
That's the worst
Yes, it's horrible
Why are you here?
Hi, I'm Jimmy Onishi
This time, I'm aiming to win the game
What's this? Invi..tation?
He is a man in a million
So we're simply asking him out
and apply economic sanctions to him
Not a good idea to invite him too frequently
This will soon give rise to a nuclear weapon
Super absent-minded nuclear weapon
I personally think it's dangerous
to have both Kuu-chan and Jimmy at a time
They're like Hwasong and Taepodong
It's way too dangerous
After my second time,
many comedians said it was hilarious
Full of confidence
He himself also finds it to be hilarious
I'm Hideko from Fuji-shi
What did you say?
Hideko from Fuji-shi...
So you're not from Kansai any more?
I'm losing two millions now
and Yoshimoto finance is not lending money to me anymore
So if I lose again, I'll be wak...wok...
working for nothing all this time
It's such a shame!
How are we supposed to deal with this
10 people?
So everyone is gathered
-Having Zakoshi here really makes me feel like winning it
-What are you talking about
-This is so awkward     -Yeah it is
This is just the usual members
It's like we're just chilling out
Can't believe that Junior-san is joining
-Good morning     -Good morning
Why did you choose all these members?
Let me ask this first,
Jimmy is that your natural form?
Are you going to start like that?
Yes
How are you supposed to go beyond that
He definitely disadvantaged himself
The contest is not even started yet
You're fine with it?
Yeah, there will be more coming
We're already used to your costume
No problem at all. This is completely irrelevant
-It's like a blank canvas     -Yes
Okay, so do I even need to explain the rules now?
You all brought a million yen
The last person to stay in the room is awarded 10 million
-Yes     -Yep
So there's a yellow card and a orange card, and if you get a red card then you're out
We've been constantly adding some minor changes every time
And for this time, you guys know it
You can ask for help from one supporter of your choice
And the helper will be coming from here
But this helper won't be here for like 1 or 2 hours,
maybe just as few minutes and we'll ask them to leave
So I brought my one million as well
-Wow     -Thank you
Let's open it...
Like you're opening a FamilyMart chicken
So you won't get your hands dirty
So this is not dirty money
So everyone, please hand me your one million yen
-I believe this one million is filled with all sorts of emotions
-Sure it is
We won't be checking this, so I'm counting on you guys
This is amazing
This is so real
Yeah this is definitely real
-This is astonishing     -I want all that
That's 10 million
So putting this as well
and this is 10 million plus my 1 million
Minus the 1 million you payed, that's 10 million to take
Given all sorts of adult matters
This money will be switched with this instead
Like money laundering right
Well, it's somehow troublesome if we don't do so
Yamauchi, are you okay?
Yes I'm fine
You don't look so well
Is there something strange about me?
Well, you seems to be quiet today
I was out from Osaka 8 o'clock this morning
And was working for all this time
So I'm actually a bit tired
Oh you came from Osaka?
-Excuse me Matsumoto-san, my face is smirking even in natural form
-Yeah it's a smirking face
Well, maybe we'll take this into account, but it's hard to say...
-You're laughing now right?
-Am I laughing?
Just try to act cool
Act cool?
Shige does tend to speak with a smirking face
He seems to be asking this on purpose though
Well, so just try to act cool
Is this fine?
-Your laughing for sure
-No I'm not
We will be taking this into account to some extent
But...
But the audience always say something like
"he's being too nice to Fujimon"
Keep in mind that this contest needs team play,
and it is still a variety show
So please trust us,
we will make sure everything goes smoothly
Jimmy, are you okay?
My hands were pinched on Shinkansen...
my hands...my hands...
My hands were pinched on Shinkansen
How are they pinched?
By the door, by the door
Shinkansen's door?
Shinkansen's door pinched my hands
Pinched?
Yes pinched...pinched...
-Your hands got stucked?
-Yes
The train chugged out of the station with your hands stucked?
Yes my hands were like this for quite a while
Your fingers were outside the train?
Yeah starting from the Hamamatsu station
Why did you leave it like that?
Why are you sharing such an interesting episode now?
Why are you near the doors?
I wanted to buy Unagi Bento
That's a proper reason
-Unagi Bento is sold near the door...
-He's still talking about it
-Then it bangs
-Yeah the doors banged!
-If you shared this later, I must have laughed
-That was close
-Stucked until Tokyo station?
-No, until Shin-Yokohama station and finally relaxed
But then my hands became like this
-The contest starts as the light changes
-Got it
So good luck guys
-This is stressing me out
-Good luck guys
-I'm getting nervous
-Let's move over there
Can I leave my bag here?
Sure
Season 5, start!
We're already here for like 20 mintues right
Yes, you're right
So it started
Yeah it started
You wanna do something?
No, I'm just thirsty
I'm really thirsty
He's drinking it
He really drank it
What did you drink?
Wait a moment, he really drank it, that's insane
It's a mouthwash dude
Gosh, it stinks badly
It really stinks
That's no joke, Jimmy-san
Well, but I'm really thirsty
You can't drink it just because you're thirsty
-And it starts to stink
-That smells
Yeah it is
Are you serious?
You replaced it with something else right?
No, that's for real
Aren't you a fool?
But it doesn't say that you can't drink it
So it's drinkable?
-Just in case someone drinks it
-Well, yeah
But it's still no good to drink it dude
-But it's diluted so...
-This is awful
Of course it's awful
How do you feel?
-It says don't use it for anything other than mouthwash
-It's burning...
It must be burning your intestine!
My chest is burning
That's really dangerous
-Drink some water
-Yeah I should, this is terrible
What are you doing man,
why did you do that right in the beginning
-You wanna eat some eggs?
-Yeah eggs should help
Eat the egg to dilute it
-Egg?...
-Give it a try
Sit here and face up
This is terrible
-Are you ready?
-Yes
This should dilute it
How do you feel?
It's probably starting to dilute a bit
Why are you shaking?
Because of the soda
Junior and Takahashi were close
You want another one?
That's probably too much
Why did you drink it without a doubt?
This is atopy
Kanoh is the same too
Are you allergic to eggs?
No, no, it's atopy
Kanoh has serious allergies
What allergies do you have again?
Well I'm allergic to soybeans, pollen, dogs, cats, house dust, and my own sweat
-Sweat?
-Your own sweat?
I have sweat allergy
-So you get itchy when you sweat?
-Yes
Yeah so I can't be sweating a lot
Shall you try some eggs then?
You're not allergic to eggs right?
I ate it already
Oh you mean me?
Can you eat eggs?
Aren't you allergic to it?
I'm not allergic to eggs
What's this?
What's happening here?
-It's therapy
-Therapy?
He's not even allergic to eggs
He laughed
Me?
Tamura-san it's not fair to wear those sunglasses
-Yeah take it off
-You're laughing right?
-Not at all
-Zakoshi-san please take a look
-Look at me
-Look at Zakoshi
Come one
Ah, he passed out
-Take off the sunglasses
-It's too hard to judge
Fine, let me get changed then,
it's awful to wear this anyway
-Okay
-Good idea
This costume is not going to make anyone laugh right?
Yeah, we're already used to it
No one will laugh right, I'll get changed then
Maybe someone will laugh if you show us a full version Ciao
Ciao
No, it's not gonna work right
-Your voice was surprisingly small
-Yes, it's actually meant to be small
People thought it will be loud
No, you have to say it with love
What about a business Ciao?
Ciao
What about in front of a swimming pool?
and it's really noisy
Ciao
That's a "kyaaa"
-Wait Junior-san...
-What about rising sun...
Junior-san
I hate Oogiri
-This isn't Oogiri...
-No it sounds like it is, Junior-san
Junior is very close
No it's not Oogiri at all
It does sound like Oogiri though
But you're indeed doing Ciao at all sorts of places right?
Yes, but if Junior-san is the one asking,
it just sounds like Oogiri
If that's the reason,
then I can't even talk anymore
Teach him a lesson, young man
There is no escape here,
You're supposed to do
whatever you've been asked to do
Yeah this young man will do
his Ramen-tsukemen gag too
At a swimming pool
Everybody listen to me!
Ramen, tsukemen, I am ikemen! Okay!
*Ikemen means handsome
He's loud
He turned around
Do it when your pet dog is dead
Look, it's definitely Oogiri
Dead?
Thank you, thank you so much
Ramen, tsukemen, I am ikemen...Okay!
No it's not okay, it's dead
Well, it's one set including "okay"
Nice one buddy
That's amazing
Well, I'll read him a lecture afterwards
You're really not feeling well right?
Yeah, it was such a bad move
Yeah it is
I shouldn't have done that
I'm pushing myself too hard
It can damage your health
Are you really okay?
Not at all, try to drink some
No way, it clearly says
don't use it for anything other than mouthwash
Well, I must be fully sterilized though
Well yeah
Zakoshi, how is your newborn baby?
They are twins
What's their name?
-It's Half-dev and Full-dev
-Stop lying
How do you spell it?
It means Half-devil
No way
What about Full-dev?
It's Full-devil
You got into trouble for that before
She's a girl
Both of them?
She's intersexual
Which one?
Half-dev is masculine woman
-So she's intersexual?
-Yes
And Full-dev is feminine male
What happens if you have another baby?
I'll call them Ambalan Dendelen
Ambalan and Dendelen?
-Yes Ambalan and Dendelen
-So if it's twins again
Junior is in a pickle
Ambalan and Kambalan
What about Dendelen?
Dendelen will be for triplets
For triplets, they'll be called
Ambalan, Kambalan and Dendelen
For quadruplets, it's Dondoron
It's Mi and Ami
-No no no
-Eh, it's Mi and Ami?
-No no
-What a cute name
And they are both girls
-For real?
-No no no
They're called Headhunter A and Headhunter B
That's the name of the twin brothers wrestling for W*ING
How did you know that
So it's Miki and Might?
It's Mi and Ami,
because their Dad is Hollywood, so they are Miami
That's awesome
No no no, it's Miki and Tetsuya
Miki and Tetsuya?
Miki and Tetsuya
*Miki Tetsuya is another owarai talent from the same comedy class,
Do-wa-zu and Ore ore are both his gags
Do-wa-zu?
Ore ore!
What a sudden Ore ore...
Ore ore...
Want to see my gag "Too exaggerated imitation"?
What about a "Too exaggerated Desuyo"
*Desuyo is a owarai talent famous for his gag "I~am~sorry~", and Zakoshi's gag is to imitate it exaggeratedly
*Desuyo's "I~am~sorry~": https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SFw1vFxwbGc
OHHHHHH
I AM
SORRY
This is killing me
Koizumi Junichiro
*Koizumi Junichiro was the Prime Minister of Japan from 2001 to 2006
Too exaggerated Koizumi Junichiro? Okay.
Hello
I'm Koizumi Junichiro
Junior is out
-That was close!
-That was really close!
You saw that many times
That was close!
-You asked for it
-So it's me?
First thing first, this applies to everyone
You're drinking too much water
You've been drinking it so many times
just to muddle through
Of course it's fine if you're really thirsty
but don't keep it here
And up to now, one person is out
-Junior
-That scared me! I thought it's me
You're basically laughing all the way
Then starting to drink water and trying to muddle through
I can't deal with Zakoshi
Yeah Zakoshi is hilarious
I was close with that one too, well done for holding on
That was amazing
Takahashi was close too
Takahashi and Junior are always at the limit
I need to be aware of Zakoshi
Junior will be given a yellow card
to serve as a warning to the others
That's all!
It's fine to laugh now right
That was quick!
Yeah that was really quick
Junior-san you are the one
who asked him to perform though
Well, I'm just asking this in rotation