THIS PROGRAM INCLUDES CONTENT THAT
MAY BE INAPPROPRIATE FOR SOME VIEWERS.
PLEASE ENJOY THE SHOW
AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION.
-Mr. Matsumoto.
-Howdy.
-Thank you for coming.
-You're welcome.
So, this is the beginning of Season Two.
HITOSHI MATSUMOTO
Season One of Documental was a huge hit.
We've been saying this
right from the start,
but this is very much an experiment.
I wasn't sure how it would go.
But I did hear a lot of positive comments
about the show.
-Indeed.
-Yeah.
PROFESSIONAL COMEDIANS
Jimmy...
Jimmy?
Excuse me. I'm going to stand.
THEY MUST MAKE THE OTHERS LAUGH...
That's hot!
WITHOUT LAUGHING THEMSELVES
A SIX-HOUR BATTLE ROYAL
Ow!
Ouch!
That hurts.
MORTAL COMBAT
"THE NO-HOLDS-BARRED SHOW"
Do I think it worked?
I think that my feelings about the show
and our viewers' reaction to the show
could be somewhat different.
However, we didn't end up with
one clear winner last time.
NO ULTIMATE WINNER
Some people were okay with that.
Others wanted to see a clear,
ultimate winner.
There were different opinions on that.
FOR 10 MILLION YEN
-Dodgebee.
-What the hell is that?
Not dodgeball?
A BATTLE OF THE MINDS
A BATTLE OF STAMINA
What if we all go home with nothing?
THE STAKES ARE BIG
Should we try an impression?
THAT'S WHY THEY PLAY DEFENSIVELY
We had players who wouldn't
go on the offensive, and to make it worse,
they stepped back when somebody else
went on the offensive.
That's like the old style of
Japanese judo.
They must go on the offensive.
Score points. Avoid stalemates.
BATTLE AGGRESSIVELY
A SIX-HOUR-LONG BATTLE
Is this guy okay?
Let me do my move.
NEW RULE CHANGES
This time I want to make sure we have...
A DEFINITE WINNER
I want to make it impossible for
passive players to win.
ONLY THE PLAYER WHO COMPETES AGGRESSIVELY
WILL BE CROWNED WINNER
You might call it an improvement.
We will be adding even tougher new rules.
I think these new rules will make
what's funny about the show more obvious.
That's how this season will unfold.
Probably.
BEFORE THE BATTLE
I am certain
that on this season of Documental
we will be crowning our first winner.
I'm nearly positive.
We'll have our first champion.
THE FIRST EVER CHAMPION
It's going to be a historic moment.
I'm absolutely trembling with excitement
already.
SIX HOURS LATER
AFTER THE BATTLE
Three, two, one...
-And we're filming.
-Good work, everyone.
That was an amazing battle.
It was an amazing battle.
That's the kind of battle I wanted to see.
IT'S HIS KIND OF BATTLE
-Right?
-Yes.
How can I put it?
It showed what happens
when comedians are really pushed
into a corner.
Excuse me.
-Good morning.
-Hi.
This is for you.
What is it?
Yes?
Hello.
You scared me. What is it?
For you.
The invitation...
You're right.
Then we'll do this.
-What?
-For you.
Again?
Looking forward to it?
Documental...
Hello.
I know what this is.
It's for Mr. Matsumoto's...
Hello.
-May I have a bit of your time?
-Yes?
So it came, huh?
I see.
Excuse me.
Hello.
I know what this is.
It wasn't like I was bullied.
They just had fun with me.
-They teased you?
-Yes. Well...
-They didn't call it "bullying" back then.
-So, you were bullied?
-Yes.
-Excuse me.
Yes?
This is for you.
An invi... invi...
'Twas in the morning sunlight,
beckoned by the swaying plum blossoms,
that I tried cleaning up outside
the entrance to my house.
I caught a cold.
It is still quite chilly.
I send you this invitation
with my best intentions.
I sincerely hope you will join me
with one million yen on your person.
I am hosting a Documental.
Twice in a row? For real?
Why didn't he pick Kurosawa?
Please be honest.
Will you accept the invitation?
At the moment, it's 50/50.
I have prepared 10 million yen
as the champion's prize.
Whether to participate or not,
the decision is yours.
It's an invitation from
the great Mr. Matsumoto.
-You're quick.
-Of course, I'll participate.
It's an honor to be invited
by Mr. Matsumoto himself.
But this is scary.
Life couldn't be better now.
I've been waiting for this.
If you are willing to participate,
I will contact you again
about the time and venue.
I look forward to your reply.
May the coming spring bring
great happiness to each of you.
Sincerely, Hitoshi Matsumoto.
There's no way I'd say no.
There will be 10 million yen,
right there.
Of course, you'd fight for it.
I can't believe any comedian
would turn down this opportunity.
I am very grateful.
And I'm excited about it, but...
I don't have the one million to compete.
When we filmed the last season,
it was a new experience for all.
I think the players were
grasping in the dark a lot.
But this time, each participant will
have already seen Season One.
They'll have that in mind.
PREPARING FOR MORTAL COMBAT
And that means,
I doubt we'll have anyone come in
completely unarmed.
EACH WITH THEIR OWN TACTICS
I expect they'll come up with
a number of different strategies.
WARFARE THAT DISREGARDS
THE CODE OF ETHICS THAT BINDS TELEVISION
I heard a bit about
Amazon's thoughts on the show.
Apparently they're
quite tolerant of dirty jokes.
TOLERANT OF DIRTY JOKES
I don't know if that's true or not,
but I guess it is.
I was even told that,
as long as we don't zoom in,
we can even show penises.
I thought,
"Oh, they really are the Amazon."
THE COMEDIANS ARRIVE AT THE BATTLEFIELD
Here goes.
Well, for the first participant...
Obviously, no one else is there.
He must be nervous.
I'm Yoshimura,
from Heisei Nobushikobushi.
I shall definitely win. Just watch!
My first response to his casting was,
"He's the least likely guy to win."
THE LEAST LIKELY TO WIN
Would any professional comedian ever laugh
at his cheap, shallow comedy?
CHEAP, SHALLOW COMEDY
There may be one thing that
differentiates me from the others.
I'm the silliest.
"THE WILD CANNON COMEDIAN"
This is crucial to boost both
my skills and my career.
I must win this title.
I've never won any awards.
Not for sketch comedy or manzai.
If I don't win this, I won't be able to
call myself a professional comedian.
I must win, no matter how I do it.
VICTORY BY ANY MEANS
It's simple. Make them laugh.
It makes no difference whether it's
the public, or comedians.
They're all just people.
I'm extremely confident.
How could I put it?
It's like we'll have a bunch of
hard-hitting, high-flying wrestlers,
and he'll be pinching them.
THE SMALL TECHNIQUE EXPERT
That's a role he'll probably find
for himself.
There's a chance he will create
something funny with that role.
This is exciting.
I can imagine it wouldn't be nice
to be first.
Of the nine other participants,
you have no idea who is coming next.
It's all coming back to me.
It's you!
No way!
Yoshimura?
So, this makes it
his second time on the show.
I am Daisuke Miyagawa. I'll do my best.
When I received the invitation,
I really thought hard about my reply.
But I ended up coming.
After actually being on the show,
at the end of the day, I guess I had fun.
Just being in that special place.
HE WANTS TO STAY IN THAT
"SPECIAL PLACE"
I think that's why I was drawn
to this second season.
Can he win? Well...
He does have experience.
I think his chances are quite strong.
WILL PREVIOUS EXPERIENCE
HELP HIM WIN?
I always used to make up games,
just for fun in the dressing rooms.
I'll play those old games,
and when everyone's off guard,
I'll take them out. That's my plan.
I called one "Analympics."
To be honest,
I plan to blitz them with that again.
He'll be very different
from the Daisuke you see on Itte-Q.
THE FACE HE CAN'T SHOW
ON PRIME TIME TV
I think we'll get to see that.
I will show my butthole.
I think I can take down two or three
with that strategy.
You sat there before, right?
-I did, but... Yeah.
-Right?
I feel more relaxed here.
I'll sit here.
It's a relief to have you here.
It must be different for first-timers,
compared to those with experience.
But...
I don't necessarily think that
the experienced players have an advantage.
You're a fierce opponent, too.
-Who is it?
-I have no idea.
It's you.
I am Miyuki Oshima,
from Morisanchu.
So, I'm here.
On Documental.
I got the invitation...
I have no idea what will happen.
She really is funny.
There are few female comedians
who could put up a decent fight here.
THE FIRST FEMALE COMPETITOR
But I expect big things from Oshima.
The thing about Oshima is,
her poker face is funny.
EVEN HER POKER FACE IS A WEAPON
People may even laugh at that.
And when push comes to shove,
she can go fully nude.
SHE CAN GO BUCK NAKED
Whether or not that happens,
we'll have to see.
"Can you do it?"
"Can you really make them laugh?"
That's what the invitation meant to me.
So, I will go on the offensive.
Her defenses are weak.
WEAK DEFENSE
After all...
Oshima tends to laugh easily.
People often say to me,
"Your husband is rich. Why do you bother?"
They're probably thinking that now.
But we have separate bank accounts.
I use a SIM-free cellphone.
They are cheaper.
It costs 1,200 yen a month.
How many shows would I have to do
at Lumine to earn this much?
How many times would I have to show
my butt to get this amount of money?
Think about that before you judge.
ONE MILLION YEN
-Has it begun?
-Not yet.
-You're building something already.
-I'm not.
-It's cold in here.
-I'm totally normal.
Someone's here.
This is bad. Bad. Bad. Bad.
A monster has arrived.
I see.
I think they may have been surprised
because they expected the comedians to be
members of the Yoshimoto agency.
Hi, I'm Yuki Himura
from the duo Bananaman.
I have really been
looking forward to this.
I will do my best.
It reflects how Mr. Matsumoto is such
a "pure" person.
I mean, it couldn't get simpler.
We get locked in a room,
and the strongest wins.
I think Himura will really be
a tough competitor.
It's like he has a black belt in comedy.
THE BLACK BELT COMEDIAN
I think we should consider him
as a contender for the crown.
-Where should I sit?
-Anywhere.
-Probably somewhere around here.
-There?
-But I don't want Himura here.
-There's no other place.
It would be an understatement to say
I laugh easily.
If I find something funny,
I won't be able stop myself.
If I do laugh, I'll just have to accept
that they were too funny.
But for the moment,
I want to have fun.
I want to enjoy the battle.
That's my biggest focus now.
The contest will be a hybrid of
"pro wrestling" and "street fighting."
I look forward to having someone
make a move on me.
There's no point in dodging every attack.
I'll take a few punches on the chin,
and sidestep some others.
That's what Documental is all about.
This will be a fun six hours.
Ideally,
I'll make every single one of them laugh,
and then take the 10 million yen.
Ideally...
-I'll sit next to you, Daisuke.
-Please, give me a break.
-I always end up with a monster here.
-Yes, Jimmy was a monster.
-I'm not a monster.
-You are!
-Not so fast.
He slapped his money out already.
-This can't be true.
-This is fun. It's amazing!
I thought we'd all be Yoshimoto.
Everyone was Yoshimoto last time?
Give me a break.
That face is going to get me every time.
Go over there.
Seriously. Move.
Now they have no idea who will be coming.
I can imagine that would be unsettling.
-You're a threat.
-And we didn't expect you to be here.
-Really?
-I really was surprised.
-You didn't expect me?
-Not at all.
Someone's here.
It's Koji.
I told you.
Not everybody's Yoshimoto.
No way.
This time is going to be tough.
Hi. I'm Kazuya Kojima from the duo Unjash.
I will definitely win today.
Take a step back with that microphone.
Hey!
And stuff like that.
I'm powerful, right?
HE'S POWERFUL?
That was impressive, right?
That's what I do.
When I first saw his name,
I thought it was a misprint.
I thought,
"Hmm? What? Who the hell are you?"
Why was I selected?
Mr. Matsumoto must really like me.
It's not a funny joke, but the fact
he keeps saying it is even unfunnier.
He keeps making that same joke,
over and over.
It must have got a couple of laughs, once.
But for the past four years,
he's been making that same bad joke.
The only thing left to say is,
"Who the hell are you?"
I don't think he'll go on the attack much.
AN EXPERT IN DEFENSE?
But I think his defenses are weak, too.
-Why you?
-Hey, I'm your senior!
-When will you learn?
-They will bug each other all day.
My comedy is simple and, um...
Straightforward.
MR. STRAIGHTFORWARD SIMPLE
To be honest,
most people don't laugh at me.
But comedians find me funny.
He is different from Yoshimura.
How can I put it?
He's a dunce at comedy,
but we'll see how that pans out.
THE DUNCE
-Another unexpected competitor.
-Really?
-No way.
-He's dangerous.
I'm laughing already
just thinking about what'll happen.
-The scenery from here is funny already.
-This is bad.
-I have Oshima in the background.
-I'm Kojima!
-That wasn't a cue.
-He meant her.
Don't use your best joke already.
-It wasn't a name gaff.
-Messing up already?
Well, Kojima is an idiot.
He has weird reflexes we can't control.
-You're back?
-Again?
This is his second time, right?
This guy showed up again?
He came again.
I'm Fujimoto from the duo Fujiwara.
This is my second time participating.
Last season,
I made it to the final four.
This season,
I hope to actually win.
I could have refused,
but I didn't want to regret
that decision later.
When I imagined a second season,
without me in that room,
it just didn't feel right.
Fujimoto isn't really one to
initiate things,
but he is a mood-maker.
He can create chaos within that room
and as a by-product of that chaos,
he may be able to trigger some laughter.
I think he'll do that for us.
-I forgot my million yen.
-Really? Then you have to leave.
-Seriously.
-Get out.
-Don't say that.
-You're way too relaxed!
This is my second time.
I tend to talk too much.
I'm always talking.
I'm always moving around, too.
I think that led to my success
in the last season.
ALWAYS ON THE MOVE
Unfortunately, Fujimoto has a weakness.
He tends to laugh too easily.
He laughs at accidental humor.
Fujimoto, red card.
Just before I lost, I had a tiny little
thought creep into my mind:
"I don't want to be here anymore."
That marked the beginning of
my downfall in the mental battle.
It's something you must
experience yourself.
Only those last four people
will understand.
What's this?
That's our question.
-It's not just Yoshimoto?
-It's not fair.
Oshima, quit making that face.
-It's too soon.
-I'm not.
-You did.
-I didn't make a face.
-You had a funny air about you.
-I did nothing.
Please stop it.
-Kojima's here, too.
-I am.
-Actually...
-Why are you here?
What's that supposed to mean?
See. He's bad news.
-Stop doing that.
-You can't do that.
-Stop it.
-Don't go full-throttle so soon.
-He was being rude.
-We have six hours.
Comments made from a straight-man
perspective make you laugh more.
Hello.
Give us a break!
This guy is funny.
-He's funny.
-He really is.
He's funny.
I'm Saito, from the trio Jungle Pocket.
I have come to take that 10 million!
Okay!
I like this player.
He possesses a quality
that I don't have at all.
A UNIQUE CHARACTER
I think that Saito will probably be
a constructive player.
This is a surprise.
Don't you all laugh too easily?
We're laughers?
-Good point.
-How true.
-I come from that family.
-The Laughers.
-I'm a laugher.
-Me, too.
Saito seems quite calm and composed.
My only weapon is the fact
that I went to acting school.
I was trained at the
Bungakuza Theater Company as an actor.
I believe that my acting skills
are my greatest weapon.
That's what makes him different
from most comedians.
He is a curve ball of sorts.
When I watch him,
that comes across strongly to me.
He makes me laugh quite a lot.
Wouldn't it be nice if
the audience laughed more at him?
Why does he bomb so much?
Sometimes it makes me wonder.
-We have a whole variety of comedians.
-Amazing.
This is amazing.
We still have three more coming?
This is enough already.
She's making a move.
Cut it out!
Quit making that face.
You don't need to use that here.
-I'm not pulling a face.
-Yes, you are.
She had a baby.
She has a little kid.
Think about that.
-She's a mother. Mommy.
-Think about where she's coming from.
-I hate this.
-They get more extreme at the end, right?
Wow.
-I see.
-Him?
-Hello.
-He's the guy who grows on you.
I'm Tsuda, from the Yoshimoto duo Daian.
This guy...
I thought it might be nice to invite
a full-blown old-style comedian for once.
HE STILL REEKS OF
OLD-STYLE OSAKA
I thought that throwing someone like him
into that room
might be worth a try.
To be honest,
I haven't even thought about what I'll do.
People usually make fun of me.
If nobody makes fun of me,
I might not do anything.
Wowowow! Wowowow!
I'm giving you a Wow!
He has a lot of power.
You're lucky to have been called.
I like him. This is bad news.
-He's really funny, right?
-He is.
Thanks, guys.
He has quite a thick skin.
I think he'll hang in there
until the later stages.
I have a feeling he'll be one of
the final participants.
I prepared half of the million yen myself,
and for the rest...
I married into my wife's family
and got it from her grandma.
HE BORROWED 500,000 YEN
FROM HIS WIFE'S GRANDMOTHER
These members are totally different
from what I expected.
Sure was different.
I have no damn idea what you expected.
-Why are you so aggressive? Cut it out.
-What's this?
-Take it easy. We're just chatting.
-Let's enjoy this.
We didn't all make predictions, you know?
-He opened the door with vigor.
-Who is it?
-It's Kotouge.
-The guy with all the momentum.
-He's on a roll.
-He sure is.
I'm Kotouge, from the duo Viking.
How am I?
Well, my heart is thumping.
He's an interesting player.
I wonder how he will get involved.
Kotouge has been on a real hot streak.
I do want to participate in this.
If I were to turn down this opportunity,
I would just be running away.
I'd be running away from comedy.
To be perfectly honest,
it's not like I'm motivated to win
the 10 million yen prize money.
It will be insanely funny in there.
I just want to stay in that room
for as long as I possibly can.
HE WANTS TO EXPERIENCE IT
FOR AS LONG AS POSSIBLE
He actually laughs easily.
On TV, he plays the straight man
who makes funny quips.
He creates laughs by getting angry.
THE ANGER ARTIST
But, even though most viewers
probably wouldn't expect it,
he laughs at the corniest stuff.
HE LAUGHS AT THE SILLIEST THINGS
Having watched the first season,
I think this is all about "Big Laughs."
NOT SUPERFICIAL JOKES
Since I was born with these genes,
I would like to use my head.
TAKE ADVANTAGE OF HIS HEAD
He has a number of issues
in his private life as well.
He got involved in some messy stuff.
He might want to escape into work.
I talked to Kotouge about this.
That's right.
-About Documental.
-Yes, he did.
-After the show?
-He came up and said it looked like fun.
I did. Yes.
Fujimoto said it was the best gig
he had last year.
That's right.
It was just as I thought.
So I said,
"If you ever get the offer, take it."
-That's right.
-Wow.
-We did talk about that.
Seriously?
He armed himself with a prop already?
Who is it?
He's started already!
You already started!
I'm not doing anything.
I'm not.
These are my normal clothes.
That's uncalled-for.
-This is how I want to start.
-Already?
That's too quick.
I'm Jimmy Onishi. I'm back for revenge.
I will...
definitely win,
and take home 10 million yen!
I'm wearing a costume and some makeup.
There's nothing wrong with that.
This isn't to make them laugh
at the start.
I just want to slip in a jab
before it starts.
I figured he'd be participating...
It's like...
he's a gift from another planet.
It's impossible for us earthlings
to understand him.
A GIFT FROM OUTER SPACE
That's pretty much it.
Apparently he was very confident
going into last season.
I'm glad that people liked
what I did last time,
but it hasn't led to any new work.
I think people don't know how to cast me.
NO EXTRA WORK
-What are you doing?
-Go wash your face!
-Wash that off. Now.
-Seriously.
-We have to make a fresh start.
-You're playing dirty.
This is a fresh start!
I will definitely win.
Then I'll buy an apartment.
I want to live near a convenience store.
Somewhere convenient, um...
I want to live somewhere that is
easily accessible.
He's an idiot,
but when it comes to comedy,
he can learn and make progress.
I suppose he will have thought up
some kind of plan.
Are you serious?
-Is that your own money?
-Of course, it is.
-I can wash it later.
-Okay, you're fine for now.
What a wide variety.
This will be amazing.
Why is Oshima acting so innocent?
She's building something already.
-What's with you?
-Nothing.
The more I know you,
the more I'll laugh, so I'm trying to...
That scared me.
Why is he angry again?
What a mean look.
I want to vomit.
You all talk a lot, don't you.
You've babbled away the whole time.
-Because we're so nervous.
-Trying to hide the butterflies.
I saw each of your entrances.
I think that this lineup truly is amazing.
I'm a little worried this might end
in a flash.
-He's right.
-I could see that.
And Jimmy, that's not...
Can you have a word with him?
This is for everyone to laugh at
before we start.
That's a bit too much.
Don't the rules cover things like this?
From the start?
-This must be against the rules.
-He won't read the rules anyway.
If you're going to wear makeup,
be more flamboyant.
It's just subtle enough that
it's annoyingly weird.
That's why it's funny.
Does everyone have their million yen?
Please take it out.
All right?
Let's see the million yen in cash
that each of you brought
for this competition.
You have the same envelope.
-His has a currency strap.
-It does!
We have many UFJ Bank users.
Jimmy, what's that?
What's that?
My bible.
-Jimmy, that's...
-Just stop it.
You didn't have to fold your envelope
and put it away in your bible.
Like I've been saying,
it's the comments made from a straight-man
perspective that lead to actual laughter.
-That's true.
-But we can't just ignore something funny.
Unfortunately, straight comments
multiply the laughs.
-That's so true.
-It sure is.
Please pass around your million yen.
The straight-man role
is the crucial element.
Look at that.
If you sense something's funny,
you can't stop yourself.
You react with the perfect timing.
Wow.
I'm passing around millions of yen.
Jimmy did something again.
He'll check one million is there.
It's not all there.
The straighter the comeback,
the funnier it becomes.
How true.
Look at that.
That is amazing.
And I wonder if you've all
noticed something.
There is 10 million yen here now.
The winner of this competition
takes home 10 million.
That's how it's supposed to work.
But that doesn't mean
you actually win 10 million yen.
It's only nine million in profit.
Leave the rest to me.
Really?
WHOEVER DOESN'T LAUGH
GETS 10 MILLION YEN
PLUS MATSUMOTO'S MILLION YEN
-Wow!
-That's 11 million yen!
Look at that.
-The currency strap is yellow.
-For real?
Amazing.
That makes more sense.
Exactly. This is how it should be.
But this looks a bit ugly,
so we'll be giving the winner this.
New bills.
And my contribution goes here.
To actually see that with my own eyes
is truly amazing.
One of you will be taking this home today.
-"The Japanese Dream."
-Come on!
That's the Japanese Dream.
Please take a seat.
Come on!
I believe that you've all seen
the last season of this show.
I'll be using these again.
-Red and yellow cards.
-Okay.
In extreme cases,
I may use the red card
without any warning.
-But I doubt that will happen.
-Okay.
If you get two yellow cards,
you will be removed from the competition.
Two yellows and we're out.
In that case,
you go home without your million yen.
Only two yellows?
Are we clear?
And one more thing. This time...
The time limit is six hours.
But if six hours have passed,
and we still have two or three people
remaining,
we'll implement the point system.
-What's that?
-Point system?
Over the next six hours,
the player who has accumulated
the most points becomes
the winner.
-This time we'll definitely have a winner.
-No draws?
IF THERE'S NO VICTOR AFTER SIX HOURS,
WHOEVER'S MADE THE OTHERS LAUGH
THE MOST WINS
So, be aggressive about getting laughs.
We will be recording who took out who.
I see.
You can't win by keeping quiet?
You can't win if you play it safe.
-We have to mrrrm mrrm...
-Sorry?
We have to make a move, right?
That's right.
He's got it.
We have to make a move.
And we've also prepared a few props.
They're over here.
You don't have to use them.
What are these clips?
Maybe they're for your nipples.
-That sounds useful.
-Okay.
-Good luck to you all.
-Thank you.
-Let's do this!
-Let's have fun.
-Are you serious?
-We should have fun, right?
Right?
We'll get to witness the ultimate show.
It's okay to lose.
What's with the shirt?
This isn't for laughs.
I liked the design.
You like how it's funny.
If you weren't after laughs,
you wouldn't wear that.
Is it that funny?
-Yes, it is.
-No, it's stylish.
Or you're a werewolf.
This is bad. Really bad.
Well then,
let us begin!
-We can't laugh anymore, right?
-This is it.
-No more laughing?
-Right.
The battle starts now.
Everyone. Have some crackers.
Crack...
-Take one.
-For us?
Yeah. It's nice to meet you.
This is my first time with Jimmy.
-It's nice to meet you.
-The honor's mine.
Please take these crackers as
a token of new friendship.
-What are they?
-A token of new friendship.
-Why crackers?
-I'll go without.
Crackers for friendship?
They make your mouth dry.
-Didn't you just laugh?
-I didn't.
The truth is...
That was quick.
-That was probably Jimmy.
-Yeah, Jimmy.
-He was laughing.
-Yes, he laughed.
-The decision's been made.
-No way.
-It was Jimmy or Yoshimura.
-Jimmy laughed.
It wasn't me.
I was just being normal.
Are you an idiot?
You laughed just like normal.
-He did.
-You laughed, right?
You were smiling the whole time, right?
You laughed the whole time.
You've been on the show before.
-Did I laugh?
-You absolutely did.
-You laughed.
-That was shocking.
You laughed before the start,
and never stopped.
The whole time.
He has the cards.
Not so fast.
-How quick!
-You laughed too hard.
You get an orange card.
ORANGE CARDS ARE WARNINGS
LESS SERIOUS THAN YELLOW
-You call that laughing?
-You really were laughing.
You laughed!
-Why crackers?
-I'm fine.
Crackers for friendship?
They make your mouth dry.
The truth is...
That was quick.
I was just talking.
-The talking bit wasn't a problem.
-But you laughed, too.
You kept on smiling,
and then you went, "Ha ha ha."
That's laughing.
You went, "Ha ha ha."
That's laughing out loud.
This is your second season.
-I hate having the clock stopped so early.
-Our thoughts exactly.
Are you nervous?
You have a weird pimple.
Please stop that.
It will become funny.
Mr. Matsumoto!
-It's bleeding.
-Stop sucking us in.
It's bleeding.
Blood's coming from his weird pimple.
-I have to take a look.
-For real?
-It's bleeding.
-It is!
No more messing around, okay?
-We get a cue?
-Yes.
Let's pour vinegar on them.
How dare you pour vinegar on my panties?
Because he was taking too long.
This is too much!
It's my fault. I used them.
Ow!
That hurt!
What are you doing to my gag?
My fingers are too weak.
They'll go rusty.
-What's he doing?
-He's not getting our point.
-Huh?
-What is this?