THIS PROGRAM INCLUDES CONTENT THAT
MAY BE INAPPROPRIATE FOR SOME VIEWERS.
PLEASE ENJOY THE SHOW
AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION.
What kind of comedian
is suited to Documental?
Well, you know...
For example, in gymnastics there's a move
named after the gymnast Shirai.
When you perform an amazing new technique,
they name it after you, right?
If we did the same for Documental,
we could name a new technique for people
who are amazingly bad.
It would be "Uchima."
That's how unsuited he was to the show.
No way!
Why?
No way.
I won't do any good with Nobu here.
But when you really think about it,
Uchima was funny.
Don't get me wrong.
It's not like I'm bad-mouthing Uchima.
Thinking about it now, you can see
a funny side to what Uchima did.
That's one example that shows
how there are many layers to comedy.
Comedy really is a deep concept.
It can't be!
What a surprise!
It can't be! You accepted?
HITOSHI MATSUMOTO
Presents Documental
It will stick to your mustache.
No, it won't stick to my mustache.
Drink some.
Bottoms up.
He drank it in one gulp.
It stuck.
-It was your own setup.
-Exactly.
We can laugh now, right?
-Daigo.
-Is it a red?
-Yellow.
-Yes, I know.
What's wrong, Kurosawa?
-She's crying.
-What's wrong?
She's crying?
-What is it?
-We can't let people like that in here.
What is it?
It's a man's world.
-"It's a man's world."
-It's a man's world?
It's okay, Kurosawa.
Don't worry about it.
You're not the first.
-We're on.
-Was that the start?
-It's started.
-Yeah.
He was so kind to her.
Now you mention it, yeah. That was weird.
-They've done it.
-You could've left her alone.
We haven't "done it."
-You were kind to her.
-Of course I was.
Have you done it?
No. Stop insinuating I was kind
because we've done it.
-What does "done it" mean?
-You two had sex?
He's saying we've done it,
but of course we haven't.
Right, Kurosawa?
We did it.
-You did?
-Really?
With Fujimoto?
-You did?
-Yes.
-Fujimoto?
-Kurosawa...
You did it?
-No, we didn't. Why lie?
-Keep going.
She's a bit unstable now. Sorry.
Who'd you do it with?
Fujimoto.
You did it?
Yes.
-That's wrong, Fujimoto.
-Why him?
You can't touch comedians your junior.
You fuck family.
When?
In 1998.
That's quite a way back.
-Right after your debut?
-Yes.
We've never done it. Why lie?
Have you gone mad?
Where did it happen?
-Drink some tea.
-Where?
-In Tameike-sanno. In the basement.
-Minato City?
In the basement of
the agency's old office.
-Before Fujimoto got married?
-In the basement.
-We rehearsed there.
-The old office?
Yoshimoto's old headquarters.
-Before it moved to Jimbocho.
-After rehearsals?
Yes.
An important issue here is,
was it because you liked him,
or did he use his position as your senior?
We didn't do it. Why do you assume we did?
In what position?
What do you call it?
It's the one where there's a head here,
and up here is...
In your face, you have genitals.
What?
The one known as a number?
A number? One even, one odd?
-A number?
-I don't get it.
Show us how you did it.
Try it.
I have to do a sixty-nine with her now?
-We just want to verify.
-Because we don't get it.
-We don't get what happened.
-So, we just want you to reenact it.
Who was on top?
Kurosawa, who was on top?
We were sideways.
Sideways?
-That's new.
-Sideways...
-"The forty-nine position."
-Is that a thing?
-That was your final position?
-Yes.
-You were like that?
-I don't get it.
-You go from behind...
Right?
-Where was Fujimoto's face?
-Here.
It was there? What do you mean?
There's no final blow...
-It's not a sixty-nine.
-Try moving...
-It's not sixty-nine!
-Lay down.
It's a new number.
What is it? It's not a sixty-nine...
Right here.
Your hands were...
You didn't really touch me.
-He didn't touch you?
-Not at all.
Oral only?
-This bit...
-His nasal bridge?
...went inside.
It went inside?
-Is that what Fujimoto wanted to do?
-Yes.
That's not really mating.
-The tip of his nose?
-Yes.
-It went inside?
-It slid in?
-The tip of his nose?
-That's not it. You were a bit closer.
-A bit closer?
-Even closer?
-Oh, yeahhh.
-It's inside.
-"Oh, yeahhh"?
-It's inside?
Oh, yeahhh.
Why are you talking like Henna Ojisan?
-Oh, yeahhh.
-"Oh, yeahhh"?
Hey. She's talking like Shimura.
Why do you talk like Henna Ojisan?
-Do you talk like Shimura during sex?
-Oh, yeahhh.
-Whenever Kurosawa is ready.
-Okay, I'll try it.
Ready? Here goes.
Oh, yeahhh.
Once more.
-And again.
-Okay.
-You don't say it every time?
-No.
-Why not?
-Maybe you're missing the spot.
-Try again.
-The spot?
-Ready?
-If it's right, she'll say so.
That's not it. That's too strong.
-That's too strong.
-It is?
You didn't come with so much force.
-He was more gentle?
-Slide it in.
-Be more gentle.
Oh, are you wearing greasepaint?
-Yeah, I am.
-It will rub off on her pants.
Of course she's worried about stains.
-Fujimoto, that's not good.
-Not good at all.
You can't leave makeup on a lady's pants.
-The conclusion is that you never had sex?
-Right.
-I'm not sure...
-We didn't do it.
-So the result is...
-It was just a nose.
-Just a nose.
-Noses don't really count.
-Could you stop checking in front of us?
-Sorry.
-Your underwear is showing.
-But they're layered.
That's not good. You're a lady.
That's not good!
What is that?
-What are you wearing?
-Two pairs.
I'm wearing one pair of regular pants,
and some boxers.
-They're the same color as concrete.
-Yes.
Like granite.
Yes. They're gray.
They mine a lot of granite in Kitagishima.
-That's irrelevant.
-It's my hometown.
-It's irrelevant.
-"The Rock Island."
We don't need to know.
-Your father collects round rocks, right?
-Exactly.
My dad...
He used to go to the beach,
and on the dunes,
he would search for the roundest rocks
that he could find.
Then he would show them
to the chief of the island.
-"The chief of the island?" Huh?
-The chief of the island.
The island has a chief?
My dad always said, "The Chief."
-It wasn't his boss at work, right?
-Huh?
Like the don of the island.
-Someone influential?
-Someone influential.
My dad would find a round rock and say,
"I found a really round one."
Then he showed the chief.
Stop saying "Chief."
Call them something else.
-Does he get paid?
-A little.
-How much?
-Five thousand yen.
That's how he raised you?
-With round rocks?
-Five thousand yen per rock?
-He only gets paid if they're very round.
-Really round.
-The rounder, the more expensive?
-That makes sense.
-What's he talking about?
-The rounder ones are worth more.
So the chief is a collector
of round rocks?
The chief runs a stone company.
You should've said so from the start.
We were wondering why they'd buy rocks.
The rocks are used for something, right?
-I think the chief just looks at them.
-Just looks?
The chief lady collects rocks
just to look at them?
The chief isn't a woman.
Really? I assumed it was a lady chief.
Sorry.
-Nine out of ten chiefs are men.
-I see.
That's a little sexist.
It's not sexist. A female chief?
You see them sometimes.
There are female chiefs.
Like Wonder Woman.
Wonder Woman has nothing to do with this.
Well, that was a great souvenir.
-It's funny.
-Who's the souvenir for?
The City of Shinagawa.
It's where I live. A souvenir.
You don't buy souvenirs?
I do buy souvenirs.
Are you good at souvenirs?
When you're out on location.
What does "good at souvenirs" mean?
-Do you have good taste in souvenirs?
-Well, you know...
I often buy local delicacies,
but I let them go bad.
-They go past the expiration date?
-Yeah, when you go to the countryside.
-But I like them.
-I see edible chili oil everywhere I go.
I've let a few go to waste.
Edible chili oil.
The thing is, because it's spicy,
you assume that it lasts forever.
-Yeah.
-You're right.
-They have "edible chili oil"?
-Yeah.
-It was all the rage.
-Really?
-Some time ago.
-Pengin Shokudo started it off.
Pengin Shokudo? Who "ur" that?
Pengin Shokudo.
Remember "throwable dumplings"?
What was that?
What are you doing?
That was pathetic!
How loud was that laugh?
He let out such a loud voice!
-You must be joking.
-No, I kept it in.
I resisted the urge.
-Seriously, you screwed me.
-I didn't screw you at all.
-It wasn't fair to stare right at me.
-You were simply the closest.
-What happened?
-What was so funny?
We talked about "edible chili oil"
then he made up "throwable dumplings."
-We heard, but...
-What is that?
I totally imagined him
throwing dumplings like this.
-Who wouldn't imagine that?
-The image popped into your head, right?
It's understandable.
But that really was awful.
You went, "Ge he he he!"
That was pathetic!
Damn. I'm so weak!
-They have "edible chili oil"?
-Yeah.
-It was all the rage.
-Really?
-Some time ago.
-Pengin Shokudo started it off.
Pengin Shokudo? Who "ur" that?
He tried to make a move first.
Remember "throwable dumplings"?
He couldn't light the cigarette
quickly enough.
But it wasn't a hearty laugh.
Well...
Yeah, but I have no choice.
Sorry.
-Thanks for being lenient.
-That was quick.
-It was quick.
-Yeah, it's still early on.
-It's only been half an hour?
-Five and a half to go.
For real?
I don't think I'll...
Can you guys do this?
If he becomes a zombie,
he'll keep coming out.
Turning him into a zombie
is frightening too.
-More opportunities to attack is scary.
-Don't leave before us.
We don't want him a zombie too early.
And she didn't know any sex positions.
Here we go.
It's no use playing your cards slowly.
If you lose, it's over.
Do you know those squeaky birds
that go "wah"? Let's play with one.
You have one?
-That sounds good.
-What's he up to?
We should play more.
Take our mind off things.
-A squeaky bird?
-They go "Wah" when you squeeze them.
-Those things that look like a turkey?
-That's right.
Kurochan just put away a milk bottle
so slowly.
You don't need to say that.
I don't remember.
-I've seen those before.
-The U.S. Marine Corps use these.
For enlistment tests
or something, apparently.
-What kind of test?
-They tell you not to laugh.
Then they play it next to your ear.
-And you can't laugh.
-It's not funny.
-Nobody would laugh.
-It's just...
Maybe they go...
What the hell?
They do something like that.
Apparently.
Fujimoto, try calling me.
Hang on. Everyone, gather around.
-It's not fair to stay over there.
-We should watch together.
Call me, and try not to laugh.
-It won't be hard.
-Yeah.
We've already seen it.
-I'm ready.
-Here goes.
-Miyasako!
-What?
-Squeeze it.
-It didn't squeak.
-That's wrong.
-What's your point?
-Well...
-That was...
Someone else try it.
How about Nishizawa?
Nishizawa...
-Try it, Nishizawa. Come to the front.
-Nishizawa has a great face.
I'm not Nishizawa!
-I've never tried this.
-Be careful of him.
-When his mind starts spinning...
-Exactly.
-Look properly.
-I will.
-Damn you. Damn you!
-They do look alike.
Should we call you?
Maybe I should kill you.
-Can you call me?
-You should've waited until we did.
-Sorry.
-Don't just suddenly turn around.
Sorry.
No, no.
Nishizawa, were you listening?
Wait until we call you.
Okay.
I brought more, actually.
No, no, no.
-What?
-I have more.
-More?
-I brought several.
-More of those toys?
-Yeah. Hang on.
He bought a lot.
-He has several?
-And you should...
Who's that on your T-shirt?
This prop could come in handy later.
-They're all a different length.
-Wow. So many!
-You brought a whole lot.
-Are they the same?
-What if you squeeze them all at once?
-Really?
-It's the whole family.
-Wow.
-Amazing.
-That was nice.
Daigo laughed, right?
-Who was that?
-Really?
Who was it?
Was it you?
-Daigo?
-If it's Daigo, he's out.
-No way. I didn't actually laugh.
-Yes, you did.
I didn't laugh.
-You already have a yellow card, right?
-Really?
-He has one yellow card.
-Daigo...
Wait. Was I laughing?
I didn't laugh. I didn't.
-He's here.
-Who was it?
So soon?
-It's too quick.
-It's still so early on.
Daigo.
Let's take a look.
I'll have another look.
I'm not quite sure yet myself.
It would be so sad to lose Daigo.
-It's the whole family.
-Wow.
-Just for that?
-No way. It was a complete laugh!
I have to give you an orange card.
-It's really worth more.
-I know.
But if I gave you this,
it would mean this.
-That's what it would mean.
-Right?
-Let's continue!
-Okay!
Stop it. Moments like that linger.
Let me calm down for a minute.
Please don't spring that on me yet.
What is wrong with him?
Daigo is so weak!
He's so weak, right? Pathetic.
Here we go.
And we're on.
-Let's calm down a little.
-Yeah.
The tempo's too quick.
-Is this quicker than usual?
-It's very quick.
One more slip-up
and Daigo's definitely out, right?
-The next time I'm called...
-Even a little smile will finish you.
-That's scary.
-Let me do it once.
-Stop it already.
-Hear that?
Each has a different sound.
Enough with that!
Sir?
Are you the hero who saved their lives?
You're holding them so dearly.
Look at those arms.
-When you squeeze them...
-Your jacket's too tight.
They flex.
He looks like a kangaroo.
Around his arms.
I knew that would happen.
-It's like an Aflac commercial.
-Hey, you're cosplaying.
-What?
-Huh?
That's not cosplay?
-Did you change your outfit?
-No, I didn't.
-What cosplay is it?
-A Kariyushi Urban Resort staff member.
The hotel.
You know Kariyushi Urban Resort
in Okinawa?
-You're doing that cosplay, right?
-No.
Really?
-Hotel staff?
-Yeah. I've stayed there.
It's a good hotel.
-Hey, what's that?
-Whoa.
You scared me.
I thought it was the buzzer.
-Does this shirt really look like that?
-It does. Look it up.
It's identical.
This is "faaast."
-Not "sweeet."
-You're right.
-Right?
-It's a bullet train.
-Nishizawa's dance...
-What are bullet trains?
Faaast!
-Shut up.
-You scared me.
Who'd laugh at that?
Yeah, bullet trains are fast.
Fujimoto, Fujimoto. Fujimoto.
Kurochan, can you dance for us?
-That wasn't funny at all.
-Seriously.
-Is that possible?
-To be completely unfunny?
Didn't you have anything?
-Any what?
-Anything to slip in.
Something of your own.
-My own thing?
-I mean,
did you really try to make us laugh?
Wasn't it halfhearted?
You asked me to dance,
so I just tried to dance...
"Just trying to dance"
won't make us laugh.
Next station is Shin-Osaka.
Wow. It speaks!
-It's been speaking the whole time.
-It's a talking toy.
Until a while ago... Oh, it's speaking!
Didn't you have such a toy as a kid?
No, I didn't.
What did you play with, then?
Video games.
What the hell?
What else?
"What else?"
"What else"?
Only video games?
-No, no.
-Then tell us.
Okay. Um... Flints.
Flints?
-Your parents bought some?
-Yes.
-Is that a plaything?
-It's not a toy.
Next station is Shin-Osaka.
It spoke again!
-Of course it does.
-That's what it does.
-You had toys like this?
-Yeah.
Whose voice is it?
-Someone famous?
-Who do you think it is?
-"Someone famous"!
-Akiko Wada.
-Maybe it's because she speaks fast.
"Someone famous"!
-I don't get it.
-Are you really Kurochan?
I am the real Kurochan.
-White-chan?
-Wrong color. "Kuro" is "black."
You're quick.
My hair's thick?
"You're quick."
-Are you Blue-chan?
-I'm not that soothing.
Red-chan?
-To my parents I'm a red-faced baby.
-You screwed it.
The only thing I screw is
my face when I'm vexed.
You screw lids, too.
Nope.
-Yellow-chan?
-No, I don't make you look bloated.
-Wow.
-So you are Red-chan?
-To my parents, I'm a red-faced baby.
-You already said that...
Hey, hey, hey!
Don't do this to your own partner.
How close can you get?
-They're a friendly duo.
-They are.
There's nothing wrong with it.
We look like we're young actors
doing a photoshoot.
-Young actors?
-They take photos like this?
Young actors pose like,
"What's going on, dude?"
During a shoot?
Something like that!
Fujimoto did that?
Why would I?
Did I?
Who was it?
-What's wrong?
-Ouch.
Wait a minute!
-What are you doing?
-Huh?
What was that, Nobu?
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
-No, no, no.
-All by yourself.
Wait a minute, wait a minute!
What? I didn't do anything wrong!
It's not my fault.
Why did everyone stare at me at once?
-Of course we'd look.
-That was natural.
You were feeding the setup.
You were reacting.
That was wrong. That was...
-Mr. Matsumoto, I didn't laugh.
-Your feeding wasn't that good either.
It seems that both of Chidori are weak.
I laugh a bit too easily.
-Chidori are weak.
-Nothing was even happening.
Nothing.
Not even the viewers were laughing.
-You were the only one.
-Yeah. What was that?
You're the only one in Japan who laughed.
That's awful. That's an awful way to lose.
We look like we're young actors
doing a photoshoot.
-Young actors?
-They take photos like this?
Young actors pose like,
"What's going on, dude?"
During a shoot?
Something like that!
Fujimoto did that?
-Why would I?
-He's already done for.
Did I?
What was so funny?
I can't do that?
What was so funny about that?
How did he manage not to laugh until now?
-If he laughs at just that...
-With a defense so weak...
That's not it. This is bad.
Anyway, you've got a yellow.
This helped me steel myself.
Everyone says that. You all do.
You say it, but no one is hardened.
There's a chance Chidori will be
the first and second to go.
I don't want that. I really don't.
I think we should try
not moving around so much.
-That's not our problem.
-No, it's not.
-That's your strategy?
-It's up to you.
-Go for it.
-It's not our problem.
The guy who laughs quickest
is giving advice?
It's not our problem.
That sure was a crappy strategy.
This may end quickly.
It hasn't even been an hour yet.
-This isn't good.
-Do your best.
-We will.
-Thank you.
Setting up a joke can make you laugh.
-It happens.
-You laugh at it yourself.
I have to rethink this.
One million yen is at stake.
Mr. Matsumoto's watching. Time to rethink.
You need to calm down.
Let's go.
Okay.
-She's squeezing cucumber slices.
-What?
-Wow. So feminine.
-What are you making?
Well...
This is cucumber...
-Has it started?
-Yes, it has.
Seriously?
-Tastes good.
-Nicely pickled.
What's that?
Pickled cucumber.
That's enough.
Have some more.
I nearly laughed
at her feeding them so strangely.
I'm okay...
-Thanks.
-Can you eat it all?
-No, I can't.
-I pickled two cucumbers.
This is enough.
It's dripping.
I can catch it.
Go ahead.
Here it comes.
Why hide it like that?
What a big load.
Hang on. Isn't Kurosawa laughing?
-She's laughing.
-What the hell?
-What was that?
-Why make yourself laugh?
She did it all by herself.
-She totally laughed.
-You didn't even try to hold back.
-She said, "What a big load."
-You grinned the whole time.
You're like newlyweds.
Mr. Matsumoto, she screwed up, right?
She did.
What was it all about?
-There was more than you expected?
-Yes.
It came out all mashed up,
so there was more than...
Because he chewed it.
Chewing things mashes them up.
Here it comes.
Why hide it like that?
What a big load.
-She's laughing.
-What the hell?
Don't talk like a prostitute.
-"What a big load."
-What does that mean?
Well, Kurosawa,
that's going to be a yellow.
Yes. I'm sorry. Okay.
-Counterattacks are scary.
-They are.
Got to be careful.
I'm very strong.
I have strong arms.
So, I'd like to pick up a man.
Can someone put these on for me?
The skinniest of you is...
No, I can't do it.
-It's Nobu.
-Nobu.
Kurosawa...
-Wait, Kurosawa. Pick Jun.
-No, that won't do.
-Kurosawa, wait.
-You've been chosen.
-She didn't choose me.
-You're the first person she wants.
I am not a good choice!
-Please pick Jun!
-But you've already been chosen.
-Do it, Nobu.
-Your junior is asking a favor.
-Can I take these off?
-Do it for her.
-My belt?
-Yes.
Kurosawa, you're...
You're...
You can wear them over your underwear.
-You're wearing polka dot underwear.
-Something is out.
These...
-I have those pants.
-Here.
Who cares if we have the same pants?
-You're so hairy!
-Doesn't Tsurutaro have the same pants?
No, I don't wear these and do yoga.
Sorry, you're too hairy.
So that's it?
-Can you help?
-What?
-I want to show how I can use my power.
-What do you mean?
-Your power?
-My power.
She says she's strong.
What is this? What should I do?
It's embarrassing, and you say
I have the same pants as Tsurutaro.
Wear these, Itoda.
Wear them for her.
-I take my pants off?
-You wear these on top of your underwear.
Which is the real Tsurutaro?
Like this?
Thank you very much.
-Are you Tsurutaro?
-He's not Tsurutaro at all.
I'm not Tsurutaro at all.
What now?
Let's pretend you came home drunk.
You pass after you come inside,
and I have to carry you to bed.
I want to show that
I can carry a man by myself...
That would be tough.
Good idea. Sounds great for a wife.
-I'd like to show everyone.
-If you can, it'll be amazing.
-That's what you need.
-There's a skill?
-Can you come in from the door?
-Am I drunk?
-Yes, so on the way...
-It's pretty far.
-Is this the path?
-Yes.
I'm home.
I'm drunk.
Oh, honey! How could you?
You're so drunk!
-You can't sleep here.
-Ahh, I'm so drunk!
Kurosawa laughed, right?
-Somebody laughed?
-Who was it?
-I think it was Itoda.
-One of them was laughing.
They were laughing as part of the act.
But just then I was...
I didn't laugh.
-Kurosawa?
-Did she laugh as she acted?
-Kurosawa laughed?
-No way! She did it again?
-When she said, "Oh, honey."
-That's out too?
That's not allowed either.
-Probably.
-I think you're right.
She was laughing like normal.
-I see.
-He said that would count too.
I'm home.
I'm drunk.
Oh, honey! How could you?
You're so drunk!
-You can't sleep here.
-Ahh, I'm so drunk!
I am so drunk.
That was...
-Well.
-Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Orange?
-You're on thin ice now.
-Okay.
-Next is red.
-You'll be out next.
You're in real danger.
I understand.
-Scary.
-We're safe now.
Right now, yeah.
You can't even have a smile.
I don't want it to end
without doing anything.
That might happen.
-That's very possible.
-It is.
-May I?
-You want to do it again?
We'll do it again.
-Sorry for pushing you.
-It's fine.
-Be careful.
-When you act, too.
Don't laugh.
Right here...
Put this through...
What a day!
-Like this.
-She put a lock on him.
Excuse me.
I lift this, like so...
Ahh, I drank too much.
He fell over.
What's this?
It's a bit different from when...
-You can lift people up like that?
-Wow!
-Watch out.
-How will she move?
-Did you screw up?
-No, but he's heavier than I expected.
-I see.
-I'm pretty heavy, actually.
-Kurosawa, what are you doing?
-Sorry, I just...
I wanted to show off my strength.
That's impossible.
It should be someone lighter.
-How far did she go?
-You crushed my balls.
How far did she go?
From there.
One banana, two bananas...
Can you bring more bananas?
-I wonder how far she got.
-Are there more bananas?
Why are you measuring with bananas?
-Iio, no more bananas. We don't get it.
-You don't get it?
We normally talk about length in meters.
-Not in bananas.
-We don't know what several bananas make.
-Stop it, Iio.
-Stop what?
"Fruit samurai."
What the hell?
Okay.
"Mother of Fruit."
-It's a character from Ultraman.
-Ultraman. Okay.
"Fruit Taro."
-Ultraman.
-Something's wrong.
But it's not fruit.
You can't make it a "fruit" series.
-You have bananas, not fruit.
-Aren't they fruit?
Well, bananas are fruit, but...
Taro is the only real son of Ultraman.
That's right.
-What about the others?
-Yes?
They're relatives and such.
"Kankichi Ryotsu."
Wow.
-"Fruit Kankichi."
-You're right. "Fruit Kankichi."
-Why keep the "Ryotsu"?
-Don't say, "You're right."
-What have you been doing?
-What did I do?
-Until now.
-I was playing with bananas...
Since you debuted.
I just made a mistake. How sad.
"Why, oh why? Fruity why."
"Bonk my eyeball."
-That's scary.
-It's not good.
That's too scary. Do one more.
-You can do it. Come on.
-Huh?
-Keep it coming.
-Keep it coming?
They'll come. There's more coming now.
Nipple beams, they point outwards, heart
You laughed.
You laugh at nipple beams?
Fujimoto, that was a laugh!
It doesn't make sense!
-What was that?
-Sorry?
-What were you doing?
-He did "Nipple beams."
After they pointed sideways!
They go outwards, then "Heart."
But that's just...
You put the pressure on him yourself.
Why, after so long,
would you fall for something so basic?
Losing to something so basic.
It was...
I couldn't hold it in.
-Kurochan's dangerous when under pressure.
-Exactly.
Fujimoto's already close here.
Nipple beams, they point outwards, heart
You can't take something like that
straight on.
-You have to dodge it.
-You took it in the face.
It came in full force.
It was so close to this...
But it's this. By a hair.
-You were almost done for.
-Close.
Kurochan gets a lot of points for that.
-Thank you.
-That's right.
-He got points, too.
-You're right.
Here we go.
Don't pressure Kurochan.
-The banana thing came from Iio.
-Iio, please stop it.
I was trying to set up something
for myself, but...
Everyone, if you don't mind,
could you all gather around?
-Here they come.
-What?
-I have ghost photos.
-Here they come!
-Ghost photos?
-You can't use them!
-Seriously?
-Don't do that bit again!
-Here they come!
-You said they bomb.
-You can't. It's impossible not to laugh.
-Just say no.
-Drop it. Not this time.
-But these ones are really scary.
-There's no way they're scary.
-It's true.
Even if they're scary, I'll laugh.
Exactly.
Let's not.
Is that face okay?
Did I make a weird face?
Kukky really likes those teeth.
Kawashima, that's no good.
-It's no good.
-Yeah.
No good at all.
That is...
That is absolutely bad.
Who are you trying to be?
You often do that, but who is it?
-Whose teeth are they?
-My grandpa's.
-His real teeth?
-Your grandpa's?
-That's scary.
-Don't bring real teeth.
He's still alive.
He's still alive?
Can I show you some ghost photos?
We're not all present.
Wait till everyone can see it.
-Put them away for now.
-Seriously.
My bad.
Put them away.
I really can't look at them.
They aren't ghosts.
They are. Look, they're very creepy.
-Here.
-When everyone is here.
-Wait till everyone's here.
-It's too soon for this.
-Exactly. It's too early.
-This one's bad too.
Show them later.
There's another Master here.
-We won't laugh at your Master character.
-Wait. Not just now...
-It's not the time for that.
-Not now.
We won't laugh at your Master bit.
Really?
-Your buckle was a hamburger patty?
-Yes, it is.
-Let me try it later.
-Chicken meatballs!
-He lives in Roppongi.
-Wow.
He came all the way to Osaka
for a drink dressed just like that.
-Wow.
-The thing was,
no one laughed.
-Wow. Really?
-Yeah.
No one in Roppongi laughed.
Is that possible?
This town hasn't changed!
There he goes.
What's the matter?
Stop looking at me like
I'm just a vegetable garnish.
We're not.
Have you forgotten?
It's me.
I'm Master Hamburg!
Now, I'll offer you hungry folks
100 grams of sizzling meat.
I was relaxing at home the other day
when my mother said to me,
"How long do you plan
to keep fooling around?
"Why don't you get a job?
"You're Hamburg, right?"
"I am."
"You'll 'meat' the criteria."
Hamburg!
He's so noisy.
-He's too loud.
-He sure has a big voice.
-Coming up next is...
-Here's your audience.
"Challenge Hamburger."
Challenge hamburger?
Is it interactive?
Please look here.
This is the dinner menu at
the hamburger restaurant Gold Rush.
I prepared it myself.
There are 14 items on the menu.
"Fourteen" is "ju-shi." Sounds juicy.
Hamburg!
Now comes the highlight
of "Challenge Hamburger."
This bit is too long.
-So long.
-He's tough.
He didn't laugh at the photos.
-Now, this...
-I could see through the photo myself.
Now I'm going to...
Please, Miyasako.
Can you hold this?
What?
I'm going to read
this Gold Rush dinner menu
as fast as I can. All 14 items.
Can you time me?
-That's what this is about?
-How long will it take?
We'll see.
Let's begin.
Challenge Hamburger, ready, start!
Gold Rush hamburger,
teriyaki hamburger,
hamburger with grated radish,
teriyaki and cheddar cheese hamburger,
West and East hamburger.
Japanese Special hamburger,
Cowboy hamburger, half-and-half hamburger,
double cheese hamburger, garlic hamburger,
garlic and cheese hamburger,
hamburger with grilled tomatoes,
Triple Rush hamburger, garlic diced steak!
Time?
Two seconds.
It was 14 seconds.
Juicy.
Hamburg!
He said two seconds.
It was two seconds.
Not your punchline?
You don't often see outfits like this.
-You're the only one I see like that.
-I see it very often.
I bet you don't see me like this often.
-I see it often.
-Very often.
You came here like that.
-From Osaka?
-Yeah.
-Like this?
-No, no.
Like this?
Both hands?
Yeah.
Or like this?
Beautiful.
Good course.
Nice swing.
Good, good.
Can you mimic some famous ball players?
Name some.
-You can?
-How about Ichiro?
He's left-handed.
But I'm right-handed.
As long as it looks like him.
It's not him at all.
Ichiro...
Doesn't he do this?
But Ichiro is left-handed, so...
I prefer right-handed ones.
Swinging right-handed...
-Someone unique...
-Ogasawara.
He has a unique motion.
He's left-handed too, isn't he?
-The Dragons' second team coach?
-Yeah, left.
But he's unique.
But I'm right-handed.
Try doing it right-handed.
It's the same.
That's not it. Mimic Ogasawara.
How about Matsui?
He's left-handed, too.
Do it right-handed.
As long as you look like him.
Like so...
We mean Kazuo.
Kazuyo?
"O"?
Kazu...
Yo.
Kazuyo?
Kazuyo Matsui's swing?
Like the videos she posted online.
Like a "What if" series?
"What if Kazuyo Matsui did..."
"What if Kazuyo Matsui swung a bat?"
-Would YouTube do?
-"What if she swung a bat on YouTube?"
The way she does, you know.
That pleading look.
-"I am..."
-Hands here.
That's pretty.
-"I am..."
-You're pretty.
"...truly in great pain."
You're pretty.
"What would happen if I,
"in this painful situation,
"was to swing a bat?
"Please watch."
So pretty.
What a beautiful swing.
Kazuyo's swing is beautiful.
Kazuyo can swing really hard.
Kazuyo can really swing.
Kazuyo can swing, right?
Swing it.
It was more emotional in the beginning
when his hands were crossed.
Yeah.
You should try it more...
More like Sarah Connor from
The Terminator when
-she talks to her son.
-Brings back memories.
I don't watch videos much.
-No Sarah Connor?
-Sarah Connor?
She says to John Connor, "John,
"if you're watching this,
"it means..."
Kazuyo was wearing the same tank top.
The exact same?
Not the exact same.
"You are..."
Can I show the ghost photos now?
You haven't seen them.
-Kurosawa isn't here.
-She's preparing? Okay, let's wait.
-I've seen glimpses of her the whole time.
-As she prepared.
Hello, hello, hello.
I'm Mao Daichi.
How are you?
Well...
I'm Mao Daichi.
Evil spirits!
I'll exorcise the evil spirits!
Evil spirits! Right there.
Evil spirit!
I'll drive the evil spirit out of you!
Evil spirits follow you.
So many evil spirits.
That'll do.
The evil spirits.
Evil spirits!
So many evil spirits.
Evil spirits.
Evil spirits, evil spirits. Wait a minute.
How can she talk so loud?
Wow.
Scary.
Evil spirits.
This.
This. There. Can you grab that side?
And here.
Thank you.
Straddle Time!
Ah, ah, Straddle Time!
Can you, Straddle Time, hold it?
It's Straddle Time! Straddle Time!
Ah, ah, Straddle Time!
Straddle Time!
We know it's that time, too.
Hold on a sec.
Ah, ah, Straddle Time!
This is tough.
Wait a minute! Ah, ah, Straddle Time!
Did Kurosawa laugh at herself?
Maybe she laughed in the back.
Was it me?
Did you laugh again?
I don't know. Maybe I did.
Look at that outfit.
What's with that wig?
If Kurosawa laughed, she's in trouble.
-Who was it?
-Was Kurosawa on an orange card?
This one was close the whole time.
But it seems they couldn't hold it
any longer.
Iio.
-It was Iio?
-Now that I think about it...
I'm sorry.
When she was doing Straddle Time,
it was the vibration on the rope
when she rubbed it that got me.
That friction...
Ah, Straddle Time!
Ah, ah, Straddle Time!
Straddle Time!
Hold on a sec.
This is tough.
He's laughing. He sure was.
That was...
-I'm sorry.
-That was, well...
Yellow, I guess.
Yeah, yellow.
-Thank you.
-Sorry.
Oh, man.
-So many people are on the ropes.
-It's scary.
Really, more and more of you are
on the edge.
What happened to the ghost photos?
-Want to take a look?
-Should we?
-If you like.
-You haven't finished yet, right?
Not yet.
-Kurosawa, can you sprinkle salt on these?
-Oh, sure.
You might drive away the spirits
from the photos.
-It's salt I used earlier.
-Not a problem. Looks like it's working.
-Pardon me.
-Oh, that's great!
Thanks a lot.
-They're ghost photos?
-Yes, and they're exorcised.
But they're still the same.
He looked normal when they were taken.
-Photos of a Master?
-Yeah. Daisuke & Hanako.
-The photo looks better than before.
-His head's small.
-His head's really small.
-He has no neck.
-The ghosts did it?
-It's the ghosts.
His head's so small.
-You exorcised them?
-They're not normal yet.
-What genre of ghost photos are these?
-Which of them is possessed?
Daisuke?
Obviously Hanako.
-Really?
-Not Master Daisuke?
Hanako seems normal.
Master Hanako's the possessed one.
Look. That's a possessed face.
Master Hanako is possessed?
Something looks shrunken.
Look closely.
-I'm looking.
-We are.
-I'm looking. I'm looking.
-No, he's not.
Miyasako's looking over here.
No, I'm looking.
-This one's a portrait.
-I'm looking.
A portrait?
I'm looking.
-I am looking.
-You are an idiot.
I brought collectible photos
for each of you.
-Collectible photos?
-For each of us?
Don't give them out.
-Each of us?
-Individually?
Each of you will get one.
Don't give them to everyone.
Give them first
to those that don't have cards yet.
-Those with cards get one later.
-Please.
-Who has a card now?
-I'm really sorry. Please.
-Please.
-Who's...
-I have a card.
-Me too.
I have one, too.
-Me too. Yellow.
-Yellow.
I beg you.
-I guess that's the right way.
-I'm sorry for this. You know.
Why start here?
Are you stupid?
-You heard us.
-Those people!
That way!
-Those without cards.
-Why don't you look at it yourself?
Here.
No, Kukky. Seriously.
We'll all be done for!
-All of us here will be out!
-It will be over!
-Choose a representative.
-Let's not do that.
-On this side we're...
-Don't slide it in.
WHEN WOMEN BARF, I GET A BONER - DAISUKE
-I was scolded for sliding things.
-By a Master?
Wait, wait, Kukky.
Read the captions.
-Is it a true story?
-It is.
Take a good look.
Look.
WHEN MY WIFE CAUGHT ME HUMPING,
I NEARLY DIED - DAISUKE
-Are you looking?
-No, Fujimoto isn't looking.
Take a good look.
Nobu's not looking either.
I'm looking. I'm looking!
This shouldn't be a problem.
I'LL GET 100,000 YEN TO EAT THESE FECES?
BON APPETIT - DAISUKE
Take a proper look, Nobu.
-What kind of face is that?
-Please don't say Nobu.
That face is no good.
-Look. That's not fair.
-Nobu?
Nobu, look.
I THINK I WAS 40 WHEN I HAD
THAT VASECTOMY - DAISUKE
Nobu, look properly.
-You're not...
-I'm looking!
-Nobu, look.
-I did. It's about the vasectomy.
-Nobu.
-Yes.
The new ones are...
Wait!
Wait a minute, please!
Everyone... You're all...
That one was...
It was undeniable!
It was undeniable.
-Enough with the cards.
-I can't believe it!
That was...
Mr. Matsumoto, Mr. Matsumoto...
-It was undeniable.
-You laughed.
What was that "kaan"?
-We've never heard that one before.
-"Kaan!"
You said "kaan!"
Mr. Matsumoto, this is...
It's impossible not to laugh at this.
"I'm gonna buy some Yomeishu."
That's the only thing he'd really say!
The most normal phrase
became the funniest.
It hit me like a body blow.
I'm looking!
-Nobu, look.
-I did. It's about the vasectomy.
-Nobu.
-Yes.
The new ones are...
That's safe, right?
Mr. Matsumoto!
That was the highest form of laughter.
What the hell was that?
-Orange.
-Thank you!
Now you're really on the ropes.
-You got orange. No more chances.
-Okay.
It's somewhere near here.
Yeah, I should do something.
-Wow.
-It's not ice. What?
A lot of white smoke's coming out.