THIS PROGRAM INCLUDES CONTENT THAT
MAY BE INAPPROPRIATE FOR SOME VIEWERS.
PLEASE ENJOY THE SHOW
AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION.
As far as a strategy goes...
I don't want to be aggressive,
and force the others to laugh.
I want to talk with them,
and point out what's funny.
I want to make them laugh
by interacting with them.
That's my strategy.
The thing is...
To be honest...
How can I put it?
It's complicated.
I actually disagree with the idea of
keeping a straight face.
I hope this doesn't sound arrogant,
but I don't usually just laugh.
I laugh for comedians.
I think that when you create comedy,
laughter is a necessity.
To be where laughter is prohibited is...
I guess I'm here for the 10 million yen.
Of course, I have to mount an attack.
But I'm more worried about my defenses
when they attack me.
How should I deal with that?
I'm still wondering what I should do
about that.
They'll do something and I'll laugh.
I have to attack before that.
I think professional comedians always...
We keep our heads full of funny ideas.
All day, every day.
I'm sure they do, too.
But what good does that do you?
It's nothing more than like
polishing your gun.
The only thing that matters is the kill.
The target's right there.
It's called laughter.
Can you rip a hole through the middle?
Can you pull the trigger
without flinching?
That's what matters.
I'm Kojima!
Me, too!
No, you're not!
What a day!
Shut up!
What are you doing to my gag?
Timing is a funny thing.
I think there was.
PLAYERS DEFEATED SO FAR:
DAISUKE MIYAGAWA
Can I wash my hands?
-No, thanks.
-Why? It's just...
I let my guard down.
That means he's out.
No!
-But you really did laugh.
-You did.
Restart.
All right.
-Let's go.
-Let's go!
-That's one player down.
-Okay.
We fell like flies last time.
What should we do with this?
We've had enough of that.
-That's enough.
-No more balls, please.
Look.
I think we've had enough.
Let's do this.
That's not going with the flow.
Let's quit it.
Go with the flow?
That's filthy.
Do you want a go?
Jimmy went that far for us. Why stop now?
-No.
-Well...
Why do you want to do it?
Himura has that streak in him.
-Kimura always...
-Kimura?
Why did you call me Kimura?
-It's Himura.
-It's Kimura.
-Kimura?
-There are no...
-It's Kimura.
It's Himura.
What?
Kimura?
Is he Kimura?
I'm sorry.
-That was rude of you.
-He's Himura.
I think we should definitely do this.
You can use my balls.
-What?
-You have balls?
Of course, I have balls.
We just saw your breast milk.
I have balls, too.
-Can we see them?
-Be my guest.
That is a bit much.
That's going too far.
We can't do that.
-But she's offering.
-Let's drop it.
Let's look. She said she has balls.
Maybe just you should take a look.
I'm fine, thanks.
-Come take a look.
-Why only me?
The others don't want a peak.
I'll pass.
I couldn't do it, either.
-No, thanks.
-Come look.
No, he couldn't.
I couldn't do that to a lady.
-Come see my balls.
-Yoshimura...
Go and take a look.
For all of us.
Nice move.
If I undo my fly, they'll pop right out.
-How about we...
-Wait. This was your idea.
You must see her balls.
You set it up yourself.
Okay. I'll take a look.
But I need a partner.
No, you don't. That's not how it works.
Leave it to me.
-Jimmy volunteered?
-Kotouge's back.
-Jimmy, what's that?
-What are you offering to do?
I have this. I can take some.
You just want to see her.
He wants to take a Polaroid of her balls.
What a pervert.
There's a disposable camera here, Jimmy.
Is that for non-perverts?
Anyway, Yoshimura should take a look.
Take a look and put an end to this.
-Oshima is offering to show you.
-I'll pop them out.
But do it over there.
-Here will do.
-We don't want to watch.
Shouldn't we suck my balls first?
This is awesome, right?
-What is it?
-It's awesome, right?
This is what they call "chainmail."
So, that won't hurt?
Not at all.
I'd be fine.
-That will protect you?
-Exactly.
-Ninjas wear them, right?
-They do.
That hurts!
God, that hurts!
It didn't work!
It didn't work at all!
It didn't work at all! It hurt!
Kojima is so close.
It didn't work! Look!
What happened?
I'm dented!
That's rough.
That is bad.
He's leaking.
But it wasn't that bad.
It didn't hurt that much.
It's not that bad.
Who was it? Who laughed?
Who?
Who was it?
Kojima.
That wasn't fair.
He didn't play fair.
However...
I'm not sure if that deserves
a yellow card or an orange card.
I think I kept it in.
If you get a yellow card here,
you are out of the game.
-That will protect you?
-Exactly.
-Ninjas wear them, right?
-They do.
That hurts!
God, that hurts!
That moment there?
-I held it in.
-What do you guys think?
I held it in.
-He didn't let out a sound.
-I guess not.
Decision made.
-That's really on the line.
-Could go either way.
Orange.
-That was close.
-That gets an orange card.
You were on the attack.
Thank you.
That was close, Kojima.
Restart.
-That was strong.
-That was dangerous.
Let's keep this injury-free.
Seriously, no injuries.
I have a weird story
I want you all to hear.
It's about my mom...
When I was in junior high,
my mom had a silver cap on
one of her front teeth.
That was a little odd.
But it got stranger.
Usually the entire tooth is silver, right?
But, in my mom's case,
the part near the gum was silver,
but the rest was a normal tooth.
-The woman in that photo?
-Yes.
-With the hula hoop?
I have a photo. It's weird.
Look at this.
See the narrow bit here?
Fujimoto...
See?
Can you see it?
She has a really thin silver-capped tooth.
What is that?
I understand the left tooth.
It's a silver-capped tooth.
What's the narrow bit in the middle?
Why is there a narrow piece of silver
in between?
Look. That's a tooth.
In the middle, there's a piece of silver.
Why?
You should show Jimmy, too.
No, I already...
No. I already know.
You know? What do you know?
I get the general idea.
You get the general idea?
You should look at the photo.
A general idea isn't good enough.
She has a silver cap in the middle.
I can't understand this narrow bit.
-What is it?
-I already saw it.
What happened there?
It's malpractice.
Then she tells me she's a javelin thrower.
Who laughed?
-It was Tsuda.
-He laughed, right?
He laughed.
-Did you cry?
-You hid.
You laughed, right?
Tsuda?
-He laughed, right?
-He did.
He laughed.
-I think it's him.
-Really?
Why?
Because of this.
-There was a trap?
-Yeah.
-Somebody laid a trap.
-You couldn't not laugh at that.
Tsuda laughed, right?
Did I really laugh?
-You did.
-At the trap.
Somebody placed Joyman's Takagi
on the hula hoop.
You laughed because of this?
You turned around and saw this?
Apparently he turned around and saw this.
He fits nicely on the hula hoop.
However, the cameras may not have
actually caught Tsuda laughing.
Let's take a look.
It's malpractice.
Then she tells me she's a javelin thrower.
But...
That was...
All I did was...
I only said, "Ha!"
One "Ha!" Just one "Ha!"
We couldn't see your face.
I didn't even smile.
-Just "Ha!"
-That's still out.
"Ha!"
Even the slightest mistake means
you're out.
Yes, sir!
-Seriously.
-Yes, sir!
-This orange card is virtually yellow.
-Thank you, sir!
Please punch me, too.
But I get why you laughed.
It's all Joyman's fault.
No more second chances!
-Okay.
-Yes, sir.
Restart.
Okay.
I have to focus.
Are you hungry?
Should I make something?
Well, maybe if we boiled some water,
we could make something.
If you're making ramen...
-Would you like some?
-That sounds nice.
We can make fried noodles.
Make it ramen.
What's with Jimmy?
He said, "That sounds nice"?
He's trying to act cool now?
Make it soy sauce flavor.
You're tired, right?
Me?
-No, I'm not...
-You suddenly stopped moving.
But everyone's busy.
I want to do something, but...
There aren't any bricks.
-Bricks?
-What do you mean by "bricks"?
Huh?
Bricks are what you use to build houses...
We know that much.
We're asking why you mentioned bricks.
If I had bricks, I could do something.
But there aren't any.
Oh, you're a karate expert?
I'm a karate expert.
-Bricks to break?
-I see!
-Did you learn karate?
-I did for a bit...
That was a surprise.
That sure was a great face.
-The classic comedian.
-Indeed.
That was the face of a classic comedian.
Two hours have passed.
That means we've done one-third of this.
-Is somebody missing?
-We've lost a few people.
-Himura and...
-Himura is gone.
What happened?
He's going to hurt himself.
Look at Fujimoto.
Is Fujimoto out?
Is he out?
I can't get a grip.
-He can't...
-Sorry.
He can't hold on and close the door.
What was that?
What was it?
He is such an idiot.
I can't take this.
That was really too much.
Isn't it amazing how
we can show our dicks here?
True. That doesn't happen
on variety shows nowadays.
You're right.
-Ouch.
-Why is he wearing a judo outfit?
I didn't try to commit suicide.
-Take a look-see.
-A look-see?
What's wrong?
He ripped his wrist.
-I ripped my wrist.
-Just then?
I ripped my wrist.
Just then.
-Are you okay?
-Don't outdo yourself.
-You're not young anymore.
-Just then.
Just then.
-We get it.
-Yeah.
-He's too much.
-Is that all?
"Take a look-see"?
-If I was closer, I would've laughed.
-Let's go closer.
-The distance saved me.
-I see.
Whoever loses rock-paper-scissors
stands here.
It might surprise them on the other side,
and they'll laugh.
-Like a counterattack.
-I see.
Rock-paper-scissors...
Who is that?
Saito?
Whatever he's trying to build up here,
it's too complicated.
Why do you like breasts so much?
Did you always like breasts?
-Breasts haven't been a hit here today.
-Exactly.
You should only try the same joke twice
if it was funny the first time around.
My blow-up doll won't blow up.
You only brought titties
to thish sh-show...
No way.
I'm out for that?
One stutter.
-My, oh my. He totally laughed.
-Yes, he did.
Is this for real?
That was a terrific stutter.
It was an awesome stutter.
Kojima.
Is this how it ends?
You can't complain.
That stutter was... It was incredible.
I don't even know what I tried to say.
Maybe we should take another look.
You should only try the same joke twice
if it was funny the first time around.
My blow-up doll won't blow up.
You only brought titties
to thish sh-show...
What kind of stutter was that?
-What did he say?
-It wasn't even a clear stutter.
-Then Fujimoto pointed it out.
-I said, "Eh?"
That finished me off.
Does that count as Kotouge's point?
-Let me think about that.
-I'm not sure.
It may be Fujimoto's.
-I think I laughed at Fujimoto.
-When I said, "Eh?"
He did make the reaction.
-But who started it?
-Me. I knew he would...
You can't give him anything.
He wasn't involved.
-There's no denying I set it up.
-No way possible.
Your titty thing wasn't even
remotely funny.
Let me get my things.
Was Kojima about to do something?
Probably.
When Kojima opened the curtain just now,
I saw Himura on standby.
He was waiting.
Why come out now?
What a waste!
-Why waste that?
-I felt embarrassed.
You lost the timing to come out, right?
He was stuck over there,
staring at the mirror.
You're embarrassing me even more.
Hurry up and go home, Kojima.
I laughed.
Losing a million yen hurts.
It's so hard to describe.
The atmosphere in that room is
a mixture of funny and bloodthirsty.
That room defies description.
My blow-up doll won't blow up.
You only brought titties
to thish sh-show...
We're all trying out
a bunch of different things.
But I think nothing is going
according to plan for anybody.
Myself included.
Then something new pops up
the moment we make a move.
It's just so unpredictable.
You can't eat yet.
You have to play out that character first.
-Do it from the top.
-It's already done.
You have to make an entrance first.
Do it for the guy on your stomach.
For this guy?
But you won't laugh.
Or do you think we should wait for
the restart?
I'll wait for the restart,
if you don't mind.
-Let's give him a proper burial.
-Yeah, it's the least we can do.
-Let's all watch.
-Okay.
Even though we won't laugh.
That definitely would have worked.
-That would've been close.
-Definitely.
-If we hadn't already seen it.
-That was a strong card.
-Nice resemblance.
-We noticed.
But nobody's laughing.
Because we already saw it.
Kotouge.
-It's not funny?
-There's no difference.
-I don't look different?
-You look exactly the same.
It doesn't work if you look the same.
It's not funny?
Poor Himura.
You really don't look different.
It looks like you got a gold cap.
That's all.
Sorry, Himura, but that's funny.
He's stuck there.
They don't suit me?
They'd be funnier on somebody else.
Why did you put them on?
-You wasted them.
-I sure did.
Himura, thanks.
-Nice try.
-Thank you.
-The ramen is ready.
-I guess I'll have some.
It may be cold by now.
-Sorry.
-Thanks.
Here.
And some chopsticks.
Thanks.
Aren't you going to eat?
I'm good.
Okay.
He can't hold his chopsticks.
It's sweet.
-It's sweet?
-It's sweet!
Why is it so sweet?
-It's sweet.
-Sweet?
You put sugar in it, didn't you?
Oshima!
-You should've been expecting that!
-She's out?
You put it in yourself?
Then you should've...
Oshima, I'm gonna hit you.
That was so sweet.
My stomach hurts.
Caught in her own trap.
So that means, Oshima...
You're out.
Oshima, too?
So, did you do something?
I made his ramen
half-filled with orange juice.
It was so sweet.
It's sweet.
-It's sweet?
-It's sweet.
Why is it so sweet?
-Sweet?
You put sugar in it, didn't you?
Oshima!
Wow.
That was a poorly written mystery.
A poorly written mystery?
This is too much.
-Ready to go?
-Yes. Thank you!
Bye, Oshima!
That was really stupid.
-Good work.
-Jimmy's still angry.
She looks like a home care worker.
-Thank you.
-She really does.
-So, it's over.
-Yes.
Unfortunately.
It went just as I planned, but...
What a shame.
Our mic batteries...
Maybe we should switch batteries.
-Should we do it now?
-I don't know.
Should we wait until we have
two hours left? Or do it now?
-Another thirty minutes.
-Let's do it.
What time is it?
Ready, go.
Should we switch them now?
-Yeah. It's already past 11:00 p.m.
-But...
This smells funny.
Who cares how long they last?
It says, "Change after 11:00 p.m."
I was told to change them
after four hours.
Are you stupid?
Why does it say 11:00 p.m. here?
That's why I...
-Idiot!
-I made a mistake!
Eh?
I'd go "Eh?" too.
Isn't he laughing?
-Not at all.
-He is.
Are you sure?
I'm like this.
But that's...
Saito.
-He laughed, right?
-He did.
What now?
Do you know this?
Super Million Hair.
Please do it.
-What do I do?
-Just sprinkle it on.
-Have you seen it before?
-Never.
Wow.
That's really... That's really scary.
-You should wash that off.
-You're right.
Do it over there.
Don't do it here.
-What was that?
-I felt a breeze. Sorry.
-Do it over there.
-Okay. Sorry.
Where does Saito want to do it?
What are you trying to do, Saito?
I want to wash his unique hairstyle
in a unique way.
Do it over here.
-Do it here.
-Come this way.
Things got a bit weird there.
I should wash it off.
We must wash it all off.
Head down, please.
What are you trying to do, Saito?
Head down.
It keeps coming.
Wow.
He keeps spitting.
He has that much?
-What's he doing?
-What are you doing, Saito?
-Saito.
-That's enough.
-I said that's enough.
What are you doing?
That's right!
Huh?
What's he doing?
The Ice Bucket Challenge.
The Ice Bucket Challenge?
I remember that.
Now?
The Ice Bucket Challenge.
That was my Ice Bucket Challenge.
I wasn't expecting that at all.
Let's take a look.
What are you doing?
That's right.
Huh?
What's he doing?
It did come out of the blue.
That's a laugh.
That is definitely...
Out!
-You do such stupid things.
-It wasn't stupid. Don't say that.
Right out of the blue.
I think it seemed like
I'd be the last one standing.
I went on the offense this time,
over and over again.
I gave it everything I had.
But Fujimoto totally beat me.
-I was challenged.
-It's been three and a half hours...
-That's why...
-Oh, sorry.
In the Ice Bucket Challenge,
you challenge other people, right?
I thought you'd all done it.
That's why I got challenged.
Who challenged you?
It was...
Are you okay?
Why are you so loud?
-I couldn't help it.
-That's amazing.
That really left its mark.
Ice it.
Let's ice that.
That wouldn't happen to me.
Even if we hit you?
No matter how hard we hit, you won't yell?
Not with a bat-spank.
Is that possible?
I should hit him hard, right?
His butt doesn't bruise?
-Don't do it.
-Stop it.
So, your butt doesn't bruise?
Will here do?
He means that he won't make a sound.
I won't yell.
Wow.
Nothing can hurt him.
Tsuda is in trouble.
It's a hard bat.
Tsuda's on his last chance.
That has to hurt.
You're fine?
How?
Why?
Nothing comes out.
-There's no padding.
-You did something, right?
How bad is the bruise?
Huh? There's no bruise!
You really are...
You really don't have a mark.
Why is there no mark?
Why doesn't he have a mark?
Take a look.
Then look at mine.
Seriously?
What's your problem?
-Would you like a try?
-Give it a shot.
It's gonna hurt.
At this time of night, it's...
It's not a good idea.
I won't hold back.
That has to hurt!
Again?
Quit it, Himura.
Me?
He won't give it a full clean swing.
I can't do this. He's my senior.
Is it okay?
You have to swing as hard as you can.
Seriously?
-That had to hurt.
-You chipped him.
-That means trouble.
-He's hurting.
Totally wrong move.
Are you a klutz?
But he's okay, right?
-No pain?
-None.
I'm sorr...
Can you hit me next?
Hit me next. I found just the right thing.
What are you doing?
-I found a ball.
-That's dangerous.
It's too dangerous.
What are you trying to do?
Tell us your plan.
I throw it, he hits it,
the ball flies by my face.
That won't work.
Give it a shot.
But be careful. Don't lose your head.
Ready?
Ouch.
-I couldn't reach.
-Really? Sorry.
Come closer.
-Maybe you should...
-Try throwing it.
-Just try it.
-Hey, guys...
Stockings are elastic.
It will bounce back.
-Back and forth.
-You need to throw it hard.
Maybe I should throw it.
If I throw it, he can hit it, right?
If I stand here, I'll hit him.
Just let it hang down.
That won't...
What are you trying to do?
-If it just hangs, I won't reach.
-But you can hit it.
I said I'll throw it.
Then throw it.
Let go!
Tsuda, throw it.
Come in the middle.
Stand in between us, then he'll throw it.
Ready?
Wait a minute.
Swing it like a pendulum.
-Like this?
-That's it.
Here goes.
Will this really work?
We can practice.
We don't practice!
You're the one who started this!
Don't fight.
Stop fighting. Just give it a shot.
Watch out for his face.
My bat won't reach.
If you hit my face...
That would be really dangerous.
-I'll throw it softly.
-Very softly.
Just let it go and sling on down.
Like a pendulum.
It won't reach if I do that.
Just try it.
Try it once.
I'll do it.
I need the perfect ball.
I know already!
I'll do it!
I'll do it.
Then do it.
-Maybe I should...
-Here we go.
The thing is,
I don't think it will reach him.
Please, Tsuda.
Just throw it once.
Then we can fine tune it.
-Got it.
-We've made no progress, yet.
-You laughed
-I didn't.
Your face is laughing.
-Just do it.
-I was angry!
-Watch.
-Drop it.
Where did the ball go?
Tell me how you thought it would work!
The moment I held it, I knew!
I knew it wouldn't reach him!
No way would it reach!
-Maybe you should...
-Listen, Tsuda.
You have it all wrong.
It's your course that was off.
Just do this.
It bounced!
It reached you!
-Like that.
-It worked.
Your throw was off.
You know...
-Jimmy already did this kind of thing.
-You're right.
We've seen plenty of this.
Aren't you being too negative?
You dismiss everything I do.
Everyone did every joke I prepared
before me.
I guess that's just bad luck.
They say comedy requires luck, right?
I lasted this long. I have some luck.
I used every gag I brought
an hour and a half ago, too.
What should I do for the next three hours?
Please tell me.
My blow-up doll won't blow up.
It has a hole.
-Try drinking soy sauce.
-That's lethal.
-I will, if you'll laugh.
-He can't.
He'll get sick.
-But if he laughs...
-No, don't do it.
You'll die.
What should we do? I'm out of props.
Why are you stealing my turn?
That was my turn.
You do that every time!
It's not my fault. We're the same type.
-Tell him about it.
-Don't blame me.
-Get it off your chest.
-Go for it.
-Every time!
Let's end this. Rock-paper-scissors.
Why should we use such a simple method?
Are you saying top comedians have to play
rock-paper-scissors to make a decision?
He's right. Seriously.
We mean hyper rock-paper-scissors.
Make it the most intense game
of rock-paper-scissors in your lives.
That's worth a shot.
From the very start, it will be full-on.
You know...
Rock-paper-scissors!
Tsuda's timing is ridiculous.
He's screwing it up.
Who's that supposed to be?
Masayuki Suzuki?
Suzuki... What's his name?
Getting back to the game...
That was all his fault.
-He must have heard us out here.
-You're right.
-He did it on purpose.
-He tried to ruin us.
-That was cruel.
-Why wear sneakers?
My dear lover
He'd never wear shoes like that.
-Your shoes!
-Are you Masayuki Suzuki?
Are you Director Izutsu?
No, no
-Director Izutsu, right?
-No, no
Fujimoto is in trouble.
-Director Izutsu?
-No, no
Don't get me wrong
Then who are you?
Oh, wait a minute.
He has a mustache.
And sunglasses...
Who has a mustache and wears sunglasses?
Director Izutsu?
No, no
"Don't get me wrong"?
My feelings
You changed it.
-The teacher from Rokudenashi Blues?
-No, no
Mr. Morita?
No...
The muscly guy.
Oh, yeah.
Who is it?
Tashiro?
No, no
My feelings
-Your feelings?
-You laughed.
I don't need any more tears
-He did laugh.
You laughed at "Tashiro."
Hara sent me the Ice Bucket Challenge!
Then you must be Suzuki.
"See you in Shibuya..."
At 5:00 p.m.
-See? It must be him.
-Yeah. Definitely.
It's definitely him.
"See you in Yoyogi..."
At 5:00 p.m.
-He laughed.
-Look.
-See you in Shibuya
-Really?
Are you telling us that was safe?
At 5:00 p.m.
That's definitely him.
Wait a minute.
-What's he doing?
-What are you doing?
That's funny.
Tsuda!
Tsuda had a lot of little mishaps,
didn't he?
He sure did.
-You did.
-Yes.
-You laughed, right?
-You did.
-Several times.
And I've already given you an orange card.
Shinya Yamamoto?
No, no
Don't get me wrong
Let's take a look.
You laughed a few times.
You laughed over and over again!
I saw your smile so much,
it became part of my daily routine.
I got used to it, too. Sorry.
"See you in Yoyogi..."
At 5:00 p.m.
The timing of your entrance was
weird, too.
In the middle of their thing.
You ruined their rock-scissors-paper.
You just strolled on out.
Even though nobody called you.
You ended up like the old guy in
the Kobutori Jiisan folktale.
That was all I had prepared.
Director Izutsu?
No, no
I did them all.
And I really liked that hula hoop photo.
I thought that would be funny.
I'm sorry, Mom.
This is bad.
Look at him.
It's stuck that strongly.
That is tough. That is really tough.
I'm ready!
That hurts!
Stop!
It hurts!
Hurry up and pull it!
They're super-stretched.