[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
Before the recording of 'Gaki No Tsukai'.
[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
The guys are hanging out as usual...
But that man is nowhere to be seen...
-We can all hang out here instead...
-What the heck are you saying?
That's right.
I think it’s because of the generational gap.
Good morning.
Hi.
Hey.
Ehm... I have another letter from our guy, Matsumoto...
Enough already.
'Our guy' Matsumoto?
We all know him...
For real...
It's been a while since we last got a letter.
Right?
And he's using such good paper... What a waste!
"You lot are just a bunch of lowlife celebs who can't hold it in your pants."
"It's so painful to see how you act like the Yokozuna in the room."
(EN: Highest title rank in sumo)
There he goes again...
So who is the true technician?
The guardian of the nipples, the nipple biting god...
We will find out who the real father is...
Hitoshi Matsumoto.
The map...
Is there a map?
There is.
Look at this.
It's apparently on a scale of 1/2500.
We can see Ucchan's house, Degawa's house and Maseki Geinosha.
(EN: Teruyoshi Uchimura & Tetsuro Degawa)
(EN: Maseki Geinosha is a Japanese talent agency headquartered in Tokyo.)
So you turn and it just says 'here'...
There's also Keiko Utsumi's house.
(EN: Actress/Manzai comedian).
It's his teacher's house.
Why is Maseki Geinosha so far out the map?
The people at Maseki wouldn't even know where this is.
Didn't he lose last time we did this?
-That's right.
-He did.
It was either you or Matsumoto.
Last time we measured the time it took the guys to suck out raisins from nipples.
Matsumoto had a hard time, which landed him in last place!
He had to take the punishment.
His task was to be filmed by a weather camera yelling in a crowded place.
He was humiliated like never before.
I'm in Shinbashi!
I'm in Ginza!
-This place is totally different from the map.
-You're right!
A hundred quintillion and one.
A hundred quintillion and two.
A hundred quintillion and three.
-A hundred quintillion and six.
-Hundred quintillion?
Isn't that a crazy number?
A hundred quintillion and seven.
He's made it to the quintillions.
A hundred quintillion and eight.
A hundred quintillion and nine.
A hundred quintillion and ten.
A hundred quintillion and eleven.
What's wrong with him?
You bastards!
You're late!
Getting to one quintillion would be crazy.
It's a lot.
For sure, for sure.
Get in line! You bashtwards!!
-Huh?
-What?
-Bashtwards?
Get in line! You bastards!!
-Get in line...
-What's wrong with you?
How have you guys been doing lately?
Have you been getting along with your partners?
My wife?
Your wife or your girlfriend!!
I'm asking whether you've been getting along!!!
Go ahead, glasses.
-Ehm... There's no one with glasses...
-Yeah, no glasses here...
Anyone! You!
You're glasses.
-You go!
Have you been doing alright?
-But he doesn't wear glasses...
Well, my wife and I are doing just fine.
But how?
Have you been doing ‘the dirty’ with your partner?
I mean, we've been married for 10 years so doing ‘the dirty' is not accurate...
But we get along fine.
So tell me, are you the type to 'suck' or 'bite'?
Huh? What?
Nipples!!
-What's wrong with you?
-You're pretty pissed...
Alright, you guys have to tell me.
Say your age, your zodiac sign and whether you 'suck' or 'bite'.
For example, I would say: "48, Rabbit, Suck"!!
Go!!
48, Rabbit, Both.
Both?!
I suck and bite.
Alright, fine.
Next!!
I'm 43 years old and my Zodiac sign is Monkey...
Don't say 'age' or 'Zodiac sign’!
-Go again!
-So strict...
-Just keep it simple.
-Sure.
43, Monkey, Suck.
-Right, that's good.
-Okay.
Keep it simple!!
Sorry...
Go next.
40, Wildboar, Bite.
Alright.
Next.
'Bite'...
40, Wildboar, Suck.
Do we have to do this?
This is so embarrassing.
-It's so embarrassing.
-Yeah.
34, Snake, Bite.
33, Horse, Bite.
Who said 'bite'?
Put up your hand!
Don't bite off more than you can chew!!
You have to be gentle and know when to let go of your bite!
Sure.
I called you over to show you how it’s done!!
-Scary!
-That's scary!
-Scary! Scary! Scary!
-That's so scary.
You're Nagabuchi!
(EN: Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi: Singer-songwriter)
That's the same as Nagabuchi!
Alright!
Let's see who can best pleasure a woman's nipples!!
This is "The Ultimate Nipple Biting Contest"!!
Come on!
"The Ultimate Nipple Biting Contest!"
Each contestant will have an opportunity to bite the doll's nipple.
And try to swing it the farthest without using their hands!
Two tries per person.
The lowest score will get a harsh punishment.
It's always the same thing, so Shozo, just go.
Me?
-I don't really know how to do it...
-Right...
You're the 'biting' type, right?
You have two tries so you can see how it goes then try again.
-Show us how it's done.
-I'm going then.
It's a rule.
You can't use your hands.
Can't use hands.
-You bite the nipple, spin around, and when you think it's time... you step forward and release.
-I see.
Are you starting from a sleeping position, Shozo?
Can I do it my way?
-Of course, it's easier if you go all in.
-Yes.
You do you.
The rules are too ambiguous!!
No way!
I've never seen them like this.
Go ahead and call her!
-Please start.
-Alright!
Our top batter is Endo.
What kind of performance will he show us in these uncharted waters?
Let's see... What nipple will he choose?\
Right.
Of course, the mood is also important.
I wonder how far he'll throw it.
We don't have a baseline yet.
You can take your time.
-You'll get an advantage the more you spin.
-Right.
Alright.
-There he goes.
-Whoa!
-Nice!
-He's good, he's good!
-Here it comes!
Oh no!
Hold on! Hold on! Hold on!
That was terrible.
-This is bad.
-So bad.
It's surprisingly hard!
What's the score?!
60 cm.
Hold on!
No way, no way!
-You didn't pleasure her at all.
-It didn't even reach the second line.
This is so hard.
-Someone else has to go now.
-Yes, please.
Then let's get Tanaka.
Alright.
-Tanaka is always last.
-That's right.
I don't wanna take a bite after someone else.
I totally get you.
We'll get a new doll, right?
Your real partners have been with someone before!!
Is that so?
-Right... Right...
-Yeah...
With 4 out of 6 losses, this is our resident loser.
Will he manage to turn his reputation around?
Alright Tanaka, let's go!
Alright!
Go, go.
-You can also spin too much and lose momentum.
-Right...
Here I go.
He's going in.
That's very aggressive.
You can't do that!
That's not the nipple!
You're just biting the breast!
Also, you cannot bite twice.
Only the nipple.
-Yes, only the nipple.
-Sorry...
-You'll get some penalties.
-Okay!
That's no-good either.
-That's good.
-Alright!
Whoa!! That's how it feels?!
What do you mean?
Haven't you done this before?
It sounds like you've never done this before.
Why's he making those sounds?
-Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
-That was bad!
It's a foul!
What the heck was that?!
Out!
That's the worst case scenario.
The worst.
Can you let me go next?
-Alright, go ahead, Hamada.
-I'll just go.
I'll show you.
You seem very confident.
For some reason, Hamada is very confident in his nipple biting skills.
How will he fare?
Here I go!
I'm going all out.
This would be okay in SunTV (EN: Commercial television station)
On a DVD or something like that.
Or an adult book.
Something like that.
Oh, he's going already.
That's fast!
It flew straight up!
Are you kidding me?!
Let's see how he did.
What's the score?!
3m 50cm.
Amazing!
New high score!
He's a genius.
You were doing this in your student days, weren't you?
As if!
But with real nipples.
-You're a pro already.
-Fujiwara, go next.
Sure, sure.
34 years old!
-Go!
-Alright!
The young comedian, Fujiwara.
He wants to impress his elder, Hamada.
This thing...
Huh? Hold on...
You can't be doing that.
-You can't do that.
-What are you doing?
Just go ahead!
Quick!
-Go quick!
-One shot!
I can't prepare myself?
Of course not!
Hurry up.
Are you crazy?!
It's all about the flow...
Hey! I told you, you can't do that!
You only have one shot!
Stand as soon as you bite it.
If you didn't grab it then that's too bad.
Yeah, that's your fault.
-He's taking too long.
-Yeah, hurry up.
This guy is already messing up.
I'm getting pissed.
What's with that spin?
He's just standing there.
He's so confused.
Right.
-Whoa it flew!
-That’s quite the distance.
It flew!
-That was so far.
-That's a nice score.
That pisses me off.
4m 8cm.
That's so good!
4 meters?!
-But I don't know how I feel about that one...
-Right...
-Inomoto, go next.
-Yes!
Inomoto!
Inomoto, the top class athlete.
How far will his doll fly?
That's fast.
-It is.
-Pretty fast.
-That's good!
-Just like that!
Fast worker!
That's good!
You can't fall off though!
You can't fall off?!
That was close!
-You can't fall off?!
-What the heck?!
Why didn't you tell us sooner?!
Of course you can't fall off.
So close!
3m 90cm.
That's amazing!
License is pretty good!
-I guess it's all about youth.
-Youth is really a factor here.
Everyone is locking their jaws already.
In that sense, Cocorico is doing so badly.
It's so bad... Terrible!
-Don't touch it!
Who's nipples do you think those are?!
You idiot!
Those are everyone's nipples!
Everyone's nipples?!
They're not just your nipples!
Alright, alright.
Surprisingly, Yamasaki hasn't lost a single time throughout this series.
But we're still worried about his performance.
Go ahead.
His movements are fast.
That's good!
-This is the crucial part.
-Alright!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
That's a very boring score.
Nor good nor bad.
It's an average score.
3m 46cm.
Whoa!
It's average.
That's amazing.
Everyone but Matsumoto has completed their first throw.
The Cocorico duo have had the worst scores.
However, they can still get back on top with their next throw.
Who will have to stomach the bitter taste of defeat?
I'll go last.
Is that so?
-Your second one?
-That's right.
Then I'll go ahead.
-Go ahead, Shozo.
-Yeah, I'm in trouble here.
You really are.
Let's go!
Alright!
It's hard.
He's quick on this one.
Alright, Shozo.
The confused look from before was a detriment.
Oh, as expected.
Oh, it flew!
-That's amazing!
-Yes!!
That's crazy!
The second attempt went straight up.
Thank you!
5m 77cm.
That's amazing.
Thank you!
-I'll go next then.
-Go ahead.
Huh? I didn't think anyone would go over the 5m line.
Start!
What's with this guy?!
He went for the other nipple.
He's all excited, this guy...
Look!
Look at him go.
-3m 68cm.
-Whoa, it's higher.
It's better.
The second try will always be better.
-He did pretty good.
-Yeah.
Next up, the comedy duo License.
They got even better scores...
And now, Yamasaki.
He's facing our way.
Huh? What was that just now?
It's dangerous... He's gonna fall.
Look, look...
Go, go, go.
Go!
I think you've messed up.
You've messed up.
This has to be the worst one.
Yamasaki currently sits in last place.
Tanaka has one try remaining and Matsumoto has two.
Which one of these three will get the punishment?
-Alright!
-Go ahead.
-So after this everyone else has 1 try left, right?
-Yes.
That's right.
Yeah.
So it's either Matsumoto or Tanaka, right?
But Yamasaki is also pretty low.
Yamasaki is also in trouble.
That's a very different starting position.
Huh?
That's very different.
These nipples are different from what I have experienced.
Have they always been like this?
What did you think they were gonna look like?
I thought they would be more solid.
No, no.
These nipples are very fluffy.
That's right.
Biting them is kinda gross, right?
Let's go!
Matsumoto, start!
That's fast.
-Oh, so fast.
-As expected.
Whoa.
-Huh?
-What? He just tried to go the other way.
That was terrible.
This was so bad!
1m 22cm.
This is bad.
Hold on.
It's the same as getting a foul.
Aren't the nipples on my doll different?
-No way, they're the same.
-It's the same.
They're all the same.
Tanaka got a foul on his first try....
How will he do next?
Let's go, Tanaka's second try!
Start!
Tanaka, just avoid a foul.
Tanaka, just give up.
-Just let me have this.
-Focus, focus!
Focus!!
That's good!
-You should spin more...
-That's good.
That's very good.
Good... Focus.
I'm telling you... You have to turn more.
That's it!
What's the score?!
3m 86cm.
What?!
-He beat Hosei.
-It's between you two.
-No way!
-You're in trouble now, Matsumoto.
That's crazy.
Do I have to go?
Of course!
I'll just win...
You'll have to forfeit if you don't go now.
Matsumoto's second try.
Can he beat Yamasaki's score?!
Alright, let's go, Matsumoto!
Start!
Come on!
3m 59cm!
Hey! Hold on!
-Hey! Isn't that cheating?!
-Hold on!
No, no, no, no.
The nipple!
What?!
You bit more than you could chew!
I didn't!
You were biting the white parts.
What are you saying?!
The rules are too ambiguous!
You set the rules!
You set them!
-You can only bite the nipple area.
-I was.
You were definitely biting the white parts.
You bastards are only this attentive when it comes to me.
No, no, no, no.
It's been the same for everyone.
Go ahead.
-Guys, watch him.
-Yeah.
He'll cheat.
-Look!
-Nah, nah, nah!
-What do you mean?
-You're trying to cheat again!
I'm not!
I've always done it like this!
You can call and ask her!
Who are we calling?!
Who should we call?!
I'm telling you, I always do it like this!
You can only bite this part.
Only the nipple.
Okay.
You guys...
He's just stalling.
He knows what he's doing.
Here I go.
-Okay.
-Alright.
Okay.
I hate this!
This is definitely weird.
What?
He's just a peeping Tom!
I can't work like this!
This shouldn't be allowed!
Then just bite the nipple.
I'm getting self conscious so please go over there.
Over there.
No cheating.
-Let's go.
-Alright!
Okay!
-That's good.
-Good.
Let's go! Start!
This is bad.
-Let's go.
-Alright!
Let's go! Start!
This is bad.
It didn't fly at all.
That was so bad.
This is awful.
Terrible.
How much?
2m 30cm.
Hold on, hold on, hold on...
That's too bad.
It really is a shame.
What do you mean?
What's happening?
-Well, you're getting punished...
-That's right.
You'll get a harsh punishment.
What's the punishment?
Hold on, hold on, hold on...
But... Really... What are we doing?
What?!
Stop it!
Who are you trying to convince?!
Let's get real here.
About what?!
What's the punishment?!
Hold on, hold on, hold on...
Hitoshi Matsumoto is the loser!!
Hold on.
I'm telling you to hold on.
What is it?
You lost already.
I mean, I get that but...
Yes?
But for real now... What are we really doing?
What do you mean?
Can we really air this program?
-Of course we can.
-Totally.
Of course we can.
But it's gonna be too harsh for me.
-Huh?
-What?
You know, my daughter is going through puberty and all...
She's still just a baby!
Guys, let's just go home.
Hold on, for real!
Wait!
Hold on, hold on.
What is it?!
-For real...
-Oh, there it is.
"Pretending to Sleep while holding 'Weekly Nipple' in town".
That's harsh.
Matsumoto, this is 'The Weekly Nipple'.
That's what you'll be reading.
Hold on, for real!
Wait!
-No way I'd do that!
-That would be horrible!
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Hold on, hold on.
I'm at a disadvantage in this game!!
-Huh? Why? Why?
-What do you mean?
It's your game.
'Weekly Nipple'!
There's lots of nipples!
I was at a disadvantage!!
What's with that magazine...
For real... Let's roll it back.
Hurry up and take it.
Hurry up.
You do it then.
-You do it then.
-Take it.
-You...
-Let's just go home!
Run!
-He's coming!
Hold on...
Hamada, you do it!
Hamada!
You do it!
Hamada!!
You do it!!!
Alright.
It's gonna be on Twitter.
It's gonna spread like a wildfire.
A lot of stuff goes viral on there.
I wonder how far down the line it will haunt me.
I probably won't ever escape this.
That's the worst.
Hamada!!
You do it!!!