2nd Gaki no tsukai ya arahende!!
Let's go to a town we've never been to and ask for the 5 best places there!!
- That was so loud, wasn't it?
- Yes!
- You always say my voice is too quiet or too loud.
- That was on purpose, wasn't it?
I was really surprised!
- It's serious.
- No way!
This is the 2nd segment in 10 months.
You guys like this segment?
We had fun last time!
We like this kind of thing, but apparently Hamada-san doesn't.
That's not true.
Hamada-san looks down on ordinary people.
He doesn't like them very much, apparently.
Knock it off!
- What are we supposed to do?
- Just like last time, these have the town's name written on them, right?
Well, let's have Yamazaki-san, the scum of Yoshimoto, draw lots.
If you put it that way, I can't draw lots.
That would be admitting it.
- You must not admit that.
- Otherwise, you will become a scum.
May I draw a lot that has nothing to do with this once?
This has nothing to do with it!
Okay, this has nothing to do with it.
This has nothing to do with it.
This has really nothing to do with it.
I don't have any of this kind of luck, so it probably says a shabby place.
Shinano-machi.
- Shinano-machi is right there!
- It's right there!!
See, I have no luck, right?
I'm glad I did not draw lots.
Shinano-machi is right there.
This is like a jogging trail!!
So, after all, let's have Yamazaki-san, our scum, draw the lots.
- Please!
- Please draw a good one!
- I'm a scum after all.
- Speaking of scum, it's you.
I don't know what happens.
You might draw the one that we really don't all know about.
He has to draw a town we've never been to.
Yeah, not if it's a town someone has been to.
I don't want to call you a scum.
Where's that?
Iwai.
- Iwai?
- Iwai??
It's in Minami-Boso City, Chiba Prefecture.
Oh, it's far away there.
- It's really far away there.
- Minami-Boso is very far away.
Where is it?
- That's great. Have you found it yet?
- Here it's.
How far away it's!
It's just before Tateyama!
That's insane!
Let's go there!
We have decided the town we are going to is Iwai, Chiba Prefecture!
Let's all go to Iwai!
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]
[One week later]
Well guys, we have arrived at Iwai Station on the JR Uchibo Line in Minami-Boso City, Chiba Prefecture.
Who drew the lots?
We had forgotten, but apparently it was Zaki-san.
And you kept quiet about it?
- Rather...
- He was trying to blame Endo.
I managed to blame this on him.
First of all, blaming someone else for our coming to Iwai station is a problem in itself.
That's right.
From the point of view of the residents of Iwai,
"Is this a town for punishment?"
They would think that.
That's right.
- This is not someone's blame.
- Of course!
By the way, it seems this is a shopping district.
Is that so?
I thought there would be something here since it's in front of the station, but there's nothing.
The rules are the same as last time.
Let's ask the residents of this town for their top five recommended places around Iwai station.
We will choose one of them and go to that place.
It can be any place.
We will get permission to shoot.
If we don't get permission, it's no good.
Sometimes it's not allowed to be shown on TV.
Let's ask them from the 5th place.
Immediately they started to ask them for the recommended 5th place around Iwai station.
Someone got off the train.
Yes, the train just stopped.
Some young people are there.
It depends on how many people get off here.
Oh, excuse me.
- Is it okay to film you for TV?
- Okay.
Hi!
We are looking for the 5th place on our list of the 5 best recommended places in Iwai.
Let's see, Takasaki Park is in the middle of the mountain.
Are we going to go to a place like that from the beginning?
But this is 5th place.
This is 5th in your mind, right?
Yes.
1st place is Mt. Tomi, after all.
You don't have to tell us the 1st place!
Okay, I understand your 1st place very well.
Your gold is wonderful!
There is gold in your mouth.
Are you okay without clothes?
What is your 5th recommended place by Kawana-san, who has lived in Iwai for 30 years and has shiny gold teeth?
Tell me again your 5th place.
The beach.
He changed it!
- He changed it!
- Isn't it a park?
He changed it from mountain to sea.
That's Iwai Beach.
It's his 5th.
I'll go there, thank you.
They immediately headed for the recommended Iwai Beach.
Everyone may answer that it's the Iwai Beach.
This might be the 1st place.
I'm a little worried about that.
This is only his 5th place, but it would be in line with other people's opinions.
That can't be helped.
That sign says Iwai Beach.
That place is definitely famous.
Ahhh...
It's so hot.
What an old poster.
Ah, Isee!
I didn't know what he was doing.
That one was tanned.
The temperature was over 30°C (86°F) that day.
They were heading to Iwai Beach in the heat.
It's hot.
It's quite a distance to the beach.
I heard it was right there.
There you go.
It's Gaki's famous.
"All we do is complain."
We really do complain a lot.
It's not good.
I watch other shows from time to time, but I have never seen any other show where the performers complain so much.
Yes, no one is saying that at outdoor shoots.
All we do is complain.
That's very negative, and you have a frown on your face.
Yes, I think that needs to change.
The dog is so loud!!
All you do is complain.
Why is there such a big bus parked here?
Oh, there are a lot of people here.
Maybe there are a lot of people here.
This is a training camp for students.
- The atmosphere has changed a lot.
- I don't know if this is good or bad.
He is Tsukitei Housei!
Hey everyone!
I'm Housei!
Look, he's Tsukitei Housei.
I'm Housei!!
Look, he's Tsukitei Housei!
No one's looking at you.
He's Tsukitei Housei.
I'm Housei!!
- Is this a training camp?
- Yes!
- What team are you guys on?
- We are a kendo team.
- Kendo team?
- Yes!
It's a kendo team training camp.
That's why they call me Housei.
Because I used to do kendo.
They don't know that.
10 minutes have passed since they started walking heading for Iwai Beach.
This is terrible.
It's very hot.
- We still haven't arrived there.
- We're not there yet?
We have not yet arrived at the Iwai Beach.
- I was sweating like a waterfall.
- Yeah.
I'm sure I'm going to collapse.
Finally, I could see the sea.
Really?
There must be people there.
This is where it finally starts.
I want to decide soon from 4th to 1st place too.
This view isn't bad.
That's nice!
It's the sea!
But there aren't many people.
- Oh, but there are some people.
- There are some people!
The view is very nice.
That's good.
This must be the place for those in the know.
Iwai Beach is a 3 kilometer long arc of sandy beach.
it's a popular beach for students and parents and children who have come to a seaside school or training camp.
So they certified Iwai Coast as the 5th recommended place near Iwai Station!
They then asked people who come to play at the beach to tell them the 4th recommended place.
It's tough to walk on the beach.
I'm going to get my feet caught in the sand.
Sand is also hot!
The temperature of the ground surface is high.
Matsumoto-san, you are at a disadvantage with those shoes.
Aren't they from Tokyo?
They might be.
- I don't think they know Iwai.
- They would be if they weren't locals.
They may have also checked out Iwai before coming here.
They're not bad boys, are they?
There are no such guys in such a place at such a time.
I'd be scared if there were such guys.
- You're 50 years old now, right?
- I might be robbed by that guys!!
Yamazaki had an injury on his face.
I thought they did that to you.
You're hurt?
- I would hate to see that happen.
- This is a pimple.
It would be sad if they did that to you.
You might get your hair pulled out by them too!
I absolutely hate that.
Which do you talk to?
若いのと1 The young guys or the parasol.
They're looking at us, so we'll ask them.
I don't think they know.
They don't seem to be Iwai locals.
Hi!
- Are you guys locals?
- No, we are here for a training camp.
Where are you guys from?
Tokyo.
I knew it.
- Are you guys in the kendo team?
- No, we play guitar and sing.
Are you guys going to a training camp at the beach too?
Yes.
Is that so?
Well then, do you know any good places around here?
We're looking for a good place in Iwai.
Is this the only place you guys know?
No wonder you guys don't know anything about Iwai.
Are they locals there?
- It may not be.
- Let's ask them.
Thank you!
The people under those parasols must be locals.
Are you locals?
No, we are not.
- Ah, you guys aren't?
- Oh, they are barbecuing.
We were going to ask you about good places in Iwai, but you guys are not locals, so you don't know, do you?
- But I have been coming to Iwai since I was a kid.
- Really?
He is very familiar with this place.
Matsuura-san has been coming to Iwai for more than 30 years. What is his 4th recommendation for a good place in Iwai?
What is your 4th best place in Iwai?
For example, there is a observatory on Mt. Tomi.
Observatory on Mt. Tomi?
If we go there on foot, won't we die?
- I think you can get there in 20 minutes by car.
- I see.
- Then I will go to that observatory.
- Thank you!
They headed to the Mt. Tomi observatory, which was recommended as the 4th best place around Iwai station.
- What was the name of that mountain?
- They said Mt. Tomi.
What kanji does that spell?
But is it okay that they are ranked 5th and 4th in the sea and observatory?
I wonder if I'll be able to find the last three spots.
Maybe these are the 1st or 2nd place.
These would be landmarks.
We could go back to Tokyo with Endo pretending to be an idiot.
- Are we going back already?
- "Huh?"
"I thought this was finished already..."
I also want gourmet food.
The town is close to the sea, so there should be.
He was eating clams and drinking whiskey with soda, which looked delicious.
I thought he would let me have some, but he didn't.
- This is a peaceful town.
- Yeah.
Yamazaki, you should live in a place like this all alone.
But I also have a 5 years old son.
He already thinks you're annoying, doesn't he?
That's not true at all.
I'm a big pillar of sup$#@*.. of my fami&*$#@*..
(I'm a big pillar of support of my family)
Huh!?
"I'm a big pill$#@*.. of sup$#@*.. of my fami&*$#@*.."
You didn't say it all.
The pillar was wobbly.
I almost collapsed on the beach.
When?
When was that?
Just a few minutes ago.
Oh, really?
See, I have more clothes on than you guys.
Then take off your jacket!
That's disgusting.
Why are you wearing it?
Indeed.
Why are you wearing that?
This is my fashion, so I can't help it.
Your fashion?
Housei-san, it would be really dangerous if you wear this today.
It's much less fashionable to collapse on the beach.
That's lame.
There's nothing else that's that lame.
Why are you wearing it?
You're disgusting.
That patchwork thing is disgusting, right?
And the car went into the mountains.
The roadway seems to end here.
There is a sign over there.
It says "To the summit of Mt. Tomi"
It says "mountain trail."
Yes, we are here.
They walk to the observatory from here.
You didn't imagine Iwai to be a place like this, did you?
This one has shade compared to the sandy beach earlier, so it's better, right?
- It was hot on the beach.
- Yes, that one reflects the sunlight.
There was no place to escape from the sunlight there.
The other day I went back to my parents' house to visit a grave in Minou.
I drove past Master Kiyoshi's house, so I glanced at his house when I was waiting at a traffic light.
His house is so big.
The fence is also very high.
- Yamazaki, you don't live in that neighborhood anymore, do you?
- Yes, I don't live in that area anymore.
- You lived in Minou once, didn't you?
- Yes.
It's said that if you live in Minou, you will be popular.
- And you broke that superstition.
- That's not true.
Thanks to that superstition.
Thank you.
5 minutes have passed since they started to climb the mountain.
Are we almost there?
- Not yet.
- Aren't we about a third of the way up now?
Is this 4th place?
Yeah.
Mt. Tomi...
Oh, there's no shade from here!
Ah, the sunlight.
It's tough to be in the sunlight.
If that wasn't a good view, I'd shit in the field and go home!
They headed for the observatory in over 30°C.
This is 4th place...
- If this had been the 1st place spot, I would've tried a lot harder.
- That would have given them a sense of accomplishment and motivation.
- But this is 4th place.
- Yeah.
The road is so twisty I can't see ahead.
Seriously?
- How far have we climbed?
- I can't see ahead at all.
Yes, there are no signs telling us how much further we have to go.
It's hot.
This is tough.
15 minutes have passed since they started climbing.
This is pretty tough.
- As I keep saying, this is only 4th place.
- Yeah.
This is before we introduce 4th place.
My pants are soaked.
I don't want to go back to Osaka like this.
- Wearing soaking wet pants?
- I certainly don't like that.
Are you going home on the Kodama again today?
No, I'm going home on the Nozomi.
If it were a Kodama, it would take about 5 hours.
That one stops at every station.
But I heard he is told by Yoshimoto to take the Kodama to go home.
No one is going down the mountain.
No one would be stupid enough to climb up to the observatory in such a fucking hot weather.
Really so.
It's hot...
It's the sunlight again.
Endo, sing a song for us.
Sing a song?
Song...?
Let's climb
the mountain
together.
Sing an existing song.
- That's what I thought.
- Really?
Don't give me that fake shit.
Was that unexpected?
Blue Jean with the good figure and beauty I dreamed of.
It's not appropriate.
The tempo is not good.
20 minutes have passed since they started climbing Mt. Tomi.
Oh, you are sweating terribly.
Housei-san is sweating a lot.
You need to drink some water or you'll collapse.
It's probably because of your jacket.
I can't help it with the jacket.
You guys don't understand this because you're not fashionable!
You're not fashionable enough to understand what I'm feeling!
Were you fashionable?
30 minutes have passed since they started climbing.
This is more than I imagined.
Are you seeing anything?
I don't know.
-  I can't see anything ahead.
- The road goes on and on.
We haven't even reached the entrance, have we?
This is intense hiking!!
That's really true.
This is intense hiking in the middle of summer.
And I'm wearing Crocs!!
I'm glad I wore shoes.
I'm so tired.
But I guess since we came to Iwai, we were destined to climb mountains.
I'm sure it will be.
But this one was ranked too early.
I wish this had ranked 1st.
But if it had ranked later, the sun would have set.
Yes, it would have been pitch black here.
And it had been 35 minutes since they started their climb.
It takes 45 minutes from here to the observatory.
Is that what it means?!
Ouch!
That's what it says.
But there's not a kilometer left.
Was the sign earlier, "1.1 km, 20 minutes," referring to just up to here?
- Yes.
- It took more than 20 minutes, right?
- Yes, it did.
- And if it takes 45 minutes even though it's not 1km, does that mean the road is really steep?
- Yes, I guess so.
Okay, we'll split up here.
If we all climb up, we will run out of time.
One of us should climb it.
Well, Hamada, please.
Please.
Wait, wait ,wait!
- Please!
You've got to be kidding me!
Why me?!
Please.
Because you're the most spirited.
No way!
If we're going to pick one of us, let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Really?
Decide by rock-paper-scissors?
One game?
Alright!
One game!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Yeah!!
Yeah! That's good!
They all have different career lengths
Yes, this is a good balance.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Really?
It can't be helped.
Rock-paper-scissors!
It's a tie!
You idiot!
- Okay, I'll go.
- Shozo Endo will go climb!
Well, I'll be going.
So, Endo is going to the observatory alone.
Next week!
The best 5 recommended places around Iwai station,
part 2.
Endo heads up the grueling road to the observatory on Mt. Tomi.
In addition, he will appear again.
And they enjoy an exquisite gourmet meal.
Will the best 5 recommended places be completed?
Stay tuned!
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]