Finally, the judgment on Ochoko-Matsumoto will come tonight.
Earlier, I introduced him to a gastropub owned by my friend.
This pub has very good food.
About six of us went there.
We drank, ate, and had a great time.
Much time had passed and it was time to pay the bill.
At that time, Matsumoto-san treated us.
I thanked him.
After we left the pub, he said to me,
"I don't want to tell you because it's your acquaintance's restaurant..."
It was only 20,000 yen for six people.
It was only 20,000 yen, really good price!
But he said,
"I don't want to say this because it's an acquaintance's restaurant, but that place is a rip-off."
It's cheap, isn't it!?
He kept saying how delicious the food was!
The six of us had a great time.
Only 20,000 yen for 6 people!?
Only 20,000 yen!
It was REALLY REALLY REALLY good price!!
But he said!!,
"That place is a rip-off."
What the hell!
I don't need you guys to tell me that!!
Do you know how many times I've treated you guys?
We want you to show us how cool you are.
You're our leader.
"Our"!?
You have nothing to do with us!!
- We belong to Yoshimoto, but you belong to Jinrikisha!!
- No! I'm in Yoshimoto too!!
- Is that so!?
- No!
-  I'm in Yoshimoto too!
- You are not!
What are you talking about?
Pants sold at Uniqlo or Jeansmate are usually around 3,000 yen.
He doesn't buy that easily in the fitting room, saying
"Ummm. I can't make up my mind!  I can't decide!!"
He's terrible.
He picked up a camouflage outfit and asked me,
"What do you think of this?"
I don't like camouflage pattern, but he is my senior,
so I said, "Oh, this is good."
He looked at the price tag and said,
"This is nice, I'll buy it."
It was 8,000 yen.
"I can't afford this."
I was surprised!
He could buy the whole store if he wanted to!
That's enough!
That's not true!
- That's true!
- No, that's not!
Fuck you all!!
So, what the hell are you!?
I'm standing on the witn...
You have a big nose and small nostrils!!
That has nothing to do with it!
- You should be in The Best 100 Noses in Japan!
- What the hell is that!?
There is no such thing.
He will definitely be chosen for The Best 100 Noses in Japan.
So, what's next, Endo?
Not from me.
The witnesses are here, may I allow them to enter the court?
- Witnesses, please enter the court.
- Please come in.
Please come here.
For those of you who don't know them, let me introduce them.
He's Matsumoto-san's manager, Fujiwara-san.
And he is Hamada-san's manager, Kimoto-san.
So, how long have you been his manager?
More than three and a half years.
- Three and a half years.
- Oh, really?
- Most of the time, the manager is with the comedian.
- Right.
He had been with the defendant for three and a half years.
Have you had any treats from him in those three and a half years?
Okay, thank you.
Don't lie!
He's lying!
What's wrong?
I bought him a cup of coffee at the L.A. airport!
What's so funny!?
What's so funny!!?
The fact that Fujiwara-san has not said anything suggests that he has never been treated by the defendant otherwise.
Next, Kimoto-san.
How long have you been Hamada-san's manager?
- About three years and four months.
- About the same as him?
- Yes.
Have you ever had a treat from him?
He often says to me after work, "I'm tired.
Let's eat yakiniku together."
Yakiniku!
Choice cut.
The meat at the yakiniku restaurant he takes him to is not beef.
- That's beef, right?
- Of course!
- Hamada-san, is that beef?
- Definitely not.
- And what kind of beef did you have?
- Choice cut beef.
- That was DEFINITELY a choice cut beef.
- DEFINITELY!
- Of course he has bought you a cup of coffee, hasn't he?
- Many times.
After all, he buys it with the money in my wallet.
What does that mean?
I'll explain later!
Okay.
Well, let's ask him about that later.
Did he give you anything for your birthday?
- It was my birthday last month.
- Happy birthday.
When I was alone with him in the dressing room, he took 50,000 yen out of his pocket and gave it to me.
Wow! Cool!!
So cool!
Wait, wait, wait!
This is not something to be applauded!
I was just doing the obvious!
Some people can't do that.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Is this a episode to praise Hamada rather than condemn me?
No, it's not.
Why did you give him 50,000 yen?
I didn't know what he wanted, so I figured he could buy whatever he wanted with it.
He is awesome.
He is cool.
Fujiwara, talk about that!
Talk about that quickly!
Did that really happen?
If so, please talk about it for Matsumoto-san's sake.
It's not my birthday, but every year on his birthday, he receives a big cake and a big bouquet of flowers from Gaki's staff.
- We all ate the cake together.
- Yes.
I tried to give the bouquet to Matsumoto-san on his way home.
Then he said, "I don't want those, you give them to your wife," so I took them and left.
That's not a present from him to you!
Fujiwara, not that!!
Talk about what happened the other day!
Did that really happen?
Talk about that.
If so, tell us about that.
Talk about that,
or rather, make something up.
That's a fabrication!
Make something up.
“Make” ?
He doesn't have that kind of skill.
But Fujiwara-san gave Matsumoto-san a birthday present.
Oh, really?
Did you give him something?
Oh, he gave me something.
Yes, I gave him a necktie pin.
Even though he gave Matsumoto-san a necktie pin, he did not receive anything from Matsumoto-san.
I think that's a problem.
Frankly speaking, I don't need a necktie pin.
Shut up!!
You guys get the hell out of here!!
We're closed!
Go home!
Don't come forward!
Don't touch me, you're disgusting!
Go away!
- Go away!
- Sit down!
Hey, what the hell is that?
What the hell is that?
- What the hell is that?
- He tickles him.
- They are classmates.
- Trip to Ise Case -
This is a case from a few years ago when Matsumoto, Kimura, Imada, and Itao went to Ise for a visit.
When we got to Ise, let's eat a lot of good food.
Yeah!
Ise lobsters are very tasty.
The four had a great time in the car and they arrived at Ise.
Yeah! Parque España!!
The four of them enjoyed the sights.
Then Matsumoto said.
As I recall, there was a Nichii earlier, wasn't there?
Can we stop by there before eating?
Okay.
He couldn't help but stop by there, as Nichii was very interesting to Matsumoto, who was interested in cheap stores.
Wow, This is a nice T-shirt!
It's so cheap! I have to buy it!
Matsumoto was very excited.
And then his shopping was over.
I'm hungry.  Let's eat something.
That's nice!
Finally, I can eat lobster.
How dare you waste my time.
But...
Don't these places have restaurants in the basement?
No way!
Contrary to what the three of us thought, Matsumoto headed for an udon restaurant in the basement.
When Matsumoto saw the food they ordered, he said,
This isn't enough for me.
They sold croquettes over there.
Kimu, can you go get me some of that?
But isn't it bad to bring them in here?
Why don't you ask the waiterabout that, asshole?
Oh well, I'll ask her.
Excuse me, can I bring something in?
Normally, you are not allowed to bring in anything, but the clerk reluctantly agreed to Matsumoto's request.
He then added croquettes, which Kimura had bought, to the side dish.
It would be gorgeous with this!
The size has increased, hasn't it?
The three were stunned by Matsumoto's delight at the udon set meal.
In the end, they had to come all the way to Ise to eat udon.
I see.
Judge, may I call a witness?
Witness, please enter the court.
He doesn't look like a comedian!
He's looking sharp.
Is it true what happened at the VCR?
Yes, I thought I wouldn't tell this story until I die if I didn't have this opportunity.
- I see.
- This is a good opportunity.
One thing is bothering me.
You guys were planning to eat lobsters and other seafood, but ended up eating udon noodles, was that lunch?
That was not lunch.
That was dinner.
Wasn't that lunch!?
No. If it was lunch, I would have udon and enjoy dinner.
- Was that dinner!?
- Yes!
That was UNTHINKABLE.
I was going to wait in the car while he was shopping at Nichii.
I see.
When he's done shopping, you guys can go to the restaurant right away.
But he wanted to see the grocery section in the basement.
That's where he found Tacchan Croquettes.
For some reason, he took an unusual interest in them.
Why? He had eaten them before, right?
The Ise one might taste different, right?!
He was so interested in it that I thought Umemiya-san might have his weakness.
"Oh, they sell them in these places too!"
Well, I can see why he was interested in it.
I've got a bit of a confession, but I figured if he ate a couple of them, his stomach would growl a little, and we could have lobster or abalone an hour or so later.
That was a mom's idea.
That's right! I think it's stingy to think like that!
That's what I think is a stingy...
Hey, why are you
looking at me?
Snap out of it!!
You came to Ise for a luxurious meal, and you're fine with udon?
He usually eats luxurious meals.
Is that so?
Nope.
"Nope"?
I also don't understand why he was so incredibly excited at Parque España.
How was he excited?
Four of us got on a boat and went on an attraction where we drifted down a river.
At the end, the river splits in two and It goes down about 3 meters and goes outside.
I thought "hmmm", but he was different.
What the hell.
He's a funny guy.
He comes up with more funny stuff, though.
I thought so.
- What the hell.
- I have something I want to apologize to Yamazaki, Cocorico, and Ameagari for.
Why?
You guys interacted with him later than I did.
I'm sorry I didn't stop his stinginess when I met him.
- It's okay!
- Please don't apologize!
Hey!!
I'll tell you one thing!!
It's no fun being
with you guys!!
It's no fun playing
Go home!
Then why did you say
"When I trip, all I need is for Kimu to be there" to me?
I was just being polite.
Get out!!
You're all a bunch of pussies!!
There is so much more I want to say, but I can't seem to say it in words, so I wrote him a letter.
Then, please read it.
When you went to Russia the other day, I got a 40 yen pin badge as a souvenir from you for the first time.
Thank you.
So cheap!
Prices are low in Russia!
Even if that is 40 yen in Japan, it might be worth 40,000 yen in Russia!
This is true!
"You're full of it"?
Who the hell are you?
Put your hood up!!
Don't see anything for a while.
Now, Kimura-kun, read it.
Do you knou it?
by Yuichi Kimura
- Was that the title?
- Do you know it?
I always carry 9 yen with me for you, because you hate saving coins.
Do you know it?
Even though the video you rented was quite overdue, I paid the late fee and return the video on your behalf.
At last year's year-end party, you gave me 10,000 yen short of the amount I wanted you to pay.
Do you know it?
At a karaoke party with about 10 people, you said, "I'll leave first, I'll give you this much," and the money you gave me was only enough for three people.
People say that high income earners who frequent Don Quijote and 100-yen stores are stingy.
How unpleasant!
After this, testimonies from his friends revealed an unbelievable fact about Matsumoto.
The trial then reaches its climax.
Judge, may I play the next VCR?
Here is a special testimonial VCR that was received from his associates.
This is 130R's Itao-san's wedding celebration case.
I wanted to celebrate Itao-san's wedding in a big way, so I decided to make the congratulatory gift 100,000 yen.
I put 100,000 yen in an envelope and arrived at the venue.
And I was curious about one thing
Maybe Ochoko-Matsumoto did something stingy.
I asked the staff how much Matsumoto-san gave him.
I got the sad information that it was a 70,000 yen.
I wanted to congratulate Itao-san, but I took 50,000 yen out of 100,000 yen and changed 50,000 yen to the congratulatory money.
I think you should give him 200,000 or 300,000 yen.
Show us a little more of what you pay for.
Please!
We played a team game in jerseys with him in Gottsu-e-kanji.
He wanted the jersey he wore for the shoot.
It's just a jersey!
Since that time you were making a lot of money.
But why did you take that jersey home?
I honestly thought you were pathetic like that.
Also, please treat me to something just once.
He has taken care of me for 15 years.
The first treat he gave me was 170 yen udon noodles from the basement of a department store.
He must be wondering what I am talking about now.
I think back.
For fifteen years I have been.....
For fifteen years...
I often go out with him by car.
For some reason, Matsumoto-san always says, "Let's go in one car."
It is because there are five of us and it is more fun to all ride together in one car than to split into two or three and trip separately.
I agree with that.
So we try to take one car whenever we go somewhere.
But one day it occurred to me.
Sometimes we go in Matsumoto-san's car, and sometimes we go in my car.
I noticed something.
"Huh?"
"He uses my car only when we goes to far places."
Don't lie!
The gas money?
He cares about gas money?
No one does that!!
Maybe I'm just imagining things.
That's it for the VCR testimonials.
What did you all think about this?
The last one about gas money was an eye opener.
I've been pissed off for a while now, why is Onuma there?
This guy has nothing to do with it!
And his suit is most autumnal!
He's been watching you the whole time.
He's been watching you the whole time!
He is the instigator of this trial.
That can't be helped.
Then, Judge, please give your verdict.
I will now pronounce the verdict.
It's an undeniable fact that the defendant, Matsumoto Hitoshi, has caused trouble for many people in spite of being so rich,
And it far exceeded our eg...expectations.
It can’t be helped.
Therefore, we consider it indefensible and the sentence is guilty.
We sentence him to the "Let's withdraw 1 million yen from his savings and splurge!"
It doesn't make sense!
It doesn't make sense, right!?
It doesn't make any sense!!
Why?
Are you guys okay with this?
Is this a Japanese TV show!?
Next time we'll do your "Too Stupid Trial".
Hey!!!
What?
...Hey.
What the hell?
And next week,
We will broadcast the execution of "Let's withdraw 1 million yen from stingy Matsumoto's savings and splurge!"
Gaki no Tsukai's original video"Flame Talk: Legend of the 20th Century Part 2", now on sale!
100 winners will be selected by drawing from among those who have purchased it, and will receive a picture book of
"The Best Selection of Stingy Onuma's Trial".
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]