Let's rendezvous without using your smartphones!!
This time, FUJIWARA's Fujimoto was the guest.
What’s the first theme?
“Historical buildings.”
This is a very wide range.
- Do you have some options?
- I came up with two.
- I used to go to the driving range at Gaien a lot.
- Picture Gallery?
- Yeah, that’s old.
It's the National Diet Building, isn't it ?
I like the way it feels.
You still think this is awesome, don't you?
Don't leave me alone.
It’s Nippon Budoukan.
They struggled a lot with this theme.
So no one could meet someone else.
The next theme was furniture stores.
How about IKEA?
Where is IKEA?
The problem is still Tanaka.
How do we get Tanaka out of the regular members?
Is someone coming?
The three of them met in front of Otsuka Furniture in Shinjuku.
Here is where they are now.
Matsumoto, Hosei, and Endo are in Shinjuku.
Hamada is in Shibuya.
Fujimoto is in Nakameguro.
And Tanaka is in Harajuku.
Will all six be able to meet tonight?
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]
The next theme will be announced.
Hey, what the hell.
“Kushikatsu Tanaka”
We went to various restaurants on Gaki before, but sorry, I've forgotten everything.
They used to come to each of Kushikatsu Tanaka's restaurants for the "Kushikatsu Tanaka Marathon" segment.
It was 4 years ago that they went to each restaurant in the 23 wards of Tokyo.
We went there on Gaki.
This is difficult!
Where did we go?
Oh, it’s bad.
I’m in trouble.
Everyone's memory is hazy.
Meanwhile, what about Fujimoto?
I have walked through there.
Do you remember the place?
There is one restaurant I know for sure.
- Where is it?
- *****.
Along Setagaya Street.
He went to the restaurant along Setagaya Street.
And what about Hamada?
There must be a lot of restaurants.
But I know that restaurant in *****.
It's the one near that intersection.
He remembered the restaurant from memory.
I wish at least Fujimon and Tanaka would come there.
I want to make it a 3-on-3.
-You were told by them about the number of people.
Yeah.
Endo said that in a smug.
So I said, "Don't be so cocky!"
- He said that in a smug?
- Yeah.
He said, "If there are three of us here, then we are right.
So I said, “Hey bitch!!”
Meanwhile, what about three guys who can talk to each other?
There's one near Tokyo Tower.
- How do you know that?
- There was a wide five-way near there.
Let's go there.
They decided to go to the restaurant near the Tokyo Tower that Matsumoto remembered.
- Do you have any ideas now?
- Yes.
In Setagaya area.
But what street was that?
Komazawa Street?
Also, there is one in Shin-Yokohama station.
But there is no way they would come there.
Even I know that.
Tanaka was deciding between the Setagaya and the Shin-Yokohama Station.
He should head for the Setagaya considering the distance.
However, there are 10 Kushikatsu Tanaka restaurants in Setagaya Ward.
What is Tanaka's answer?
Please head to ****.
As I remember, that is on Komazawa Street.
As far as Tanaka remembers, there is the restaurant on the Komazawa Street.
I really need to meet with someone, please.
I'll do my best, please.
Please, I want to meet someone.
Will Tanaka's prayers be answered?
Here is where the six of them are heading.
This is a difficult theme because of the number of restaurants.
What will happen?
Fujimoto was heading for Setagaya via the Old Yamanote Street.
That would be in front of the station or some other convenient location.
Wasn't that just down the street?
A restaurant you found by chance is a no good by the rules.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- Is that a no good?
Oh, It was there.
I know!
Yes, right there.
It was there.
Is this no good?
It's not no good, right?
You didn't come up with this restaurant.
But I said, "It could have been down the street."
Can't you do something about it?
No.
- I should have gone to there!
- This is another place where celebrities might pass by.
Come on!
A few minutes later.
Hey, is it serious?
Is it serious?
The restaurant isn't open yet?
The restaurant in Shinsen-cho Fujimoto passed was the one Hamada had chosen.
They regrettably missed each other.
I was talking about that restaurant.
- Please say, "Go to that restaurant.”
- But, hey...
Isn't that too strict?
If only Fujimoto had chosen Kushikatsu Tanaka in Shinsen-cho, he could have met Hamada.
Now we're here.
Which restaurant did he arrive at?
- I think you arrived quite early.
- Okay
Kushikatsu Tanaka in Setagaya.
He waited for the others with slight expectation.
At that time, Tanaka arrived near his destination restaurant.
Thank you.
Now, I arrived at the restaurant in *****.
Would he be able to meet someone?
Ah, there he is!
Yeah!
Tanaka!
I'm so happy!
Welcome!
- I'm so happy!
- Thank you!
Tanaka came to “Tanaka”.
The street Tanaka thought was the Komazawa Street was the Setagaya Street.
He met Fujimoto with flying colors.
And time was up.
Where is the restaurant where Matsumoto's team arrived?
They confirmed each other's whereabouts over the call.
Did you guys meet someone?
Yeah.
Tanaka and Fujimon?
That's right!
Where are you?
We are in Setagaya.
I didn't know about that restaurant.
I'm amazed you caught a stray dog.
A stray dog?
Please don't call me that.
Anyway, as long as we catch that stray dog, we'll be all right.
Where are you, Hamada-san?
I'm at a restaurant near the intersection of Shinsen.
Where's that?
- Is that the Old Yamanote Street?
- Yes, it is.
How do you know that place?
This is the road from Daikanyama to Ebisu.
And where are the three guys?
We are in front of a pizza shop.
15 minutes ago.
They were heading to a restaurant near Tokyo Tower, relying on Matsumoto's memory.
- Kushikatsu...huh?
- Huh?
Frozen pizza?
That closed on November 23, 2020.
This restaurant, which used to be Kushikatsu Tanaka, has become a frozen pizza production and sales store.
Apparently the restaurant I remembered is now a pizza shop.
It had turned into a pizza shop, that's a problem!!
This restaurant turned two years ago.
- That's no good.
- If it's changed into a different restaurant two years ago, it's not gonna work!
But the skewers are still on the ground in front of the shop.
No way.
You guys think it's okay even if there's no restaurant!?
We're meeting next!
See you!
- Hey, the phone went dead.
- They hung up the call.
I complained and they hung up.
They should give me more praise for catching Tanaka.
I don't like that way of talking.
Three hours have passed since the start!
Here is where the six of them are now.
They are relatively far apart, so it's important to take someone's thoughts into account when deciding where to meet up.
Next theme announced!
It says something strange again.
[Large Bookstore]
This must be that place.
There is no other place but that place.
In Shinjuku?
1, 2, 3...
Kinokuniya!
Why did only I say it?
The person who said Shinjuku was also silent.
- Is Kinokuniya the big bookstore in Shinjuku?
- Yes!
How about that store in Daikanyama?
- Tsutaya?
- Oh, Is that Tsutaya?
Oh, which one's better?
Why are you even thinking about it?
They headed for the Kinokuniya bookstore in Shinjuku.
Meanwhile, something unexpected happened to Fujimoto and Tanaka.
- What?
- Here we go.
A large bookstore.
Let's meet again in a row!
Does that mean we say where we are going at the same time and match?
I don't know where it will be, but I'll definitely meet you again!
Let's show them our bachelor potential!
Do you understand the rules?
- We move together.
- Oh, sorry.
Are you serious?!
Do you know this segment?
Of course, this is a very popular segment!
Fujimoto spoke this way at the beginning.
You said something about us split up again.
- You're not watching Gaki, are you?
- I'm watching it! This is a very popular segment.
You said that at the beginning.
But you didn't understand this at all.
Ouch!
He said, "Let's meet again!”
I didn't understand what you were talking about.
Fujimoto didn't understand the rules at all.
That was not good.
“Let's meet again!!”
How many times do you have to say that?
He was teased by Tanaka constantly.
For the time being, they discussed in the taxi which large bookstore they would go to.
- Hamada-san is in Shibuya.
- Yes.
- Right now?
But there aren't any large bookstores in Shibuya, are there?
What came to mind?
The one I just came up with is Sanseido in Carrot Tower in Sangenjaya.
Not there.
So, where did you come up with?
After all, it's that place.
It's next to Takashimaya in Shinjuku.
- Is it next to Studio Alta?
- Next to Alta?
No, next to Takashimaya.
I know the Kinokuniya bookstore next to Alta in Shinjuku.
- There is a Kinokuniya bookstore there.
- Yes.
The store Fujimoto is talking about is Kinokuniya's Foreign Book Store.
It is just a few minutes' walk from the main store.
Their fate depends on which one they choose.
Then, please head for Shinjuku.
Either way, it is in Shinjuku.
They headed for Shinjuku for the time being, without giving an answer for now.
Meanwhile, what about this lone man?
A large bookstore.
Two old stores come to mind.
But...
But I'm here and I can't ignore *****.
What was Hamada's answer?
I should probably go to *****.
I don't think they will go to Kinokuniya in Shinjuku.
He decided that no one would come to the Kinokuniya bookstore that the other members had chosen.
What will be Hamada's fate?
Four hours and five minutes had passed since the start.
This is the chance for Matsumoto, Hosei, and Endo to meet Fujimoto and Tanaka.
Hamada predicted that no one would come to the Kinokuniya in Shinjuku.
What would happen?
Fujimoto and Tanaka headed for Shinjuku, still wondering where to go.
Is there anything else?
Let's consider Hamada-san's location.
Yes, we have to consider Hamada-san.
Wasn't there a Junkudo bookstore somewhere?
- There is also a Kodomo-no-Shiro in Aoyama.
- Yes, there is!
There is.
What is the answer they came up with?
- It is next to Alta, after all.
- Yeah, that Kinokuniya bookstore, right?
Yeah, that is famous.
Their destination was decided to be the Shinjuku main store of Kinokuniya.
And another team was going to Kinokuniya bookstore.
Where is the store they arrived at?
Please.
Really, please.
- This is the only place.
- And it's big.
After all, this is magnificent.
They chose the Kinokuniya Shinjuku main store, as did Fujimoto and Tanaka.
However, Matsumoto had one concern.
But I am not sure if I would have come here if I were alone.
If so, where would you have gone?
I might have gone to the Tsutaya bookstore in Daikanyama for my troubles.
If no one came after all this waiting, it would be impossible this time.
Matsumoto's hunch was right on target.
Hamada came to the Tsutaya bookstore in Daikanyama.
Where did they all go?
And...
Nobody's coming.
- Sorry, time is up.
-Really!?
It's so bad!
I waited so long!
Really? I'm so shocked!
Where did Fujimoto and Tanaka really go?
Hi.
They confirmed each other's whereabouts over the call.
We waited so long!
I waited for the three of us!
We met!
Actually...
Fujimoto and Tanaka were on their way to the Kinokuniya main store in Shinjuku.
On the way....
I remembered that.
Just before Tanaka arrived at Shinjuku, he remembered the Tsutaya bookstore in Daikanyama.
Yeah, Tsutaya in Daikanyama!
Let's go there.
Excuse me, please head there.
Tsutaya in Daikanyama.
Expecting Hamada to be there, the two of them hastily changed their destination and headed for Daikanyama.
Twenty minutes after the change of destination, they arrived at the Tsutaya in Daikanyama.
Let's go!
Thank you.
Thank you!
Seriously?
Here they come.
They met Hamada with flying colors.
What took you guys so long?
Sorry, I've been through a lot.
Were you guys planning to come here all along?
Or did you change here on the way?
We were heading for Kinokuniya in Shinjuku at first.
But on the way I remembered Tsutaya.
FLAAAAASH!
You didn't!
Where did you guys really go?
We are in Kinokuniya in Shinjuku!
This place is venerable!
I see.
- Tanaka.
- Yes?
Where would you have gone if you were alone?
I was headed for the store in the carrot tower in Sangenchaya.
He's nuts, right?
That was close!
You really like Sangenchaya!
You really like Carrot Tower, don't you?
I want to finish with next one.
Let's finish with next one
- Isn't he a bit annoying?
- Yeah!
That's because he met someone earlier.
The next theme was announced.
Make it a very simple theme!
Ta-dah!
Hey, what’s the hell is this!?
[Tree-lined street]
This is that place.
There's the only place for this.
A tree-lined street.
- It’s okay.
- This is that place.
Have you come up with yours already?
This is a piece of cake.
That's the only place.
Wait a second.
- I came up with it even before I saw the theme.
- What are you saying?
No way.
That's the only place.
Wait a second.
I know.
You don't.
Matsumoto, Hosei, and Endo were at the Avenue of Gingko Trees in Meiji Jingu Gaien, one of the most popular sightseeing spots in Tokyo.
Meanwhile, Hamada and the other three arrived near their destination.
They must have come here.
Where did they arrive?
The stupid team doesn't come at all.
The smart team has been waiting for them.
The smart team is always waiting for them.
- They are evil.
- That's right.
- Stupid is evil.
- Yeah.
You agree with me too much, don't you?
I've been quiet.
And...
There is a light over there.
- There's a light coming from over there.
- Really?
There's a light like ours coming this way.
I've seen them before.
Finally, you guys are here!
We did it!!
I met you!!
There's no other place but here, right?
Thanks for your help this time, Fujimon.
You caught this stray dog.
I feel I was very helpful too.
- But...
- Hey, that's enough.
- There is one thing that surprised me.
- You don't have to tell them.
I met him at the Kushikatsu Tanaka in Setagaya.
We were so happy.
Then we had a call with you guys.
The next theme was a large bookstore.
After he saw that theme,
he said, “Okay, Tanaka, let's meet next again!”
And he left!
He has never watched this show before!
Hey, that's a big problem.
What do you mean?
This guy thought that all six of us had to be there at once.
If that's the rule, we'll never get it done.
Wouldn't that be more fun?
We can't do that.
We have a report here, too.
Yamazaki-san called us the smart team and you guys the stupid team.
Thank you.
Really thank you.
It sounded good.
That's not true.
I just agreed with Matsumoto-san.
You are terrible.
I only agreed with him because....
See, he's pissed!
It's no wonder Lamborghini is angry.
Lamborghini is also angry with you.
[subbed by RAIDEN1017]