Murakami Shoji's classroom series started without anyone wanting it
It started with a ninja class and then a green beret class
And then it continued with a pirate class
The pilot's class was held under the blazing sun in midsummer for the first time
What kind of the classroom will be held this time?
You think this is just a bicycle, don't you?
Follow the damn rules!
Did we already do it two or three times before?
It snowed for a bit before
It's so cold now
Seems like we're doing it again
Well he made us to
Is today a piano... pierro (clown) class?
We don't have a piano class now
Do you know, this classroom series has always had the lowest rating?
When it's out the ratings are already at the lowest
Let's tell that to Shoji san now
Like Shoji san, frankly speaking...
He probably knows that already
That's why there's no use
"Arrival on site"
It's so damn cold
The hell's that?
Today's temperature is 2°c
Their training begins in the cold
Even a real clown would take today off
It's so far away
It really takes so much time to get there
So damn cold
We should just move to keep ourselves warm
It's so dabbled here
Where do they take us at such time?
We're here, Clown's class
In that tent
I already wanna have a break
"Gather here for the Clown class"
Get out of the tent already
Wait a second
Yamasaki san
Yes?
Should I enter it?
Come out already!
Good morning!
Good morning
Did you wake up?
The person that appeared on stage with his dog was Murakami Shoji
What did you guys say to me?
Today...?
We want to quit it, because the weather is so bad
That's already enough for us, big brother
Hamada, whom are you calling a brother?
I'm sorry
Maybe that was someone that drove you here?
Am I wrong?
I'm chief
Got it?
Yes
Chief, isn't it cold(lame)?
That's my style of performing
What's the matter?
You got it wrong, we mean is it cold?
What's cold?
Listen all of you
You always say it's hot when it's hot and it's cold when it's cold
How come that you're so affected by the weather?
I'm so stuffed with your whining
He always hates you
Isn't is sad being a man?
We're clowns today
Endo
I'll say something
Chief
Can I ask you one question?
Fine
Chief, this series'
ratings are always in single digits
That's right, it's the lowest in Gaki
Can't we do anything about it?
What?
Single digits?
Up until now we've done 4 already and it's always...
Well it has nothing to do with it
Are you afraid to get involved with me?
That's not what we mean
Let's start with greetings
Greetings
Can you do it?
Please show it to me
Lets work hard together
Don't talk!
Clowns don't talk
All of you should show it with your body
You shouldn't speak
I'm going to be very strict today
Finally, the practice training to become a clown begins
Starting with a pantomime
Clowns must know pantomime
Let's see how you can do it on your own, Hamada
Do the one with a wall
Why don't you try it?
That's quite difficult
Well that's not so bad for the first time, Hamada san
Try that a bit wider
You do it too tiny
I see
So you should do it wider
Tanaka
Do the one with a rope
Try it, pulling a rope
We're watching closely
What's that? You like you've caught a giant eel
Are you an idiot? You should do it like that
Hamada
I'm sorry
Are you a laughing idiot?
I'm really sorry
Don't say that it's cold (lame)
You think you're cold (lame), that's why you're cold (lame)
If you swap the meaning of words, it will be a completely different sentence
Get rid of all that "cold (lame)" stuff
Think it's stiff
Stiff?
Stiff
To put simply... you know...
Well, anyway
I'm really sorry, I didn't manage to finish it
Well, that doesn't matter
Come here
Do you listen? A clown should not speak at all
We see
You know, sadness, and other different emotions you shall portrait through your body
You should make it seem like a play
And without a single word
Alright?
Hamada, get inside there
Inside?
"Hamada's challenge"
That's so cramped
That's how it is?
Sit down there inside
First of all
Hamada kun is ordering ramen
And it's Hamada's favorite
Enough of that
Ouch!
I'm sorry!
You shouldn't speak
When there was no half-boiled egg, you decided to bust the shop owner
Why don't you try it?
Ready?
Go for it!
That's no good. Can't you do it?
Can't you do it properly?
You shouldn't show words, and also
Do you get it?
That was the correct way
What was that?
You can't show like that?
Yes
I'm sorry, didn't know that
Can you freeze for a moment?
Yes, just like that
Look at that face
OK
Thank you very much
Good job
Thank you
So far so good
Let's go
Who's next?
You're next
"Yamasaki's challenge"
Please, do you best
We're counting on you
Yamasaki
Yes?
The truth is
there was diesel fuel in here
Before you've entered
Let's go
All of you, let's go
Excuse me, chief?
Balance is vital for clowns
Next up - tightrope walking
Take one each
Yes
Don't do anything stupid with them
That's quite a bad idea
Don't say such things
You should do it with a good mood
I'm sorry
That is Macchan's
Thank you
I'm not really into it
You take that
Take it!
No way that's mine
It is yours
Do what your teacher tells you
Take it!
Please take it
It's heavy
What are you doing?
Do you want to quit?
I will do it!
For how long will you be acting like that?
Listen, this is 50 meters high
50 meters? So tall!
And you shall hold to it
You should walk like this
This way
And you definitely should not fall down from here
Why don't you try?
"Everyone's challenge"
You definitely shouldn't come off
Yes
Let's try now
Be careful!
Most certainly
Not bad!
Just like that! Grab it!
Keeping a balance?
Just go like that
Stop for a moment all of you
You fell down
You already fell down
Teacher, that's impossible for me
There you go again
That's what the youth says these days
Can't you do it at least for 10 or 20 seconds?
Are you happy that you fell down while walking?
You come in here with an unknown potential!
However, I really can't do it with such a big log
Look at everyone, am I wrong?
You know, you shouldn't think that that's impossible
Why's that?
You know, your father
Was a great man
I'm talking about Serube Yamasaki
Back in the day he could walk that easily
On the rope to the Robiaru building
Your legendary father didn't know such words like "I can't do it"
Should we finish already?
The bell's already ringing
That was not as usual
It already tells us that we should go home
Why does that always happens with me?
Do it
"Yamasaki's challenge again"
Do your best
Look, like that keep yourself balanced
Pay attention to your body
Grab it properly
Do your best!
Why not just carry it?
"Why not carry it?"
I'm telling you to grab it
Why can't you just garb it? Just like that
That's how an expert does it
Why is difficult just to do it like this?
Just roll it a bit in your hands, you idiot
Just do it properly
Like an annoying child
Hold it, and now walk
Don't look down
You should look ahead for 10 meters
That's your first time saying it
'Zaki san, do your best!
Just like that
Good
Very good, don't forget 'bout the balance
And then do it like that
Yama chan is absolutely fearless
Fine, enough of that
Let's move
You're absolutely worthless in this one
Let's have a brake
"Break time"
Shouldn't we start from my Senpai
Take it
2 or 3 cups, take as much as you want
So cool. Really?
Than I shall take it, thank you
You're next
May I?
Thank you
No way
What a splendid tea, it's so good
Excuse me
Mine's empty
May I pour some?
He's pouring it by himself
Thank you for the tea
Do you have a right to drink?
I'm able to drink
Don't say that as if you'll be able to drink
Don't you think that's strange?
But, I tried hard
Although Russians and Chinese don't quarrel
It sounds just like telling them in Japanese to stop it
Completely meaningless
The other party also
I'm completely cold (lame) today
Sorry, completely terrible
Cold? Maybe you meant stiff?
Yes, stiff
I'm completely misled
At this point
Next up, the clowns should know one of the most exciting part of their show
This what audience is the most excited about
Look, you hold the fork
They throw you that
It falls on you
And then you strike a pose
And then the audience claps
This is what clowns never stopped doing
Fine, why don't you try?
Me? I think I'll be able to do it
"Matsumoto challenge"
Are you ready?
Do your best!
Let's do it
Great! So cool!
The hell did you do now?
What was that, Matsumoto kun?
But I caught it
Does that mean anything to you?
It was supposed to be like that?
I'm sorry
I just thought that I should have tried harder
You shouldn't try so hard!
You're trying hard in wrong direction
And now you did your "best"
I'm sorry
I'm so pissed off now
Hey, you, try it
I'm sure I'll be able to do it
"Yamasaki's challenge"
Do your best!
Alright, did you get that?
"Yamasaki's challenge"
It's quite rainy
Do it like a pro
What's with him?
Go, get it!
Chief, could you please throw it more careful?
Let's do it with an apple
With apple, right?
Can't he stop that?
Please throw it
Because, chief, I will definitely be able to do it
I am confident
I'll do it properly, so please throw it
Where's that confidence?
Chief
Let's stop that already
Please, give me a chance like you did to others
It just hit his shoulder
That just hit your shoulder
You just have no motivation
I'm motivated!
Motivation Energy Iwaki (Japanese politician)
You don't have any of that
You absolutely have nothing of that
Motivation Energy Yamasaki
You're hopeless
I'll do it
Come here
Take it
Hamada, try throwing a fork
Please stop that, chief. This is definitely dangerous
The last one is the toughest obstacle for the clowns
Not to speak at any time
Shall we train not to speak?
Yamasaki
I told you to be quiet!
Yamasaki, didn't you do the training to be silent
Anyway
That's the last training to be silent
Yes!
Bring it here
What? Wait a minute!
Now, you'll be chased by this Shepard dog
That is our final training
This is the next step for a person in not letting any voice out
In that case...
Matsumoto?
Why don't you try?
Wouldn't it be better to see a demonstration?
What?
By chief
That's just a suggestion
Can't we have a look at our chief's demonstration? Please!
Alright
I'll do it
Please be careful
Please, chief
"Chief's demonstration"
So he should be chased by it? That's scary
Look carefully
Yes!
It's coming!
That's no good
So scary!
Ouch!
Chief that's too scary, no way we're doing it
Chief, that too bad, we're not doing that. See you next time, chief
Miss owner, stop it!
"After recording"
That was too scary!
You're all snotty
Blood come out, wait that's paint
I got so scared from that!
I forgot that I was a clown