My life has changed a lot since I did my trial on this show some time ago.
But I got unbelievable information.
What a surprise, there was a man who was even more stingy with money than I was.
His name is...
Hitoshi Matsumoto.
What the hell, asshole!
I hereby request the opening of
the Too Stingy Matsumoto's Trial.
Wait.
What's so stingy about me!?
Is Matsumoto really a stingy bastard?
The truth will be revealed tonight.
The Too Stingy Ochoko-Matsumoto's Trial is now in open session.
Prosecutor and plaintiff group, please enter the court.
Next, the defendant, Hitoshi Matsumoto, please enter the court.
Defendant, please take a seat over there.
Then, the prosecutor should read the complaint as this court is in session.
Hitoshi Matsumoto is a popular comedian who has appeared in many regular shows as a comedian and is ranked high in the billionaire ranking every year.
However, behind the scenes, he has been discovered to be a stingy man to the point that even Director Onuma was taken aback.
His mind is as shallow as an ochoko.
What does that mean?
I don't really understand it when I hear that.
It means your mind is this small and shallow.
It was discovered that he was causing a great deal of trouble to the people around him.
Therefore, I hereby petition for the opening of Too Stingy Ochoko-Matsumoto's Trial.
Understood. We will open the  Too Stingy Ochoko-Matsumoto's Trial.
Prosecutor Hamada, please present your evidence.
There are reports from all sides of the defendant's cheapness.
Please watch this VCR first.
- The Poolside in Saipan Case-
This case happened when Matsumoto went on a trip to Saipan with Yamazaki and a junior.
It occurred on the last day of the trip.
Matsumoto-san! We have three hours before our return flight. Let's do something.
Yeah, what should we do?
Oh, there is a very luxurious pool at a nearby hotel, so let's go swimming there.
Sounds good, let's do that.
Yeah!
Let's swim!
The three of them moved to a nearby hotel and went to the pool.
But...
What?
Hotel security stopped them.
They were told that in order to swim in this pool, they had to pay an admission fee of $20, unless they were staying at the hotel.
Then Yamasaki said,
I guess that's how it is.
It's only $20, let's pay it.
But Matsumoto said,
I don't want to pay it.
It's only $20, and if we don't pay it, we won't be able to enter the pool.
No! Why should I pay it, asshole?
Besides, we swam a lot yesterday, so we've had enough!!
As soon as Matsumoto realized that he had to pay the $20, his attitude suddenly changed and he became furious.
The hotel security guard, who couldn't bear to see it, said
Huh?
That's boring, let's leave.
Yamazaki was about to leave, thinking it was pointless if he was not going to get in the pool.
But Matsumoto was different.
Hell yeahhhh!!
He began sunbathing by the pool.
Oh, it feels so good...!!
Yamasaki reluctantly went along with him and stood by the pool for three hours.
What the hell did you do?
Judge, I'm calling witnesses on this.
Witness, please come to the witness stand.
Yes.
As you know, he appeared in the VCR.
Did he do the same thing as that VCR?
Yes, he did. That was my first trip in a long time.
At the end of the trip, we wanted to swim in the pool but had to pay.
We could not get into the pool for PREE...for free.
Huh?
We could not get into the pool for free.
And hotel security said...
Don't say crazy things today.
That's right!
He is the only one who says crazy things today.
If you do something, my character won't stand out.
That's right.
I'm very aware of that.
What's "PREE"?
"The pool for PREE"?
Well, all right.
We were stopped by hotel security by the pool.
“No, no, no.”
I see, exactly the same thing happened as in that video.
Just one thing to confirm.
You guys had to pay $20 to get in the pool.
That's only about 2,000 yen.
You were going to pay 2,000 yen.
Because you can swim for 3 hours.
You told him you would pay him 2,000 yen to get in the pool.
But he, who has more money than you, sayd, "Why should I pay this?"
This is the point.
Is there anything you want to say?
I want to make something clear.
Let me tell you what happened before that day.
He loves to gamble.
Hama....Yamazaki.
Who?
Yamazaki.
You got a problem!?
Who is Hama-Yamazaki?
You didn't hit me at all.
I just hit you.
I just barely dodged it.
I completely dodged it.
Okay, does he like to gamble?
Yes, he does.
Since the day we arrived in Saipan, this idiot has gambled like a fool.
This time we came to Saipan with the intention of playing in the direct sun.
But this idiot gambled all the time and ended up losing 400,000 yen.
- No, it was 800,000 yen.
- He lost 800,000 yen!
He lost 800,000 yen.
Think about it.
I am his senior,
so I can't let him spend any more money!!
Then why didn't you pay for him?
It's only $20.
That's unrelated!
What the hell.
If you don't want Yamazaki to spend any more money, you just pay.
What can I say about this?
How do I say this?
Why didn't you pay?
Why should I pay?
If he's going to pay, there's nothing wrong with it.
I wanted to say that to the hotel security.
"Do you know who he is?"
"He's Yamazaki, the guy who lost 800,000 yen, and you want him to pay another $20?"
"Give him a drink of water from the pool."
- He lost 800,000 yen. So paying another 2,000 yen won't make a difference, right?
- Yes.
- I wanted to enjoy the last three hours.
- Yeah.
Well, let me tell you this.
What's wrong with me?
What?
That you didn't get in the pool?
Is it wrong for me not to pay my $20?
What's wrong with me?
It's only 6,000 yen.
Shut up, asshole!
He's so mad.
Stop bitching, asshole!
What's wrong with me?
What the hell is he?
I've never had fun on a trip with you!!
We had fun!!
Fuck you!
Put him to death!!
I never had any fun with you!!
We had fun!!!
Sit down!
Fuck you!!
We had a lot of fun!!
And wander around unaware that you are dead!!
Yeah, I'll wander around for sure!!
Get sick!
Sick?
- "Get sick"...?
- Don't worry.
Get sick on the weekends!
- I don't want to be sick this weekend.
- Don't worry about it.
- Invitation to Matsumoto's House Case -
This was a few years ago.
It was the first time Miyasako of Ameagari Kesshitai was invited to Matsumoto's house.
Come in.
Thank you for inviting!
Wow! There's a billiard table!
I knew Matsumoto-san was great!
Here we go.
They played billiards for hours.
After a while, Matsumoto said,
I'm hungry, let's get something to eat.
That's nice!
I'm sure Matsumoto-san will treat us to a fancy meal.
But.
Miyasako, go to the convenience store for us.
Get something to eat.
Oh, and don't forget to buy Donbei.
I love them!
Miyasako's hopes were dashed and he reluctantly went to the convenience store.
Then he returned from shopping.
- Sorry to keep you waiting.
- Oh, I've been waiting for you.
Here's 1,000 yen.
Looking at the shopping bags in Miyasako's hands, it was obvious that 1,000 yen was not enough.
But he couldn't tell Matsumoto that he didn't have enough money, so he paid the rest.
Meanwhile, Matsumoto said,
Donbei is the best!
This is the most delicious food in the world!
He kept praising Donbei, saying so.
These horrific cases occurred.
Witnesses, please come in.
Are you all right?
Hang on!
Just tell us what you think.
He won't hurt you.
I became a comedian because I had a dream.
If I work hard in this world, I can become rich.
I can eat a lot of delicious food.
That's what I thought.
But I don't understand why he, now that he is rich, says Donbei  is the best in the world.
Back then, I was married but had no money.
My wife was also very thin.
Hang on!
Let's get the issue straight.
You didn't take delivery or go to a restaurant.
I think that's fine.
It's okay to have those days.
He doesn't blame you for that.
When you saw the food he bought for everyone, didn't you think it cost more than 1000 yen?
First of all, I have something to say.
I don't want to make him think that Downtown Matsumoto is great.
I don't want him to see the arrogance of a comedian.
I want to treat him like an ordinary person
I dont want him to think im above him.
I know how you feel.
That's why you told him to go to the convenience store.
I know exactly how you feel.
- But you also knew that your junior was paying for it, didn't you?
- Yes.
- You didn't give him money to go shopping, did you?
- Right.
He came back with a lot of stuff.
You didn't notice he paid more than 1000 yen?
Simply put,
I had noticed it.
- Did you notice that what he bought cost about 3,000 yen?
- Yes.
And how much money did you give him?
I gave him about 1,000 yen.
Oh, you're short 2,000 yen.
Why is that?
Meanwhile, I was still talking with Miyasako.
I gave him tens of millions of yen in invisible money.
He must have stolen a lot of skills from me.
"In this situation, say like this."
"In this situation, do this."
I taught Miyasako the secrets of comedy and how to do comedy.
If you think of it as a tuition fee, a few thousand yen is a small price to pay!
Hey, baldy.
Witness, be careful about your language.
Sorry.
This was quite a while ago,
But you have to pay me.
Why?
Because I want to give my wife a good meal...!
- Can I say something unrelated?
- Okay.
Can't your buddy speak?
By the way, defendant, no, witness.
Was he there?
Yes, he was.
Did you see it too?
I don't know.
- He was there!
- Yes, he was!
- We were all there!
I was there too!
- I don't know.
- Why don't you know?
That didn't happen, did it?
I think so.
- Is it true that you paid 2,000 yen on his behalf?
- Yes!
But the defendant says it was a tuition fee.
What do you think about that?
I have NEVER learned anything from this guy!
I see.
There are many things that he has taken away from me!
I have never learned anything from this guy.
I see.
What's wrong with me!?
When I have dinner with you, I usually treat you.
At least when you go shopping at the convenience store, you pay for it!
Thats not what you did at first.
That was the first time you and I met.
At that point, you had never treated me to anything.
In fact, I treated you first.
You'll have more memories of Downtown Matsumoto
from now oooooon...
That's only the first time!
Do you know how many times I have treated you since then?
Indeed you usually treat me.
At that point, you had never treated me to anything.
You should at least say thank you to me.
I'm going to have to take you to court for something else if you keep talking like that.
I didn't do anything wrong.
All you do is engage in foursomes.
Thank you, witness.
You do that?
Unlike you, I have a household!!
I have a household!!!!
If everyone knew I was having a foursome, my wife wouldn't be able to walk out the door!
- Rock-Paper-Scissors in a Gastropub Case -
This was when Matsumoto, Imada and Yamashita went to a gastropub.
Imada, you have been active lately.
It's okay.
How about you, Yamashita?
I'm not good at all.
You have to be better.
The three  were having a great time, and when the meal was over, it was time to pay the bill.
Let's have a game of rock-paper-scissors to see who pays.
Oh, sure, that's fine.
But it is obvious that Yamashita earns less than the other two.
Give me a handicap.
I win if I win one game.
Imada-san wins if you win two games.
Matsumoto-san wins if you win three games.
How about this?
Then...
Why should I give you a handicap?
I'd rather have the handicap, asshole!
Matsumoto, who earns hundreds of times more than Yamashita, did not accept his offer.
And they ended up playing one round of rock-paper-scissors.
It's a big game!
Here we go!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Oh, no!!
Hell yeahhhh!!
I won!!
In the end, Yamashita, the loser, paid the bill.
I got free food!!
There was another case like this.
Judge, I would like to call a witness.
All right. The witness, please enter the court.
He is Yamashita-kun, who was in VCR.
Please explain....hey, are you all right?
Are you okay?
It was fine for me to play rock-paper-scissors.
- Actually, I had played rock-paper-scissors with Yamazaki-san and Miyasako-san before.
- Oh, really?
That time, Yamazaki-san suggested giving me a handicap.
So I enjoyed playing rock-paper-scissors.
This time was a similar case, so I said to him, "Please give me a handicap."
But he said, "Why should I give you a handicap? i'd rather have the handicap."
Why does he need a handicap?
Yeah, why does he need a handicap?
- For what it's worth, I'm the one who needs the handicap.
- That's right.
First of all,
You're nervous.
Calm down!
It doesn't matter.
I don't want to talk to a nervous comedian.
Hang on!
i'm gonna go crazy too!
I'm not nervous!
What are you talking about!?
He says he's not nervous, so it's okay.
I adore Matsumoto-san.
I want to see him looking cool.
But the other day I saw him being uncool.
Lately he has been drinking a lot with SMAP's Nakai-san.
And Nakai-san always treats Matsumoto-san.
That is not good!
This is hard for me!
-That is not good!!
- As Matsumoto san's junior, it's fine for me to say thank you to Matsumoto-san.
But for me to say thank you to Nakai-san is complicated.
If it were me, it would be fine, but I don't want to see Imada-san, who is older than him, saying thank you to Nakai-san either.
Don't let them do that!
- What the hell, asshole!
- Matsumoto should not let them do that! I know how you feel!
Defendant, what do you think about this?
This is not a personal exchange.
This is not "Hitoshi Matsumoto and Masahiro Nakai."
This is "Yoshimoto Kogyo and Johnny's."
Do you know which office is making more money right now!?
No, no, no, Nakai has nothing to do with it.
Yes, he does!  This is an exchange of offices!
No, it's not.
You are older than Nakai!
Their new song "Lion Heart" sold like hotcakes.
But they don't get much money.
That doesn't matter to me.
Anyway!!
What the hell are you!!?
I'm just telling the truth.
Go home.
I was there when it happened.
He always does, right?
First, Nakai-kun said, "I invited you today, so I'll pay."
Then Matsumoto-san once said no, "No, I'll pay."
Then we thought the conversation would go:
"I'll pay,"
"No, I'll pay,"
"No, let me pay,"
"No, no , no, let me pay."
But he immediately said, "Oh, really? Thanks."
His will is really weak.
Are you idiots!?
What do you think you're doing!?
Why didn't you pay?
I paid, asshole!!
You didn't pay!!
I paid!
You didn't pay!
I paid for everything!!
Go for it!
What the hell!!
You didn't pay AT ALL!!!
Please pay up!!
I paid for everything you didn't know.
I paid after that.
I always keep your wallet and pay on your behalf.
So I know if you are paying or not at that time.
I see, you are paying instead of Matsumoto.
And I always see Nakai-san paying!!
No, it's not!
It's because he invited me!!
No, you didn't pay when you invited him either.
It doesn't matter if I didn't pay.
Fuck you all!!
You're a bunch of pussies!
Low-brow comedians!!
That's absurd.
You, you, you, and you are all low-brow comedians!
Fuck you all!!
But Yamashita, just go home.
I don't like that!!
Let me be one of them!!
Unbelievable testimonies are revealed one after another!!
Is Matsumoto really a stingy bastard!?
The second part will be aired next week!!
Finally, Matsumoto will be sentenced!!
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]