Gaki no Tsukai presents the 1st,
"Wait until weep! Cuckoo Championship~!!"
Shōzō Endō
Naoki Tanaka
Hōsei Tsukitei
Masatoshi Hamada
Hitoshi Matsumoto
COCORICO
DOWNTOWN
Matsumoto-san, what's this all about?
I'm not enthusiastic about this at all.
This is just at one's own timing.
Well, everyone will be put in various situations,
Yes
in which you'd cry for real at your own timing.
(Today's aim)
(A contest of dramas that will make you cry)
Yes... for real.
I'm not looking forward to this at all.
What are you talking about?
It's really hard.
Tsukitei-san seems relatively enthusiastic though
Yeah, I worked hard for this.
What I heard was that Tsukitei-san and Tanaka-san were all in for this idea.
Not at all.
It's more like...
Tsukitei-san and Tanaka-san want to earn as actors as well.
No, no, no.
Not at all.
Endo-san wants to do the same but his acting skill just isn't up to par.
Lacking in capacity.
The rules are quite simple: the act will continue until tears have been shed.
It's not a time trial race, however timing is paramount.
Giving up is also possible.
Now then...
Basically, there's no talking involved.
Ah yes, it's all about emotions.
(Rule 4)
(Plays must be silent with no lines/script)
Yes, just emotions.
You sure seem to be brimming with confidence.
No, I'm seriously not.
I'm serious.
Tanaka is just great at it.
Really?
Can you just stop..?
Tanaka's already working seriously with Yomiuri TV.
Yomiuri TV
Lead actor in
"Settlement Lawyer"
The connection between
Tanaka and Yomiuri TV is no joke.
He did an insane amount of work for them.
With that said, let's see Tanaka's acting skills as he takes on the challenge.
Will he be able to cry?
What scenario is this?
Summer...
Sad situation
Visiting a grave
I see.
He's playing himself.
Seems so.
This is...
Seriously, what is this?
Obviously, he can't hear us.
* Tanaka cannot hear the member's voices.*
So that we don't disrupt his concentration.
Who's this supposed to be?
His father?
Maybe an ancestor? Depends on how Tanaka's looking at the situation.
Looking at this face though,
he's already begun acting.
Sure does.
He's an actor after all.
He is an actor.
Wow.
That's an actor's face.
It sure is, alright.
Like he's channeling it all in.
He looks like Saitou Yosuke here.
He's an actor, time to show his skills.
He's been staring at it the whole time.
The acting's already begun.
It's slowly building up.
He's doing well. Eyes are getting heavy.
It's coming.
You're kidding me.
It's coming. It's coming.
It's coming.
There it is.
No way.
It's comin' out.
Go, go.
It's really coming out.
Yomiuri TV definitely won't be cutting him loose.
Fall, fall.
They won't let go of him.
Seriously, the tears won't fall if he blinks.
That's right.
Wait until he cries, right?
Yep.
Nope, he blinked once.
He messed up.
He got excited instead.
And he was doing so well.
Just one more step and he'd have nailed it.
The thread of tension has been broken.
He has let an early big chance go...
Will he be able to create that feeling once more?
But still, that's an actor's face.
Looks good.
He's attempting to pull it off from expression.
Seems so.
Rather than tricking the mind, he's trying to trick the brain with expressions.
His mouth though...
it's shaking.
His mouth is shaking.
Looks like he's trying to trick his mind into it.
He sure is an actor.
Hang in there.
Ah, this is where you've seriously just got to hang in there and keep at it.
Once he crosses this hurdle...
He couldn't pull it off on the previous one.
Come, come, come.
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon.
There, there, it's coming...
Just a bit more...
It's coming.
Go, go, go.
When it's about to come out, he blinks.
His heart is betraying him?
That's because he's making the expression.
This pressure...
Nope.
It stopped.
Did it?
I'm already tired of watching.
By the way...
Certainly, nothing's really changed.
Entering an unexpectedly long battle
The more he panics, the more he is unable to cry
No need to move your mouth.
That mouth is... cheap, isn't?
A cheap move.
Normally at those times there's a priest with a harisen.
Note: A harisen is a giant paper fan used for slapping. It is used to smack a funny man in response to their jokes or idiocy.
There has been no change whatsoever.
That's his normal face.
It's his normal face.
It's that normal face since his debut.
So true.
Only the time heartlessly passes by.
There it is.
(They can GIVE UP by pushing the button)
The button is there in a worst case scenario.
We're watching the same thing, but it's kinda different now.
Hang in there, Tanaka.
You're the lead after all.
It's funny watching the same thing, but...
He's always getting stuck there.
That's right.
A bit more, go for it!
Look, in the corner.
Yes, the corner.
From the outer corner, come out.
Ah, it's coming...
Yes, yes
Fall, fall, fall...
Fall, fall, fall.
Stop blinking!!
Nope!
You won't recover if you blink here.
Yeah, if you blink, the tears won't come out.
Nope, he lost it.
Of course that happened.
He messed up blinking his eyes.
The hell're you laughin' at!?
He did his best.
He was very persistent.
This is tough.
It truly is.
I didn't even imagine that Tanaka would fail here.
I'm sorry.
So quiet.
24 minutes 6 seconds.
My real dad...
Ah, you were thinking about your father.
He's still kickin' around.
But the tears just wouldn't fall.
Yeah, it didn't.
Even then it didn't come out.
We were here forever.
Yes.
I'm so sorry.
Was it hard?
Yes, it was hard for me.
I couldn't do it.
Actor-comedian Tanaka unexpectedly gave up.
Who will succeed!? Stormy premonitions!
TOFU PANDA FANSUBS PRESENTS
Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Translator(s):
J-Hive
Solari
JAPENGSubs
Typesetter(s):
KazumaSanjaya
GakiFanSub
Wrathz (Lloyd)
Extra Help:
Nicole (Team Gaki)
James (Team Gaki)
Tonight, truly tearful dramas
A must see! "That man" crying aloud?!
TOFU PANDA FANSUBS
His acting abilities are unknown.
Tsuketei Housei, will he be able to cry?
What's his scenario?
That's the question.
He's a dad.
Ain't this some serious shit?
Just how much does he believe in himself?
You can't do it
without confidence.
Dad, may I have a word?
What is it?
What do you wanna talk about?
He actually has a daughter.
Dad, thank you for raising me so preciously up to now.
This is hitting his core.
Sad situation
Greetings from daughter who is getting married
I am getting married today.
I'm sorry for all the times I've worried you from misbehaving.
I'm truly happy having been born to you and Mom.
From here on, I want to have a happy marriage like the one you and Mom share,
It's coming.
Wow!
It's already coming.
with a family household which is fun.
I'm truly grateful for everything you've done for me so far.
It just keeps on coming.
No way, this idiot...
Damn!
So quick!
Wow!
Damnnnn!
That was too damn quick.
Something's definitely wrong with him.
Just amazing...
That was too damn quick!
There it is.
That's it, it's over.
The daughter's letter was just perfect.
I think there was more to it.
It could've been just the middle part of the letter.
Just amazing...
That's enough.
He still can do it.
Even now he's crying.
Too long with his winning mode.
So quick!!
This one's the winner.
You were terrific.
Crying time:  2 min 3 sec
Just about 2 minutes.
Yamasaki-san, you were great.
2 minutes.
You were definitely thinking about your daughter, right?
I absolutely was, but...
It was coming outta your nose too.
It was coming out nonstop.
Like Ishida Ayumi.
Coming up, how does Matsumoto lament?
Is this guy an idiot!?
As a movie director, he can't show an embarrassing performance.
Will Matsumoto be able to cry?
A park?
It is.
Looks like it.
There's a kid playing in it.
Ah, it's the real thing.
Yeah, in the sandbox.
There's a kid playing in it.
What's the matter?
What's this supposed to be?
Sad situation
A young boy playing in the park
Like after a divorce...
Ah! He can't be with his son
as much.
Something like that.
We don't know his job.
He probably can't see him as much.
Ah! But...
He's getting into it through expression.
He totally is.
He's going down that route.
Ah, but...
He's doing well.
Isn't it coming?
It's the first hurdle...
Yes, this is the one.
But man, it's hard to look with those wires.
You're right, that wire is hiding his eyes.
I see, it's tied together so perfectly.
The wire should go away.
The damn wire.
But there's a bit coming out.
Ah, it's there.
Can he do it on his first try already?
If the tears don't come out here, it'd become impossible
He'll do it!
It's out.
The tears came out.
What the..? He's amazing.
Just amazing...
There it is, there it is.
That wire was getting in the way.
Wow, amazing!
That's just amazing.
It really is.
The tears came out.
You've gotta be kiddin' me.
Is this guy an idiot!?
Since he has a real daughter...
No wonder he felt sad.
So quick!
Even faster than Yama-chan.
1 minute 50 seconds.
No way.
He's still into the act.
He's still at it.
The act is still ongoing.
What's with him?
Man, he was great.
Damn, that was amazing.
He definitely created some story in his head.
He wasn't able to be with the kid much.
Looked like it.
Was that fast or what? Amazing, right?
You were quicker than Yamazaki.
Eh, I wonder why?
Crying time:  1 min 50 sec
You timed at 1 minute 50 seconds.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You were amazing.
Damn!
What were you thinking about?
Seriously, it looked so sad seeing him play all alone and by himself.
Ah, is that so.
I see.
We thought you couldn't be with your kid.
Yeah, and that you just couldn't be around as much.
That... whoa, whoa, whoa, I did it.
Hamada-san!
Finally.
Anyway, when you're out there, you shouldn't think of the staff as variety staff.
You have to think those staff members are proper people.
I see.
With two successful challengers in a row...
Will Hamada be able to cry?
What's with the scenario?
He's a kid?
This is...
Note: Shiro was Hamada's pet dog in his
childhood. It was based on the true story.
Sad situation
Beloved Shiro ran away
This is one big hurdle.
Shiro ran away.
Feeling dumbfounded after noticing it.
Well, Hamada's dog...
This is just...
You know about his dog, right?
Yes, yes.
Surprisingly, it's about his dog.
He's in trouble.
It's the same scenario?
This is just wrong.
Looks like he's accepted the situation.
Seems so.
With such a difficult situation, he's unable to get into his role.
However, the crying switch is suddenly turned on.
What's he going through here?
I wonder too.
But, somehow it's taking effect.
It's coming.
It's coming, look.
C'mon, c'mon.
It's accumulating.
For real?
Yes, yes, yes, Hamada-san.
It's not a joke.
This, this here is the important part.
This, this, this is the important part.
After he feels, he just need to wait.
It's starting to look like it will take a while.
The first hurdle.
It's headed in the same direction as Tanaka.
Come here already Hamada.
It was so close.
The situation changed to a long war battle.
Come, come.
Left eye!
You can do it!
Don't! Better not lose here.
It's come down to this.
Yeah, the button appeared.
During my turn, it wasn't
there at all.
(They can GIVE UP by pushing the button)
I didn't where it was.
He looks like
Mikawa Genichi now.
See.
What the hell is this?
This is like a Fumakilla commercial.
So true.
It's been 10 minutes since the start
searching for a breakthrough
He's not looking towards Shiro at all.
Where's he looking at then?
What is he thinking about? Shiro?
Yeah, you would've thought he would at least looked towards where Shiro was.
What's this?
You gotta shit or what?
He's trying to bring out with expression.
It's come down to expression.
His expression is already taking 10 min.
At this point, he has to rely on expression.
No good.
It's tough after all.
He's coming back.
Man, it looks tough.
Oh man, too bad he couldn't do it.
In the end, no good.
Next one is the last one.
It's too bad.
That's just impossible.
When I first saw the dog house,
it kinda cracked me up.
We were crackin' up on this side as well.
We could only see it as a Fumakilla commercial
Seriously, you've gotta get it right on the first try.
From the start.
Speaking of Cocorico,
Tanaka failed.
I apologize.
The connection to Yomiuri TV is beginning to disappear.
The person in Cocorico who can't act;
will Endo be able to do it?
Concert?
This?
This is a tough one.
Sad situation
The changing room after his pro wrestling retirement match
He's so strict on himself.
This is tough for him
and for the program.
What is this?
He was holding a flower though.
Retirement?
Ah, yes...
I wonder what it is?
It's should be hard to see with that mask on.
His eyes look like they're...
Looks like his eyes are becoming red.
Really?
Yes, good.
Looks promising.
This looks promising, ah he's taking it off.
It's better to take it off.
It's better to have it off.
That was fur?
I didn't really find that funny at all.
A wig.
He's acting while looking at the mask,
while thinking of various past events.
I see.
He's waiting now.
This guy, to begin with, his acting is fishy.
But...
A moment please...
His first chance.
It's coming, it's coming.
He widened it.
That ain't good.
He opened it.
He opened his eyes wide.
This smells like Daiei Film.
You're right.
He's really glaring at the mask.
He has to reflect on his good memories; there must be something.
Ahh, no good?
He came back to zero again.
He let the chance go?
He lost it.
Lost the first chance.
He changed?
He changed.
He changed the setting.
Doing it from the belt?
Endo fails at the start.
He started to move now.
I see.
Trying to find a breakthrough, he tries various things.
What's he doing?
Yomiuri TV's watching
That tan he got from golfing...
He doesn't look like a pro wrestler at all
That's a polo shirt tan
He's keeping his eyes wide open this whole time.
That's just dirty.
Leaving them open to make it dry.
What's going on?
Enough already! Go change clothes and take a shower.
It's no good. He didn't live up to the expectation.
That's right, next, the expected mediocre show.
He's doing a big expression.
Mori Shinichi's out.
You're right.
And after this?
Ah, he widened his eyes.
This pattern.
It's a public drama.
Ah, he's looking up and having it open the entire time.
He might be able to pull it off.
He's really at it.
Using the glare of the studio lighting...
How cheap...
He's gonna burn his eyes.
Shameful and hideous.
Hurry up.
What's with the face?
Note: Mori Shinichi is a Japanese male
enka singer and composer, who also
sings folk and pop music.
Like I said, Mori Shinichi.
What the heck is this face?
This is Mori Shinichi when caring about his mother.
"Eh? Really?"
"Then, what song should I sing?"
20 minutes pass
Cocorico has seriously taken a boatload of time.
Really, how much time he's taking? More than all of us together.
Cry already.
What's the matter?
What the? This is new.
Compared to the previous expressions, this is something new. Isn't this good?
He's should really just stop widening his eyes.
That was no good.
What impeccable timing.
Struggling with this hard time, but the conclusion wasn't long enough.
He did it.
The chance was at the beginning.
That's the way to do it.
Return faster man!
You stink at acting.
I stink at acting?
When you widened your eyes...
What were you thinking about when you were looking at the mask?
I thought maybe I should take it off.
Getting into Shikoku's mindset?
That I got the championship belt mindset.
You also looked at the belt.
The fight with Escargoman
If you were thinking of such a thing, of course you weren't able to cry.
What's the point of the fight anyway?
In the end, only two members cleared and three failed.
For Tanaka who had worked on many dramas, hopefully this won't affect future offers
Tanaka, wanna give it another go?
Such situations do actually happen.
But, that...
Whoa, this is just...
it's too difficult with this.
This thing here is just amazing.
I see.
After using this return to me, okay?
I'm going to borrow this.
Are really going through with it?
I really don't think it's gonna work.
Ah, how about you visit the grave with the Shikoku mask on?
Ah! You were fighting your opponent in the ring and you accidentally killed him.
And you visit his grave wearing this.
And he's your best friend.
So just wear this that you'll be nail this quickly.
I got it, here goes.
Tanaka's weeping performance revenge.
How'll he fare?
How nostalgic.
I definitely think he'll pull it off.
Sad situation
Visit his beloved opponent's grave
Looks good.
Sure does.
Compared to the
previous attempt...
Such a restless pro wrestler...
You can totally tell it's a fake Shikoku.
Yeah.
But he also knows that if he doesn't succeed in the first 3 min it's over.
He has a long opportunity to concentrate.
Good, it's coming.
So fast.
Looks like if will go like this.
He's moving his jaw like this.
Good, good, good.
It's coming.
One more gear, c'mon.
C'mon.
Vroom~ come out.
Can't do it.