Subtitles by: /u/CatZombies
Airdate: 2019-05-12
A celebration! Hamada Masatoshi's birthday celebration.
High Tension: The best 10!
Well, hello~. Good evening~.
Matsumoto-san, over here please.
Good evening.
Hello, good evening.
Hello, hello. It's been quite a while, hasn't it?
It's been a while. Um, excuse me.
The title is...
Ah, today is a special compilation.
For Hamada Masatoshi's birthday,
Okay.
to celebrate, they're going to do previous High Tensions for you today.
Is that right?
Yes.
There may be some reluctant people here as well...
Well, let's get started at once.
Okay!
This week's 10th place is!
At 71 points, "Let's celebrate. Around the Loop 7 Road."
by Cocorico's Tanaka Naoki.
Congratulations!
The title is rather interesting.
10th place?
10th place, but before that
congratulations.
No, no. Thank you.
No, enough of that. Thank you.
We sincerely thank you for taking the time.
We often ask the first person, but
what's the feeling backstage?
Well, basically no one is talking.
There is something I heard,
from the staff.
The oldest among today's performers is
a 62-year-old person.
The staff is unbelievable too.
They're rehearsing them over and over I heard.
In addition, there are some that aren't familiar with High Tension.
Simply put, they're not used to television.
There's at least one person.
There's a person like that?
Well, Tanaka-san.
If you would.
Please go on standby.
Alright.
This week's 10th place. Cocorico's Tanaka Naoki with
"Let's celebrate. Around the Loop 7 Road."
Loop 7, oi!
Is this High Tension?
Ah, here we go.
This is a bit more like it.
What is this? What is this?
Is it the Loop 7? Is it the Loop 8? Is it the Loop 6?
Let's meet at all those places!
Hamada-san, bugya!
Alright, thank you very much.
Okay.
Back there, the people that are going to come out made "ugh" sort of groans.
Those leaked out a bit.
Let's continue.
This week's 9th place is!
At 87 points,
"Ka-burlesque" by KABA-chan.
Congratulations.
Your first appearance.
Thanks for having me.
Happy birthday.
Thank you very much.
Hamada-san loves sexy, doesn't he?
He loves sexy.
Therefore, I want my sexiness to be on full display.
Today is that sort of day, isn't it.
Yes.
Well, please go on standby.
I'll do my best. Thanks for having me.
The one after Tanaka-san is KABA-chan.
That's right.
This time, all the people coming out will
have some relation to Hamada-san.
Ah! So that's the case. Got it.
This week's 9th place, KABA-chan with "Ka-burlesque".
What is this?
Well, she's good at dancing.
She's good.
Yeah.
She's a dance choreographer after all.
Huh, what's she doing?
What's this?
Huh, that's unexpected.
That's truly unexpected.
Since we've enjoyed the dancing enough,
So this comes after.
this is the finisher...
Hamada-san! Happy 56th birthday!
Thank you for being born!
Thank you!
So, is it over?
Are you okay? Be careful.
Watch out. Watch out.
Well, we can take in the sexiness here as well.
Ah, that's right, isn't it.
Watch out. Watch out...
She's doing it anyway.
What is this?
It's hot.
Hot, hot, hot!
Alright, thank you very much!
She did quite a few things there.
This week's 8th place is!
At 152 points,
"Calligraphy" by Harada Ryuuji.
"Congratulations!" we'd like to say, but
Eh?
It seems this person's schedule didn't fit, so
So, that's the case.
we have a video that we'll be watching.
Is that so?
Ah, thank you.
To the contrary, no matter what, they really wanted to appear.
That's right.
Indeed.
Let's go. This week's 8th place.
Harada Ryuuji's "Calligraphy".
Masatoshi-san!
For your 56th birthday! Sincerely!
Happy birthday!
I'll use this hair stick!
For your 56th birthday.
I want to celebrate!
Hair stick?
A garage?
He's in a garage.
I'll be using India ink!
He's really letting his voice out.
It's amazing.
Here we go!
He's an idiot.
He's a moron, isn't he. A moron.
Woah, woah, woah.
No, no, no...
It fell!
This is a celebration!
Celebrate! Celebrate! Celebrate!
Celebrate! Celebrate!
Celebrate! Celebrate~!
No, enough now...
Masatoshi-san!
You can really see his d*ck.
For your 56th birthday! Sincerely!
Happy birthday!
Thank you very much.
You saw 10th, 9th, and 8th place. What do you think?
You guys are next with 7th place.
Can I share my honest thoughts?
Yes.
I'm trembling.
7th place. "Instrumental 2019" by License
It's here. It's finally here.
What?
They're celebrating.
What is it though?
In regards to the current comedy world,
I feel like I know License's exact position.
I feel like I get it.
Where License is in the current comedy world.
It felt like it embodied us.
This week's 6th place is!
At 343 points,
"Pretty Pretty" by YOU
"Congratulations!"
Huh?
we'd like to say, but
Again?
Just like before with Harada, she'll appear by video.
Eh?
She's appearing by video because she has a high fever
or something like that.
Hamada-san, happy birthday.
I'm Ishino Mako.
Hamada-san is a big Mako fan I heard, so
It seems that when you were young,
you used me to "sate your appetite".
Thanks for taking care of me...
Ah, am I taking care of you?
Thanks for everything.
That said, today
Mako will be doing a challenge I'm not good at.
I'll do my best to celebrate for you.
Ah, that "Pretty Pretty".
The song.
Uh huh.
♪ Some things don't go so smoothly.
YOU-san is also a musician.
Yeah, that's right.
♪ Have you ever been so sulky?
She's good at singing as well.
If she was able to go to that location, wouldn't she be able to come here?
♪ Everyone's more grown up than last year.
That's right...
She's singing.
♪ I don't understand.
Woah!
♪ Why are you standing aimlessly in a dark window?
She's sounding a little enthusiastic.
♪ Aren't you different from usual?
♪ ○△□×☆※…！
♪ Your usual...
♪ It's nothing he said.
Wow, that's amazing.
♪ And yet, you've caught my eye.
Wow, it's scary.
♪ Dance with me, Pretty Pretty Pretty.
♪ I don't understand.
♪ I don't understand!
♪ I really don't understand.
♪ My troubles are
♪ Not those, not those things.
♪ I don't understand.
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
How was it, Hamada-san?
I certainly haven't seen that sort of thing recently.
That's right.
With her.
I was a little worried that rain was going to start drizzling.
"Is it going to start drizzling?" I thought.
Let's continue.
This week's 5th place is!
At 488 points,
"The Woman of Rumors 2019" by Hiroki.
Congratulations!
Now this?
Hiroki-san.
This is getting really personal.
Thanks for everything.
Well, the staff said
there's no harm in trying and you might be pleased.
Yes, I'm Maekawa Kiyoshi's son.
My father sings without making the slightest movement. That's his style.
I too...
In a situation even more harsh than my father's,
I'll do it completely without the slightest movement.
You're doing it like that?
I'll sing Hamada-san's favorite song for you.
Understood.
Okay.
♪ The sadness of a woman's heart.
♪ I don't understand.
♪ To the people of the world.
♪ A woman.
Thank you very much.
You did a wonderful job smearing mud in your father's face.
Happy birthday.
Thank you. Really.
How has it been? From what you've seen so far.
Right.
This is my first time here too, but
I'm quite nervous but
well, it's his birth...day.
I'll hang in there until the end.
You can't speak properly!
Not once! Not even once.
You can't speak at all.
Not at all.
4th place. "Besting the King. The first year of Reiwa" by Azuma Mikihisa
Hey!
I never thought I'd have to fight you.
This is the first time I've seen you this close.
It's said you're the king of the fruits.
I'm going to take that title of king.
I'm going to become king, heh.
It smells terrible.
I see.
He's crying a little.
Not so bad, you!
Amazing, isn't it? It's over here as well.
Listen now, I'm going to shove you up both my nostrils.
It's incredible.
Now then, let's do battle.
Shove it up his nose?
Yes.
Here goes.
Woah.
For Hamada-san... he's doing this for Hamada-san.
Woah, already...
I'll insert this.
Hurry it up.
I'll definitely stick it in.
Okay.
Alright!
It stinks!
Oh~.
Woah.
This is amazing.
Wow.
Oh...
Woah.
Hamada-san,
Yes?
happy birthday.
Alright, thank you very much.
Eh~!?
Thank you very much.
It stinks. It stinks.
Let's continue...
Everyone hates it.
It seems something in this direction stinks.
Can you go home? Just him.
Well, let's continue. This week's 3rd place is!
At 732 points,
"The Loop 7 Road ~If pushing doesn't work, try pulling.~"
by Cocorico's Endo Shouzou
Why did you do that so grandly?
Your usual... your usual skit...
Like that?
As for this High Tension,
I already have high expectations for Endo-san.
Thank you very much.
He's a veteran. A veteran.
You're going to show us a perfect act.
I'm a little sorry for all the previous performers.
It seem this High Tension...
Stop that!!
I'm speaking right now.
Ok, sorry.
I'm telling you to stop.
Like when you're driving, there's the Loop 7 Road.
That's right. After all, um...
I've liked cars from the start.
Ah, is that so?
Stop that!!
It's okay to touch, but
you have to stop pinching!!
Still, let's continue.
Well, let's go to standby.
Alright, please go on standby.
That's also something we always do.
We always do that. That's all we ever do.
This week's 3rd place. Cocorico's Endo Shouzou.
"The Loop 7 Road ~If pushing doesn't work, try pulling.~"
What's this you bastard! Hey!
I just happen to be walking around the Loop 7 Road near Kaminuma.
Why is there a shark here!?
Why do I have to get bitten by a shark?
Eh?
Give me a break. Seriously.
Where did you come from?
Did you come from Nikotama over there?
That means, this way is Shibuya. Is that right?
Is that so? Alright.
Well then, you and me,
let's go buy Hamada-san's present.
Alright, let's go!
I like that.
We're passing Mishuku now.
Mishuku.
Alright, let's go back for a second.
He's going back?
He's got good stamina.
Yeah.
From here, we can go straight and it's on the left.
The restaurant where Hamada-san sometimes takes me to dinner.
So it has that sort of message too.
Huh?
Cut it out!
Why is he hitting it?
What's happened?
Is he having a breakdown?
Why is he hitting it?
I want to go to Shibuya right now!
Be quiet for me, okay?
Alright, let's enter 246.
We have to be quick...
Alright.
Why are they together?
What is he doing?
This street is getting crowded.
This street has gotten crowded.
Alright, I have no choice.
I'm going to fight you.
I don't care!
Even if the streets are crowded, I don't care!
Alright, just a second.
This is stupid.
Do it properly.
This guy is an idiot.
He's an idiot.
What the heck?
I don't know how this is going to end anymore.
Hmm, what's happening?
Alright. Alright, now.
I'm taking you back.
Eh?
Alright, Nakameguro's...
Those cherry blossoms are pretty by this river.
Float away.
Don't come back again.
Got it!?
♪~ Da-dum
Alright, thank you very much.
That was long, wasn't it.
Tanaka-san, are you okay?
Yes.
Backstage,
he was calmer than anyone else.
And yet, you did that?
It's strange. That you were calm doing that.
This week's 2nd place is!
At 835 points,
"Is magnesium oxide good for you?"
by Shoufukutei Shouhei
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
Thanks for having me.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
That's right, it has.
This guy?
That's right.
To get 2nd place on my debut here,
I'm really sorry about that.
But still,
we heard you had a very thorough meeting.
Well, well. More or less.
More or less.
I spoke with the High Tension's directors and producers.
There is that sort of thing.
Well, I'm a little sick, but
I'm not sure if I can do High Tension, so I'm worried...
Ah, we understand.
But, you saw everyone, they all have that feeling.
But everyone's been very good.
Excuse me.
Yes, what is it?
Please laugh a little more when you talk.
Please laugh more.
How much are you getting paid?
The amount? It's amazing, isn't it?
What the heck are you doing?!!
My nail came off.
What's funny about that?!!
Please go on standby.
Ok, got it.
What's funny about a nail coming off?
They're his senior.
It's because they're his senior.
They're senior.
This week's 2nd place. Shoufukutei Shouhei with
"Is magnesium oxide good for you?"
♪ Hama-chan,
♪ Happy birthday~!
♪ Hama-chan's birthday.
♪ Happy birthday.
Pardon me.
What? Who are you?
Hey, hey... wait please.
Why did you come here?
Let's stretch.
Stretching? Stretching!?
Alright, let's rotate.
What, what? Posture?
Alright, inhale.
Exhale~.
Ah~!
Okay.
Wait, stop already. Please stop.
Exhale.
Done~.
I kind of don't have anything to say.
There's nothing to be said.
Did you drink a lot today?
You drank a lot strong liquor today, didn't you?
He's not saying anything.
This week's 1st place is!
At 986 points,
"Chinchin-beta, sousou-beta, koukou-beta."
by Tsukitei Housei
Congratulations!
Well, 1st place again.
It really is always Housei.
You really spend a lot of money.
Only you spent a bunch of money.
Umm, how is it?
Whether this outfit is funny or not,
please tell me.
Hmm, I don't like it.
You don't like it?
I don't like it.
Well, but, well, well...
Alright, I'll go on standby.
After I answered his question, he got a little pissed off.
Ah, he's positioning. Good.
Ah.
This is good, isn't it.
Let's continue.
At this week's 1st place,
Tsukitei Housei with "Chinchin-beta, sousou-beta, koukou-beta."
Ha! Sou sou sou!
Sou sou sou sou sou!
Today is Hamada-san's birthday party~!
You knew that~!
I've been invited!
Let's have a little break.
♪ Chinchin-beta, sousou-beta, koukou-beta. Sunlight through the trees.
What is that?
You appeared!
You squishy Unakowa guy!
It appeared. It appears every time.
Turn around.
That scarf,
I'll grab that red scarf.
We often see this.
We also often see this.
Huh? What now?
You're here.
Hamada-san, you've finally appeared.
Happy birthday. This is the end.
Thank you very much!
It's not over yet.
There's still more to come.
There's more?
Yes, there's still more.
Ah, he's found something.
You're not Hamada-san.
It's continuing. This is continuing.
He's an imposter.
Who are you?
You... ah, you're ***'s kid!
Alright, he's dead.
He's dead. He's dead.
Ah, Hamada-san.
Hello.
"Hello" he says.
Happy birthday.
This isn't High Tension at all.
It's normal. It's normal.
This isn't High Tension.
What a face.
I don't understand this emotion.
It's the belly part.
We're to the belly performance.
It's come to this.
Amazing.
Is it alright if I eat more?
Not at all!
He's mad.
That hurt him.
I'm shocked.
We're sisters after all.
You're my little sister.
This is nonsense.
Nonsense.
Happy birthday!
Is that good, Hamada-san?
No good.
You're kidding?
Alright, thank you very much.
Let's take a commemorative photograph.
Okay, pose!
Alright, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I've eaten this before.
I have before. I have.
I'm still shallow, huh.
As expect! So cool!