First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende:
Yakiniku Toraji
Yamanote-line 25 store challenge!
TN: The Yamanote line is a loop around Tokyo.
This is our fourth time!
We gotta finish this one.
Yes. We've never finished one before.
That's true.
Have any of you been to Toraji?
I've been to Toraji.
Hamada-san?
No, I haven't been.
You know, I've heard,
out of all the eating episodes we've done,
there hasn't been much excitement.
But I've heard, this guy is just insane about yakiniku.
Don't just make stuff up!
He gets extremely excited over yakiniku.
I'm looking forward to that.
The base is different.
Shut up! What do you mean "base"?
His appreciation.
He is, Mister Meat.
I've heard that a lot.
At the planning meeting he always says "Let's do Yakiniku"
"GAHAH GAHAHA"
When he heard about this episode,
He stood up on his seat and went like this.
He was towering above the table.
Who told you this?
Typsetting by GakiDave
Translation by senor_wristband
Food Marathon #4: Yakiniku Challenge
Starting at Ginza 8-chome, they aim for 25th store at Shiodome.
At each store, they choose from 1 dish from 25, and work together to finish to proceed.
If they finish the challenge, they win 100,000 yen!
But if anyone gives up, they must pay for everything eaten so far.
We're almost there.
Ehh?!
This way.
The first store.
'Morning
This was close by.
They've failed 3 food marathons before,
Will they finish for the first time?
What dish will you start with?
Actually, let's try #9
Thick cut beef tongue.
I see!
They decide on thick cut beef tongue for their first dish.
It's here.
It's quick, as expected.
Thick cut beef tongue is here.
They're big.
There's one extra piece.
Inomoto can decide.
I can decide?
I choose Mr. Meat.
I'm gonna smack you.
You've accepted your role as Mr. Meat!
"I'll smack you!" he said.
We need to cooperate at each store right?
Yup.
Five men should be able to finish this.
Enough of that.
You're so naive. You don't respect the yakiniku.
What an amateur!
Well said, Mr. Meat.
Bon appétit!
Itadakimasu.
It's delicious!
Way good!
Who's eating this?
Mr. Meat.
It's all burnt, Mr. Meat.
You're treating him like your senpai.
He's a one year senior to everyone.
Well done!
Finished!
They're close together.
We were at 8-chome just now, next is 6-chome.
A 3 minute drive.
But I'm still fine, I wanna eat more.
It's brought out your hunger.
By the way, you're free to order a side.
But if you order something,
you have to pay for it by yourself.
Our money?
Yes.
They arrive at store #2, Ginza 6-chome.
They choose the specialty short rib.
This way...
Ah, once again,
Ginza 6-chome store!
Let's finish the 2nd store.
Can I order the egg soup?
Egg soup?
You'll get sick just eating meat.
That's true actually
Sorry Matsumoto-san, that'll be 580 yen.
Now?
He has to pay now?
Are you being serious?
It's the rule after all.
This show can't even afford egg soup.
Just cancel it then.
A show that can't afford egg soup...
Just cancel it!
It's here!
Specialty short rib.
There's six of them.
That looks delicious.
Here's your soup.
The egg soup is a necessity.
This is the garnish dish.
Why are you dicks placing it?
This is the sauce right?
How is it?
Delicious!
Can I have 2 pieces?
Oh you're going for it?
Delicious.
Just meat is difficult.
Mmm....this is tasty.
How is the egg soup?
The egg soup was the right choice.
The quantity is a lot, so you can share it-
No no way.
You're not gonna finish that by yourself.
Yeah, just split it.
It's a waste, you're gonna leave it anyways.
That's true.
So slow!
The time is important.
This is how the average Japanese consumes egg soup.
2nd store finished!
That soup was the right idea
Easy to eat. I want some chilled noodles too.
The next store is also in Ginza.
Ginza Core store
There's so many in just Ginza.
Let's go
The 3rd store in Ginza today.
Ginza Core location
This way
Alright
The 3rd store. What is your choice?
Since we're pretty hungry,
Yeah totally
The first stomach, what do you think?
First stomach
OK, first stomach please!
"First stomach, and"
I do wanna say "and, "
Let's look at the side menu.
Side?
Enough already.
You've got a huge appetite.
I want chilled noodles.
Are you sure? There's more stores to visit.
When I'm this hungry I get really stressed out.
I just want to settle my stomach.
Well let's see the stomach first.
We have to drive to the next store too you know.
It's unfortunate eating just this.
You can order half size chilled noodles.
I'll get half then.
Okay then.
Who's gonna eat this meat?
You are of course.
You kept saying you want to.
I mean fine,
Woah that looks good
It's alright, it's alright
You don't want to split this?
This is gonna be good
He's being serious
You're not getting this? Are you guys sure?
I do want to eat it
That looks ready
Server: It's done
Matsumoto-san can have 2 here, right?
I totally can
(tasty!)
I think I'll get noodles at the next store too.
Finished! Next store now.
Easy peasy, let's keep going.
So easy.
I'm getting hungrier and hungrier.
A side is a good idea, I'm telling you.
Maybe I'll get sangchu.
TN: Sangchu is lettuce salad.
No need to pretend like you're holding back.
The next store is also in Ginza.
What's wrong with Ginza?
I mean like, "Wow! Ginza again?"
What do you mean
I was just amazed, Ginza has 4 stores.
It's nice that it's close.
It was a positive "ehhh?!"
A 3 minute drive later and they reach the Ginza VELVIA location.
Let's do this
They choose the Diamond Cut Skirt Steak, as well ...
Can I order a side?
You want to order?
I want to order for myself.
The sangchu?
You don't want to split it?
Diamond Cut Skirt Steak
How many are these? Oh?
We have to cut it.
Oohh, this is amazing!
Woahhh that looks delicious
Smells great
Do you guys want rice?
Can I get some rice actually?
An order of rice?
Looks amazing
This isn't enough for 5 people
If just 2 people want to eat here that's alright.
Well he ordered rice.
Just those 2
Do you want to eat this with me Hosei-san?
Hmmmm I think not.
I want to eat just 1 piece.
1 piece is good for me.
Yeah actually, the rice looks delicious.
Eating it with this meat.
Damn I want rice.
Can we split the rice?
It's up to him.
Let's stop this hoarding of side dishes.
Actually, let's split it.
This time I want us to work together.
I see, that's the important thing.
Delicious!
We can't bring the rice and the sangchu with us.
Of course we can!
Why would you bring sanchu with you?
Yeah
You cut such small pieces of that sangchu
What's with that?
Why not bigger pieces?
Exactly
What are you doing seriously?
You've been exposed.
The meat is finished.
Just that sangchu.
Maybe eat it with miso.
I'll take this with me.
You can try,
ut the store might not let you bring it in.
You're bringing that into the store?
That's no good
You can bring it home if you want
You can eat it in the car.
No way,
Eat it while observing Ginza
Eh? I can't bring it?
Just bring it for now.
This is the side dish problem.
You said I could bring it.
You can't bring it inside.
That's- I can't eat it now.
Bringing it in is...
You can order it in the store again.
It's gonna be a hassle.
Asking "is this OK, is that OK?"
Eh really?
Wait this wasn't my intention!
Just eat it now
Then, what should we do
Each of you give me 100 yen
Why 100 yen from everyone?
At the 5th store, they get the set meal.
There's quite a lot.
Looking at it like this
Bon appetite!
Delicious.
This is way good.
The 5 work together and finish quickly
However...
The meat juice is hitting hard...
Well done! Finished!
I see, this is how it feels.
It comes all of a sudden.
I mean I can still eat,
But I'm starting to feel a little sick.
The rice was a bit much.
The chilled noodles were a bad idea...
Of course!
We're almost there, the Hibiya store.
With little time to spare, they reach Hibiya.
So, the 6th store
What is your order?
Let's get the king crab?
Seafood?
Let's switch to seafood
King crab it is.
I'm gonna take a sh!t.
Hurry up and go.
We'll wait for you to come back.
Of course.
We gotta preserve the teamwork.
I do want to eat Le Crab.
What the hell is "Le Crab"?
Certainly, the greasiness is a lot.
You feel the meat hit after eating.
Hamada, out of 10, how full are you?
Around 6 I think. 5 or 6.
I guess I'm also around 6.
Around 6 for me too.
After,
I'm still,
Tanaka you're fine?
2 to 3 for me.
The meat hits you all of a sudden.
Really? I wouldn't know.
It's cause Tanaka is the tallest.
There it is.
He says that every time.
That's not it.
Ah, he's back.
He looks so dissapointed.
It's not here yet?
Nope.
You could've finished while I was gone.
It's not here yet though.
It's here, right on time.
Wait you didn't wait for me right?
Right on time.
Tanaka says he's not full at all, by this point.
It seems he's really starving.
No no, we were all talk-
He said he's at a 2/10
We all said we're around 6.
Woah, you guys are already at 6?!
Hear me out, you guys haven't eaten that much.
And you're still at 6?
I mean I'm at 8, but...
Cause I ate the noodles!
That's your fault.
Let's eat!
This change of taste is nice.
Man this is a culture shock for me
I didn't know the Gaki members could eat so little.
I've definitely eaten the most.
Finshed!
Let's go!
I want a bit of a challenge here.
I've calculated this choice.
I didn't think the stores would be this close by.
Diamond Cut Short Rib
They arrive at 7th store while complaining about the distance.
We're here.
Okay, let's get past here.
I think I've caught a cold.
Do you have a thermometer?
I might have a fever.
You don't!
Is there a thermometer?
There's a chance that my appetite will be affected.
Cause you have a cold?
It's here!
There's just one.
Just one piece, please use these scissors.
Here, the still hungry Tanaka makes a statement.
I will definitely eat half of this.
I'll get this piece.
Impressive.
Tanaka takes responsibility for half, while the other four munch away.
Here I go.
We will remember your initiative here Tanaka.
Remember it please then.
Finished! Let's go to the next store.
Liscense, you guys gotta pay attention
Yamasaki isn't eating at all!
That's true.
I mean if you eat from the side menu,
I'm eating the same as everyone,
and I've got a 40 degree fever.
TN: 40 degrees Celsius is 313.15 Kelvin
40 degrees?
I said maybe, I don't know.
It might be higher.
Pork Jowl Wasabi
Meanwhile, they arrive at the 8th store, inside the Marunouchi Building.
Here, they take Matsumoto's temperature.
My throat definitley hurts.
I can feel a cold coming on.
If you switched bodies with me.
You'll say;
"Woah, seriously?! This guy is really pushing himself!"
"How can he be this eager?"
You guys would collapse and this would end.
I'm not sure about that.
What are you doing?!
It'll be 80 degrees then.
Seriously I do have one, I actually do.
How high?
It's a real fever.
In that case we'll understand.
Pork Jowl Wasabi
There's wasabi coated on the meat.
Take it from him.
How high is it?
That's a normal temperature.
36.7 is like the best isn't it?
The best temperature, yes.
What do you mean, best temperature?
If it was serious, it would be over 37.
Who will have that piece?
I'll have it then, I'm still fine.
Alright, Endo you go.
I'm going for two pieces.
It's good?
It would be good with alcohol.
Finished!
Next store.
Let's go.
I feel sicker than expected.
It hits afterwards.
The 9th store is pretty close.
It's close by.
Filet
With no time to rest, they arrive at the 9th store in Yaesu.
Six again.
There's six piece again.
I'll get this one then.
Really?
Yes.
They cooperate, feeling the burden of the fattyness.
They aim to finish.
Oh this is delicious.
It's good, right?
Finished!
Let's head to the next store.
We will reach the Akihabara store soon.
Have you decided your order?
I've never seen Gopchang before.
Ahh let's go for something we haven't seen.
It's a cute name too, Gopchang.
Let's conquer the gopchang.
It's made of intestine.
They decide on gopchang, a perfect balance of umami, sweetness, and fat.
Hmm.
Who will eat the extra pieces?
I will take care of them.
Can I see the side menu?
Side menu at this point...
I see.
I think I'll get a salad.
I see, add some vegetables.
There's a lot of fat on these.
They look ready.
Sorry for the wait.
Whoa, here it is.
No that's alright, he's eating that by himself.
Man, I wanted to split it this time too.
It does look delicious after all.
Tasty.
It's sweet.
Yum!
Finshed! Let's go.
How do you feel now?
Honestly, I feel just right.
Are you at a 5?
Nah, like full.
So a 10?
My stomach is nice and ... plump, like this.
I didn't think I would feel this full after two...
There's no escape.
Next week; Yakiniku Toraji Part 2.
A new rule changes their fates!
Ready, steady, flip!
Save me please.
NO MORE!
Will they be able to finish?!