The 1st Gaki No Tsukai Arahende! chikichiki
Brilliant movie director
Tsukitei Housei breaks into the movie industry~!!
Thank you for your hard work.
Another quiet intro.
Excuse me. What are you doing?
With the nose spray?
Figured it was a good time...
with the overall mood being terrible.
The mood is not terrible.
Tonight. I finally got full control.
To break into the movie industry.
Movie industry?
Well, we all got to appear...or should I say, more like, allowed to participate perhaps?
Yes, well, I was responsible for the casting and did this and that, but...
what do you all think is booming right now?
Eh? I wonder.
Yes, Tanaka.
So sudden.
Movie industry? Period pieces?
WROOONG!
So noisy...
Right now. There's an unprecedented, heart-warming love-romance boom.
This movie is really for the T1 class...
You mean teen, right?
Yes, the teens are booming.
Right now in the movie industry, an unprecedented heart-warming love-romance boom!
From the top 20 movies released last year...
6 were heart-warming love-romance movies!
That's where, tonight...
brilliant director Tsukitei Housei, produces an All-Gaki member heart-warming love-romance movie!
Here is the cast over here.
I picked all these. Even the names.
- Oh really?
Hamasaki, Iku.
This girl's the main character.
"Iku" as in to live.
- Yes, Iku as in to live.
Later there'll be an explanation as to why.
And Hamasaki Masayuki [Hamada Masatoshi]
Iku's father.
And the Principal is Matsumoto Hitoshi.
The Teacher role is Tanaka.
And the PE teacher is Endo.
However, it's all the "Iku" character.
For me, that sticks out.
Yeah, now that you mention it.
Yea, you're right! I could've written "Vice Principal" or something.
For me, honestly, my screen time wasn't very much.
- That's true!
Mm, I really apologize for that.
You could've even flipped these, I feel.
Tanaka was on screen a lot.
I was pretty much non-existant.
Right, what was that with me and Endo?
Well, that was your acting skills.
Wait a minute.
I can understand me, but Matsumoto-san?
But he was the lead in Busjack 2.
It's becuase I saw that.
I doesn't stink that much!
OK, let's go! This is our heroine! She's awesome!
Boom! Taira Yuna-chan!
A super popular actress!
The main character, Hamasaki Iku, is Taira Yuna!
Just the last year, she appeared in 9 movies!
Playing the heroine in many heart-warming love-romances. A popular young actress!
So shall we get started?
Start what?
- "What?", we're gonna watch it.
The finished product?
- The finished product.
You're not finishing it.
It is finished.
I did read your script one time. I don't think it's as rich as that though.
You praised me, didn't you?
What are you talking about?
After you read it, when we were in the restroom...
You said, "You're a smart fool."
- "A smart fool."?
I didn't say it like that. No, I...
read your script and thought it was a little amusing.
Now, how it plays out, I'll have to see it to understand.
This is Tsukitei Housei's first directorial project.
VTR...
enjoy.
what?
Written and Directed by Tsukitei Housei
Let's Go Home Together
Please...be my girlfriend!
I'm sorry.
C'mon, Iku! How many is that now?
I told you he was a good catch!
Is he?
Graduating alone is lonely too, y'know.
Or...is there another boy you like!?
That's not it!
what~
you can tell me.
huh?
[Art Room]
(♪ Himawari no Yakusoku - Hata Motohiro)
Teacher!
Iku...
Are you going home?
Let's go home together!
To find out you're a pizza-bun fan, too.
We're the same.
Also, aren't you a fan of Hata Motohiro?
I'm a fan, too.
We even have pendants.
We're so much alike.
It's just coincidence.
More importantly, you better get home soon, Iku.
Right. That name, Iku. I don't care for it.
Iku as in "to live". Sounds kinda lame.
Isn't that the name your dying mother gave you so you could live on?
Don't talk like that.
How do you know that story, Teacher?
I...I heard it from someone.
Right. Just by chance.
Tanaka-sensei! We have a problem!
[Principal's Office]
What's your teacher teaching!?
I keep hearing he's walking with my daughter!
It's not like that!
Sir, please calm down. It must be some kind of misunderstanding.
It ain't no misunderstanding!
Get it together! I'm really pissed!
Excuse me!
Why you! You're a teacher and you're nearing my daughter!
You bastard! Don't you come near my daughter!
I...I understand.
I won't...near her again.
Excuse me.
Oy!
You gonna run away again?
[Graduation Ceremony]
Teacher?
This is where you were.
Found you.
Iku...
Congratulations on graduating.
Thank you.
Today I graduate from school, but...
I can't graduate from you.
Tanaka-sensei...
I love you.
Iku.
I love you too.
Really?
Do you know why I love you?
It's because...
I'm your real father.
A joke, so you don't have to date me.
It's not a joke.
Is that...
me?
No...
Your mother, Misako, and I...
along with your dad, Masato, were all friends in college.
We were college classmates.
Me, the gloomy guy, only interested in art.
From Osaka, the always funny, Masa.
And the sickly, but always happy, Misako.
We were from different backgrounds, but were always together.
I started dating your mother a year later.
It was a great time.
I was so happy.
And still...
You're so selfish!
Think about Misako!
I couldn't give up my dream of being an artist and left for France.
I had no idea you were inside your mother's stomach.
Misako...
didn't want to get in the way of my dream.
Supporting...
her decision to raise you on her own...
was Masa.
When you were born...
and after Misako passed away...
Masa raised you on his own.
Now you understand, Iku.
I'm your real father.
That's why I can't...
Stop.
I understand now.
But...
you're not my dad.
My dad...
my real dad...
there's only one in the world.
♪ Why...do...
♪ you...cry?
♪ When I haven't even cried yet.
♪ You...grieve...
♪ more than me...
Teacher?
Thank you.
For telling me the truth.
The name, Iku.
I love, now!
Let's go home together!
♪ Wanna be by your side...
♪ to do anything for you...
♪ if it's within my power~
♪ Always for you~
♪ Forever for you~
♪ I wish you to stay smiling.
Her smile...
looks more and more like yours.
♪ her unbending gentleness...
♪ her warmth, her everything~
♪ From now on, I too...
♪ hope to achieve...
♪ that happiness, in my heart...
♪ I now realize~
What the hell!
What's wrong?
What kind of tears are those?
It's bad.
What's bad?
Well it is bad.
It could go either way.
No.
Wait.
Um...
I'm crying so much I can't breathe.
Wow...really...
you're...
you're serious, aren't you?
I heard a rumor...
you cried when writing the script.
Is that so?
You cried.
Seriously?
- I cried as I wrote it.
What part was the sad part?
That's...
um, Iku...
the person she liked all this time, was her real father.
But she doesn't accept him as her real father.
Right?
he raised her...
Sorry, but...
you're copying, "Yamachan ain't quitting".
With this setting.
We can't take you seriously.
But you're serious, aren't you?
It was amazing.
Isn't the timeline a little off?
She suddenly graduates.
That's because graduation was nearing.
We didn't know that!
You would know. It's because you weren't watching properly!
Talking and jibber-jabbering.
It didn't even feel like Spring.
You couldn't tell what season it was.
No, it all flows...smoothly.
Yes, all the supporting scenes were taken.
What does Tanaka think? You worked the hardest!
No, no, no. Actually, there wasn't much direction.
Yeah!
A behind the scenes glimpse!
Director Housei and his problem scenes.
You're learning your lines now?
Sorry, sorry. I can't remember them.
Do we need that part with you singing?
Of course we do.
What would we do without it?
What is this?
What the!
Who are you?
Does a director appear this much?
It would've been fine with just the music.
Yea, no, what do you think Matsumoto-san?
What do you think about the song?
Well, it's a lil out of place. It's kinda like you were from another dimension.
- Yes, yes...
Like no one can really see you.
You keep saying, "Yes, yes" but...
You didn't even explain any of that!
Ah! Is that what you meant?
- Yes, yes...
My only scene...
it's so small to begin with.
To have my small lines cut out was quite the shock.
I keep hearing he's walking with my daughter!
It's not like that.
Sir, please calm down. It must be some kind of misunderstanding.
It ain't no misunderstanding!
Get it together! I'm really pissed!
Excuse me!
He wanted to retake it.
I didn't think it was a real take!
I thought it was a practice run. "OK! It's OK." EH!?
I thought it was rehearsal so I wasn't satisfied.
No, it was good.
I wanted the Principal to do it halfheartedly so it was really good.
But my voice wasn't quite ready, kinda hoarse.
This is the take Matsumoto wasn't satisfied with.
Where does Hamada-san sit?
What's with this guy?
What the...
Please.
All cast.
Thank you very much.
Matsumoto-san, you're over here. Thank you very much.
Here's Yuna-chan! Thank you very much!
Director, will my feet show?
Your feet?
Would this be fine?
Will the feet show? How's the angle?
You decide!
You're the Director!
Should I wear shoes?
Shoes? You're fine if they don't show. How's the angle?
Shouldn't I wear them?
- Says he should wear them!
They won't show.
- The won't show!
This part's the foreshadowing.
It's the heart of the story.
You're learning your lines now?
Sorry, sorry. I can't remember them.
Not, "I can't remember them."!
For real, I can't remember them.
- Let's stop with the, "I can't remember"
I keep saying the same lines so I can't remember.
- How can that be?
We have you properly in the frame so...
What was that?
Ready...and...start!
OY!
What's your teacher teaching!?
I keep hearing he's walking with my daughter!
It's not like that! I was the one who...
Sir, please calm down. It must be some kind of misunderstanding.
It ain't no misunderstanding! I'm hearing it!
Yes! We got it! Thank you very much!
(Director: OK!)
We got an "OK" from the Director.
(Director: Good! Good! Good!)
Was that good?
It's good.
- I didn't like it.
It kinda got rattle-y.
I didn't think it was a real take...
Are you kidding?
That might be a good take.
What does Tanaka think? You worked the hardest!
No, no, no. There wasn't much direction.
Yeah!
Felt neglected?
Felt neglected so I wasn't sure what to do.
He wouldn't tell us anything.
I wasn't exactly sure how to deliver my lines...
No, in fact, I was pondering that too.
Pondering?
Were you pondering?
[Director Housei's pondering scene.]
OK. We got it.
Oh, oh, nice, nice.
That last part...
maybe she's looking at Tanaka?
On the outside looking in...
Director, how was Hamada's acting?
I was...moved.
What are you talking about?
Um...Papa to Nacchan, was it?
I saw that back in the day and...
you've really matured.
So he wasn't good back then?
That part where Tanaka reveals the truth, you should've had her shocked more.
Yeah, that's true.
In Hamada's scene, Iku already knows you're behind the tree.
The tree's too far away.
The tree and Hamada are too far away.
There's no way he would've heard with the cicadas.
He did hear it.
What's with this guy?
What role is that?
He ain't even directing...
I don't get it.
Let's get started!
Alright! Here we go!
Big scene! Big scene!
I'm leaving at 5.
It doesn't matter, waiting is work too.
It's been a while tho.
Ready...and...start!
Thank you very much.
He was feelin it! He was feelin it!
Those were real tears!
Also Endo's scene...
the picking up of the signboard.
That acting...stunk.
That stunk too!?
Director Housei on Endo's stinky acting scene.
"Tanaka-sensei~"
I didn't say it like that!
Also Endo's scene...
the picking up of the signboard.
That acting...stunk.
That stunk too!?
[Endo's Stinky Acting]
There I am.
(Stinks!)
Eh!? That's it!?
Did it stink?
- That didn't stink!
The way you moved.
- No, not at all!
Was that OK, Director? It seemed to stink.
It did stink.
Even the part where he calls Tanaka stunk a little too, didn't it?
A little. What is it? It's like you know he's there, but he isn't.
He comes in and is all like, "Tanaka-sensei~".
I didn't say it like that.
To all the movie producers out there.
This movie is...
for sale!
Please...
Buy it!
- Sorry, I don't understand.
Can you explain it a little more?
This movie is up for sale!
We weren't aware of that.
We have press intros prepared.
I just had a tiny part.
I ain't doing no press intro.
There's nothing to say.
♪ ...gentleness, her warmth, her everything~
♪ From now on...
They're filming.
Filiming? Oh, sorry.
Director Housei's next project! Look forward to it~!
[Next week!! Dance until you go viral!]