The Future Century
Squadron: The Five Rangai!
Speaking of which, I went to
the hospital. - How did it go?
It's nothing. just a little late.
- Good for you.
When I told to the manager,
he is like, "Yes!".
Made me mad. - That's what men are.
They have no idea.
Yes!
Evening.
I didn't think you are such a bad sailor.
You were throwing up all over.
You went on board?
Why did you go? - Why didn't you
tell me you are a bad sailor.
So you guys had a date?
- Shut up! Mind your own business.
What?
- It's for you.
How about a drive then?
- Sure. - I said I know!
Help. Heeelp!
Stop!
Red Rangai!
Blue Rangai!
Pink Rangai!
Yellow Rangai!
Green Rangai!
Our powers combined!
The Five Rangai!
Ladies, run now!
- Thank you.
Lead the way for then, Pink.
Bring it on!
Wait! You seen to be eager to fight.
You really think you can fight?
You must fight with us today.
- Come on!
You said you got a young
lively man last week.
I didn't say he's young.
But I think he's pretty lively.
He's nearly weeping.
How old are you, grandpa?
I'm 81.
Bring it on!
- Stop!
He's 81 for God's sake!
Where did you get him?
He's no problem. Really.
Here. Are you ok?
Let's fight.
Pink Rangai!
Watch out, Pink.
Wait. Look at him.
He doesn't have his heart in this.
Hey!
- This is not Pink Rangai!
He hasn't  recovered
from his brother death.
He said he wants to stay this way
...until the 1st anniversary.
But, he can't hold this. He have to fight.
- Don't you ever touch this.
Pink Rangai!
Cut it!
Don't jab him.
Let me duel him.
Let me see what he's got.
- No!
If he needs your protection...
- Pink Rangai!
Cut it!
Why are you protecting him?
Get out of my way!
You won't get away
without fighting this time.
I said, I will.
- No. Don't mark pink, please.
Fight with 5 of us. Not just with Pink.
- Let's face it. We can't do it with him.
Pink Rangai!
Hey, you went straight to him!
He pisses me off.
The way he say it.
Pink Rangai!
Why do you mark him?
- He's only saying his line.
He's not up to this job.
Think about it!
He's just a little girl.
- He's only an old guy!
He is, at his heart.
You made him gasp!
Pink Rangai!
He peeves me.
Let's us do the job. Only thing
you're doing is trying to attack pink.
Pink Rangai!
He touches my nerve!
He makes me mad!
I don't know why, but he does.
- That's a kind of play on our side.
The way he says it.
What are you doing?
Pink Rangai!
Please.
- No way.
I'm not gonna fight
with this old guy.
We realized we were just bunch of kids
and could use some grown man's help.
He's of no use. He'll only drag you.
Think about it one more time.
Tell me. You think you can do this?
- I'm the only one who can, you idiot!
Come again?
You don't know what you are saying.
- This is his ability, to provoke you.
Ok, well think about it.
- You, what do you think?
I think he's capable. Aren't you?
- Of course!
How can he do the actions?
I'm sure he can't move quickly.
- Yes, he can.
Ok, then let me see it.
Can you do this?
Show him, Pink.
Pink Rangai!
Hey, I get it.
You're making him say it.
Oops!
- You uncover it finally.
Your pat on the back is the cue.
Damn.
- Our secret is disclosed.
That explains his right timing.
You have to say that on air?
No way! I can't fight.
We have to start all over again.
Please give us a little time.
We'll talk about what
we should do about Pink.
You really need do that.
I understand.
What's that for?
What did you touch me for?
- I... will try harder...
I said what's that for!
Pink Rangai!
- Don't act like a puppet!
Thank you very much.
we'll come again next week.
Pink, run, run!
Sorry about that. - Thank you.
- You think it through, OK?
The Future Century Squadron: The Five Rangai!   To be con't.