http://zurui.blogspot.com
Translations: Zurui
Oonyudo-kun
Good morning
Here it is
Hurry, you're slow
I'm sorry
Here you go
Hamada-san, how old is your kid now?
3?
Imada-kun, you're not married right?
I am
Oh, you're married?
Yes
You are?
Any kids?
Eh, 2 kids?
4th and 2nd graders
Must be rough
Well... Yes, it is
I guess
Excuse me, but can I have this gum?
Why?
It's my older kid's birthday
Sorry about this
Well, it can't be helped, he only makes 1000 yen a day
I see
I can only afford food
Get a part-time job
Yes
Excuse me
What?
Actually I found a new partner to perform comedy
Again?
Well, this time it will be good
How could you find him so quickly?
I happened to meet him at a bar
Yes
OK
Well... he's here
If you are OK with it, I would like you to meet him
He's here?
Yes
Whatever
It's OK? Thank you!
Oonyudo-kun?
Oonyodo-kun!
Hi! Good morning! Master, Good morning!
Thank you for taking a good care of my
partner! Everyone Good morning!
Good morning! Good weather,
isn't it today? It's good, really..
He's my partner
Thank you! Thank you!
How old are you?
I'm 22
22?
Yes
Do you work?
I was an office worker, but I wanted to try and win a
successful gig... I really watch you everyday on TV
I really think you are great and it
is really great to see you, yes
Any siblings?
I have 2
2?
Yes
Which?
I have one younger sister. She is a big fan of yours, well
but I didn't tell her that I was meeting you today...
Yes
Seems he can talk
Ok, so show me your performance
Is it OK to show you?
Yes, everyone please watch
Thank you. It's short, but I wrote it so..
Really? Did you write it?
Yes
Is that OK? Thank you, let us start
Yeah
Hi I'm Shinji from Sakigake-sandaizu
I'm Koji
By the way, I really think we need to try harder. Now that its
the information age, we have to challenge a lot of things...
Yes, you're right
For me, even when I have nothing to do, I don't doodle
You don't doodle?
I usually use my PC
Do you? Cool
You need to know how to use PC. Do you?
Yes, you're right
Oh please! Of course I can use it!
Can you? Please show me what you can do
OK
Use the PC
No problem
Try it
First of all, press the key
Bring a PC! We don't have PC here!
What is that!
You are being too precise!
Bring a PC from there!
OK, I understand!
Chop chop
I'm bringing a PC... and putting it here
And type like this...
You didn't turn it on!
Power? Come!
PC won't work without the power on!
Alright, alright! Turn on the power and type..
Continue..
You didn't plug it in!
I don't care!
OK, I will!
Plug in, turn on, press keys and
you can see letters on screen!
Letters appear
What's wrong?
Let's continue
Hey, Master is watching...Press the keys! And...
...Press..the keys..
Press the keys
Press the keys!
Screen appears
Say something!
Oh no...
Oh... I'm sorry... I'm sorry!
That's enough already!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry
I forgot the script
What are you guys doing!
Didn't you practice?!
Yes
That's it!
You wrote that right?
He tried hard
It is old fashioned
Is that so?
What are you doing?
What's the matter?
He gets nervous on stage
Oh..
But I think he is talented
But the theme was old
Are you OK?
Hey hey hey, Imada!
What is going on?!
Hey! Hey!
Oonyudo-kun!
Oonyudo-kun! Oonyudo-kun!
Please somebody call an ambulance!
You take him!
I'm sorry..Somebody...I'm sorry! Oonyudo-kun!
Are you OK, Oonyudo-kun!