Subtitles: Zurui
Ma-kun
Where's your mom?
She's not home, she's at her part-time job
She's not home so let's have some fun...
Stop! Your mom might come home!
She wont!
Not today!
What do you mean not today?
I said no!
Do it just a little bit...
(I'm home!)
(Ma-kun?)
(Ma-kun!)
What?
Ma-kun are you home?
Ma-kun it's mom...
Oh!
What do you want?
Oh, who is this?
Good afternoon
Good afternoon!
May I ask your name?
I'm Nishihata-san
Nice to meet you!
You and Ma...Ma.. Ma-kun..
What's happening Ma-kun?
Don't call me Ma-kun!
What do you mean?
Is this your girlfriend?
It doesn't matter!
I didn't know, you should tell me these things
What? Why?
Nice to meet you
Never mind!
Shes cute... cute!
Go downstairs!
When your girlfriend is here you should fix your hair
STOP IT!
You look stupid..
Don't touch me!
I have to tell him
Go downstairs!
What are you saying...
I'm not feeling well
Go downstairs and sleep!
I came home because I need to go to the Hospital
Go!
Why are you yelling at me!
Go downstairs!
She's laughing at you!
Right?
What are you doing??
I'M BRINGING IN THE LAUNDRY!!
You're irritating me!
Sorry I can't welcome you better, Nishihata-san
It's fine
I didn't do anything
What?
No.. it's fine
Nishihata-san do you have any siblings?
No, I'm an only child
Oh is that so?
Being an only child is lonely, right Ma-kun?
Having siblings would be nice
Right?
Ah, yes
Having trouble studying?
Um...uh.. not really
I'll sit here
What are you doing?
What?
Go downstairs!
I'm folding the clothes
Do it downstairs!
Doing it here is fine
I want to talk with young people
with young people
Ma-kun... do you remember, my lower back...
was bothering me?
Really?
I had a CT scan, you know
There's a lot of different CT scans
Scary, so scary, my heart was beating wildly!
It's Ma-kun's...
Ma-kun!
What?
Are you changing your underwear?
Don't show it!
There's always poo stains...
Fold it nicely!
I'm gonna kill you!
There's always dried and hard poo in your
underwear, what are you doing??
It makes me feel bad!
I'm definitely gonna kill her!
Why are you going to kill me??
Definitely gonna kill her...
Hurry get downstairs!
I'm going downstairs..
always...really...
you young Yakuza!
You talk like a young Yakuza!
Always saying those things...
this kid always saying such things
Can you talk like that at school?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING??
Changing...
Why are you changing here? Idiot!
I want to change before I go to
the Hospital, it's embarrassing!
Do it downstairs!
What?
Do it downstairs, stop taking it off!
I know
You know, but you're still taking it off!
Here is fine, don't peek!
Nishihata-san, this looks like your size...
What are you doing? Stop it!
I'm really going to kill you!
What?
Understand?
I'll kill you!
Even if you look at me with
those eyes, I'm not afraid
I'm not scared!
Want to fight?
Your mother won't lose!
Always complaining about the smallest things...
I'm going downstairs!
Hurry up and go!
What are you going to eat?
What?
Food
I don't know, it doesn't matter!
Shall I make curry?
What? You really like curry, huh?
Why is today something special?
Oh, I'll make something different today
It doesn't matter just go downstairs!
What?
What's with you?
Hurry go!
I'm sorry Nishihata-san
Never mind!
It was scary but...
Don't start to sitting down again!
Go already!
You're eating this junk again?
You won't be able to eat your dinner if you eat this
Right?
Never mind!
IT'S NOT NEVER MIND RIGHT?!
WHAT'S WITH YOU? ALWAYS COMPLAINING!
JUST TELL ME YOUR GIRLFRIEND'S NAME!!
COMPLAINING! COMPLAINING!
I'm going to tell your dad!
Mother, get out already...
Why are you always so messy??
Don't touch it!
So messy!
Don't touch it, really!
Ouch! Ouch!
Why are you so rough, you
know my bones are weak!
My arm will break!
Hurry.. hurry get downstairs...so irritating!
What do you mean irritating..
Hurry, go! Hurry!
What?
Hurry go!
Your underwear...
What about it?
You better change it!
Ok, idiot!
Understand?!
YEA! IDIOT!
I'm sorry Nishihata-san, please come again
Thank you very much
Don't be shy
Barley tea... do you want some tea?
We don't drink tea..
Oh ok
Ok, bye Nishihata-san
She so bothersome..