Subtitles: eChie
Young colt
I got it
Icchan
What?
I gotta go home
It's still early
No, I have to chop some firewood
OK, then I'll go and help you
Are you sure?
Yea
- Then it's ok
Magic ball!
Icchan
What are you doing?
Sorry sorry
I think it's that way
What's wrong?
A horse?
Dead?
What's this?
Hey! What are you doing?!
What!?
Eh?
Who are you?
Well...
Come closer, I can't see
Come here!
Yes
Where are you from? I'm gonna kill you!
What are you doing?
Uh...just..
playing catch
It's dangerous, do it somewhere else
Uh..but
This is my backyard...
It doesn't matter who's yard it is
Can't you see that I'm sleeping?!
Sorry...
Stupid kids!
Sorry...I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry
Grrrr
Then lets leave
Wait wait wait!!
Where is your house?
Um... this is my house
Is it?
- Yes!
What about you?
I'm his friend...
and came here to play today
Where is your house?
From here...
about 15 mins away
15 mins?
- Yes
All right then!
I'm taking you home
Huh?
I'm saying I'll take you home
No, you don't have to
Are you alright?
What?
Uh... it's ok
Get on me
Hurry
Here
Hurry up and ride!
You're messed up
What do you mean messed up?
Just ride
You stink
Look!
Uh-oh
What's wrong?
You know..
- What?
You are rotten
I can see your ribs
Don't say that. I'm so scared
But it's true
I'm not rotten
Yes, you are
Really? But don't tell me that
I'm seriously scared
But I'm not lying
Because I was lying on that side
So I'll try lying on this side, and everything will be fine
Will it be?
Yes
Stuffy nose?
It will not be fine
- It will be
You look sticky
Stupid, this is my mother's love
Hey...Hurry up and ride!!
Don't make me shout, stupid
- I'm sorry
Ouch, ouch!
You stink at riding!
Oh my god
Hey!
Are you alright?
Yes?
Help me stand up
What?
I will run for you if you help me
Hurry
Well..
I'm telling you to hurry
Hurry
What should I do?
Icchan, but..
Oh..my mom is coming home soon
She will scold you
Well..
Can you help me dump it in the river?
Hey Hey Hey!
What are you trying to do?
Eh?
You know..if you are here, we will be scolded
By who?
Aunty
- My mom
She'll be home soon
So what?
Well..
Why don't we go to the river?
River?
- Yes
What will we do at the river?
Dump you
What?!
Wait!
NO NO NO
I don't want to go!
We will be scolded
Stop it! No river for me!
Mom will scold us