http://zurui.blogspot.com
Ok, lets go
Did you shut the window? Oh, it's shut
What?
What are you doing?
What are YOU doing?
I'm stuck
Oh, really?
Yes, I am
Are you ok?
I'm fine
Can you get out?
Of course I can, idiot!
If you can, then get out
I'm not feeling well
You feeling sick?
I was eating Okaiyu
Rice porridge?
Where we're you eating Okaiyu?
I ate it in the back
Don't lie! What are you doing?
I'm stuck in here!
Stuck?
You can get out by yourself, right?
Yes I can
If you can, then do it!
I can't do that
What are you saying, old man?
My legs are rotten
You ok?
Yeah
Are they really rotten?
- Yeah
Shall I call an ambulance?
I don't need an ambulance
If you can get out, then get out!
Shut up, I already told you, stupid!
Who you calling stupid?
I'm going to beat you up, old man!
Hurry and get out!
I said I'm stuck!
Kurimoto-san!
- Yeah
Kurimoto-san?
- Yes, yes?
Yes?
Kurimoto-san!
Excuse me!
There's this strange old man here
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm stuck!
You have to get out!
Don't touch me, my legs are rotten
He's stuck?
You should get out, old man
I want to, idiot
You're being a nuisance, right?
My kid is taking his exam soon
My kid is in an entrance exam war!
So, why are you here?
I'm praying!
Why do that here? Go to a shrine!
Of course, I want to go to a shrine!
If you get out, I'll show you where the shrine is!
I told you I'm stuck and can't come out!
Maybe we should call the police
- Can you go and get the police?
Yes!
What?
We called the police just now
Police?
- Yeah, the police
Ok, that's fine
If you can get out, get out now!
I can't get out
Oh, thank you for coming
Can't you get out by yourself?
I can
Then why don't you come out?
Because my legs are rotten
Well, if your legs are rotten, I can take you to the hospital
I can't get out, but I want to get out
Hey old man, if you are stuck there, you can't do anything
Ok, how's this?
What?
We'll give you some money
Money? I want money!
Ok, we'll give you money
I'll take as much as you give me!
Right?
If you get out, I'll give it to you
Really? How much?
100 yen
100 yen?
- Yeah
100 yen huh?
That much?
Yes 100 yen
- 100 yen, how many times?
One
100 yen, I guess that's pretty good, huh
Give me 300
Ok, if you get out, I'll give you 300
You can give me that much?
300...
How much?
I'll give you, 100 yen x 3
300?
- Ok
Ok get out
He had a knife!
You were swinging your knife around
Yeah
Why are you carrying a knife like that?
I felt I was in danger
We're the ones feeling danger
That's not good
- Why?
Old man
- Yeah
Old man you must be hungry, right?
Yeah, I'm starving
I have some Castella in my apartment
Wow, Castella
Let's go eat
- I love Castella
If you get out, I'll give you lots of Castella
Hey!
Old man!
You shouldn't swing your knife
Throw down your knife
Why?
Old man
- Yeah
You were thinking to rob one of these houses, right?
Then you hid in there, and couldn't get out, right?
I was thinking to rob a house and got stuck in here, yes!
That's premeditated
Ok? That's a crime
Crime?
I will arrest you
My kids will cry
Yes, they will
My kids will cry...
- Yes
I'll also cry
I'll cry too
Why you smiling like that?
Take this seriously
- Yeah
Like right now, think, I will always try my best...
not to get into prison
You won't try to take me to prison
- I wont
You can trust me
- Really?
Anyway, throw down the knife
- Throuw down the knife
Come out, quietly
- Come out quietly
You can't do anything if you stay in there right?
Yeah
Ok, just come out, ok?
Get a job
I'll get a job
That's right
You must work
I should work
- Yes you should work
Ok?
- You speak well
What?
Are you a professional speaker?
I'm a policeman
Ok? I'm just a regular person
Ok? I'm telling you the truth
Ok, throw down the knife and come out
Will you arrest me if I do it?
No, I just want to question you, then you can go
Really?
- Really, I wouldn't lie
Old man
- What?
Did you understand what I said?
I did
- Then get out from there
So you want me to come out, right?
Yes, if you come out, everything will be fine
You're sure right?
- Yes, yes
Throw down the knife!
Ouch ouch ouch ouch!
Hey hey hey hey!
Get out already
How can we finish this?
It's up to you
Ok... I'm coming out
Come out with a good attitude
Well, I don't have my knife
I guess I can't make them laugh either
Higashino
- Yeah
Wanna do this again next week?