Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Thank you
It's good to get paid for this
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Welcome Shoji Tomoharu
-Mikitty-!
Was that a deliberate lowering of the volume just now?
I'm trying my best!
Didn't you do a silent version last time?
A "sprayless" Mikitty, indeed
Now is not much better than then
-Nothing has changed
So why today...
Because no one laughed last time
Okay, so...
Changing the subject
It's not too late
-Yes
I bring this theory today
The Second "While lecturing someone, it's ok to add Nagabuchi's lyrics"
The last episode was a big hit...
We just did the first one
-Yes
If you saw it already then it'd ruin it
That's why both were recorded before the first broadcast
I challenged the song "Captain of the Ship"
It was a good attempt
-Yes
"Captain of the Ship" is unusual
It's very dense
And the second half is like a speech
Do you have any thoughts about the songs of Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi?
I only know the song "Cheers"
Haven't you heard of "HOLD YOUR LAST CHANCE"?
Never heard of it at all
Haven't you ever heard of "Life of an Asshole"?
Is there really such a song?
Don't you know that "Dad Who Became a Crane"?
What's that?
Don't know it?
The dad turns into a crane!
You're making fun of people, right?
No no no, I swear
It's feels a bit like that.
-Right?
No, it's not
So, later is the second leg of the "lecturing with Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi lyric's"
You're "really not nice"!
And
Does the child look-alike still look like the celebrity?
And the Wife Battle:
Who can make their husband laugh with supposed sleep talking?
Favourite
2nd "While lecturing someone, it's ok to add Nagabuchi's lyrics:
The first challenger is
Thanks for having me
Viking's Kotoge
This time, the title is also chosen from these songs that are suitable for lecturing
Kotoge's choice is
Three songs have already been chosen
Nagabuchi's "It's Not Like That"
Will this one work?
It's a bit difficult
Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi's famous song "It's not like that" includes the lyrics "pipipi"
It feels like something I would say
And i've been known to spit out some golden nuggets of wisdom from time to time
This time, the lyrics are also divided into 10 stages according to the ease of use
"pipipi" is not possible, right?
The time limit is 30 minutes
If the content is pointed out as lyrics by the junior in the process of lecturing
They will be immediately disqualified
A sentence with fewer words will score relatively less
The target is a junior from the same company
Darlings Oda
He lured Oda out with a fake plan of "having a talk with a senior who is close to him"
The rest period before the supposed recording is used for the "It's not nice" lecture challenge
What will be the result?
But ah
No its not like that
No, no, no, no, no, I mean you
You said it
No more "i'll come"?
They are referring to participation in Viking's live performance
In which he failed to say hello to Kotoge
This incident is used as an entry point to start the lecture
This may be a little bit of that
Generally speaking, at least let us know
I'm very sorry about it
-Because I...
Until now I also don't know what to say
I also thought about saying something about it to you, but I didn't think it was appropriate
I wanted to tell you in person, but I'm sorry
You shouldn't have done that
I'm sorry, yes
Really
The "heart is torn" and the "heart is chastised"
It can be said like this
Can't you hear?
That feeling
Yes
What...what do you say, no reply?
Reflecting
How long has the show been over? It's been 2 weeks
"A night of remorse, sadness, and misery"
That's not good, right?
A little dangerous...
I was shocked
But completely...
Yes...
Indeed
Unexpectedly, there are very serious complaints
And Kotoge brings in Nagabuchi's lyrics with a good rhythm
You've also entered King of Conte, right?
A tiebreaker.
-2 times?
Yes
It's like that
"It's something that's hard to catch when you're drowning in stumbles."
Very good.
-Very clever
You're not happy about it, are you?
-Yes
Next
Coming here today
"Say this, say this," or something like that
Do you have an idea in mind?
Ah, I do
For example, what do you want to talk about today
You've remained unchanged from before to now
Have been drinking green juice or something?
Well well well well...
I would like to talk about foreign travel if I can
What's happening abroad
When traveling to Thailand
When we went to the bar together
Gradually we became very close to the female customers in the store
With the local girls
But you were unexpectedly unpopular
And you kept saying, "Oda, open up Yahoo!"
"Let these girls know what an awesome celebrity I am"
I wanted them to see it, but there was no Wi-Fi in the store
I wanna talk about that fatal blow to you or something
What the hell?
Let me tell you, this thing in Thailand or whatever, it's not good, OK?
Yes, so...
"It's not like that." Seriously
Nah, that can't be told, right?
Although you "pipipipipi pipipipi" keep on talking
There it is!
You can't talk about that, OK?
Something's not right
Right?
Yes... I'm very sorry
He's laughing
No. If it's funny, forget it
Found out?
From "not like that" to "pipipi"
Oda can't help but laugh
As I said earlier, because of this occasion
We have to be good... we have to be sure of everything
Is Kotoge doing too much?
100%, be 100% sure before you say
Yes, I came here with this realization
Keeping up the didactic atmosphere, the challenge continues into the final stretch
Thrilling
Next
It is not "pushed from behind by something invisible"
Not a good idea
Normally you wouldn't say such things
Your "love always looks like a big lie"
Speak up!
I've really "become comfortable with being alone without realizing it"
Keeps stacking
Practically singing already
Without mentioning anything, 30 minutes pass
Close call
So, the truth is revealed
Passed?
-Yes
It's a theory.
-A theory, is it?
"While lecturing someone, it's ok to add Nagabuchi's lyrics"
Correct answer
-Whoa! Is that an awesome guess?
After Kotoge said "pipipi"
I was going to say something, but instead he moved on to the next lecture like he was running for his life
Sort of realised, then
The next challenger is
Thank you for having me
Jungle Pocket's Saito
I think a more direct song would be better
"The Only Flower in the World"
The best-selling SMAP song "The Only Flower in the World" is used to lecture SPIKE's Matsuura
What will be the result?
Well, how can I say this
The M-1 or The W is basically the same
Everyone has a strong feeling of "wanting to be at the top"
Similar contests are all like this
But its not really appropriate to compare your work to that of another comedian
"Even so, we humans always want to compare ourselves to each other." Absolutely
Very smooth
Very smoothly slipped in
Such a long line
People have different ways of doing things
Of course, there are all different types
But really, although there are many different types
This girl is quite strong
-Really willing to engage
Not convinced.
-Yes
Because the personal characteristics differ
Yeah, that's right.
-Yeah
Like different flowers
"You just have to work hard to make that flower bloom."
A little dangerous
It feels like it will be exposed
Totally lyrics!
Bring out your own personality
That's true
Connecting to SPIKE's current status
Familiar lyrics cleverly do not register
When female funny entertainers are funny
I think it's really awesome
I think "every one of them is beautiful"
When you say "beautiful", do you mean in a funny way or something?
No, no, no, no, no
So what? Generally speaking
So scary!
Won't you be criticized for your ugly appearance or something?
But yet, in the midst of this
Solidly winning the audience's laughter by being a funny female artist
I am not commenting on the beauty of the appearance
But I think everyone is very attractive and looks very beautiful
Ah - so that's it!
No feeling of being lectured at all...
No sense of admiration whatsoever
I've been walking on the road of being funny
The happiest part
Is seeing audience members waiting outside after live performances
Just for us alone
"Though we don't know the name of the person, he showed his smile to us on that day"
And has been our fan ever since
That made me feel very happy
The final task...
Is dropping a super-famous lyric
Anyway, it's not like you have to become the top, right?
You don't have to be No.1, right?
There's no such thing as becoming No. 1
After all, there are so many monsters around
"You don't have to be No.1" to do it
Just do it with the feeling of "Only one is special"
This is not a problem, right?
But I am now striving for "only one"
No problem?
-No problem at all
SAFE
I am now running my own Youtube channel
Even after uploading videos, the number of plays is only about 23
This is pretty close to "only one" as you said
It's not at all like being lectured
With only 5 minutes remaining
Saito makes his last attempts
So there is such a thing
"We all saw all kinds of flowers in front of the flower store."
This does not work, right?
This is the lyrics at the beginning
What're you talking about flowers?
What do you mean, flower store?
Hey, flower store...
Isn't that the lyrics?
Lyrics to "The Only Flower in the World"?
What?
Haven't you been filling me with the lyrics to "The Only Flower in the World"?
Saito Disqualified
So we reveal the truth
It was super natural. In retrospect
Very relevant to the topic
"In front of the flower store" is destined to be noticed, right?
I felt like a fool when saying it
Next is the final challenger
Panther's Ogata
I choose "Poem Without a Name" by Mr. Children
The first time "Poem Without a Name" by Mr. Children
Will be used to lecture Ogata's junior
Isn't that hard?
-It's hard
Why did you choose him out of so many people?
We all know
First of all, his intuition is not great and then there is...
He's a very honest and nice guy
He should take everything I say at face value
Your instincts aren't any better
Let me tell you
I think you've been a little uninspired lately
Oh, really?
I am quite worried
That's not the case!
To have spirit... is the most important thing
No, Ogata, I'm super energetic
He's saying he has spirit
I'm just saying what I see.
-Oh, is that so?
He said he has
-What kind of lecture is this?
I hate people with no spirit.
-I'm sorry
When you are in front of people, it is absolutely necessary to have spirit
I'm super lively, okay?
-No, you're not
It's obvious
-This is just what I think
I'm most upset by people who have no spirit
Let's just say I'm in good spirits.
-That's enough
I've had enough of this.
-I'm really energetic
Not really, at least in my opinion
I can't be fooled
On the subject of "having spirit"
These two idiots have a discussion about a fake subject
Are you not quiet when you're alone?
But very lively with everyone
-Very lively
Because I treat everyone as my own people
"Even if you are a good friend, the night of loneliness will still come."
I'm glad he added it in
Ah, there is a bit of a mistake
Sounds extreme, what lonely night?
I've had some, quite a long time ago, for example
We performed in the same theater
Didn't we have noodle soup?
-Yeah
I saw you had some vegetables left
I really hate people who don't finish their food
The two are inextricably linked.
-I understand
No one around will have the leftovers
Some people can't even get enough to eat
You can say it to me
-Say what?
"If it's just a little dirty, I'll help you eat it all up."
All of that just lead up to this
But it'd be weird to give it to you
It's okay. I just want to eat
Thanks to the thick skin of his junior
Ogata somehow manages to say the most difficult lyrics
You really are a bit gloomy
I'm not, Ogata, I'm super lively, okay?
I'm honestly lively, Ogata
How to put it
I'm feeling "despair and disappointment"
Huh?
What are you "sulking about"?
The other side is saying "huh?" now
Sulking can not be helped, right?
I've been working hard even if you don't think so.
-What are you sulking about?
I'm not sulking, I'm trying very hard, what can I do?
Wait, what?
What's with "despair" and "disappointment"?
I can't believe what i'm seeing, this guy is not right, really
From now on, work hard for me
I'm doing it already!
You have to work even harder after making it
Whether it is "Love, Freedom, Hope, Dream"
What, ah what?
"It will all roll under your feet"
Look, it's all under your feet!
Too dumb, didn't realise at all
Huh? What love and freedom?
Hope and love
-What the hell!?
You've become a philosopher
-Listen carefully
"Love is not something that is fought for or given, but something that is around when you look back."
Such a long speech, why the hell are you talking about love?
Very bad attitude
Toward his senior
It's okay to talk about love, right?
So it also depends on who is doing the lecturing
But it's a good thing he was able to get in
"Falling in love naturally"
"even if it may sometimes hurt others"
"It is no longer the time to be sad about it."
What the hell is this bullshit?
It's normal to say!
That's a song!
It's about time to realize now
You're so noisy, stop talking about this time and that freedom
The responses are nothing like what you'd expect from a junior
Despite becoming extremely heated
He still fails to realize everything he is being told is a lyric
He can't realize because he's getting too angry
He's sick of being told off
When 5 minutes are left
You
Wow, enough, it's enough, surely?
Look at you
"The weakness of not being able to continue to live with a free mind"
It seems to me like "blame it on whose fault it is and live"
Very afraid tone
This is the part of the chorus
Something is wrong, something is wrong, something is really wrong
That's enough. You must think I'm short of brain capacity
"I have insufficient brain capacity"
Don't joke with me, I went to university, OK?
What about insufficient brain capacity!?
I went to university!
I know!
But insufficient brain capacity
Now he's doing it!
You
So weird
-You are my...
No more "you", it's really weird, every sentence is super weird
"If you doubt me, come and slit my throat."
Mr. Children!
Mr.Children!
Ogata Disqualified
"Cut your throat" is the lyrics of Mr. Children
The truth is revealed
What?
Mr. Children!
It was Mr. Children
Indeed, Mr.Children
I was really angry, I thought "this guy is super annoying"
"This guy" is not quite right, is it?
The results are shown in the figure
Although Ogata got a lot of points, the 1st place is Kotoge as only he was not disqualified
There you have it
-That's the results
Only Kotoge wasn't disqualified
Comedians are not very strict when it comes to the senior-junior relationship
The lyrics weren't the point anymore, more the interaction that made it interesting
It just confirmed how despised Ogata is
So it still depends on who's lecturing
I think there is still room for development on this
How about "Yesterday" or something like that?
No way!
It's too strange to start speaking English all of a sudden
Let's welcome the next presenter
It's Kanazuki
Thank you for having me
First time on the show?
Second time
So it's the second time?
First time was having professional impersonators impersonate teachers
Ah that one was very touching
That won a Galaxy Award
Award-winning
-Indeed!
Then they were immediately warned by the broadcasting ethics agency, right?
Erratic programming
On behalf of all impersonators, I would like to apologize to everyone
What?
Without further delay, the theory I bring today is this
Does the child look-alike still look like the celebrity?
I want to see it
First of all, he appeared in the parody segment of "It's okay to laugh", "Parody of Red and White" and other shows
On the show many times
Really?
Often on TV
A child who looks like Toshiaki Karasawa
6 years old?
After 15 years
Does he look more like the celebrity as a grown-up?
See him now at age 21
Not similar at all
Indeed
No similarities still exist
Completely went in a different direction
Since when did you stop being told you look alike?
After junior high school I began to become a bit of a gangster
Turned into a punk
There was a time when even my eyebrows were shaved
Ooohhh so excessive
And my hair was permed into short curly hair
Looks bad
His appearance completely diverged from Toshiaki Karasawa
Of course, no one said I looked like him anymore
Although Nakazawa was once similar
He has undergone a complete transformation and now works in a decoration company
Next is...
Two children who looked like Nishikido Ryo
Ren and Rei Morita, 4 years old at the time
So cute
-Very similar
Both of them are similar
They appeared in many shows as the "Nishikido Ryo Twins"
Really similar
13 years later they've become these high school students
17 years old
Although not dissimilar, they're also not especially similar
But the temperament is similar
-Well, the temperament does remain
Do people still say you guys look like Nishikido Ryo?
No one says that at all anymore
Thought so
Did you think that you would continue to be in show business?
Although I didn't really think much about it
Inside
I was happy to be on TV
Doesn't seem happy at all
I just want to live a normal life
For some reason, the mood of the two men is worryingly low
Thankfully they agreed to the interview
Next is
Mikupi, who looks like Naomi Watanabe, was 16 years old
New member Mikupi! Nice to meet you!
Thank you everyone
Though it was me for a second
Joining an agency, she participated in various shows
Let's see her 5 years later at the age of 21
Eh? Lost weight?
Totally different
Not alike at all
Losing half of her weight, she became a different person
Weight loss
What kind of work do you do now?
Artistic activities have come to a halt
Now i'm a conservationist
After Naomi, who has changed a lot, the fourth one is...
A child who looks like Aina Ashida, who is only one year different
So cute
Although the celebrities and impersonators, so far, have not been similar
Will it be the most similar?
Will these two still be alike having both gone through the process of growing up at the same time?
Highest probability
What is the result?
Although the traces of Aina Ashida are vaguely recognizable, it is no longer possible to say that she looks similar
There is a hint of the look that remains
Do people still say you look like Aina Ashida?
-Not anymore
If I had to say, it's more like Aina Ashida and Meiko Nagano combined and divided by two
Because the elements of both sides are not that strong
So, the further one grows it seems the less similar they become
The child who looked like Oguri Shun also
Is
Also not similar anymore
The child who looked like Yuzuru Hanyu previously also
Has changed completely
But he's grown into an interesting look
In the midst of this, in 2004, he appeared in the parody segment of "It's okay to smile"
The Tiger Woods kid
I'm not sure about this one
His name which is also Tiger, aged 8
Do you also have this?
After 17 years, here's what he looks like now
Hello. Nice to meet you
Not the same at all
If the kid doesn't look like them to begin with, its even less likely for them to look alike when they're older
Since junior high school, because the singer JERO was often on TV
At that time, they said, "Jero, Jero, Jero"
When I was in high school, the singer Chris Hart was always on TV
Then in college it was Anthony
Basically just any well known black sports players or stars who were on TV in different eras
I would be told I looked like them
So far the theory is practically dead
So, with such expectations in mind
Let's look at Tanaka, also known as Ma-kun, who has a younger lookalike
With the experience of having won out of 3,300 people in a 27-hour program broadcast in 2016
Does this child buck the trend?
Hmmm
Ah, very similar
This one is awesome!
Exactly the same
Katsuki Masuda at 11 years old
Very similar
Not bad for a kid who won 1 million yen
So alike
With such a similar look and feel
What does he look like now, five years later?
Come on, look a little bit like ma-kun
He's grown into a perfect likeness
Do you play baseball?
Not at all
What club are you in now?
The science department
Make some slime, send rockets into the sky, that sorta stuff
This is a big event for his department
Making slime and flying planes
Since this is a rare find, we take it a bit further
Not that similar? After putting on the hat
In summary
The result depends on the original similarity
I gues so
It's hard to get people to perform
When they all come out, everyone just replies, "Uh-huh."
I feel sorry for them now that they've grown up
It feels like only 15% of the image is left
I still think the Nishikido Ryo twins have retained the same vibe
They're today's best
Awesome
-Great, right? They're good fun
It's a good thing they are willing to be on the show
Still willing
Well, maybe Nishikido Ryo is also like this nowadays
There's no way!
Let's welcome the next presenter
Who is it?
It's Kawashima!
Hello everyone
Thank you for having me
I'd like to ask a question
Do any of you talk in your sleep?
Has your wife ever told you "you talk in your sleep"?
Do you, Hamada?
No, but I grind my teeth
He grinds his teeth very badly
I think he has talked in his sleep before
When we used to go out for performances and sleep in the same room together
"Mattsun, eat quickly"
Dreaming of being good friends
-A great relationship
Dreaming of his student days
-Yeah
Hamada had already finished eating, right?
Who knows?
Do you, Toyosaki?
I don't know if I do
But my husband and kids often do
What do they say?
Yesterday it was "That's the wall over there"
Your husband said it?
-Yes
I have no idea what kind of dream he was having
The dreamer can't explain it either
Maybe he's playing an escape room...
In relation to this, today I bring you a theory about sleep talking
Who can make their husband laugh with supposed sleep talking?
Can it be done?
Honestly, when sleeping people suddenly talk, everything they say is pretty interesting, right?
Yes, sleep talking itself is very interesting
If they realise, then the round finishes
That's for sure.
-That's when it ends
So if you want to score highly the words you say will have to be dissonant
Otherwise they'd realize its fake
-Indeed
You also have to make it funny
-Make them laugh
And pay attention to naturalness and all aspects of rhythm
A sense test!
Who can make their husband laugh with supposed sleep talking?
This time, these three wives are participating
I'd like more tolerance
What does more tolerant mean?
With this couple that frequently appeared in the past
Why is he naked
First of all, each determines a natural setting to encourage sleep
Maruyama's location involves an overnight stay
Sleep nice and heavy
Paradise' Nakagawa's and Kazuyo's setup is
Let's go take a bath, Dad
Want a drink? Yeah, sure
One falls asleep after drinking
Harukara Izumi and Wednesdays Hikari are in their living rooms waiting for their husbands to finish work
Pretending they fell asleep while waiting
I'm back
At this point
So hot, so hot
What's he doing!?
Wednesdays Mitsuhashi gets naked as soon as he arrives home
Is there such a person?
This guy really takes it all off as soon as he arrives
That seems to be the case
It can't be helped
The husband naked in his house as before is already in place
He can't live without this
So annoying!
The 30 minute period begins
Unbearable
The "amuse the husband with sleep taking" tournament begins
Don't want to go near that couch
Direct contact with the sofa is disgusting
First is the Kikuta family
He's a comedian
Harukara Izumi's first attempt is...
My husband is incredibly fond of Tsuda
He likes him so much he always uses his jokes at home
So he should laugh if he hears me saying the jokes in my dream
su-
su
Sleep talking begins
su su su
su
I offer a su to you
Smiling obviously
Not wanting to wake up his wife, Kikuta laughs quietly
And
Saying something meaningless should make him laugh out loud
On the elbow
Sitting up and listening now
Please tattoo the dog on the elbow
Faced with this interesting event, Kikuta couldn't help but take a video
What should I do with the tattoo of the dog, Okabe?
Laughed
Nice phrase
Okabe says put the text on the forehead
You can hear it very clearly!
And Maruyama...
So sleepy
Let me sleep
Sleep talking
Not only did he not laugh, Ben didn't respond to the sleep talking at all
Ignored
But there's a reason
I usually talk in my sleep
So saying usual sleep talking stuff wont make him laugh
I'm going to be radical
And exaggerate
Wouldn't be surprised
So
Lets introduce the participants
Talking normally
No way
No reaction at all
First, Alcinder
On the left is Bismarck
Kitazawa and
Center back is Emberma
The goalie is Oliver Kay
Listening carefully now
Disappointing
What do you mean? I don't understand
Can't laugh!
And Paradise's wife
I...
What?
Ah, shooting a video
I...
I am Shinnosuke
What are you talking about?
So boring
Laughing super happily
And
Hello, give me a grilled salmon
It's sold out
Conversation begins
Then regular salmon is fine
We're talking to each other
What?
Finally, Wednesday Izumi's attempt
A dream of being wooed
To make sure he listens carefully
It'll be regarding Toshida
Although his senior
He has a really good relationship with him
Don't do that...
I've just gotten married
Always naked...
What, what?
I'm coming to save you
Coming to your rescue!
Don't do that, Toshida
The butt is really there
Why Toshida?
This angle
Why?
Looks like a dugong
Why
I can't believe it's Toshida...
At this time 15 minutes has passed from the total 30
The current scores are as shown
As much as Maruyama would like to score...
Does Alcinder eat chow mein with sauce?
Don't you want to pour on the sauce?
What?
Don't do this. Don't brand me
Never brand people on the forehead
So radical!
The soccer team can not be branded on the forehead
At least do it on the arm
It's the same
I said you can't do it on the forehead
Impossible
So noisy
On the other hand, the Kikuta family, now in second place, is...
No laughing
Welcome~
Thank you for visiting so frequently
S...S isn't available
M isn't available
Very good performance
Is that OK?
Well said
Barely noticeable
Gold Member~
Please come this way~
And so, Izumi accumulates points smoothly
Not exposed at all
Even trying this too
Locust pose
Too much, right?
This definitely won't work!
The yoga pose proves a step too far
Yeah
As such, she is forcibly awakened by a worried Kikuta
So Harukara and Izumi have a final score of 100
Kawashima, what about you?
On public transport once I shouted "stop" when I was particularly tired and drunk
The office worker put down his egg sandwich in an instant
I really made a noise
After some time, the Paradise family's husband moves into another room
Yes, this could happen
Ah, gone
And so
By doing the Woman Rush Hour bit
He should laugh by hearing his own skit
Coke Coke Draft Beer Oolong Tea
Wait, don't order so many at once
I don't know what to do, ah
It's fine
This voice...could it be
Can using manzai succeed in making them laugh?
Coke Coke Root Beer Oolong Tea to Wine Coke
Ah, I don't understand, I don't understand
It's fine
Although not laughing, she successfully summoned the performer
The entrance is disgusting enough
Successfully summoned though
But...
This voice...could it be
Eh...
It's over, right?
The voice is the captain of the workforce
A disgusting way to get someone to tell the truth
No, no
Really disgusting
What is he doing?
Surely exposed
Help
We're seeing something bad
Looking for bare skin
As we can no longer allow Kazuyo to experience this
Her round ends with a score 90 of points
So scary
Next: Maruyama, who has not yet scored anything
Sleepwalking?
Jiang shi?
What are you doing?
Is that dreaming?
Really
Jiang shi?
Yeah, jiang shi
You're definitely awake
Exposed
No matter what, it can't be like this
The exposure ends with failure
Final score 10 points
Blocked
Creepy
He said creepy
On the other side is Wednesdays...
Not even for dinner
Don't play this shot
Now, the approach changes from cheating to a lover's quarrel
Like Yu
What's up with this guy?
Like?
Super like
-Me too
It seems to be working but...
Enough
Impossible
What are you doing?
What's starting?
It's starting. It's starting
What are you doing?
Mitsuhashi Bad Switch: ON
Thankfully the specified time has ended
And so, the truth is revealed
What are you doing?
-That was close
I saw on the Internet that people who talk in their sleep do it because they're under a lot of pressure
So you must've accumulated a lot of stress
No, no, there's nothing wrong with kissing your wife's back
What are you doing?
It's mutual
At home she's always sleep talking
This was a light one
Sometimes she chants mantras
What kind?
-Arabic or something
Something I can't understand
-No way
I'm not sure
And so, the winner is Kikuta's wife Hanako
I see
So there's the result
Maruyama's jiang shi routine was little too much...
She just had 0 at the point so she had to take a big risk
What Maruyama said was also radical
But her usual self is actually more radical
Thats true
Her husband barely reacted at all, right?
Impressive
What do you think, Toyosaki?
The couple's relationship is very clear from the videos
I saw too much
-Agreed
Wednesdays are really ready to go
He must be stopped
Imagine if the camera crew came in just a bit later
A shocking video would be captured
Tell him to observe silently in the future
It made it more interesting though
-True, more interesting
The guy was really naked all the time.
-Really was
It's not that disgusting of an ass though
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03