Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Savannah's Takahashi
Today I bring a theory about IKKO
When it comes to IKKO
She has phrases like "what the hell?" (don da ke) and "like a dream!"
So this time we bring a theory about IKKO's catchphrases
IKKO catchphrase contest
This involves getting IKKO to use her catchphrases without her noticing
A contest on naturally leading her to say certain phrases
Like setting up IKKO, right
-Yes
So for instance, what would you do to get her to say "what the hell?"
Honestly, I'm always on location
IKKO will say "what the hell" even if I just turn to her like 'uh-uh-uh'
Is it that simple?
-Amazing
If I go "uh-uh-uh"...
-That's too easy.
That does not need any preparation
You don't have to say anything at all, you just have to go, "Uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh..."
This'll definitely get a "what the hell?"
So, three groups of comedians will attempt to get IKKO to say certain words
Who can make the most amount of noise without being called noisy
The Daily Life Loudness Competition
Also, is it possible to teach a woman a figure four leg lock hold over the phone?
IKKO Catchphrase Contest
This time, these three groups are participating
And are invited to a fake shopping show with IKKO
First, they draw lots to determine the IKKO catchphrase for each group
Shoulder drop~
What the hell?
Like a dream~
I am a beginner
"Shoulder drop~" is so hard
If you create a certain situation, it should be doable
"Shoulder drop~" would only occur when something rude has been said
Its the same as something like "I'll beat you up"
Then, IKKO, who knows nothing about it, enters the scene
And so, the contest begins
Let's give IKKO a warm welcome!
Hospitality~
Really beautiful!
No, no, no, no. Really? You guys!
Very moist and shiny
What are you laughing at?
-You're laughing too much
Your eyeballs are so prominent
Looking from the side
※Medaka: a fish with huge eyes high on its head
Medaka fish～
Medaka fish?
-Medaka fish
Never heard of medaka fish?
This is your first time meeting us, right?
Do you know us? Do you know us?
Ah, you are Morita
Hey, what about me?
Suddenly sounds obscene
Let me take a look in your pockets
Like a dream~
Fujimoto accidentally invokes Goodbye Light of Youth's phrase and starts the game with a mistake
Let's go~
Here we go, here we go
Eh…？
We're here at Odaiba shopping street
The first store is the Shooting Gallery, commonly known as the airsoft store
Please
So happy~
This is a store where you can experience the airsoft stores of the Showa 30s
You were born in Showa 30, right?
-I was born
※Showa 30：1955
Were you born around Showa 12?
-No
※Showa 12: 1937
Showa 20 years?
-No
※Showa 20 years: 1945
Taisho 5 years?
-I said no~
※Taisho 5 years: 1916
Jomon...?
※Jomon period: 16,000 years ago to 2300 years ago, Named after the rope pattern printed on the excavated pottery
Jomon era?
Who?
-IKKO
It's not that long ago. It's not that long ago, is it?
Like a dream~
As Morita takes over Fujimoto's joke, he grabs a "Like a dream~"
I hit the...
What are you up to?
What the hell~
IKKO, this is not your level!
You knocked down something you shouldn't
You can't do this, seriously!
Really, if you do it again, you'll...
What's the matter with this guy?
You'll get it next time!
He'll get it?
You do it again and i'll really take you out
Hand that over now! Hand it over!
Konsang Amida~
※"Kongsang Amida" Japanese pronunciation of Korean for "thank you"
What're you talking about?
What the heck!?
How can you let her say "Kongsang Amida"? It's too rude to IKKO!
Why is there a "Konsang Amida"?
Sorry. Excuse me
Look, Ikko, you should try and stretch forward as much as possible
What the hell~
Well done, IKKO
Fujimoto unwittingly gives points to another team again
Watch me
Shoulder Drop~
It appeared!
What the hell~
Kongsang Amida~
Why? Why?
Hey, what's with the "Konsang Amida~" again?
Don't bring out the "Konsang Amida" Oi! So rude!
Hey, what's up?
I thought this was a target. Sorry
You're too dangerous, right?
Shoulder Drop~
What are you doing here?
I'm trying to do this again!
Shoulder Drop~
Eh?
A fully automatic over-the-shoulder machine
At the end of the first stage, the scores obtained by each team are as follows
FUJIWARA is one step ahead
Here outside of the first half, IKKO is isolated
At the other end
This is simply a game of "You tell me, I guess"
If you queue her up, she'll say it
I set them up well
It's not a long game
By the way, what the hell is that "Konsang Amida"?
How should I respond to that statement?
I don't really get how that started
A mini-review session
The next stage is a snack store
And the phrases are changed
Penniless~
Theft~
Super cheap~
Why is this in red?
The red words are IKKO's usual phrases
Yeah it is
You didn't hear her say it?
Not even once!
Next is this store
So happy~
So retro~
I like snack stores the most
These are just 100 yen!
This 100 is so casually stated!
Can it be bought?
Can I buy it?
-Yes, you can.
Buy buy buy
How much is 100g?
400 yen
It's a bargain!
This is only 200 yen!
200 yen, from 450 to 200 yen
It's a bargain!
Instead of the selected phrase, Ikko surprisingly uses "It's a bargain" instead
So Morita attemps to change the situation
IKKO, this is only 5 yen, you can buy loads!
But
Hey, is it really 5 yen?
Oh its not
They said its not. No
Fujimoto immediately blocks his play
Let Haranishi pay for it
This is for IKKO-san, get the money ready
100 yen
I don't have 100
Not even 100? So stingy~
Ah... what the hell~
So stingy, wont even give 100 yen, stingy, right?
Stingy~
Seriously stingy!
You only have 20 yen?
I just brought 20
Stingy!
Reality~
Although they try to elicit a "penniless~" by saying stingy, it doesn't work
You have a lot of money in your pocket
It can't be helped
Next, Diane attempt to setup a play
This way
IKKO, this seems to be 20 yen
IKKO you are leaving the store!
You people are so annoying~
Wait a minute
You're just going to walk away, are you?
No, wait a minute
You're just going to leave?
Go back. Go back
We're going back~
But this play is also prevented by Fujimoto
Konsang Amida~
This sentence has been said so many times
What does that mean exactly?
What are you saying?
What are you doing?
What are you thinking?
This is no good, this is stealing!
Yeah
I'll pay for it. Give it to me
Fujimoto used an iron wall defense
Haranishi, Haranishi, come and pay
He really is Hara-stingy
I just don't have the money!
Really Hara-stingy
Penniless~
Said it!
Finally a "Penniless~" is obtained
IKKO bring that here
Over here!
No~
This end, this end, this end...
Here, over here
This, this and this, i've bought~
At the end of this second stage
The scores for each team are as follows
Adult's purchase~
※Adults purchase: things you can't afford when you're a kid, so when you grow up, you buy a whole box
Next is the third stage
Condolences~
Everest~
Photoshoot~
The words were changed again
Shoulder drop～
But none of the groups were able to get even a single point
Finally, the last stage
Reality~
It's the same~
Delicious~
The respective IKKO phrases are as follows
I want to go on a date with IKKO!
I really want to date together, but that's just a dream
Like a dream~
Reality～
It's a dream come true!
-Great!
Ah, it's a mirror.
-This way
Is it?
Special effect~
What to do...
Please tell me it's a dream~
Reality~
And thus, the contest ends
The results are revealed
What is this?
What what?
We FUJIWARA win!
Wait, wait a sec, hang on
Wait a minute.
-What?
What is this?
Thus we explain the project to IKKO
Does IKKO know what this program is?
What comes to mind? The program name
That one, right? The one with Matsumoto and Hamada.
-Yes
Wednesday Downtown~
Fooled~
Penniless~
This is a mess!
-No rules
For Downtown...
Konsang Amida~
In summary
IKKO's most frequently used phrase on the day was "Kongsang Amida" at 16 times
Interesting~
-Funny
What do you think, Matsumoto?
What the hell is with "Konsang Amida"?
"Thank you."
-It means "thank you"
This is the most used phrase, right?
I have no clue what the rules were for that
She shouts constantly, right?
I think her voice is probably even stronger than B'z's Inaba
Let's welcome the next presenter
Audrey's Kasuga!
Twoos
Thank you Thank you
Are you allowed to be on TV?
※Kasuga proposed to his girlfriend of 11 years on April 18 on the variety show "Human Watch" and was later revealed to have met a blonde 10 days before the proposal
It's okay, it's not a crime.
So its ok...
You can't do that.
-I didn't commit a crime!
But it might be on the same level as a crime though
I'm sorry for causing a crime level disturbance
This time is the loudness tournament
But if it is just an ordinary voice then its not interesting
So another element has been added
This is what was decided
Daily Life Loudness Tournament
Daily life?
When drinking with other artists in your daily life
How loud can junior comedians be
With seniors right in front of them
If the seniors say "You're so noisy" or something like that, they are disqualified
And they'll lose their points
I see
The seniors do not know this thing
-Of course
It depends on how they control the situation
Gradually increase the volume.
-Yes
Does this show not do theories anymore?
That's true
That was a contest, this is a tournament
Daily Life Loudness Tournament
This time, comedians known for being loud invited their seniors, who are usually on good terms, to dinner
Juniors and seniors
At the meal, they will attempt to speak up without getting called out for it
And will compete to see who can reach the highest volume
The first challenger is
Mikkity！
Shoji Tomohara
Confident?
-Yes
Don't I have the loudest voice?
It would be nice to use a loud voice subtly in conversation
The target is...
Penalty's Wakki
My wife said the landlord is coming today
What is this hairstyle
So find a good one...
Isn't that a clock?
Behind the targets is...
This is to measure the volume
A special volume meter with radio microphone is installed
That, to begin with, will appear simply to be a clock
It will be used to record and show the volume
So that challengers can confirm the decibels they are producing
And so, the tournament begins
And quickly...
What are you doing?
Peak Volume
Drinking
Seriously, that...
By making the "drinking a beer breath", the volume went up to 95.9 decibels
Impressive
This is the same noise level as a barking dog
Pretty loud
It is ignored by Wakki
My instagram followers are gradually becoming less and less
It can get lower?
I've always had very little, only 42,000
Always
And the number of likes is also really small
Damn it
I always upload photos from manzai shows, right?
Only 350 likes!
Damn it
Lamenting the number of instagram followers hits 99 decibels
In addition, the challenge will end when the special call button is pressed
The highest decibel value up to that point will represent challenger's performance
Right at this moment
This is soup noodles
-Soup noodles?
I might like that
What is this sense of sophistication?
Here Shoji fights to win
It looks like I'd like it
Please can we have some more soup noodles
Another serving please
So powerful, over 100
Your voice is too loud, right?
Shoji is disqualified
Thus, the project is revealed
Seriously?
You're out because he pointed it out
Eh?
Really?
The sound was too big, too big!
What is this?
I thought I was doing pretty good...
He figured it out?
-Yes
And what is this?
The next challenger is
Miki's Kosei
Ah, he's noisy!
The target is
Nichokenju's Shuji
Are you starring in Jimbocho today?
No, how do I put it?
It's more of a special guest kind of thing
Invited by whom?
Hurrica~nes' Arai and the like
So loud, so loud
After the event there...
The sound is so loud
Slightly annoying
Kosei starts by exceeding 103
Which NSC class were you in?
-Osaka 12
※NSC is a comprehensive arts academy founded by Yoshimoto, called "New Star Creation"
You're 12?
I'm 30
-You went to NSC?
I didn't go, but i'm in that age group
You were 12! We're 18 years apart!
Why does he have to say this loudly?
You were just a kid when I started out, right?
It was '93.
-93?
9…93？
This is how you win high scores in a row, by overreacting
Next
Is this it? Is this whale meat?
It's not the same at all
I'll try it
Super delicious!
It's super tasty. Try it too.
-Really?
In this way, Kosei continuously hits 100 decibels
So strong, so normal as well
Eat it, please
This is delicious!
Yes!
This bewildering "yes!" reaches a record high of 106.5 decibels
Next
Is it good?
-Super delicious
Eh? What?
Here the button is pressed to end the game
I made it
With a record of 108.5 decibels, Miki's Kosei is temporarily in first place
Impressive to reach 108
The next big voice artist to challenge is
Sunshine Ikesaki
He's usually pretty quiet
The target is
CoolPoko.'s Ono Majime
A good choice
What do you want to eat?
Well, how about... tempura
Don't make so much noise!
Don't be so loud
Sunshine Ikesaki is disqualified
Too fast!
The next loudmouth challenger is
Jungle Pocket's Saito
The target is
Captain Watanabe
I'll start with a draft beer
It's not just about winning at Oaks, you can't afford not to win anywhere
But Oaks and Derby these two weeks
※Derby refers to the Tokyo Yusen horse race, which is held by the Japan Central Horse Racing Association at Tokyo Race Course.
It's hard to win in Tokyo, but last time it was at the high-speed track, wasn't it?
※High-speed racecourse: A track where horses can enter the line quickly.
The horse farm, right?
So it won't work at the high-speed track.
-This can't be helped
The conversation turns to the topic of horse racing, a common hobby of the two men
Aren't there Kawasaki Milers today?
※Kawasaki Milers is a prize horse race held at Kawasaki Racecourse by the Kawasaki Horse Racing Group in Kanagawa Prefecture.
I haven't seen it yet.
-You haven't seen it yet
I watched the game and the last one
But the last one I didn't win any
I already know the results.
-You do?
You better not say, please Cap
Don't say it, really. Don't say it, really
Don't say anything? I just wanted to give you a little hint
No hints, don't say anything
No tips either!
Seriously, don't say it!
The tug-of-war between betting on the outcome of a horse race horse is constantly interspersed with jabbing attacks
Wait wait
Was your horse in the top three?
Are you gonna look?
Shall we look together?
They watch the video to confirm the results of the match that Saito doesn't know yet
It's started!
Ah, we're up and running
The start is good
After
It's coming!
Charge, charge, charge!
Can't you? Can't you?
Charge, charge, charge, charge!
Charge-
Charge! Charge-ah-rush!
While pretending to fully support the horse he bet on
In fact, he is staring at the decibel meter while sending out loud and continuous noises
Next
Can you hear the song of the combatants?
Drumming is that what~ you know that song?
Hot blooded life is about to start anew♪
Not at all
The direction is changed to musical style singing
Next
Can you hear the song of the combatants?
At this point he is just one step away from the reigning champion
A record of 107.9 decibels
You love to sing too much, right?
Although picked up on his behavior
Since this is not a volume alert, it is considered safe
However
I'd like to order a cup of oolong tea with sake
-OK
I'll have an oolong tea
This is delicious.
-Yummy
It's really delicious.
-Thanks
Combatants~
You're so noisy!
Don't do such things to the workers
As he couldn't resist in front of the staff
He is warned without hesitation
Thus, Saito is disqualified
The last big voice artist is
Good choice
Hollywood Zakoshi
The final stage of the competition involves...
Certainly loud
The target is
Nadani Takeshi
With only Hollywood Zakoshi left
Wow, only one person succeeded!
Will he be able to take the top spot?
So
What's that?
-Bearded Baron
I don't see it, its too exaggerated
A usual exaggerated imitation hits just a little over 100 decibels
Despite commenting on the imitation, the loudness is ignored
And
The show just now
-Club?
The club in Shibuya
There was someone exactly like my act
-Who?
The person in charge, he wasn't funny at all and got angry
What was he like?
I can't thank you enough!
The sound is so loud and strong
I really thank you for coming.
Wow ah ah ah ah so strong
Through a succession of exaggerated imitations
He is just 0.2 decibels away from matching the current reigning record
108.3 decibels
Next
The unfunny guy?
-That's the guy who invited you to participate in the unfunny bit
Tani reacted like "It's a cold day..." in the lounge
How about I pretend to be in charge and say this to you?
Ok i'll do a bit
A few days ago I was condescendingly criticized
Really, it wasn't by a friend either
Well, they could be considered a friend, thank you very much
Then the scene changes
Thank you for your hard work.
-Thank you so much
I'm so thankful you're here
That's pretty much it, right?
Eh, what is this?
In summary
Hollywood Zakoshi is invincible in this type of project
Impressive
I see
Unsurprisingly, Zakoshi was good at it
It was wonderful, the whole process
As a musician, what do you think?
For typical drinking sessions, the style etc
I do have the impression that there are a lot of people who can make a scene
But in terms of comedians or other people from the entertainment industry drinking
I think teams are probably more over the top
Bands?
-Well, musicians
It's not a band, it's a team?
Because you said "team"
In Saitama everyone says "team"
I've kept it going
Zakoshi's throat is really resitant to so much sound
It's really as resistant as B'z's Inaba
※B'z is a Japanese rock group formed by guitarist Takahiro Matsumoto and vocalist Hiroshi Inaba. Inaba-san is known for his unique voice and singing ability.
We've heard enough of that!
Why enough? I'm trying to salvage a previous conversation
Next is everybody's theories
Tonight's presenter is
Super Sasadango Machine
Hello everyone
It's been a long time.
-It's been a long time indeed
Yes, that...
Sorry, your mouth is a bit crooked tonight
Ah, really?
The mask is still new...
There you go
Most of your face is visible
Basically, you can see...
Is it okay to continue shooting like this?
It's fine it's fine
That, because it's been three years
I want to start over again with self-introductions
Excuse me, my name is Super Sasadango Machine and I'm a wrestler
Live in Niigata-shi, Niigata, Higashi-ku, Yuraku 2-chome
Now 41 years old, father of two.
-Your whole life story
It's Dad!
Normally a member of Tokyo DDT, a wrestling group
It belongs to Matsutake Arts
Ah, it's Matsutake Arts
Yes, activities are carried out under Matsuzake Arts
I have two surefire techniques
One of them is the "Vertical Drop Rayman Impact" wrestling technique
The other is ppt presentation
In a nutshell, violence and the power of presentation
With these two powers
I can solve most of the world's tasks
I think so
Violence is included
Roughly these two can solve everything
Is that so?
-Yes
The topic we want to solve today is this
The general public's thoughts
Are that wrestling moves can be easily done
Most people think this way
I want to erase this impression completely
For example
Muto Keiji-san's unbeatable technique figure four leg lock
It's a joint technique that holds your opponent's leg in the shape of a 4 and tightens it
How powerful is this move?
The memory should still be fresh in your mind
October 9, 1995, a long time ago
New Japan vs. UWF Inter Total Matchup
Exactly two months before I was born
Two months before your birth?
-Yes
Muto Keiji made Heisei's fighting king Takada Yoshihiko surrender by using the move
Although it is such an intense move
You may still think
"It's easy to do?", possibly
So, the theory I bring today is this:
It is impossible to teach women the figure four leg lock over the telephone
What the hell is this?
So, with haste
We hand a phone to the Asagaya sisters who know nothing
Instructions will come through the phone that was just given to you
Eh? Instructions?
Someone will call?
Yes, you will then follow the instructions
Eh? Eh?
The instructions are...
How to perform the figure four leg lock
This is the way to decide the winner. This is my...
Figure four leg lock
It involves fixing the opponent's leg in the shape of a number 4 and tightening it
It is one of the most famous wrestling moves
To teach this move by phone is this man
Keiji Muto
Are you confident?
I call myself "Japan's No. 1 figure four leg locker"
So, the verification begins quickly
Ah its here
Hello, this is Kimura
Hello, I'm the wrestler Muto
Oh, hello
Is it Miho of the Asagaya sisters?
-Yes
There's no time so i'll start
Who is it?
-I'm going to teach you a wrestling move
Rule 1 Restricted Time 5 minutes
Be sure to do as I say
You have a partner, right?
Yes, I do
First, let the partner lie down on her back
We're starting now?
Let's start now... because there's not much time left
Okay, so I can do it?
What? What "can I do it"?
That... fall down on your back... fall down...
Fall down fall down
What? What's going on?
Fall down quickly
Ok ok, get down quickly
-What?
Shoes... its better to take off
Shoes are best taken off
Have your partner take off her shoes.
-Okay
Rule 2        Only give clues
And then... on your partner's crotch
Crotch, okay.
-Crotch?
Put your right foot at the base of your hips
-Good
Can you say anything other than "yes", Miho?
What do you want?
-The crotch... ah...
Is that so?
Put your right foot in the crotch area
What do you want?
Left foot on the outside of the opponent's right foot
You're too noisy!
The right foot is under the hips, right?
The crotch... stand by yourself...
Stand on your own, stand on your own
Then bend from the waist down
Can you grab the opponent's left heel?
Eh?
Left foot, eh?
Bend down, after bending down, how to put it...
Put the head... the head...
Extend your foot a little bit, this foot
Like this? Is it like this?
Twister?
It's kind of...
I just grabbed the heel from the crotch
Then grab it while landing on your buttocks
From here, this way?
Ah, it feels like a trick of some kind
Then the opponent's left foot is like the shape of a V
A V on its side
The V is slightly more medial than the heel
Put your left foot on it
Hey? Like this?
The left foot put on top
So like this, the other person is in pain, right?
Not at all. Even a little sleepy
Very sleepy
It doesn't seem to hurt at all
What's more
Done?
It shouldn't be like this
Really?
What do you think, referee?
Is the move complete?
Rule 3  the judge decides
No! Fight!
Fight? Fight?
Eh? No?
It's tough
What the hell?
I'm obviously trying super hard to explain
Sure enough, it's impossible
The next challengers are
Ganbare Luya
This time we switch the figure four leg lock
Do the swastika hold
A telephone explanation by its creator, Genichiro Tenryu
It's impossible to hear anything he says
The meaning wont come through at all
No problem, don't worry
Have you ever been put in a figure four leg lock?
-No
But i've been licked
Licked? What do you  mean licked? Licked what?
So... knees
What the hell are you talking about?
Now, Tenryu explains the swastika hold to Ganbare Luya by phone
The point of this has changed
Hello
Yoshiko
That... I'm Tenryu
Now, can you move around like I say?
Quite frightening
Sounds like a kidnapper...
Where is Mahiru?
Hey... how to say, can she get on all fours?
Mahiru on all fours
Ok
Then Yoshiko
- I'll do it
Can you go around to the left side of Mahiru?
Mahiru's left side
Go around to the left
Can you use your right foot to hook Mahiru's left foot?
It hurts. What's wrong?
It hurts...
Good kick
Yoshiko mishears "hook" as "kick"
Probably doesn't know hook
Start all over again!
I don't understand, can you please speak a little louder?
If Mahiru doesn't stand right its not possible
If Mahiru doesn't stand we can't do it?
Bending a little is better
Mahiru needs to bend a little better
Focus your strength on the lower body
@#$%*&...the pose
I'm sorry, could you be a little more clear? I'm sorry...
Mahiru's body bends forward
Wrap your right foot around Mahiru's left ankle
My right foot is wrapped around Mahiru's left foot, right?
So is my right foot in front of or behind Mahiru's left foot...
-The front
Wrap from the front
Good question
Go through the front and stop right at Mahiru's ankle
Ah, I see. Okay, okay
It's hooked, right?
-Yes, yes, yes
Mahiru is bent forward
Mahiru bends forward
You'll be under Ma's right armpit
Use your left hand to pass through to the neck area
What kind of posture is Mahiru in at this time?
Just stay bent forward
Then you bend down a little more
Hands should not touch the ground
Pretty good?
Cannot touch the ground
Concentrate power on the abdomen
Concentration of force on the abdomen
Ah, I got it. I did it
@#$%*&...and it's okay, right?
Huh? What did you say?
You are wearing good quality clothes so you should be fine
What?
Ah, forget it. Nothing.
-Sorry
Don't say irrelevant things
Then put your left foot on Mahiru's head
Put it on Mahiru's head
Prepare then hitch it up
OK？
Referee
OK
The Tenryu and Ganbare Luya Team complete swastika hold in 4 minutes and 12 seconds
Therefore, the next step is to raise the difficulty of the move to another level
Winners and losers are yet to be determined...
Bow and Arrow
Fixed head and foot lift
Lifting the opponent with the knee
A rather complex trick
Looks so painful
Challenging this trick are these two
The same persona
The caller is this old acquaintance
The plan is explained
Ah, no problem at all. It will be done immediately
"Bow and arrow hold", right?
Well, well, well. "Bow and Arrow" is a sure win!
Really?
So the validation begins
I am the beast god, Liger
Then I'm counting on you
What? What? What? What? What? What? What?
Let Nishino lie prostrate on the mat
Lie on your stomach here
Suzuki, standing right at the waist.
-I see
Stand well
Suzuki's toes
-Yes
Slightly tense both toes
-Tighten up, ok, tightening up
A state like this
Put your toes tucked in under her stomach
Is that so?
-Terrible, terrible
Tuck your toes under the belly
-Tucked in
Hold this position and slightly seat yourself on Nishino's waist
Okay, I'm in position
-It hurts
So painful, so painful, so painful
Then bend Nishino's left foot up
After that, the difficult "Bow and Arrow" hold is taught with precise instructions
Then
Then, Suzuki, hold the chin position and flip backwards.
-Ok
Nishino's waist is just above your calf in the posture
Can I put the phone down for a while?
-Yes
Then i'll do it
-My jaw is about to burst
Say "one, two"!
Okay, I'll start
Ah, scary
One, two
Great!
Thank you very much
Relying on Liger's mind and Suzuki Nana's physical ability
Outstandingly, the "Bow and Arrow" hold was successfully completed
In summary
Depending on the number of moves some can be taught successfully
Only the four figure leg lock did not work
-Yes
Awesome
Ikoma, is it doable?
Remember?
Most people who watched it should be able to complete the four figure leg lock now
The four figure leg lock?
-Yes
Yes, I would like to try it
Please do!
With whom?
With my mom, like this
To your mother? You can't do that to your mom!
Mom's knees would break
A late Mother's Day gift
A Mother's Day gift?
Sounds good
What the hell?
What is this, what's going on?
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03