Seven-colored dusk descended
The wind is somewhat cool
Saturday night is lively
Even a gloomy feeling is soon cleared up
And everyone is getting excited
Let's go DOWN TOWN
Hello.
It's amazing.
It's packed.
Even the front rows are packed.
We've got people sitting all the way to the front row.
But you guys are looking forward to Shimashimans after us, right?
Shimashimans is the last performer.
-  I didn't know that.
- I thought you guys were waiting for them.
This is tough!
Hamada-san is very excited at times like this.
You guys know that, don't you?
- No.
- We all have those energetic annoying uncles right?
Suppose you go out for dinner with your relatives and get harassed by a thug.
And when that happens, your uncle is surprisingly not doing anything about it.
You are that kind of person.
- I'm not that guy.
- I am very lazy to do this.
This is hard to do.
Incredibly many juniors are watching us at the side of the stage.
It doesn't matter.
We were told to do something here.
But I'm a legendary comedian.
And I'm charismatic.
This is tough.
I can't get rid of my charisma by taking a bath.
I want to get rid of my charisma.
That sounds like a tough.
Yeah.
- They said to do it, so let's do it.
- Yeah, we don't have a choice.
- What was that like again?
- What are you talking about?
I mean manzai.
Yeah.
We haven't done that for decades.
Yes, and Hamada-san said that we only do manzai for money.
No, you said that!
I don't think that's a good idea.
But you got rich.
I see, you say that.
- I see.
- That's not what I meant.
Do it properly.
I was worried you were not going to do this because you're rich.
You have more money than me!
That's absolutely not true!!
- What are you talking about!?
- That's not true!
You DEFINITELY have more money than me!
You're scaring me!
Heeey!
Everyone come out!!
- What did we do in our manzai?
- We did a lot of things.
Audience: Kidnapping one!
Oh, yeah.
Who the hell are you!?
Sorry.
He is this kind of person.
He often shit talks everytime.
We've done kidnapping one and doctor one.
Audience: Researchers one!
Yeah, that's right.
So who the hell are you!?
If you do that twice, you're persistent.
Ah, we also did ghost one.
- Oh, the ghost one?
- Yeah.
And the quiz one.
How about a quiz once in a while, just to warm up?
Let's do a quiz.
- What should I do?
- Well, let's do a quiz to warm up. Then give me a common quiz.
You want me to do it?
It can't be helped.
We are a duo.
If we were a trio and Yanagida-kun was here, I would have asked him to do it.
But there is no Yanagida-kun.
There is only Matsumoto and Hamada.
It can't be helped.
I'll give you a common quiz.
Hmm...
- Whatever.
- Really?
How many meters is Tokyo Tower?
How many meters is that?
"How many meters?"
Hey, this is a quiz.
So how many meters is that?
I give you the quiz and I have to give you the answers?
It doesn't matter.
No, it's not.
I'm scared of you.
What's wrong?
It happens all the time.
You asked me to give you a quiz, so I gave you one.
And why are you asking me to answer?
Hey, it happens all the time.
I'm scared of you.
Okay, so I'm supposed to give you the answer?
Yes...
You don't know the answer?
For that matter, what is the answer?
It's 333 meters.
Huh?
Hey.
What's wrong?
This is pretty tough.
What do you mean, "this is tough"?
This is more than tough, it's heartbreaking
Heartbreaking!?
This can't be heartbreaking !
I just asked a question and gave the answer.
We came all the way to NGK(Namba Grand kagetsu) today.
- That's why I don't want to fight with you.
- Fight!?
Why should we fight?
We are graduates of NSC.
We are the first generation of New Star Creation.
We should not be fighting at NGK.
All right, that's enough, Okay.
Hey, what's okay?
I gave you the answer.
Yeah, I know that.
I don't understand what you mean by this.
Anyway, the Tokyo Tower is 333 meters tall.
Well, I'll tell you this.
It's not that tall.
Eh?
What do you mean?
It's not that tall.
Sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
No, no, no.
- Thank you so much.
- What are you talking about!?
I'll send flowers to your dressing room.
I'm so sorry.
The answer is 333 meters.
What do you mean, "it's not that tall"?
I said that because it's not that tall.
Eh?
I said that because it's 333 meters tall.
No, it's not.
No, it is 333 meters!
I might embarrass you because I said this.
Can I say this?
Go ahead.
I lived by the Tokyo Tower for a long time.
- I lived there for two years and renewed my lease.
- You renewed yours?
So I lived there for two years and a half.
When I woke up in the morning and looked out the window, I could see Tokyo Tower.
- Was it that close?
- I used to look at Tokyo Tower from my window every day.
Okay.
- There were days when the windows were covered with lace curtains.
- I don't care about that.
But even if there were lace curtains on the windows, I could still see it!
Even if the lace curtains was only slightly open, I could see it from there.
So I could see it almost every day.
so I say that it's not that tall.
That's all!
- Sorry. I'm so sorry!
- No, no, no.
- Does your stomach hurt?
- I'm fine!
Hamada.
Oh, his name is Hamada.
He's playing a rough character.
I wish you could at least remember his name and face.
Shut up!
How do you know it's not 333 meters long just by looking at it?
I know that!
I know that, Hamada!
No, it's officially stated to be 333 meters tall.
- That's 333 meters tall.
- No, it's not that tall.
I saw it, and I'm telling you, I'm absolutely right.
But you only looked at it!!
What you see is all there is.
What are you saying?
No, what are YOU saying?
- You're scaring me.
- Okay, how tall do you think it is?
I don't know!
I don't know that.
But it's not 333 meters tall.
It happens all the time.
You don't need to know the right answer to know that someone is wrong.
For example, suppose someone suddenly says, "Hello," and you reply, "Hello,".
But it is obvious that person is not Shoei.
That's what I mean.
What is this guy talking about?
It happens all the time.
And he is an elementary school student.
What do you mean?
I'm so fed up, I want to go home!
It happens all the time, right?
You don't need to know the right answer to know that someone is wrong.
But you only looked at it, right?
This is tough.
What's wrong with you?
Are you nervous!?
How could I be nervous!?
Are you nervous about the live viewing?
If so, let me know.
If so, let's take it slow.
Let's do it so you don't get nervous!
I really don't want you to be nervous.
we're getting nowhere with this.
Personally I don't want to get anywhere.
What's wrong?
So how tall do you think it is?
Just tell me that.
It is officially 333 meters.
You said you didn't know the right answer.
But if you saw it every day, how many meters would you guess?
200...
200?
More than 200.
"More than"?
"More than 200"?
This is the kind of symbol.
(200～)
There is a chance that your 333 meters is correct, too!
After all, that's MORE THAN 200!
So I'm sorry if you were right!
That's what I'm saying.
But really, that thing is 333 meters tall.
- But...
- 200 KARA (More than 200)?
"KARA"(more than)?
You know how they say,
"Yakyu - wa - 2 out - YAKARA".
(Because baseball is two outs)
No, no, no...
"Yakyu - wa - 2 out - YAKARA".
(Because baseball is two outs)
Wait a second.
- Baseball starts...
- Once, in a public bath, an older man was watching TV and said, "Yakyu - wa - 2 out - YAKARA".
- No, no, no...
- "Go for it! The game is about to begin!"
It's
"Yakyu - wa - 2 out - KARAYAKARA."
(Baseball starts with 2 outs.)
No, It's "Yakyu - wa - 2 out - YAKARA".
(Because  baseball is two outs)
"Daijoubu - ya! Yakyu - wa - 2 out - KARAYAKARA", right?
(Don't worry! Baseball starts with 2 outs.)
Too much KARA.
- That's kind of too long.
- I don't know what to say...
Forget it, it doesn't matter.
Weren't you the one who brought it up?!!!
It doesn't matter.
"NGK YAKARA".
(Because this is NGK.)
You don't have to say that.
That' s enough.
- It's okay.
- What's okay?
- Wait a moment.
- What?
Are you still going to do this?
Of course.
My heart is pounding
- That's why you're nervous, right?
- No, I'm not!
It's because you didn't talk with me.
It's tiresome to have a meeting, isn't it?
I'm worried about what you're going to say.
Maybe so, but we're doing this now, so why not?
- You're a great guy.
- You're the only one having fun.
For a middle-aged man, you're doing great.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
So I think you're good.
- Okay. So do you know how tall Mt. Fuji?
- Are you going to continue this?
Do you know how tall Mt. Fuji?
Everybody knows how tall Mt. Fuji.
Then how tall?
3,77...
(5? 6?)
About 3,776.
- 3,776 meters?
- Yes.
That's for....real!
That's for real!
Hey, why couldn't you guess the height of Tokyo Tower?
It's not like that.
I saw it from a distance on the  bullet tarain.
You wouldn't know the height just from this!!
I saw it from a distance and that's how I knew how tall it is!
It was a great spectacle!
I've never climbed Mt. Fuji, but even if I had, I wouldn't know how tall it was.
The Rainbow Bridge is beautiful, but you would never know it by crossing it.
I understand that.
- Disneyland is not something you see from a distance, but you don't know how fun it is until you go there.
- That's enough!
Why are you laughing?
- What do you want?
- That's my line.
What?
It's hard to say.
I don't mind if I end up with this.
But this is why you get angry when you get home.
What the hell is that?
It's better to solve that right now. This is why you always get angry when you get home.
I want to eliminate uneasiness here.
No, I won't get angry later.
I don't want to make you feel bad.
You might be offended if I tell you this.
You are not the type to give quizzes?
Of course!!
You've been quizzing me all along, so you should be the one quizzing me today.
You only told me, "Think of one or two common quizzes."
"So that's it!?", I thought.
Hey.
And you keep talking about whatever comes to your mind!
It's okay if I'm a grown man like that.
Yeah, I get it.
Come on.
Give me a quiz.
Okay, you're not the quizzing type.
There are three types of people: those who give quizzes, those who don't give quizzes,
and those who don't use comforters.
- Was that funny?
- No.
Okay.
- Then let's do it.
- Hey, are you still going to continue this!?
Hey, why do you want to go home?
What do you have to do?
What are you going to say?
I'll give you a quiz, right?
That's what you want to do, right?
Well, I'm doing it because I have to do this.
Then give me a decent quiz.
You know Munch's Scream?
You know that?
Yeah, It's a picture of a man with his mouth wide open, right?
That's Munch himself.
- You think Munch is screaming because he has his mouth open.
- Yes.
But if you look closely at the painting, you will see that Munch is covering his ears with his hands.
But it's titled "Scream," right?
He is covering his ears because someone is screamng too loudly.
It is not "Munch's scream," but really "Munch is being screamed at."
What are you talking about?
So the answer is "Munch is being shouted at."
Answer!?
You didn't quiz me yet.
You didn't quiz me.
You were just talking to yourself.
You have to read the room!
You have to read between the lines!
This is that kind of quiz.
That's what this is!
When I say, "He is covering his ears..." answer "Munch is being screamed at"!!
- This is that kind of quiz.
- I can't.
This is a new type of quiz.
New types are hard.
So sorry.
(*The sound of an incorrect answer)
That's enough.
You still want to continue?
- Do you know what a bullet train's bar is?
- What bar are you talking about?
Right?
I said, bullet train's bar!!
So, where's the bar you're talking about?
I don't know if you said that.
I'll explain it to you now!!
Then tell me quickly!!
What's the matter?
Why are you so upset?
- No, I'm not.
- Is it a hormonal problem?
What the hell!
- Something wrong with your hormones?
- No, no, no.
- Are you not feeling well?
- I'm feeling fine.
- Are all your teeth hurting?
- No.
Are all your teeth hurting?
I didn't say anything.
I didn't say my teeth hurt.
Are all your teeth hurting?
If so, you should go home.
You seem to be having fun.
No, I'm not.
- It's the bar that you can grab in the men's restroom of the bullet train.
- Yeah, I know what that is.
That bar.
- You were talking about that bar.
- Yes.
I think that bar is the dirtiest bar in the world.
Because everyone grabs it with the hand that touched their dick.
There might be pee on their hands when the train arrived at Mikawa-Anjo station.
They will be grabbing that bar with their hands.
If I grabbed that bar, I wouldn't want to put my dick in my pants with my hand.
That bar is even dirtier than dick.
That's how dirty I think it is.
I asked others if they would grab that bar.
They all said, "I never touch that stick because it's dirty."
Nobody touches that bar.
I mean, it's the cleanest bar in the world.
Give me a quiz!
I did!!
Ding dong!
"That's the cleanest stick!"
Of course it is!
Read the room!!
Are you nuts!?
Enough with the nervousness!!
- That's hard.
- No, it's not hard at all.
No, it's very hard for me.
Are you a fake-Hamada?
Give me a break.
If you want to give me a quiz, give me a decent quiz.
- Well...
- Hey, has the quiz started yet?
Tell me!
- There was a cafe.
- Is that a quiz?
- There used to be  a cafe called Rika in the neighborhood of Nippon TV in Kojimachi.
Cafe Rika.
When I was looking at the Cafe RIKA(りか) signboard, I couldn't let my guard down while I was watching RI(リ).
As long as I am only looking at RI(リ).
I can't let my guard down until I see KA(カ).
If there is a curve with KA(か), RI(り) is hiragana!
But if there is no curve with KA(カ), it is katakana.
So you can't let your guard down!
Right?
You could say the same for both
Aichi(愛知)  and  Ehime(愛媛).
You can't determine which is which by the first letter
In other words, things should not be determined by the upper half of the body alone.
If an older man was in the bathtub, you still don't kno w if he is an older man or not.
If he stood up, he might be a centaur.
So don't determine things only by the upper half of their body!
I would say don't determine things based on the first half alone!
Wait!!
What's the answer?
- "Don't determine only by the first half."
- Weren't we just talking about Rika?
Cafe Rika.
Ding dong!
"Don't determine only by the first half!"
You were supposed to get 2 points for this.
I've never heard of points before.
Weren't we just talking about cafes?
What do you want?
- Eh?
- What do you want?
That's my line.
What do YOU want?
(Are you crazy?)
If anything, I'm on a roll today.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
It's hard.
It's better to solve that right now. This is why you get angry when you go home.
You keep saying that, but I won't get angry later.
I'm worried that you'll get angry later.
- You?
- Yes.
I don't care about that.
All right,
Let's play the quiet-quiet game.
What the hell is that?
So you get points for being quiet.
It's so easy.
What's the right answer?
You get points for being quiet.
I get it.
How many home runs did Sadaharu Oh have in his professional baseball career?
868.
Be quiet.
I just told you.
This is a quiet-quiet game.
Be quiet.
- Right?
- Okay.
- It's officially the quiet-quiet-quiet game.
- I don't care about that.
- That's what I call it by abbreviation.
- Okay.
What's the question?
Be quiet!!
Are you nuts!?
I told you.
You get points for being quiet.
The points go up like rats reproducing.
If you talk, you'll lose more and more points.
Okay, I get it now.
Oh, there's one thing I forgot to tell you.
What?
Don't talk!!
That's not fair.
Don't be such a cheat.
Don't talk.
How many liters are in a gallon?
A gallon...?
Don't talk!!
I'm scared.
Can't you concentrate?
Hey.
Is your article going to be in next week's magazine?
If that were the case, I wouldn't be in such a good mood to do this!!
Why are you so set on yourself that it's a scandal?
There is no way they would publish a good article about me in that one!!
You never know.
No way.
- Be quiet.
- All right.
- All you have to do is be quiet.
- I know!!
He's here.
My stomach hurts.
Ow...
Ow ow ow...
Wait a moment.
Ah damn it!
I just shit my pants.
Ow ow ow...I shit my pants.
It's serious.
I absolutely shit my pants.
Huh?
I didn't.
That's enough!!
Don't talk!!
What the hell is that?
Hey.
What the hell.
It's my line.
What do you want?
You just say whatever you want.
Give me a more clear-cut quiz.
Since we are standing on the stage.
How about a three-choice quiz?
- Three choices?
- Three choices is too hard for you?
- You're going to say something...
- It would be hard with your stamina.
I have stamina!
- You're going to say something crazy to me again, so give me two choices.
- Okay.
- Really?
- Yes.
- So, please.
- Two-choice quiz?
Yes.
Then answer with A or B.
My father passed away a few years ago.
At that time, who was the comedian who came to my house, offered incense, and sobbed with his hands together in front of the Buddhist altar?
A:
Hamada Masatoshi
B:
MASATOSHI HAMADA
It's me .
You finally get the point!
It's me.
You finally get the point.
It's easier to understand than the previous quizzes.
Okay, second question.
Are you still going to do it?
You're thinking of a question now, aren't you?
What is the sound of a bush warbler?
A:
"Ho - Hokekyo"
B:
"Mister...!"
"Mister, thank you so much for everything..!"
Stop that.
"Mister, Mister, thank you so much for everything...!"
What the hell.
The answer is all me.
Third question.
Are you still going to do it?
- That's enough.
- What did Gagarin say when he saw the earth?
- This is a good question, right?
- Yeah.
A:  "The earth is blue."
B:
"Why did you die, Mister!?"
"Mister!"
That's enough!!
Thank you!!
Let's go DOWN TOWN