Documental Season 5 - Finale
Hello, I'm Hollywood Zakoshisho
I know that I'm the type of comedian who attacks aggressively
I have a pen, I have an apple
Apple pen
However, Funakoshi Eiichiro cheated on me
He chose another woman over me, he cheated on me
Hello, I'm Chihara Junior
When a comedian gets absolutely no laugh,
to be honest, we become really depressed
I'm about to cum
We just have to believe that "this is getting a laugh, no problem, this is funny", that's all we can do to get through
And I'm actually easily amused...
Nice work   -Thank you
I feel tired too just by watching it
There's quite a lot of good scenes this time
Everyone has been working really hard
Well, I have no complaints at all
Huh? I have so many cards?   -Give some to me then
I need to touch my eyes in order to wear this
Hey, wait a second...
Attack points
We've never worked together on our own right? Junior-san?
Yeah, you're right
I'm really happy   -Yeah
Let's start
Okay, okay, please give me some time to prepare
Here comes the exaggerated Akira 100%*
*Akira 100% is a Japanese comedian whose act is completely naked, wearing only a pan and neck tie
Aren't you feeling a bit cold?
Chilly, chilly
This is hilarious
Nice one, keep it up
Is he going to do it at this distance...
Aren't you feeling a bit cold?
Chilly, chilly
Okay, good...
He endured it
Junior-san, you don't know much about games right?
I know nothing about games   -You don't play games right?
You mean like Famicom?   -Yes, Famicom
So Famicom gags won't work then
Oh, you wrote it all down?   -Yes, it's all here
There's so freaking many   -Yes, there's freaking many
I'll do Toshi-chan, you wanna watch Toshi-chan? (Toshihiko Tahara)
There's so many others and you wanna do Toshi-chan?   -Yes, Toshi-chan
I'll do it now, please look at me, Junior-san
Umm...
Umm...I'm...
I'm...umm...I'm Toshi-chan
I'm Toshi-chan
I'm Toshi-chan...
I'm...
Toshi-chan...
I'm Toshi-chan...
I'm Toshi-chan, Toshi-chan, Toshi-chan
I'm Toshi-chan
I'll imitate IKKO then, IKKO
(I'll imitate IKKO then, IKKO)
You're not saying his well-known line?   -Nope
You're not saying it?   -Nope
So you're not saying it?
Is there a version where you say it?   -Nope
Time to let the zombies out
Zombie time
Ah, the zombies are coming
Hey, I want you guys to meet someone   -Who?
I want you guys to meet someone   -Oh, really?
Is it fine?   -Yeah, well, we're quite busy here though
But I really want you guys to meet someone   -Okay
Please sit here   -Oh, sit here?
But we're quite busy though, very busy   -Excuse me
Well, but I think you guys will be happy to meet this person
So it means that we know this person right?
Yeah, I think so
Please come in
Do you recognize him?   -Not at all
You should recognize him   -Eh?
No, I don't   -Yes, you should
Eh?   -He looks so angry though
So scary   -Come on, you should know him?
No, I don't   -No idea at all
He's Jouto no Teru (from Be-Bop High School)
Are you trying to mess with me, you idiot?!
Give me you pants, dude!!
I'm the boss Teru, if you've got any problem with this, come find me at Jouto, you idiot!!
You understand me?!
Holy crap, he's really that Teru
Of course
This guy is still wearing his pants
Give me your jeans, dude!!
Ah, it's stuck...
His shoes...
You laughed just now
Was something stuck?
Well, no...
I laughed because this wasn't going smoothly at all
I feel like Takahashi is the one who made me laugh
Yeah, it's difficult to tell
But Junior is out for sure   -Yes
However, there's still some time left
And since you laughed because of the zombies
Zakoshi will be enduring the zombies on his own, until time runs out
And if he couldn't make it, it will be a "no contest"
Wahh, there's still like 30 minutes left   -Yes, 30 minutes
Anyway, Junior is out
Junior, why did you laugh?
Well, because I thought like "this is not going smoothly at all!"
Ah, it's stuck...
His shoes...
Your body went like this...
Thank you very much
You were in a pinch during the first half right?
Yeah, I was in a pinch, and to be honest, I even thought I'll be out in 20 or 30 minutes
Something gummy came out of him...
Hello, I'm Koizumi Junichiro
Junior is...
And Zakoshi, that guy is too strong
Na, ka, ta, Nakata
I'm a per---fect human
He's too strong right?   -Yeah
Too damn strong
Wahh, I'm the only one left
I'm the only one left, on my own
Come on, zombies, you idiots!!
Come on!!
Okay, let's start
Zombie time
Eh? I need to endure the zombies for 30 minutes? That's hellish!
All I can do is to hold back my laughter
Please come in
Let's sit over there
Sorry, it's a little bit messy
You've been here once before right?   -Yeah, about 6 months ago
So you're a repeat customer   -Are the girls still the same?
No, the girls are different, it has been a while
The girls are different...
Come here, lie down over here
Young man, over here
You were eating sushi?
Yeah, today is Chinese's home party
Yes, over there, lie down over there
Oh, you look slimmer   -Really? Thank you very much
Are you busy with your work?
Face down?   -Yes, face down
Sit here?
Young man, you look slimmer than before, are you tired?   -Yes
Which part of your body feels tired the most?   -Umm, around my waist
And my legs as well...
Is it raining outside?
-I don't know about the weather outside
-I see, you're always staying indoors
Okay, I'll give you a massage
Young man, this feels really comfortable...my service...
The girls here are all very cute, Lily-chan, Lulu-chan, everyone is cute
Lily-chan from Dalian
Ah, Dalian?   -Lulu-chan...
Lulu-chan from Shanghai...
They are all very cute
Are you his friend, young man?
Yes, I'm his friend
Starting from here
Thank you very much, young man
Okay, please give me the VIP course then
Is it cold outside?
Oh, not really cold today
There's not many girls during this time, it's February, it's the Chinese new year, the girls all went home
You're in a good shape, young man   -Thank you
You're really muscular   -Thank you very much
Do you have a girlfriend?   -No, I don't have a girlfriend
Nope? Chu-chu-chu-chu-chu...
This guy has a wife though
You have a wife?   -Yes
So you can't hang out, huh?   -Yeah, I can't
So you can't come to these shops, huh?   -Yeah, I can't
This young man is always coming though, chu-chu-chu...
You're getting too excited   -Excuse me
Okay, young man
Okay, lymph
Lymph massage, lymph...
This is the lymph massage, young man, the most comfortable massage
Comfortable massage, lymph...
You don't have any pubic hair, young man?
Yeah, many things happened...
-You must be hanging out a lot, young man!
-Many things happened and my pubic hair is gone
Having no pubic hair means you're hanging out a lot, right?
Thank you, young man
...VIP course...the best...
Okay, please give me the best VIP course
Thank you, young man, I'll give you the best VIP course
The most comfortable course...
The most comfortable course, the lymph course...
The lymph course for you, young man...
The lymph course...
What are you doing, young man? Stay still!
Don't move, come on, it scares me
Okay, the lymph course
Young man...
The super lymph course...
This is so embarrassing
Young man, did you visit our shop at Tamachi?
Ah, I didn't visit the one in Tamachi
The girls are all different now   -Oh, really?
I went to the one in Shinbashi instead...
The first-time customers need to take reservation on phone
After that, I will be here giving them a massage, the VIP course...
The lymph course...
Okay, young man, thank you very much
You're not allowed to touch here
If you want to touch...there's another touchable VIP course...
The touchable VIP course...
You want to touch?   -Yes...
Okay, you can touch here only
Okay, young man, the comfortable course...
Okay, this is the most comfortable VIP splash course
VIP splash course
You want it clockwise or counter clockwise?
Ah, counter clockwise feels good...
Okay, the comfortable course, the comfortable course...
The most comfortable course...
The most comfortable...   -Wait a second, wait a second...
(Oh my god...)
The course is finished   -It's his turn now
(Okay, I see where this is going)
My turn?
(That's a good idea)
This must be tough
(This is just...this must be tough...)
This is his first time
This is a difficult hurdle to jump
I'll take off your hat   -Okay
Young man, just lie down and relax   -Okay
Just like this
Which part of your body feels tired?   -My neck feels sore
Young man, VIP course right?
Yes, VIP course please
Okay   -Turn around, face up
Okay   -Face up
Okay, young man, the comfortable course...
What a big body!
You're eating a lot, huh?
Look at yourself, this thing here
What? Booo?
What did you eat, huh?
It smells so bad   -No, I don't think so
Young man, chu-chu-chu-chu...
Okay, VIP course, here starts the VIP course
Okay, young man, next the lymph course
Good, good, lymph course
The lymph course
Young man, the lymph course
The lymph course, young man
Okay, young man
What are you doing? You're like a cockroach!
Have you finished showering?
Not yet?
Shower...
(Is he actually laughing?)
(Should this be count as laughing?)
Okay, young man, the last bit
A final touch
Hey no, you can't touch me, this ends if you touch me
Okay, finished
We're done, young man
Do the rest yourself, we're done
Okay   -Thank you very much
Did you feel comfortable?   -Yes, very comfortable
It's the best to come here with your friends, very interesting
Do you want to take a shower?   -Yes, please
Have you finished showering? Not yet?
(What will happen if Jimmy is the one to do this?)
(I really want to see it)
Okay, young man, you're done?
He said it was comfortable   -Yeah, very comfortable
Are you guys waiting for your friends?
Yes, we are   -Okay
Hello, I would like to get a massage
I would like to get a massage
Did you make a reservation?
Well, umm, I made a reservation just now
Can we stay here as well?
Excuse me
My Singapore, Singapore, Singapore*
*Singapore can also be interpreted as "hidden pole (芯がポール)"
So, can I get a massage please?
You're wearing something interesting, huh?
Should I lie down with my face up or down?
Face up, please
You guys are staying with your friend, huh?   -Yeah
Can I start now, young man?   -Ah, yeah...
VIP course?   -Eh?
VIP course?   -Eh? Beat course?
VIP course for this young man...this is quite disturbing though...
Should I take it off then? What should I do with my Singapore?
-What to do with this Singapore?
-I'll let you decide what to do with my Singapore
This Singapore looks interesting, so just keep wearing it   -Really? Okay
Lymph massage, okay?   -Okay
Come on, nothing strange about this, this is not anything dirty
Macau...
Macau?
Macau, Macau, oh, Macau, Macau...
Oh, that's your Macau?   -Ah, Macau, Macau...
Hey sister, wait, sister...
Oh, sister, wait a second...
Please wait a second, sister, I'm about to cum, I'm about to cum...
Sister, seriously, please stop, sister...
Seriously, I'm about to cum, wait a second, wait a second...
Please, don't let me cum, it can't be aired...
You're so loud, young man   -Excuse me
Wait a second, not that, my Singapore, Singapore...
(Zakoshi is incredible)
I'm gonna cum, sister, I'm gonna cum...
Sister, please no, sister...
Do it yourself if you're gonna cum
Okay, young man, go take a shower and do it yourself   -Thank you
(He's incredible)
Excuse me   -He's incredible
Are you going to take a shower?
You're not?
Well, shower, umm...
That was close
Excuse me, are you free right now?   -Eh?
Well, my friend...
He's a Kabuki actor, and his costume has been stolen
Eh? That's no trivial matter
Yeah, and we're finding it now
Is it fine for us to find it here   -Yeah, sure
He said okay, come in
Tamura Ken's helper - Moriya Biyori
We have to find it, or else you'll be in trouble
How does it look like?
It's for the Shumei ceremony*
*Shumei is the name succession ceremony held in kabuki theatre, taking on new stage-names, most often those of the actor's father, and hold great honor and importance
Today is the Shumei ceremony?!   -Yes
And you can't find your costumes?   -Yes
Eh? You're in big trouble
It's my son's first stage appearance!
Today is so important!   -He don't even have underwear on
Not this one right?   -No, not this one
Holy crap
No, I didn't take it
Really?   -Yes
Jounetsu Tairiku has been filming me for a long time
*Jounetsu Tairiku is a famous documentary TV show
Well, that's none of my business, I didn't take it
No, it's not about whether you took it or not
Eh, he has a wart   -Excuse me
He has a big wart there
I found this   -He has a big wart
I found these shoes   -Ah, those are mine
He found it!   -Let me wear these first
Are these your shoes?   -Yes, let me wear these first
You can do tap dance?
Maybe I'm quite talented with this
My legs are dancing on their own
This is his first time
I should have learnt tap dance instead
Didn't you learn it before?
I'm really talented with this, I should have learnt it instead
You must've learnt it in order to do those dance steps
He's a Kabuki actor, dude   -Really?
He couldn't have learnt it before   -Well, yeah...
It's impossible for him to say "YOOO" during his dance, right?
*"YOOO" is one of the shouts and calls used in Kabuki theatre
Well, yeah, you're right   -Try it out
YOOO
I should have learnt tap dance instead
What do you think?
Yeah, he should have learnt tap dance instead
He has a wart, by the way
Please look at his wart
Eww, what the heck!   -Where?
A wart   -Which one?
This one   -Where is it?
This one   -Which one?
This one, dude   -Where?
Right here!   -Where is it?
Which one do you mean?
This one, this one, this is a wart
Look at it   -I looked already
Ouch!
Thank you
Be careful with your wart
Okay, not much time left
He's here again?   -You should definitely quit
I still want to do it
The power of your punch dropped
I think you should quit too
I really want to do it again
Sit over here
Try to hit his body
He hit me just now, but the power is totally different comparing to his golden age
I think you're losing your vigor too
Go for it
He's definitely weaker
This is nothing compared to his golden age
No need for him to be naked though
This is just...completely...
He's absolutely weaker
You don't even have the power to knock him down now
Ah...he's so weak...
Eh? Me?
One, two, three
He sure is becoming weaker
He definitely won't laugh because of this, come on...
My poop is coming out
He won't laugh because of that, come on...
He must be professional, right?
Eh?   -Is he professional?
This hurts so badly   -He won world titles in three weight classes
No wonder it hurts so badly
You don't know about him?   -Eh? Who is he?
(He don't recognize him?)
(Eh? He don't know Hozumi Hasegawa?)
Thank you very much
I don't know much about boxing
What are you doing?
I'm Miko
Timotei, Timotei*
*Jimmy is imitating the famous Timotei shampoo CM:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YXj8xj47FIY
I'm Miko
He was close just now
Okay
There's not much time left
Is there any more happenings?
Come on, come on   -Yeah, they should
Zombies, come on, come on, come on!
Not coming?
What will you do?
So scary!
It's so noisy here
You're being noisy, young man
You understand me? I can't take this anymore
Well, I think he got him
Well, I'll give you an orange card   -Yes
That one got you   -Yes
So scary, so scary   -This is scary
You're being noisy, young man
You understand me? I can't take this anymore
Okay, orange card
And 5 more minutes   -Okay
Akiyama, let's go
This is terrible
Zombie time
What the heck?
What's going on?
I'm Miko
I'm Miko from the municipal office
I'm Miko from the municipal office, in charge of police affairs
Got it
My at sign is JJ   -JJ?
I'm Miko   -You are Miko
Please call me again   -Okay
I'm Miko   -Okay
Got it
No more time left   -Thank you very much
No more time left, they need to be more aggressive
Last 3 mintutes
This is terrible
Can you go immediately?   -Please wait a second
Hopefully they can make him laugh
But that's a tough challenge
Hey
You laughed right?   -No, I didn't
Why don't you laugh?   -I did laugh
Laugh more, dude! You're always easily amused
I did laugh   -Laugh, dude
I did laugh
What's wrong with you?   -You wanna start a fight?
Is he laughing slightly?
Hell no, my knee is going to break
Just laugh, dude
My knee is going to break
God damn
It's so dry
Eat some sushi, dude   -I'm eating
One more   -One more?
Dig in
I'm waiting for you
Probably the last one
You're being really noisy
You hear me? Be more considerate
This is so scary
Are you listening?   -Miko, Miko...
I'm Miko, Miko...
Come on, be more considerate
Okay, time is almost up
Let's start the countdown
(10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1)
-Give me toro, I want toro   -Here you go, toro
Finished!
Incredible!   -Oh, finished?
It's finished
Finish!
I endured it   -Yes, you endured it
I endured it
Zakoshi is the winner!   -Thank you very much
He's so strong
Good job, he endured it
I was so worried, when he came in the last second
Well, this is really incredible
Thank you very much!
I did it!   -Congratulations
Thank you!   -That was amazing
Yeah, he's amazing
No complaints   -Really?
No complaints   -Thank you very much
Look at this
It's 10 million
I did it, it's double of R-1's cash prize
Where did you almost laugh?
Akiyama's zombie, which I actually laughed
You understand me? I can't take this anymore
Anyone will laugh at that one
And Kanoh Eiko's toy as well
What are you doing, buddy?
(What are you doing, buddy?)
I'm waiting for the toilet, dude!
(I'm waiting for the toilet, dude!)
That was awful
That was just...
Everything you do comes back to you
Am I the fourth champion?
Yeah, there was no champion for the first contest
Hooray!
This is 10 million
Well, my last wish about this contest,
please don't let any robber come to my home
I have to say, I have no complaints at all
Aren't you feeling a bit cold?
Of course, as an audience, I really want them to make him laugh in the end
He's strong in both offense and defense, right?
Yeah, you're right   -He's not laughing
Yeah, he's not laughing...
And the unknowledgableness of him, for not even recognizing the former champion Hozumi Hasegawa
That was really unexpected
He's probably just thinking "what's wrong with this guy"
But anyway, he've been attacking all the time as well
So I think this is a victory with no complaints