"The points so far."
You just don't know Kitamura-san...
-You're angry.
-I'm not angry.
-It's in here.
-It's coming out.
You lowered your guard!
And the winner is...
The final 34-minute attack.
Here we go!
The meat looks delicious.
It was really good.
Okay, can I take a moment, then?
What's with these sunglasses?
I'm Toshi-chan!
Enomoto!
Jungle jungle jungle!
Toshi-chan jungle!
Toshi-chan jungle jungle jungle!
Toshi-chan in jungle!
Jungle Toshi-chan!
Toshi-chan.
Toshi-chan...
Hey!
What was with that time lag?
It just happens sometimes.
—Come on!
—That was funny.
It's impossible.
—Pretty much, huh?
—He's cheating!
That was my two-sword style.
I might've held it with just one.
Let's take a look.
Toshi-chan...
Come on, Miyazako!
You're not out yet, but you get an orange!
You're slowly piling them up.
Your points...
And time's almost...
The end's getting near.
Yeah.
Zakoshi's doing everyone in.
Can you sit here?
I guess I have to go then.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If only we could get rid of Zakoshi.
I just have to sit here?
It hasn't started yet, right?
—It hasn't.
—Here we go.
It has a switch right there.
Hello!
I'm Katou-tii!
You see, Katou-tii was just...
...called a demon!
Intense!
Don't worry about the little things!
This is pure chaos.
What should I say?
—I'm Katou-tii.
—Katou-tii, right?
"The results are...!!", "The results are...!!"
"The results are...!!"
Someone's here.
That was close.
Who are you?
—Tokyo!
—Tokyo! (Editor's Note: Announcer at the IOC who announced that Tokyo will host 2020 Olympics)
So he was that kind of person...
—Tokyo!
I almost died.
Wait...
Everyone's gone.
It's kind of chilly here, huh?
What is that?
You know I wanted to become a boxer, right?
Yeah.
Because I'm pretty confident in my reflexes.
Yeah, yeah.
Try throwing those from a close distance.
—I can throw these at you?
—Yeah, I'll avoid them all.
—Really?
—Sure, it's no problem.
See?
Not a single one hit me.
They didn't, right?
Do you use the mail?
—Yeah, sometimes.
—The mail?
What would you do if you couldn't get rid of this?
When you're having a snack.
Couldn't get rid of it?
You can't get rid of it as in,
you have nowhere to put it in.
What do you do?
Guess I could tuck it between my legs.
That's amazing!
What's with that belt?
I don't really eat stuff like that at this age.
I guess so.
I'm eating one more.
Here I go.
So what do you do when you can't get rid of this?
I can't think of that scenario, though.
You bastard.
That looks like it's gonna fall for sure.
—It won't.
—Really?
Of course.
You can put it in?
Boy, boy.
Boy.
Zakoshi is a pain in the ass.
I want to eat Shinbashi's oden again.
This is a mess.
Something's here.
This is too much...
That's cruel.
The tiger-step wasn't particularly interesting.
Here we go.
Zombie time!
Five seconds before I fall in love for real!
Here we go!
"I love dogs"
Alright, let's do this!
—That's the other way around.
—It's the other way around.
That looks pretty tight.
Ready?
We can do anything as long as we're happy!
Here we go! One, two, three...
Cha...!
You said you couldn't do that, though.
—Master.
—Master?
There's a master too?
—Who's that?
—What's that?
A sea turtle?
Koyabu!
If you don't laugh with this, you won't laugh with anything!
He's not laughing at all, master.
You shut your mouth!
Koyabu!
The reason you can't make Zakoshi laugh
is because you don't know laughter yourself!
And you want to take down Yoshimoto?
—Listen and take a look.
—Okay.
—You too, Zakoshi-san.
You know Comedy Number One?
Yeah, I do, I do.
Master Sakata.
I wanted to be like you.
Twelve dogs!
That's twelve dogs, sho~!
How do you use this?
How do you use this, Zakoshi-kun?
You turn it on right here.
Here, huh?
Hey!
Hey, that's not the mode I had in mind.
Hey, that's not the mode I had in mind!
Not the mode I had in mind!
Damn it sho!
And that guy just keeps rubbing his cock, huh?
That's right, Tamuken!
These guys are too difficult.
So that's it, huh?
I've got to admit it's a little funny.
Thirty four dogs!
What's with all those dogs?
What are you counting for all along?
While you're swinging your dick.
I'm sure you smiled earlier.
I didn't.
Ouch!
It's red already.
It really hurts.
Looks like it's about to come off.
No one's laughing at all.
Maybe someone could've, though.
What's the best gum you've had so far?
Like Quick Quench or something like that?
Isn't Quick Quench that sports thing...?
Yeah, with the lemon.
This is the best gum in the entire world.
So just give it a try.
Two... you can have two of them.
You can take two each.
That's one too much for me.
No one's noticed yet.
—Can I eat this?
—Yeah.
Ah, this is my helper.
He's Koume Dayu from my office.
I think he has some great jokes,
so I'd like you to have a look.
Please go on.
Do the Two Lions Dayu one!
Whenever...!
I tried to eat an octopus...!
I got...!
Sprayed with...!
Ink!
Stop it! Stop it!
Funny, right?
You do this on stage?
He's super slippery.
I don't know what I should be laughing at.
Okay, just one more time.
Chikuwa goes...!
Stop it! Stop it!
Funny, right?
So he says "Chikuwa goes brr".
Why does he want the chikuwa to stop?
He wants the chikuwa to stop going brr?
Is it bad at it?
I love chikuwa that goes brr.
Then why do you want it to stop?
Just because, you see.
Just because?
Just because.
I guess...
...there's some weird stuff on twitter, too.
So you've been seeing me?
Every day...
Seeing me cursing every day?
You do that one every day?
Cursing every day?
—Do it once, just once.
—Ever- Every- Every day...
Cursing every day?
Just do it with "chan cha"
It's the first time I've seen this live.
You thought it looked like a circle,
but it turned out to be a triangle!
Damn it!
I want to see the "do re mi fa" one.
You have that one?
Do re mi fa...
That's right, yeah.
Okay, I got it.
Ah, that's right.
—Why?
—Huh?
Did you say to do the "chan cha" thing? Huh?
Why's it not coming up?
Wait a second. Didn't you say "chan cha"?
Your forgot it?
I do remember the joke, though.
He's always this slow?
You can start with the "chan cha" part, though.
Let's do that, from the "chan cha" part.
Do... Re... Mi...
Fa... So... La...
Ti... Do...
If you think about that...!
Fa... Fa... Fa... Fa...
That's how it was!
Ah, damn it!
—What happened?
—What's going on?
Don't lie to us.
I was expecting a full on "Do Re Mi Fa" thing
but it turned out to just be "Fa fa fa fa".
I guess it's time he does the MRI one, then.
He should just do the MRI.
—The MRI?
—Go do the MRI.
What?
He can do that?
—The MRI?
—I guess he can't do it just like that.
I got an MRI.
And after running some tests,
there was only a single thread in my brain.
Ah, damn it!
If he can do that, he can do anything.
That's wrong. You were saying something earlier.
You said you had no brain at all earlier.
I didn't have a brain...?
Do the one with teachers from bad schools.
That one...
This has gone too far.
I went to a school...
...with poor records...
...the teachers were chimpanzees.
Damn it!
That has to be a lie!
There's no way they were chimpanzees!
Where's that school?!
Where in Tokyo?!
—Not in Tokyo.
—Where is it?!
Answer me!
—Why... Why?
Tell me!
—Where is it?!
—Where?
—Where's that school?
—It's not real, it's not real.
It's not real.
It's not real?
So it was a lie after all?
It's not real.
—I lied.
—Why did you lie?!
That was the joke...
Hey!
—That's the joke.
—You're an insane bastard!
Come here and touch the tits.
Touch the tits!
—Hurry and touch them!
—What's this?
—Touch them already!
—What's going on?
You can touch them more.
—You can touch them more.
—Wh-What's going on?
The tits.
What do you think? How do they feel?
Koume-san.
Why don't you suck them?
—Suck them!
—Suck, suck, suck...
Suck them now that you're here.
—Suck?
—Yeah.
I have to suck this? Suck right here?
—Suck the nipples.
—Why do I have to suck this?
They have nipples, so suck them.
—They have nipples.
—What's going on?
—Who was it?
—No way...
—Koyabu?
—He went all the way...
And just when I thought we weren't making any progress.
There he goes.
Because we made him suck them.
It's time for hell now.
He could've just sucked them normally.
"But he kept going all "huh? huh?" and I just laughed.
—Koyabu!
—I guess it can't be helped.
This is an orange!
Damn it.
I never thought I'd laugh.
—I have to suck this?
—Yeah.
How do I suck it? Like this?
—They have nipples.
—Why do I have to suck them?
They have nipples.
—They have nipples.
—What's going on?
That face, though...
It's the first time I've seen someone like this.
There's no more time.
There's really no time.
—Thank you Koume.
—Sure, thank you.
Thank you.
See you tomorrow.
From now on and for the next 15 minutes,
we're gonna have to go free-time.
Here we go.
Hey, what was with that fart?
Zakoshi-san, what was that fart just now?
It was just a fart.
No, it was all... "buuuu".
—It's just a fart.
—You're insane.
Why do you care about it?!
That fart was insane.
It wasn't.
Touch the tits!
-Why do I have to go through your hell...?
-Just do it already. Touch them. Hurry.
Make sure you give them a good touch.
How is it?!
Now touch them from the front. Come on.
I've had enough.
With an ass like his, of course it's going to sound like that.
It flutters around.
It sounds like that.
Touch them.
Why do I have to? Is something going on?
Hurry.
That hurts, that hurts, that hurts!
Ow!
They're not even looking at each other.
It's pretty funny, though.
Double payback.
Two hundred million payback.
Just what is that sound?
It came all the way from the Chuo line in Tokyo.
-Katou was pretty great to the halfway point...
Two hundred million payback.
It came all the way from the Chuo line in Tokyo.
-I'm Hanzawa Naoki.
Payback.
-but the last half has been...
-I'm Hanzawa Naoki.
Payback.
...mostly Zakoshi's fault.
Wait, what did you do?
Yeah, what did you do?
What do you mean "what" you bastard?!
You're always like this.
What do you mean "always" you bastard?!
Are you being serious?
Wh-Wh-What are you talking about?
—Say it, Katou!
—Are you being serious?
Wh-What do I have to do if I am?
In that case, try to hit me!
What are you doing?
In that case just take your blade.
If you can do it with this, it'll all be your responsibility.
Okay, come here!
Hey! More!
Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Touch the tits.
What are you doing?
—Touch the tits.
—What are you doing?
What's up with that?
What was it, Koyabu-san?
You look like you want to touch some tits.
I've been waiting for a long time,
but what the hell happened to Kitamura-san?
Kitamura-san! I think it's about time we have a call.
For real! I forgot about him altogether!
Just what does he have in mind?
Okay, Kitamura-san.
Kitamura-san is definitely going to call us.
How can you tell just by looking at the phone?
How do you know he's gonna call?
I got a Line.
What does it say?
That he's going to give us a call.
-Ah, I guess it's alright if he said so on Line.
-He's going to give us a call?
This is annoying.
It's all a mess.
You guys know the Konami Code?
Yeah, up, up, down, down...
Yeah, if Sen Masao did that he'd go... (EN: JP Singer)
Up Up! Down Down!
Left right! Left right!
He'd sing that?
Did he say "Down Down"?
Okay, in the NES' golf,
there's a difference between Wood 1 and pitching wedge.
First, Wood 1.
Pitching wedge.
That's the putter.
—OB
—Ah yeah, I know that.
You know it, huh?
Okay, and this is the one from Gargoyle's Quest when you die.
It was like that?
Sure. When Firebrand shows up.
—That's the one that looks like a bat.
—Yeah, exactly.
Can I do Hyokkorihan next? (EN: JP Comedian)
—Hyokkorihan?
—Exaggerated, yeah.
That's good.
So he's going to put on the glasses.
Can he do an exaggerated Hyokkorihan, though?
Here's Hyokkorihan!
Okay, I'm Hyokkorihan.
Here, here, here!
I'm Hyokkorihan!
Hyokkoricock!
Here, here, here!
—We have to do this.
—Almost five minutes to go.
Come on, it's been six hours already...
My feet are starting to skink.
Won't you smell them, Kato-kun?
—They stink?
—Aren't you just saying that?
—They're that bad?
—They're putrid?
—Give them a whiff.
That stinks!
What do they smell like? Do they stink that much?
Feet smell...
They smell so bad?
That stinks!
—That stinks.
—Do it again.
Are you for real?!
I already smelled them.
Are you rotting or something?
I want seconds!
This is hell, this is hell, this is hell.
—I'm feeling sick.
Can you smell them, Zakoshi?
Give them a whiff, Zakoshi.
Na-ka-ta! Nakata!
I'm a perfect human!
This is too much.
That stinks!
That was hilarious.
—What are you doing?!
—That was too bad!
That was impressive!
This is too much.
—What was that just now?
—Let's see!
You saw it, right? Koyabu, Miyazako!
You're out! We went double this time.
That smelled terrible.
For some reason my left one's fine, but the right one stinks too much.
Left is usually stinkier, though...
But if they did that to me...
How did you come up with the "perfect human" crap?
Na-ka-ta! Nakata!
I'm a perfect human!
This is too much.
Yeah, that's way too much.
More than I expected.
He turned a tight spot into an opportunity.
He's truly a role model.
Just having Zakoshi here was a mistake.
Well, we only have 1 minute, 51 seconds.
I never thought both of you would be out so close to the end.
—He's too strong.
—He is!
I lost.
I couldn't do anything I wanted.
Na-ka-ta! Nakata!
There's no way we wouldn't laugh at that.
I was always walking a tight rope.
I felt pretty close to laughing at Zakoshi all this time.
I wonder what someone like him has inside his head.
He's regularly a great guy, too.
His methods to make us laugh
were just too much for us, for real.
I was just completely outplayed.
Here we go!
Well, that sure was amazing.
Okay!
Katou...?
Hey, did you just look at me, you asshole?!
—I didn't!
—You fucking did!
I fucking didn't!
Who do you think I am?!
Who the fuck are you?!
You want me to call my boss?
Go ahead, shithead!
Pissing your pants?!
—What the fuck is it?!
—I'm calling him!
—Who the fuck?
—My boss!
Boss right back at ya!
Right back at you!
Two-layered return!
Two-pieces of squid?!
Right now I'm acting an exaggerated Chidori!
—Hey.
—What?!
—Touch the tits!
—What's your problem?!
Hurry, touch the tits!
These are some good tits!
That's my woman! Touch her tits!
How are they?
Touch them more!
Did you like that? Did you like that?
Two-pieces of squid?!
It's over?
It's over.
Okay, that's all!
And the winner this time is...
—you!
—I did it!
Really?!
—It was a perfect victory.
—That was too much.
Thank you very much!
That's Hollywood Zakoshisyou's victory!
I did it!
I'm so happy!
Thank you very much!
That was way too funny.
—You destroyed us all.
—All of them.
Even earlier,
I was really struggling, man.
Back there with the dog, right?
That was close, huh?
You really did your best, right?
It just hurt too much and I did it without thinking.
I thought he'd laugh if I kept pulling.
I think I was really on the verge of laughing.
But even if you had laughed,
that would've just been an orange card.
—It was too much.
—Thank you very much!
Thank you very much!
He got the 10 million!
Well, to be honest I do feel defeated.
I might've jumped the gun too quickly in the first half.
My tits!
It exploded!
You're angry!
And then there was the time the phone didn't ring.
Kitamura-san isn't calling me at all.
Kitamura-san is coming....
My gags are usually pretty pointless,
so I feel like there are times where I just make them angry.
I'm only seeing equations written here.
That's right.
There's no answer.
So mean.
Who's mean?
I am.
Alright then!
Here they are! 10 million!
I guess I could win two back to back after all.
It was really close at times, though. For real.
Sorry for using other people's passports.
I ended up laughing once pretty early on.
But Katou sure was strong!
—What about you Katou?
—No way am I eating that!
Why's he so pissed off?
But he kind of lost steam at the end.
Maybe I pulled off more gags.
—Good job.
—Good job to you too!
This time was insane.
I just laughed to exhaustion I guess.
—Especially Zakoshi.
—Yeah.
I don't know if I should say he met my expectations,
or he actually succeeded them.
It was amazing.
He also managed to turn his struggles into chances,
and to be honest, this may sound a little bad,
but I actually think Katou was insanely funny.
You don't know Kitamura-san, right?
Katou was far superior in the first half.
I actually wondered if that was really Katou.
But the latter half,
Zakoshi went around amassing points little by little.
He didn't waste a single moment to the very end.
Two-pieces squid!
He was incredible.