Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks for watching!
So yesterday
a spin-off went live, right?
Well, it was shot, actually
So what's the difference
between streaming shows
and broadcast shows?
Well... I felt a difference in intensity
"Joshimental" consists of...
Mostly non-comedians.
Female non-comedians
And well, it was pretty intense
Or so I think, really.
And well... "Documental" is...
A group of comedians
So it gets more and more intense
And it get funnier as well.
You don't have a title, though
I have... well, a few in my own turf
What title?
You know... that...
A shoe flicking thing...
I guess we're fine then.
You drink first
There's no way...
That's pretty serious!
-Yellow!
-I'm sorry!
Yellow, yellow!
Damn!
-Watch out!
-This is serious!
Watch out!
Let's go then
It's only been 15 minutes!
For real!
I'm curious about this
You're doing that?!
Let's do this!
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's do it!
Alright, drink up!
Drink it.
Alright, so this is the proof!
-He put something in there...
-You put something in?
Huh?
-No, no, no!
-No one's drinking that!
No way, no way!
No one's drinking that
-It's great.
-You liar!
-Looking at your own face...
-What's this?
It's great
There's no way it is!
You even put something in!
I think that's enough, though.
Give it a rest.
No, no!
It's fine, it's fine!
What's he doing?
What are you doing?!
I'm filling it up
Since I made it for everyone.
Something's floating!
There's something in there!
Are you out of control already?!
There it is!
He's totally out of control
Get it, get it!
Go!
This is insane.
I'm doing it
What's with that color?
-Justice.
-Justice!!
-There it is!
-That's gross!
Just stop it!
-It came out.
-Gross!
-Stop this...
-Stop it, man!
This is just wrong!
Is this justice?
-This is awful.
-What are you doing?
Just someone...
There's so much left!
-No way, man.
-No way!
What about a nomination?!
Can we nominate someone?!
Out of control!
Don't do it!
That's completely insane!
He's totally insane!
Don't do it!
So a nominee?
Out of control!
Junior-san
There it is!
You do it.
You should do it
-How honest...
-The smiling samurai
-For real...
-You're the smiling samurai
He's really mad now!
Huh? Junior's...
-The smiling samurai
-He's mad now!
You just said you were looking
for nominees, but chose on your own
That's a shame!
Good job
There's also a Guitar Samurai,
right?
With the mask, yeah.
-So what is this?
-Bear bile
Why do you drink bear bile?
Bear bile?
It's great for your body
But he looks pretty sick
Junior-san
are you alright?
It's great for you, though!
No way...
Please don't go overboard.
Who are you anyway?
Me?
Yeah
I'm Mimiko
Who the hell is Mimiko?
I have a trick.
I wanted to show it to you.
I'm talking to Mimiko!
Go on, Mimio-san!
Are you that mad at
Mimiko and Mimio?
He's not that mad, though
Excuse me, guys.
We're looking at Mimiko!
Sorry
Excuse me
...So what about Mimiko-san?
Mimiko is...
Where did you come from, Mimiko?
From a world that you know well
Huh?
-A world we know...?
-Where's that?
Second block, Douguyasuji,
Setagaya Ward
-Douguyasuji?
-That's in Osaka!
That's all for Mimiko
Huh?
-So it's my turn.
-Go, Mimio
So now I'm Mimio?!
Like I'm your ally or something?!
Mimiko interrupted saying
she had a trick
But that was nothing
so now it's Mimio's turn
So you're the tsukkomi
from Shimofuri Myoujou
who dumped Mimio onto me?
You're Mimiko—
Mimio-san, right?
You're Mimio-san, right?
My nose...!
Do you know the kanji for Mimio?!
Raise your hand if you think
it's "ear" and "man"!
There... there... there!
You're correct!
-Alright.
-That was correct?
Crazy Man, huh?
-So now a trick?
-It's not "ear-man", though...
So I have
great balance, right?
This is really, uh...
So I want to show you
a performance that I've tried before
Ah... I think I've heard of this
-Right...
-A special skill...
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-It's just a regular...
-thing he does.
-Where are you...
-Where are you putting that mic?
-Are you alright?
Is that part of your performance?
It's not.
It's not, right?
-That's insane.
-That's pretty crazy!
-No way!
-So this is my setup.
That's an interesting setup
Chicken setup (Editor's Note: 1)
No, it's "chicken tandoori"
Not chicken setup
I'm really sorry
Are you doing it?
Who said that?
I don't know
how you got your yellow
You don't just do this
out of nowhere
Huh?
What was that?
I'm safe, I'm safe.
No way! No way!
That was just
-I should get that!
-Wait a second!
You smiled on your own!
I got one for the same thing!
-No way!
-You self destructed
You smiled for sure!
-Matsumoto-san!
-He saw it!
I haven't done anything!
-Well...
-Lots of self destructs today
Does anyone know?
Huh?
It wasn't me?
It was Seiya, right?
It was Seiya?
The reason I'm here is...
Soshina
What?!
For real?!
If you're saying it, I'll check
It was me?!
Soshina was smiling all along
From the beginning!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Let's look at Soshina
All this time he was just
With a general smile
Are you doing it?
Who said that?
I don't know
how you got your yellow
He's smiling!
-You're right!
-You don't just do this out of nowhere
Not yet!
He smiled, he smiled!
That's what I thought
But Seiya definitely smiled!
Maybe it's both Shimofuris
We're getting a double card?
I didn't do anything
Are you doing it?
Who said that?
I don't know
how you got your yellow
He's grinning
You don't just do this
out of nowhere
I'm safe, I'm safe!
He's safe!
No fucking way!
He smiled!
He was smiling!
-For real?!
-He smiled
It can't be helped then
-For real?
-That's quick!
That's quick!
Let's go with one for each of Shimofuri!
You two!
That's quick!
This is bad!
That's pretty bad!
We're not even 30 minutes in!
It's all too sudden
-This is rough
-Since your partner's here
That's one disadvantage
That's right.
Watch your expressions, Soshina
Tighten them
Okay! Good luck!
Whoa, that's scary!
Too scary!
This is insane
Let's laugh
Double card
Since we're here,
why don't we...?
Yakko-san,
let's not go there
Why don't we face our fears?
I even put the mic on my left nipple
It's an inverted nipple
-"Clang!"
-Hey, you!
Wanna fight?!
Stop it, please!
Please!
What's going on?
What happened?
For real, don't do that.
Don't do that.
-That's not funny at all.
-Thank you
You didn't change much.
Nothing changed!
Of course I did!
Maybe we can
fight as a combo now!
Put it on
Put it on, come on
-It's really not funny.
-You don't change at all!
For real,
there's no difference.
We can fight
as doubles now!
Who are you?
I can't see anything
so I have to open it
I was watching!
Soshina was smiling now, right?
Junior-san!
You too!
For real
Soshina's in trouble
Soshina was smiling normally!
Wait a second
That's no good!
Let's start over
I'm-I'm sorry
-Yakko-san
-20 million, you know
I was just saying...
We haven't done anything yet!
Why don't we do what Oniyakko-san said?
You wanna do that?
What was that?
We're just facing our fears.
I think it's fine
doing it in front of others
-What's that?
-Sea squirts. (EN: 2)
Sea squirts?
I feel like
you'd like them anyways.
That's right.
I get that a lot.
But I can't eat them at all.
I see...
I feel like you're doing it right
You hate them?
They're squirming?
That's crazy
I can feel...
The worst of the ocean...
All in here...
But I wanted to get over it
Are you using daifuku
to help swallow them? (EN: 3)
I love bean daifuku
That's an awful combination
It must taste awful now
Now you'll hate daifuku too
Are you alright?
You'll remember this
next time you eat daifuku
-Switch it
-Do you want me to switch it?
They're long...
You don't have to
call them long right now
I want to get over this
right now
That's what I'm doing
You're right
Right, Kubota?
That's...
It sounds kinda hot
Kubota has been giving me
these dirty looks
Is that soft?
It's so soft
So soft
I told Yakko-san that
I loved her a long time ago
Ah, really?
But eating these is just...
-Kinda erotic.
-Eating that?! No way
Don't do it now.
You can eat just the tip
I just want to feel
this part right here
Can you throw this
at my face?
With strength and all?
Yeah, do it.
Yeah, I just...
Can I do it from up close?
I want to feel it.
I'm covering my eyes.
-Right.
-Please go on.
It hit his hand.
His left hand.
Can you do it
one more time?
I can feel Yakko-san's smell!
The smell of her mouth
That stinks!
You're being rude
to Yakko-san right now!
That's just the daifuku
Isn't it just...
your own smell?
So today!
-I'm going!
-Yakko-san...
Try pinching it
That's right. That works.
I'm gonna do it!
Is someone making something?
Who's making this?
Me
You're making curry?
That's me.
That 18 spices curry is pretty spicy
That's right, yeah
I've never tried it before
Huh?
Comedians usually...
Put that through... right...
For the first time ever
That face is disturbing!
Really?
Are they alright?
Alright, choose
That's so uncomfortable to watch
Ah, they're the same?!
They're the same
-They're not.
-What's this?
They're twins.
-Twins?
-Like when you buy four of these...
You buy them in pairs?
Well, I'm guessing
that there are four different types
Like one type each...
For four people...
Four people...
That gather...
What the hell are you saying?!
He can't speak.
Alright...
Then twins and triplets
What the hell are you saying?
I think I got
the twins and triplets thing
I think he's saying
that siblings can be annoying
You know? I feel like
I would've found these funny as a kid
Well, yeah, right.
Did you see it?
Alright, today!
I thought about several games
So we can face off intensely!
-And I'd like to play them.
-Let's do it!
I have four games.
One is "Intense!! Pop Corn Talk!!"
"Hyper Galaxy
Nipple Clothespin"
"Smelling Dad's Farts, the Game"
"The Ice Duel of Exploding Gags"
These are the four games.
So which one do you wanna try?
What do you mean?
We're all playing?
They're for any group of people
I recommend this one, personally
So we're playing that one?
Alright, let's do it.
I'll get it ready then
Does it take too long?
Well... about five minutes?
That's pretty long
Well, I guess two or three minutes...
So can I show something meanwhile?
Yeah
So a lot of girls
stay at my place
Right
And they leave their stuff
all the time.
Like as a way to
mark their territory?
To let other women know?
Stuff like this
That's pretty interesting
Like make-up and stuff
Pretty normal
So they asked me
To give them back
There's some panties in there
Really?
They're XL size...
I don't know the brand
It says "Treasure Hunter"
I see...
"Treasure Hunter"
"Treasure Hunter", huh?
They're ripped
So they're for pirates?
Where does it say that?
Where's it written?
"Treasure Hunter"?
It's not there.
Huh?
It's not written?
It's not written, man
That's not good
Stop that, Junior-san
That's pretty cold
I'm just saying that...
You know what that means?
It means he's ready
to wrestle, you know?
As a comedian?
No way!
It's not written, though
Even if it isn't, that's just...
It's a little funny, but
Now I'm really pissed off
And he's so neat
They're soaked
Huh?
They're soaked?
Yeah
I washed them.
Gross
-Huh?
-Did you dry them?
No, I just...
hung them up
It doesn't say "Treasure Hunter"
anywhere
"Treasure Hunter"!
You know?
You're just lying, Kubota-san
I wouldn't lie
about something like that
You know how some driers
have "pure life" written on them?
Pure life sounds pretty fun!
I can't do anything with this
Yeah, I get that feeling right now
He's so grossed out
I feel bad for him...
He's so delicate.
He's really delicate.
That's just...
It's soaking wet
All of it?
This side's dry,
and then it's wet here...
That's nasty!
I'll return them, then.
It doesn't say
"Treasure Hunter" though
It does
It doesn't
Huh?
What about the Pop Corn Talk?
We're ready to go!!
Let's do this!!
You're so annoying, man
Shut up!
It's a challenge!
What what what?
A challenge?
Let's do this
with intensity!
What's what?
Intense!! Pop Corn Talk!!
You get in a teabagging position
Your ass goes down like this
I see
And you heat it up
In the meantime with someone else...
You start a live talk broadcast
Right right
And once pop corn starts popping
The instant it hits your ass
Even if you're talking...
if it touches you
You have to shout
the name of a fruit
That's so complicated
Why something like that?
It's hard to remember
You're bad at this
That sucks!
So you start with
a conversation!
Someone gives you a topic
and you talk
But the pop corn
will start popping
and it'll touch your ass
Once it does...
What are you even saying?
Seemed like you
almost laughed explaining
What was the last step?
If it touches you...
You shout the name of a fruit
-Once it touches you?
-Once it does, yeah
A fruit?
A fruit or vegetable.
What's with that?
Whichever's fine
Fruits and vegetables?
So- So one by one...
What's he trying to say?
You can't complain
or say it's hot?
Yeah, we wanna
avoid that
Instead, shout the name
of a fruit
or a vegetable.
So you don't lose
if you complain?
Well it's a conversation
So how does it end?
Once you're out...
of pop corn.
There's a lot there!
What's he talking about?
I see.
I wanna give it a try
Who's gonna do it?
Goto-san.
He's gonna teabag?
Well, I don't mind
but Abareru can do it if he wants to
-If someone wants to do it
-Just go ahead
Well, I have the t-back, you see
You have a t-back?
What's with the string?
Why do you have that?
I'm curious about the string
Do you always wear that?
I do
Is that tied to your dick?
-Tied?
-Tied
A dick tie?
So I'm going to do a check
We're counting on you!
Well he's the oldest after all
Something fell!
So it wasn't tied to it?
Didn't Abareru-kun just smile?
It wasn't tied
You look like Mikawa Kenichi (EN: 4)
Kuwata?
Well he just took it off
What are we even doing?
That's just a coincidence
-Wasn't Goto-san doing this?
-It's just a coincidence
What about this?
Well, I guess we'll go
with Goto-san!
He can do it!
Then we'll decide with this
With the ones Abareru brought
That's good!
Alright get one first
Yakko-san is a woman, so...
Right, yeah.
Then I'll go with this
And I... me too?
Right
What did I get...? Ah, right
If you get the X,
you do it
One, two...
Goto-san got it!
No way!
That's incredible!
Pop Corn Brother
So Goto-san will do it?
So what now?
Can they even
do it in the first place?
I don't even get the rules
Alright, we're all set.
His legs are short!
Short legs man!
That's funny
It looks good
Isn't your dick
too tight in there?
I just have it
higher than most people
Like the junction?
The junction is too high!
Really?
Do you have three dicks?
Junction?
-Are you alright?
-It's a cerberus cock
I haven't seen someone
with three cocks
This is pretty hot, huh?!
No, no,
we definitely need it like that
This is scary, man!
I'm scared!
Is this okay?
We're doing it right away?
Well, it'll last
for about a minute
So get in position
That quickly?
Alright then, let's go.
Intense!! Pop Corn Talk!!
What's the topic?
The topic!
Junior-san, please!
Alright then, "Yesterday"!
-"Yesterday"?
-Yeah
Yesterday I did this or that...
Yesterday?
Right, right
-So yesterday.
-What did we do?
Yesterday there was
the thing with Lumine!
-Ah, Lumine!
-Right
That's amazing.
Even though Yoshimoto is quite old
He's still going on stage
We did three performances...
Well, and because of covid
there were plenty of empty seats
Because even if you sit
next to each other
you had to leave two empty seats before
And then we changed it to like...
Um...
So you're getting more people?
Sitting next to each other
And haven't the laughs
died down a bit?
No, no. When we had to
leave gaps between seats
Yeah?
Uh... well, everyone was kinda...
Scared, you know?
It felt like that.
-But now...
-So it got difficult to perform?
Now I think it works better
You know, when the audience
is all stiff...
Here it comes!
Here it comes! Get ready!
So you did it yesterday?
Goto-san! Talk!
We have to talk!
Almost there
The pop corn is starting
to change
We're almost there
Mandarin!
Mandarin
Pineapple
Takuwan, daikon seeds
Aren't those the same?
Mine are still the same
There we go. Vegetables!
-The third one was takuwan?
-Vegetables?!
It has to be off
Watermelon!
Talk!
Watermelon
Abareru's in trouble
Pumpkin! Kaiware!
Kaiware for a second time...
Please sit down, Goto-san
Enoki!
Kabocha
You're too high!
Talk!
Tomato!
-Broccoli!
-Tomato!
Tomato slice!
Broccoli sprout!
What's going on?
They're not popping
-We have to talk!
-Cucumber!
What was with Lumine?
Ah! Kabocha!
-Kabocha!
-Peach!
-Ouch!
Carrot!
More, more...
That burns!
Smells great though
Melon!
Whoa whoa!
We're getting the other side
Ouch ouch!
-Kabocha!
-My balls are on fire!
Kabocha carrot!
My balls are done for!
Goto-san, good luck!
My balls are dying!
My balls are splitting, for real!
That's all
My balls are splitting!
That was long!
It's over when
your balls burst!
Looks great
Hey, my balls... burst.
They burst?
Abareru's face...
Busting?
Bursting!
-His balls busted?
-His balls burst
That's a weird size
Kinda looks...
like hemorrhoids.
Like a prolapse?
Looks like a prolapse
Well, this is just...
Why don't you come with me
for the following year?
Why are you doing
Master Nikaku? (EN: 5)
It's from an entire year...
I couldn't do this
until my first year.
Just cover that up, please.
Kubota, what does that say?
It says "Treasure Hunter"
on the back
That again?
Stop touching it
That's not very good!
I think he reformed!
He was very gentle.
Of course not.
Why are you blushing?
The conversation
was pretty good!
So you gathered more people?
They were really talking
So can you guys
look at my act?
Act?
I made this thing
What's that?
It produces sound
Whoa!
So I put this on...
And I'll sneeze
And make sure
it doesn't produce a sound.
Because it'll do so right away
It really seems like it
With his breath
That's impressive
He's inventing...rather
developing stuff!
What does it say
on Osada's shirt, Kubota?
-"Treasure Hunter"
-Of course not
It's "Forrest Gump"
It says "Forrest Gump"
What's with that T-shirt?
A Forrest Gump T-shirt?
What does it say on the back?
That's huge
It says "Treasure Hunter"
That's Forrest Gump!
Stop that already
So you won't make a sound
even if you sneeze?
With a paper strip
That's loud!
So loud...
What's that?
They held it
Well, I made this so...
Who wants to try?
-Wanna give it a try?
-With a new one?
-You have more?
-I do
No way!
He made some for everyone
That's just...
Let's clean this up?
Do we have like a broom?
It's about holding it, right?
We could put that on
and play the popcorn game.
Ah, that's right!
In that case...
Ikeda and Goto-san should do it
I'm fine.
I've had enough.
It burns!
Then I could choose
someone else
So you do it, Ikeda
That's a new one?
It's a new one, so it's fine
Alright, I'll do it
How many do we have?
Three more
Wanna try?
Really?
-With this one?
-That's mine
I wanna try it
You wanna do it?
-Really?
-Junior-san
-You have one?
-I do
That's crazy
No way
That's huge
That one's insane
With that one?
It's fine
That's amazing.
It's totally different
You went all in
That's amazing
That's so damned cool!
So this is the normal one
That's normal
This one's better
Junior-san gets the
ultra mouthphone
How does it sound?
It's crazy
Huh?
That's what I expected, yeah
No way!
It's so gentle
-Is that right?
-Yeah it is
That's wrong
That's not the sound
It's so gentle
It's so puny!
Puny!
You can't even see him
Isn't he laughing?
He's smiling?
Well, I guess he was cutting it close
Huh? Another show?
I can hear music
When you slip up with your story! (EN: 6)
The best people have gathered together!
That's Suberanai's opening!
We have gathered the specialists today!
Huh?
Who's that?
Who are you?
It's time to talk!
Chihara Junior
Thank you
for talking to me!
Right here
out of the narration!
You're always talking!
A talking-specialist!
Junior Chihara!
That's wrong, Wakamoto-san
Hey, the narrator isn't—
When you slip up when talking!
This guy sure
can handle a non-slip!
This guy?
He can handle the sweetest talk
and the toughest smack!
Osada from Chocolate Planet!
The talking candy factory!
That's wrong, Wakamoto-san
But someone here...
With people this talented...
You're not talking at all!
You shouldn't talk
when it isn't time
The man that doesn't talk
when it's not time
He can only talk as a presenter.
He won't talk when it's time to.
He won't talk
when he should talk!
And even if you stare at him
he won't talk!
He won't talk
when he has to talk!
Talk— He won't talk!
Talk, he won't talk!
Terumoto Goto!
He won't talk at all
It's not time to talk!
Not talk time!
When Goto is on TV
He won't talk at all!
He doesn't talk!
He won't talk!
Who was it?
-Who was it?
-Who?
Who was it?
-Abareru?
-I think it was Abareru-kun
It was Abareru!
Me?!
It wasn't me!
-I didn't smile
-Neither did I
Well, that was complicated!
Let's take a look!
Yeah, yeah
It was Abareru-kun
Alright!
I'm glad I kept going!
When Goto is on TV
He won't talk at all!
He doesn't talk!
That's a little close!
It's so close!
I'm glad I kept going!
I think it's a little tough!
But I have to remove all feelings
Alright!
I'm glad I persisted!
You went on and on!
This is Seiya's point
Thank you very much!
I'm glad I pushed on
A yellow for Abareru-kun!
-Damn it!
-Another yellow!
Okay, I did lower my guard!
Now raise it back up
20 million on the line!
20 million, right!
Already one hour in
Stop it with your persistence!
You're so annoying!
Well you just won't smile!
It's just like with
Mister Sakata back then! (In S7)
He also attacked me
That was close!
But I can laugh!
Well, well.
Being persistent is valid
They just wouldn't laugh!
It's not against the rules
It can't be helped
Sorry!
I have to clean up
A broom!
We don't have any brooms!
I'll do that right away
I like how intense Seiya is!
I feel like he targeted me
Always
-Huh?
-What's that?
That again?
Huh?
You can hear it, right?
On a trip
From Michinoku!
The mic's off
A trip from Michinoku
From your own...
Your own Michinoku!
She borrowed the glasses
She asked to borrow them.
A travel from Michinoku!
Michinoku!
Your own travel from Michinoku!
What's going on?
Your own Michinoku
A trip from Michinoku!
Michinoku from trip!
-What's going on?
-I don't get it
What's that?
I wasn't expecting that face
She asked to borrow them
I wish I didn't
It's like the whole "besharu" gag
-So you covered it...
-That sort of thing
You know, I was waiting for that
Instead of the trip from Michinoku
I was waiting for it
Like the talk, talking
Time to talk...
Something like that
Huh?
What's that?
A crocodile?
What? A crocodile?
There it is!
It's real!
What's that?
-Crocodile meat?
-You can buy that?
Your act is... too redneck
Stop eating
inedible crap!
His gags have all been
about crap like that
Right?
How does it taste?
How is it?
How is it in terms of a performer? (EN: 7)
Performer?
Tagawa Yousuke
I don't get it
And how do you feel inside?
Like Takahashi Hideki-san
That's pretty fancy
Fancy, right?
And the aftertaste?
Takeshi-san.
That's pretty huge...
You shouldn't use
Takeshi-san's name in vain
We had a broom!
We have all kinds
of stuff in here!
Ah! Master!
-Good morning!
-Master?
Huh?
Who's that?
Who is that?!
Master Kiyoshi... (EN: 8)
Good job
His face is huge
Did he have a body like that?!
Those are great pecs!
A perfect triangle!
An isosceles triangle
This early in the morning
Master Kiyoshi, what are you—
This is kinda fun
"I'm feeling sick"
So you can't speak?
I see, I see.
He's writing
What happened?
Are you alright?
It's like FRISK
What's that, Master Kiyoshi?
Thank you!
That's a lot!
He's like a young senior
Master Kiyoshi...
That's a lot of FRISK,
Master Kiyoshi
Huh?
Ah!
Give me some more
Junior-san's in trouble
Give me some FRISK
Master
They're great
He laughed, he laughed!
Goto's in trouble too!
Thank you very much, master!
I think he was laughing!
"But I can rap"
You can rap, Master?
I didn't know that!
I'm sure he has a sore throat
Rap?
You can do it?
Here we go!
Are you alright?
On the back... Seiya-san
Here we go, Master
I think he's feeling sick, though
Is your mic alright?
Here we go, Master
Here we go!
What happened?
That's amazing
Huh?!
That's a lot of BB pellets
That's a lot of them
So he felt sick
I'm sorry for hogging the FRISK!
FRISK?
They survived?
You ate too many FRISK
They were all stuck
in my throat!
That's a lot!
I've been eating them
since Kiyoshi's time
That's a lot of them
Well, you're Kiyoshi-kun, right?
Sorry! This guy's just
obsessed with FRISK!
Master Sakata (EN: 9)
He puked a lot of FRISK
on his first appearance!
And not a single soul laughed!
You were living together...
We get along
Kiyoshi! You can't pull crap like this!
So can he rap?
What happened?
For a long time,
you've been pulling crap
Time and time again
How is it?
Are you alright?
This is it.
This was an everyday thing
in Gion (in Kyoto)
All the time.
Right, Kiyoshi-kun?
But you're Kiyoshi-kun.
Why can't you remember that?
You're Master Sakata, right?
You're not a real Think Tank!
I'm sorry.
But you sure get along
Something happened!
Watch out watch out!
Careful, careful!
Careful, careful, careful!!
It's all inflated!
Come on!
Wait!
Don't kill yourself!
What happened, Master Kiyoshi?!
You're no good!
He's terrible
You can't heat the curry
in the bag, and then tear it!
And drop it like that!
It's an awful impression
Hey, Kiyoshi!
You're one to talk tonight
Leaving your personality aside!
You're nothing more
than an infant, baby!
You say I'm an idiot,
but you're worse!
Yeah! Shikuwasa happy wasa!
Thank you!
Where did your daddy go?!
Your company went bankrupt!
I'll call Yasushi, so wait right here!
Yasushi's coming so let's wait!
What a weird combo
So Master Yasushi's coming?
So he said
Thank you! Action!
Sneezing!
It's the spices!
Let's burn it up!
Let's go home!
Burn the house down!
It really smells!
That curry is crazy!
You've never seen
hip hop like this!
Smoking hip hop!
I'll go on
even surrounded by smoke!
Only concerned
by the present!
Yasushi...
That's a strong smell!
I'm dying!
At my age,
I'm gonna die!
I'm dying!
How am I going to explain
that I died like this? To my family...
Family!
You don't have a family!
I don't have a family
But you guys are family!
Yasushi-kun!
That's... Yasushi?
Kiyoshi-san
Yasushi!
You turned all pink!
What's going on?
This is the real
G-Dragon!
I'm Yasushi
No, I don't remember
Master Yasushi looking like that
What's that performance?
Yasu—
What's that?
Wait, Yasushi-kun!
That's not Yasushi-kun
Master!
That's just a monster
Your opening act
is really weak!
Leave!
Osada...
Huh?
Who are you?
Something came up
Anpanman? (EN: 10)
Anpanman...
It's real Anpanman.
But the needles...
Are you hungry?
That's creepy
I am!
Whoa!
He took all of it
That's hard to eat
Thank you
Currypanman
died right here!
He just screwed up
with the curry...
He destroyed
the spicy curry...
Currypanman
No one died, though
This is amazing
Huh?
Don't cry!
It smells like
Currypanman!
Curry?
It smells like
Currypanman!
It's just curry
Stop stop, that's creepy!
Watch out walking with that!
He was a great man!
-Currypanman?
-Currypanman!
He's not dead!
He was a little tense.
I see
No... I know.
-He's not dead.
-He is.
-He's not dead!
-He is!
-Currypanman is dead.
-We're just eating curry!
Go and take a look!
Take a closer look!
It's curry rice!
Watch out
There he is!
That's just curry
Well, you can judge it
It's curry
His brain has...
His cerebrum has...
You sure like eating that, huh?
What isn't that amazing?
It's so spicy...
You'd eat it
for a penalty game
Yeah, 18 spice curry
I think having burnt it is... you know
This is just too much
It's serious
The whereabouts of
the Skull Stone are— (EN: 11)
Inside Papaya Suzuki's afro!
Where?
What's that?
What happened?
Are you okay?
It's an experiment?
It sure failed
It was a success
It was a huge failure!
You're all charred
You changed your haircut?
You're not growing any more
The experiment failed
Yakko-san's face
That's long!
It wasn't that long
That was the...
main objective, right?
Making her hair
way longer
Like growing it
That's pretty useful, huh?
Growing your hair suddenly
Seems like it's kinda risky though!
Leave it to Doronjo's assessment (EN: 12)
Why have you been
Talking about me
while touching my ass?
Taking that cold attitude again?!
Don't touch my nipples either
Leave it to Doronjo's—
Why?!
Don't touch my ass, man!
I'm not Doronjo!
You're not Doronjo?
Well I think
she's much more Doronjo!
You're right.
I'm meant to be Momoi Kaori (EN: 13)
Kaori
Ah, you're Momoi-san?
That's right.
I came here from LA
Why were you there?
I got married in LA
That's creepy!
Really?
Really? You did?
They showed it at an Okinawa theater.
You didn't know?!
Where was that?
Sorry, I just didn't know
That's right
So you broke up... and came here?
We didn't break up!
Huh?
I'm just back home
So you live there
And your husband...
-Is living there as well?
-That's right
So why was the screening
with Yoshimoto?
Well, you see, the film...
was meant to be screened with Toho
You know Okumura-san, right?
-Okuyama-san?
-Okuyama-san!
He pushed for several releases
with the film production
He used to work in film, right?
He cut us off all of a sudden.
At a live talk.
It was unexpected!
I don't know what's real anymore
That's illegal!
I don't really mind
I was telling Okumura-san
-It's Okuyama-san.
-I was telling Okuyama-san
That shooting a
wedding film was hard
I told him, so it's fine, really
But still, the timing was...
Probably a bit awkward, you know?
You're right.
You'd think there'd be a place for that.
-Because Okumura-san was saying
-She's really talkative
that it would be a huge scoop
for the reporters as well
that's what Okumura-san said
It's Okuyama-san
Maybe it was Okuyama-san.
He was great for us
but at the same time, you know...
In the end we decided
to host a screening later
So he said that on stage
and then went backstage
You didn't fight because of that?
Well, yeah, you know...
Right... since it was like that...
I had to make sure
we were at an appropriate personal level
That makes sense
And he didn't come back
Well not that it matters
since it was a talk show
And then he said that
me getting married was a bother
But I didn't say I was
You want me to read
some Karuta I brought here? (EN: 14)
You have Karuta right here?
I have a special
Momoi Karuta right here
I wanna see!
So you say it
you say the first character
Well... "Mo"
"Mo", right?
Momoi's Mo is...
Uh... Momoi's "mo"
"Make it black
like lies or like truth"
It was "mo", though
That's "ma"
"mo"
Just a little while ago
It's a little strange
It's so strange
Well, I only have hiragana here
So you don't have everything?
I don't, yeah.
-Do you have "Ta"?
-"Ta", right?
A Karuta game should have it
Right?
Anything goes, really
Doesn't this work?
"Tasked with life"
That's "ta", right?
It's kinda... concrete.
That's a collection
of Momoi's phrases.
What abour "Re"?
"Re", right?
"Re", huh?
"Take the soup,
throw out the shrimp!"
No, "re".
That's "ta"
"Take the— Take the soup"
"Re", "re", "re"!
Do "re"
This is pretty difficult
I might not be understanding
She's totally smiling, though
"Mo", right?
She's smiling
I think this might be...
That's too much
"Dreams are like lies"
Do "mo", please!
She said she doesn't have "mo"
It's Momoi's "mo", after all
-Huh?
-It's Momoi's "mo"
So that's why you don't have it?
What about "re"?
"Re", right?
I love this one
"Take the soup,
throw out the shrimp!"
He totally laughed!
He laughed out loud!
That's a red!
A direct red!
You're out, man!
Wait a second!
Change that!
What's with the shrimp?!
You laughed
on your own!
It's because of the shrimp soup!
Well this is just...
I think we all know who it was
This might be a red!
It's my first one!
I think we have to take a look
Do you have "re"?
"Re", right?
I love this one
"Take the soup
,throw out the shrimp!"
He laughed out loud!
You're out!
It's my first one!
You laughed!
-No, no, no!
-You did
No, no, no, no!
Momoi-san sure does talk, huh?
Momoi-san does talk a lot
She sure does!
She just wouldn't stop
Well, well
Well, precisely because
she was leading you
-I'll keep it low...
-I'm sorry!
And so
-Yellow
-I'm sorry
No second chances
-Understood
-You almost got a red
But it's yellow
I'll die!
Eat the bread!
Whoa!