It's actually quite difficult to matchmake for this
This is her first appearance, Yuriyan Retriever
This is a battle between 10 contestants, so I try to avoid having overlapping characters
But also not people who repel each other
Girl, another girl
Women-only?
So maybe all women except him?
Why me? What am I capable of?
I actually thought about having a women-only contest too
This is like a group dating now, you guys are having a good time, huh?
But that could end up going on the wrong track
So we've decided to put some men in
So hot...
What the heck are you doing?
That's too much...
I'm not the goodwill ambassador of nipples, dude!
Please wait for a while
Wait until Daigo is finished
Please learn to wait
How long have you been a comedian? Please learn.
Shoji-san
Yellow card
Because you clearly said  "Ta-ha"
Come on guys, let's go slowly
Agreed, that's better
This is going to last long, so you'll be tired, right? Shoji-san
I think I'll take a nap   -No, you can't
Let's start
It started
Let's calm down
What are you doing Kurosawa?
I wrote "don't laugh" on it
You should know the rules already
I feel like I'm going to forget, so...
Are you still feeling a bit nervous?
So she wrote this to alert herself   -Are you fine?
I'm fine
(Are you fine?)
Kurosawa, are you fine?
I'm fine
Oh, is this soda?
It's written on it
Oh, it says soda water
Daigo, right? Daigo was close
That's definitely Daigo
Wait a second, wait a second, seriously?
Daigo definitely laughed at that one
Because I heard it behind my back
Which makes you imagine
Yes, because I didn't see that
What's so funny about it?
What's so funny?
Because he did it behind my back
"Pushuu--...Oh, is this soda?"
I won't laugh if I saw it
Kurosawa, are you fine?
I'm fine
Oh, is this soda?
It's written on it
Oh, it says soda water
I thought it's water
This is quite difficult to judge
Because it accumulated
He's always laughing slightly
So it accumulated
Daigo, yellow   -I understand
Well, it's just yellow, so still a long way ahead
But I hope you can try harder to keep a poker face
Got it
Okay, let's go slowly
Yeah, we're in a spin
Can I tell you guys a story then?
Yeah, sure
Let's start
It started
Do you guys know about that?
This man that appears in dreams
Eh? What's that?   -I heard about that
You did?
It's really scary
In overseas countries, a women had a counselling for mental illness
And she said this same man always appears in her dreams
And she never met this man in real life
So the doctor asked her "how does he looks like", and drew his face
And she's like "Oh, it's him!"
The doctor said "So this is the man who appeared in your dreams, okay"
And he left the drawing on the table
After a while, another patient came in
And she asked "Why is he here? The man who always appears in my dreams?"
Remember, she's another patient
The doctor was surprised and asked "this man appeared in your dreams too?"
And after the doctor published it
Hundreds of people from all over the world, said they saw the same man in their dreams
And this, is the man
When this picture was published, people from all over the world said "this man appeared in my dreams too"
So scary
When I saw this picture
I thought like "Huh?!"
He looks exactly the same as someone I know when he was young
Who?   -Please take a look at this
They look the same
Incredible   -Shimura-san?...
Shimura-san when he was young
This man who appeared in the dreams of people all over the world
If you ask what did he do in their dreams?
He gives people relationship advice
Relationship advice?
Shimura-san gives advice?
Oh, is this soda?
So heavy
He said it's so heavy
Because he's carrying a steel on his back
What do you think? Did you ever co-star with Shimura-san?
Nope
Can you do Dafunda (Shimura's gag) for us?
Dafunda
You don't watch other people's gags, huh?
I don't
Dafunda should...   -Dafunda
Make your eyes cross first
And make a funny face
Good, looking good
And then please say it
Dafunda
You never watch other people's gags, huh?
Won't you be worried about overlapping with other's gags?
Did your gags ever overlapped with others?
Gags that overlapped with others...
Oh, yes there is
My gag "Bonjour, mademoiselle, kakimazeru (stir it up)"
Who's gag did it overlap with?
Ikemen (handsome)...I am...
*The original phrase is "Ramen, Tsukemen, I am ikemen (handsome)", which is a gag from Kanoh Eiko (Season 5)
Ikemen...
Tsukemen...
I am...Nuke (idiot)...
I knew it
It's Daigo, right?
Fujimon is suspicious too
He can't say it at all
Because I don't know about it   -Not at all
He's not saying it properly at all
I don't know about his gags
Tsukemen...I am...Nuke...
What do you mean by Nukemen? Please just say it smoothly
I wonder who it will be
I'm sure it's me
Let’s judge this matter
I think I laughed
Well, there's more than one person
And I think it's Daigo
Daigo is smiling all the time
Yes, he's always smiling
He's smiling even when he's talking
So Daigo...
Eh? Please wait a second
That one just now should be Fujimon-san
No, no, I only let out a "hun" sound
So you said "hun"?   -Yes, but...
He said it, he laughed
Then it's Fujimon
All I said is "hun"
Ikemen (handsome)...I am...
Ikemen...
Tsukemen...
I am...Nuke (idiot)...
Look, he's laughing
No, I'm not laughing
I'm not laughing, right?   -Seems like you didn't
That should count as safe, huh?
Probably safe
That shouldn't be counted, that's too harsh   -Yes, too harsh
Umm...how should this be judged
That's too harsh
Okay, okay, got it
So everyone is safe   -Hooray!
Thank you very much
Just say it smoothly, please!
Oh, it should be Ramen, right?
Why did you say Nukemen then...
Because I thought I have to say something
What does Nukemen even mean?
He even said Bokumen...
Bokumen...
He knows nothing about other's gags
Let's start
Fujimon always watch other's gags, right?
I watch a lot
Can you do that "Ikemen, Tsukemen" gag?
Of course I can
You remember those moves?
You don't really need to move though
It has some moves like this...
What's your favorite gag recently?
Gags that you want to do recently
Gags that I want to do recently?
The new Haneda Tokyo International Airport
Tanoshingo...
Who's gag is that?   -Tanoshingo
That's pretty old though
You thought it's better to do old gags?
I bet he likes old things
Yes, I like old things
Old gags are more promising (teppeki)
Teppekin!!
*Teppekin is the catchphrase of a famous deodorant beads CM by Suzuki
*https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Rpz5FweaWYg
That's not a gag though
That's not a gag...   Teppekin!!
That's not a gag
If he (Suzuki) sees you do this...   -He's gonna feel unpleasant
Because that's not a gag
But Shoji-san is promising (teppeki) too, right?
Huh?
Please say it again
Shoji-san, how long have you been a comedian? 40 years?
42 years
That's really promising (teppeki)
Teppeki?
Fujimon always watch other's gags, he's really promising (teppeki)
Teppekin!!
And Shoji-san is very promising (teppeki) as well
What's up?
Let's cook something, shall we?
-Sounds good! There's many girls in here
-Yeah, the girls can cook well
It's rare to have so many girls in here, so...
Girls, girls, girls, huh?
If you think women should cook, then you're making a big mistake!
Women should cook, women should wash clothes, women should clean up the room?
No, that's not what we meant
We just thought girls can cook well
We can cook well
Then it should be fine, right?
People who can cook well, have to cook?
No, well, there's no need to get angry for this
There're four girls here, so let's ask them to cook something?
That's not what we meant...
You guys have been treating girls like this all the time, right?
What do you guys want to eat?
Well, just whatever is in the refrigerator
If you want an Oden (one-pot dishes), please decide the ingredients
For example, Konjac, Goboten (root vegetable)
Please decide it first
Anything is fine with me
Anything is fine...
There's always that one person saying things like this
If you don't tell us, then we won't know, dude
Same for the broth, it could have Konbu, Katsuo or Niboshi
It's different in different region too
What happened, girls?
What's going on with all these man in here?
Excuse me
They kept asking us to cook for them, very annoying
These dudes should just go ahead and suck women's breast!
We are always ready to let you dudes suck
All we asked for is to cook for us
In our world, you don't get to eat if you don't spread your legs
*The original phrase is a Japanese idiom:
"You don't get to eat if you don't work"
Exactly
And when we say mata (legs), it's not the mata meaning again (same pronounciation)
Why did you add that?
There's always that one person like this within a group
Don't try to analyze us, dude!
Don't kick things, seriously, Haruna
I'm not Haruna, I'm Reiko
Remember my name
What is your title? Like the Reiko from something...
I'm the Reiko at the window*
*From "Totto-Chan: The Little Girl at the Window", an autobiographical memoir written by Japanese television personality Tetsuko Kuroyanagi
Remember that
That's from Yanagi-san...
Totto-Chan...
My name is Kasae
What's your catchphrase?
The arrogant and outrageous Kasae at the roadside
That's so long
The arrogant and outrageous Kasae at the roadside?
I was found at the roadside   -Oh, I see
Oh, so you're an abandoned child?
I'm not an abandoned child!
Yes you are   -You're an abondoned child
You were found at the roadside
Don't treat people like an abandoned child
Because you said you were found at the roadside
So, Kasae-san?
How do you spell it?
Kasae's Ka is Kagawa's Ka
Kasae's Sa is Satou's Sa
Do you mean the Sa with ninben (written as 佐)?
No, the one with ishihen (written as 砂)
Oh, so sugar (Sa with ishihen means sugar)   -Sugar?
The sweet sugar   -Oh, I see
And E is Katagana
That's an odd name
What about you, what's your name?
I'm Marin from Kitakyushu
I'm Marin with the best pussy in Kitakyushu
The best pussy?
Yes, the best pussy
So every man will be intoxicated after...
After trying Marin-san's pussy?
They say I'm like an octopus sticking to them
What's your name?
I'm Kuniko
Kuniko?
I'm Yamada Katsutenai Kuniko!*
*"Kuni-chan no Yamada Katsutenai" is
a variety show hosted by Yamada Kuniko
So you gals are not going to cook for us, right?
Sorry for making you gals upset
Where is Shoji-san?
Shoji-san didn't appear for a while
I've just remembered this, but...
I won the Yamanashi (Prefecture) championship of egg-flying contest
Egg-flying contest?
What do you mean by Yamanashi championship?
Well, Yamanashi championship, Egg-flying championship
What egg is it?   -It's quail eggs
Why are you taking off your pants?   -No...
You need to put this quail egg
In your butthole
And make the egg fly out of your butt
You won the contest?
Yes, I won the contest
Can we have this contest here?
Do Yamanashi (Prefecture) have these vulgar contests?
Excuse me!
Someone, please give me some Kumis
*Shoji-san is wearing the costume of people living in the remote valleys of Kyrgyzstan's mountain region, producing the traditional drink of fermented mare's milk, 'Kumis'
Huh?
Give me some Kumis
Ba...?   -Some Banyuushu (Kumis)
We're having a traffic jam over here
Excuse me
Kumis?   -Yes, Kumis
Kumis? Well, Mr. Kumis
Some Kumis...
Excuse me, where are you from?
Eh?
Where are you from?
From Hirakata (city)...   -From Hirakata?
In Osaka?   -No, no...
I'm from Ulaanbaatar...   -You changed it
What is your name?
Ari...Arisalau
Pardon me?
Arisalau...
Why didn't you decide it beforehand?
You know we're gonna ask you about this, right?
No, I don't know...
Which part did you expect people to laugh?
Please look back and tell us which part
Please look back and tell us which part should we laugh...
Don't look back like this
Please come in and do it again, and raise your hand when you expect us to laugh
Oh, okay, I see
The part that you expect all of us to laugh
Show us what was your plan   -Okay
Sorry, Jimmy-san   -No problem
Excuse me
Okay, please come in
Here he comes...
Please give me some Kumis
Not here?
Kumis? What is Kumis?
It's here
Oh, that's it?
-So that's why he didn't have a clear answer
-Yeah, because he expected it to end here
You're really promising (tepekki), Shoji-san
Yes, I am, because young people don't do these kinds of gags nowadays
Young people nowadays...
Tepekki...
Tepekki?
He totally...
What happened?
He was surprised?
Shall we do this then?
Can you really do this?
Yes, well...
Quail egg-flying...Yamanashi championship
It flew out?   -Yes
It's not Yamanashi championship though, it's quail egg-flying championship
It's a quail egg-flying championship in Yamanashi
Did you win the contest, though?   -Yes, I won
How far did it fly?
Eh...about 3 meters
Eh? That's amazing, honestly
How should we prepare for this?
Well, this is done in a unique way, so in your butthole
Where should the audience watch this?
Eh? Just watch it fly out
Can we watch it from the side?   -Yes, you can see it fly out
We can see your butt clearly, are you fine with that?
Well, just watch the quail egg fly out
Is this going to work?
Hey, hey, eww...
Well...this...umm...
The quail egg will fly out
The quail egg will fly out?
Eww...he's putting it in
Oh my god   -I don't think it'll fly out
Yes, it will fly out
No way, it won't   -Yes, it will, it can fly
Please give me a moment, I'll put it in
Be careful, be careful!
Jimmy-san, that's so dangerous
The quail egg fell on the floor
Please wait a second, the quail egg will fly out   -No way, it won't
The quail egg?
Do it over here, get down on all fours   -Good idea
Better do it over here
Oh, I see
Did you really win the contest?   -Yes, I did
Huh?
Maybe I'm a little bit nervous
Wow, it's going in   -It fits?
It's going in! It's going in!
This should work, right?
Yeah, it went in, it went in   -3 meters?
It went in?   -Yes, it went in
Is this going to work?   -Are you okay?
Ah, it went in, it really went in!
Ewww...
How many meters did it fly?
Huh? Where is it?
On the floor...   -It fell on the floor
So it won't fly
No, it did fly during the contest
For 3 meters?   -Yes, 3 meters
I was looking forward to it
I thought it will fly like "pon---"   -That will be hilarious
It's gonna be funny if it flew like "pon---"
This is hand soap...
What are you doing again, Jimmy-san?
(He always washes his hair and his face)
Because...
I did something dirty just now
Why did you wash your hair though?
Well, because it's dirty   -Wash your butt then
You didn't use your hair just now
No, I need to wash my hair, or else it's dirty, right?
No, the problem is your butt
(Exactly)
You're not going to wash your butt?   -I'll just leave my butt like this
No, but...
I actually want to try it one more time
You want a last chance?
May I?
Will it fly out like "pon---"?
The egg crashed inside, so it's slimy now...
It flew out
He clearly laughed
Come on, that's self-destruction
Is that the one in his butt?
I don't know   -Eh? So scary
Is it the one right here?   -Yes
That's the one in his butt
Seriously?
What happened?
Jimmy-san laughed of his own accord
What's so funny?
That dude spat out the egg that was in my butt
And that was funny?
He clearly laughed, and at a strange moment
He clearly laughed but let's take a look
Will it fly out like "pon---"?
The egg crashed inside, so it's slimy now...
He's trying to hold back here
The face of him holding back was funny
I don't understand that one
I don't understand either   -That's a self-destruction
What was that?   -I totally self-destructed
I didn't expect him to put that dirty thing in his mouth
Yellow card, Jimmy
I just have to accept this   -Yes
And what were you trying to do with that quail egg?
What is that Yamanashi championship?
You're lying, right?   -No, it's true
There couldn't be such event
It really did, in a snack bar
In a snack bar?   -Yes
Oh, I see   -So a snack bar in Yamanashi?
Yes, a snack bar in Yamanashi
Did it really flew out?
I told you it flew out
Can someone put it in my butthole for me?
It probably won't appear vulgar if it can fly out like "pon--"
So can someone put it in for me?
Did you know?   -Huh?
These girls were...   -What?
Looking at Jimmy-san as if they were looking at a trash
No problem, I don't mind at all
It will fly out, right?
Yes, just let someone put it in for me
Why did you wash your hair just now?   -Yeah, why?
Because it's dirty, right?
Your butt is dirty   -You're hair is clean
You can just put it in with chopsticks
No, no, that's too dangerous
I'll put on some lotion
Put lotion on first?   -Yes, I'll put some lotion on
Are you ready?   -Yes
Is it really going to fly out?   -I told you it will
(I really hope it'll fly)
Can't believe you're doing this, Fujimon
Will poop come out?   -No, poop won't come out
Really?   -Yes, really, really
I'll do it properly...
Hey...that's too much...and not there...
No need to put it on the sides!
I told you that's not necessary
Only the hole, dude
Only the hole
(Why is he putting it around his butt?)   -Only the hole
Ouch, it hurts! And I told you only the hole
Ouch, ouch, it hurts
Just put it in quickly
I told you it hurts
What the heck are you doing?
Are you the one who asked me to wait at your anus?
Nope...
Are you the one who asked me to wait at your anus?   -No, I didn't...
I'm the gang boss, Takahara
Can I ask him to put it in now?
Come on, just put it in quickly
Please, just put it in
It's incredible if it really flies out
Which one? Where is the hole?
There's a hole down there right?
(There's a hole right...)
Right there, right there, the hole
Yes, right there, did you put it in?
Wait a second, not yet
Put it in quickly
It went in, it went in!
It went in?
Let's go
Probably need another one
Why putting in two...
One more?   -One is already in it though?
It will fly out if you put in two
It's gonna be stuck
One more? You're not making a large-sized fried rice, dude!
Can you shut up, please?
We're still working on this
Is this going to work?   -Yes, I think it will if you put one more in
There's two in it now
It's in it, right?   -Yes, unbelievable
It's in it?   -Do you need one more?
That's awful   -Enough, this is enough
I'll make it fly now
Okay, let's go
Ready, set...
It's stuck   -It went inside
It won't come out anymore
I'll try to slap your ass, okay?
Are you ready?   -Yes
Your poop is going to come out, dude
Let's stop   -This is not working
This is enough
It went inside, right?   -What are you going to do with it?
Yeah, it went inside   -Is it fine for it to stay inside?
It went inside already
Those two eggs are still inside
Someday, someday, it will come out...
Hey! It's gonna come out as a bird
You're saying the wrong joke all the time
The egg will rotten while staying inside
No, it's okay, it will come out when it comes out
It's gonna become century eggs, you know, century eggs
Shoji-san...
Please behave yourself
(Well, he's right)
Will it come out as poop?
Did it ever stuck inside before?
Did it ever stuck inside before?   -What stuck inside?
The quail egg
I'm not in a good condition today
There're 2 eggs inside, please remember that
Yes, there're 2 eggs inside
What are you doing?
What is he doing?
You're not going to wash your butt?
Please take a seat
Sit down with this thing inside?
He's the one who did this
He did it himself
He did it and he laughed   -Come on
What happened?
I didn't expect it to be so quiet
You bursted into laughter
This one is hard to judge too
Mastumoto-san...
Daigo and Jinnai, maybe...
Umm...no...
Am I right?
I saw Daigo laughed, so I thought it's safe
Come on...
There're 2 eggs inside
What are you doing?
What is he doing?
Please take a seat
Sit down with this thing inside?
What about Jinnai?
-Daigo clearly laughed, but Jinnai..,
-Yeah, Daigo is the one who laughed
Really? You laughed after Daigo laughed?
I saw Daigo laughed, so I thought it's safe...
Well, let's take a look at Jinnai
This could be a double kill depending on the situation
Sit down with this thing inside?
He's already smiling here
And after this...
Jinnai...   -Jinnai laughed at the same time!
They laughed at the same time
So Jinnai, yellow card
And Daigo
Orange card
I'm in trouble, I'm in trouble
Oh my god, that sound was awful
Okay, so let's restart
It started
Did you guys ever play the puzzle ring?
Puzzle ring?   -Yes, I did
I'm really good at it
Please let me show it to you guys
So basically to unfasten this puzzle ring
And then?
What the heck is wrong with this thing!
What's wrong with this thing!
You won't be able to solve the puzzle if you become irritated
Chan Noah?*
*Similar pronunciation as puzzle ring (chi-e-no-wa)
Who the heck is Chan Noah?
Chan Noah!
I'm Chan Noah
Chan Noah
Are you an English teacher?
I'm Chan Noah
No, you're not
Both of them are trying to Boke
Sorry for keeping you waiting
The is the ramen that you've ordered
So tiny...
This ramen is so tiny...
What's this?
This is for the person who ordered Okowa
*Okowa is Japanese steamed rice dish
Not me   -Who ordered Okowa?
Fujimon right?   -Probably Fujimon
He said he wants Okowa
Or do you want this tiny ramen?
You ordered Okowa, right?
Why Okowa...
Here comes your large-sized Nama Beer
Daigo-san and Fujimon-san
Your large-sized Nama Beer   -Thank you
Cheers   -Cheers
It looks even smaller like this
It's really refreshing, huh?
That's what we're proud of
That's what you're proud of?   -Yes
Do you drink with your wife?
Akina?
Yu...Yukina?
Yukina? Is her name Yukina?
How many followers does she have on N...NSN?
It's SNS   -Yeah, SSN
SNS   -SS...
He's completely messed up
SNS
NS...   -It's SNS
What does SNS stand for? Shoji-san?
S...
SNS   -S, N, S, they all stands for something
Story...
Please say it quickly
Story?
Story...   -It's awkward if it takes too long
Because I don't know   -Just say it quickly
N for News, and S for short
SN...
Story News Short?
It could be anything, just say it quickly   -Exactly
It's all about speed when it comes to these things, Shoji-san
But I can't speed up anymore now
Just say it smoothly
SNS
What does MC stands for?
Huh?   -Someone is here
Microsoft
That's MS
Mi...micro...   -Wait...
He got nothing right
Yo, yo...
This place is full of tension, huh?
Excuse me, who are you?
I'm Akira   -Akira-san?
Where are you from?
Godo Retto   -Wow
In Nagasaki?
Nice to meet you
I'm quite good at crisis management, however...
This place is truly full of tension
What brought you here?
I heard that it's full of tension here
You mean here?   -So I thought I have to go there
You like places full of tension?
I want to compete in a place full of tension
Compete for what though?
You guys are competing for something, right?
So I thought what's going on here?
And so...
What do you do for work, by the way?
Akira-san, are you working?
I'm working a lot
What do you do for work?   -I'm free
Free, free, free   -Do you mean Freeter?
Not Freeter?   -Free, free
You mean Freeter, right?   -I told you it's Free
I do anything
What are you doing now, Akira?
Abs workout
You're always working out?   -Yes, I'm working out
I'm asking you guys to stop
Where the heck are you from?
I'm living at the park over there
And it's really noisy over here, so I'm asking you guys to be quiet
This place is under my control
I'm the one who allowed the gangs to control here
And I'm the one who controls the gangs
No, I'm the one
I'm the one who's in control, I'm the one who allowed all these shops to open here
And I'm the one who took money from these shops
And I'm the one who made those money, for all Japanese citizens
I'm the one who made those papers
I'm the one who chose the tree and chopped it down
I'm the one who chose the tree, and chopped it down, and peeled it into paper, and printed those money
Why are you talking like that?
Why am I talking like this? Then why are you talking like that?
You don't have the upper right teeth, huh?
I do have the upper right teeth
Yes, I do
I'm the one who made all those teeth
No, I'm the one, I'm the one
No, I'm the one
I'm the one who made all those teeth
I'm a dentist
Both of you are lying, all the time!
You're lying!
You look dirty
People like you always lie
I was a pilot before
You're lying!
I was indeed a pilot before
I was a pilot too, I was also an astronaut
Me too, me too
I was the first person to be on the moon!
So many strange people here
Is it fine to let them argue here? Waitress?
Umm...please behave yourself
I am behaving myself
Someone's here
They're arguing now
Excuse me
What happened?
I have metal allergy
Because you're wearing this thing, right?
But then you don't have any red spots over here, huh?
It's even on your face
Theses are herpes   -Oh, those are herpes
How dare you come out with just that?
Huh?
Well, I just wanted to show you all my metal allergy
Metal allergy, and that's it?
That's it
That's all I want to show you guys
Your performance   -Yes, performance
We all came fully prepared for the contest
So please don't show things like that   -I'm sorry
Sorry, I'm sorry
Please don't say that
That's the style of our performances
Well, yeah
We didn't learn other kinds of performances from Akashiya Sanma*
*Shoji-san and Jimmy-san both belongs to the Sanma Family, led by Akashiya Sanma
We didn't learn those proper performances
What did you learn from Sanma-san?
Okay, what's next?
Maybe let someone out?
Okay, let someone out
Excuse me!
Eh?
I have the most Guinness World Records in Japan
I'm Cherry Yoshitake!
Thank you, Cherry Max!
Oh, Cherry-san
Shiratori's fiancee   -Thank you very much
Congratulations   -Congratulations
Thank you very much
He's actually my helper
Eh? Daigo-san's helper?   -Yes
I became friends with Cherry recently
And Cherry is incredible
He has many Guinness world records
Look, he really has a lot
Wow, amazing   -Incredible
He holds many records
It's rare to see world records in real life, right?
Never saw one
So, let's ask him to show it to us   -May I?
I heard about you before   -Thank you
Cherry is doing a radio show, right?
Yes, thank you very much
He's doing it with a partner   -I'm doing it with Neko Hiroshi
At where?   -At Kiba Studio
Who the heck will even listen to it?
People living at Kiba will listen to it, right?
Who the heck will listen to Neko Hiroshi and Cherry's radio show?
What are you going to show us?
I'll move 29 beans to this bin with straw within 30 seconds
Incredible
The current world record is 29 beans
Eh? Incredible
So if he can reach 30 beans within 30 seconds today
Eh? Will this be approved?
If this can be approved, then that's a new world record
So, there's many seniors here
Cherry is probably nervous too
Within 30 seconds?
Yes, 30 seconds
I'm ready   -Are you ready?
Ready, start!
1, 2, 3...(counting)
There's still plenty of time left
10 seconds have passed
20 seconds have passed
5, 4, 3, 2, 1
Time's up!   -28 beans
Time's up!   -That's 28 beans
Cherry, time's up
Cherry, Cherry   -Cherry?
Cherry, time's up!
Cherry!
Cherry!!
Cherry!!!
Daigo...   -Daigo-san
Time's up!
Daigo-san...   -Cherry!
Daigo...
Time's up
I'm sorry
I really wanted to break world records   -Sorry guys
No problem, that's fine
He's really focused
Yeah, he's concentrated, so...
But Daigo is being too harsh
You're outrageous
Please stop him gently
Sorry   -You got it?
I'll challenge another world record now
What's this, Cherry?
I'll ring the bell with my jaw within 30 seconds
That sounds quite easy   -I'll challenge this
Within 30 seconds?   -Yes
Ready...   -I'm ready
Start
He'll probably break the record for this one
10 seconds have passed
20 seconds have passed
Hurry up!
5, 4, 3, 2, 1
Stop!
Cherry, stop
Cherry!
Hey, no, no
Cherry!   -Cherry, stop
Cherry!!!
Daigo...   -Cherry!
Cherry!   -Daigo...
Cherry!
Stop! Cherry!
Cherry, stop
Hey no, Daigo
It's not a big deal
No need to stop him like that
Because he doesn't stop   -Well yeah, it's Cherry's fault too
Can you really break the world record like this?
Eh?   -Huh?
Because he's not stopping at all
And Daigo will become angry at you
Would you be able to stop?
Yes, I'll stop
Shall we shout like "Stop!"
Yes, I need someone to shout it out loud
Just shout like "Stop!"
Okay, so we will shout "Stop!" together
Thank you
So, let's challenge this world record?
Oh, what's that?
I'll suck in the tape of the crackers within 30 seconds
I'll set of the cracker
Ready, start!
Almost got that one
10 seconds have passed
20 seconds have passed
Not much time left
Go go go
5, 4, 3, 2, 1
Stop!
Stop!   -Stop! Stop!
It's over!
Hey Daigo...
Cherry!!!
Daigo, that's your fault
Hey Daigo
Daigo kept setting of the cracker
Even after we said stop
He's not stopping at all! You guys clearly said stop
Because Daigo you kept setting it of
Because you kept setting it of, of course he'll suck it
Of course he has to suck it
Sorry guys   -No, no problem
How do you feel now, Cherry-san?
I feel sorry for not being able to break the world record
That's it?   -Yes, of course
What do you think about Daigo then? Nothing?   -Yes
You feel thankful, right?
Thank you, Cherry Max
That one was quite small, huh?   -Yes
The pose is different from the first time
You did it differently on purpose, huh?
How did you do the pose when you said thank you to me for the first time?
That was small, huh? How should it actually be?
Thank you, Cherry Max!
Why didn't you do that for the first time!!!
Daigo, Daigo-san...
Why didn't you do that right from the beginning!!!
Daigo   -Daigo-san
You're gonna lose if he fights back
Cherry, thank you very much   -That was awesome
Thank you very much
Can I have your attention please?
What happened?
Within these 2 or 3 hours
I found out something   -What did you find out?
There's a terrible person among us
Huh? Among us?   -There couldn't be
What's this? Suspense?
I already know the truth
That's you!
"A dangerous person"
What's going on?
What does that mean?   -The bear?
She said there's a terrible person among us
So the bear is the dangerous person?
Is there someone inside?
No idea
What's going on?
I just have to wait until Yuriyan is back
Where did Yuriyan go?
Ah, she's back
Please believe me
For what?   -Believe you for what?
I'm from the future
What's this thing here?
Are those your eyes?
Those are not my eyes
Those are my eyes (making fun of Fujimon's Kansai dialect)
It's Shishito pepper (brand name)
Shishito pepper?   -You're working at Shishito?
Well, Shishitou's "tou", is Minshintou's "tou" (Democratic Party)
Oh, so the Shishi Party
You're talking nonsense
What's that "Dangerous person"?   -Yeah, exactly
Who's that? The "dangerous person"?
This bear is the dangerous person?
Or do you mean someone is inside?
Wow, so dangerous
What are you here for? From the future
To bring in the laundry
Hey, dude!
Why didn't you expand the conversation like you did just now, when I'm the one performing?
You're being so indifferent to me
Fujimon actually did try to expand
Yes, I did
No way, not at all   -Yes, I did
But even if I try to expand...
Nothing...
Don't treat people like a handkerchief, you idiot!
Like a tiny, tiny handkerchief
What do you mean?
So it won't stretch
And it's impossible to expand
Isn't it better to say like a tissue? If you mean to pull out something
I'll take that
Your hands are shaking like a leaf
Are you really writing it down?   -Yes, I am
Amazing! Your palm lines are incredible
Yes, someone told me about that too
You'll live a long and healthy life   -Yes, exactly
The palmist Hosoki Kazuko said I'll become popular at the age of 75
Exactly, your palm lines say so, I can totally see this!
I'm almost there   -Yeah
I'm 60 years old now   -Work hard! Work hard!
Work hard! Work hard! Work hard!
Uchuchuchuchu...
Work hard!
You'll become popular at the age of 75?
Will you become popular?
Ms.Hosoki said so
Apologize to her!
Apologize to Ms.Hosoki
Ms.Hosoki is the one...   -But Ms.Hosoki sometimes get it wrong too
Never!
She got everything right
Say it clearly, ok?
"You..."
"Good!"
"You will become popular at the age of 75!"
"George-san"
That's what she said
Eh? But I'm Shoji...
And that scene was aired too
Did she mistaken you for someone else?
That's why I'm trying to make both of them my name
Both Shoji and George
You're just Shoji though
Nope, if someone call me George, I'll turn around too
George-san?   -Yes?
Look
Fatal Attraction (Kiken na Jyouji ≈ George)
Sharon Stone   -Sharon Stone...
Basic Instinct   -Stones from the top
What are you doing Jimmy-san?
Well...umm...I'm just...
What are you doing since...
Are you a "rucksuck"?
Are you a "rucksuck", dude?
It should be rucksack   -Oh...
Yeah, rucksack...
I just said "taha"
Naturally   -Very naturally
Like a habit
Naturally, you laughed naturally
No, I didn't laugh
You laughed   -That's a Tsukkomi
No, no, you laughed naturally...
That's a kind Tsukkomi from your Senpai, you idiot!
Even if you speak in a loud voice, you clearly laughed
I think someone laughed naturally, right?
It's him!
No way, it's Shoji-san   -Just take a look
It's Shoji-san, right?
You laughed naturally
No, I didn't laugh
Are you a "rucksuck"?
Are you a "rucksuck", dude?
It should be rucksack   -Oh, yeah, rucksack...
You clearly laughed
Orange card
I just have a smiling face
And he'll be out next time, right?
Yes, he'll be out next time
Your habit of laughing...   -Better stop that
It's impossible to stop a habit
But you have to, or else...
So, let's start
Do you play guitar?
"Last night"
"I saw you in my dream"
"Under the dazzling morning light"
(I think I heard this song before, who's song is this?)
"If you feel like something is going to happen"
"Then come and find me"
(Knock, knock) Someone's inside
(Oh, it's Takajin's song)
"Sometimes it's sunny, Takajin"
"Close your eyes, Imagine"
(Can't believe that you know this song)
"Today will definitely be better than yesterday"
"Sometimes it's sunny, Takajin"
"Be a little rough, Blue jeans"
Why are you looking this way, dude
Wait a second...wait a second...
You did it yourself!
You completely laughed
It's definitely Fujimon   -He completely laughed
Ahh, I screwed up
Wait a second, no, no, Jinnai...
No, it's not me, it's definitely Fujimon
Ahh, this is the worst, I screwed up   -It's definitely Fujimon
You bursted into laughters
Fujimon, you bursted into laughters
He tried to make me laugh, but...
Well, let's take a look
He said "Why are you looking this way, dude"
Well, but...that was actually quite interesting
And I thought how did these people hold back on that
Someone's inside   -Someone's inside
(Oh, it's Takajin's song)
"Sometimes it's sunny, Takajin"
(Everyone held back here)
"Close your eyes, Imagine"
(Can't believe that you know this song)
"Today will definitely be better than yesterday"
"Sometimes it's sunny, Takajin"
"Be a little rough, Blue jeans"
Why are you looking this way, dude
You're laughing from "Blue Jeans"
Yeah, I'm laughing from "Blue Jeans"
Orange card   -Eh?
Suddenly orange card?   -Yes, suddenly orange card
Well, you laughed out loud at that one
So yellow card is not enough   -Well, yes...
Oh crap! Oh crap! Oh crap!
I admit that you tried hard to attack though
And seriously, there's no need to say "someone's inside"
That's not a knock   -Not a knock
Please just watch my performance
I didn't know that
Alright! Let's do this
Did you laugh today, Jimmy-san?
Only once, with a yellow card
Oh, just a yellow card?
Yes, just a yellow card for now
You were out really fast last time
Excuse me
Probably nasal irrigation?
Sorry, please excuse me, I have a stuffy nose
May I do this?
Sure   -Because I have chronic rhinitis
I see, we're in here for quite a while
Yeah, so my nose starts to feel...
Amazing
Aren't you putting in too much?
You do it like this every time?
Every time? With that much?
That's gonna cost you a lot
(Jinnai...)
This feels so good, very refreshing. You guys wanna try it?
No thanks, I'm good
Just do it
Jimmy-san, you wanna try it? You have a stuffy nose too, right?
Well...umm...
Is it refreshing?
Super refreshing
It will spill out though
It feels really good
But Jimmy-san seems to be used to this
Did you try this before, Jimmy-san?
Well...umm...maybe I did
I bet you did this to every hole in your body
Is this fine? That looks painful
Incredible...
Much more came out than it went in?
More than it went in, because of his own saliva and snot
It's doubled
When you put it in, say "ahh" at the same time
It's more stuffed than before
It's more stuffed than before?   -Yes, it's more stuffed
Isn't it refreshing?
I mean over here, the back of my neck
The back of your neck? So the cervical spine?
Yes, the cervical spine   -It's hurting the cervical spine?
Yes, my cervical spine hurts
It hurt your cervical spine?   -Yes
Your neck joints?   -Yes, neck joints
You're talking absolute nonsense   -Eh?
What do you mean by "Eh?"
How do you feel?
Well...umm...that's enough
If you want to feel more refreshed, you can try this (wasabi)
No, seriously, that's gonna destroy my body
You're using this? Fujimon-san?
Yes, I'm using this
I bet you'll feel refreshed
With this? In my nose?   -Yes
It's gonna be painful
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Ouch! Ouch! It hurts!
It really hurts! It really hurts!
Is there anything that can help? Anything?
Oh! I need soda water!
I definitely need soda water for this!
Oh, it's soda water
Only soda water can rescue me
I have to put some soda water in my nose
Ouch!
It hurts! My nose hurts!
You bastard...Fujimori...
I shouldn't have listened to you
Because...because he said Fujimori...
Yes, he did
You're out? Are you out?
That's terrible
This one is hard to judge too
This is just...
Barely, barely safe
It's either Fujimon or Daigo
But either way, that person will be out
I think it should be Daigo
I definitely need soda water for this!
Oh, it's soda water
Only soda water can rescue me
(Daigo is already laughing here)
I have to put some soda water in my nose
Ouch!
My nose hurts!
You bastard...Fujimori...
Barely safe! Barely safe!
Barely safe!   -No, Daigo...
Daigo...   -Barely safe!
Barely safe! Barely safe! Matsumoto-san!
I beg you! Barely safe!
You're out!   -Number one
Number one
You have to accept this
And how many times did you say "it hurts"?
It really hurts so bad
You said it for like 40 times
Because it really hurts, you can give it a try
He really did say it for like 40 times   -Exactly
If you're in a hospital, they're gonna let you go in first
You're saying it for so many times
So the first person is out only until this time, which never happened before
Well, Daigo should be out anyway
Yeah, he's always smiling
He's out even faster this time
That was close
I'm so weak
Maybe I'm too weak, or maybe they're too strong
Of course one will laugh at that
I understand that it's painful to have wasabi in your nose, but...
Something came to his mind, and he went to take the soda water
Oh! I need soda water!
I definitely need soda water for this!
And mistaking the name of his junior, who has been with him for several decades
My nose hurts!
You bastard...Fujimori...
I shouldn't have listened to you
I lost one million for soda water?