There are six contestants this time.
What are some of the new attempt or systems you are trying?
These six are stubborn.
They are tough as rocks.
This time we will include observers of our choosing.
Are observers allowed to laugh?
Of course.
They lighten the mood.
This is the new study.
"Study"?
No, it's the new test.
What's wrong with studying?
Testing is also studying.
Moreover, studying is a sign of a positive attitude.
You got a problem with that?
It's disgusting!
Documental - Season 10
Episode 3  “Activation the Special Rules”
You're really not funny when you're wearing clothes.
Don't....
He laughed.
He is laughing.
Hey, it's not here!
Not here!
Kubota is so close!
Damn!
I blew myself up!
Yellow card.
This is them normally.
Yrah, this is them normally.
So big...
His hand was swollen!
Orange card.
Someone will be here soon.
It will be soon.
I blew it.
I blew myself up.
I got two cards.
That’s too bad.
Coo-chan has two cards.
You and you have one card.
- Kubota has one card, right?
- Yeah.
- Do you have two cards?
- I have one card.
You guys don't have cards?
They do not have a card.
Fujimon, would you like to go?
Yeah!
- Go play with them. If nothing happens, come back.
- Yes.
I will go.
Then I'll restart.
Can I show you my video?
- Can I go first? Because his is very intense.
- Go ahead.
Big hand were hilarious, weren't they?
What are you wearing?
What are you doing?
I was on my....
You always have such bad timing.
I was getting ready in the locker room and you guys started watching videos, so I came over.
Sorry, hold on a second.
I'm here looking for a kappa.
You are not a kappa?
I'm a kappa, so I came here looking for another kappa.
(Note: 1)
Are you looking for a kappa?
One of these people must be a kappa.
Hey, you're a kappa, right?
- I'm not.
- You are like a kappa.
Yuriyan and Zako are already naked.
So...
You call him Zakoshisho.
I don't mind.
He's my senior.
So Yuriyan and Zako are...
You're stubborn.
Do you have a plate on your head?
A plate.
- How do you prove it?
- Yeah, I have a plate.
But you don't have it, right?
You're a kappa, right?
No, I am not a kappa.
The zipper is not closed.
Because you tried to close it yourself.
Then you close this.
No, I don't want to touch the kappa.
I'm just a kappa.
You are a kappa.
- I'm not a kappa.
- Just come.
He is scary.
Kappa.
He was taken by him.
Shappa.
Since they are not there, Kubota's video should not be shown yet.
It can't be helped.
Let's wait.
- Then why don't you watch my video one more time?
- Okay.
But they are not here.
It's okay.
I just want you to look at the big hand I just mentioned.
Then please show it.
- So young!
- This is normal Daisuke&Hanako.
This may look a little strange, but this is a normal photo.
Let's find the three difference.
- Three difference?
- His forehead?
Yeah, correct.
- Her fingers are thin.
- No.
- Her fingers are long.
- Correct!
There's still one left.
- What's that?
- Did he get more teeth?
That is wrong.
- Want to know the answer?
- Yeah.
Look at his ears.
How small ears.
- Very small ears.
- You've never seen ears this small, have you?
He really likes ears.
Let's look at the next one.
This is a normal photo.
- Is this a normal photo?
- Yes, it is.
- He has always had a large face.
This picture clearly shows what Hanako always tells him, that he has a large face.
After all, he has a big face.
Remember this picture.
Three, two, one.
It’s very obvious that his face is huge.
First, Daisuke's face.
And?
The parts of Hanako's face are closer to the center.
The parts are closer to the center.
There is still one more diffelence left?
Is he wearing gloves?
His hand is big.
So let's check it out.
Hanako...
Hey.
They came.
They are wearing kappa masks.
- That is a very realistic mask.
- That's not good timing.
It's a realistic kappa face.
- We are kappa, right?
This is too realistic.
This is not the kappa I imagined. This is scary.
What kind of kappa were you imagining?
I was imagining something like a Hanakappa.
(Note: 2)
I was imagining something cute, but this is very realistic.
We are the real kappa.
And I knew he was a kappa.
Kotouge, How do you feel now?
I'll strangle you, pig!
He called him a pig.
He called the kappa a pig.
You guys are kappa, right?
I'll strangle you!
Hey, pig!
Stop it!
- Stop it!
- It's like hell.
No one saw us.
Don't fight with other kappa.
- I feel sorry for Kotouge-san.
- Yeah, I feel sorry for Kotouge.
- Did you guys have a meeting?
- Yes.
Really?
- Fujimon, please go to the room.
- Okay.
- Then let's show Kubota's video.
Fujimon!
I'm jurous becaus you able to laugh.
I'm allowed to laugh.
I'm jerous because you able to laugh.
You guys are doing great.
I'm glad you're here.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- The atmosphere will be better.
- You make it active again.
- I'm easy to talk to you.
- You are easy to talk to me?
- I'm very happy!
You guys make me feel very welcome.
- Are you laughing?
- No.
What makes you think that?
Did anyone laugh while saying I'm happy?
- They beamed.
- Yeah.
I have one question for you.
What did you think of Yamamoto-san and Kotouge's kappa?
I wondered why you guys did that.
Let them change into their kappa costumes one more time.
That was enough.
- Wear this one more time.
- That's enough.
- Please Kotouge!
- Don't do it! Kotouge, you say no to him.
Please!
I feel sorry for Kotouge.
Hey, Yama-san.
That was not funny at all.
Why did you do that?
No one was laughing at that in the other room.
You haven't done anything funny all day.
Today you are not funny at all.
Don't wear the mask as an excuse to run.
You're trying to get back on your feet after last time, right?
Yeah.
Right.
Then try harder.
Kubota.
Hey, that's mine, right?
- This is my cigarette.
- That's right.
I feel very sorry for Kotouge.
What's wrong?
I did not laugh.
- Didn't you just laugh?
- No.
- You are still laughing.
- No, I am just barely holding on.
- You're laughing right now.
- No, I am not laughing.
- You are laughing.
- You are laughing too.
- When I get stress my cheek twitch.
That counts as a laugh, too.
- Koge is angry.
- That's enough. Let's not do that, Yama-san.
He apologized, but I would not forgive him.
I know how Kotouge feels.
Everyone gets angry in such a occasion.
Get your act together!
Do you understand, Yama-san?
Oh my God.
No one laughed.
- I will stop blaming Yamamoto-san.
- That's good.
Because I understand his feelings very well.
Why?
How do you know that?
He is close.
Answer me.
How do you know that?
I know how it feels when a joke bombs.
Oh, you know that because your jokes often bomb too?
So...
- You know how Yamamoto-san feels, right?
- Yeah.
He almost laughs more than once.
I may as well give him the card.
- You're laughing all the time, though.
- No.
- You are laughing a little.
- You are laughing.
- Please don't point this out to me alone.
- No, you are laughing a little.
Right.
- Be careful.
- Yes.
Don't point this out to just me.
- Really don't do that.
- Even now you are laughing.
- Listen. Even now you are laughing.
- I am enduring.
I allow you this time, but from now on I will be more strict in pointing out your laugh.
- You are not Matsumoto-san and you don't talk big.
- Right.
Hey, looser.
We are winners.
Don't get carried away.
He laughed so hard.
Hey, don't be silly, Kubota.
What did you show him?
This is my favorite one.
Matsumoto-san, what should I do with this?
- I don't want to show this to anybody else.
- I see.
You laughed.
- Did I laugh?
- You laughed so hard.
Fujimon was right, you were laughing the whole time.
- Why did you attack me?
- I thought it was the right time. Sorry.
That's not fair.
You have been laughing ever since Fujimon came.
When Fujimon comes in, it becomes relaxed.
That was like a camp school.
That sounds fun.
Coo-chan, you are dismissed!
He's going to have jokes he hasn't shown them yet.
Is he leaving?
You didn't win three in a row.
This is Kubota's score.
What he showed him is still a secret.
I just worry about that.
You are not been fair.
You guys have been grinning since Fujimon got here.
Really so.
- His laughter is infectious.
- Yeah, he is laughing.
Because I am allowed to laugh.
That was so funny.
You laughed too, Yama-san.
I didn't laugh.
And you laugh at me.
I just laughed because you are funny.
Guys, it's not good to smirk.
Thank you.
Oh, really?
Thank you, Cookie-san.
Thank you!
I wish you all the best.
Good luck, Yamamoto-san.
- I can't.
- You can.
Thank you.
What did you show him?
I was quite caught off guard.
How could I have won if I had no defense at all?
I am the kind of person who guards with plastic board.
In the end, my enemy was Kubota.
He gave me the final blow.
It was Kubota who cut off my head.
I really do not know who will win.
Zakoshi is strong.
But Kubota might win too.
Either Zakoshi or Kubota might win.
Yama-san, the kappa one was terrible.
Here we go.
That was terrible.
The kappa one wasn't good?
What were you going to do with the kappa one?
Your jokes always lack punch lines.
Right.
I don't think about that.
It's fine, right?
It's not fine.
I shouldn't have gotten involved with you.
And so are you.
Why?
You're also fucking with them.
Why is that bad?
That's not bad.
Then it's fine!
Then it's fine.
But that's what I mean.
- What do you mean?
- That's what I mean.
- We are a group that fuck with people.
- Yes!
but still they're competent.
- Was I the worst?
- Honestly, you are the worst.
How long have you been watching me?
From the beginning.
What time did you get here today?
That has nothing to do with this.
Let's watch the video.
Yeah, let's do it.
Okay, let's watch the video.
Don't keep staring at them.
Come, Yama-san.
Don't do that, Kotouge.
You bastard!
(Note: 3)
They do it because you react that way.
- Stop it already.
- Why did you throw this!?
It's best to do so.
Guys, stop it already.
Why did you throw this!?
Because you react that way.
You bastard!
Yama-san,
You have the longest career, so you should be more imposing.
But I have a 10 year gap.
You right. Sorry.
Please sit down.
- Really sorry.
- Please calm down.
- It's my fault.
- I feel I said too much, sorry.
What the hell are you looking at me!?
Yama-san, stop it already!
This guy has egg on his forehead.
I don't really care if it's detailed.
- Do we have to wash our hair every time?
- Yeah.
Zakoshi, you are also...
Every time?
Let's not do this anymore.
Hey stop.
Do we have to wash our hair every time?
You are scared.
Are you scared?
No, he isn't.
Now let's watch the video.
Yama-san, please do not talk back to them.
Do we have to wash our hair every time?
He is wrestling again.
Zakoshi, you're not good either.
This guy is so annoying.
You're also fuck with them.
Fuck with them?
- Should he have washed his head?
- That's enough!
You are both fucking with them.
Yeah.
You both are.
- I'm not like that, but she is.
- He is!
You are both fucking with them.
You guys are doing something you don't need to do right now.
So I shouldn't have done that!?
I've been saying that all along.
He's telling you not to do that.
It is not better to do everything.
But I should do that.
Yeah, but...
We should do that shushutto(≒quickly).
What do you mean?
What's "shushutto"?
You don't have to do it either!
So I shouldn't have done that!?
That's right!
I've been saying that for a while now.
- Kubota, can you get started on that?
- Yes.
I'm looking forward to it.
What did Coo-chan see that made him laugh?
This is a composite photo of someone and someone's face.
Yuriyan?
Great.
One side is Yuriyan.
How many faces did you composite?
Two people.
- Two?
- Yawara-chan?
No.
It's hanako and someone I don't know.
I can see that one side is Yuriyan but I don't know the other perosn.
Who?
Yamamoto-san.
No way.
If you mix Yuriyan and Yamamoto-san's face, this is the result.
- Let's look at the next one.
- That's interesting.
- I know who this is.
- Who is this?
It's Takashi Hosokawa.
(Note: 4)
- Do you know who the other person is?
- Yeah, it is indeed his hair.
RG?
(Note: 5)
It is not him.
- Then who?
- It's a characteristic baldness.
It's Yamamoto-san.
Yamamoto-san?
Yeah, this is Yamamoto-san's baldness.
It's Yama-san?
Yeah, this is his hairline.
How about this?
Who?
Is this difficult?
I recognized one of them.
Who is this?
Matsumoto-san, right?
This is Matsumoto-san's mouth.
I wonder who the other person is?
- Barack Obama?
- No.
The correct is Antony.
(Note: 6)
Ah, Antony.
I didn't get it.
Matsumoto-san and...
Oh, I messed up.
This has nothing to do with it.
This is Matsumoto-san.
This is almost Matsumoto-san.
- Oh, shit, I made a mistake.
- This is almost Matsumoto-san.
What did you do?
This is Matsumoto-san, who gained weight using an app that can make someone gain 7 kg.
Why did you fatten him up?
By the way, Cookie-san laughed when he saw this.
- Oh, really?
- Oh, this was it.
He would laugh if he suddenly saw this.
What the hell is that app?
It's an app that can fatten someone up.
Didn't you just laugh?
I am not laughing at all.
Hey, Kubota.
You are laughing.
This is a symptom of my disease.
Matsumoto-san knows this.
Even so, you shouldn't do that.
When I get stress my cheek twitch.
- i'll stop playing videos for a while.
- Can I show mine next?
- Yeah.
I will show you the rest later.
Hey, hey, hey...
What's that app that can make someone gain 7 kg?
- There is such an app.
- Why 7 kg?
If it were 7 kg, I don't think it would be so fat.
Did you have to say that?
Yes.
- May I begin?
- Sure.
Hosokawa-san?
[KILL YOU]
So scary.
- I would like you to watch one more.
- Hey, what the hell is this?
Is this a set up for a joke?
It was so scary.
Watch this.
No sound?
- There's no sound?
- I could hear the sound.
So fast.
It's too fast.
It's too fast...
...look like its not moving.
It's very fast.
[KILL YOU]
What the hell.
Hey, what's this?
I don't get it.
Who is this message to?
It's too much of a leap to make sense.
What's this?
I will show you a better one.
Hey, listen.
May I show you one more one?
Fujimoto-san, don't look at me because I am about to laugh.
Please show this.
[NATAYOOO]
"Natayooo"
- It's Kinoshita of TKO.
- "Natayooo"
(Note: 7&8)
Plastic bottle...
Let me watch it again.
Kotouge is about to laugh.
I want to watch it again.
"Natayooo"
He says it.
Where was this taken?
I don't really care where he's shooting.
Why is he repeating this part?
He has thrown that one many times.
It's getting faster.
It's so...
So fast.
[NATAYOOO]
"Natayooo"
Kotouge laughed.
- Did you just laught at your own joke.
- No, I didn't.
It could be me.
"Natayooo"
Who laughed?
It's Kotouge.
It was very funny.
Kotouge?
He was patient, though.
Who laughed?
Kotouge.
You were so smiling.
Yes, that's right.
- You just seemed to be having fun.
- He laughed because Fujimon was there.
I didn't do anything to you.
I laugh when my eyes meet yours.
Why do you laugh when your eyes meet mine?
Is this your first time getting a card?
No, this is the second time.
This means that...
Oh, gosh.
- Fujimon, please leave with me.
- Yes.
And let's get someone to come here.
Are you leaving?
Good luck.