Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!
Well... to be honest...
The thing is that...
we had to let it go…
and put it away.
The highly controversial work
But I negotiated something
and I think some people
may actually like it.
Especially since we
went so far with this one.
And if possible,
I'd really like everyone
to take a look at it.
It has to be around R60
"An R60 work"
The one that pissed off Amazon!
The lost season: who messed up?!
The Emergency Meeting
I did it!
I'm the humble
teddy bear!
I did it!
Whoa!
Thank you...
—Thank you for your time
—Thank you too!
"Zakoshi Show's Victory V2"
"The birth of a king"
I did it!
Don't you think it's amazing...
what Zakoshi can
make you laugh about?
He's a psychopath for real.
So you wonder if
someone like him will win,
"Only psychopaths can win?"
So you wonder if
someone like him will win,
"Only psychopaths can win?"
"Today's contestants..."
"are five veterans..."
"and five novices."
and then wonder
if you have a good balance
"The bullied professional"
"Miyzaki's flaming mad cow"
"Post Ikko"
"The unwavering Backstage King"
"The thousand character man"
"Miracle face"
"The new generation flag-bearer"
"The craziest homo sapiens"
"The uncrowned lying emperor"
"The comedian killing champion"
Although many have appeared so far
there are still many more
that haven't made their debut yet.
Many of them.
Comedy is incredible.
In half a year
these people will have
already appeared.
That's incredible.
And then…
they'll have to compete
against more experienced ones.
That sounds fun.
"The craziest battle."
I have my eyes wide open
when I come!
"The craziest battle."
I have my eyes wide open
when I come!
Always with this expression
That's a lot of piss...
"The controversial work"
"I grow potatoes in my garden at home"
"so the kids in the neighborhood came over"
"and had a potato picking contest."
"And then they came back all muddy and said"
"you can have the potatoes."
"We split them and ate them together."
"They were good."
"Well then, I'll give you
something to think about."
"Would you be willing to come
and bring along a million yen?"
"A new Documental is coming."
"The winner gets ten million yen."
"You're free to decline."
"Those interested will be
informed of the time and place."
"I'll be waiting for your answer."
"I'll be waiting for your
participation this autumn."
"Matsumoto Hitoshi"
"The performers' entrance"
Alright,
here we go again.
Whoa!
First one here?
He might be
the youngest one today.
This is scary!
Where should I sit?
I'm Soshina from Shimofuri Myojo
Documental!
Whoa! That's unexpected!
Whoa!
Too loud.
For real?!
My partner was on it already.
I was really jealous
of him, to be honest.
Yeah
"M-1 2018 Grand Prix Winner"
"R-1 2019 Grand Prix Winner"
"Contest Earnings: 1.5 million yen"
I feel like we've been
doing comedy nonstop
since we won the M-1
but I'm feeling pretty excited
for the first time in a while.
I like Documental
as a comedian
And I laugh
with the straight man role.
I hope the others are funny.
Something I'm expecting from this
is for Soshina to be able to
take a new step forward
during this competition.
Depending on the other
straight man roles,
I might have to
refine my strategy.
Maybe I'll go all out,
or look at the others,
and act like an idiot.
He's pretty orthodox,
and doesn't have
experience with women.
So you have to wonder
how far a cherry-boy (Virgin) like him can go
Second one!
I wonder what he'll do
after 20-30 minutes.
Alright, a guy...
Yo-san has some good surprises for you.
Whoa!
Good morning, Sensei!
—Akiyama-sensei!
—You're here? Hey!
You too, Soshina?
Akiyama-san!
I'm Akiyama Ryuuji from ROBERT.
You can leave
Documental to me.
I wonder
how many times it's been.
This is already
his fourth time.
So I want to see...
what else he can do,
or come up with.
I also wonder if I might
use up everything
that they haven't seen before
this time around.
I've already used the
Umemiyage act before,
so I've added some improvements
and I want to give it a try.
"The reliable creators"
I want to put up a fight
for the ages this time.
So I was talking to a female announcer,
and she got all embarrassed,
and told me she watched it.
I asked if she watched
the "hand service" part as well.
So her face got beet red,
and she left.
Maybe she liked it.
It wouldn't surprise me
if he won it eventually.
So maybe this time?
Finally?
I'm sure no one
would complain if I finally
won it all.
It's finally time!
Finally! Documental!
For real, I have to
settle my score here,
or I won't think straight.
Yeah, I know
this is how I'm ending the month.
What's with those sandals?
Who's gonna show up?
Wait, that's too soon!
You're dressed like that?!
So Matsuo's not coming?
I'm Matsuo from
Chocolate Planet.
I came to take
the ten million today.
Huh? Which one—? Whoa!
Ah right!
Matsuo-san!
Matsuo-san from Chocolate Planet...
Don't read as Ikko-san!
You should leave Ikko-san
for later! Later!
Chocolate are funny
and sometimes spontaneous,
so even if he has no plans
I still think
that maybe something good
might happen.
I'm the Kamikaze Captain
in Chocolate.
They like more
power play and stuff.
But the destructive one
tends to be me.
Recently,
I've been doing impersonations.
So I've prepared
a few of those for today.
How much?! (Alternatively: How long?!)
I don't think many people there
will be doing impersonations.
So I think this might be innovative.
I usually do Ikko-san
on TV, but
I want to do an Ikko-san
more aimed for comedians.
So... a pleasure to
be here today.
I hope I won't
cause much trouble to you all.
Just don't hurt me physically.
Next year, it'll be 15 years in comedy for me.
But I've never tried any
solo comedy so far,
so I think winning this
might make me a better comedian.
That's why I'm here today.
What happened to you there?
I just had...
an incident, you know.
Another guy...
Oh no...
I hate this.
This is a newcomer.
No way...
Someone good showed up.
No way, man!
Koumoto-san!
Come on!
I'm Koumoto from Jicho Kacho.
I'm so nervous
I feel like
asking someone to
switch places.
Good morning!
Take this.
I've seen this.
It's finally here!
It's hard to believe
but this is his first time!
I guess I wasn't
expecting it,
or maybe the timing was
kind of funny.
Koumoto tends to laugh a lot.
Yeah.
"Well then, I'll give you
something to think about."
Come on!
You laugh at everything...
I do!
So...
I'm the type to laugh
even when I'm in the shower.
It can't be helped that I do
so I'll take advantage of it.
I'll teach you a lesson, okay?
Give me a break!
Koumoto-san! Damn!
He might be older
for sure.
Maybe that'll put
some pressure on him.
I didn't prepare any weapons,
instead I was thinking of
counter-attacks.
I have high expectations,
So I'll try to
do things my way.
Stop it, guys!
Huh?
You're trying too hard!
Matsuo, right?
Stop it, you two.
You two?
You're trying.
I'm not trying anything.
The Oguri Shun impersonation.
Who's doing that?
Oguri Shun?
I'm sure we'd know immediately
if he was.
Seems like everyone
brought a lot of stuff today.
I've never seen this
from up close.
I hate this, man.
Huh?
Hello!
I'm dead!
This sucks!
These guys are all great!
Sorry!
I hate this already.
I won M-1 2017.
I'm Kubota from Toro Salmon.
I do everything aside from
shady business and lying.
I want to make a mess.
Good morning.
What? I have to quit?
Quit Yoshimoto?
We haven't seen each other for a while.
So I thought it was fine.
I thought it could be fun
to see him explode.
Late last year...
I made some remarks that almost made the country explode, and burned bridges.
And that's how I got here.
I think maybe I shouldn't
be talking about this,
I thought I was going to die
and I was planning on dying
late last year,
but I couldn't take the last step
and I'm still alive
Damn it! I wanted to die!
But it's finally time
Can I send everything to hell?
I don't care if they cancel me.
Are you sure you want to have me here?
You didn't get the money from the Omura boat race?
Now's not the time.
I like that!
Don't do that now.
Don't do business now!
Damn, this is scary.
Pretty bad, for real.
How did you choose to do that?
Look, look!
There he is!
There he is, this is serious!
For real?
Drop the T-shirt!
What are you doing?
I'm Inada from Einstein!
I'm ready to lose face!
A million yen!
I'm glad but also scared.
A million yen sounds good, though.
How much was your hair transplant?
1.04 million
And it moves?
Lately he's been
pretty incredible.
Like deep inside he's...
breaking all kinds of walls.
With a face like mine, it would be embarrassing
to lose against anyone else.
I used to suffer from stage fright,
and I didn't laugh much either.
But if you meet people's true selves,
you realize they're mostly good people
Just like yokai
so I started laughing a lot more.
I started questioning
if he really was so clumsy.
And he definitely is clumsy, but...
you know...
I started getting my hands dirty
and I wanted to become a filthy
but cool
type of comedian.
He's here! Damn it!
This is Documental
He's huge!
Good morning
I guess you could call him a regular by now!
Are you getting used
to that door?
You should be too!
Hello, I'm Kendo Kobayashi.
This is my third time here.
It's here?
I've lost a lot, so I have no real right to be here.
My age!
—So this time...?
—I'm going for sure.
I'm going.
I just don't have the right.
I want the money.
Koba has been trying
with this show for a while.
He's kind of a team with Akiyama.
He does pretty filthy things
but he's not super filthy.
I think that's his strength.
But he can't win with that.
And I think Koba
believes so as well.
I just wanted to be relaxed.
I should have probably been more nervous.
I think it's weird, to be honest.
Why was I so relaxed,
with a pink dildo inside me?
We can stop right now.
The bastard with phimosis showed up too
That doesn't matter.
That was a personal thing,
I was with a girl, and she said it.
This isn't about comedy, though.
I ended up doing it with
one of those TV girls that come and go...
That wasn't me but Jinnai, by the way.
It wasn't me.
I'm counting on you.
This is too scary.
He has a travel bag and...
he's ready for anything I guess.
No way he's here!
That's enough.
This is getting fun.
He's a newcomer.
Where are you going?
I just brought some weapons.
I'm Nadal from the Korokoro Chikichiki Peppers.
This gets me the most nervous.
Damn it!
There it is!
I think that Nadal has
a pretty good defense.
I don't really know what
makes Nadal laugh.
I get the impression that he's
kind of a psychopath.
So he can act like one if he wants to.
I kinda feel that
it would be nice to see him face off
with Zakoshi someday.
I'm happy as a comedian, yeah.
Right now, whenever I'm on TV,
I usually get pranked,
or bullied a lot.
But you know?
I guess I can try something different here,
and do my best.
I don't think
I have much pressure on me.
But I want Matsumoto-san
to think that I'm funny.
That's a huge amount of baggage.
But I'm sure that you'll be laughing
in just two minutes.
Please do that! I've come here to learn.
Don't tell me...
He's tall!
No way!
There he is!
Again?!
They're also shocked he's here again.
You got ten million already, right?
No, no, I don't have that anymore!
Hey, I'm Cookie from Yaseibakudan.
I don't wanna, I don't wanna.
Anyways, nice to meet you.
Good morning
This is for you.
There's the red letter.
This is Cookie's fourth time.
Is this some sort of
champion round?
Give me a call when you do one,
no more regular ones.
You did one?
Ten million!
Sometimes I watch Cookie on amazon
But sometimes even I can't watch.
I can't watch him drink sock sweat.
He's pretty... reckless.
That's enough already!
You can't run away and win.
I think either Zakoshi or I
will become Documental's emperor.
That's why I have to win this time,
and get a little nasty
with Mister Documental.
Who's the only one left?
This is enough!
It's no small fry.
There he is!
He's too quick!
That's enough!
Why are you like that already?!
He's acting already!
I'm Jimmy Onishi!
I'm going to win
no matter what today!
Excuse me!
Good job today.
This is for you.
There it is...
There it is.
This guy's not going to win.
But I want to see how far he goes.
This isn't just for laughs.
I have to put pressure on everyone from the get go.
What's up with your eye?
I don't really get his lead ups.
He's prepared a lot of things.
He looks like he'd bring dynamite with him,
but not a lighter
I have to give it my all, or else...
It's gonna be bad.
I trained for a full week
with my manager.
I got good laughter at first,
but I ran out of ideas along the way.
That's how I became Jimmy-san.
I'm always serious, but this time
I'm several times more serious.
I have to win this.
Ah, sorry
Why are you dressed like that?
Did you quit comedy
and become an escort?
You said that.
No, they told me I couldn't.
Who?
The company told me I couldn't.
Told you to respect yourself?
They told me I couldn't, yeah.
Good morning.
Hey!
We have a good cast
Is this a good cast?
I changed the color of my hair.
It looks really good.
Really? Thanks.
It's dull.
Pretty dull.
He's a first timer.
And well... the regulars, or veterans would be
about half the room.
Koumoto hasn't been here, somehow.
I haven't, yeah.
My first time out of eight.
I remember Nadal doing pretty well...
Stop it, I haven't been here.
You haven't?
I haven't.
I really thought you had been here once...
I haven't! For real!
Ah, and then there's Ina-chan.
This is serious!
You're laughing.
You're laughing just looking at him.
It's like it's your first time.
And you have time, right Kubota?
Yeah, I'm free right now.
Why?
I said...
Something that shook the country
to a woman.
You're an idiot.
And so I'm here.
I don't even know how much time I have left.
A lot happened, huh?
Are you sorry?
I'll repent, come back to life, and participate here again.
Feel free to get nasty here, though. It's fine.
So uh... you all brought it?
We can gather it, and
This is a big competition.
It's huge! Just look at how much
money we have right here.
Everything okay? I trust you all!
So this is almost ten million,
but right now, we only have 9 million.
That's why every single time, I do this.
Really, every time.
I have to use this envelope
as soon as possible,
we don't know
when it'll be over
Yoshimoto's going to be over?
It's going to disappear?
No, no, it's not.
Thanks to your effort,
it's not going anywhere.
And so this becomes this.
And now, this one
goes here, right? Right here.
And that's how it is.
We also have the rules,
which I think should
be fine, really.
But this time,
they're a little special.
We have a new stage,
a different room
where you can do what you want.
I think it can
be pretty useful.
So first we have yellow, then orange.
And finally the red.
You can get it directly, if it's too obvious.
It can happen.
Got it?
Okay.
You can try to stop it.
Huh? What?
That's enough of that!
Seems like all of you have a lot of baggage today!
That's good, I think it shows spirit!
And we have some toys
around here as well.
You can use them
or not, whatever.
To take a look
make sure you do.
—Okay, Jimmy-chan?
—All okay!
We're the same age, so I'm counting on you!
Are you the only one
without anything?
That's what's unnerving!
I'm getting nervous!
What's going on, man?
So we can't just
target Jimmy-san, then.
Sorry, but I'm
not laughing at all today.
Are you actually sick or something?
Is it contagious?
It's onset is at dawn!
Show us your eye!
Do it right now.
We want to see!
—You sure?
—It's the best option.
But I'll lose a chance!
Maybe two.
You're already two down.
Before we begin... it's nothing special.
Why did he take it off now?!
—You laughed!
—We haven't started yet.
Why did you take it off?
Everyone told me to do it!
Documental start!!
You laughed though!
When you chat with Matsuhito
at this distance,
do you get nervous?
Ma-Matsuhito?
Matsuhito?
Yeah, Matsuhito!
No one calls you Matsuhito, though.
Ma-chan is better!
Has anyone called you Matsuhito?
If you were still a novice
and we met somewhere
would you ask for a handshake?
Yeah, I would've.
Yeah, me too.
But now I'm used to it.
That doesn't matter!
Startled me.
Why did you shout?
Why did you call us four here?
Just tell us what's going on!
This is Documentary of Documental.
So I asked you all
to come here.
We have to talk.
You know the newest Documental
has been delayed, right?
Yeah, kind of.
I thought it was
about time it released.
Yeah, yeah.
And that's what
Matsuhito said as well.
Stop it with the Matsuhito thing!
And he does it like...
Keep it up for a couple days
Well you see, we had
a bit of trouble.
Trouble?
That's confusing, right?
I think it is, so...
So I want you to
take a look at this.
Hey, hey, hey.
Huh?!
Huh?
Why?
What's going on?
—No way!
—I guess that's that!
That's that, yeah.
Vulgar?
Whoa!
They called him out directly!
This is serious.
It's family-friendly?
Right, right.
We're sabotaging family reunions.
Hey, Kubota...
Wait, is this real?
They called you out.
You're blacklisted for sure!
It's like a
murder report!
What's going on? Why?
It was vulgar!
Too vulgar!
That's not just this time, though!
It's a weird translation, right?
It's kind of backwards!
Aren't they saying
that it was good?
For now, yeah.
Maybe it's a typo?
—So they're angry?
—A little!
Originally, next year was already
rearing up to be great content
for Amazon.
But it's all Kubota's fault.
What? I'm reported everywhere now?
What should I do?
To be honest
we were also pretty shocked.
Well, we had pissing too, yeah.
So those bits were
family-friendly after all?
Until now, yeah.
Maybe it was worse than pissing!
Toro Salmon's Kubota is
going to become a slur now!
So why had everything
been fine until now?
We didn't really remember either
and we had our doubts...
So today we wanted to
see what went wrong with you guys.
We're settling this?
We're debating like this.
Yoshimoto is debating Amazon
on what to do to get it online.
But they don't
have much hope.
I want it to go live!
It would suck if it didn't.
We thought that Amazon
would accept basically anything
Everything goes, right?
But it seems like
we went too far.
We went all the
way with this.
So now we know that
there really was a limit!
Why can't they tell us?
So let's see where the line is.
I think it might
have been that thing...
Well, I want to check
and see in real time what went wrong.
So let's have a look.
Documental start!
You laughed!
But before it started.
Let's get our bags.
What's up with your eye?
This?
The eye that's to your left?
No, it's to our right.
It's to our right.
—To your right?
—Yeah.
Your left eye
is to our right.
Touch it.
Touch your own eye.
Huh? What?
Huh? What was that?
Why don't you touch
where it's red?
Here?
(No way!)
Was that you?
You have-You have to be silent!
Be silent?
Is that a
"be silent" sampler?
Don't push me!
Why?
What was that sound?
Who was that?
That was Tamuken-san, right?
Icchan, that's not funny.
What's wrong?
Um... just phlegm.
You have some?
Do you have some allergies?
Huh? It's coming back?
No, I think
it has to be that thing.
That's kinda funny.
It's going smoothly.
It's good,
same as always.
See? It's the same.
There's no punchline, though.
Back to the phlegm?
What was that?
Why do you always wear
a tank top to Documental?
Well, it's just
to regulate my temperature.
This, this!
You know this, you guys?
Matches?
You know how to stick them together?
Huh?
You go like this,
and stick them...
—No idea.
—You don't know?
You stick them like this.
Don't grab that.
It's hot!!
Eh? Why?!
Yeah...
I wanted to see them stick together.
What's going on?
What kind of matches are these?
Read this.
Those matches are huge.
Positive...
Positive matches?
I'll do your reading.
A positive and simple heart.
You gonna stay as Ikko?
What do you mean?
A regretful heart.
—A thankful-
—Admiring...
admiring heart.
They don't know shit.
A responsible heart.
He can't read properly, man.
What do you mean?
A loser's heart. A helpful heart, thankful words.
He's getting it all?
For real?
Watch out, man!
They won't stick!
They're not sticking!
Look, everyone!
I couldn't do it.
Why?
We have to put out the fire.
Watch out.
Let's put it out. Wait, I'll do it.
Watch out! Put out the fire!
Ready? I'll do it
let's put it out!
Extinguish!
Nothing's sticking anywhere.
Hey, stop it.
Can you stop it?
It won't come out from the mouth.
You're soaking wet, besides.
Stop it.
Just for a little while.
It's stopped, it's stopped.
Stop it! Stop it! Just a little!
I stopped, I stopped!
Okay!
There's no more fire, it's fine.
Stop, stop! Stop it!
It's leaking everywhere.
Stop it~ Man~!
Did you put it out?
It got hot, but yeah.
Looks like I pissed my pants.
You can't piss in that direction.
Please stop when I tell you.
Now I look
like I pissed myself.
Hey man, you think you could
put some tuna inside your foreskin?
No, I don't wanna.
You don't?
Do it man!
He's older than you!
If he tells you to put tuna
on your dick,
you fucking do it.
Okay, but...
You're a Yoshimoto, right?
You do it if he says so.
Stop it, stop it.
You have to do it right away.
I've hurt people, you know?
I'm sorry.
You need help?
Ah, kind of.
Is this it?
Isn't this it?
This is it, right?
Jimmy-san, the time.
What time is it right now?
What?
I mean, look.
2 hours 45 minutes.
It has to be this.
This is serious.
In just a second.
Everyone reacted like that.
2 hours 46 minutes.
This is Sato-san...
This sucks!
That one has
no mosaic at all!
You're really fucking with me, man.
What were you thinking
showing that on air?!
What did you show?
What did you show?!
Come on, man
Scold him, Matsumoto-san!
This might be
more than a yellow.
I think this might be
close to a rule violation!
Let's verify at once.
I'll fully admit that
I laughed, of course.
But punish Kubota
I see, I see
Because there's some things
we can't do, right?
Did he show you from his phone?
It's a video...
Are you stupid?
Why do you have that?
You use that?
But there's some females later.
What good would some
female porn do?
Actually, I think female
porn would be even worse.
I'm sorry
I'm glad Coo-chan laughed
this early on!
It was nervous laughter
This is Sato-san...
We're in a pretty tight spot!
At first I thought
orange was good enough,
But Coo-chan, you get a yellow!
Yeah, I get it. Thank you
He was just like a
bystander watching.
But there's that!
Let him see
Look at the time, man...
You're both the same!
Why're you mad at me?!
This is just like playing concentration!
One pair!
Now, I won't say it's
classy or anything
We've had stuff like that before
We have, yeah.
We can edit something like this
with a mosaic and stuff.
Looking at it
I'd say this part is safe.
Of course, objectively speaking
we're insane
Yeah, definitely.
But in the world of Documental...
A fictional land...
In that world, yeah...
I'd say it's safe.
Yeah, I don't think Amano-san minds this...
Which means,
that was fine, right?
If we crossed the line
then what bothered Amazon?
We don't see the problem so far.
I'm starting to get sad.
This was on about the same level
as Hirunandesu.
Idiot!
So this is Nanchan standards?
Nanchan wouldn't be able to handle this!
Hey man, that's rude!
No, no, no
No matter how you slice it,
a "boke" doesn't set standards.
Because it doesn't suit him, right?
Someone could misunderstand you
Sorry, sorry
Sorry for doing that.