Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks for watching!
I hate everything now!
I hate everything.
So far this has been
[A big incident in 2019]
[Season 8]
The winner is Kubota!
Whoa!
So far we've been able to
mostly do whatever we want.
That includes me as well.
I thought there was no bottom.
At least that's what
part of me thought.
I was wondering when
we would hit the limit.
But finally something
crossed the line.
[The 10 million got held back]
I haven't slept at all
ever since that day.
Please look at Amazon Prime's
comments.
In favor of Kubota
I'll do it again if I have to
To get back my 10 million
So the 10 million
are in a state of limbo
And the winner this time
gets 20 million
So this is just...
This is uh... it's amazing.
It's 20 million!
Both M-1 and King of Conte
are 10 million each
So this time only one person
will take 20 million
So this is a type of "Documental"
where we'll be checking
how people's feelings change.
It's almost a documentary.
This time
just to try
we've decided to keep it a little shorter
Down to 4 hours
And since we've cut two hours
Uh... I think...
It might be more spectacular
And they'll be more aggressive
It's a great contest
I want it to end
before it gets old
Lately I've been ordering salad
to stop mochi from getting stuck
in my throat
But getting my hands on
the osechi's kumquat (Editor's Note: 1)
it still got stuck there.
I started asking for water
and making a ruckus.
Well then, I present this idea to you
How would you like to earn
10 million yen?
We'll be hosting a "Documental".
Participation is voluntary.
Anyone interested in participating,
go to the instructed place and time
I'll be waiting for your reply
Here's hoping we bring
a new spring together soon.
-Matsumoto Hitoshi-
[The contest stage]
There he is
It's Soshina
He's one of the top hitters.
And he doesn't know
who else is coming.
I'm the first one!
Soshina is the first one
I'm Soshina from Shimofuri Myojo
I don't smile.
Hey!
I'm so happy.
In all my years
working in comedy
This was the most fun I've had
He's an incredibly clever guy
He tends to act
in the shadows
[The young-serious pioneer]
He gathers points
little by little
Alright, you can't smile, okay?
You can't smile
I've even wondered if maybe
he's scheming something incredible
I want to become a presenter
on TV
For a morning
or a noon show
that's what I'm aiming for
So let's stop it
with the dirty jokes
Stuff like that!
Touch me!
What's with that?
Whoa!
I've been on a losing streak
I lost 7 million in 3 days
I'm known as
"the legendary loser" online
Who are they calling loser?
I'll be betting 1 million
as a gambler
Nine more
Nine more, right?
Please bring me
someone shady
Whoa
Two straight-men/tsukkomi, huh?
Two tsukkomi, right.
But they're kind of boke-tsukkomi (EN: 2)
Both of them
I'm Goto from Football Hour
Back again
Hello
Whoa!
There it is
I have no reason to refuse
I see, I see
Goto-san!
[One of the top tsukkomi in M-1]
I don't think I've seen
this shot often enough
[One of the top tsukkomi in M-1]
I don't think I've seen
this shot often enough
Attacking by myself
And making someone laugh
Is naturally
part of my strategy as well
[The Serious Sniper]
Performing a counter is the best, though
He puts on this makeup for one show,
and the next show needs him to be in this makeup, right?
That's pretty smooth
Yeah, it's pretty nostalgic
Not yours
He sometimes laughs at himself
Sometimes I laugh
even if I said it
It's thrilling
for better or for worse
He plays the tsukkomi now
but he used to play the boke
He's on the offense
The person I love
is a disinfectant
He gathers points
little by little
Maybe that's his plan
So you're dressed like that now
In grey
Goto sure is laughing today
Maybe I should push the button
Right now
That's right
I wonder if a boke is going to show up now
So do I
Or more tsukkomi
Well, Soshina plays the tsukkomi
But you're not completely serious either
The third one's here
Whoa!
Abareru!
Abareru-kun with a deep tan
Maybe he went
to a remote island for a tan.
He has a lot of stuff as well!
Maybe he went
to a remote island for a tan.
He has a lot of stuff as well!
What's with those
newspapers?
I'll bring this out later
I went on a party goods
rampage yesterday
You hoarding?
I'm hoarding
Good luck, you guys
I'm really nervous.
You're hoarding, though
I'm Abareru-kun.
I came here to win!
Excuse me
Thank you for your hardwork
Whoa! It's Documental!!
Alright!
Abareru could do it!
Waraitoreru-kun could do it!
That's what I was thinking
I'm going full throttle!
Like his name suggests,
I expect him to be scandalous (EN: 3)
I think he's extremely
well suited for this
He's the aggressive funny type
[The Passionate Red Bald Guy]
He's got stuff!
I was in a huge rush yesterday!
He's shouting
So I bought this
You're shouting
You are
I can't identify volume
And everyone else is a comedian
And they'll see
what I'm doing
Thinking about that
This will be a
battle to the blows.
Can you hear
the laughing bells ring?
[Refer to Kuwata Masumi] (EN: 4)
I think I've managed to get here
more by pushing myself
than by sheer comedy.
Have you ever eaten a lizard?
Have you ever drank cow puke?
And so...
I'm against champions!
Ah right
Against great champions!
For real
Since none of you have titles
You don't have
a single title either.
No titles...
Well, I have a few on my own turf
Which ones?
It was a shoe flicking thing
I guess we're fine then
I'm confident I won't laugh
I usually laugh
a lot when I'm here
I'm always struggling
But it'll be alright
Alright, the fourth one's here
There are several people
I don't want to show up
Hello there
Alright
Abareru-chan!
Abareru-chan
Full scandal!
There we go
Yuriyan is bad news as well
I see, she's got it!
I'm Yuriyan Retriever
I'm so nervous
Excuse me
Come in
There we go!
You just laughed, right?!
Ten million! Eleven million!
I'm so glad!
It was so fun
And I didn't feel
any pressure
I'm really wondering how different
this slimmer Yuriyan is going to be
Maybe losing weight
will affect her
I wonder if it'll
have an effect on her
I'm fatter than Mizuki Arisa-san. (EN: 5)
[The Slimmer Hitting Girl]
I'm sure she's glad
to be stuck with us
Yeah, typical Yuriyan
She has a knack for this
-A snack?
-A knack, idiot
She's already
going at it
I get stereotyped
for making
dirty jokes or getting naked
Great job!
As if I could ever get naked!!
She just can't be stopped!
I'm happy to be here
It's good to see you all
The next one has arrived.
Good evening!
Good morning!
Yakko sure is amazing
This is her first appearance
I'm Tsubaki Oniyakko.
Getting hungry.
Excuse me
This is for you
An invitation?
I don't wanna,
but I'm also scared of saying no.
I really don't know what to think.
She's pretty funny.
Yeah
And she has a bit of a
costume fetish, right?
I don't know why
that came to mind, though.
Just thinking.
[The Unique Hoarse Medusa]
I've been with Yoshimoto
for over 20 years.
And singing for about half of those
So this feels like an opportunity
to show what I have in store.
Like wanting people to listen
to a good song I've written.
This is pretty weird!
It's a different crowd
from all other times
I'm the only newcomer?
No, it's my first time too
Really? First timers?
It is!
She has this nerdy laugh
and when she's into it
she's really loud
I'm kind of slow
on the uptake
But sometimes I get
lucky strikes.
I've had 36 consecutive wins
on Garou. (EN: 6)
I'm so nervous
I felt my heart in my throat
coming all the way here.
And then what?
Did it come out your mouth?
No, it just stopped in my throat
Well, I guess you're fine then.
Can you stop that already?
Stop it, really.
I really don't think I'm gonna laugh
I wonder if Goto will keep that up
Maybe he won't...
Stop that already!
I'm making you laugh!
He might also
shoot himself on the foot
We're all counters for bokes here
A lot of younger kids too
A carry bag and a lot of stuff
Osa-Osada!
For real?!
That's a lot of stuff!
Really?
He's Osada-kun,
a small tool manzai performer
I'm using everything in here
You are?
I'm Osada Shouhei
From Chocolate Planet
There it is!
Matsumoto Hitoshi...
There it is...
I love "Documental"
And I've been watching
since Season 1
He's pretty technical
Kind of like Akiyama
in certain aspects.
Especially not knowing
any limits
Osada-san!
Things are changing drastically!
He's the craftsmaster!
-Really, yeah!
-Lots of tools!
"The craftsmaster"?
[The DIY-making Performer]
I specialize in small tools
So I'm thinking of
bringing out a lot of them
I'm canceling everything.
Work, everything.
I'm gonna hide in the workshop
I don't think there were many
mechanical people before
So I want to open the door
for that this time
Mikitty!!
Matsuo, you're out!
And get revenge for my partner
I'm here to take revenge.
I want people to know that Chocolate Planet
is not just Matsuo.
Osada is great too
I'm going to...
everybody else
So you brought it on one end?
So I brought it on one end, and...
last night, I burnt my finger.
So you do make mistakes!
Aren't you talking about yourself?
Abareru-kun isn't great at
being serious.
This is pretty serious, right?
Even I feel it....
Like this is bad.
Hello! I'm Sunshine Ikezaki!!
Here you go
There it is!
About time!
He's kinda loud
I'm keeping it cool!
Be thankful!
Thank you!
I said it for you
I wouldn't want to
sit next to him
Seems like we're competing
to see who's the funniest.
But there's no point in doing that
if I'm not there!
So the real "Documental"
is finally getting started.
Congratulations!
[The All-Purpose Screaming Machine]
Let's do it, man!
Come, come, come!
[The All-Purpose Screaming Machine]
I don't know how he'll take the gags
But he's pretty solid mentally.
I'll show you the fun
of really loud shouting.
Everything's funny when you shout
Let's do it!
Hey! Who are you?!
Now that I'm here
Let's call it a "godly battle"!
That's what I'll make everyone say
Let's start the "godly battle"!
It's still pretty early
I just wanna say...
I don't want to sit
next to these two!
Though I think we're
the same type of comedian.
Are you older, Ikezaki-san?
Yeah, I'm older...
By one generation
We're the same generation.
Really?!
Let's settle this!
He's so annoying
Is it the cover?
Yeah
What's with these pants?
Another hyper energetic guy?
I think we have enough already.
There's no way!
-My heart's stopping!
-They're partners!
-Soshina's here?!
-I didn't know!
So the two guys from
Shimofuri Myojo didn't know?
I'm sure this was kept a secret
Hello! I'm Seiya from Shimofuri Myojo
My theme is mobility
Good morning
Whoa! What's this?
Take this
There we go, "Documental"!
A second time?!
"Documental" is really tough
Last time there were a few
points where I just laughed
and I got worked up
and ended up failing
You're out!
After living last time's experience
I wanted to be
a bigger part of another "Documental"
He's pretty young
And he's pretty strong as well
I want to show the willpower
of a young generation
I think freshness is a strength
[The Compact
Community College Machine]
Maybe appearing with his partner
will be an advantage
But it might also be a disadvantage.
I think it would be amazing
if we had a Shimofuri showdown
at the end
You're too young!
Both of you are!
And maybe the oldest veteran is...
Goto-san?
-I'm the most successful!
-Successful, yeah!
Goto is the only veteran!
If we don't climb past these walls
we'll have a distinction
between juniors and seniors.
My biggest weapon
is making people wonder
what the hell I'm doing
Nonsense humor
I'll keep my heart
in its right place.
Now what?
You're all older than me
This is pretty unexpected
I felt more at ease
when there were more seniors.
Goto-san is the oldest after all.
Excuse me!
There he is!
It's Junior-san!
Empty-handed as well!
So cool!
I'm Chihara Junior
from the Chihara Brothers
I'll do my best
-A red envelope...
-Here you go
I'm going to open the envelope now
And that's going to happen.
You can have it!
Junior is
I guess pretty orthodox
Like that old wrestler...
Bill Robinson
He doesn't really play dirty
He's kind of a gentleman.
[The Unwavering
Logical Specialist]
Whoa! No way!
-Justice!
-Justice!!
I'm so glad I watched it back then
I was pretty disappointed
last time
And I got scolded a lot for it.
People telling me
that was a dumb way to lose
So an automatic one
is like this
When I was a student
I almost never had fun
with other people.
That's why I enjoy it so much
But when you lose,
you first notice
that you feel really alienated.
Like when you're
at a friend's house
and everyone's staying over
but then all of a sudden
your mom comes
to pick you up
It's really depressing
That's why I want to
stay until the end
with my friends.
Justice!
This is pretty bad
He controls everything!
How annoying
There we go
I saw some skin
-This is enough!
-No way!
No way!
-This is bad!
-Don't show up!
-You can't be here!
-Let's stop this!
I came here to pick up
my 10 million.
Whoa!
You're banned!
-You're banned!
-Only from NipponTV
Don't make me say it
He's banned from NipponTV?
Last time I lost 10 million
I'm Kazunobu Kubota
I haven't been happy ever since
And people die
with equal happiness and grief
I know that already
I can't take this anymore
Just give me back my 10 million
10 million...
I just heard
he didn't get it
And I don't want to
see that ever again
For real
Let's get it this time
It's a mess
He's always breaking
the rules
Ready... go!
USA!
I'm gonna poop while standing!
I win the M-1 and then a slump
I win 10 million, and then a slump
I came here ready to die, so...
[The Never-ending
Self-Destructive]
If he reflects...
[The Never-ending
Self-Destructive]
If he reflects...
Still nothing good
will happen
He might take it
even further
And if he does that...
We might have a 30 million
carry over
Be it fate or hardship
I never get a peaceful day
I'm not the same
as the other crap comedians
I'll lead you
Early in the morning,
walking, being stupid
I'm taking the skies,
grabbing the sun while crying
Remember this!
This is serious!
-For real!
-This is serious!
The excitement's rising!
Tension, tension!
Tension tension!
Good morning!
Good timing
That's great timing
That's a lot of baggage!
It's quite scary
What's with this?
I had never seen this much!
I'm worried...
Everyone's worried
Everyone's here, right?
We have... a pretty young crowd!
Pretty young, right?
I feel younger too
Young and pretty rowdy people
Pretty loud people as well, right?
Everyone, please take a seat
Thank you very much
Kubota is the trouble child, right?
Yeah, I was here
last time as well.
And you even won,
but didn't receive a prize.
That's right.
Though there are some things
I can't accept.
Hard to accept, right?
So you're going to
take it back?
Of course.
Did you see the canceled episode?
I don't know
what you mean.
No, I mean...
You didn't hear about it?
You see, abroad
Japanese people don't know yet?
About the canceled episode?
Yeah, yeah.
In the end... it got a 4.5 stars ranking.
Whoa!
That's pretty good
Even though it was pretty dirty
Everyone loved it, with a 4.5
That's the same score
as "Grave of the Fireflies"
They do have a lot in common
—In what way?!
—Because you'll cry
I didn't cry.
Well, Kubota did die.
Setsuko and Kubota have...
both died.
Kubota took a big shit though
I didn't!
Alright, everyone! Your million!
Right right!
Please hand it over
Let's collect them at once
Alright, over here!
That's good!
That's so good!
Let's go!
I haven't counted yet
Huh? Hey!
Transportation costs!
I need to pay for transportation!
Are you a government official?
Don't get nervous!
Alright, this looks pretty neat
Of course, these are all bills
And here we go
Whoa!
That looks heavy
No way!
I wanna touch that!
It wouldn't be that tight
with old banknotes
Yeah, you're right.
And then!
What?!
Last time Kubota-kun won, but...
We didn't pay him the 10 million, right?
No way!
So this time...
It's carrying over!
No way!
This is amazing!
For real?!
I'm being serious
For real?! 20 million?!
There's no way!
You can buy a luxury car!
So who's going to stand laughing?
You're right!
This is heavy!
I'm really worried!
And we have also
changed the rules a little
It might be just for this time
This time we're doing just 4 hours
So you have to go all out
I don't think we'll be using
any more orange cards, really.
That's what I have in mind
No way!
And so...
We only have these two
For real?!
That's what I've decided
That's pretty strict!
You all look really scared
Well, you know... it's 20 million!
I've never seen so much money
Right?
Junior's face really changed
when he saw the 20 million.
That's fine!
Junior-san changing
worries me!
I've never seen him
like that!
So this time
You'll be joining me monitoring
if you're out.
That's what I've thought
Ah, really?
That's what I have in mind.
Kubota, if you screw up this time as well
We're really making it a 30 million carry over!
How would I even screw up?
So make sure you keep that in mind
That's right.
Please do.
But what do I even have left without
dirty jokes and vulgarity?
Then don't show up!
Do your best!
Just don't get naked today!
There are different types of vulgar!
Well, that's true
I can do that, then!
But dirty jokes aren't forbidden.
-That's right.
-Yeah, you're right.
Just don't go overboard.
-I'm counting on you all.
-Alright!
Well then
We're starting!
Abareru-kun!
Please don't go!
One more!
Matsumoto-san!
-Just laugh!
-20 million!!
That's just, you know...
I don't like this!
I preferred losing 10 million!
The battle's making me nervous
This is totally different now
These changes kinda
make me nervous
I'm really nervous!
Well then
"Documental" will start!
It's started
Seiya... what's with
your sleeves?
-This?
-They look like nine-parts
They are
You're correct
Do you wear that normally?
Well, yeah.
I wanted one of these
Is that like an ethnic costume?
No...
It's just normal clothing
I've never seen you wear that
even though we're partners
Is that from Mongolia?
It looks kind of ethnic
Well, I didn't just buy it
because I went to Mongolia
Actually in Japan...
You bought it yourself?
My... mom got this for me.
She has great taste
So your mom bought it?
And you wear the stuff
your mom buys for you?
Well, yeah, I do.
Where did she buy it?
This?
Yeah
-In Mongolia.
-Mongolia?
Your mom is from Mongolia?
Is she Mongolian?
My mom is... Mongolian, and
Really?
And my dad is Bongolian
Combine the two
and I'm MongolBongol
-Get it so far?
-As if!
Alright
Alright!
You know...
Let's do it, man!
You're annoying!
He's so loud!
Let's do it then
A battle to the death!
Do you see any power?
One murder
-One murder?
-Yeah
One murder?
Soshina
Didn't you just smile?
What?!
I didn't.
You did!
-That's one point!
-I really didn't
He just smiled
It was pretty maniacal.
-Right...?
-I didn't smile, though.
Really?
Really Soshina?
I really didn't smile.
Can I brush my teeth?
Sure, sure. Do it!
Excuse me
Just for etiquette.
Yeah!
I got a new
electric toothbrush
It's fully electrical.
They're super compact
nowadays, huh?
It's really amazing.
Alright Osada
This is pretty great
With this, you don't have to
even move your hands
Who made it? Phillips?
The maker?
This is from Sunstar
Sunstar makes
stuff like that?
It says "Makita", though
Yeah, this is a Makita
I'm using it then
No way!
That's crazy!
He did it!
Isn't that dangerous?
Isn't it too strong?
Watch out!
It's pulling!
Does that even work?
It's hitting your uvula
with the toothbrush like
It really goes in deep
Is your palate okay?!
Your face is all screwed up
Stop that, man!
You should lower the intensity
It's because it hits your uvula!
Old men shouldn't be
gagging early in the morning!
Why not lower the intensity?
Do it slowly.
Go easy
That's too quick
Too quick
That's insane, yeah
This is no game
That's industrial speed
It's pretty bad
It's stabbing you.
Are you alright?
No way, that's insane.
Can someone else do it?
Who's doing it?
I'll do it if we wash it
I have a new toothbrush actually
Let's do it
I wanna try
You wanna try?
Why do you wanna do that?
Here's the power
Good luck today
Seiya, what's with you?
What's wrong?
What happened?
This guy just
said something that only
I could hear
I didn't, though.
I just warned him
not to pace around
Pacing around is not good
You guys, I'm not okay with this
Could you stop
Thinking that one of you will remain
And take the ten million?
-No way.
-We haven't done that!
-That's pretty bad!
-You're basically colluding!
Like with the Mongolian stuff earlier!
It seemed like it!
You're pretty rude
So what if it's true?
I couldn't change it
That's a shame
It didn't fit
I'm sorry
I want to apologize
So I made something to drink
Really? Thank you!
What's that?
That's scary!
So I wanted to get
some feedback from everyone!
That's pretty rough looking
That's scary!
No way!
Let me know
what you think!
Hey you...
This is pretty bad
Give it a try!
No way I'm drinking that!
Just give it a try!
No way!
It's great
for your health!
That's pretty scary
You brought it out!
What do you think it is?
That's piss, man.
It's not.
Is it really not?
It's not! That's definitely not!
I wouldn't make you drink that.
This is good.
-Then what is it?
-Let me know how it tastes.
Then you name someone, Bareru
You call him Bareru?
That's what you call Abareru-kun?
Bareru?
Should I name someone?
No way, man! Not me!
That's pretty wild!
What even is that?
-What's that?
-Is it homemade?
Is it homemade?
So whoever gets the circle, drinks
Alright. Just one?
One person?
Whoever gets the X drinks
That's the opposite now
It's reversed
You drink first
to show it's okay
-Alright.
-That's true
From the producer himself
Not by name then?
That's right.
The producer's face...
Show us it's safe to drink
Should-Shouldn't I just
tell you what it is?
Just drink it up.
Can you drink it?
You drink first
There's no way
That's pretty serious!
Osada just laughed, right?
Who was it? Osada?
He laughed!
Osada-san!
You definitely laughed!
Why?!
What happened?
What?
I did it.
You lowered your guard?
This isn't the time for that, man!
It's too early!
What happened?
Why, Osada?
That was Osada, right?
Yeah, it was me.
What? What?
Nothing funny happened!
Nothing happened!
Yeah, nothing happened.
But I guess it was the atmosphere
It's just
It was like pure magic!
I was just really freaked out!
You have to hold it in!
Yeah, you're-you're right. That's not good
What were you laughing at?
Well, I was just thinking
that he wouldn't drink it himself.
That's true
That's a pretty straightforward reason
Well, let's take a look anyway
He's got it, right?
You drink first
There's no way...
That's pretty serious!
What happened? Why?!
It doesn't make sense!
What happened?
He definitely laughed
I don't get it
What was funny?
Well, it wasn't a full laugh
It was just...
It came out
What a waste!
That's pretty bad!
It might be a straight out!
That was pretty bad!
He'd be out immediately
after four hours!
Straight red!
I'm sorry, everyone!
Please give me a break!
-Yellow!
-I'm sorry
Yellow, yellow!
But watch out
Yeah, let's do so
That happens sometimes
Yeah, it was out of habit
That was surprising
That was pretty close!
Osada, no second chances!
-Yeah!
-That's rough!
No one can pull that off again
Shut up, shut up
I actually got married!
Who was it?
Master Kiyoshi
Good morning!
Try a three-point-inversion in the morning!