I've always wanted to do this someday.
Finally, we decided to do this.
This is great.
"Just when we thought we've reached the end, there was more."
I want all the previous winners to appear and decide the true champion, the King of Kings.
"The King of Kings of Documental"
The 100 million tsukkomi.
The movement has stopped.
The chill revolution ended long ago.
Nationalism in this country is about using meta jokes and basic jokes to ridicule each other.
What you need is not an ism, but a rhythm.
Notice the distorted cognition.
More than enough is too much.
Keep the beat witty.
A trackmaker who does both ordinary jokes and dirty jokes is even better than the melody of the flatterer.
The big fight @ the underground arena deeper than the culvert.
A dark gambling worth letting your earned money turn to dust.
Rogues aim for the head of the KING of COMEDY, where chaos is planned.
Xiaoli doesn't work either.
Four trillion subliminal returns.
Take it down with a forehead Joyman.
Stars and Stripes of Human Bullet vs. Resurrected Gold Pig.
Inflate the tenga with your nose and shout this.
"I want to know defeat."
"I would like to lose just once."
"Give me the sweet humiliation of a loser."
Gera Get Out
(Gera: A person who laughs easily.)
I see...
A champion tournament.
Great! I'll do it!
A champion tournament...
Am I allowed to compete?
I'm a challenger.
Because I think I'm the lowest.
I won't run away because I'm a fighter.
I have to do things that push myself to the brink of death.
I want to crush Zakoshi in the champion tournament.
Make the drawn masks laugh.
Violence that changes the form of the tyrant of comedy.
Exorcise the loveless guardian angels and turn it into a laugh.
Raflesia and Amnesia with big smiles.
Hamelin's Pied Piper's Cheesing.
The cost of Malice&Mice.
Get 'em a contingency fee without orthodox method.
It's exciting because God only knows what will happen.
"The Room for Spirit, Time, Comedy, and Patience"
"They are the ones who never laugh
but can definitely make you laugh."
"Super-crowded space
with destructive and defensive capabilities."
"Ultra high risk
Ultra high reward"
"Anyone who does not compete in the Documental
is not a comedian."
The winner of this tournament should go abroad.
That guy should represent Japan in the world championship.
That's a good idea.
Gera Get Out
"There can only be one."
"This is the King’s Tomb."
Documental - Season 10
Episode 1 “The Resolve of the Kings”
To My Dearest
The long rainy season has made every day a good day for mushroom picking.
The mornings and evenings have gotten much colder and I am wondering if I should take out the kotatsu these days. (Note: 1)
This time, we have decided to invite all the winners of the past Documental competitions to the Grand Champion Tournament.
Since this is the champion tournament, you do not need to bring 1 million yen.
Please come empty-handed.
The champion will receive a cash prize of 10 million yen.
Of course, you may decline.
But I am sure you will all come.
The season of waiting for spring will begin again.
I wish you all a glorious spring.
From Hitoshi Matsumoto
"The Contestant Comedians Entry"
Today is the Documental Grand Champion Tournament.
It's great!
This time we have a new position called observer.
Please come that room once in a while to stir stuff up.
Of course you guys are allowed to laugh.
Oh, I'm allowed to laugh?
That sounds like fun!
Only the challengers are not allowed to laugh.
You are all allowed to laugh.
But we are not in the habit of laughing in that room.
Right!
I'm sure you're right.
Yeah, it's kind of a weird feeling, I guess.
Also, if you laugh, we'll take a small cut of your fee.
Hey, are we just going to take risks?
Do they know who's coming this time?
- Of course they do.
- Only the winners will be here this time.
I'm the first one here?
- Kotouge did a great job.
- Yeah
Hello.
Here you are.
The time has finally come.
I want to do a dirty comedy that cannot be aired on TV.
"He was the winner of Season 2,
earning 10 million yen in prize money."
He is the one who made everyone think that Documental are hilarious.
Was it really a comedy?
That was a great scene that will go down in history.
"A shouting comedian
from Sony Music Artists
who excels at offense and defense."
If anything he's more of the dramatic type.
Cheap jokes will never work on them.
"Raging Machine-gun Monk"
Documental has no rules.
I want to take away all the limiters and give it my all.
This is a comedy street fight.
I have to be prepared to break 5 or 6 bones.
I have no idea how much this will affect my future TV work.
I don't care if I lose two or three of my regular shows because of this.
I haven't been here in a long time.
Oh, hello!
Here he is.
Yamamoto of Gokuraku Tombo.
You are carrying a lot of his stuff.
Did he win?
Yes, he did.
Yeah.
But we were criticized by viewers who asked "Did he win?"
Excuse me.
No thank you.
I can't.
I can't do it.
"He was the winner of Season 3,
earning 10 million yen in prize money."
I think Yamamoto will be very spirited this time.
Because he's been criticized a lot.
People say, "Yamamoto didn't win."
I have competed in the same season as him.
At some point he tried to go under the radar.
He knows that.
He must be coming here today with the intention of showing off something great.
"Resurrected Gold Pig"
I have done many simulations since I received the offer.
No matter how many times I simulated, I always lost.
Then I decided to enjoy it.
I didn't think I would be here again.
They know who will be here, so they will take their own measures.
Yeah, it's totally different from our match.
It's totally different.
This is a nostalgic place.
That was quick.
Here comes Cookie from Yasei Bakudan.
He has already won twice.
TWO TIMES!
Hello.
A champion tournament?
Actually, I've been waiting for this.
I've been wanting to compete in the champion tournament for a long time.
Finally this letter reached me.
"He was the winner of Season 4 & 8,
earning 20 million yen in prize money."
Cookie is the favorite.
But his defense is the weakest among today's members.
He laughs so easily that he has to go on the attack first to counteract it.
"Comedian Killer"
I have never seen a view beyond the "hilarious".
I'd like to see it.
I want to crush Zakoshi and become champion for the third time.
"Finally, the two encounter each other."
I can't lose to him.
But I can't imagine losing to him.
I can only imagine my victory.
What should I buy with 10 million yen?
He is a crazy person, so he will laugh if I do something crazy.
I will seppuku him in front of zakoshi.
And he will laugh if something funny comes out of my belly.
I lost to Yamamoto-san.
I was there when you won.
I don't know how I won either.
You were with Yamamoto-san when you competed for the first time, weren't you?
It wasn't the first time, it was the second time.
I was in the season 1.
Then that's the second time.
- Zakoshi is here.
- He is strong.
Only the strong guy come here.
Here you are.
Oh, I received this again!
Nice!
Documental is me.
This is my show.
This is my tournament.
"He was the winner of Season 5 & 7,
earning 20 million yen in prize money."
He was attacking relentlessly.
How many jokes does he have?
The number of jokes will determine the winner.
This guy is incredibly strong.
And hilarious.
He never looks our way.
He only thinks of himself next.
He does not let his guard down.
I'd like to hear what he laughed his belly off at.
"Dump Truck Without Brakes"
I enjoy Documental the most.
I make jokes every day so that I am always ready for the Documental.
I don't spend my days slacking off.
No matter who comes, they are no match for me.
After all, zakoshi is strong.
He's scary, but I'm looking forward to him.
Even if we know what he's going to do, we can't stop him.
His digital jokes are insane.
I am Mr. Documental.
I'll give you a scolding!
I'm going to change the shape of you!
(Note: 2)
Are the winners entering in order?
Maybe so.
They are all shaved heads.
"The theory that shaved heads are the winners."
Is there a theory that shaved heads will win the Documental?
Everybody wants to win.
Who doesn't want to win?
I don't think I can.
Then abstain.
Here she comes.
She's the only woman.
She's a tough opponent, too.
Here you go.
Is this the mileage card I applied for?
I'm very honored and pleased.
"She was the winner of Season 6,
earning 10 million yen in prize money."
Her defense is solid.
She continues to attack with weak jokes.
Opponents won't like that.
She is very persistent.
She does one thing all the time.
If you fall for her tricks, you are in trouble.
"The smashing girl who has lost a lot of weight”
You've lost weight.
I'm fatter than Arisa Mizuki.
(Note: 3)
See?
That's a depressing joke.
I don't challenge as a winner.
I challenge as a loser.
So I'm not stressing.
I want to compete with the intention of learning from the skills and balls of my seniors.
I'm very excited!
I really wonder what will happen today.
How cute.
This conversation is out of this world.
You all have beautiful eyes.
What's so beautiful about this guy's eyes?
He has eyes that look like they were carved with a carving knife.
He is the last.
Here he comes.
You all have a lot of baggage.
This is the finale, right?
It's not a finale.
If we do this champion tournament, it's the finale, right?
Hello.
What? What is it?
Ah, here it come!
"Dear Kubota
I'm in love with your talent."
" I want you to compete it."
"Downtown also grew up watching Kubota in some ways.
I'm waiting for you.
From Hitoshi Matsumoto"
Hey, is this for real?
It's going to be fun and stimulating.
"He won the Season 8 that never came to be,
but was stripped of his prize money."
"But he won in Season 9,
earning a total of 20 million yen in carried-over prize money."
I'll crawl out of hell as many times as I have to.
I wanna be very popular with women and get laid with them very much.
I wanna kiss a lot of women in this day and age.
I haven't laid with a woman, but I've laid with the Goddess of Comedy.
Kubota is really hilarious at times.
I have high expectations for him.
But sometimes he is not funny at all.
He has quite a few ups and downs.
"Never Ending Self-desperation"
In another five or six years, comedy will die.
So I'll make memories.
Kubota is insane.
Hello!
Hello.
You guys are getting a long fine.
It is the champion tournament, right?
You guys are getting a long fine at the champion tournament?
Sorry.
Should we have been tense?
I was going to out all of you.
Is that over?
That's not going to happen.
Shall we all go around to places with spiritual energy?
Yeah!
That sounds more fun.
Today we have gathered only those who have experience of winning.
For Kubota and Zakoshi, they may win a total of 30 million yen.
Right.
This time you guys are not giving out 1 million yen.
So you guys will not lose anything.
Let's decide the true champion today.
But you all are used to seeing this, right?
No, it's not!
I still can't get used to it.
It has power.
Yamamoto's victory spark controversial.
Controversial...
You were very criticized in the review section.
I did something controversial...
Are you already depressed?
It shows on your face.
Stay strong!
That being said, I won.
I brought three more cards today.
You will be ejected when you get a red card from me.
The time limit is six hours.
Six hours is still better.
Is that so?
Yes, I prefer six hours instead of four.
Really so?
This time, unlike usual, there are people called observers.
We prepared someone just to stir stuff up.
Will they come to this room?
In some cases they will come here.
Basically, you are the only people in this room.
Of course, oservers are allowed to laugh.
But please do not laugh along with them.
I see
May I use them for my jokes?
Of course you can.
In six hours we will find out who is the King of Kings.
Good luck to everyone.
It will begin a short while after I return to my room.
- Are we starting already?
- Of course.
Do your best!
Thank you!
See you.
Use the props around here as you like, as usual.
Good bye.
Let's not laugh.
Ugh, is it about to start?
It's okay to laugh now, right?
If you want to laugh, now is the time.
I'm a laughing easily, so I'm going to laugh right now.
You smoke too early.
Then let's start.
Champion tournament!
The Documental Grand Champion Tournament is started!
Let's not mix up our bags.
Yeah.
Who's going to attack first?
They will all have come up with a strategy.
I am about to laugh.
Everyone has a big bag.
Mistaking a package for someone else could be fatal.
Ah, I am about to laugh.
Come on!!
The vibe is so different from the past.
Yeah.
Their enthusiasm is different from the past too.
Let's do something to cheer up!
Are you going to do it already?
Let's do something!
They are still in the locker room.
Were you trying to do something?
Let's do something!
Zako, you smacked me upside the head earlier, didn't you?
What?
You smacked me earlier.
No, I didn't.
Suddenly you...
And please don't call zakoshi Zako.
(Note: 4)
Why?
I can call this guy Zako, right?
That is my concern.
You should call him Zakoshi or Shisho.
He is Zako.
It hasn't even been a few minutes since we started and suddenly you don't want to be smacking other people's heads.
Once it starts we should be allowed to do whatever we want.
No, no, no...
Kubota...
You can't help that anymore.
And it sounded good.
Yuriyan is holding something in the back.
Yeah, right
Maybe she'll hit him too if he's off guard.
Yeah!
Do they staring contest in such a situation!?
Do they make funny faces?
Do they staring contest in the champion tournament?
I haven't seen this in a while.
It's a great opening.
Coo-chan seems to laugh.
He's  laughing?
Kotouge too.
If I were here, I would be laughing.
I didn't expect them to have a staring contest.
It was truly a showdown of power.
I think we have opened up to each other.
Don't you think so?
I really think so too.
Right?
I want to smack him, too.
- Go ahead.
- Can I smack you?
Sure.
He's almost laughing because it hurts so much.
Excuse me, can only a shaved head do this?
That's right.
You want to do it too?
- Can she smack you too?
- Go ahead.
- Sure.
There's a lot of baldness.
Yeah.
High baldness rate.
- Nice.
- Good!
You can do it harder.
Can I do it?
Do more.
Kotouge is throwing that.
He's throwing that.
Hey, he put water in it.
Don't put water in it!
Hey, there's water in it.
Oh, that's nice.
Wipe the water off.
This is dangerous.
Don't hit people with that!
- Can I do it?
- Sure.
Big Kinoshita!
It’s Kinoshita.
Did he laugh?
He laughed, didn't he?
Who's Kinoshita?
(Note: 5)
It was a good cheering up.
- Really?
- Yeah, it was good.
- I actually have a Guinness record.
- What kind of record?
What is it?
I let my nails grow too long.
Ugh, that's gross.
It looks like a Medusa snake.
That's gross.
I've seen it in pictures.
It looks just like you.
Can this be used as a scarf?
In winter, yes.
Can I eat this?
Of course.
What is he doing?
What does he think it is?
Hey, Coo-chan!
Don't suck my nails!
What is this?
Oh, it stinks!
Whose impression is that?
Who?
People who just smell.
You are not an impression of someone else?
Don't sniff a woman's nails and say stink it!
So I'm supposed to apologize!?
No.
IIIIII'M SOOOOOOOOOO...
This is an exaggerated Desuyo.
(Note: 6)
RYYYYYYYYYYYYY!!!
Cookie!
This move is funny.
Yeah.
Should I have given Coo the card?
Why did you smack me first?
Let's not talk about that anymore.
That's enough.
Don't you think it would be better for you if I smacked you?
Give me a reason.
I'll say it for you.
It's because you were expelled from Yoshimoto.
(Note: 7)
He spoke collectively.
It's because you're an asshole.
You're a piece of shit.
You are a fucking pedophile.
I'm not...
Fucking pedophile.
Who is the celebrity you would most like to lay with?
Who?
Please answer seriously without cheating.
Haruka Ayase.
(Note: 8)
That's not true.
I answered like this because I didn't want to hear your prepared response.
Wha...huh...
Hey.
You can't just ask me all this crap and then give me that bland answer.
You do that sometimes.
You're trying to pick a fight with him.
You're scary.
You ask me all these questions about me, and when I answer you, you say, "huh."
Hey!
Serve you right, fucking pedophile!
"Don't take it for granted!"
Don't make fun of Kato!
(Note: 9)
- "Don't take it for granted!"
- Don't make fun of Kato!
Say Kato-"san"!
You caused him the most trouble!
You're the one who has to say Kato-"san"!
Yeah!
You fucking pedophile!!
Do you even know what you've done!?
Do you even know what you've done?
Why is he like that when he gets mad.
What the hell did you do!?
Hey!
- Reflect on it.
To top it off, you were selling meat wrapped rice balls?
You idiot!
(Note: 10)
What's that!?
Don't sell those things.
"You are not humble!"
"If you were one of our employees, I'd call you an idiot!"
"I'd call you an idiot!"
It's Money Tigers.
(Note: 11)
"You are not humble!"
It's President Kobayashi.
Well noticed.
- That's President Kobayashi, right?
- Yes!
Jackpot!
He likes Money Tigers so much.
Please don't ever do that again.
This is coming from a woman.
Don't be so clear about it.
Sorry.
- I'm kind of sorry.
- Don't worry.
Please apologize.
Yamamoto is laughing, right?
- Sorry if you guys are offended.
- That's okay, it is what it is.
- You don't get first place when you have to apologize.
- Why are you in first place?
You're third place.
You're third place, right?
Then come on, who's second or third?
What?
If I'm first in something.
If I'm first in something, who's second and third?
- In what field are you first place, asshole?
- Don't say asshole.
Pedophile.
Don't say it yourself.
Don't you ever feel reflective?
Kubota laughed?
Are you a pedophile?
Don't say that.
I'm not a pedophile!
You're a pedophile!
You have pedophile blood in your veins!
If you're not a pedophile, what are you?
Answer him.
Then what are you?
If you are...
You guys are really out to get me, aren't you!
What are you guys doing!?
Indeed.
Because you...
You guys teamed up or something!?
No!
I'm blind in one eye.
That’s bad!
I'm blind in both eyes.
That's just violence.
He hit the woman.
Are you okay?
This is terrible!
This is dangerous.
Are you okay, Yuriyan?
Don't touch her boobs!
She is in danger!
Hey, don't touch her boobs!
Yamamoto laughed!
Yamamoto-san laughed.
Yamamoto-san?
No, it wasn't me.
I don't think this was me.
Wasn't that Kubota?
No.
I don't know but I think it was Kubota.
Who laughed?
You know...
You were just chilling.
What does that mean?
Were we grinning?
Yes, there is such an atmosphere.
Among them, one in particular was laughing.
Yamamoto.
Me!?
You almost laughed several times, but somehow you managed pull through.
But the boobs thing definitely made you laugh.
Was I laughing?
Let's watch the replay.
Yamamoto was grinning throughout the whole thing.
She fell down in a weird way.
This is out.
Really?
Yes, this is out.
You're still laughing.
Does that count as laughing?
You absolutely laughed.
You were like a audience member at a comedy show.
Then I should laugh more.
I give you a yellow card, of course.
I understand.
I'll be on my guard.
You should keep your guard up and look as if you are angry.
Like this?
Why are you doing it now?
Why are you trying to make us laugh now?
You think you're gonna get points?