When comedians get married and have a wedding ceremony
It will be loud and boisterous, with other comedians messing around and making fun of each other
Say cheese, okay
Can I take another one?
However, I never feel comfortable in those situations
So this contest is like a wedding ceremony without the bride and the bridegroom
Is that glue?
Norika? Did you say Norika just now?
He clearly said it
I've always been watching this
And since I love egosearching, whenever I see questions like "who should be the next Documental contestants"
My name always appears in the answer
Apple pen
So I always wonder why am I not invited yet?
I've been waiting for this
I've always been waiting for this!
I'm more used to do owarai with others together
So I'm worried that my type of owarai may not be effective here
I have to complement the things that others did, either purposely or accidentally
He loves fishing, so maybe he wants fish sausages instead
Of course I want others to think that I'm interesting
Or else, this contest is just too tough to bear
Paying 100 million to join a contest that no one thinks you're interesting, that's too tough right?
Orange!
Don't put your arm around my waist
This is double kill
Is it necessary to put on that much?   -What the heck is this?
What a gentle penis
OUT!!
Eh?   -Do you need some more?
You want to put more?   -Is it enough?
Yeah, this is more than enough
It's easier to remove with more wax   -Eh? You must be kidding
Yeah, it's too hard already
Seriously?
It won't stick anymore
Oh, I see
Ouch, it hurts, ouch, ouch, ouch...
(Aww, I really hate these kind of things)
Can I hide it for a moment?   -Eh?
Can I hide this thing for a moment?   -Ok
It seems to be on the right track
Ouch, ouch, ouch   -It hurts?
I can't believe Tamura-san left this to us
What a terrible present
Better pull it off in one-shot
Please hold his hand
Is this going to be fine?
I don't think this is going to work at all
Just give it a try
Give it a try and finish it in one-shot
Are you ready?
Ready, set...
Wow, it removed a lot
That's amazing!
A joyful harmony
Better pull off the other side too
It removed a lot of hair   -Yeah, incredible
And that was a great harmonica melody too
(But yeah, it removed a lot of hair)
So these are those dots just now
It hurts? It doesn't hurts?
It hurts? It hurts?
It hurts?
You want us to stop this?
No, don't stop
You want to do this?   -(Takahashi...)
Do it?   -"Do it"
Put more?
Do you want to put more?
"Put more"
This is gonna be painful though, Koba
Oh my god...
Will your penis be fine though?
It definitely sticked to his penis
Are you fine with this?
I'll do it
Wait a second, you're holding his pubic hair?
Is it fine to pull if off like this?
He said "no way"
But then this is never going to end
Can he hold your hair?   -Just try it once
Can I hold your hair?
He said "just for once"
"i-kai-da-ke (just for once)"
He said "i-kai-da-ke (just for once)"
I'll finish this   -Finish it
Ready, set...
The pain surpassed the harmonica, and we can even hear his voice
What about putting the vibrator here and switch it on, so he can focus on this instead
Oh, I see what you mean   -So to shift his focus
Zakoshi is starting something
Oh, it's on
It's coming, it's coming, I can feel it
-Are you ready?   -Wait a second...
Zakoshi is here
Are you guys still doing it?
You mean this?
Yeah, are you guys still doing it?
He stopped
He stopped all of a sudden
Hey you, touch here, touch here
Touch it?   -Yes, touch here
Why?   -Just touch it
I almost cummed
Touch here, touch here
I just cummed
He cummed?
I almost cummed
-Is he laughing?   -I almost cummed
(Nice, nice one)
(Very nice, very nice)
I almost cummed
It was such a tough time
Why didn't he let me cum?
Please let me make a call
Food delivery?
No, someone asked me to call him
For this time
Well, I've been thinking about this for a while
They can invite one helper
Did something happen?
They can ask someone to come
So an outsider will blend into the group
Just like Windom in Ultraseven
A capsule monster, so they can use one capsule
He consulted me
Hello   -Hello
Hey
I've told you about this in LINE already, but I really think you should quit
No, please let me do it again
No, that's impossible
I feel like I have the potential to do this, please let me try once more
It's gonna be tough
I'll work hard, I can do this
That's just your opinion
I can do this, seriously, let me show it to you
Can you come over here now?
I'm nearby, so yes
My seniors are here too, so let's finish this quickly
No problem   -I don't think I'll change my mind though
Got it, I will be right there   -Okay
Sorry for this   -Who's that?
My friend consulted me   -You tell him to quit?
Yeah, I told him to quit, but...
But he still wants to do it?   -Yes
Excuse me, please give us a moment
Who is it?
It's just impossible, honestly
Hasegawa Hozumi
Boxing world titles in three weight classes
I really want to return to professional boxing
I told you that's impossible
I can definitely do this
No way, we're at the same age so I know this, there's just a limit to our stamina
But I really feel like I have the potential to do this
Just for once, please
Fine, show me your moves then
Why is he consulting Yamauchi?
I will test your reflexes, to see if you're qualified
If you can do well, then I'll think about it
Are you ready?
What the heck can you test with that?
This is meaningless
Hey, this test is meaningless
This test is...completely meaningless
He said it's meaningless
This test is meaningless
But he still completed it
Next, show me your punch
One, two, got it?
Did Yamaguchi boxed before?   -Never heard of it
Just like this
Good, okay
One, two, good
Now one, two, and hit my body
Let's see if your punches can do any damage
Take it seriously
Come on
One, two, body
It's doing damage
Come on, one, two, body
This is amazing
Please stop, better stop this, Yamauchi
Yamauchi, seriously, please...
Just let him return to professional boxing
Hey, Yamauchi...
No, Yamauchi, come on...
Your body is being destroyed
This is incredible
You regained your strength
Can I still do this?
Yeah, I think so
I'll contact you later
Return to professional boxing...let me think about it again
Please contact me again, thanks for your time
This is unbelievable
He's Hozumi-san, right?
How come? Have you boxed before?
Not at all
Not at all?   -Yes
He regained his strength
No way, you don't know about his golden age
He said he wants to do it again, so...
Is this the studio?
Huh?
Did I get it wrong?
Well, yes, this is the studio
How can we help you?
I mean, is this the music studio?   -Oh, nope, this is not the music studio
I'm actually a musician
So you guys are not having a music festival here?
Nope, we're not   -Oh, I see
I'm actually a freelance musician now
Okay
I'm self-employed
And I sing whatever comes to my mind
Like a singer-songwriter?
What songs did you write?
Well, the song of order
Order? The song of order?
The song of order
The song of order?
A song that questions the order of things
That's unique   -I wanna hear your song
"Date first then have sex, or have sex first then date", that's what the song is about
Can you sing it for us?
"Date first then have sex, or have sex first then date"
The tempo is like this
That's the song of order
Are there other versions?
Yes, there are, I basically sing the story of people's life
All about order?
Yes, the song of order, "Date first then have sex, or have sex first then date"
Is that the climax of the song?   -Yes
So there's other parts too?
Yes, of course
It starts with "What did you do after a date?"
"We went to a hot spring after a date"
"What did you do after going to a hot spring?"
"We went to a hotel after going to a hot spring"
"What did you do after going to a hotel?"
"We drank sake after going to a hotel"
"What did you do after drinking sake?"
"Yes, of course we had sex"
"Date first then have sex, or have sex first then date"
This is the song of order
What is the message of the song?
Well, I'm really curious, do people have date first then have sex, or the other way round?
Oh, well, both can be true, it depends
That's why I made a song about it
Like do people wear jeans first then wear shirts, or wear shirts first then wear jeans
Is there a version about wearing clothes?   -Yes, of course
Wearing clothes?
So all about wearing clothes?   -Like jeans and shirts?
"Wear jeans first then wear shirts, or wear shirts first then wear jeans"
"Wear jeans first then wear shirts"
"Wear shirts first then wear jeans"
"Or wear shirts first then wear jeans"
"Wear jeans first then wear shirts"
"Nope, wear shirts first then wear jeans"
He has a powerful voice
I see
What do you guys do?
Well, we are comedians
I aimed to be a comedian before too
Eh? You aimed to be a comedian?
Did you aim to be a comedian first, then became a musician?
Or did you became a musician first, then aimed to be a comedian?
"Aimed to be a comedian first, then became a musician"
"After becoming a musician, of course we had sex"
Had sex?
Yes, I really love it
Having sex?   -Yes
Do you write music first, then write lyrics?
Or do you write lyrics first, then write music?
"What do you do after writing lyrics?"
"Of course we write music"
"What do you do after writing music?"
"Of course we do recording"
"What do you do after recording?"
"Yes, of course we have sex!!!"
He really likes it, he likes sex
Come on, please leave
Please leave
Hey! Someone, please!
Hey!
Someone, please!
Hey, someone please
Hey, someone please?
Does anyone have a PSP charger?
What did you say?
Does anyone have a...
...PSP charger?
No, we don't
Oh jeez
What game are you playing?
Are you talking to me?
I have been playing Tetris
Tetris?
We, the Takarazuka Revue, is doing a theater performance nearby
*The Takarazuka Revue is a Japanese all-female musical theater troupe. Women play all roles in lavish, Broadway-style productions of Western-style musicals.
And I planned to play games during my spare time
You're from Takarazuka?   -Are you a women?
Are you a women?
I'm sorry for being remiss in not introducing myself
I'm Osuda Kaoru from the Takarazuka Revue
Osuda Kaoru?
Please call me Osukaoru for short
You're a women?
Which troupe do you belong to?
*Takarazuka Revue is divided into 5 troupes: Flower, Moon, Snow, Star, Cosmos
The North Troupe
The North Troupe?
Not the Flower Troupe or the Moon Troupe?
Yes, we're divided into the East, South, West, North troupes
Our...   -Our?
Daga...Taka...Takarazu...
Daga?
That's how our Takarazuka Revue works
Does anyone have a PSP charger?
Nope, we don't
How could this happen to me?
How should I spend my spare time then?
Fine
If this is how it's gonna be
I'll just have to dance happily and cheerfully
Shall we dance?
Eh?   -He's inviting you
No way, I know nothing about Takarazuka
No worries, I will lead you through   -Let him lead you
By the way, did you ever dance?
No, not at all
Then just let me...
Please stand up...
Eh? Let you what?   -Please stand up
Let me lead you through
I'm really worried
"The brightness of hope and dreams"
"We all have our dreams"
But what should you do when you feel frustrated and overwhelmed?
I will...
"It will soon become our memory"
"So when you are feeling sad and frustrated"
"We shall face forward and..."
"Move forward"
Finally, I managed to kill the time
I am really thankful to you   -No problem
If anyone found my PSP charger
Please let me know at the venue nearby
Venue?
*The Takarazuka Revue only performs in their own Takarazuka Theater
We are doing performances at other places now
It's called the "Weekend Takarazuka"
Something like the "Weekend Yoshimoto?
*Yoshimoto holds Owarai live performances "Weekend Yoshimoto" at many difference places
I've never heard of that, but ours is called the "Weekend Takarazuka"
Yoshimoto has performances called "Weekend Yoshimoto" too
We, Takarazuka, has the same thing too
So please come and watch our performance
Thank you for your time
He attacked aggressively, huh?
Yeah, he attacked aggressively
Akiyama, take a look at this
What is this?
I borrowed this from someone
Someone we know?
Flip it over, right?
A Gold driver's license   -Why the heck is this dude Gold?***
*Gold is the highest rank of Japan's driver's license, only given to drivers who didn't break any driving rules for 5 years
*However, the owner of this license, Tsutsumishita Atsushi, was found by a police officer to be in a groggy state in the driver's seat of a car after having taken sleeping pills, and was put on suspension by Yoshimoto
Even this dude is Gold, come on
He's a Gold driver?   -Yes, he's Gold
You borrowed this from him?   -Yes
He changed his LINE icon recently
Oh, really?   -Yes, he changed it
To what?
He changed it to Peepo-kun*
*Peepo-kun is the mascot of the Toyko Metropolitan Police Department
The police mascot?   -Yes
That's provocative   -Unbelievable
Only Eikoh-chan is not from Yoshimoto, right?
Well, yes
You wanna take a look at Yoshimoto's wage slip?
Eh?
Who's wage slip?
This is for real   -Is this the real one?
Yes, it's the real one
I wonder who's wage slip is it?
Is this fine? I feel guilty
For January
Who's is it?
You don't always get to see other's wage slip
Should I hide it first?
Oh, it's Tsutsumishita Atsushi
Which month?   -January
It's really long
Look at his wage
Minus 5,400 yen
The cost of finding other comedians to replace him
What is this?
Look at how much he earned for appearing in Ametalk DVD6, 25 yen
What did he do at all?
Because he's suspended, so...   -Exactly
So all he can earn is from those DVDs   -Yes, exactly
Lincoln Comedian Sports Day
1 yen   -1 yen?
How can you even transfer that money?
So how much did he earn in total?
9,513 yen
This dude is earning a lot, huh? Tsutsumishita
Yeah, he's earning so much
Given the fact that he didn't work at all
How much did you earn when you were suspended, Eikoh-chan?
Zero   -Oh, zero?
All I earned was from those DVDs too...
So, let's go for the zombies
Zombie time
This scared me
We have to endure this
It's Jimmy-san, right?
Jimmy-san and Tamura, that's awful
He looks exactly the same as before
Many hours have passed already...
And he still looks exactly the same, nothing changed at all
World cup
Please give me a moment...
Just give me a moment...
Singapore*
*Singapore can also be interpreted as "a hidden pole (芯がポール)"
Singapore is written on it too
Oh, so you mean a hidden pole?
Singapore
Ouch, ouch, ouch
Raw?
Yeah, it's raw...
Ouch, ouch, ouch
I said it hurts
Where did you buy this thing?
Eh?   -Where did you buy this thing?
Online sales
1,980 yen after discounts
Is that how it is?
Eh?   -Is that how it is?
You didn't do anything to it?   -Eh?
You didn't do anything to it?
No, I didn't, that's how it is
You can buy this thing?   -Eh?
He never understands the questions at the first time
But if you lift it's chin, your pole can come out smoothly
My Singapore
Is it fastened?
Yes, it's fastened, my Singapore
Actually...I...today...
Ouch!
On the Shinkansen...
Ouch, ouch, ouch
Hey dude, don't flip my skirt up, it hurts
It really hurts
When I was on the Shinkansen today...ouch...
Can I just take this off?
Nope, you can't
But it hurts
Wait...ouch, ouch...
The tip of my toe is...   -The tip of your toe?
No, not the tip of my toe
The tip of your toe?
It hurts?
Not the tip of my toe
The tip...the tip...the tip of my penis
The tip of my penis
It feels like it's pinched by a zipper
That must be painful   -Yes, it hurts so bad
Are you having an erection now?
No I'm not, no
It's just pinched, so it's really painful
Ouch, ouch, ouch
There's nothing we can do though
Because I have phimosis
Coming out all of a sudden
But there's nothing we can do though...
Well, it doesn't matter
It doesn't matter?   -Yeah, it doesn't matter
When I was on the Shinkansen today
My hands got pinched by the door
And they're congested now
Not only my hands though   -Not only your hands?
My feet too
You feet are congested too?
My feet got pinched too
How did that happen?
That's just impossible
I got pinched like this
No way, that's impossible
Both my hands and feet got pinched like this
That's why they're red?
Wait a second, wait a second...
-It's so round   -Wait, wait, wait a second...
Stop, stop, wait a second...
They're congested
His balls are so round
You have bunions, huh?
Eh?
It's fine for you to laugh, Jimmy-san
You can laugh, Jimmy-san
Oh, really?
You're a zombie, so it's fine
Oh yeah, I'm a zombie so it's fine...
Sorry for this
Let's play Russian Roulette
Scary, scary, God knows what's inside that gun
Shall I go first then?
I'll go first, so...
Pass this around and take your turn
Scary, scary, what happens if the pistol is loaded?
Well, you'll probably die
Eh? Die? For real?
How many bullets are there?   -I don't wanna die
Why can't you understand it at the first time?   -12 rounds
No way, that's impossible
Isn't it 6 rounds?   -Yes, 6 rounds
So one in six shots
Will fire?   -Will fire
It's gonna sound like "Bang"?
Eh?
How else could it sound like?
Will something come out?
Eh?
Excuse me, will something come out?
Stop asking others to repeat themselves
Eh?
Bang, just Bang
What's that cap for?
This is just for firefighting   -Firefighting?
Anyway, I'll go first
I'll go for it
So it's me
Better heal your bunions
I told you it's fine to laugh
That was so close
Singapore almost got me
How he tries to hold back his laughter is funny too
It's funny that he didn't get changed too
What's that for, Zakoshi?
I just wanna take a bath
Eh?
Bath
-Quite difficult to adjust the temperature though
-Both of you are taking a bath
You're gonna take a bath?   -Yes, I want a bath
It's so hot! So difficult to adjust the temperature
Oh, it's just right now
Is this gonna work?
I just really wanna take a bath
Is this fine?
Will it break?   -I told you it's impossible
It should be fine
It's just impossible to take a bath with that
Of course I can   -The size is different
Is it safe to do it on the table?
Maybe this will break?
Better just do it on the floor
What the heck are you doing, Akiyama?
He's taking a bath for real
He's having a perfect bath
How is it?
The temperature is just right
Oh, I see
They are taking a bath in different styles
Oh, maybe it's a bit too hot   -Too hot?
Let Akiyama take a bath with that too
Is Akiyama taking a bath with cold water?
May I?   -Yes, sure
Ah, it's a bit too hot
Yeah, it's a bit too hot
I think it should be just right now
Can you please let me try it again?   -Yeah, sure
Excuse me
The temperature should be just right now
Ah, so warm
Maybe a bit too hot   -A bit too hot?
Is this how you take a bath?
That's pretty unique
This is how you should wash your penis
You have to soak the root of your penis in hot water as well
Or else you could catch a cold   -Catch a cold?
I remember Gauguin did a painting about this
That's quite rare
Can you fit it all in?
You can?!
Just with that?
Oh, he's done
So he's taking a cold bath now*
*After coming out from a hot onsen, people usually use a cold water bath to cool down
Ah, this feels so good
Thank you very much
Maybe it's time to let out Tamuken zombie?
Okay, let's go for it
Zombie time
This really scared me
It looks so much fun, huh?
Yeah, it looks really fun
Oh, really?   -Yeah
I was actually quite confident with that too
I really like that one
It's really popular in Osaka
Heh-monica*
*"Heh" means fart in Japanese, so combined with Harmonica, the game is called "Heh-monica"
Hey everybody, Jimmy wants to play Heh-monica
So please stand over there
Eh? Again?
If you hear him letting it out, remember to let us know
Huh? Let what out?
The sound of the Harmonica
You lose if you let out any sound, that's Heh-monica
Okay, so Jimmy is playing this
We can clearly see it
What?
He's still wearing his Singapore
Are you wearing it?
Nope, I'm not   -You're definitely wearing it
We can clearly see it
What are you laughing at?
Better just hold it
Are you ready?
Remember not to let out any sound
I'm going do it now, are you ready?
Oh, where did it go?
It's broken
My Singapore too...
It's sticking out!
Singapore is sticking out
These things could happen, huh?
La
La?
He has perfect pitch
Was that La though?
La
The pitch was different from the first one, dude
Give me a Mi now, Mi
Mi?   -Give me a Mi
What is it?
Mi
Say La, dude!
You should say La here, dude!
Don't say Mi
Even if it's Mi, just say La
We'll be back
We've been alone for so long
Ouch!
Oh my god! That was close!
That almost got me!
That was so close!
I feel like that's the origin of Owarai
We tried really hard   -I'm sure you guys did
I think two people laughed
Eh? Who?
Probably Takahashi and Jinnai
Eh?
No, Takahashi definitely laughed
But I endured it
Let's take a look
We've been alone for so long
Ouch!
That's just the same kind of face that Junior did before
You laughed out loud at that one
Yes, he did, he did
Both of you are out
Hooray!
Both of them?   -This is a big turning point
Yeah, this is a big turning point
Everyone is nearly out now
Except Zakoshi
Yeah this dude, Zakoshi...
He's zero, right?
Yes, zero
What the heck?
But Zakoshi has been attacking aggressively too
So no complaints to make, honestly
Yeah, if I didn't attack, then...   -Then, yeah
Anyway
We're leaving   -Good work guys
How should I put it?
That place is magical, honestly
"What did you do after drinking sake?"
"Yes, of course we had sex"
"Date first then have sex, or have sex first then date"
That place is a lot more magical than I expected
Arghh...I just feel...umm...
I feel frustrated
Well...arghh...
Yeah...
Jimmy-san is just too much
Ouch!
I have no choice but to laugh
I know I will be out at some point, but...arghh
Pheww...
That was incredible
That was incredible, but I wonder what will happen next
Let's start
Zakoshi can you sit on the sofa over there
And imitate Kurisu Masanobu by yourself forever, since it never got a laugh
Okay, sure
Kurisu Masanobu, you got it?   -Yeah, no problem
But Junior-san don't know him, right?
He won't laugh even if he knows him anyway
Kurisu Masa..?   -Masanobu
Who is he?   -A professional wrestler
A bald wrestler
That imitation didn't even get a laugh from wrestling fans
Just do it by yourself
What are you doing, dude?
Of course I have to give him the Final cut (wrestling move)
What the heck are you doing?
Just get out of my way
I told you to get out of my away
Get out!
What are you doing, dude?
What's this?
What the heck is this?
What are you doing, dude?
I'm in a tag match now
Of course I have to give him the Final cut (wrestling move)
Get out of my way!
I told you to get out of my way!
What are you doing, dude?
I told you I'm in a tag match!
That scene was interesting
This thing is amazing
What the heck is this?
Superb
That was superb
Who's point is this though?
The points go to Kanoh, who brought this toy, and Junior, who passed him the Harmonica
Akiyama out!
You worked really hard though
So the last hour
Only one more hour left?
Zakoshi is so damn strong! He's even the nearest to that toy
That scene was just...I couldn't avoid it
I won't laugh if it's just the sound of a Harmonica
But that monkey replied in the exact same pitch
So I just have to give up and laugh
There's actually still a lot of items in my bag
And there's still plenty of time for me to make them laugh
So I want to change my mood and try my best to make them laugh
Let's start
Zakoshi, this time...
Do a imitation of Fuyuki Hiromichi over there, which never got a laugh on stage
Fuyuki can definitely get a laugh
Fuyuki Hiromichi?
With Chono, right?   -Yes
So Chono (wrestler) is over here
And Fuyuki Hiromichi is a wrestler who is bad at speaking smoothly
And he said "If I team up with Chono, no one can beat us, right?"
But because he's bad at speaking smoothly, so he said it like this...
If I team up with Chono, no one can beat us...right?
So he's gonna do a imitation of this?
He did it just now
That's all
I did it already
Okay, let's go for it
Zombie time
This scared me
So zombies again
That was close
He came back immediately as a zombie
My body is feeling heavy recently
So I started doing gymnastic formation to train my body
And of course I'm not doing it alone, I'm doing it with ordinary people
Well, you know, it's quite troublesome to go to gyms
So I've invited someone today
Excuse me, please come in
Nice to meet you
Nice to meet you too
Thanks for coming   -Thanks for having me
Do you know me?
Yes, I'm a big fan of yours
I've chosen you from many other applicants
Thank you very much   -Let's work hard together
Do you know what we'll be doing? Basically gymnastic formation
Yes, that's all I know
We'll be moving our bodies a lot   -Oh, I see
So please come over here   -Okay
Excuse me
Let's choose the theme randomly from this box
Sorry for being dumb...
Thank you so much for coming today
Asakusa? Is this Asakusa?
Anyway, let's choose this one
Oh, so Asakusa's Kaminarimon
Asakusa's Kaminarimon
How should we do this?
How?
It's gymnastic formation, so...
How should we do this? So...
Please spread your legs like this
Spread your legs wider, this will be the gate*
*Kaminarimon literally means "Thunder Gate"
There're many tourists here, so...
So please spread your legs wider
Okay, looks good
Oh, is this the Kaminarimon?
Woohoo
Oof...
It's pretty rare to go through the Kaminarimon like this
Oof...woohoo...
You're such a small Kaminarimon, huh?   -Yes
A narrowed Kaminarimon   -I'm short
What did you say?   -Because I'm short
Why is this different from the Kaminarimon that I know?
Because I'm short
But it looks attractive from here
Thank you
Why is it so attractive?
So attractive...
Well, let's go for the next one?
Let's do more
What will this be?
(Amazing! How come no one is laughing?)
-Piano performance
How should we do a piano performance?
Because you're a lady, so you can be the pianist
And I'll be the piano
Please give a performance, come on
Yes, good, just like that
Why classical music?
Come on, play over there too, the high notes
The high notes...
The keyboard is down there
The keyboard...not here...
Where is the keyboard?
Come on, tell me where is the keyboard?
Keyboard? I can't find the keyboard...
Aha? You're ignoring one part of the keyboard, huh?
No, I'm not   -She's ignoring one part, right?
You're ignoring one part of the keyboard, huh?
She's definitely ignoring one part
Let's go for the next one
What will it be?
Driving a bulldozer
How do you drive a bulldozer?
How should we do this?
Do you know how to drive?
Yes, I do
Okay, then let's do this...
Just drive like this
Drive like this?
What do you mean to drive like this?
Sit over here
Sit over there?   -Yes
Why?
Ah, that's embarrassing!
Please sit over here
That's embarrassing!
You have to sit here to drive
No, no, no...
I've chosen you from many other applicants
I could have chosen anybody   -Okay
Not okay, please sit over here
That's embarrassing!   -You have to sit here
Sit over here, this is the chair...yes, good...
Move forward, more, more...
Eh?   -More, more...move forward
You have to sit here to drive
Because this is the chair
You have to move forward
But that's so embarrassing!
Come on...   -That's embarrassing!
What's this?
Sixty nine? What does that mean?
Sixty nine?
That's my age
That was close, that was so close
I just can't take this anymore
The shyness is just right, which makes her really cute
Thank you very much
She's not being overly excited, which is brilliant
Yamauchi was very close, but...
Barely safe
Koba!
You completely laughed, right?
Yes, I laughed   -You completely laughed
Let's take a look
What's this?
Sixty nine? What does that mean?
Sixty nine?
That's my age
You clearly laughed
But it's a pleasant laugh
A heartful laugh   -Yes
So...
You're out
I really want to watch that 69 though
Four more people left
Well, actually...
This may sound like an excuse
But the casting was terrible for me
How come?
I came here to pick a fight, but then I found out they're all my friends
And I was panicked because of that
On top of that, those pleasant moments just got me laughing
So I laughed twice, both because I felt warm and pleasant
Do you need to put on that much?
What the heck is this?
What a gentle penis
Yeah, he has a smart penis
It looks like a Mizuame now
I came here to be banned by the broadcaster, that's how determined I was
But then, I simply had a good time
Let's start
This scared me
Can I take these off now?
Eh?
Can I take these off?
Yeah sure, of course   -It looks scary
Oh, really?
Can you take these off for me?
No, no way   -Too scary to touch other's eyes
This is actually my first time to wear contacts by myself
But others can't take it off for you
Others can't? Legally speaking?
Not legally, but still...
Well, legally speaking, of course others can
Hygienically...   -Hygienically speaking?
It's dirty
Eh?
Tissue?
I've been rubbing my eyes like this
Don't use tissues   -Just take it off with your hands
Not yet, not yet, go further
Jeez, I really need to touch my eyes
Wait a second, wait a second...
Wait a second, come on...
Come on, wait a second...
Why do I need to laugh at testicles?
Did you laugh before?
Are you out?
They're so mean
These 3 guys are so mean   -Yes, they're so mean
But you just have to accept it
You completely laughed out loud
Let's take a look
Jeez, I really need to touch my eyes
Wait a second, wait a second...
You completely laughed out loud, huh?
Yes, I'm sorry
You're out!
Hooray!   -At this point in time?
Zakoshi is too damn strong   -He's too damn strong
No, no, not really
He doesn't even seem to be enduring
Let's go
Sorry, good luck everyone
Only 40 minutes left, 40 minutes
Come on, I even scored some points...arghh...
I'm so freaking frustrated
I watched all four seasons, but honestly...
It feels completely different to be on the spot
All of the people around me are so amazing
And I started to feel ashamed for the gags that I've prepared
It really takes courage to perform, even if I'm prepared
Does anyone have a...PSP charger?
No, we don't
Oh jeez
But for being able to stay until the last 40 minutes, I think I did a great job
Let's start
May I call my helper now?
You even have a helper?   -Yes
Sure, of course   -May I?
Please come in
Zakoshi's helper
He's my junior
From the same agency?
Yes, also from Sony
His name is Charming Jiro
Is he ready?
Please come in
Nice to meet you
-Jiro-chan, show us that gag
-Eh? Which one?
Show us Female version, Female version
Female version?   -Female version
Eh? Female version?   -Yes
But I need some time to prepare
Come on, dude! You came in here and you still need time to prepare? No way!
Sorry, but well...I really need some time to prepare
No you don't!
Fine, prepare yourself over there then
Female version, right?   -Yes, Female version
Eh? Female version?   -Yes, Female version
Hurry up! Get cracking and come back quickly!
Hurry up, you got me? Female version
Female version?
Hey! Hey!......Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Female version! Hey!
Male Version! Hey!
Hooray! We did it!
Yeah, they got him
That was really surprising
The speed of him getting changed   -Yeah, the speed
His speed...oh, nice to meet you   -Nice to meet you
Never met you with your clothes on, but nice to meet you
Thank you very much
That lightning speed is unbelievable
That really surprised me   -He's really fast
Yeah, he really is
Let's take a look
Show us Female version
Eh? Female version?   -Yes, Female version
Hurry up! Get cracking and come back quickly!
Hurry up, you got me? Female version
(We're back to those naked jokes again)
Hey! Hey!......Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Female version! Hey!
Male Version! Hey!
Well, you just have to accept it
Zakoshi and me alone?
Only us? Only me and Junior-san?
Yep
Oh, really?   -Yes
Okay, come on!
Yamauchi worked really hard too
I really aimed to win the contest, honestly
But when I first saw his face
He doesn't even look like a comedian
Which is already so funny
He looks more like a writer or researcher
He got changed in lightning speed and came out naked
And that's not even Female version
Female version! Hey!
Male Version! Hey!
Arghh...I really want to stay for a bit longer
I'm frustrated, but...
Zakoshi is just...
Too damn strong...