I thought this had come again.
For the past weeks, there has always been a Documental somewhere in my mind.
Only bastards have competed in Documental.
You bastard!
You have the longest career, so you should be more imposing.
I have a 10 year gap!
You right.
Sorry.
First of all, Matsumoto-san is a bastard.
The bastard head and his bastard minions are in charge of this.
Aspiring is not to be chased, it must be chased.
We should do that shushutto(≒quickly).
What do you mean?
What's "shushutto"?
You don't have to do it either!
So I shouldn't have done that!?
That's right!
I've been saying that for a while now.
Documental - Season 10
Episode 4  “Unleash All of Your Power”
We are winners.
Don’t get cocky.
Yeah.
Coo-chan, you are dismissed!
He's going to have jokes he hasn't shown them yet.
"Natayooo"
Kotouge laughed.
This means that...
If he gets another card next time...
Here we go.
I envy those who have videos.
Can I still show you my video?
- Sure.
- If you have it, please show it.
I have a lot of that.
- You have a lot of that?
- Yeah.
Please show this.
[Hell Butterfly]
Hell Butterfly.
This was shot when I was in Hawaii on my honeymoon.
Why is he calling this hell?
Why the hell is this "hell"?
Sometimes you can see a foreigner behind him.
What the hell.
This is terrible.
It's tough to watch this looping video.
[Are there any after-parties?]
[KILL YOU]
Why should they be killed?
This is a message to all of you.
How can they stand not to laugh?
- Goto, why don't you go to that room?
- Okay.
- Well, I'm off.
- See you later.
- Can I play another one?
- Sure.
This is a pretty good one.
I know you are all mentality is tired, so please listen to the classics.
- I'd love to hear that.
- Sounds good.
[A Touching Classic]
You guys are mentally tired.
Kotouge is about to laugh again.
- Kotouge is about to laugh again.
- Yes.
- He is playing great one.
- Yeah.
There's more?
There's no end in sight.
What's the hell.
- What the hell is this?
- What is the genre of this video?
What is the genre of this?
Yuriyan is attacking.
She keeps looking at Zakoshi.
[Nice]
What's nice about this?
[KILL YOU]
I was told kill you again.
- I don't want you to kill me.
- Stop killing me.
Stop killing me.
Oh, here he comes.
- Hello.
- Goto-san.
- He came.
- Are you done playing videos?
- You brought a lot of videos.
- There's more.
- Really?
- To show you everything right now would be waste.
Not even half the time has passed yet.
I'm off to the bathroom.
I will follow you.
Don't follow me.
Are you okay?
You have almost laughed several times today.
Sorry.
I can laugh with you, right?
- Huh?
- I can laugh with you, right?
You can't.
Oh, really?
- Of course you can't.
- Only I am allowed to laugh.
- I see.
- What's wrong?
- Didn't you just laugh?
- No.
You have almost laughed several times today.
Sorry.
Really so.
Come on.
Thank you for the tip.
I'm okay.
And, I have one request.
Please change your clothes.
Certainly that outfit is ugly to look at.
You should change your clothes and change your mind.
Sorry.
Do you mean I should go back to square one?
Hmmmm, yeah.
You are more of a negative than a zero, though.
Goto is allowed to laugh, though.
He seems to have a habit of not laughing in that room.
- He must be influenced by them.
- Yeah.
When I came, they were all gone.
Whatever.
What shall I set them up with?
Come over here once.
Goto came all the way here.
"What happened?"
You are Katsuo?
(Note: 1)
"What happened?"
She did that one in THE W.
(Note: 2)
"What happened?"
There was no one here earlier.
They have to fight here, but nobody was here earlier.
Why did they leave here?
What do you think they should do?
Kubota-san,
"You are making a big mistake."
No, I've been here all along.
Can I do an exaggerated Timon D impression?
(Note: 3)
Sure.
First, this is a normal Timon D impression.
"You can do it if you try!"
And this is an exaggerated Timon D impression.
"You can eat shit if you try."
Let's play a game together.
A game?
- Sounds good.
- Nice, nice!
This is an electric griddle for takoyaki.
(Note: 4)
First, put the balls in here.
Next, turn on the switch to make this hot.
Then compete with me to see who can withstand the heat better.
That's dangerous!
Can you show your balls?
- So I brought the skirt so as not to show it.
- Okay.
It's not good.
This is going to be very hot.
Okay, I'll do it if you do it.
Who will do it?
I will do this first.
Is it okay?
If you are so worried, watch me do it.
- Are you okay?
- Can I take it all off?
Sure.
This is where my balls come out.
Then put my balls in here.
This is scary.
You don't have to hold back until your balls burn.
- You don't put your balls on it when it gets hot, do you?
- Yes!
- This is going to get hotter and hotter, isn't it?
- Yes.
I will place this here.
Yamamoto-san, you should see it too.
This might be better placed a little higher....Oh, well.
- You have to bend over quite a bit.
- This looks dangerous.
I don't think you can do that.
Are you sure you are okay?
Don’t worry I won’t hold out for that long.
Do you measure time?
No, this is not that kind of game.
Now, turn on the power.
- Do you just stop when it gets hot?
- please wait a second.
It is better to have water to cool the balls.
Water for cooling?
A cup of water.
- Balls Cooler?
- Yes.
Let's get started.
Are others going to do that after this?
I won't be forced to do so.
- Only those who want to do it?
- If you want to do it after seeing this, please do it.
It's your balls.
Oh, it's a great balls.
- I'm scared.
- Is he okay?
I just heard the sound sizzling.
No.
I'm still totally fine.
I'm still fine.
Ouch!!
Cool it with water!
It smells like...
burnt balls.
It stinks.
I think your pubic hair got burned.
Or the skin of balls.
It stinks!
I knew this would happen.
It must be because my balls were burned.
Did you get burned?
Anyone want to do this?
No.
Nobody wants to do that when they see that.
I'll do it.
You don't have the balls.
You don't have that.
Damn it.
It's dangerous.
So nobody does this?
I don't want to do it.
Yamamoto-san, I think you should do this.
Why!?
Why should I do it?
This is a chance to rise your manliness.
- Why should I...
- Because you haven't done anything so far.
You have nothing to say back to him?
You should do it.
Yamamoto-san, can you do this?
You should do this.
You really should do this.
The kappa one was the worst.
The kappa one and the rap one were really bad.
(Note: 5)
Why can you do the kappa ones and not the ball ones?
- I don't want to do the kappa one any more than this one.
- Go ahead, try it.
Please try it.
Why do you guys only want me to do that at times like this?
Why don't you just do it?
- Earlier I did the kappa ones with you.
- That's because you said those things.
Kotouge was doing that one with you earlier.
You know it's impossible to do something like that.
Why don't you just do it shushutto(≒quickly)?
- You've never done that before, right?
- Let's do it shushutto(≒quickly).
"What's going on?"
Hey, here comes something.
- "What's going on?"
- What the hell is this?
"I'm penis-kun, who wasn't funny at all last time."
Too many jokes about dicks.
After the balls, the dick?
Do you really want to make it work?
"I love this."
- Penis-kun.
- "What's wrong? Hello."
- What do you want with it?
- "I'll answer anything, just ask me for advice."
He won't burn his balls.
"Who do you guys think is to blame?"
"I think the person who started this is to blame."
Yes, that's right.
Maybe it's my fault for bringing this stuff.
But I brought this as a game for everyone to enjoy.
So, if Yamamoto-san does this I can play games with him.
"You already know who's to blame, don't you?"
"The person who started this is to blame."
"You have to say I'm sorry."
"Hey, something is spurting out."
- Did he fail again?
- Something is spurting out.
Something thin and short spurted out.
Although it failed last time, this time it was a success, because it spouted more than last time.
- Did he ejaculate?
- Right.
What's supposed to happen?
I really wanted to make it a success, but this time I had no choice.
- Did you get burned? Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
It was hot but did not burn me.
Is your skin okay?
Something spurted out.
What's with the weird colors?
And...
Hey, there's a lot of something coming out.
- Hey, that's the wrong color.
- Why didn't you make it white one?
No blue one comes out of it.
This is because the tip of this is rotten.
I see.
- What's that?
- What the hell is this?
It stinks!
Enough jokes about dicks.
- Too many dick jokes.
- Yes, that is too many.
You did the balls joke.
You burned your own balls.
Yes, I burned my balls.
You think you can get this over with without doing anything don’t you?
I will do this because it is a good opportunity.
What's this?
Let's do it shushutto(≒quickly).
Shushuttoooo.
Let's do it shushutto.
This is something Goto needs to do something about.
That's so...
This is getting hot, so shushutto it.
It's gushing out.
No one has ever wet the floor like this before.
- This is dangerous.
- Yeah.
I'll shushutto with my penis-kun too!
Shushutto!
- His is not spurting at all.
- This is a worst-case scenario.
This is a worst-case scenario.
This is bad.
Yeah, this is bad.
- It was a mess.
- It's dangerous if you don't wipe the floor.
- Yeah.
His is gushing too much and his is not spurting at all.
It can't be helped if I shushutto.
No one is in this room again.
And you did not burn your balls.
Balls burning is over?
- He should have done that.
- Right.
I will wipe up the rest.
It's okay.
Thank you.
- What's wrong?
- It’s nothing.
You're trying to make me laugh, but there's no point.
You should make Yamamoto-san laugh, not me.
There's no point in making me laugh.
Who are you?
"Shinji, you pilot the Eva."
I'm Gendo Ikari.
(Note: 6)
The light reflects off his glasses, making them glow.
"Shinji, you pilot the Eva."
"If you won't pilot it, go hooooooooooooooME!"
- It's not like this.
- Yeah.
"Fuyutsuki."
"Fuyutsuki, you pilot the Eva too."
He never says that.
"If you won't pilot it, go hooooooooooooooMEEEHHH!"
You are doing a much exaggerated impression of him.
"Eva, you pilot the Eva."
Eva cannot pilot the Eva.
I'm Gendo Ikari.
Right, I'm doing this job because I want to pilot the Eva.
(Note: 7)
Osaka dialect?
Are there any after-parties, hey?
- He loves this phrase.
- Is that what you want to know?
It's impossible to not have a party.
- Why is he speaking in Osaka dialect?
- That's not good, not good.
Right, this is the "Human - Are there any after parties? - Project".
(Note: 8)
All he cares about is the after-party.
That's all.
He is an idiot.
Was this an exaggerated impression?
He's a helpless guy.
"Are there any after-parties?"
- Finally, half the time has passed.
- Yeah.
The rest of the time is half.
- Let's clean up around here.
- Yes.
- half the time has passed.
It's yours, so you should deal with it.
You should get rid of it.
- That should get rid of it.
- Please, throw that away.
I am taking this home with me.
You're bringing it back?
Will you use it again?
Where will you use it?
Lumine the Yoshimoto.
You should not do that in Lumine.
(Note: 9)
No one will laugh if you do that in Lumine.
I am the only one here.
Wait a second.
But...you should change your clothes for jokes.
I'm fine with this.
Others are changing now.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You should change your clothes.
You should do something.
But others are changing now.
But you ended last time by saying, "I didn't get to do any of the jokes I had prepared."
I have nothing to change into anymore.
You came here with a big baggage.
I've already done most of them.
Are you okay?
Sorry for shouting.
It's okay.
But please be quiet because there are other patients.
Who are you?
I am a doctor.
Shall I examine you?
"Hi, we are Sandwichman."
(Note: 10)
"That's enough."
"Hi, we are Sandwichman."
"The store manager has become the topping of this."
"That's enough."
"Hi, we are Sandwichman."
"Hey, you're disgusting."
"That's enough."
"The store manager has become the topping of this."
Was this guy really listening to their comedy?
- Are you Date-chan?
- I'm Date-chan
"The store manager has become the topping of this."
"That's enough."
You are Date-chan?
- He might say something like this in his home, too.
- I've never seen him say that.
"That's enough."
"Thanks."
I don't think he would talk that way.
"Are you okay?"
Are you okay?
Apparently...
- You and I are alone.
- Yeah.
- We are three.
There are three here.
You said yeah but that is wrong.
You are wrong.
Why don't you change quickly?
- He doesn't have a change of clothes anymore, does he?
- Someone is using the locker room right now.
Yamamoto stopped acting at all.
Last time I checked you were wandering around doing nothing.
Right?
- That's right.
- Yes.
"That's right"?
I was finally alone.
There are two.
No, it's fine.
We should not all go to the locker room.
Yeah.
What's this?
It's mine!
Did you bring your own chimbou?
Everyone is bringing their own chimbou.
That's right, everyone brings a chimbou.
Hey, don't stretch it...What's this?
- Hair came out of it.
- This is a white hair.
Wouldn't you feel disappointed i%&*#$.... someone...
Why did you stutter?
- That doesn't matter.
- Why did you stutter?
That doesn't matter.
Wouldn't you feel disappointed if someone you admired had white hair?
Did he laugh?
Kubota laughed?
He almost laughed at what he said.
- Would you like to play a game with me?
- Okay.
- Really?
- Okay!
Okay!
Let's use this.
Pop-up Pirate?
Yes.
Do you want to do it on the floor?
Or on the table?
I think it is easier to understand if you do it on the table.
The loser have to eat shit.
Are you serious?
- Don't do that.
- That is eatable shit.
There is no such thing in this world.
No, it exists.
It is sold at Don Quixote.
(Note: 11)
The ones that are on the market?
It is quite realistic.
If you lose this game, eat shit.
Okay.
And...
Here's...
the shit.
- Huh?
- Here's the shit.
The loser has to eat it.
Is that on Kotouge's butt?
Yes, I have shit on my butt.
- Is that eatable shit?
- Yes.
This is not uneatable shit.
So the loser has to eat my...
Some people can eat real shit.
This is not real shit.
It's Shimiken-san, right?
(Note: 12)
You don't have to say who.
Since we are here, why don't you join us, Goto-san?
But you are not a contestant, are you?
I have no problem joining in on this.
Then, Goto-san, please join us in this.
You like this kind of thing, don't you, Goto-san?
You used to masturbate to porn videos of women licking toilet bowls, didn't you?
I have heard that rumor too.
Hey, it's true.
Really?
Is that why you want to do this so badly?
- You seemed very eager to do this.
- Are you excited?
It's Spitton Toilet Bitch.
Spitton?
- Don't you watch those?
- No, I don't.
What do you usually watch?
I often watch videos featuring amateurs.
I watched "Chimpo kari sweat" the other day.
This can be divided into three words.
Chimpo (Dick),
Kari (Glans),
Sweat.
What kind of story is that?
Why do you want to know Chimpo kari sweat's story?
Women run marathons...
Women run marathons, drink sports drinks, and have sex.
Chimpo kari sweat...
I don't want to do it.
I don't want to eat shit.
I definitely don't want to eat that.
This is not real.
It is just as close to the real thing as possible.
- Does it smell?
- Yes.
Let's begin.
I'll do it first.
This is only the second one.
Is this possible?
What's going on?
- Are you serious?
- Don't worry.
There's nothing here.
I can't do it!
Help me!
Goto-san, help me!
This is eatable shit.
Even if that is eatable shit...
This is really eatable shit.
Even if that is eatable shit, if you spread it on there, we can't eat it anymore.
Can I trust you?
This is really eatable shit!
If you spread it on there, we can't eat it anymore.
This is really eatable shit!!
Trust me!!
This is eatable shit!!
Why are you talking so passionately about this!?
You eat it first.
Okay, this is eatable shit.
This is really hard.
Oh, you eat this?
He ate it.
You shouldn't do that.
- It’s shit, right?
- Yes, it's shit.
Yeah, it's shit.
This is eatable, though.
More importantly, your ass stinks.
That's the smell of the shit.
It smelled like a Koumon (asshole).
Koumon-sama.
(Mito-Koumon)
Not that “Koumon”.
(Note: 13)
- What should I do?
- Why did you suck it?
Because he won't do it.
- That said, why did you lick so much?
- I would do it.
I wouldn't do it.
If there is shit there, I would do it.
"When are you going to do it?
Now, that's when!"
(Note: 14)
You don't do this?
Okay, I'll do it.
You want me to smell it?
No, please eat this.
Here is a lump of shit and you should eat it.
This is tough.
You lost, so you should do it.
There is also piss there.
That is the yellow one there.
You're the worst.
This is drinkable piss.
We can't drink this!
Eatable Shit and Drinkable Piss!
Where did you find this!?
- Both are sold at Don Quijote.
- Don Quijote is insane.
- Is this really eatable?
- Of course it is.
This is an eatable one.
What does it taste like?
- It tastes like shit.
- Then it's shit!
I really don't want to eat this.
But you are...
Hey, someone is waiting for us.
- Yeah.
- Someone is waiting.
- We are doing it over here now, so please wait a bit.
- Okay, I'll do it.
Hey,
I got dressed and came here and this was the situation.
Who are you?
Guess who?
Are you Fuwa-chan?
(Note: 15)
Ah, Fuwa-chan.
Yeah, it's Fuwa-chan.
Correct.
Is that correct?
Are you Fuwa-chan?
Fuwa-chan doesn't dress like this.
He's like a Street Fighter's character.
Chun-Li?
(Note: 16)
Fat Chun-Li.
I don't know Chun-Li.
Come on.
Then I'll do it.
Yes, let's deal with this first.
This is really eatable.
This is eatable shit.
Ugh, this is tough.
What's going on?
- How do I eat this?
- You see the lump?
You nibble the lumps.
With front teeth.
- This really stinks.
- Have you ever had it?
- Does this smell like piss?
- Yes.
Smell it first.
Does it stink?
My sense of smell is numb and I can't smell this.
It stink!
It doesn't smell at all.
I smell piss from this.
Then you can drink it.
That's drinkable piss, so you're good to go.
- What's drinkable piss?
- My sense of smell is numb.
Are you okay?
Yeah, that's piss.
I know this taste.
This is what it tastes like when you lick the hand that touched the back of your balls in your stuffy pants in summer.
Is that salty?
- And it tastes like piss, right?
- Yes.
But you can drink this.
This is drinkable piss.
He seemed to like this very much.
Why did you drink it again?
I found myself drinking this.
It must be an addictive taste.
This is not good.
Shit, piss, and dick....
This is really...
This really smells like the back of balls in summer.
You don't know that.
I know that!
You haven't dick.
You haven's that.
I have that.
You haven't.
What the hell.
You haven't dick.
Then let's play chess to decide who wins.
Chess?
Is his Fuwa-chan done?
"Rassun Gorerai"
(Note: 17)
"Explain this."
- He does a lot of things.
- Yeah.
Are you Hama-yanen?
"Rassun Gorerai"
"Wait a minute, wait a minute, old man."
- Old man?
- I think if he exaggerated that one, he would probably say old man.
Not bro.
"Rassun Gorerai"
Oh, Zakoshi!
He laughed for the first time.
He definitely laughed.
- Who laughed?
- Me.
- Did you laugh at your own joke?
- Yes.
- Have you lost your mind?
- Yeah.
- This is serious.
What was that?
He definitely laughed.
I blew myself up!
You laugh at things like that.
You laughed.
You were completely unharmed.
Yellow card.
- It's the first time, right?
- Yes.
The only one intact is Yuriyan.
It also matters how many points you are earning.
Did you have Fuwa-chan's costume?
And you're showing them now?
I thought I had to come out when the buzzer went off.
Ugh, It's not going well.
- You want to come back with me?
- Yes.
- Don't go!
- See you.
Here we go.
Two and a half hours remaining.
Please make me your disciple.
I don't need a disciple.
Do you want to become Zakoshi's disciple?
I can exaggerate too.
Can you really do that?
Only my nipples can do that.
Only one side?
This side is retracted nipples.
- Are you exaggerating your nipples.
- Yes.
That is too much of an exaggeration.
- Will you take me as your disciple?
- I don't need a disciple.
Why are you touching it a little?
- I don't need an disciple.
- Make me an disciple!
Excuse me, can I get by?
ACHOO.
Remote licking?
Remote licking.
- Ouch!
- Oh, sorry!
- So sorry!
- It hurts.
Sorry.
Really sorry.
That hurt, didn't it?
I'm sorry.
I would definitely laugh at something like this.
It shows the gentle side of Kotouge.
He didn't mean to go that far.
It's like shaking hands.
Thank you for your time today.
Thank you.
We are friends.
She is an idiot.
The thing came off.
Kotouge is so close!
- Look at this.
- Wait a moment. Yamamoto-san, don't...
He is so close!.
- It was close...
- Thanks.
Yuriyan, go put something on.
This nipple is insane.
- Too many dirty jokes.
- Yeah, especially the nipple is not good.
- Don't make any more nipple jokes.
- It's over.
- Hey, get your nipple somewhere else.
Really?
Hey, don't do that!!
Hey, don't stir my coffee with your nipple, asshole!!
Don't stir this with your nipple, aaaaahhhhh!!
She laughed.
She just laughed.
She was completely unharmed.
He made the defensive Yuriyan laugh.
That was close!
What the hell.
Yuriyan!
Yuriyan laughed.
Yuriyan's stronghold was broken.
That was close.
Kotouge did well.
This is pretty awesome.
It is rare to see Yuriyan laugh so clearly.
This was too hilarious.
Let's see the replay.
She laughed clearly.
You laughed.
You laughed, right?
She is laughing hysterically.
She laughed for the first time.
Yellow card.
Now everyone got a card from me.
Good luck.
Come on.
I was really close to laughing when your nipple came off.
I was really close.
That was too hilarious.
Yeah, that was insane.
Here we go.
It has started again.
- He did tsukkomi and won point.
- Yeah.
The time has finally come.
Come on!
What's going on?
Again?
- He got hit on the head again.
- He is always being hit by someone.
Why did you high-five?
Ow.
Hey, what's going on?
He suddenly....
It's only natural that this would happen.
Yeah, it's only natural.
Stop doing that.
Hey, someone's here.
Oh, I forgot to bring sunglasses.
Please don't do that.
Oh, I forgot....
Oh, I forgot to bring sunglasses.
Long ago it really happened to you.
I can't see ahead.
You forgot to bring your sunglasses when you were performing at the office gig.
You had no choice but to paint the glasses in the waiting room black.
He went out on stage.
But he was wearing those sunglasses and couldn't see in front of him, so he fell off the stage into the audience.
I forgot to bring my sunglasses, so it can't be helped.
Don't say "He".
I am Sakurai of Mr. Children.
(Note: 18)
I forgot to bring sunglasses.
You fell off the stage because you were wearing it.
- I am your fan, Sakurai-san.
- Huh?
- I am your fan.
- Really?
- Yes.
What part of this looks like Sakurai?
Sakurai-san, your...
I forgot to bring sunglasses.
Your sunglasses are black.
Because I forgot to bring it.
If you paint the glasses black, they will become Sakurai-san's sunglasses.
You want me to put this in you?
Please!
- You want me to put this in you?
- Please!
Is this the urethra?
What's he doing all of a sudden?
This is...
- You want me to put this in you?
- Please!
- Hey, you want me to put this in you?
- Get your ass over here!!
- Yes!
- Hey, you want me to put this in you?
- Please!
He drew a sudden urethral opening.
- He drew beautiful straight line.
- Right.
It is hard to believe he was the first to draw this.
He drew a very beautiful line without a mirror.
- Are you cleaning here every morning, Monk?
- Yes.
- Thank you Monk.
- He has not acted since wearing Fuwa-chan's clothes.
- Yeah.
Monks seem to be busy every morning.
Actually, I am not a monk.
Who are you?
I am still in training.
But you seem pretty seasoned.
Monk, look behind you.
Who are you?
Phimosis.
This is dangerous.
Can he breathe?
Are you trying to pull back the foreskin?
You can't  pull back the foreskin?
That's a pain.
How can I help you?
I can't pull back my foreskin.
Someone please surgery on me.
He seems to want surgery.
Is there a doctor here?
I'll cut foreskin off, just wait a second.
Now you can easily pull back the foreskin.
How do you like it?
It's much easier to pull back my foreskin.
Can you pull back it?
Veins become visible.
There are eyes, nose, and mouth on the dick.
- He is laughing.
- Yeah.
Kotouge laughed.
Maybe it's me.
You blew yourself up again!?
What's going on?
Well...
You blew yourself up again?
I got that look on my face again.
He had the same look on his face when he cracked the egg.
Because it was funny.
Kotouge.
I blew it.
I know how you feel.
I know you did that look as an expression, right?
Yeah, right.
I get what you were doing, but you're on thin ice.
Let's see the replay.
This is like an accident.
It's....
You showed your face with a smile.
This may have been an accident.
I know exactly how you feel.
But this can't be helped.
Kotouge, you are dismissed.
I am very sorry.
- There are only four of us left.
- Yes.
He pulled back his dick foreskin and dismissed.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Oh, I lost, it's frustrating.
More often than last time I almost laughed.
I thought I could hold back without laughing, but I did.
But I didn't fight a battle that I would regret.
I showed my shit and my dick.
I am the kind of person who finds shit and dicks funny.
So I'm glad I finally did that one.
Grand Champion Tournament winner is....