First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai Ya Arahende!
Life of the "Ogoo" Pteranodon Endo!
Downtown
Tsukitei Housei
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Alright!
Matsumoto-san      - Well, that's how it is
There was that gag on our last New Year's special
And that's Endo's Pteranodon
Yes
I think it will be forgotten soon
Wouldn't it be good?
PTEROSAUR
THE PTERANODON'S  UNREASONABLE REQUEST!!
Endo was suddenly requested to act like a pterosaur
And that gave birth to a new character:
From "No Laughing Prison" (2014)
Endo Pteranodon
Raise your voice more!!
Mooooooore!!
That's completely off!
His character was born from a cornered situation, but still...
I think that...
I can't let it sleep like this yet...
I want it to make a comeback this year...
But I have to come up with something good
For the sake of its comeback...
Endo promised to bring his Pteranodon back
He promised a comeback
What will his challenge be?
But how will he?
Today Endo is going to be alone
And he'll show us the life of Endo Pteranodon
The whole thing, from its birth to its death
L I F E   O F  E N D O  P T E R A N O D O N
Endo will perform all by himself its circle of life
In a 60-minutes-long play in 5 acts live on stage!!
In a theatrical form      - That's fucked up
Yeah, I agree
That's a pretty wide scale!
But you see, when he was doing this before
He made a lot of mistakes
He had troubles
Does it mean he's ready now?
Well, I think that
When Endo tries something and makes mistakes is the funniest!!
And if he succeeds?
When he does
And he's like "I got it", that's unreasonably not funny at all!!
That's because it contains Endo's peculiar unskillfulness!!
It does get boring
His harsh taste comes out !!
I really want them to have high hopes for today's play...
And when it's over
I want them to think "So that was its comeback"
AN
UN
KNO
WN
LENGE
Tonight's episode of Gaki no Tsukai
CHAL
Lies on Endo's hands
Endo Shouzo in:
Life Of The "Ogoo" Endo Pteranodon
Curtain Raising
Hundreds of million of years ago, in the Cretaceous Period
The four of them are monitoring the play from another room
The Earth was shrouded in warm temperatures
I like this clip
And full of rich natural environments
Such majestic plateau
Was the kingdom of enormous dinosaurs
That's amazing
The winged Pterosaur soars the sky
the pteranodon
That's it, that's
On the land, both carnivorous and herbivorous dinosaurs
for this, right?
He mistook it
Lived in such era of fighting for the survival of the fittest
Yeah, I think so
He did the
Triceratops
And in the midst of such era
A singular new life was about to make its first appearance...
Seems interesting
From its birth...
Woah, cool!
He did a good job
The beginning of "Ovo" looks like this
note: a touring circus production by Cirque du Soleil
Did Ovo had this?
Yeah it did
He's born
Endo Pteranodon
That's the birth of Endo Pteranodon
Can you smell the
unskillfulness?
Well, if you ask me if I can, then I'll answer:
I can smell it!!
would take more!
I thought it
It just started
It's already set
He said "Ogo"
- Yeah, he said it
Just when he
was born
So, that's a baby
What's going on?
I can already say
This is way better than "Busjack"
ENDO'S FIRST MOVIE
The Bus Hijacker
note: you can watch the reaction episode for its sequel on www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
I mean, I know
this
what I'll get from
I see
Here comes his
harsh taste
STAGING TIME
Look! His hand
is kinda...
Their shape is...
It's forming up
- Yes, right
The hell is he--?
Let's stop here
He stood up
He's finally up
note: I'm not subbing any "ogo" he shouts, it's just his cry
That was clear
That much?
Was it necessary?
What is he doing?
He ate it
- Yeah, he ate it
Eating the shell to stuff his belly
Endo Pteranodon is eating the shell of his egg
That's his
nourishment
But in that moment...
Oh!
What is--
ROOOAAARRR
A carnivorous dinosaur suddenly draws near
There he goes
His hash taste rolled out from him!!
Well, you see
I did warn you
STAGING TIME
8 minutes passed
since it began
I told you so, guys
The hell is he doing?
As soon as it starts raining, the carnivorous dinosaur leaves
It started raining
Right, woah
used the leaf now
He should have
- That's right
Poor thing, huh?
- Yeah...
He took it again
Are you sure that
is the right way
to use it?
With his hands
Are those his
hands?
At this point he--
What the? Why
is he eating again?
Eating the shell to stuff his belly, once more
He ate a lot
The hell!
He's eating a lot,
what the hell
Matsumoto-san,
Do you think our audience can endure this?
For our Endo Pteranodon,
born in the age of dinosaurs,
A voyage known as "life" is about to begin
It's starting now
- Oh, yes
End of Act One
I see...
That's the end of the first act
STAGING TIME TILL NOW
Why aren't we watching it under the stage?
If we were there, we would talk too much
Oh I see
We'd be noisy
He would hear us
We'll be heard talking by him
I see, I see
And then
If he notices we laughed a bit, he'll repeat that same thing forever!!
Translation & Subtitles by Shion
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
www.facebook.com/shionnotsukai
Want to support my translations?
Consider donating @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
Act Two: Childhood Arc
The season changed?
It surely changed
- It did change
He can now
perfectly stand
He has a pattern...
True, on his body
How old is he
supposed to be now?
Well, looks like
he feels at ease
He's lively
Yeah, a lot
He surely is lively
He's an infant
now, right?
He's playing with
interesting
what he founds
Ok but seriously,
what are those?
Are those hands?
Not fangs?
- Right
I mean, he always did this
Yeah, he did that last time
And now he's doing this instead
And now he's
doing this instead
So hands-- hands?
Those are hands!
Looks like it
I'm pretty sure
by the time this
will be over
He'll end up with
two broken fingers
He smacked em
Why is he-?
He's wiggling
He probably thinks he's cracking us up with this!!
I bet he's
thinking that!
You think so?
- Just now, yes
STAGING TIME
He found a lump of meat stuck in a tree
Endo Pteranodon, who just found some meat on a tree,
Decides to climb it to acquire it
Come on,
Those are hands...
Prove me wrong
He goes "ogoo" whenever he can't use his head
That's because "ogoo" means he's thinking...
Oh, he made it
Good, good, he did it
Huh? Looks like he
still can't reach it
- And what now?
He can't reach it
Oh, come on! He's
clenching his fist
Where did his fangs go ?!
Geez...
This is no good
By this point our audience probably changed channel !!
They're all watching YORUTAMORI
- Yeah, most likely
note: A variety show broadcasted every sunday (2014-2015)
That's bad
End of Act Two
Geez      - Oh! We're done
STAGING TIME TILL NOW
I have thousands of complaints about this
Well, we can't speak directly to Endo at the moment
Yes
So, let's call the staff and told them to say him "the situation's harsh"
Now!?     - How can that be better?
If we say that now...
- Yeah, it'll probably influence him
Act Three: Adolescence Arc
That's his adolescence
His tail!
It became huge
It grew so long
- It really grew up
Even his face...
Right
He became an adult
Never saw that
face on him before!
It's a new face
He became handsome
For our grown-up Endo Pteranodon, the season of love is about to arrive...
The season of love..?
I guess for us humans
It's around the 20s
It's a female Ogoo
A female Pteranodon appears
Yes, a female
Disgusting
- Creepy!
What the...
- It's freaky
It's an Ogoo girl
Ogoo girl...
What will he do?
COURTING DANCE
That's his
courting dance
He's not saying
"Ogo" at all
- He's not...
You're right
His hands again
So that's how it
works with Ogoos
Here goes
He didn't hesitate
- Yeah right
Endo felt the urge
to add this scene
What the hell
So considerate
- He made her a pillow
I see, he used his
tail as a pillow
A tail pillow
point of that arm?
Then what's the
his hands!
He keeps using
I guess they're a couple now...
They are
Is that so?
Yeah
Endo Pteranodon has found a partner
, but suddenly...
A rival-in-love dinosaur appears
A
lival
in rov--
A rival
-in-love
Wha-?!
dinosaur
appeared
He stuttered!
I didn't know
it was live
surprised me
That's what
Really...
So it's not
pre-recorded...
He made it!
- Got him
Like that, go!
"I protected you"
He's saying
"until the end"
He protected her?
what that meant
I think that's
But it's still there
What the?
trying his best
of someone who's
That's the sweat
What was that?
are types of sweat
I don't think there
that type
I think that's
I don't think we
can win against
YORUTAMORI tonight
We can only hope they're doing the exact same thing on YORUTAMORI
If that's the case, we're good
You think so?
They've been glaring each other for 6 minutes
Endo's still
not done yet
There's still more
Of course
And once he's done
- Yes?
won't move
The dummy still
I see
get confused
And he'll
I see
This is a battle between him and his other self
What's that battle
supposed to be?
is such a bad guy!
That stage assistant
He's not moving
that thing off stage
He won't move
for instructions
He's just waiting
Yeah...
See? Now he's---
What the?
Oh! He's going away
in the end
to do something
Of course he has
[censored]
End of Act Three
When it began I thought it won't have much story
But by now
STAGING TIME TILL NOW
We're at the fourth act, how will the story unfold?
Good point
I must say, it really got my attention somehow
I agree
I think that
Our audience must be thinking
"What the hell are those idiots talking about?!"
What are you being so serious about?
Don't worry, we've been just spitting out lies right now!!
Act Four: Adulthood Arc
After experience love many times
Endo Pteranodon, which is now an adult,
Has now a family
Oh! I thought so!      - I'm glad!
small before
He wasn't that
That's a human baby
They're raising him
shoulders changed
- The shape of his
Ok, I got it
Those are definitely hands (not fangs)!!
It's a sort of pond
Some fishes discovered in a pond
There are fishes
His baby!
He fell
- I don't think so
Did he noticed it?
stance is weird
His mom's
Is he mad?
This is...
This is the scene
to briefly see
In which we get
son bonding moment
This father and
All live
STAGING TIME
But even with such an happy family...
It's coming
What?
pretty big---
That must be
Oh, it's the same
A rival-in-love dinosaur appears
So irritating...
The hell is this?
He came again
- Yes
natural enemy
It must be his
scene from before
That's the same
He likes his wife?
What's his deal?
targeting him?
Is that why he's
- Yeah...
- It's not, right?
That's not really clear
He passed by
- Did he noticed him?
He just passed by
He hugs his wife
He protected them
He looks relieved
So, he protected his family?
That's right
What the hell...
He picked em all up
- Yeah, all of them
He's back
Again!?
The rival-in-love dinosaur appears again
He's back at it
expecting that
I wasn't
or two is fine, but...
I mean, one time
Oh! He got him!
ever come again"
He's like "don't
Exactly
He got angry
He hurt him good
The moments spent along with
his beloved wife and son were
the happiest for Endo Pteranodon
STAGING TIME TILL NOW
End of Act Four
About the "ogoos", it's more about variation than frequency...
Meaning, that's the...
Hardest part      - Exactly
But in the end he didn't shout for us any remarkable "ogoo"
I can't understand why!!
He must be lost in thoughts
Is that it?
Must be that, yes
Amazing
As expected from him
I think
I think a nasty ogoo boom is going to happen this year
There will be statues of him!!
note: he actually says "hagoita", japanese ornamental paddles
Final Act: Old Age Arc
Endo Pteranodon: last chapter
so old!
Woah! He became
He surely aged
He aged all at once!
Is that the way they grow old?
He's just an old man!!
His son has left the nest
and his wife was gone before him
But something is about to unfold before his very eyes...
old for this now
Come on, he's too
You're right
An UFO comes flying in
unexpected twist!
Well, that's an
- I know right?
It's an ashtray
Isn't this a surprising turn of events?
This...
An alien appears
So it happened
What a great finale
that face
Can't blame
It was too sudden
invader he saw
That's the first
He bowed before him
It's like a God
I don't get this
What is he doing?
But just on that moment...
Meteorites
Huge meteorites crash down on Earth from space
Huge meteorites crash down, the Ice Age approaches
The sky becomes covered in hot clouds
And the Ice Age starts instantly
STAGING TIME
The ice age, huh
He's still small
You're right
the nest?
Didn't he left
Enough with that
- So long!
Why?
It's taking so long
kinda touching
I gotta say, it's
- It is, right?
It would been good if the dinosaur popped out now...
His rival, right?
he'll pop out now
I don't think
STAGING TIME
left to do
There's nothing
Is that him?
- You think so?
about to end!
Just when it was
He was ready to die!
He's a gradnpa
A fighting grandpa
protecting him
And yet he's still
come on, fight!
Protecting is ok, but
What now?
What will he do?
He's standing!
nonchalantly!
He's standing
Sorry, I'm lost
what's going on
I have no idea
at each other
They're glaring
His opponent is...
Ohh, he hid well
STAGING TIME
He must be tired
It's almost over
I want it (the dinosaur) to appear one more time
I won't let this play reach an ending!!
He's unkillable
He's back!!
He came again!
What will he do?
Ogoo!
What now?!
This is the best
He doesn't give up
Of course he's doing
The inoki-ari-jotai
note: a MMA style consisting in fighting while lying down
He's done for
What the hell
The End
TOTAL STAGING TIME
In the end the last act was the longest
Yes, you're right
It never crossed my mind
How long this was taking
What?
Are you for real?       - I swear
After this...
An unexpected situation: they'll call for a retake!!
Hi
Hey
Congrats
So...
Do you think the "Ogoo" will become popular?
Well...
To be honest, we all agreed that
You hardly ever said any "ogoo" all over the play
Oh, I see...
He's right, that was the main issue
Would you  mind do it one more time for us, please?
Only the beginning was good
Ohnuma, come here
producer
Ohnuma Akihiro
Raise your voice more!!
You're scared when you shout
At least with the first "ogoo"
But then, the more you shout it, the less scared you become
The more you do it, remember
Come on, one more time!!
He didn't shout much...
Yeah, too soft
That's the issue
Come on, you gotta shout more,
wait a sec!!
It's not coming out from your very first "ogoo"
Translation & Subtitles by Shion
Again
Ok
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Shout it from there
www.facebook.com/shionnotsukai
I still can't feel it
Want to support my translations? Consider donating @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
Please, don't ever say "ogoo" again in your entire life!!
main website (archive): www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
for updates & support like my page: www.facebook.com/shionnotsukai
want to support my work? Buy me an Oyan Fifi: www.ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
are reserved to their respected owners
This is a no-profit translation made by a fan for other fans, all copyrights