First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai
Comedy Guidelines Decision Meeting!
Good evening
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Downtown
See, lately when it comes to variety shows
Cocorico
Tanaka Naoki
There are lots of batsu games and such like always
Endo Shozo
But in a way
Saying "this is comedy" or "this isn't comedy"
is becoming difficult
I see
I mean, sometimes they do more than they should
Yeah, like injuries
Yes, those too
That's why we in Gaki
Comedy Guidelines Decision Meeting~!!
Today we'll decide the correct comedy guidelines
of various "comedy" which could appear on Gaki no Tsukai!
Decided to make some guidelines about what's comedy
We'll decide em?
That's the plan     - I see
So, we'll have our guinea-pig-comedian...
Guinea pig?
That's him
You shouldn't call him like that, come on
You'll make him sad
Anyway, please come here!
Thank you!
Comedy Guidelines Judge
Yamazaki Housei
Lookin' young
It's a pleasure
Good evening
So if you judge something as "non-comedy", we'll never do it on Gaki
Rules
If Yamazaki decided that something "is not comedy"
That will be banned forever from Gaki no Tsukai
I see
Not anymore
What kind of comedian are you?
I'm a guinea-pig-comedian
He willingly accepted it
That's why I'm all white
He recognized it
More like a lab rat
Yeah, a rat
I don't need colors
translation & subs by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
Want to support? Like my FB page: facebook.com/shionnotsukai
Or donate @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai   /  patreon.com/shionnotsukai
Is this comedy ?! Or is it  not comedy ?!
Yamazaki will decide the correct comedy guidelines!
First off we have:
"Where's my mouth?"
Where is my mouth!?
"Helping Hands Wasabi Sushi"!
Helping Hands Wasabi Sushi~!
So, Matsumoto-san
This is an easy one
Well, this one
I think everyone knows it
Helping Hands Wasabi Sushi
Let's see if it will be judged as "comedy" or "not comedy"  !
Eat wasabi sushi aided by helping hands
But we haven't thought about it seriously
I see
So, Yamazaki will be in front
Yes
And then we'll have our "foremost satisfaction of comedy" behind
So we'll have Hamada-san
Sitting behind him
Alright
Idiot    - They'll have wasabi sushi
So you're saying that it has to be Hamada after all, right?
Well, we're talking about guidelines, so
We want a full swing on it
It's easier that way
Right
Well
I'de be fine with Tanaka doing it though
I'm not the best at it
Do you want to do it with Tanaka?
Yeah, Tanaka's good
But our "satisfaction" is the best one there is
What the hell is this "satisfaction" crap?
We've been told before that's dangerous
To mix Hamada and wasabi together
And so
Will "Helping Hands Wasabi Sushi"
Helping Hands Wasabi Sushi:
Will it be comedy !?  Or not comedy !?
Be labeled as comedy or not?
Be sure
To judge this only after the camera draws near you
After the camera comes?
How am I supposed to...?
We'll let you know, don't worry
Please do your best
Basically I'll eat sushi, right?
Yes
Hamada-san?
- That's it
With his hands
Shall we begin?
"Where's my mouth? Helping Hands Wasabi Sushi"
Start!
That's how it's done
That's fair enough
Makes me wanna eat sushi too
Oh, thank you
Looking good
- Looks delicious
His hands are dirty
Delicious
- Looks good
Thanks
Good, good
Second one
That's too much
Hamada-san? Hey!
Good
- It's too much
Too much wasabi
But we have to test it, so it has to be like this
Oh, like that, nice
Come on, some more
Just like this, a bit more
Keep this pace
Like this, come on
Good, good
That's perfect
How about we go for the verdict?
So...
Your verdict?
How do you judge it?
What happened?
What's wrong?
this is a performance Yamazaki is doing as a professional comedian
please do not attempt to imitate him
Was it that bad?
What's wrong?
He pushed
his finger way too inside
He pushed it too much?
That... sounds terrible
We could never do something like that
That's unthinkable for us
Just say it
- His finger?
It went through my esophagus
That's impossible
You were just eating sushi
I think I got injured
You injured your esophagus?
For real
I got injured for real
So it's no good?
It's not comedy?
It's messed up
How far did you insert it?
My voice isn't coming out anymore
You voice hasn't changed, it's your vocal cords
He fiddled with em
Was that the quantity of wasabi?
I don't know anything about wasabi
The problem was his finger...
What's up with that voice?
My vocal cords...
Something's definitely off
- It is
Maybe
Maybe he changed channel inside you
Try to shout
He tampered with em
He sounds like a trumpet shell
Are you really ok?
VERDICT: HELPING HANDS WASABI SUSHI
IS NOT COMEDY !!
"Put em on, take em off! Face panty hose"!!
Put em on, take em off!
Face panty hose~!!
Well...
Are you ok Yamazaki-san?
What's wrong?
Are you ok?
Well it's that
I have to stretch this part
'Cause you've been injured already, right?
That's right
So, about this
We've seen lots of panty-hose on faces before
You did it before too, right?
- I did
But right now we'd like to do something different, together
So we'll make you wear one and take it off and so on
Put em on, take em off! Face panty hose!
Wear panty hose and have them get off in succession
Let's see if it will be judged as "comedy" or "not comedy"  !
Oh, I see
I'll have you help me
So we'll make it in succession
I think it'll be hilarious
You mean his face?
- Yeah, even his face
It does sound like something good for reactions
I think that
It'll be a complete success
You'll get plenty of comedy medals for this
"Comedy medals"?
I want those!
That's your chance for redemption
- I have to take them
I really want them
So, we'll
Go in order, like
First Endo, then me, and so on
Alright
Let's at least aim for 10 of them, or even 100
That hurts
Alright, let's begin
"Put em on, take em off! Face panty hose": start!!
Lookin' good
Just like this
That's it, good
Let's do it in succession
Nice
- Let's go, let's go
That's enough
Nice, nice
Come on come on
It hurts---
Let's keep this up
Let's go let's go let's go
We can do this
Go go go
Lookin' good
Let's go, let's go
["let's do this" "good" and "come on" all over]
M--- my eyes! You got my eyes!
Ouch
Here comes
Your verdict?
THE HELL ARE YA DOIN' ?!
Could it be not comedy...?
Which is it? Is it comedy or not?
HOW CAN THIS BE COMEDY ?!
"No way", he said
- For real?
It was not...
What have you done?
The atmosphere felt good
- It did
Midway
In the middle of it
I started feeling intense pain here
It's not strange, it's all about this
You hit me to the utmost, right?
No way we could do it
- No way
Some of you did punch me with all his strength, I'm sure of it
But this is "face panty hose"...
They're your juniors
No way we'd do that
- We wouldn't dare
As for myself
I'd never hurt my beloved junior
Who was it?
What do you mean?
Who did punch me like that?
I did like anyone else, just normally
Yeah but while doing it, you kicked me, right?
Was it you?
No way I would do that to my senior
Why treating me like that?
I think if we pull this a bit more, he'll make a funnier face
This is hilarious!
- Isn't this comedy?
What do you think?
This is good, it's hilarious!
It went "bam!" as it came off
VERDICT: PUT EM ON TAKE EM OF - FACE PANTY HOSE
IS NOT COMEDY !!
"Middle-aged men sneezes on face: 10 hits"!!
Middle-aged men sneezes
10 hits on face~!!
So, what's this about, Matsumoto?
We can say this is something
New to this industry
We'll have some middle aged men
Middle-aged men sneezes on face: 10 hits~!!
Have some old dudes sneeze on your face in succession
Let's see if it will be judged as "comedy" or "not comedy"  !
Sneeze on his face for 10 consecutive times
This is...
I think this will make you earn several comedy medals
Isn't it good?       - I see
What do you think about it, Yama-chan?
I think that if I'm
Getting sneezed at---
His voice is actually messed up
That's true
That's from before
When will it come back?
I'm starting to worry
It won't
If they're gonna do it, they have to jump at me properly
Let's call our guests, please come in!
There's plenty of them
I see
Alright, Yamazaki-san
"Middle-aged men sneezes on face: 10 hits":
Start!!
At this point he's ready for everything
That's right
He just have to accept it
He can only take them
It's ten hits, you know
There are still 8 left
That was weak
They're different
Yeah, there's a lot
That too?
He drew back!
This dude...
I can feel malice in this guy
It's him again
This guy is evil!
- He's good
How about number 4?
- He went before
All this guy does is to draw back
Number 3 is hilarious
He's the main star
Here he comes
That was good, wasn't it?
Number 1 hasn't sneezed yet
They're having a blast
Bring the camera
Bring it, yeah
Here he comes again!
How was it?
It stinks
Who cares about that!
We want your verdict
Is it comedy or not?
Tell us please
It stinks
It reeks
This is...
Ok but is it comedy or not?
IT WAS HUMILIATING !!
In other words...?
THIS KIND OF SHIT IS NOT COMEDY !!
You got through it though
My my my
It stinks...
That's cause Number 3 hit you lots of times
It reeks!
- He became a new character
We can't blame anyone for this
- Hey
Lend me something for wiping
I don't think there's anything like that
- Please
What the hell?
There's nothing
- So, it's not comedy?
Is it not?
We can't use it?
He said that for all of them
Yeah, and this one was fun
We could have used this gag!
Yes, it was hilarious
I can see that
It was fun, right?
- A lot
So fun
- Is it not good?
It's not good
No?
- No way
How does it feel like?
Uhm...
- I mean, getting sneezed at
Well,
It's humiliating
But we had them wait so much
Can't help it, I waited too, it's humiliating
Your voice is so raspy
I've never smelled something that bad
Woah, was it that bad?
VERDICT: MIDDLE-AGED MEN SNEEZES ON FACE - 10 HITS
IS NOT COMEDY !!
Down from the tower!
"Down from the tower! Small watermelon head-crack!"
Small watermelon head-crack~ !!
So, Matsumoto-san
What now?
We used small watermelons lots of times in Gaki
And I think we all agree it's funny to see
one of them smacked on someone's face
But what about having it fall on someone's head from 10 meters?
Small watermelon head-crack!!
Break the small watermelon dropped from an height of 10 meters with your head
Let's see if it will be judged as "comedy" or "not comedy"  !
I think we have to set some guidelines for it
This is pretty solid
It will be aimed at you
This weight...
Got it?
This will fall from 10 meters, so it will be a lot more
Its weight, yeah
I already think
This is not comedy
You can't say it yet
- Wait
Something you judge as "comedy" has yet to appear, geez
He's right, you said no to everything
Yeah but I mean, this is really...
It's gonna roll all the way and fall on your head
For this one
We'll have Tanaka-kun go up and do it
I think Hamada-san is better suited for this
It's not like it has anything to do with Hamada
And he's also not good with heights
That's true
I think it's about time we get a "it's comedy" from you
I agree, I really want this to work out
I want it too, really
Also, how many will hit you out of the total of 36?
You gotta be kidding me!
We don't know
We didn't ask how many there will be
You already broke my throat!
Well, at least
Let's see how the first one goes
And so,
Will "Small watermelon head-crack" be
Small Watermelon Head Crack:
Will it be comedy !?  Or not comedy !?
Labeled as comedy or not?
I've seen this on TV before
- Are you for real?!
This is...
- I'm here
Alright, everything's set
This is incredible
Wait a sec
- Ok
He'll just place the watermelon there
and it will roll down automatically
Is comedy supposed to be something this scary?
Well, it's all about
Having this tension turn into something to laugh about
This will be better than the previous ones
Comedy medals will pour down on you like hail
Are you ready!?
Are you for real?
Wait, for real?
That's all he's been sayin'
Can I toss it!?
Alright!
Come on, Tanaka is getting pissed
Ok, shall we begin?
W-wait
"Small watermelon...
Wait--
...head crack":
Start!!
Wait, wait!!
Here comes
Scary!
- Here it comes
That's so scary!
Wasn't that good?
How will he judge this?
Which is it?
Is it comedy or not?
It broke so good
This isn't comedy
But that is comedy
How can it not be?
- You sure?
It was so good
- It broke so nicely
He got sniped
We did it good
Right, Yama-chan?
It was good, right?
this is a performance Yamazaki is doing as a professional comedian
please do not attempt to imitate him
It didn't hurt, didn't it?
That was such a clean shot
- I know, right?
What's wrong?
You're not bleeding
It's not
Your acting really sucks
You're not bleeding
We all
Worked hard for this one, right?
- We did
But really...
I can assure no one was laughing that much
No way, no way, you're wrong
We all shouted "woah"!
We were surprised
In a way, on that moment we weren't laughing
And that's why it's not comedy
So what should we do? We don't really know either
I can see you're determined
But "effort" and "comedy" aren't the same thing
Ok, but...
When you think about it, it's funny
- Yes, if you re-think it
No good?
- No good
Also
Did the watermelon get inside my eyes?
It did not
I can feel it inside em
Like
In your eyebags?
Exactly
Are they full of watermelon juice?
- Yes
I can feel them pressing
Well, I can't deny they seem swollen
Right?
You sort of became Marlon Brando
Marlon Brando
That's true
How come?
It's cause it got inside
- It did, yeah
So it's not comedy?
- Seems like it
Even though it was so good
- Yeah...
Sorry, Tanaka
Was it no good?
Yeah, no good
Are you done? I mean, I have tons of watermelons here
Are you idiot? We're done!
He said you're idiot, Tanaka
It's not comedy
Got it
VERDICT: SMALL WATERMELON HEAD CRACK
IS NOT COMEDY !!
Drink up!
"Drink up! Megaphone water truck gulpin' drinking!"
Megaphone water truck gulpin' drinking !
So, what's this about?
We have a water truck prepared for this one, today
Megaphone water truck gulpin' drinking
Gulp it all down by catching it with the megaphone!
Drink up the large amount of water fired by the water truck:
And we also have this plastic megaphone, a large one
We'll have him hold it like this
Basically
It's a all-you-can-drink
You have to catch the water fired from the truck
With this and drink it
A water all-you-can-drink
I mean, don't you like drinking water?
You drink a lot of it!
I saw you drinking it lots of times
That's where I got the hint for this
One time we had dinner and I saw him drinking water
And there I got the hint for this
Of course you'd drink it
Yep
"Yep" my ass
This time
Will this megaphone drinking challenge
Megaphone water truck drinking:
Will it be comedy !?  Or not comedy !?
Be judged as comedy or not?
"Megaphone water truck gulpin' drinking": start!
Here goes!
Cold!!
It got in, Matsumoto!
We should aim higher
Is it getting in?
Matsumoto-san, how is it?
He should lower the megaphone a bit
Yamazaki, lower the megaphone!
Alright
WHAT THE HE !!
"What the he"...?
That's what he said
"What the he"?
- We don't get it
What happened?
WHAT THE HE, THE HE, THE HEEE !!
That's a combo
What's wrong?
How should we judge this?
I mean, is it comedy?
Matsumoto, do you think water got inside the megaphone?
I mean, Yamazaki's technique...
I can't deny he had one, but
He had to improve his posture
- He should have raised it more
After all I don't think he didn't make it
He's rising up
This is like "Goodbye Yamazaki"
I've seen this before
Stop this!
What are you doing?
- Why did he attack him?
Back up, Tanaka
I have no idea what just... is this comedy or not?
Which is it?
- Let's make that clear
Which one?
- Is it comedy?
Please tell us
Tell us if its comedy or not
Tell us please
Just tell us this
- We have to know
I wonder why he attacked Matsumoto
Why isn't he talking?
- Is it comedy?
THAT CAN'T BE COMEDY !!
So it's not comedy after all...
But we really want to find comedy...
If someone turns the tv on now
I bet they'll think this is Piccadilly-san
Piccadilly Umeda
No one could tell, he shouted just like him
Alright then
Our last one is
"Burdock strike match!"
Burdock strike match!
Let go!
- Don't run!
Stop, Yamazaki!
This part is repeating, so here's a fun fact: Burdocks are very healthy - they can help preventing high blood pressure and blood vessel hardening; they also prevent high cholesterol and constipation, and they're good for hair health.
Go get him!
He's running
- Where is he--
How is this?
Bring the camera over there
Get here
How is it?
- Come on
THAT'S JUST A TREE BRANCH !
A tree branch!
Say something!!
JUST SAY SOMETHING !
SAY SOMETHING!!
You weakling
He really hated this
To think we had Moriman to come all the way here!
Yeah, from Hokkaido...
They came from Hokkaido just for this episode
Tanuuma Man
Holstein Morio
Moriman
That's right
It's been a while since they came here
He got away really quickly
He really was fast
Alright
Cocorico, maybe you can go and bring him back here?
- Should we go look for him?
We'll try to catch him
- Yes
I mean seriously, that guy
Didn't say anything
And they both came from Hokkaido
- Yeah...
He ran away like crazy though...
He was so fast
Is he under a car!?
Under a car--?
A car--?
Is he a stray cat?!
We can't go further
No problem
He's frightened
- We'll take the digital
Here
He won't get out
We should just go home by now
Come here, come here
Come here
- It's fine
Don't be afraid
- This is too funny
Here kitty kitty!
Get out, we have canned tuna!
It's your favorite!
This is hilarious
Come on, we have tuna
Yama-chan...
- It's good tuna!
Don't be afraid!
- We have tuna!
Don't worry, they got home with AIR-DO
note: Hokkaido-based airplane company
Really, we don't have much time
They really took an AIR-DO
Yama-chan!
Do something, Tanaka
Zaki-san
- We have canned goods
It's ok
- Don't worry
He bit him!
Come on
I think he became a misanthropist
I think so too
'Cause he got bullied
- He holds a grudge
Against us humans
- Yama-chan...
Yama-chan, we'll make that Hiace (car) go boom
We'll turn this on
This...
- We're moving it
Maybe we should move it, yeah
Could it be...
...That he's pregnant?
Eh? For real?
Now you've done it!
More Gaki & japanese comedy @ shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Updates, news & more @ facebook.com/shionnotsukai (like it)
...and on Twitter @ FGRNDNoises (follow it)
...or on Patreon @ patreon.com/shionnotsukai
You can support my works on ko-fi @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
Reminder:
this is a no-profit fansub, made by a fan for other fans