First ever, Gaki no tsukai ya arahende episode 8 Absolutely Tasty Hot pot
Matsumoto-san, episode 8?
Episode 8, according to the season, it is for hot pot
That's right
New idea
New idea has been coming out, example the Maneli hot pot
We can do it
The reward is good
If it's good, why nobody did it?
Heck i know
Let's begin
Top batter is Tanaka, the hot pot of his idea is?
It's Okinawa hot pot
Everything is Okinawa's
Surprisingly there is no hot pot fit the Okinawa image
Hot
And cold
Obviously from the point of health, the ingredient contains lots of nutrients
This is hot water
This is salt from Okinawa to give the distinct taste of Okinawa
There is a lot of mineral
Of course there is lots of mineral but what we care is the taste
There is no taste Tanaka
Put in everything
Everything
The pork and other ingredient will give the taste
That's right
I'm not sure about the taste
Here is Orion beer
1 can?
1 whole can
Whole can
Then mix it
Seriously?
The alcohol will be cooked
I see
Ocean taste
Then next
Ocean taste bad
That's worst
Next is Endo, The hot pot he wanted to try?
Everyone ate French cuisine before?
French cuisine is luxurious
Eating French cuisine always take a long time
So this time i bring this
French cuisine full course Hot pot
It will take a short time to eat
It's fun
It looks bad
Don't tell me this is dessert?
Is it?
It is
Dessert too?
For French cuisine there is Consomme
This is delicious
Is this right?
It is
Veggie and meat
It smells nice
This is the one,
It's the bad one
Stop~~
Stop
Without this one i think it will work
This is a must
That is bad
I wanted to try full course
Together they become tastier
Are you really sure it's okay?
Next is Yamazaki, what kind of ingredient is he using to challenge Endo?
If Endo is going for French
I am going for America
Amazing
This is fun
This is
Fine
This
Soup
Coke
It's coke?
So America
Soup?
This is the soup
That is what we drink?
Lots of fats
The fats cooked with the coke
The carbonic acid will break it down
This is dangerous
It's coke right?
I want to eat it just like this
Can i pour it together?
Take it like this
Okay, see
Japan 2-sword style
2-sword style
Dangerous
This is dangerous
This is absolutely delicious
They are drinking
They can do it
Amazing
I'm interested
Next is Hamada who bring his Hometown ingredients
Osaka
This is the mark
This is
Image of Osaka
Again?
This is something that i want to avoid
The soup is the usual
Bonito Soup
In this..
I don't know what it taste now
For real?
You liking this much is amazing
Then it's this
Okonomiyaki
1st is Okonomiyaki
Wait, this..
The smell is not bad
Yeah, the smell
The smell not bad
Takoyaki
If we can finish this one, we will include rice
At the same time?
It will taste like brackish water
Wait, this looks delicious
Last is Matsumoto, what kind of Hot Pot will he bring?
I am thinking of something fresh
It's salad Hot Pot
Salad Hot Pot
All is veggie
All is veggie and this is Bonito soup
In this..
Everything will be veggie
I am making a serious face
Face expression don't matter
Amazing
I see
Because it don't have much taste
Wait, it's not Hamada's sauce here..
Mayonnaise
It's too much
It's okay
Healthy-themed
This is seriously tasty
For real?
It's still not done
There is finishing touch
I see
I always have extra ingredient
There is extra
Producer told me to do it
Don't lie
After we finish ours, it will be reveal then
Let's eat
First is Okinawa Hot Pot
Let's start, open
It's here
How is the appearance
First look, it's delicious
It's Hot Pot
It looks extremely good
This is Hot Pot
This is, how you say it?
Pork soup
This is surely the taste is good
This is absolutely delicious
However there is no Bonito taste
Lacking taste
The pig or whatever, the broth is in the soup now
There is only salt for flavor
How is the soup
The soup is ridiculously delicious
Seriously
The taste is there
Shut up
All the taste is there
Good
It has a very subtle taste
Ain't it?
This is not bad
It has a similarity to normal hot pot
The soup is
Make you liking it more and more
Lacking something
For the lack of taste, i am thinking of using
Sima Togarashi
Put just a drop
Enhance taste?
I like this
Just a bit
Delicious
This is delicious, you try this
You put this in, it become super delicious
A little spicy
Delicious
Very tasty
This is delicious
How many point for this?
This one is good
I will give it a 4
I see
It's not I see
Only perfect score can satisfy this one, after you guys saying delicious all over
9 or 10 is fine right?
9 or 10
9 or 10?
It fits this right?
I think 7 is fine
Then 7 is fine
Se-.. I see, it's still first one
So for the first one
Taste like the usual Hot Pot, receive 7
Next is Endo with his mixed dessert French style Hot Pot
French cuisine takes time
This one is dangerous
This one is kinda messed up
This one please enjoy it everyone, Open
Is it okay?
What the heck
This is not good
This is bad
The cost is high right?
Yeah it's high
Around 10000 yen
You are using wine glass as container?
Obviously, this
Wine glass is essential for French cuisine
Seriously?
For real?
Then for Hamada
You should just put in meat
For being special, i will give you the dessert
I don't want!
Hamada like it a lot
He is fooling around
This is messed up
Is this okay?
I am serious
What taste will it be
The appearance is the worst
Delicious
Um, delicious
It was because there is no dessert in yours
Delicious
How is the dessert
Tasty
The meat and fish is very delicious
Delicious
Tasty
Endo, this is delicious
Even though it looks bad but it is delicious right?
Delicious
I still prefer to eat my full course the usual way
How is it?
This is completely 4 right?
Seriously?
Completely 4, completely
Around the region of 4
Around 4
We say it's delicious, however it is still not THAT delicious
That's right
The same as always
Endo
Why attack you junior
This is 4
With the worse appearance however still taste good full course hot pot, 4 point
Next is Yamazaki's USA hot pot, with coke as the soup
Let's start
Let's see
Bad
It float
Looks like Oden
Is this all right to use the name America for this thing
It stink
The smell
This is bad
The smell is bad
What did you make
This is the best mascot for making enemies out of America
Wasn't the word stop fooling around came out from your mouth?
What is it?
It looks the like the same as the previous one
He is fooling around
The soup color is fine
True
True. It looks like Tempura Udon
If the taste is not enough we have ketchup and mustard
To begin with I don't like this
If it's not enough you say?
Just put it for people who like it
The soup looks good, but
Let's eat
Terrible
This is scary
Wait, wait, don't say that before tasting it properly
Wait, this is delicious
It's bad, the first mouthful already bad
Wait, eat it properly
Terrible
You didn't eat it
This is terrible
Bad, bad, bad
Wait, i don't want this
We said it's bad
I don't want this
Why don't you eat it?
Yamachan, this is bad
This is bad, this is total failure
This is total failure
Sweet
Ah, but maybe
Yamachan, try it
Wait, stop it already. Stop it
It's too much
It's fine
Why are you being so gay
There is no problem at all
Looks good
It's spicy
You are noisy
Why are you suddenly being such a wuss
Dangerous mark
Both looks and smell bad, USA hot pot get Dokuro*
Next is Hamada who wan born Kansai, he make an Osaka Hot pot
Then let's begin, open
Hamada's Kansai idea, how will it taste?
Hamada unforgettable Hot Pot, what will it taste like?
Okay let's begin, Open
It doesn't look bad
Is it okay?
The sauce can even mix with the rice and it will taste fantastic
Osakan
Kansai people
Hamada actually I am not that
You mix it
The yakisoba still maintain strain by strain
Let's eat
Together with rice this is very simple
This is confusing
What the heck is this
This is
Surely
There is no solidity
The noodle is too soft
We can't bite it
Although with that reason, inside me i said, delicious
It's truly delicious
Delicious, i like this
Have you tried the Takoyaki?
Yes, delicious
This is not bad
Would it be better if we add pepper?
I don't really know
Would it be better if adding pepper into it?
after i add the pepper, it just power-up
Adding pepper make it extremely good
Delicious
Too delicious
Not just delicious but too delicious
It's extremely delicious
I am shocked
Everyone, how many point?
Right, how many point will you give?
It's troublesome
That's right
Although it wasn't that good at first but it deserves 10 right?
In any case, it's 10
It's 8
Let's make it 8
Although i have no right to say, but i say 10~~
Endo say 10
This deserve 10 right?
I will give it full point
Full point
Let Yamazaki decide
Then it is near 6
What the heck, WHAT THE HECK!
Too strict
Everyone is praising it so highly, so why is it 6
Because Yamazaki have a good taste, what he said is true
What the heck
What the heck? 6?
Yes, it's final
Sharing the same fate as Cocorico's creation, Osaka Hot Pot get 6 point
Next is Matsumoto's salad Hot Pot, what is the unique way of eating?
Let's see this, Don
What's this
I see
It's mayonnaise
It's mayonnaise?
It will come out like this
It looks healthy
It has an interesting smell
Ain't it?
Why eat hot salad?
I am still not done
Bring that over
Ice?
Because it's salad, i will prefer to eat it cold
This is salad Hot Pot core
But it's HOT pot, wouldn't it be okay to eat it hot?
What the heck?
So, i just put in the ice
Now eat it
Why the heck
You are just fooling around
Fooling around is the thing i hate the most
Danger, danger, it's not like that, what are we talking about
Let's eat
Don't stir
This is originally..
It looks so plain
Originally the soup is from Bonito, so it is fine
Wouldn't it be plain?
There is too much water
Asparagus?
It's asparagus
There is no taste at all
Not even a taste
Just as i thought
Not a slight taste
I actually has thought about this
That one..
What? what?
Sauce to dip
You have sauce?
Dressing
Like my secret weapon
I see
Mix it well then eat it together with the salad
This is..
acceptable
Right?
Try it
With the sauce it's fine
Right
Delicious
Why you didn't bring this out
Why you make this into Hot Pot?
True
First of all, it's edible
It is fine
The taste not strong enough
The mayonnaise didn't contribute much
Not a hint
How's this
How is it?
I see
I am also thinking of 1 or 2
I think Dokuro
I think 2
Dokuro too
I am truthfully, this is
This is just experiment, I have another one
I don't really care whether it's Dokuro,1 or 2
Is that so?
My main is next
Because it is still edible, 2 then
Far from the actual Hot Pot, Salad Hot Pot receive 2
What is Matsumoto's Main Ingredient?
Let's look at the ingredient, it's so called Healthy Hot Pot
Healthy hot pot?
What the heck did you bring
This is seriously..
This time is amazing
This is expensive
Cobra
Cobra?
What's this?
This is that one..
Deer's testicle
Testicle?
It stink!
What smell is this
What is this smell
What makes it so stink
It's the smell of testicle, it is still not clean
Dirty
I WILL not eat it!
It's fine right?
Everything here is exotic ingredient
How will it taste
Everything is exotic
True
After that, to add meat inside, i will use eel, this is amazing
After you eat this you will be..
You will become a nerd
Exotic ingredient is used, in this exotic Hot Pot, how will it taste?
It smells okay right?
You put in, leek
Leek is in there
If you eat this, you will be full of energy
For real? How you know?
The day to eat this will be Saturday
Normally it will be one day too
Eating this day by day
This is a big piece form the turtle
What the heck is that
Recently Tanaka
has been very hardworking so his portion will be big
Collagen
We cannot take the cobra
We will get the cobra later, now let's just eat what's in our bowl
I think Vacuum Fujiwara would like to eat it
He will eat it like a delight
It will be our first time watching someone eat rice with these
Bring the condiment
Young ginseng and
Don't need this
Do this
Stop, stop, stop it, it's bitter
Are you a kid? Stop because it's bitter
What's this?
Shredded ginger
To remove stench
It also has the function to remove stench
Because it stink though
The main purpose is just to remove the stench
Wa- What are you doing
What we doing?
Seriously what are you doing? It looks like cigarette lighter
Let's eat
This time round let's just drink
Strange taste
What's this
It just spread around mouth
True, it just go "GAH" inside the mouth
True
It goes "GAH"
This is the characteristic
Amazing
You must treat this seriously
Tomorrow you wake up your **** will be up
I don't want anymore
True, i don't want it to be up
Stop saying such disgusting stuff
Why?
Amazing
It's not something bad though
Amazing this one goes "Gah"
Please eat that, it's head
It's damn tough
Stay tune, eating champion Vacuum Fujiwara
Is it okay? Vacuum
Please
We prepared rice for Vacuum
Good day to you
Go with this one?
The soft texture
Collagen too
Collagen only
This one is soft
It's soft right?
It's soft, can i get a bowl of rice?
I knew it will be like that
With rice he can eat anything
Maybe collagen is a good side dish
Amazing
The best way to eat collagen is with rice
It looks good, the collagen is delicious right?
You being able to eat collagen with rice, what are you?
In actual truth you cannot eat it
Because of courage