What?
Endo Shozo
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Tanaka Naoki
You know, from my experience I can tell
When we start an episode in small parks like this
Yeah?
It's not going to be fun
It's a matter of fact, you know
I can explain
Is it a sign?
That's what I personally think
Tanaka seems to know about this
Does he?
Yes, I've been told actually
Do you remember last year's year-end party?
Yes
Remember it started with that character, Freddie?
You remember him?
We do
broadcast on January 27th 2019
provided by
Freddie, the man who sang for this year's year-end party
We got a certain suggestion from him
Mr. Freddie said he wants to do a walk-around-the-city show
Aaand denied
Alright, let's wrap this up
Wanderin' around with Mr. Freddie
We'll have Mr. Freddie join us as a guest and we'll stroll around the city!
We're not done
I don't get what's the point of this
We're not done, come on
Who the hell is mr. Freddie?
We're in hurry so let's go
Are these things still around today?
Let's call him here with us, please!
provided by
Is he singing?
Oh, is this a live performance?
It is
Oh, is it?
You're right
Sorry
I'm talking to that man watching us
Sorry for this
Sorry
Sorry for the bother
We're going to leave soon
We're just playing around
Haha, sorry
Here's mr. Freddie
Today's guest
Mr. Freddie
Good morning
Good morning!
It's the real deal
It's a pleasure
Sure...
What are y'all doin'?
What a voice
What do you mean?
You look so full of energy today
What are ya doin', huh?
We just got here
His volume is really something
It is, it comes from his stomach
Aren't you cold?
I'm hot
Is that so?
Aren't y'all hot?
Well, not really
You sure you're not cold? Mentally?
Look at this face, wow
He's so energetic
S-so, today's plan...
We're all going to visit the shop district
from Freddie's hometown
While Freddie recalls his best memories we're going to visit his hometown
"Hometown"...?
That's right
It's really close to where we're now
It's his hometown, you can take a look at it here
Right here
What's this?
You can read here he's this town's tourism ambassador
Is he?
He is
Oh, you're right
That's how influential he is
Is this the same sheet?
Oh, no
It's a different one
I see
Oh, what's this?
It's a leaflet
Looks like a Freddie stamp rally
The winner gets rice, huh
Eh?
Are you a comedian?
I'm not
I'm Freddie, dontcha know who I am?
No I mean, I know, but...
From Queen
Sure...
You just told us
Is that true?
It is
Dontcha know?
No, no
I do know about Freddie from Queen
It's me, Freddie Mercury from Queen
He's mr. Freddie
Are you that exact same person?
Of course I am
This is so crazy...
Let's go
He ignored you
Feels like he wanted to cut it
Let's move to the shopping district
It was so sudden
Are you walking all day like this?
He's so lively...
At this point I think
By the time he loses this spirit, it'll be over
True
That's right
He just has to do it
Yeah...
He knows it'll be over as soon as he slows down
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com | fb.com/shionnotsukai |
ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai | patreon.com/shionnotsukai
translation by SHION
typeset by KEDOMAS
Downtown's
Gaki no Tsukai
ya Arahende!
Mr. Freddie's beloved hometown's shopping district
They finally arrived to mr. Freddie's beloved hometown shopping district
Let's explore Freddie's memories of this place
What do you like about this town?
I think that yeah, it's easy to walk
Easy to walk...?
Yeah
Is there any hard to walk town to begin with?
Do you usually go to kakuyasu?
I do actually, love it
What do you buy there?
I like sparkling wine
Sparkling wine, huh
It figures
I really like Mitake
Maybe it's been displayed 'cause I like it?
How should I know this?
So friggin' loud
His voice is really something
I have no idea, man
We don't
But man, his voice
I wish he'd be quieter
And I have no idea what he's talking about
Hey pops
What now?
Oh
Freddie?
Boy, it's been so long!
This is so stupid
How many years?
I wonder...
Can I...?
Man, the memories!
What's wrong?
Can I ask you one thing?
As seen on "Freddie's stroll", it says...
Oh
Is this show a thing?
This is mr. Freddie
You're right
I did that, yes
Before?
It's like Jun Sanpo, right?
Those kind of shows
I used to run this show
Oh, in the past?
Any recommendation here, Freddie?
I'm gonna have the usual
The usual? Coming up
Does he have an "usual" here?
Well, it's his town...
But he said "it's been so long" before
True
Maybe it's because he's always busy doing stuff
That's right
Oh boy...
This episode makes me suffer
Come on
Such a bother
Well, if I had to describe this somehow...
It would be "bother", wouldn't it?
Yeah, kinda
Something like that
I wonder which croquet we're gonna eat
Boss?
These are croquet, right?
They are
Where's the boss?
It's taking him forever 'cause he's not the real shop owner
Sorry for the wait, they're freshly done
Thanks
They're hot, be careful
Thank you
Take it, but careful
Thanks
Oh, nice
Here, careful
Thanks
It's pretty big
Mr. Freddie's beloved croquet
Their size is what makes em popular here
They're delicious
Really good
I'm diggin' in
They are
The boss here wants to...
It's kinda sweet, isn't it?
You like it?
It's good, yeah
Thank you
I was saying, the boss here has a
request for Freddie, am I right?
That's right
You know, he made a song based off this croquet
You remember it, don't you?
Which is it?
I do
You did...?
Based off a croquet?
Huh?
A famouos song?
It's based off this?
Yeah, that's what I've been told
Uh? Really?
I wonder which one is it
That's how he wrote most of his songs
Here!
provided by
You heard this one before?
No, it's my first time
He just said "croquet"
I clearly heard that
Radio gaga~♪
Radio gaga...
Hey!
What does it mean?
So Radio Gaga is based off croquet
I'm not sure what's going on
It's hard to grasp
Who would have thought?
Incredible
Alright, shall we go?
Already going elsewhere?
How about a photo before?
Ok ok
He just wants to go
Let's take a pic, folks!
We're lucky we got to hear him singing live
Yeah
Take care!
Thank you
Sure, see ya next time!
I'm gonna come back soon for more croquettes!
With everyone!
Ok
Nice
There's a lot of people here 'cause we're filming
But I swear not a single one of them was laughing
Ah, is that so?
Yeah...
Oh
What?
Here's another shop he's very fond of
Mr. Freddie's beloved jazz bar
bon appétit​
Really?
It seems that way
You know...
Yes?
This is the place where I formed my band
Eh?
Huh?
It's the place which gave birth to Queen
Let's get inside!
Like that...?
Does it mean that...
Yes?
We're gonna meet the owner?
Probably yes
It feels like a jazz bar, doesn't it?
Please come in
Look how big it is
Wait---
Huh?
The members
surprise appearance
Queen Band Members
Wha-?
Oh, come on!
Freddie! It's been a while
Just a moment, just a moment!
It's Freddie!
Are you kiddin' me?
We're here for you!
What the?
It's been so long
You tricked me, didn't you?
Was this your plan?
Oh, no, no, we didn't plan this
I bet ya called 'em here
That's not true
C'mere!
My boy!
Where have you been?
Oooh!
It's been so long, man!
You played me a nice lil trick, didntcha?
Y-yeah, a little surprise
You didn't know?
I did not
Sorry about that
It's a nice surprise, isn't it?
We didn't even know
That's right. Hey, how about you introduce them to us?
Alright, I'll start
I'm Brian and I play guitar, yaaaay!
Brian, huh
I'm John, my pleasure
I'm Roger, I play drums
Come on, sit down
Sure thing, Freddie
No need to be so reserved
Please
We're gonna sit too
There's no need, ya know
We're not
You're one to talk
Has it really been that long since you last met?
Just a few minutes ago...
Mr. Freddie told us the band was born in this very place
So you got the idea here?
At first it was just me and this guy here
I see...
Who and who?
Me and him
- That's not it
It was me and him, then Brian lured us in
That's not how it went, that's another story
He already forgot
- He really did, duh
Cut the bullshit, guys
This is no place for talk sessions
Ohh
'Cause we're all talking, huh?
Always thinkin' about sessions, aren't ya?
Got any questions for them?
Well, since we're here...
Any questions?
Not about me
Yeah, I mean, we got all the members here
Do you have, like...
Any failure story to tell us now that Freddie's here?
We have loads of those!
- We do have 'em
- Right?
Remember when he wet his pants?
Eh?
Yeah, he couldn't help it
Huh...
So pathetic!
During which song?
Which song was it...?
- Eh? Song?
A song...
It was a copy, wasn't it?
We were doin' a cover
A copy?
Uh, yes
You did covers too?
Not an original song?
What the heck
I could be wrong
A copy, huh
Oh, here it is! Our pizza!
A pizza?
Eat up, please
Grab a slice
Mr. Freddie's beloved mixed pizza
This is really good
Are there any memories related to this?
We used to eat this all the time
What do you like about it?
Well, I think...
You'll get it just by looking at it
First off, I really like pizza
But if you look at this one
You know
I hate square-shaped pizzas
It's not really a thing
They're usually round all the time
But which is the most unique feature to it?
See--- listen, ok?
You can see there's a lot of salami here and there
Yeah
Yes
There's also corn, and cheese...
Mhh
Mh-mh
Well, I love it
It's your pizza, to put it simply
Yeah, that's the pizza I always think of
Your first choice
You guys like it too, right?
We do, yeah
Right?
Are those guys Queen?
Yes, it's them
So in other words... Sorry, I don't know much about them
Yes?
Yes, yes...
You did several tours around the world, right?
Of course we did
World tours and stuff?
Yes
Which country did you like the most?
Maybe something around the Mediterranean Sea
- I think-- yeah, that
Eastern Europe, maybe? I liked that
- I liked the Mediterranean area too
Ya know, we started with steps
Steps?
Steps, right?
Yeah
That's incredible
How was it?
[bohemian gibberish]
What are we looking at?
[gibberish]
How long is this gonna take?
It's so bad
What is this?
Gotta appreciate it
[still gibberish]
Thank you, thank you, enough
Thanks for this
We just witnessed a rare session
We're so lucky we got to listen to it
So that's how you do it?
Was it ad-lib?
That's how they do it and why they're so famous
Whatever
I was just wondering how it could have been
I always wondered how
We still got it guys
This is a bit unexpected...
But today
Mr. Brian
Yes?
Brought with him a letter of gratitude for Freddie
I know it's out of character, but whatever, boy!
Oi
What the-
A letter of gratitude for mr. Freddie
Dear Freddie,
At the beginning of our debut
I didn't have any confidence in my own guitarist skills
And one time
I told you I wanted to quit the band
But when I did
You told me, "Brian... I was born...
...to love you!
So why don't you play for me?"
Had you never told me that at the time...
I would probably be rotting in prison by now
Thank you, Freddie!
Come on, don't cry...
Let's cheer up!
Look at 'em, the wig boys
Wigs
You're the wigs
But we have something from Freddie too
Yes
Huh?
He wants us to listen to something
Really?
A surprise gig?
That's right
What the...?
Maybe we won't get it as much as them
That's right
We're not musicians after all
Yeah, that's it
Yeah, sort of
Okay
provided by
Was it like this?
Sure
We all know this one
It's his most famous song
We all know it
It's not really a surprise
Huh?
What do you--
That sucked so bad
What do you think of Freddie's performance?
Outstanding
As expected
You're a rakugo artist, aren't you?
We're going to Freddie's house
Where are we going next?
Yeah, where?
I've been pranked all day by you
Why are you doing this?
Oh
We--- we just wanted to surprise you
Why do you enjoy surprising people?
I'll be surprised when I feel like being it
I know it was a surprise but... it was a good one, I guess?
Yeah, it was nice
There are people I don't wanna meet, ya know
Huh?!
Wha-
I hate him!
Who...?
The croquet guy
croquet shop boss
The shop owner?
You should have know I hate him
We had no idea, you even sang for him
I used to be bullied by him
Ah, when you were a kid?
That's right
I was the only one to receive half-sized croquettes by him
Well, we---
Why are you trying to surprise me?
He's getting so angry
But we---
I'm going home!
Oh, sorry about that
Come on, mr. Freddie
We're sorry
I really hate them
Uh? You what?
I hate surprises
He really hates them
I really do
We got it
Oh we--- we arrived?
Ah- oh no
We're here
What?
Come on, we're here
Here
Come on
I think this is his house
Where are we?
Is this your house?
That's right
Look at the dog house, its name is "Quinn"
Ohhh
Wow
This is impressive
He has lots of the same outfit
He really likes this style
Yeah
It's barking like crazy
It is
Sorry doggy
It's getting familiar
Can you pet it a bit?
Sure
Come here, boy
Good boy
Here
What the hell are you doin'?
They don't know each other
They're both on guard
What the hell is this
Alright then
I can't feel any mutual trust out of this
Let's go
Meeting face-to-face with mr. Freddie's family
Let's just go
Ok
Woah, amazing
I'm home!
Welcome back
I'm back, baby
Please get in
Thanks, are you busy?
Come in
Excuse us
Is this his house?
Yes
Good morning
Nice to meet you
Thanks for always taking care of my Freddie
Who's this?
His wife?
Yes, I'm Freddywife
It's a pleasure to meet you
Freddywife
Freddywife...?
Is that your name?
Yes
This is...
Please, come in
Please
Today's been--- are you sure we can?
Make yourself at home
With all the cameras?
Dont' worry
I can see a resemblance
Want some tea?
Yes
Please get in
Who
Who's that?
That's
My son, Freddyson
Freddyson
He's going through puberty
Oh, I see...
You can tell
That's why he's ignoring us
Yeah
Go say hello to our guests
Freddyson...
Freddyson
It's ok
Have a seat, please
Sorry
We get him
Let him enjoy it
Please make yourself at home
I'm surprised he didn't run to his room
You can tell it's his house just by looking at it
Yeah, I agree
Of course you can
Did you do kendo?
Huh? I'm interested
Yeah I used to
There are lots of pictures there
You see
They've been taking photos of me since I was born
Since you were born?
Like this one?
Is this...?
You looked like this when you were born?
Of course I did
You were a newborn here?
Yes
Incredible
It is
I really wasn't a showy baby
I think it's... about time we leave?
Already?!
You just got here
Yeah but---
You still haven't seen them
My family
But--
We just met your son
Hey!
Come here Freddaughter
He has a daughter too?
Freddaughter? Come here
A daughter
Papa Freddie!
Freddaughter
His daughter...
What were you doing?
I was playing
Which game?
Tag with my plushies
Tag with your plushies!?
Today
We all played tag at the kindergarten
You played tag? Was it fun?
It was fun
Ohh, tag
Which oni were you playing as?
Mhh...
The oni of ice!
The oni of ice, huh...
The oni of ice?
They seem really...
Yeah
They get along
Seems like it
I think it's time to...
Yes
What's with the hurry?
No---
I mean, we met your son and daughter...
You wanna go home that bad?
I told ya you haven't met 'em all yet
Huh?
My family
But we saw 'em, wife and kids
It's a nuclear family, right?
Daddyfreddy! Mamafreddy!
He looks normal
Thanks for taking care of our Freddie
Daddyfreddy
My name's Daddyfreddy
I'm Mamafreddy
Mamafreddy
It's a pleasure to have you here
This is horrible
I'm having a horrible time
I hate this
The pleasure is ours
Your parents are here too, huh
Do you all live together?
Ah, is that so...
Daddyfreddy looks like a normal person
You're right, it doesn't feel strange on him
Alright
It's still early to leave
You came like 5 minutes ago
That's not true
It's way more
It's been way more than that
It felt like a year to me
What now?
Actually...
Yes?
I wanted to do today's gig for this too
It's been 30 years
Mr. Freddie wrote a new song after 30 years Its title is "We Will The Champions"
A new song?
Yep
Is it new?
It is
Oh my
Papa is going to sing
Freddie's new song's performance
Wow
Is it really a new song?
We will the champions
So...
See?
I heard this before
It's a bit wrong here
It went down
Huh? It's changing
Mo ee de ♪
(enough)
He said "enough"
I heard it too
Mo ee de... ♪
(that's enough)
Kaere ♪
(go away)
He said it!
Really?!
Mo ee de, hayo kaere ♪
(I had enough, just go home)
Go home?
He said "just go home"
Mo ee kaere, kaere ♪
(I'm done, just go home)
We've been asking you that
Look
Your son is laughing
Your son just laughed
Your puberty boy
I saw him laughing too
Kocchi da ♪
(the exit's here)
Kocchi ni ike kaere ♪
(exit from here and go home)
There?
What the heck
What the-
So sudden
Thanks for having us
Thank you
It was a pleasure
(staff) Ok, thank you
"Ok" what?
There's nothing "ok" in this
What's ok with this?
Look what I almost took home with me
shop district flyer
This is frightening
I'm not gonna take this home with me
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
TWITTER.COM/FGRNDNOISES
FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TRANSLATION BY SHION
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT FAN TRANSLATION MADE BY FANS FOR OTHER FANS TO ENJOY. NO COPYRIGHT INFRINGMENT INTENDED.
TYPESET AND QUALITY CHECK BY KEDOMAS