1st Time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arrahende
"I'm the One Who Understands you Best!"
"Anyways, I Think You'll Like this Item!" Mizusawa Ally Edition!!
Can I say something?
Do you really need to be so loud?
It really was something.
It was right?
It felt like it just kept getting louder.
Let's just move on, we don't need to keep talking about this.
I get it.
Let's get going.
A special series on Gaki, where the members buy gifts for guests based on their interests!!
(Also known as: Ari, Arie, Ali)
Today's guest is Tōkyō Girls Collection model and fashionable talent, Mizusawa Ally.
The five member's will present a top and an accessory which they think will suit our guest.
However, will the members be able to choose something to suit the 24 year old!?
This is Mizusawa Ally, didn't you mistake her for someone else?
I mistook her for Omiya Ellie-san.
You just changed up the letters.
Remember who our guest is.
I will, I will.
We can't have you messing up her name again.
I won't mess up again.
How was it this time Matsumoto-san?
This time was pretty tough.
I mean, we've only seen her TV image.
That's true.
And she's the youngest guest we've had so far.
Add to that a young woman.
It's not exactly our speciality.
Yeah that's true, she's quite young.
Well, without further ado, let's welcome our guest, Mizusawa Ally.
Mizusawa Ally
You've got a completely different image!
I think I've only seen you with blonde hair.
Oh yeah!
Don't change your hair just before filming!!
You didn't just change it for today?
No I didn't,
I just kinda felt like this recently.
The hair change has really thrown me off.
Ah, you thought of me as a blonde.
We've swapped haven't we!!
She's using Tameguchi, a more casual way of speaking, which can seem a little impolite when speaking to your senior.
You're speaking really casually right now!
Sorry, sorry.
Before the show started, the Gaki members went shopping.
The image I have in mind is a dress but...
Shibuya
...the others will probably go for something like that.
So I should go for something a bit different
maybe try a more casual place.
I'm not really sure what to look for
I wonder if this is too normal.
Man I hate this.
I think I've gotta find something more casual.
Well, Mizusawa Ally-chan, I think...
Omotesandō
...has a face which suits hats.
Her face is quite bright,
so I was thinking I don't want anything too flashy,
to have that kind of contrast.
I like the feel of this one.
It's quite a different image...
This kinda feeling...
...this would suit not only Mizusawa Ally, but anyone.
I want to find an item a young lady would love to wear.
Harajuku
Are these stockings?
Ah, I see.
These are nice.
Look at these flashy ones.
Pretty flashy right?
Should I go for these or...
Will this go with my other item?
What should I do?
Wait a minute... I've gotta think this through.
I'm looking for the hottest look, the most trendy.
Shibuya
Ah, this is perfect!
There's loads to pick from here!
What a selection!
This is great.
I'm looking for something...
...Omiya Ellie-chan wouldn't buy for herself.
Mizusawa Ally
Ah, Mizusawa Ally!
Mizusawa Ally-chan...
I have a feeling that this guest doesn't like wearing hats and stuff
Marunouchi
so maybe, an umbrella is the answer.
Isn't this pretty good?
I think this looks pretty good.
I'm gonna have a look around and come back to this if I don't find anything better.
In search of something to suit Mizusawa Ally, Matsumoto moves to another floor.
This... looks like something Naoto Inti Raymi would wear, right?
Naoto Inti Raymi (Nakamura Naoto) is a Japanese singer-songwriter and composer
The Naoto Inti Raymi collection.
How's this?
This isn't it right?
Nah, this isn't it.
But it's not far off.
I can't walk away from this.
I could definitely see her wearing this.
As usual, the guest will take home their favourite items.
The member with the worst item will have to pay out of pocket.
So, let's get going with our first items; a top for Mizusawa Ally.
I'm confident with this one.
I'm confident!!
That means nothing from you!!!
Even I admit... last time wasn't great.
It was like you were shopping for the Joker.
Definitely something for the Joker.
First to present his top to Mizusawa Ally is Endō.
Moussy
The colour is...
Ah, no Endō!
This is just wrong!
This is perfect for her.
Look at that smile, this'll suit her perfectly.
Price conversions are approximate for time of airing.
6,912 Yen (£40/$67)
It'll look nice with Ally-chan's figure.
It's so dull.
No it's not.
Look at the face she's pulling! There's no way she likes it.
Look, she's smiling.
Why did you buy it for her?
Would you like to hear my reasoning?
I'd like to hear.
I was thinking, you have quite a bright face
You don't want both your face and clothes to be flashy
because they'll end up taking away from each other.
Ah, a balance?
So by having a plainer top, it'll make your face shine brighter.
It's just boring!
There's just one thing...
When I was buying it, I was picturing you with blonde hair.
So truthfully it might not work as well with darker hair.
She'll look like an older sister when she's at home!
This is for wearing at home right?
Simplicity is sometimes nice.
That's true.
Next up is Hōsei, how will it go?
This is the first time I've seen this brand.
It's cute.
Cute?
Ally-chan, you'll probably hear this a lot but the moment I saw this, I knew it'd suit you perfectly.
22,680 Yen (£132/$221)
She's laughing like crazy!!
YAY!
What are you cheering for!?
Hmm, yeah, thank you!
Aww man that's bad!
I think it might be slightly better than Endō's.
It's better than that.
It's better than Endō's.
It feels more like something I might wear on TV.
This can be used for both your free time and work.
Man this is tough!
Timed, Typeset & Translated by Inepped
"I Think You'll Like this Item!"
Hamada is next to present his top to Mizusawa Ally.
I was going for a rougher casual style
that you can just throw on whenever.
This doesn't look quite right.
It's different from what we've seen so far.
12,960 Yen (£75/$126)
Nah this isn't it.
CUTE!!
She just let it out!
Cute! This is super cute.
I have no idea any more.
"That" is cute?!
This would go great with some jeans.
This is perfect for when it gets slightly chilly.
A cardigan is cute? It's so ordinary.
These black lines here are cute.
Are those needed?
That's what makes it unique.
This part here is super cute!!
You're joking!
Surely you don't need those lines.
Without these it would be ordinary...
...but with these lines it's super cute.
What?!
What if it had them on both arms?
Just the one is cute.
Next up is Matsumoto, what sort of top has he chosen?
With this one I went with...
...a cheaper option.
That's ok, I don't mind that.
If you think about it,
young ladies probably go for the style over the price.
When I was getting this there were loads of people in there.
It's cheaper, but still good quality.
Ah, this is a cheap place,
but it has cute stuff.
See, she said it has cute stuff.
See!
This is the one!
You can't go wrong with a dress.
5,990 Yen (£35/$58)
It looks a nice fit.
I think it would've looked nicer with my lighter hair.
Yeah, I was shopping with the image of you with light hair.
Were you going for a simpler look?
Yeah.
To begin with we're going for different themes...
We're not talking about your theme right now!!
I was just saying we were coming at it from differing angles.
I don't care about your theme!!
I was just thinking how lame your's looks!
APOLOGISE TO ZARA!!
Lame?
Last up is Tanaka. How will he fare?
Tanaka, I've got to say this...
...you've gotta stop messing around.
I'm not messing around at all.
This time you'll see how serious I am.
I'm confident in this.
Is that store well known?
It's quite well known.
It's a pretty small bag...
Wait, wait she's laughing!
8,575 Yen (£50/$84)
TANAKA!!
Wait, wait, wait...
It's a tank top!
It looks like a burnt up curtain!
What were you thinking?!
No, no... Ally-chan
has a flashy look, and having the sleeveless look...
Ah, maybe a sunbathing outfit.
Having the stomach exposed is a bit much.
Maybe if it wasn't it'd be ok.
It would be hard to match something with this.
Well, it'll be no surprise where this lands.
She's using Tameguchi again, using -kun instead of -san.
Maybe this would suit Tanaka-kun more!!
Well, I can't help if it suits me.
So, which of these will be Mizusawa Ally's favourite!?
Tanaka
Matsumoto
Hamada
Hōsei
Endō
Be honest.
Be honest, we're not looking for laughs.
To be honest, when they laugh, it really hurts.
Here we go.
Tanaka
Matsumoto
Hamada
Hōsei
Endō
In first is...
This one.
Well, she said it was cute.
This part here is super cute!
Don't you want to wear more bold and unique clothes?
When it comes to unique things...
smaller things are better.
Really!?
So, what's in second place?
This one.
As I thought...
Downtown are amazing.
When you think about it.
The Shōwa era: 25 Dec 1926 - 7 Jan 1989
Downtown made their debut in 1983
It must be the Shōwa era running through us.
I like the brightness of the colours on this one.
I see.
A nice and bright feel.
This.
And in third is Endō's dress.
So, which of these two tops will come in last!?
All that's left is Yama-chan and Tanaka.
That's enough with the joking around now.
Yeah, be honest.
Time to be honest and pick you're actual favourite.
Ok
So, please show us last place.
The worst please.
The worst...
Tanaka
Hōsei
Please
In last is...
This
Well, when you compare it to the others...
I could wear these on TV and they're quite pretty
but this one
just shows off everything.
Are you worried about that? Showing off the shoulders?
The shoulders and arms not so much
but around here is a bit too much.
Tanaka has to pay out 8,575 Yen (£50/$84)!!
Next up finding an accessory to suit our guest.
First to present is Hamada.
You might have quite a few of these
but maybe not in this colour.
Ehh, I wonder what it is?
It's quite small but it should pack a punch.
Ah, I think I know what it is.
30,132 Yen (£175/$294)
Sunglasses
No good
Why are these no good?!
You can put them up here, they're great for a summer look.
Nah, these are no good.
He's just picked out the first thing he saw!
No I didn't!
I saw some in black, but I thought she probably had loads in black already!
They don't suit her at all.
Stop it! Stop it!
They look weird, take them off!
They don't look weird!
Don't put them on again!
What's up with you guys, dunking on me like this!
Next up, Endō will present his accessory.
Orange coloured?
Orange? What is this?
Take this off.
There it is!
There it is, Endō's...
10,368 Yen (£60/$101)
Well, it's a hat...
This is the worst by far!
This'll definitely suit you.
It looks great!
Try it with the glasses on.
The hat ruins it.
I think this really suits you.
Just take it off for a sec.
Is it a straw hat?
Yeah it is.
What's this tag say?
UV Cut.
Oh right.
You hate UV right?
Hmm...
Girls hate it right?
I hate it.
Right, you hate it. This cuts it out.
I hate these two together!
Get back here!!
That's enough!
In last place with his top, how will Tanaka do with his accessory?
I'm much more confident with this one.
It's small.
I think you'll love this!
I wonder what it could be.
Take a look.
What is this?
A handkerchief?
They're tights!
Tights?!
YES!
This is... this is a perfect item for a young lady.
Tanaka, it's creepy.
Why?!
This is a great buy.
I don't think I'd ever pick out tights.
Really?!
What is that?!
It's a spring pattern.
It's a spring pattern, but also what surprised me is...
You have a dalmatian right?
Yes I do.
If you look closely, there are hidden dalmatians!
Who cares?
Look, look!
3,240 Yen (£19/$32)
Who cares if there's animals on it!
No, wait...
Among the spring colours are...
Ah, I see them!
There's a bunch of dogs' faces!
This is just gross!
What?! Why?!
Tanaka, change your manager!
He's definitely steering you wrong.
How many teams have you gone through?
It's still the same one.
Change it already!
Yoshimoto doesn't need a team of weirdos!
Hang on, seriously?
Should I try them on?
These actually might end up weirdly suiting you.
These are anything but sexy.
This is bad!
Really?!
Why? Why? Why?
These are super cute!
Seriously, don't listen to these guys.
It looks really odd with your current clothing
but what sort of clothes could you wear with these?
I'd like to hear your ideas.
Your usual clothes would work.
That sort of flashy...
Stop it with the "flashy" stuff.
Trousers are the only thing you can wear these with!
Long trousers.
These are useless.
No, no we want to see them.
You've seriously got to start trying!
I'm giving it my all!
Fourth to show off his accessory is Hōsei.
This is...
12,420 Yen (£72/$121)
This is just awful!
This is even worse than Tanaka's!!
So, why did you pick this?
Who's the character on it?
Bartman
He's a small hero, Bartman.
So is this for using whenever?
Of course, it'll be great anytime.
This is just terrible.
It's not even spelt the way I thought!
I've lost all confidence!
I feel sorry for Yama-chan now.
Will Matsumoto's accessory suit Mizusawa Ally?
This item also wasn't too expensive.
Shoes?
Nice reaction.
Nope!
9,612 Yen (£56/$94)
Don't you think these are cute?
Nah!
These are quite nice.
Did you hear that?
She said "These are quite nice".
What do you think?
I can't picture her wearing those.
I wear quite a lot of heels so...
They're so nice, the whole studio is speechless.
That's not why they're quiet.
It'd be troublesome if they were all talking.
These are pretty cute.
They look great!
Hmm... They don't suit her.
Terrible.
Just terrible.
They're nice, maybe I'll get a pair.
So, which of these items will be Mizusawa Ally's favourite?
How is it Ally?
Have you decided the ranking yet?
I'm still a bit unsure.
How about first?
First is the one I'm unsure about.
You're not unsure about last place though, right?
Hmm...
I am a little unsure!
No way!
YES!!
How can she be unsure about 'that'!?
So, which of these items will be Mizusawa Ally's favourite!?
Alright, here we go.
Tanaka
Matsumoto
Hōsei
Endō
Hamada
In first is...
This!
As I thought...
It's obviously the Shōwa era running through me.
It's like being bombarded by loads of pitches.
Since I'm always wearing heels, I've been wanting something like this, so these are perfect.
I always see you in heels.
I see.
They're super nice.
So, in second place?
This
See!
This is... this is a surprise.
I actually really wanted something like this.
Out of all of those you chose 'this'?!
I quite like the American Pop kind of styling.
This
In third is Hamada's sunglasses.
Tanaka
Endō
All that's left is the Cocorico duo's items.
Can Tanaka avoid being last once again!?
Tanaka
Endō
So, the worst is...
In last place is...
This
Of course.
I thought that this one was quite cute but...
I hate ribbons!
Ribbons?!
You hate them?!
If this didn't have the ribbon attached, it would have been first.
Can you explain why Tanaka-san's was in last place?
Please tell me.
I've thought about what this could work with.
After thinking it through, these are just impossible to wear!
Really?!
Kagami mochi (mirror rice cake) is a traditional Japanese New Year decoration. Usually consisting of two round mochi (rice cakes) stacked and a daidai (Japanese bitter orange) with a leaf on top
Don't Kagami mochi end up looking like this?
Tanaka has to pay out for the second time, 3,240 Yen (£19/$32)!!
I'm not so sure about the cardigan and Yamasaki's bag.
The cardigan was nice!
It's cute!
As for the bag, I'm not so sure!
What? It's definitely cute, right?
It's cute.
You got it 'cos it's eye-catching right?
Yeah yeah.
Stop bluffing!
You don't know anything!
The slaps are getting louder, since it's skin on skin.
Referring to Hōsei's male patterned baldness.