First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai
"Let's improvise a lame ass Shinkigeki!!"
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
It's easy to misinterpret this title
We're not saying the Shinkigeki is lame
No of course
Without any meeting or anything,
Just adlibbing
This is a pretty difficult one
This is gonna be bad
Tonight's Episode
A Yoshimito Shinkigeki without scripts or rehearsals
How lame will it turn out?
This time, just like the Shinkigeki in Kansai, they'll perform on stage
Without any scripts, just pure improvising,
The purpose of this project is to see how lame this will turn out!
Despite how it seems, the Shinkigeki requires rehearsing properly
Yes yes indeed
Of course there's a proper script and everything
Tsukitei Hosei
They rehearse properly and then perform
Yes exactly
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
You're not allowed to use any of the gags they use on Shinkigeki
None of that?
They have to be your original ideas
Rurle
Gags that have been used in Shinkigeki are prohibited
Original...
And there's the tsukommi as well of course
Yes yes
Tsukommi: Like the retort to a dumb joke
We have to come up with the story too
NOTHING is decided Yes indeed
Should we do this?
Should we?
Who's the one that suggested this
Translated by: senor_wristband
Typeset by: Kedomas
Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!
This time it's not just us, we've invited a guest,
Come in!
Thank you, let's do this
Jimmy Onishi
(Slightly senior to DownTown)
You came huh?
Thank you
The idiot is here, the idiot
Please, don't call me an idiot
Look at this, just one side is sticking out
Such an idiot
C'mon Jimmy
It's supposed to be like this
Just this side?
Both sides should stick out, it's fashion
But both sides weren't sticking out
I'm very sorry!!
Let's get along please
Yes
If Jimmy-chan wasn't here, we would be scared actually
Cause he's used to this
He is
In all the Shinkigekis I've done,
I've only ever gotten a single line
Oh really?
Yes always,
Ah that makes sense
The rest is up to me
Oh that's great then
That's perfect
However!
We're gonna decide the roles right now
We could even have Jimmy-chan play the lead role
Oh really?
The owner role
Well let's take a look at the roles
Oh yes
What kind of roles are they?
There's the udon store owner, the owner's daughter,
You don't need to hold it
Why did you try to hold it now?
I was trying to help
Such an idiot, such an idiot, right?
The hippie son that comes back after a long time
The roles:
setting: Udon Store
Udon store owner
Owner's daughter
Hippie son that returns all of a sudden
Gangster
A rich kid in love with the daughter
The master of the cafe across the street
The setting is the Udon store common in Shinkigekis
What do you think text text
The lead role is the Udon store owner right?
Yeah I guess so
It does seem that way
He can retort too
The decide roles by lottery
And then the important role lottery
This is how it turns out huh?
It's Hamada-san
Wow!
Matsumoto
Returning hippie son
Jimmy
Gangster
Endo
Owner's daughter
Hamada
Ownwer
Hosei
Rich boy in love with the daughter
Tanaka
Master of the cafe
But if Hamada-san is the lead role,
Yes, you're right...
He seems the best for it
Jimmy-chan, do you wanna try the owner role?
No, no way I can't do the owner, no way
I do wanna see that though
You've come as our guest after all
No way...
You're definitely into this sort of thing
I'm not!
I just think I shouldn't do it
Yeah, yeah that's fine, it's no big deal
You can take this role
I see
With that, the important lead role of the Udon store owner goes to Jimmy Onishi
Owner
Jimmy Onishi
Daughter
Endo Shozo
The owner's daughter, Endo
Rich boy in love with the daughter
Tsukitei Hosei
I definitely need to do some gags
There's gotta be gags about a  rich kid
Master of the cafe across
Tanaka Naoki
Master huh...
Gangster
Hamada Masatoshi
Having Jimmy-chan do the lead role is better,
He's gonna be talking complete nonsense
I could just say "GIMME ME MONEY!"
Hippie son that came back
Matsumoto Hitoshi
And Matsumoto plays the hippie son that came back home
Anxiety is all I feel!
Of course!
You can't blame me for this OK?
Scriptless Rehearsalless  Shinkigeki!
Finally Begins!
Sure was busy today
We had like, 800 customers today after all
It was hard serving 800 customers in this small place
Well today, anytime now,
It's time for the lunch break soon
I'm gonna drink a lot of tea
I'm back!
Ah, Yoshiko!
Yoshiko? That's not it!
My name is Shoko!
Ah, Shoko
Why did you get it wrong?
Shoko you picked up the delivery?
Yeah, just over there
I just brought these back. How were the customers today?
Today, we had 800 customers
That many?!
That's amazing!
Cause, father you said this shop might be demolished soon
I'm the 8th generation owner after all
You're the 8th generation?
Yes, so, um,
So let's try to preserve this store
But 800 people? How did they even enter?
They were lining up Ma'am
Ma'am?
They were lining up
I'm your daughter!
Cause they were lined up
Eh no way
That's the first time people have lined up for this place
It must've spread through word of mouth
Wow how did you manage that?
ESS EMM ESS EH
ESS EMM ESS EH...?
ESSE-
SNS you mean?
Yes yes using that
SNS = Social Media
That's the era we live in now I guess
Yeah
But like yesterday there weren't any customers at all
Will we really be alright?
We'll be fine
Really?
But wow, 800-
Welcome
Oh?
Master?
Master!
It's Master!
Welcome
Standing By
Someone correct him!
Say something like "You're not supposed to say welcome" !
I came to eat lunch
Ah, you're hungry?
Yes yes
What do you want to eat?
I think I'll have a curry udon
Hold the curry
A curry udon then?
...
Standing by
Respond to him!
Respond to his joke!
Hold the curry alright? Hold the curry
That's just normal Udon!
Oh right of course
Then I'll have a Kake Udon
Kake Udon?
I'll have a Kake Udon
Alright I'll go make it
I'll leave it to you!
OK
So, how're things?
We're doing sort of alright
Oh?
What about your shop Master?
We had a lot of customers today
Maybe they came to my store after yours?
The customers
Ahh
They might've come to my place after yours maybe
Umm
I think today, the flower watchers,
I think a lot of them came
Umm
Eh
Master you've been doing this for a long time right?
Yes
Yes, our store has been running for a long time
Right?
Yes
Ah
Yeah
Master, are you, what do you call it,
Your employee quit?
Yes, yes they really quit
It's the recession after all
Yeah I really thought "Damn this is a recession"
Standby
It's such a normal conversation
Make jokes!
Sorry for the wait!
Oh it's here
Making Udon was too annoying, is just tea alright?
Dig in, please dig in
You can at least make some Udon!
It was just too annoying
Annoying?! This is an Udon store!
I'm sorry
Dad, you help out too
Make some Udon at least!
Welcome back!
Rich boy!
Oh, master is here too
Standby
I started to crave Udon
Udon please! Burdock tempura
How much is it?
Eh?
Father, how much
Father, how much?
Sorry, but this is an Udon restaurant
Burdock Tempura Udon please. How much is it?
450 yen
Oh really
Yes
I thought it would be 4,500,000 yen!
Of course that's impossible!
It's 450 yen
I thought I wouldn't be able to pay 4500000 yen!
All you do is make jokes!
Can I pay with my card?
Standby
Enough already!
Just for today, you can pay by card
Oh really?
Yes
Alright, then with this please!
You can't pay with a T-Point card!
Ho-Hosei-kun, by the way, were you our kid?
Are you sure, Father?
Eh?
Thank you very much, I've been waiting for you to say that
Please, give me Shoko-san!
I really love her
Shoko-san, please, give her to me, please!
Please, it's too early for you two to be doing that
Standby
Retort! Strongly!
What the hell
Chaos as Hamada appears!
What is it?
When are you gonna pay your loan back?!
I apologize, Father
Father...
It was too soon for that right?
You still haven't gone to elementary school
I don't want that! It's my life!
Please
Shoko-chan,
Do you like Hosei-kun?
No way no way!
There's someone I've already decided on
Father...
Please give me Shoko-chan!
Cut it out!
You've always been like this. Ever since we were classmates!
And you're still my classmate aren't you!?
I dated Shoko-chan!
It's obvious for us to get married!
Do you know why Shoko-san broke up with you?
I don't know
Father, do you know why?
That's,
She was dating you?
She was dating you and broke up with you you mean?
Standby
Do something!
You, you dated her?
No
In fact,
Tanaka Master,
Is Shoko-chan's...
Long lost brother!
How do you...
Everyone knows it
I didn't know that!
Which means...
Umm, umm
Mom's, you're a different mother's child?
What are you saying father?
You're mistaken Father!
Get it together Father
Is that true?
Hurry, just come!
Marry me!
No! No! no!
No! no!
Marry me! Hold on!
Hold on
Shoko-san...
Standby
Eh?
OIIIIIIWWAAYEAAH
Oi!
What, what?
When the hell are you gonna pay your loan asshole!
Stop it please!
Oi!
Eh?
When are you gonna pay your loan?
I didn't take any loan though!
What the hell do you mean no loan?!
But I really didn't
Are you gonna pay me back asshole?
Umm, uhh,
I pay you every month don't I? 100,000 yen
100,000 isn't enough you've past the deadline!
Huh?!
Hurry up and pay me
But you're known for having high interest
Yes yes
Huh?
You're known for high interest-
You're the one who came to borrow money
Are you gonna pay me back? Huh asshole?!
No no I'm sorry!
STOP IT PLEASE
Who the hell are you?
How much is it?
Who the hell are you?!
I am the rich boy from over there!
Where the hell is over there?
Please stop this violence
Please stop the violence!
Are you gonna pay up then?
How much is it, please tell me
Ten million!
Let's pay ten million!
With this card
Like I said you can't pay with a T Point card!
Oi! Are you taking the piss?
Oi!
I'm sorry
Who's gonna pay?! If you're not gonna pay, you're the daughter right?
I'm gonna take you as payment
Please not my daughter!
Damn!
Finally Matsumoto makes his entrance
It's been so long!
Damn!
I wonder if mom and dad are doing alright
Hurry up and enter already
Oi you!
No!
Hold on!
Dad!
Hitoshi!
2 Kitsune Udon please!
No no-
This is not the time for this! Are you the son?
Are you their son?
Who are you? What are you doing here?
I'm here to get my money back from this guy
Your dad is in debt, are you gonna pay it?
Loan? What loan? I didn't hear anything about this
This store,
Yeah?
Is in the wed!
What?
It's in the wed!
What? What?
People stopped coming in-
In the what?
In the red!
Hold on, didn't he return after a long time?
Yeah a long time!
It's been a long time
Then say something about that!
It's-
Hitoshi
Dad
You've come back after 30 years,
Surely 30 years is too long...
That's really weird
You've come back after 3 years,
Yes
Since then
Yeah?
The store is in shambles
So I got into debt
Why did you go into debt?
Buying fridges and stuff
Fridges?
I'm sorry, I renovated the kitchen
You renovated the kitchen?
It's expensive
That does sound expensive
Cause your renovated the kitchen after all
I heard you were doing pretty good, that's why I came
No, that's all lies
In reality, no customers come
So,
I wanted to do something real,
I wanted to renovate the kitchen too
I wanted a new fridge too
That's just your selfishness
If you can't pay I'm taking your daughter
Hold on that's not happening
I can't allow that
Brother!
Yeah?
I'm asking you who's gonna pay for this?
Master, I think he can manage to take care of this
I don't care who as long as I get paid
If you're gonna do it, then hurry and pay up
How much?
Weren't you listening?
How much is the debt?
It's ten million!
Ten million?!
I can't pay ten million yen that's too much
Of course ten million is impossible!
Alright I got it, you come with me
No, not my-
No!
Who the goddamn hell are you?
I'm from that famous place over there
Please...
Please give more details What the hell?
Couldn't you please wait?
I've already waited a long time!
We will do our best to make it up!
Could you wait 8 years?
8 years...
8 years! Just wait 8 years please!
If I wait 8 years, you're gonna be able to pay me?
Yes!
Alright then
Yay!
Thank goodness!
This was awful. This was awful.
Yay it all worked out!
Thank goodness
This is awful!
This is awful!!
Let's watch it
This...
It was crap right?
This was crap right?
This guy pisses me off...
Time to watch the improvised play!!
Look at Matsumoto dragging his feet
Time to reflect on the improvised Shinkigeki
Ahhhh
Today was so busy...
What is this end of the day vibe you're giving out
Customers don't come to this shop at all normally
Exactly
And all of a sudden there were 800
Then the loan shouldn't really be a problem
Yeah
800 people all of a sudden...
Welcome
Oh?
This made no sense
Retort!
I thought they would retort
I tried to set it up for him
Yeah
You're supposed to retort!
I thought he would
Like "It's not your shop!"
How are things?
We are doing slightly well
This is where the hellish time starts
Just a normal conversation
Master, it's been a long time right?
This was terrible
Yes...
Yes our shop has been open a long time
Yeah
Master, what do you call it,
Did you give up on that new employee?
I did, I gave up
What kind of conversation is this
It's the recession after all
Yeah I really thought, damn this is a recession
Nothing to say...
You can't come up with anything
Nothing, just nothing
Just a cliche calm conversation
So cliche
Welcome back!
Nobody said anything
No response
Rich boy!
Everyone ignored your very first line!
Hosei-kun,
By the way,
Hosei-kun?
Were you our kid?
"By the way"
What a turn of events
Are you sure, father?
This turn of events...
Thank you very much, I've been waiting for those words
Please give me Shoko-san!
Oh, right
I really love her!
Please give me Shoko-san!
I guess groping was the next move
Please!
Right here it is, the father
Please, it's too early for you to be doing that
So gentle
Such a gentle lecturing
He won't play along with the joke
Do you know why Shoko-san broke up with you?
I don't!
Father, do you know why?
That's...
You dated her?
You dated her right?
You dated her and then broke up, right?
What is with this guy
Seriously
This guy...
This guy pisses me off
Matsumoto and I were stomping our feet
The hippie is here
It's been so long!
I wonder if mom and dad are doing alright
Oi!
No!
Wait!
Dad!
Hitoshi!
2 Kitsune Udon please!
Uwah...
Uwah....
Master,
He can manage to pay it
I don't care as long as they pay
You passed it to me here
Hurry and pay up
How much is it?
Were you not listening?
He did say it
Yes
How much is the debt?
Ten million!
Ten million?!
I can't pay ten million!
Such a normal response
I'm sorry
Could you just wait 8 years?
If I wait 8 years, you're gonna pay up?
Yes
Alright then
Oh no
That's not good
We did it!
Thank goodness!
We did pretty well didn't we?
Oh really?
The ending was kinda funny. He's gonna wait after all..
Strange...
It turned into something strange
What did you think of it Jimmy-chan?
I thought it was a good play
Which part?
Your standards are too lenient!
Translated by: senor_wristband
Typeset by: Kedomas