Translation, subtitles & encoding by Shion [@FGRNDNoises]
More clips? Subscribe to this channel: Shion[ガキの使い用]!
For other gaki clips visit www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Gaki no Tsukai's dressing room
I have a bad feeling about this
You do?
Yeah, like...
Like, you just feel it? A premonition?
Yamazaki Hosei
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Yeah, just a feeling
I see, I see...
Endo Shozo
Cocorico
Tanaka Naoki
As if someones's about to come here
Yeah that...   I guess there's no doubt it's going to happen
Fujiwara Kazuhiro
License
Inomoto Takafumi
You can easily guess it by looking at us right now
Exactly, I can tell!
I feel like Gaki's gradually becoming easy to foresee!
It is!
'Morning  See? He came
Downtown Manager
Oda Naoya
Just as we thought
We already felt like someone was about to come here
Right
So we kinda expected you to come
Uhm... This is a gain from our Matsumoto, you know, for everyone
"Our Matsumoto"
He kind of is
"Everyone"?
Do I have to read it?
Yeah
"The sexual performances of you scumbags can't even amount to 30"
"Such comedians with such a tiny weiner"
"Can't even imagine to take a woman to ecstasy,
* Matsumoto wrote the final section in a archaic-sounding fashion,
What the hell?
It came out, that style
"So I, the sex emperor, a true technician..."
* Pun between "sei-naru" [聖なる,"holy"] and "sei-naru"[性なる,"sex","sexual"]
"Shall make clear once more who's the best-willy-billy between you"
"Come forth towards the places signeth on the map"
* Again, messed up archaic forms. Also, there's Matsumoto Hitoshi's sign at the end of the letter
There's a map drawn in here
What the hell is this?
Let's see...
It's right after the "shop Nishida Hikaru goes often"
* On the map, from bottom to top: "shop Mizutani Yutaka
goes often to", "shop Nishida Hikaru goes often to", "here".
Nishida Hikaru is a J-pop singer and actress, Mizutani Yutaka is an actor.
Where is it?!
As if someone could know all of this!
How can we tell its distance?
Does anyone know those places?
I'm not searching for this
It's impossible for us today
Yeah but
Our Matsudok... he's waiting for you guys
Eh?!
He just stuttered!
You straight up stuttered! " Our Matsuko", what was that?
Bra hooks unhook challenge
So fast!!
Here's the technician challenge! Matsumoto already had 4 of those previously
Nipple fondling match
Its aim is to question the authenticity of one's manliness as a man
Panties removal championship
And so, several furious and incandescent challenges were unleashed!
Speed Kiss Match
What will we see on today's challenge?
Enough...
We're doing this here!?
Just down there
Yeah, after all
Hey!
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
He was waiting for us
He's there
'Mornin-
You could tell it was me?
We got that immediately
We were brought here
What is that?
What?
Me?
It was you who called us here!
You just call us here and now you'r-
Anyways!
Yessir
The reason why I summoned you here is
Mhh...
You know, right here we also have guys who divorced...
Right?
I mean, those who can't even satisfy their own wife
He keeps on telling us the same thing every time
Just what have you been doing?!
You know, that guy over there, the last one
Fujiwara
Come on,
You've been cheating your girlfriend for quite a while now
God, you're just hopeless
He did it again?
"Again"?
E? " Again?!
It's a thing from the past
If there was an "again" to this story, I think
that's something I'm discovering only right now
Why does Matsumoto-san know all of this?
Whatever you're just...
In short..!
Yeah?
I've been thinking that maybe you guys don't
know anything about how to use your hips
I thought that by moving them at high speed...
You can manage to satisfy a woman someway or another
Yeah...
Well even if I said so...
You are not allowed to put a swimsuit produced
by the Speedo company around your d*ck
* As you may know, Speedo is a famous trademark for professional swimmers' swimsuits
I don't get it...
Don't worry, just ignore what he says - Ok
I think that's what he means
What?
Me?
Enough with this bullshit already!
The hell is that supposed to mean!
Excuse me, can you be clearer if you please
If you please
Anyway!
That's how I came up with this system for today
We don't really car-
Let the curtains down!
Woah! Amazing!
In short..!
Uh...
That's what we'll use to make your hips move!
Ascension! Hip-shaking Match!!
Rules
Equip the belt of the machine and send out air by shaking your hips
Compete by promptly send the inside pipe higher
In a set amount of time until it reaches the doll on the top
The point is to shake your hips with all your love!
The one getting the right speed and pouring his soul on his hips will win the challenge!
Just listen carefully, everybody
When you move your hips back and forth
Please do not do it by laying your hands over here
Oh,I see. Yeah, yeah.
Because if you do so
The audience ratings will drop
No good
I see... - We have to be careful then
So you can just use this to avoid placing your hands over here
Rules
The match will be done while holding maracas
So that's why those were there
Yeah, but even if we hadn't these we would have find a way to have them anyways
Guess you're right
Wouldn't it be better if we quit this?
Of course a harsh batsu-game has been
prepared for the one who'll lose this match
If you lose, you'll face a batsu-game!
Enough with these batsu-games...
Can we practice with this thing first?
No training allowed!
Eeeeh?! - So we have one shot...
Aren't we having a test round?
By the way we had out AD manager, that... uhh... who was him again?
Is it #@"%$/&=-san?
* I don't know what's the censoring beep for
Who's @"$!#¨&]?
[censor beeps festival]
Tetsuo
He's our Johnny Depp
Or maybe our Jack Bauer
It took him around... 30 to 40 seconds to clear it
Eh!? It takes THAT long?
I said "Jack Bauer" but I meant to say "Jack Sparrow"
Come on, hurry up and take turns
Come on Endo, you go first
Should I go first?
Yeah...
You guys should look carefully at the first one...
So we could learn from him?
This thing of me being first one is getting old
Our first challenger is our usual Endo
What will his true strength be!?
Ok, so, just take a look on what  this all is about
Right, right
Starter
Producer Nakamura
Are you ok Endo?
I'm good
All right, then Endo, give it a try!
Endo's challenge
Ready...
Ehh?! - What?!
That's bullshit! - Not going that well
No progress so far
Wait, what the hell?!
Nothing's happening
Stronger, stronger! - Wait a minute!
Ah! - It's rising!
That's absolutely AMAZING!
Woah!
So how was I?
How was-- eh?!
You know it kind of... it stored up heat up to a certain degree
What do you mean?
Yes? - Oh, and it went up all at once
Yeah, it went up all at once just now
Is that what happened?
I see, I see
I think it changes from person to person
Oh, I got it!
So, how did the first one score went?
Let's find it out
Here!
Woah! - WOW!!
Pretty fast, huh! - Yeah, he was fast - I think that too
ENDO'S RECORD
SEC.
Our staff's record was around 40 seconds - Yeah, he's right
So you have to do it lots of times to get it higher - That's the point
But really, with 23 seconds...
We're all about to fall miserably, right?
Tha`s because we had Endo going first, he made a nice show
* The first one going to have a challenge is called "top batter". "catcher mitt" is a joke on this saying.
So next up we'll have our catcher mitt going next
Wait wh-- Oh, it's Hamada-san
Am I doing this?
Hamada, a sadistic man
Will he show us a proper hip-shaking?
Is everything alright?
Yeah...
Ok, with that being said, it's Hamada's turn!
Ready...
Let's go!
Hamada's challenge
Ready...
See? - Look at him!
See? It got up! - It is!
It's falling! - Watch out!
It's friggin' exhausting
Hamada is exhausted!
Oh! Here it goes!
I think I'm dying!
Do you want to get your batsu-game, Hamada-san?
That's no good! No good at all!
This is really exhausting!
Okay, it got to the top!
I think he was pretty fast
Eh? Wasn't that long? - I don't really think so
So, for how much did he...?
It's hella tiring
BEST RECORD
ENDO
23 sec.
For now I think we're actually doing well
Yeah but it's risky - He took a risk
Here's his timing!
Wow, 30 seconds! - So it took me 30 seconds, uh
HAMADA'S RECORD
SEC.
Just 30 seconds...
I think it differs from our difference experiences
Yeah - I think he's right
I mean, like the way you look at this
After 30 times it starter to get higher faster
Oh, I've scored better than him!
Yeah
I couldn't understand why, I was shaking my hips all the time
Yeah, you just don't know why (it doesn't go higher)
Yeah, no idea
Inomoto, the youngest of the group
Are his hips ready for this challenge?
Don't we just have before our eyes the fastest hips-shaker?
Ok, Inomoto!
Yes!
Give it a shot!
Inomoto's challenge
Ready...
Woah! - He's fast!
It gets hard from this point on
Oh, it's going down
This segment is the worst, you just have to overcome it
Yeah
He's right
You just have to go through this
You're failing us, Inomoto!
Maybe it's better if you move faster
That way you pump much more air
Woah, back to the start!
Not a single inch!
It's not getting higher at all!
This might be impossible giving how much he's moving...
Oh, he's going!
Oh, here it is! Go go go go go!
Almost there!
He endured pretty well I must say, that alone deserves praise
That was harsh!!
Another important thing is the space of each movement
BEST RECORDS
ENDO
23 sec.
HAMADA
41 sec.
I think this could make one's self confidence disappear
My body lower half is aching
Yeah but to be honest I think the timing was pretty bad for this one
Are you serious?!
I think he did pretty well, actually
Here's his record!
Woah! - Long! - No bad, not bad... - That's 'cause it moved only by the end
INOMOTO'S RECORD
sec.
If things stays as they are Inomoto will face the batsu game!
Oh yeah! - Oh shit!
Yessir!
Okay so, Fujiwara, your turn
Show us what you can do
Here comes our Fujiwara
Here I come!
Our incredibly idiot Fujiwara
There!
Fujiwara, the idiot
Will Fujiwara's hips movements will be worthy of attention
Which type of hip-shaking will he show us?
Even though he's facing this challenge with pants, for some reason?
Uhm, guys a minute, what I wanted to say is that the thing that's bugging me...
Yes?
Is the fact that I find disturbing how almost no one's shaking the maracas at all
Ah... - Well, he's right
If you don't shake your maracas more, you won't make your woman satisfied at all
I understand
Wouldn't she be just bad about it?
Ok, Fujiwara...
Come on!
It's your turn!
Fujiwara's challenge
Ready...
Go buddy!
Go!
Yeah yeah, like this!
That's the right speed!
That's it!
That's the right way!
He nailed it
He got this
It gets hard from now on!
He's not shaking them (the maracas) at all
Just a bit more! Come on!
Come on, almost there!
He was fast!
What was that?! You were amazing!
That was flawless
Incredible
You were moving so lightly!
That's the right spot, just right there
Oh I see
There's no need to go that behind
Oh I see! - So that's it
Just doing this, really
So you made short movements
Precisely
Now I see...
He managed to complete it with it
BEST RECORDS
ENDO
HAMADA
INOMOTO
23 sec.
30 sec.
41 sec.
I think he may surpassed Endo in terms of speed?
I think so - He was fast!
This is a new record - Yeah - I'm sure of it - Right?
Here's his record! - Yes
Oh yeah!
That's incredible!
FUJIWARA'S RECORD
sec.
Alright!
Woah Inomoto, you're in danger aren't you?
BEST RECORDS
FUJIWARA
ENDO
HAMADA
INOMOTO
16 sec.
23 sec.
30 sec.
41 sec.
Yeah that's bad
Cross your finger dude - INOMOcchan, you're in danger
Ok, so...
Our lil' champion Yama-chan
Yeah!
Oh! - Are you going?
Alright, alright
I got this
Yamazaki seems to have grasped something
But how will his outcome be!?
You have like a timing you're aiming for or something like that?
Yeah actually for this
I just saw how Fukiwara was doing...
Yes?
I think I can go around 10 seconds too
For real? - Yeah
That's impossible, no doubt about it
Okay Yamazaki, are you ready?
Ready
Then let's go!
Yamazaki's challenge
Ready...
Why did it immediately lift?
It didn't before
He's fast
It stopped!
It has stopped
He's not shaking his hips at all!
Not a single movement!
That's why it stopped
Come on, shake them! - Thrust them more!
You have to pile up more heat!
You're about to lose!
Don't give up! - It went all the way down!
Put your hands up! Shake the maracas!
Didn't help at all!
What?!
He was doing so well
Yama-chan!
Get it higher! - That's impossible
Yama-chan, higher, higher!
The maracas! - Maracas!
This is bad
Yama-chan! Come on!
It's all in the maracas! Shake them properly
Yama-chan!
Maracas!
It's falling down, it's falling down
He made it!!
That was bad
It took him way too much time
There's no way this is going to be good
That was miserable
I'm safe, right?
I think there's the possibility he went over a minute
It felt like a difficult delivery
Why did it stop?
Well it's that - It wasn't enough
You took away too many breaks
That's where it fell down all at once
Why
His face became really something terrific
* "Kaigen" is a brand of medicines against cold
It became just like the old guy drawn on "Kaigen!
Yeah he was frightening
His face was really scary
Here's his record!
WOOOAAAAHHH !  !  !
That's the worst score! - This is bad...
YAMAZAKI'S RECORD
sec.
min
I may do it...
That's just...
You've done it Zaki-san
BEST RECORDS
FUJIWARA
ENDO
HAMADA
INOMOTO
YAMAZAKI
16 sec.
23 sec.
30 sec.
41 sec.
3sec.
1min.
Well, to be honest
You know, Tanaka is... about this game, he's like...
He's holding a record
Yes, I scored 3 losses in 4 matches in total
By the way, huh...
We had Tanaka's manager check the location of the batsu game
Ahead of time?
Before even attempting
Tanaka, the man who lost 3 of 4 matches
Will he be able to redeem himself!?
come on Tanaka, I'm counting on you! Please lose!
I'm sorry, not this time Zaki-san
Come on, I don't want to be the last
Also I've already said this countless times
The fact you all are not shaking the maracas...
Got it
Is extremely unpleasant
Actually if you start shaking them
You'll lose like, 20 seconds
What the hell?
Tanaka-san! Give it a try!
Tanaka's challenge
Ready...
His shaking the maracas!
What? That-- - That's not going so well, isn't it?
What is he doing?
This is awful
Shake your hips more! Your hips!
Come on!
This is bad... - Just like Yamazaki
But look, it's getting higher!
He's not shaking the maracas at all!
He's doing it even with his head!
Shake those hips!
His head might fall off
Well, at least he can shake the maracas properly
Back from the start again
Shake them more!
Maracas! More!
Tanaka!
Tanaka!!
Tanaka, man, for real...
It's back
Tanaka!!!
Tanaka!
Tanaka-san!
Oh, here it comes! It's going, it's going!
Shake the marac-
He surely shook the maracas
You made it
Dude
In the end the air piled up and it wen all the way up at on
It skyrocketed
How was it?
Was it hard?
You were too delicate
Is my score worse than Yamazaki's?
BEST RECORDS
FUJIWARA
ENDO
HAMADA
INOMOTO
YAMAZAKI
16 sec.
23 sec.
30 sec.
41 sec.
1min.
3sec.
It'll be a great match
This one really is an epic fight, isn't it?
For real
His way of shaking his hips was really horrible at the beginning, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was awful
Skon sko-kon sko-kon sko-kon sko-kon
All the others went like PAM PAM PAM PAM PAM
Yeah but I shook the maracas a lot, right?
You were like a chihuahua, a chihuahua I say
WE'LL SEE TANAKA'S RECORD LATER!
Before getting to see Tanaka's score, who's facing the risk of getting the batsu-game...
IT'S THE TURN OF OURS STAR MATSUMOTO!
Our star Matsumoto will finally join the challenge!
Matsumoto, the sex emperor
Let's take a look at his true power!
I'll warn you, it takes a lot of time
Yeah but really...
Don't worry about it, the meal I had before was balanced enough for this
You had a meal before this?
I had my dose of unmilled rice today
'cause I'm having unmilled rice for this whole week
The whole week?!
Matsumoto-san...
If you please
Let's go!
Matsumoto's challenge
Ready...
* We just saw this before, therefore no subs
Oh!
The maracas, Matsumoto-san
You're not shaking them at all!!
The maracas, you're not s-
He got stuck!
Not moving!
His shoes slipped away! The shoes slipped away!
It's not helping at all!
This is bad, bad, bad!
This is bad, it's going so bad!
The maracas! The maracas! The maracas!
The maracas!
You're not shaking them at all!
He's in real danger!
This is not going to turn out good!
Something's wrong, something's wrong
This is wrong, so wrong!
I'm telling you that's not how it is!
This is wrong!!
This is bad!
That's impossible
Hey!!
I'm telling you, something's wrong
Something's wrong
Come on let's go
What the hell, it's not moving!
Not a single inch
Matsumoto-san!
It stored up energy!
Look, his making a face just like Kaigen's!
He's the real Kaigen!
He became Kaigen
Almost there!
You're almost done
This is wrong, something's wrong
I think by now it's one of you three guys
That was deluding
THAT'S NOT HOW THINGS WERE SUPPOSED TO GO!
GIMME A BREAK!
This is so wrong
What is "wrong"?
The shoes, my shoes!
Well the shoes were
They slipped away because of my socks and I couldn't move back and forth at all!
That's a bit...
I did it without my shoes too, you know
He's right
Yeah, he's right
Fujiwara too wasn't wearing them
I'm dead tired
I think it's about time we...
With this I think now it's all about the three of you
Yeah you three guys! (Yamazaki, Tanaka & Matsumoo)
That's a really difficult situation
WHO`LL FACE THE BATSU GAME!
Surprisingly Matsumoto too is now part of a may-get-the-batsu-game triangle
What will the record of the remaining two members be?
YAMAZAKI'S RECORD
min.
sec.
From who should we start?
(Staff) - From Matsumoto-san
Ok, got it
From Matsumoto-san?
Yeah, let's take a look...
Matsumoto-san's score is...  - Come on, this is so irritating
This!
HELL YEAH!!
MATSUMOTO'S RECORD
min
sec.
I did it!
With a 2 seconds difference! - Still, it took you one minute...
That was risky!
You barely made it
The risk wa--
I barely friggin' made it!
You always end up in this position - Yeah that's right
BEST RECORDS
FUJIWARA
ENDO
HAMADA
INOMOTO
MATSUMOTO
YAMAZAKI
16 sec.
23 sec.
30 sec.
41 sec.
1min
1sec.
It's always like that, what the hell!
This may be his special ability
Must be it
That's not a talent at all
Even if you say so... - So,
Finally we'll get to see Tanaka Naoki
So...
Alright, how about we hide the seconds displaying section?
Should we hide it? - Oh, I see
I think it'll be fine even if we cover it up until  1 minute and 0 decimal seconds
Yeah that's it
Ok so, let's reveal Tanaka's score timing, please!
Is this part ok?
Should we see the last one first?
Oh, the last one?
But if we see the last one we'll get it immediately - He's right
Show the minutes first - It's surely 1minute, so...
Okay, 1 minute - Oh, there it is
So it was it
Let's check if it's 1 minute and 0-something seconds - Yeah, let's
We just saw the 1, let's move on
This will be fine, it's surely a 0
Here I go
It's a zero!
There it is!
If now comes a 2 you're good
How is this going to end?
Ok, let's see it!
Alright
One, two and...
Here!
TANAKA'S RECORD
min
sec.
Just one second!
And the batsu-game goes to...
Tanaka Naoki!
TANAKA GETS THE BATSU GAME!
BEST RECORDS
FUJIWARA
ENDO
HAMADA
INOMOTO
MATSUMOTO
YAMAZAKI
TANAKA
16 sec.
23 sec.
30 sec.
41 sec.
1sec.
3sec.
4sec.
1min
Just one second! - The hell, man! Only  1 second difference
So, what's the batsu-game for this challenge, Matsumoto-san?
Eehh, this time's batsu-game will be... - Yes?
The street corner hip-shaking punishment!
STREET CORNER HIP-SHAKING PUNISHMENT!!
I wonder what is it about?
It'll basically be like what we just did, but around public street corners
I see
You went to a lot of street corners, didn't you?
Yeah...
We'll have you dance in those
That's a pretty harsh punishment...
I see but... - Mmh?
Can we please stop this series? Please?
Is it okay to cancel it?
AFTER THIS...
TANAKA WILL FACE HIP-SHAKING STREET CORNER!
Yuurakuchou
Ehh...
Right now
THE MAN WHO FACED THE BATSU-GAME 4 TIMES
COCORICO TANAKA NAOKI
I'm here in Yuurakuchou
Uhh...
And this is my batsu-game
Why do I have to undergo this batsu-game, you ask...
I don't really know very well myself
But I can say for sure I'm full of feelings of shame for my wife
I'm going!
TANAKA'S BATSU GAME
HIP-SHAKING STREET CORNER
Hoshi furu machikado
by Toshii to rato happi & blue
Aoyama
Shibuya
Shinjuku
Roppongi
Around Tokyo Tower
Odaiba
May we have your autograph?
Sure
Can you hold onto this please?
Done
Thanks a lot - No problem
Good luck for this! - Good luck!
Thanks
I think this one
May be the most exhausting
Among all the batsu game I faced
Finish
After the stage recording
was over
The performers and staff went back to the waiting room
The staff and performers go back to the waiting
WHEN NO ONE WAS THERE THAT MAN CAME TO THE STAGE!?
However...
A single man came on the stage everyone has left...!
LIVE CAMERA FOOTAGE
Here follows the footage our live camera captured
THE ONE WHO CAME IS THE GENERAL DIRECTOR HEIPO