You've accepted your role as Mr. Meat!
Food Marathon #4
Yakiniku Toraji 25 Store Challenge
They choose one item from a menu of 25 at each store
There's a 100,000 yen prize waiting if they finish
If anyone gives up though, they have pay for all the food eaten thus fart
Starting in Ginza 8-chome, they've cleared 10 stores
Just 15 stores remain
Will they be able to finish this time?
The second part starts now!
Typset by GakiDave
Translation by senor_wristband
There's 15 stores left
Can you guys bring in a substitute?
A substitute?
You could ask "Garage Sale"
Garage Sale?
Garage, or NEGO6,
Garage Sale
NEGO6
What can NEGO6 do?
Someone like Hello Keisuke
Hello Keisuke
Why did you include Garage Sale with those guys?
Shall we decide the item for the next store?
Let's try the Specialty Salted Tongue
Let's cross that one off
Part 2 starts with the New Employee Store in Ikebukoru
They still aim to clear 25 stores
It's hella spacious.
Ikebukoru is hella spacious
Natural light is nice
Very nice
Have you decided on the specialty Salted Tongue?
It's the most popular dish here
This is number 1?
Your Salted Tongue is here
Toraji Specialty, Salted Tongue
Season with salt and cumin, an explosion of umami
Someone needs to eat the extra one
Let's do Rock Paper Scissors
Rock, Paper, Scissors ...
Ahh that was close
No, it's just you two
We all put out a rock
That makes no sense, that's dumb,
Then I win cause I have scissors
Now that makes no sense
Do it again
So it's Matsumoto-san then
This is the most popular one right?
The most popular indeed
Up until now, everyone has eaten 13 pieces
They still find it easy
Hamada-san, how is your stomach doing?
Well, for now, I'll stay with you
TN: Unclear about this line
Are you some lead actor who found a new love?!
"I'll stay with you for now"
Tongue is pretty small
Finished!
Let's move on
They get to rest on the drive there,
However, for one man this is not enough...
Digging in to that Reimen there ...
It was like I was a big league person
I was slurping them down, right?
And Endo's white rice, I think that was bold
Thanks.
"This kid's got moxxy"
"He just doesn't have any presence"
In response to Matsumoto's challenge,
One man rises to the occasion
Anyone ordering from the side menu?
I'll have the galbi gukbap.
Galbi gukbap!
Let's succeed here
Very nice
Pork Jowl and Galbi Gukbap please!
He's a Tough Guy
This is the Iberian pork jowl, seasoned with lemon and a side of wasabi
Iberian Pig  Pork Jowl
An exquisite combination of meat and fat
Who will eat the extra here?
I'll do it
If you can make it past this, you'll get a Lipotovan D advertisement deal
TN: Lipotovan D is an energy drink
For real?
His "Tough Guy" image is too strong
It's just too strong
The fatty pork jowl is a real burden to their stomachs
And then...
This is tough
Tough?
You said it very clearly
He did just say it
"This is tough"
No no no
I mean the wasabi, putting too much makes it a challenge to eat
I was just taken aback
Can we see the difficulty start to show?
However...
Here it is, Kalbi Gukbap
Kalbi Gukbap here
This looks amazing.
You'll get the lead role in "Ore No Sora"
You're kidding me!
A regular Yasuda Ippei
Yama-san, do you wanna help him out?
I don't
Mr. MeatLover then
I'll have a little then
Then I'll have some too then
Let's all finish this
I think I'll have some too
The second half has started it seem
Like "let's work together"
Is this much OK?
Yeah no need to hold back
The spiciness is perfect
What about you Zaki-san?
I'm good
When Tanaka put this in it broke my heart
Huge!
Such a massive piece
But still, the members eat with vigor
Finished!
However, a dark cloud looms over this challenge...
Actually, how are you guys feeling?
In terms of the broadcast
We need to figure out how to end this
Just the ending
Maybe one of us can pretend to collapse
But that might be a bother for Toraji,
I guess a sprain is our best option
As soon as you get off the car, go like "OW!"
It just depends if anyone will fall for this shitty acting
I think Endo can do it
You did say he doesn't have any presence in his works
Finally, he has a chance to shine
You never know what chance will come...
I might stand out this time
Putting aside the Food Marathon, Endo takes on a new challenge
The car reaches the 13th store in Shinjiku
How will Endo's acting turn out?
Alright!
Let's go,  Shinjiku
Ow ow ow ow ow!
Sprain, I sprained it
Why? All of a sudden
I used to... I used to play baseball
I think I twisted something from then
Seriously?
I think it's dislocated
C'mon Endo-kun, let's go.
Alright, we're going.
You're ready to eat?
Yeah I'm good.
Just like Endo's health, their appetite is just fine
This is what everyone's eaten so far,
Matsumoto's side dishes stand out
Just 10 stores left
The goal is in sight now
You know,
I wonder if we can allow some people to rest instead of eat
I see
But we need one person to volunteer to eat 3 pieces,
We need a "New Age" to dawn on us
Exactly, we need that to happen
Matsumoto-san, Dr. Meat, and I, we're all pretty old
That's true
We need the youth
The Fresh and Vigorous
We're in our 40s you know
There's no young people on Gaki
No young people on Gaki
Alright I got it, next time,
We'll decide, with cards
We'll flip the cards and see who gets to rest
Up until now, they've eaten together,
But now they begin the resting plan
Will this be a blessing? Or a burden?
Let's see
From now on, they will move mountains
These are the cards
This is an amazing game
Let's decide who rests first
Decide who doesn't eat
A battle of luck; Who will get to rest?
Alright, I got it
The answer...
Ready...set... flip!
Matsumoto-san doesn't have to eat!
I'm so glad!
Very lucky
What the hell
Next, they decide who must eat 3 pieces
Please go ahead
I really wanna avoid this one
This is definitely not good, I don't want to get it
Decide on who shall eat 3 pieces, please!
Ready, set... flip!
It's Endo-san!
Alright!
Well alright then, let's eat
For the 16th store, they decide on Harami (Skirt Steak)
With less fat, a light item
Very nice
It's light
Endo should be the one to find this difficult,
But then,
What is this, "Look how hard I'm working"
You barely ate!
He puts the last piece in his mouth
He did it
Finished!
Let's continue
Can I see the menu?
What should we do?
We have 3 more stores here?
Yes, in Ebisu
We have 3 in Ebisu
The largest hurdle, Ebisu
There are 3 stores within 10 minutes of each other
Falling behind here is unnacceptable
Let's do this!
They've cleared 16 stores thus far
The meat and grease tortures their stomachs
Seeing the word "Toraji" is starting to piss me off
Even these stairs are a pain
Even before they eat, the stairs take their toll on the members
Shall we do pork?
The short rib?
Yes, then we'll be done with pork dishes
Let's see what the cards decide then
The cards will decide who eats the short rib
I'm definitely not gonna lose!
The second card draw; There is a large penalty this time
And... flip!
Really?!
He got them in a row
After Matsumoto's double breaks, who will eat 3 pieces?
Here we go, Tanaka open
Alright, just 1 piece
Meat Lover, open
NO, PLEASE
The 17th item, pork short rib
A reasonable portion, and a very popular item
They're all the same
This one looks good
I've already decided on my 3 pieces
Look at him, eating like a Big Leaguer
Are you chewing tobacco?
OK!
He's definitely not gonna finish
Yamasaki has given up the most in the past
But unexpectedly, he finishes!
Finished!
He's crying
Can we go to the head store?
Let's go.
Alright, let's go!
8 hours since the start,
They are no doubt feeling very full
My steps are so heavy
There it is.
We're here.
This way
Next up, the 40th Toraji store in Japan, Toraji Head Store
Like their appetites, their stamina is at the limit
Since this is the head store, we gotta get the specialty short rib
Whoever gets the Skull must eat 2 pieces
That's hot man! Right above the stove
Your way of getting it was weird
If you get the skull you have to eat 2
Let's do it on go
Ready, set,
Alright, Thank god!
Specialty Short Rib
Thank you for waiting
King Of Yakiniku - Specialty Short Rib
Taste, and volume, fit for a king
The head store...
This is some good looking short rib
Yakiniku is just right for now
For now I like this
Here I go
The taste is of course fantastic, however the fattiness is really getting to them
I'm really, I'm really working hard here
We wanna see you doing that
Matsumoto shoves down the second piece
Finished!
Let's head to the next store
The last store in Ebisu
This time it's Seafood, to change things up
They decide on Squid
Tana-chi, give me a small piece
Me too, Tana-chi
A break from the greasy meat,
Their chopsticks keep moving
Squid will never let you down
I don't think squid has let anyone down
Hmm?
That piece is way smaller than mine
That's definitely smaller!
When I was cutting them,
you said you liked squid,
So of course,
I want to give more to those who like it
If you tell me some trivia about squid I'll forgive you
Octopus have legs, but Squid have arms
That's actually amazing,
Why didn't you tell me this amazing fact before
Where would it come up?
Finished!
Next store!
This is no good
No more, I can't
NO MORE!!!!
That counts as giving up
You totally just gave up
That scared me!
I don't want to end by the roadside like this
That's what ******* was also thinking
"I don't wanna end by the roadside"
Yakiniku Toraji Marathon - Just 6 stores left
A long battle
Their stamina has long passed the limit
If it was something else could you eat?
A different food?
I can't swallow anything
If it was a crepe?
If it was a crepe, maybe I could swallow it
After that, Yamasaki...
The 20th store
I'm actually in trouble here
What happened?
It seems he can't walk
That doesn't just happen all of a sudden
Yamasaki limps into the 20th store, in Aoyama
He's burping a ton
Really?
I think we should cross off the Specialty Skirt Steak
It's lean meat
Are we doing the 1 person eats 2 rule?
The 1 person rests rule is needed right now
They want to relieve their stomachs
One man really wishes it is him
Ready... flip!
Endo is safe!
Shozo you ate a lot before
This is the deciding point!
Ready, set, flip!
You're too loud!
He's crying!
Just a bit, for now
C'mon man
You're overreacting
Wait a minute!!! Really?!?!
Specialty Harami - Will they be able to make it past this?
What's with this greasy shine?
This greasy shine is the origin of Yakiniku
I've never seen such greasiness
That looks cooked doesn't it?
Give Yama-chan the 3 best ones
Please enjoy these
They aim to finish the challenge,
They ignore their suffering, and swallow their food
Just Hosei-san's 3 pieces left
Next store is Nishiazabu
Let's get there
He's slowly picking up his chopsticks...
He just can't raise them
Alright.
I give up!
He didn't eat a single bite
Giving up without eating
You can't lift your chopsticks?
I just can't, I was amazed,
Something that heavy is impossible
This means the challenge ends here!
28,340 yen, Hosei-san please pay that amount
Amazing, look the stars have come off
I only have 26,000 yen
If you eat this one piece,
No way, I don't wanna
Can I make it up later?