1st Time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arrahende
"I'm the One Who Understands you Best!"
"Anyways, You'd Look Great in this Thing" DAIGO Edition!!
The "DA" was so loud!
The "DA" of DAikkai.
And the "DA" of DAIGO.
Yeah the DAIGO "DA"  too.
Ok, but after the first one it was smooth.
You mean after "DA" of DAikkai.
It's been a while since we've done this.
It's been a year and a half.
The guest of last time is no longer with us, Pe-e.
That's not true.  She's alive and well.
I heard she fell in a river...
A special series on Gaki, where the members buy gifts for guests based on their interests!!
So, without further ado, let's bring out today's guest.
DAIGO
Are these your casual clothes?
They look similar to your stage clothes.
They're pretty similar.
So you wear this normally?
Yeah, but...
You even wear this stuff casually?
Pretty much.
Perfect.
What I've got is perfect.
This is totally ok.
It's ok?
I'm not sure about Hamada-san though.
Hamada-san seems less confident.
I went a completely different direction.
We might yet see a new DAIGO.
That's true...
...but only if I feel like it.
What sort of answer is that...
Timed, Typeset & Translated by Inepped
Before the show started, the Gaki members went shopping to find a top and an accessory for DAIGO.
Shibuya
If you're over 40 you've gotta shop in Shibuya.
I was thinking of getting something a bit oversized.
Staff
These look nothing like DAIGO-san's image...
It's not, but...
I'm going for something different. When you see him on TV it's all...
Black
Black, white and grey.
This feels like what youngster's would wear casually.
I bet his wife wants him to dress like that too.
I kind of want this too.
This is completely different from his usual image.
I really want to come in first.
Harajuku
I think I'll go quite aggressive this time.
This is super interesting, what is it?
It's a leather harness.
58,724 Yen (approx. £360/$410)
There's masks as well.
This store's pretty interesting.
Staff
It's transparent...
It's pretty interesting.
What do you think?
32,180 Yen (approx. £200/$225)
It's think it's alright.
What about these sunglasses?
28,484 Yen (approx. £175/$200)
I can actually see out of them.
This time I've come to BUCCA...
Ebisu
...it's TKO Kinoshita's store.
These photos are pretty gross though.
BUCCA's stuff is kinda baggy...
...it's usually a larger size.
This set...
IT'S KINOSHITA!
I'm looking for a visual rock style.
Kanda
When thinking of it...
Bondage comes to mind.
Rubber...
See
It makes such a great noise.
It's even waterproof.
This is super cool
is it breathable?
Store Manager
No it's not.
So it's not breathable.
Can you wear this for surfing?
I guess so.
This is...
...this would be impossible to put on by yourself.
It shows off your body line.
It does.
Store Manager
You have such a nice body line.
I think this place should be good.
Yurakucho
This time is gonna be pretty tough...
Shimura ZOO is a Japanese TV program
Since he's on Shimura ZOO...
...maybe this handkerchief would work.
This is...
Right... It's not bad at all.
Price tag
276,000 Yen (approx. £1,165/$1,920)
But it's not bad...
Really?
DAIGO will take home his favourite item, the worst will have to pay out of their own pocket.
First off we will be presenting the tops we've picked to DAIGO.
Surprisingly, the tops this season are a bit...
That's true.
I was a bit unsure this time.
In saying that...
...I still found the perfect top.
Since you've said that...
...let's start off with Matsumoto-san.
We start off with the confident Matsumoto.
This is...
...truly
truly perfect.
I'm excited.
Let me just preface this...
...this is a bit of a more mature style.
He doesn't really have an older style.
That's what I was thinking.
That's true.
I don't think I have a single thing that's older.
I think you'll like this.
Can you pull it out?
It's so short!
5,292 Yen (approx. £34/$37)
What's with that?!
Is he a hotel porter?
Of course not!
What's this?
There's no button.
That came off in transit, sorry about that.
Can you try it on?
It's just so short.
I'm sorry about the buttons coming off.
It's so short.
This is something completely new!
The size is just...
This is bad!!
This is so bad!!
It looks great!!
So great!!
Look! Doesn't it look good!
How about buttoning up the front?
This? Ah here.
You look like a prince.
This suits you perfectly!
No it doesn't!
It's just so small.
So cool!
So uncool.
Can I just do my own check?
Here comes the Rock check.
Alright, that's enough!
Next to present his top, Hosei.
Have you just bought senbei?
Senbei = Japanese rice cracker
It's not senbei
See.
Really!?
What is that?
What sort of texture is that?!
It's rubber.
It feels...
It's nice right?
It's waterproof 'cos it's rubber.
What do you think of this guys?
It'd be impossible to wear in the summer.
Do you put clams in the pockets?
How much is it?
It is 27,864 Yen. (approx. £172/$195)
Really?!
A small price to pay for this quality.
So expensive!
Can we see the DAIGO check?
I feel sorry for DAIGO.
Hamada has a slightly surprising top to present.
Your usual image is something like this.
I think this sorta thing is good to wear casually.
The bag is pretty small.
It's a baggier look.
I don't have anything like this.
A baseball shirt.
It's a different look right?
This is just troublesome...
No it's not!
This kinda thing is comfy to wear.
10,584 Yen (approx. £68/$74)
That's a good point.
This is something new to me.
You haven't worn anything like this before, right?
You can wear it open or closed.
Nah. This isn't it.
It's different, but isn't that a good thing?
It doesn't suit him at all!
This is the worst so far.
I can't say for certain, but...
...judging by his face, it's not great.
This is gonna be a new DAIGO.
That's enough already!
Next up is an attacking top from Endo.
We've seen that...
...you mostly wear tight clothes, right?
I thought maybe something a little baggier.
I don't have anything in this colour.
Wow!
My eyes hurt!
It's baggier like mine.
5,389 Yen (approx. £35/$38)
It's way too big!
You're saying it's too big, but...
...this is from BUCCA, TKO Kinoshita's store.
The meaning behind the name of BUCCA is baggy.
Instead of being tight.
It just looks like a pain to wear.
It looks great on you!
Stop lying!
It really looks great on you!
It really doesn't!
It really suits you!
It's certainly adventurous.
There's a lot of adventure here.
Please do your check.
Is that alright? Ok here we go!
That's enough.
Hoping to show an excellent top, last up is Tanaka.
This is...
You beating the others?
Yes, this is truly on another level.
Look at him laughing.
That's not what this segment is about Tanaka.
It's not about the laughs.
I'm being serious here.
Really...
...I'm truly being serious.
This is truly nice.
What is this?!
It's really cool!
Tanaka-san, what are you thinking?
This is really cool.
It's a leather jacket.
It's a rocker's leather jacket.
It's full of holes.
Did you spend all night making this yourself?
It's undersized right?
32,184 Yen (approx. £205/$225)
Yes.
I found this in Harajuku...
...it's nice right?
It's a true rocker's style.
See.
See, doesn't it look great!
This is the first time I've worn such a light leather jacket.
I'm gonna do the check.
That's enough.
Which top will DAIGO choose as his favourite?
This is...
What are you unsure of?
Is there something?
I'm not sure...
It's kinda...
I'm in a bit of a panic.
In first place is?
Tanaka
Endo
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
First is...
THIS!
YOU GOTTA BE JOKING!!
NO WAY!
This is first because...
...it feels like a new rock.
Now we're in a bit of a panic.
In second place is?
In second is...
Endo
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
This one.
Thank you.
There's no way.
DAIGO-kun has no idea.
Truly no clue.
No way this is top two.
Of course it's this.
The reason?
I just don't have anything like this.
I also like the idea of fusing baseball and rock.
There's no way.
They just don't go together.
So, which is in third place?
In third place is...
Think this through properly.
Endo
Hosei
Matsumoto
It's this.
YES!! I DID IT!!
It should've been first though!
Nah, it's third.
You're kidding right?
I'm being serious.
Wha wha wha wha ... what's good about this?
It's even short on the arms.
That's what's good about it.
I actually really like this sort of thing.
Which of these tops will be ranked the worst?
Endo
Hosei
Ok, here we go, last place.
In last is...?
No way!
I also thought so...
To be honest, it's just too far away from what I'd wear.
It looks like something you wear for the 24 hour batsu.
It's not that bad.
Endo has to pay out 5,389 yen (approx. £35/$38)
Next up...
An accessory to suit DAIGO. First up is Hamada.
I don't think you wear shorts very often.
I never wear them.
I don't have any shorts.
You don't have any shorts?
Yeah, I don't.
Is it an accessory?
There are all sorts of accessories.
That doesn't suit his image.
5,400 Yen (approx. £34/$38)
Yeah but, he said he doesn't have any shorts and...
...they can also be used as swim shorts.
This season's spring and summer collections...
...and high fashion have this kind of look.
You don't have to force yourself.
I'll go and try them on.
Really?
You want to try them on?
I feel sorry for DAIGO.
He's really trying hard.
It's a different image for him, wearing shorts.
He should be done, come out DAIGO.
Why are you still wearing the boots and gloves?
The boots make it look weird.
DAIGO can you do your thing?
Sure, let's give it a go.
Looks great!
There's no way!
First with his top, how will Tanaka do with his accessory?
I'm avoiding last.
He and I have got the best connection...
...out of all of us.
I'm gonna win this one too.
Earlier was just by chance.
It's small.
I think this is a great accessory.
What is this?
A choker.
Ah, a choker.
Lame.
This guy really gives off weird vibes sometimes.
10,584 Yen (approx. £66/$73)
How is it?
It's pretty sparkly.
Does it say "SEXY"?
That's so lame.
Why is that lame?
It's super cool.
You don't have anything this size right?
Nothing this big, no.
Sengoku busho = Armoured generals of the Sengoku period (1467–1615)
This is what Sengoku busho wore around their necks.
Endo's accessory is little different, animal style.
If I'm not mistaken you're also on a horse racing program, right?
Ah, horse racing.
Yes I am.
What's that?
They're gloves.
Gross.
The gloves feature a horse's hoof.
2,230 Yen (approx. £13/$15)
Midori no Makibaō is a Japanese manga
about a mule becoming a racehorse
It's Midori no Makibaō.
There's also boots...
There's four of 'em?
2,680 Yen (approx. £17/$19)
Are they covers?
Yeah, you can wear them over your shoes.
I do really like horses but...
But...?
You look great!
You can't see his hands!
You're signing right?
We can't see his fingers!
This is certainly something new.
This is unfair!
This is too good!
Next up to present his item to DAIGO, Matsumoto.
This is...
...this is the one.
This is the winner here.
This is...
Right?!
Yeah yeah yeah.
It's rock.
A fan?
It's a rock fan.
This is pretty apt.
Exactly.
27,000 Yen (approx. £167/$187)
This is truly fresh!
This is the sorta thing you should be getting!
You guys are the strange ones!
Nah, we're not.
Do you wanna...
...do your rock check? It'll look so cool.
Ok, here we go.
Here we go.
Last up to show his accessory, Hosei.
I also like rock style stuff, so I've got a good sense for this.
You can't forget about the rock.
This is something, but...
What is that?
It's a skull, but...
Huh?
What is this?
This...
...it's a bag.
A bag?
Ah, I see.
It's so small.
It looks so weird.
It's so weird.
You just carry it like that?
Yeah.
You can probably wear it over your shoulder too.
Try it over the shoulder.
Tengu = A creature from Japanese folklore.
It looks like a Tengu.
Tengu's are often depicted with red faces and long noses.
Where's the Tengu's nose?
How much was it?
It was
21,384 yen (approx. £130/$148)
So expensive!
Everything you get is expensive!
Ok, I'll try it out.
What is that?
It's like a festival dance.
The Tengu looks like he's been cremated.
His nose has burnt off.
Which of these will be DAIGO's favourite?
In first place is...?
Hosei
Matsumoto
Endo
Tanaka
Hamada
In first place is...
This one!
YES! Of Course it is!
It couldn't be anything else!
There's no way it'd be anything different!
I felt like Matsumoto-san really put some thought into this...
Wind of Rock.
It's the
I want him to feel the
Let's move on to second place...
Hosei
Endo
Tanaka
Hamada
In second place is...
This!
Thank you!
Well, that makes sense.
Of course it does.
Since you don't have any shorts, and they work as swim shorts too.
If we were looking for a new DAIGO, then this is first.
Thank you.
It really is...
...Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arrahende!
In third is...?
In third is...
Hosei
Endo
Tanaka
This one.
Of course.
You're joking right?!
With "SEXY" on it!!
Ehh, really?!
These two again!
Which will come in last, Endo's horse gloves or Hosei's skull bag?
I don't think I should lose to that.
So DAIGO...
in last place is...?
Hosei
Endo
In last is...
C'mon.
Please.
The worst is...
It's this.
Of course it is.
Endo to pay 4,910 yen (approx. £30/$34)
But, DAIGO.
Which was worse... well of course this was worse...
...but what about this one?
This was... the opposite of Rock.
Maybe something to stick to the fridge.