TEAM Gaki presents:
Timing/Typesetting:
Sacro
Translation:
Michael
Lei
Final checker:
James
Special Tachinomi Advisor
Oolong
The first annual Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende
bet your life on one bite for a 100 thousand yen prize
Kiki Canned Tuna!!
So, this marks the 30th episode
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Wow, it's really the 30th?
Yamasaki Hosei
We haven't done canned tuna, have we?
No, we haven't
Let's look at the recent results
Yes, that makes it easier to understand
Well, with canned coffee
Right, we started with that
The results definitely fluctuate
Like Hamada-san will constantly get it right
Everybody is already saying that
"Everybody is already saying that"?
Did they say that?
Yes, they did
With that, today is canned tuna, however
the staff was thinking of using 15 types of tuna
but thanks to my sense of justice, they changed it to 12 types
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Thank you so much
It was my sense of justice
Your sense of justice!
No, when you came in this morning you said, "15 is impossible!"
That's true
Can I just add something?
Out of 21 people, only 5 people got it right
Results from staff simulation: 5/21 people
You always say that, but
The data isn't accurate
yeah, truly
They always lie
That's surely not a lie!
It's because they eat cheap food!
Maybe that's true
Seriously
Did it have this scent before?!
Let's just have fun
I DID IT!!!
The Kiki series 30th installment
Kiki Canned Tuna
To celebrate the 30th Kiki episode,
it's canned tuna!
Kiki Canned Tuna
They will eat it while blindfolded,
then identify which brand it is out of the 12.
While blindfolded, they will identify the brand they are eating out of the twelve.
If they get it right, they will receive a 100 thousand yen prize!
If they get it right, they will receive a 100 thousand yen prize!!
If they get it wrong, they will receive a severe punishment!!
If they get it wrong, they will receive a severe punishment!
Endo, are you going to be able to do this?
I'll do my best!
First up is Endo, who will try to win for the first time in 5 years
Endo's challenge
Top Value Light Tuna Flakes
(Ion)
The brand is Ion's private product, Top Value Light Tuna Flakes
I'll eat now
This seems to depend on how it's handled
or how it's taken apart
I wonder how this one will turn out
You checking it out?
He's checking it out...
You will even check out tuna?
I'm gonna check you out!!!
At first the oil filled my mouth and after about 10 seconds the oil drained,
but when I squeezed it again some oil came out
so I'm relying on that bit...
I bet they're all like that...
I have no idea what he's on about...
I'll go with this one
Currently tasting
Inaba Light Tuna Flakes
Correct answer
Top Value Light Tuna Flakes
The smell is extremely similar
What, seriously?
You always say "I got it!", or "it's wrong!"
It filled my mouth with oil like it did earlier,
There he goes
and after 10 seconds the oil is gone
and it's kind of dried out
after that, there's still some oil that I can suck out
It's exactly like the one I ate 3-4 minutes ago
I think it's this one, but
I would think so too
but
Correct answer
Top Value Light Tuna Flakes
I can believe that if I came over here I'd say "oh, this is completely different"
He suddenly gave up
What the hell!?
You had that thought process
Keep going
This must definitely be wrong
There's no way I'd get it this quickly
Alright, here I go
The tuna that I ate is NOT Inaba Light Tuna Flakes
This is quite a big moment
I really thought that was the tuna can I ate, so now I think it's around here
and the ones here are significantly different
One time?
Yes yes yes
Yes
There is a Korean brand here...
Korean brand?
Yes, right here
Tougen Canned Tuna
Currently tasting
Ah, this is different
The smell... this is just
This has no smell
Whoa
Excuse me, I'm really concentrating
Chew, fart, shock, then laughter
Continue
Correct answer
Top Value Light Tuna Flakes
Currently tasting
Tougen Canned Tuna
The tuna that I ate is NOT Tougen Canned Tuna
In spite of Hamada's interruption,
Currently tasting
Tuna in Tonno Olive Oil
he cleared 2 rounds!
2 ROUNDS CLEAR
Maybe you should get to the correct one for your tongue's sake
Now, I will try "Oltis Fatty Tuna in Oil"
Even though I keep saying it's over here
you keep going over there
You're trying to be on screen as much as possible, aren't you?
Is that wrong?
Who are you?
His throat sounded so dry...
Okay, okay, then, sorry
Let's get to it!
Alright, then is it really okay?
Of course!
Yeah!
You should be okay
For me,
this was the most similar to it
Correct answer
Top Value Light Tuna Flakes
These were all completely different.
Interesting.
So that means...
Which means that it must be from the same company: Inaba
these white tuna flakes
I think it'll be this one!
Yeah, then go
Currently tasting
Inaba White Tuna Flakes
There's the oil
then after a bit the oil goes away and it becomes dry
It's got to be this one...
I'm just gonna do it!
Please, I'm begging you
Can I go?
Go ahead
Please do!
Here goes!
The tuna that I ate IS Inaba White Tuna Flakes
Oh, what is this...
This looks grave...
There he is
I'm scared
What?
What is this?
I'm going to check you out like a frozen tuna!!
It's coming off of his face
This was the right answer
That? It was the next one
Right!
It was the next next one
The next one
If you went from the left
Wow, I wouldn't have known...
Well go on and taste it
It says "top value"
Oh this is definitely it.
Are you serious?!
Really?
Next up is
Tanaka, who claims he doesn't really eat canned tuna
Tanaka's challenge
Maguro Light Tuna Flakes in Oil
(Ito Foods)
Tanaka's challenge uses domestic rice bran oil,
Maguro Light Tuna Flakes
Wow, that's really oily
Is that so?
Yes
It's different from what I imagined
Interesting
Very wet?
It is very wet
Oh, that could serve as a hint
So it's possible that you
haven't even eaten it before?
Yes
The flavor, though
It's upside down
Your spoon is upside down, you're not getting anything
Man Tanaka,
that wasn't funny
I could have done that!
Correct answer
Maguro Light Tuna
Flakes in Oil
For the first one, I'm going to try the most expensive one
then I'll gauge the difference from there
2,110 yen (about $18)
Yes, this one from France
ah Spain, uh, the Vatican
Cut that out!
Currently tasting
Vatican Tuna in Olive Oil
I will eat now
Definitely not!!
How quick
It's wrong!
The tuna that I ate was NOT the Vatican Tonno Tuna in Olive Oil
That's right
This is just what I think, but he should make it a short battle
Yeah, he's going to forget what he ate
I see what you're saying
The oil will dry up too
And his mouth will get oily
Maruhachi Ni-ichiro
Currently tasting
Akebo's Natural Oil
Light Tuna Risetta
(Maruha Nichiro)
Maruhachi Ni-ichiro
Lately though, everyone
puts too much emphasis on
when someone says something wrong
We should be a little less harsh?
Yes, we should...
Yeah but even if you say that...
I don't know, but since when did we get so focused on detail?
How is it?
It's not it
Oh really
It wasn't so...
Tooth #$% is different too
Whatever
You're overthinking it
Correct answer
Maguro Light Tuna
Flakes in Oil
Currently tasting
Akebo's Natural Oil
Light Tuna Risetta
(Maruha Nichiro)
Even though his tongue was tied,
he tastes the tuna with certainty
Currently tasting
Inaba Light Tuna Flakes
(Inaba Foods)
Currently tasting
Inaba White Tuna Flakes
(Inaba Foods)
and clears 3 rounds!
4 rounds clear out of 12
He still has 8 left...
I will try this Kurashimoa
Oh you're going that route
Yes
Currently tasting
Kurashimoa Light Tuna Flakes
(Nihon Ryutsu Sangyo)
I'm thinking that
I might as well take care of this suspicious section here
You tried it?
No
The smell is extremely similar
How #$%
Tanaka is very #$%
But we've never heard him say it
Well, he is very #$%
He's trying to make us believe that he isn't #$%
What a pro
Can I go for it?
Of course that's okay
You decide that
Nobody can stop you from doing that
If they told me to point out the difference, that would be difficult
I'm going to do it!
The tuna that I ate IS Kurashimoa Light Tuna Flakes
How difficult!
I'M GOING TO FREEZE YOU AND YOUR SMELL,
YOU ROTTEN SCENTED COMEDIAN!!
I'm scared by the smoke that comes out
This is what you ate earlier
Yes, yes, yes
Oh, it's the same!
Third up is someone who can boast about winning 5 times, Hamada
Hamada's Challenge
Inaba Light Tuna Flakes
(Inaba Foods)
His challenge is very familiar from commercials, Inaba Light Tuna Flakes
What is he doing..?
How disgusting
He's very different
Different
He has a different touch
His approach is different
Yes
It's completely normal
Normal?
This is too normal
There are many kinds
Well the fact that it's normal is a hint
Yes, it's your hint
There's your answer!
Correct Answer
Inaba Light Tuna Flakes
(Inaba Foods)
I'm exhausted
What?
Amazing
He truly
What the hell?
looks like he's at a Osaka tachinomi bar
translators note: a tachinomi bar is where customers stand and drink; tachinomi = drinking while standing
"What the hell man?"
"What're you lookin' at?"
Let's try this one
Currently tasting
Top Value Light Tuna Flakes
(Ion)
Ah, no
That was the correct answer for mine
That was Endo's
No, this smell
Ah it wasn't this kind of smell
It didn't have such a dry body, it definitely had more flavor
BODY
The tuna that I... wait where is this from?
The tuna I ate
So far!
Incredible
He's so far from the can
That's how it was
He can't even see it
He can't see it...
Ion Top Value-
He can't see it right now...
Was NOT Light Tuna Flakes!
He's definitely not seeing it
Correct Answer
Inaba Light Tuna Flakes
(Inaba Foods)
Currently tasting
Maguro Light Tuna Flakes
in Oil
Next, he tastes the tuna that Tanaka had,
and he clears two rounds!
2 rounds clear out of 12
Nihon Ryutsu Sangyo, Kurashimoa
Currently tasting
Kurashomoa Light Tuna Flakes
(Nihon Ryutsu Sangyo)
It's similar.
But you know, the body...
It wasn't so dry when I squeezed the body...
"The body"
Squeezing it?
You squeeze it tight with your tongue
You would squeeze it with your tongue
No, there was definitely more flavor
What is he talking about with the "flavor"?
The body has a flavor
Not the body, but the combination
The body's flavor
of the body and the oil creates not a saltiness but a sort of flavor
This is the first time he's said this
It definitely builds up
How interesting
It's bland but I feel like there was a saltiness at the end
Damn it man, so annoying
This needs to stop
I don't wanna hear this
Let's just do it
Just do it boss!
Let's just have fun
He's been saying nonsense
It didn't have that final saltiness
Nope, this is wrong
Too far from the can
As always
He memorizes it and then moves it closer
He's not seeing it, he is seeing it
He can see it right, and then he memorizes
Memorizes...
The tuna I ate
was NOT Nihon Kyutsu Sangyo
You can't even remember the name?!
Kurashimoa Light Tuna Flakes!
He can't even say it
Well that was one hurdle he's cleared now
I'll go with the most bland one
It's becoming more precise
Currently tasting
Inaba Light Tuna Flakes
(Inaba Foods)
Currently tasting
Inaba Light Tuna Flakes
(Inaba Foods)
This must be the only option
If we're measuring by blandness
Inaba
Bland
DID IT HAVE THIS SCENT EARLIER!?
Please, please don't get angry, sir.
Don't get so upset!
Let's just have an enjoyable time
This is wrong, it was supposed to be bland
It has a scent
Well that's kind of how it is
Whoa, this really smells
Well the amount of oil
isn't too different
But at the end, a little saltiness...
The important part
The saltiness
The saltiness, yes
But when I was smelling it over there, I didn't
smell such a strong tuna scent
What if I get it wrong and it buzzes and they say "this was it"
and I smell it and it has a scent after all, what am I going to do?
We don't know, you're supposed to guess that...
Maybe I should just choose this one
Instead!!
After this: Will Hamada break the record with 6 right answers!?
He's staring at us
Definitely
He's staring hardcore
Correct Answer
Inaba Light Tuna Flakes
Currently tasting
If I do say so myself, it's very close
He probably can't see it
The tuna I ate WAS Inaba Food's Inaba Light Tuna Flakes
CORRECT!!
Are you kidding!
You're SERIOUSLY amazing!
Producer Dancers
Nakamura Yoshinobu
Kobayashi Hiromichi
INCREDIBLE!
You really got it!
I wanna get it right!
I wanna be correct!
That's how it goes
THANK YOU!!
Hamada since 2010 "Strawberry Jam"
receives 100,000 yen prize!!
YES, THANK YOU!
Nice catch, Hamada-san!!
There it is!!
It's really there!
I'm just wondering if it had that scent before
Here, we'll get it out
It was this one
Ah it does have a scent
What the hell?
Next is Yamazaki, who has gone 8 years without getting one correct
Yamasaki's Challenge
Deliciously Prepared Tuna
Hotei Foods
His challenge has only 54 kcal, Deliciously Prepared Tuna
WAIT A MINUTE!
It already has a scent!
It smells like bonito!
Bonito or a fish scent!
Well obviously
It's tuna flakes
Of course it'll smell like fish
This is chewy
You really think of a lot of ways to express yourself
I've eaten this before
Really?
Definitely
Okay, so which ones have you eaten before?
This one, this one- oh I've eaten this whole section
You eat a lot of canned tuna
Correct answer
Deliciously Prepared Tuna
(Hotei Foods)
Can I try this one?
Currently tasting
Maguro Light
Tuna Flakes in Oil
(Ito Foods)
Well you already touched it, so you have to
Maguro
Totally different
Quick
Um, Maguro Light Tuna
This again?
Too far, too far!
Nobody has good eyesight?
His arm is too short
THE TUNA I ATE
WAS NOT Maguro Light Tuna Flakes in Oil!!
How far does it have to be able to read it?
I can't see it
Right? It's like this
Endo's eyes are bad too
This is where I can see it the best
Oh, he's doing something
Sorry sorry, we interrupted
SO LAME!
This guy is so lame
He's a potato
Correct Answer
Deliciously Prepared Tuna
(Hotei Foods)
Currently Tasting
Top Value Light Tuna Flakes
(Ion)
He concentrated on 5 brands he's eaten before,
Currently tasting
Kurashimoa Light Tuna Flakes
(Nihon Ryutsu Sangyo)
Currently tasting
Akebo's Natural Oil
Light Tuna Risetta
(Maruha Nichio Foods)
tried 4, and got them correct!
Currently tasting
Inaba White Tuna Flakes
(Inaba Foods)
Next, he will challenge the last Inaba Light Tuna!!
4 ROUNDS CLEAR
You're doing good
Really well!
Super good!
Yes, very good
Currently Tasting
Inaba Light Tuna Flakes
(Inaba Foods)
So that means-
Huh? Wait-
What?
It's different
Just smell it again and stuff
Yes, just smell it
I totally thought it would be this
There's absolutely no scent
If it's something you've had before
This pattern is
really unfortunate
Whaaat? Wait-
It's different, completely different
Alright, let's start here
Inaba Light Tuna Flakes, the one I ate-
What?
What kind of grammar is that?!  *(or, anastrophe)
IT IS WRONG!
Y-LOOK!
Y-look?
Y-look!
"Yossha" and "ora"  (ora means look)
It was different!
Correct answer
Deliciously Prepared Tuna
(Hotei Foods)
Currently Tasting
Tonno Tuna in Olive Oil
The one he aimed for was incorrect, but he tastes the next ones with certainty
Currently Tasting
Ortiz Tuna in Olive Oil
(French F&B Japan)
and he miraculously clears 2 rounds!!
8 clear out of 12
So just these left?
Wow, amazing
4 more to go!
This-
I'll try this
The Korean one
Currently tasting
Tougen Canned Tuna
Even though this is my first time eating this,
I've eaten this before
This is the one I ate before
Really, really!
He's really going at it
I'm very confident
The tuna I ate WAS Tougen Canned Tuna
I really thought he would get it
You took so much damn time
You were so close!
So close! What a waste
You were so confident!
You really believed it
YOU ARE COLDER (lamer) THAN FROZEN TUNA!!
Yama-chan...
Zaki-san!
Hosei-san!
Come on, you just ate this!
I don't know what this is
Of course
Da-dun!
In that case, you can't do anything
Last is Matsumoto, who has also gone 7 years with no victories
Matsumoto's Challenge
Top Value Light Tuna Flakes
(Ion)
His challenge is the same as Endo's: Top Value Light Tuna Flakes
Just tell me who picked it out!
Here!
Is this it?
Yes!
What is this?
I might not know this brand!
Ahh what do I do!?
It's not that oily!
Are you guys serious?!
You guys didn't bring me one that wasn't an option right?!
THIS ISN'T FUNNY TO ME!
Everybody went home, didn't they?
I wondered what the hell I was supposed to do
That was quite the one-man show
You guys are dirty!!
Well, but we didn't distract you
Yes yes yes
You were able to fully concentrate
Correct answer
Top Value Light Tuna Flakes
(Ion)
So I think
my theory with these games is that you guys always repeat the previous answers
The one just now (Yamasaki's) was this one, right?
Yes
I can believe that you guys chose this one
if I place myself in your tiiiiiny brains
I can imagine that
my ENORMOUS brain
compared to your tiiiiiny brains-
Hurry up already!
Go on!
Currently tasting
Deliciously Prepared Tuna
(Hotei Foods)
Usually you guys choose the previous answer
I've gone and done it...
I'VE REALLY GONE AND DONE IT!!
What the hell?
The one that Yamazaki failed to identify...
you guys, who gave it to me,
are TRULY disgusting people!
You are so nasty
You are extremely indecent
So, anyway,
even though I said a lot of mean things
He's regretting them
I already have so much confidence,
so there's no way I can quit now
Just by looking at Hamada's face,
I think I'm probably correct...
anyhow,
we've been a pair for 30 years
Alright, I got it
HERE I GO!
The tuna that I ate WAS Deliciously Prepared Tuna!
I'm begging you, I'm begging you...
It was completely different!
On the first try!
He didn't get anything correct
He always does this
You're going to eat tuna tonight anyway, right?
Huh, what?
It was this one
What the hell is with that?
What the hell is with that normality?
What pieces of shit you guys are!
Then which one would you have liked?
Yes, that one
You just ate that one, come on
I have absolutely no idea