Gaki no Tsukai's backstage
We're here before the filming of a Gaki episode
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada strained his left leg during the filming of another show
This guy strained his leg
Yeah, it surprised me
He's almost 50 now, this ain't the right time to do that
Maybe he wanted to go through that experience
He's been fine all these years
Yamazaki Hosei
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Intact for so long... and now he goes
Now it feels like he has to sprain more than that
The hell are you talking about?
Oh?
Man...
Where's your partner (Tanaka)?
I don't really know
Where's jaw?
He's not even here to say hi
That's odd
'Morning
Inomoto Takafumi
Fujiwara Kazuhiro
License
Good morning folks   It's License
About Tanaka... I don't think he's coming today
Yes?
Again?
Why is he not coming?
He's not?
What does he mean?
He says he's getting very angry lately...
Oh, cut the crap...
What's the deal with him getting angry? I don't get it
He's not like that
No idea
On March Tanaka got mad at something Matsumoto said
That was because of Matsumoto, right?
That's right
But we're fine now
We've reached a compromise
Did you really?
I mean, it was a 800'000 yen worth compromise
With money?!
No idea why he didn't ask for a million
So close yet so far
It doesn't make sense
He said "I showed them how angry I can get and yet they still don't understand it"
I have no idea what he's talking about
What the hell?
He also said "I'm never filming Gaki again!"
He can't say that, come on
Oh, really?
We don't actually know what he's mad about
So we asked a staff member to go check him out
The reason why he's angry:
The staff asked Tanaka Naoki about it on this VTR
Do you mind watching it?
Oh boy...
What just happened?
It's getting hard to deal with him
Sorry for this
True, it's getting hard
Now that I think about it, that time we had his wife on our show she said he's hard to deal with
Kohinata Shie
He's a problem child
His wife said so?
Yes, his wife said so
She said he's hard to deal with?
Heading towards Tanaka's meeting place
Hey!!
Eraser!!
(nickname)
He's shouting so much
I'm here!!
TRANSLATION BY SHION
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
VISIT SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM FOR MORE EPISODES!
HOW TO SUPPORT THIS PROJECT:
- LIKE FB PAGE @FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
- FOLLOW @SHIONNOTSUKAI ON TWITTER
- DONATE @KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
- BECOME A PATRON @PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
WHY IS HE ANGRY?
IS SOMETHING STRANGE HAPPENING TO TANAKA?!
Why is Tanaka so angry?
What caused Tanaka's anger?
What is he angry about?
We went to our meeting place feeling uneasy
Hey!!
Eraser!!
(nickname)
He's shouting so much
I'm here!!
Here he is
staff) Good morning
There's something in his mouth
Hey!!
'Morning
We're glad no one was around
Because his voice was way too loud
Even his appearance left us speechless
Hey!
Good morning
We got to experience that same
out-of-place feeling from last time
Hey
staff) What's the deal with the luggage, Tanaka?
I had lots of away-from-home jobs lately!
Use the right word for it!
staff) So you're just carrying them around?
Yeah, lots of 'em recently...
We have a word for that
What the...
staff) Can we ask you something?
Where?
staff) Here, come with me
Creepy...
Oh, sorry
What do you want?
Rude!
staff) We want to ask you a lot of things
Is the easygoing Tanaka we see on tv just a facade...?
Why are they showing this again?
staff) Alright Tanaka, we want to hear something  from you
The weather is perfect though
- It's great
This is crazy
That thing is huge!
He ignores our questions and bites down
a huge chicken on the bone
Look at him go
Looks tasty...
It's way too large
Maybe he was hungry...
He's eating so much
Not the cleanest
scene to look at
He ate it all!
staff) We heard that you recently got really angry...
Yeah, it's 'cause of that
It's 'cause of Yamazaki's "Comedy Guidelines"
Remember the watermelon bit?
Yes
I'm angry 'cause of that
Huh?
What is he talking about?
But he helped us
DID YOU MISS THIS EPISODE? IT'S SUBBED! FIND IT ON:
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM/2019/03/13
Tanaka denounces a Yamazaki-focused episode aired before
That was all about
Yamazaki, wasn't it?
Looks like the reason was this gag in which he dropped
a watermelon on Yamazaki's head from 10 meters...
Dropping a watermelon from a 10 mts height
And making it fall on Yamazaki's head: here's the trigger...
Nice one!
I remember this...
Incredible...
Tanaka's role was to drop the watermelon on him
At that moment, Tanaka's role was to drop the watermelon from above
But what did really happen here?
What made him so angry?
What happened?
I went up here (the 10mt platform)
And everyone down there was excited, like "yay yay yay"
What about me, huh? Didn't think of me up there, huh?
No way, man...
Before the drop
We looked at the footage again, and it's true that they're
having a good time before the watermelon was dropped
Oh, don't you lie to me like that!
No, we won't
And Tanaka was left behind
Left behind...
Did that hurt him?
After the drop
Comedy and effort are completely different
Yeah, but we kinda...
Even after the performance, there was no highlight for Tanaka...
No place for him...
It's safe to say I came to this world to drop watermelons
Is he for real?
staff) But that was... I mean, you shared roles...
I can't hear ya!
Well, he's right
I can't hear ya, Eraser (staff)!
So, I drop one watermelon, it splits up nicely
And I'm like "want me to drop another one?"
Do you remember what Yamazaki told me?
Sorry, Tanaka
Was it not good?
Yeah, not good...
Don't you need more? I have plenty here
What do you think?
Are you an idiot?
I've been told "idiot" so many times before
But that's the first time it came from an idiot
Hey!!
- Whoa, slow down
That's too much
By the time I got home, anger kept on building up...
He's an idiot!
How did he even hear that?
- That's so dumb
staff) So, is Yamazaki the cause of it?
It's not really about who it was or who did it...
It's about how I don't feel fit for Gaki anymore
He's making such a
big deal about it...
staff) And that's why you're this angry?
That's why my ass
The hell is this?
What the hell...
Yep
Who cares about that?
staff) Is something wrong with your hand?
Don't touch it
It stinks
Yeah
The smell won't come off
That's 'cause you ate
His teeth are so dirty
- So dirty...
Just look at his eerie, soulless smile
His creepy smile felt very strange...
This is disgusting
He's freaking me out
- Really-- what?
I would have love to see him hurrying his way down the stairs
and get right in front of the camera
In haste?
You're right
They should have set a camera up there too
Yeah, that's right
There was no camera following him step by step
That's the issue
That would have required more staff
Makes sense, he's angry at Gaki
I guess that's right
By the way, did you know that
He recently made this group called "Tanaka party"?
Never heard of it
You know? When groups of comedians regularly do meetings and stuff? He made one of those
Well, it's a private thing
Nothing wrong with that
Actually we got invited to it ourselves...
To "Tanaka party"?
Yes
We took a video of it,
how about we watch it together?
Sure
Can't deny I'm interested in it
Me too
But I'm scared
Why would such an introverted man
found a meeting group?
We can't help but be concerned about this "Tanaka Party"...
We're worried about his mysterious meeting group...
P.M.5:52, Tanaka Party Infiltration Day
On this day, License were invited to Tanaka Party for the first time
Nice weather again
- It's always so nice
staff) I can tell by your pace you're nervous
They're moving quickly
That's right...
Maybe with License it's not impossible
for us to get some nice footage
But we can't help but notice the gloom
of those who know Tanaka's other face
And then...
Whoa!!
That caught me off guard!
Holy crap
Gimme a break...
Geez, what was that for?
He's evil
What are you doing?
Hey!
That's really something
watermelon
What Tanaka threw down from above their heads...
That's dangerous
- It is
Was a watermelon
It's not like Yamazaki's
Yeah, that was all gravity
Maybe he couldn't control his emotions
Exactly
Why?
I'm coming back
Sure!
Is that the shop?
Good evening
'Evening
Hi guys
His teeth again...
Did I scare you?
Stop it...   Give us a break
Shall we go?
Sure
staff) Is it ok if we film this, Tanaka?
Ah, today we have Gaki's cameraman...
Sorry about this
It's fine but this isn't gonna be fun at all
Is that ok?
staff) Yes, it's fine
Is it ok? Sorry
Let's go!
Thank you
His voice...
I know...
Thanks for that
Don't be so tense!
Of course I'm gonna be after that!
That's not the
person I know
It appears a violent Tanaka lived somewhere inside him
He's not that type of guy
- That's messed up
His look spells "danger"
They're gonna meet up in a Izakaya
I think everyone's already there
Already?
The atmosphere inside feels different
And that's what made it frightening
Hey!
'Evening
Hey hey hey hey hey!
Hi there
Excuse us
Good evening
Welcome
It's a pleasure
That's the cameraman for Gaki
Ah, really?
Here's License
Oh, it's a pleasure to meet you
It's a pleasure
Is that Nezumi Senpai...?
- Oh?
- Eh? This is...
That's right
I didn't know he was part of this
Nezumi Senpai
- It's really him...
There's a lot of people, yeah
Ohhh, I see...
- It's Nezumi Senpai
staff) I don't know most of them, I see Q-Taro here but everyone else...
You should be able to tell
Such a burden
- Who's this?
- Have I seen him before?
Cheers!
Cheers to us!
What's the relationship between him and these people?
We didn't get an answer from him
Look at him go
He's going for it
That's impressive
He doesn't drink much,
does he?
- Yeah...
One more beer please!
A draft beer, please
You surely can drink...
Who's this guy?!
- I have no clue
Never seen him before
Eat up, Tabe!
Ah, sorry!
- "Tabe"?
staff) Are you Mr. Tabe?
Yes
They're Tabe and Tanio from Hiyashins
We're Hiyashins, nice to meet you
Hiyashins
Tabe
Tanio
No idea who they are
As always, his appetite is immense
Food is disappearing in a blink of an eye
License are observing the situation
Some words a member let out...
And they're surprised to hear something the members often say...
Why is his arm broken?
Are you familiar with Tanaka?
Yeah, Our Tanaka has taken good care of me
Oh, is that so?
"Our Tanaka"?
"Our Tanaka"...
Yes   Eat up!
Everyone seems to refer to him as "Our Tanaka"...
Nickname
"Our Tanaka"
Our Tanaka...
It's like I was totally captured by him, you know
I'd say I went through a complete change
Tonfer
Yamanishi Akihiro
Q. Why do you refer to Tanaka as "Our Tanaka"?
It's like Tanaka is the nucleus and I've been absorbed as a part of it
The hell is he
talkin' about?!
Nezumi Senpai
It's Q-san who introduced me to him, and since I got here I started to call him like this
What the hell is this?
I don't get it
After all I've always respected Our Tanaka even before
And now I feel like I respect him even more
Charisma
According to the members, it seems
like Tanaka has a lot of charisma
We're all "Our Tanaka", including Our Tanaka
Tonfer
Kohama Ryuuji
I get my ideas because Our Tanaka exists
Zatsuki Sakka
Konda Mitsuo
We all work here, and...
Hiking Walking
Suzuki Q-Taro
It's really starting to look like some kind of cult
So, we're all here and...
Feels like I'm dropping feathers, you know?
The party goes on...
Are you still losing hair?
Eat up, Noe!
Sure, I'm diggin' in
staff) Miss Noe, how did you get in here?
Yes?
She just got in on her own
On her own?
By the way, I'm currently banging her
- What the hell is he saying...
- That's so unlike him
He's always joking like this
This is messed up
Hey, you gotta deny that!
In a way we can say it's like that
He's a senpai I really admire
Ageha Noe
Q. Is that the relationship you have with Tanaka?
Who's this?
- No clue
It's like...
Maybe she's worried about Tanaka's family
I like this place and...
Unclear statements...
But the way she talks is ambiguous
At any rate, it's good being part of "Our Tanaka"
This meeting looks boring as hell
Yeah, it's so stupid
Now that Tanaka is drunk and is feeling good, we asked him about women
Asking Tanaka about his relations with women
Wanna go for one of the ladies?
Eraser (staff), use your dick some more, use it!
What is he saying...
I've been drinking so much
- He's not the type
who would say that
Yeah...
Yeah, I know
- Yes...
I drank way too much
We're only left with a smile with no room for answers
Tanaka is always hanging out with somebody, lately
Second day of filming
Today it's Q-taro again
staff) Where are you going today?
To Kanaria's Bon's house
And do what?
He's got the key
We wanna scare him for good
staff) Do you often do stuff like that?
All the time
Come on, they're over 40...
They got the key of a junior they don't like by threatening his manager
Breaking into the house of a junior he doesn't like
I mean, that's something
you'd do when you're young...
And now they're breaking into his house
That's a crime
Q-taro is evil too
- He is
Lemme step in!
Oh shit you scared me!!
'Morning!!
Kanaria
Bon Mizokuro
Lemme see ya house!
No wait---
Look at this!
So dirty!
What's going on?
Hey, clean up!
Let's get rid of this
Sure thing
Wa-- wait, what are you doing?
Please stop, Tanaka!
Let's clean up
Don't joke around
I'm helping here
What the hell is this?!
Et voilà!
Voilà!
Wait a moment--
What are ya gonna do about it?
Stop for a second, please!
Your house is so dirty!
So dirty!
That's not true--- what's going on?
Is this where you live?
No! Wait! Don't!
Tanaka's abuse goes on...
Tanaka's abuse knows no bounds and it's going on
Wait a sec!
He's laughing so much
Maybe we should have stopped him...
But that wouldn't have stopped Tanaka
We'll come back again, Bon!
No wait--
That's crazy
What's this about?
staff) Are you just leaving it as it is?
That's the plan!
I don't care!
Let's go
Yeah let's bounce
We won't interfere in comedians' business
It's something between comedians...
No way
4th day of filming
One morning, he called License to a certain shopping district
He's got piercings now
Q-taro is with him again
And he's always eating something
- Why though?
Is there something good?
Let's see...
I really like backpacks
Oh, backpacks?
Yeah...
It happened when Q-taro was looking at the backpacks...
That one?
Oh, stop it, Our Tanaka!
What's with that name?
Oh please don't
- "Stop, Our Tanaka"...
Your pants
What the hell, man...
That's no good for tv
It sounds so weird
He got caught on tape
How can you address
someone as "Our Tanaka"?
These grownups surely love kids pranks
Come on
So stupid
And now he stops before a beauty salon
It's getting crowdy
- Is he peeping?
That chick is hella hot
That's so dumb
He's not ok
He just found a woman he likes
Ah, he's chewing a gum,
that's what it is
Oh shit, I'd love to bang her!
Oh, is that it?
- Yep
Can't you just--
Look, there's a crowd around us
I don't care, this is important
No I mean--
There are so many people watching us
Tell me your (phone) number!
Tanaka, please...   Wait, Tanaka-
Hey, calm down
Tanaka...
Your number, please!
Calm down, Tanaka
Oh boy
Tanaka, please--
Let's leave
Once his lust kicks in, there's no way to stop it
Wow, they're surrounded
Oh boy, I wanna have sex
Your voice is too loud, Tanaka
We're in a shopping district...
Tanaka is even more outspoken than before
staff) You speak a lot about girls, don't you?
Well, my dick is always ready
But recently my sexual desires are impressive
The way he said "dick"...
He put so much stress on the word "dick"!
His growing desires are slammed against a vending machine
Oh!
Is that you?
You can't do that
That's messed up
- The hell is he doing?
Do you hate him?
No, I'm not angry!
Let's just stop doing this--
What are you doin--- seriously? Stop it!
What the hell, man
He has lost it
You're the worst!
I would have killed him
- He's crazy
Man, you're the worst!
It's fine
Inomoto, that's fine I say
Are you serious?
Fine? What's fine?
This is close to madness
Come on now
That's too much, man
And his fangs are ready to bite everything in this world
That looks delicious
Is that meat?
That's dry-cured ham
Don't tell me...
Oh no, quit it!
You can't do that!
- Oi...
He merciless bites off a dry-cured black iberian pig ham
He's pissing me off
It's hard to watch
This is too much
What are you doing?
That was so delicious
We thought "let's quit filming this"
But just before we could finish that thought...
We felt a thirst for blood in his eyes
Looks like there's something in front of him
What's wrong?
What happened?
No way
Wait!
Eh!?
Hey, hey, hey...
That's too much
Wait, calm down
What the hell are you doing?
What was that for?
Oh man, it's hard to watch
Was that necessary?
Camera!
That must have triggered him
- That's right
What--- how much for these?
Just like a volcano, Tanaka's dormant
dangerous sentiments exploded
Dangerous sentiments...
Forbidden watermelon
It was the forbidden fruit, the watermelon...
It's always like that
Is that so?
Whenever I see a watermelon, I start punching 'em around
And yet, his eyes looked lonely to us
That sad look in his eyes worried us...
One day we happened to see a new
face at the game center at night
6th day of filming
A paradise for lovers
That's a place commonly associated with couples
And then we realized Tanaka was part of them
I like you!
That's it?
We couldn't believe our eyes...
And there we saw something we couldn't believe...
Coming next
Something unprecedented at the game center!!
What is he doing?   No way
This guy...   That's not ok
6th day of filming
We happened to see Tanaka in a game center during the night...
The reason why he's here today...
Is to spend his free time with his secret lover...
Secret date with his lover...
You're pretty good at this
I'm almost there
Come here, come here!
It feels as if they just fell in love with each other
That's a lot
So we decided to quit filming
But as soon as we decided that...
This one here
That's really cute, isn't it?
It is
It's cute
Just like you
What are you doing?
No way
It's so embarrassing!
I hate this
Tanaka was completely defenseless
What the hell
If this kind of info gets on the media, Tanaka's comedian career could be ruined for good
Given that he has a wife and kids
I'm embarrassed...
Come on, baby
The hell is he doing?
What are you embarrassed for?
What the fuck
Just stop it, please
- What's this?!
We can say he's the first comedian who made such a complete transformation
Is this legal?
I don't know anymore
Check out her calve muscles
They felt incomplete
We couldn't just stay still in front of a colleague of ours
- You're right
staff) Tanaka, Tanaka
Sorry
You...
'Evening
What are you filming?
Sorry for this
staff) Is that your girlfriend?
That's right
staff) Have you been dating for long?
Not really
staff) I've been filming you for some time by now
staff) It's been some time
Why are you filming us?
As a tv star, you should avoid doing such things
But-- I mean...
I have no problems with it
The hell is he doing?
- Seriously, what the...
We are left speechless
It's hard to watch
- I'm really sorry
This went way beyond what we would have thought of
I don't know what to think
- Yeah...
Quit filming, you
The hell is this?
We couldn't sense any happiness in him leaving with his lover
All we could sense was his poorly concealed loneliness...
Carrying loneliness on his back...
I'm not used to see him stand out so much
Yeah, that's incredible
I agree
Even the other folks were awful, saying "Our Tanaka" here and there
Yeah, right
Q-taro couldn't stop saying it
Yeah, that guys sucks too
You could explain to me the meaning of
"Our Tanaka" a thousand times, I'd never get it
Same for us, actually
I have no clue
By the way, that guy you saw sometimes
on camera is an actor called Mr. Taka
Oh, is he an actor?
That's a big problem
Coming next
The eccentric man appears!!
Is that his type?
Oh?
'Morning
What should we do?
I mean, he felt very lonely...
Even if you say so
He still has his calve muscles lady with him
Yeah, she had some bruises too
That's a big problem
Yeah...
Is that his type?
Oh?
'Morning
It's Tanaka
Tanaka?
Wait
Man, you're...
Good morning, Matsumoto
Have you lost it?
Don't just... Not like this
It's all out, man
Quit it already!
I've said it before, haven't I? "I'll go around naked", didn't I?
And here I am, naked!
Yeah let's just stop---
We got it, alright...
This is a small watermelon
It's really good
You're shouting so much
This is really good, please eat it up guys!
Sure...
Got it, got it
Now, let's go filming!
Go wear a jersey
Dress up first
Your jersey
If you wanted to go naked, then why are you wearing panties?
Oh fuck
This guy is pissing me off so much
Quit it, Tanaka
What now
What are you-!?
Producer
Nakamura Yoshinobu
What is...?
This is no good   Understood?!
You can't
That's what ya get from the watermelon dropper!!
Remember that!!
It's our producer, you know
I'm going ahead first!
How can we start filming with this atmosphere...?
Yeah...
He's crazy
Do we have a towel here?
My partner has lost it
And for some reason Nakamura got involved in this
I'm sorry about this
He snapped at him
He's --- oh no
Oh shit he's back
Watch out!
What the hell, man...
I'll wait for ya!
Sure, whatever
Got it, just go
I'll wait
Sure, go ahead
Wear your jersey, man!
Nakamura is completely drenched in watermelon
That's too much...
Sorry about this
It's fine
Anyway, what should we do about---
He's here again
Again?!
Stop it!
Let's go!!
I'll wait for ya
We're coming
It made a weird sound
Come on!
We're coming, we're coming
What are ya waitin' for?!
His head made a weird sound
He has lost it
Let's just go
Yeah, let's not waste time
The Tanaka stalking VTR are all fictional.
Even the objects Tanaka interacted with
And the people he came in contact with
Were all staged and prepared in advance.
TRANSLATION BY SHION
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
VISIT SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM FOR MORE EPISODES!
HOW TO SUPPORT THIS PROJECT:
- LIKE FB PAGE @FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
- FOLLOW @SHIONNOTSUKAI ON TWITTER
- DONATE @KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
- BECOME A PATRON @PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI