TPF
The second annual Gaki no Tsukai Ya Arahende chiki chiki nostalgic retro Famicon gaming!!
Right, second annual
Yup
It's the second time, isn't it. The theme has changed a bit this time
Exactly. This is the results from the last one.
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Ah, is that it?
Seriously, you guys were completely crushed
I know, Matsumoto-san won by so much
Tsukitei Hosei
You were in last place, weren't you?
You were just so bad, in Donkey Kong
you got 0 points. You really are an old geezer
Hamada is the only one with 0 points
Tanaka has one that is "No record"
Cocorico
Tanaka Naoki
Endo Shozo
There was something wrong with the game
I couldn't get it to work. Yea, that was it
Even though it's a show, you still occasionally mess up
No no, please don't say that
This place has 572 games in total
Total number of NES Games: 572
Awesome
The person who prepared all of these games for us is here... Welcome!
Game collector, Sakekan
Game Collector
Sakekan
I'm Sakekan
NES Games Appreciation
Firstly, everyone will go over the nostalgic NES games that have been prepared by Sakesan
The games from last time are here as well.
Yup, yup
This (Mappy), I haven't even heard of it
How dare you show up today without even knowing Mappy
No, I really don't know what this is
Me neither
1984 - Mappy
Action game: Mappy, the police mouse,
recovers stolen goods while evading enemies
Surely you know what Mappy is
It's very popular
Nope, I don't know Mappy
You've actually been arrested before so how do you
not know about Mappy
I have never  been arrested
I have never been arrested
Hamada-san never usually looks directly at the camera...
Yeah because I have to make it clear...
Looking directly at the camera
Hmm, I don't know any of them, what should I do...
Ah, Doctor Mario
Doctor Mario
I was really hooked on this
1990 - Doctor Mario
Using capsules, Mario eradicates
the viruses in the bottle
I've heard of it before
I could play this forever.
Doctor Mario throws capsules at you and they start falling faster and faster.
It would suddenly get really fast, making it extremely difficult
And when you lost, Doctor Mario would just do this
and I'm like 'It's because you're going too bloody fast!'
You really remember this well, don't you
This one is also recommended
Ice Climber, hmm... I've definitely heard of it before but never actually played it
1985 - Ice Climber
Action game: Ascend to the summit
by breaking blocks using a hammer
It's fun
Could you explain it roughly
Explaining it through rap would be better
Hosei Rap Battle
Aired on 22/9
About that
I really want to draw a line under that
How about here? Any one of these you guys know?
As expected, only the recommended ones. For example this, Wagan Land
Nope
No idea
What kind of game is it then?
Um, well, it's like this
Please explain it through rap
Yo yo
I wanted to try doing it without hesitating but,
in the end, I still did
Yeah, me too
I wanted to make it really good too but then I knew it was impossible...
You looked like you were about to cry
I thought steam was going to come out of my head
Tofu Panda Fan subs presents
Down Town's Gaki no tsukai ya arahende!!
Translators:
Typesetter & Proofreader:
Hans & Mickstar
(Team Gaki)
Otviss
**We also have facebook and twitter.**
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
NES Gaming Episode 2!!
Selecting from the 572 nostalgic games each member will pick a game to play and be scored
Today's format
Cocorico Tanaka
Which will he choose?
He brought one from the 'recommended area'
Yup, it's from the recommended
Ah, it's Pac-man
Here it is
Pac-man
That game sold so much
Released in 1984
Pac-man
The player controls Pac-man in a maze to eat up all the dots while evading the enemies
I'm really really good at this!
Seriously?
There's a pattern to it
I was into Pac-man a long time ago
Since Yama-chan has so much confidence, he should be last. Let's go down the line.
Pac-man
Tanaka
Actually, I've never played this before
I played it a long time ago
This brings me back
So nostalgic
Okay, okay...
What a nostalgic sensation
Isn't there an order to eating the dots?
The order is...
Pac-man
Tanaka
There, you've left one behind
You're in trouble
This isn't good
Tanaka, you're in trouble
Oh, I see
Tanaka, you're seriously in trouble
Oh, that's good
In the end
You've got to eat them quickly or you're in trouble
Woah, woah, oh, okay okay, finally
Quickly, quickly
Pac-man
Tanaka
He's going to wait in that corner, see he's waiting.
But that was the last power-up
Yeah you're right
So now he has no way to counter them
All you can do is run away
All you can do is run around
Let's get past at least 1 level
Pac-man
Tanaka
They're getting close
You're in trouble
You're in trouble now
Here they come, here they come
They're really coming now
This is bad, this is bad!
He did it!
Awesome
Tanaka level 1 clear
Pac-man
Tanaka
Tanaka somehow cleared the first level, however...
You're in trouble
What was that?
Such a lame ending...
Yea, but still, I honestly didn't even think I could clear the first level
Tanaka 4480 points
Yea, a whole level
I'm still plenty satisfied
Pac-man
Endo
Next up is Endo, who during his childhood was only playing baseball, hardly playing video games
Yes!
What the hell are you doing there?!
He went for seconds*
*Translators note: Okawari means second dish. Going back for more of the same dish.
Stop going for seconds
Pac-man
Endo
What are you trying to do?
This is bad
You'd better get there quickly
It's alright now
You're good now
What are you trying to do?
Why are you going that way?
Whaddahell!
"Whaddahell"
Because I haven't playe~
He finished with "Whaddahell"
Haven't played since childhood
Endo 2520 points
He's the Kansai version
of the jeans detective!
That's the Kansai version of Nanja koryaa
Hamada's turn
I'll beat his score
Hamada, are you good at this?
Why would you say that?
You've definitely played this many times before, haven't you
I think Hamada,
Pac-man
Hamada
When this came out, he was in dorms
Yes, I was
Because he lived in a dorm,
Other games seemed crappy, maybe not "crappy" but,
Pac-man was popular at the time
Yea, yea
It's so hard to move
Because at that time, Pac-man was the only game that actually played well
That's bad
Good job on losing
610 points with one life left
The staff are laughing so much
Who was the one laughing hysterically?
Man that pisses me off
Pac-man
Hamada
That's good
Really?
Yea, sure
Nice, just go back again, huh?
Hamada 1950 points
Are you a gangster?
Why are you going towards them?
Gangster?
Matsumoto's Pac-man Trial!!
Next, previous champion, geezer gamer, Matsumoto
Because this isn't exactly what we call a joystick,
Pac-man
Matsumoto
It makes it harder
In the cafe, it used to be a joystick controller
You're so fast
This part's particularly difficult
It seems like you get faster when you power up
Exactly. This definitely
Doesn't feel like we're playing in a cafe because of this
Yea, it doesn't
Pac-man
Matsumoto
Even though operating on an unfamiliar controller, he is still able to do well
All you can do is run now
The dots are scattered all around
Woah almost almost!
What are you
What were you doing running about the same spot?
What were you doing walking about the same spot?
Nice one
Pac-man
Matsumoto
You should turn around
Oh this is bad, you're so dead now
You were backed up into the corner, there's no way to escape
You're right, it's more difficult than expected
The controller movement, right?
Pac-man
Matsumoto
You should be able to make it through now
Isn't that dangerous over there?
He turned and ran towards them
You're a gangster
Gangster!
You must be
I've only ever played using the joystick...
Matsumoto 3730 points
Hosei's Pac-man Trial!!
Lastly, Hosei, who is super confident in Pac-man. Will he be able to beat Tanaka's high score?
Pac-man
Hosei
You're doing fine
You actually wanted to go the other way, didn't you?
Yeah but you can do it like this as well
What pattern?
You've got to be kidding me
Hold on a second
Looks like an orange peel in the end
Pac-man
Hosei
What are you doing?
It'll be fine
Aren't you in serious trouble here?
Why didn't you go up just then?
Here's how it works, you gather them together and then... wait, what?
This bloody controller
Hosei 3230 points
We all used the same one
Everyone used the same controller
Yup, exactly
That's so annoying
That was unexpected
Pac-man Results
Hosei
Matsumoto
Hamada
Endo
Tanaka
Tanaka?
Yes, it's me
Yea, it's Tanaka, 4000 something
Quite the boy genius, aren't you?
I only cleared one level
It was only level one
Released in 1983
Mario Brothers
The game that Endo has chosen is the highly popular and first of the Mario series, Mario Brothers
Action Game: Enemies emerge from the pipes, bump them from underneath
Knocking them out, then kicking them away
I'm going to start then
Endo's Turn
Mario Brothers
Endo
You shouldn't have used that power-up this early
You used it
The turtles fall over
Yea, they fall over
Yea, that's right. Only once though
He's gone over there now
He got back up
What do I do?
You're just messing around with them!
He bumped him twice
You have to kick them away when they are down
Mario Brothers
Endo
What the hell is that?!
It became purple
Go, kick'em
Now's your chance
That's the way
A coin...
What's this?
What are you doing?
Mario went like this
What happened there?
Mario Brothers
Endo
Don't get hit by the fire
Okay
It's here. That's good
Why'd you bump him again?
Didn't we tell you to not get hit by fire
Endo 900 points
You broke your promise
Mario Brothers
Hamada
Next up is Hamada, a beginner gamer. How well will he perform this time?
Wandering around the bottom won't do anything
Old man, what are you doing?
That's bad
That's so close
Hamada, why are you only sticking to the bottom level?
Almost
This is so scary, Hamada-san
You can't stay on the bottom
So close, so close
You really are a gangster
Hamada 1600 points
No no, that's not it
I thought there was enough space to jump over
Tanaka 4850 points
Next up is Tanaka, who does much better than the previous two
Hosei's Mario Brothers Trial!!
Next up is Hosei, who is well-experienced in the Mario series, how well will he do?
Mario Brothers
Hosei
I remember playing this in cafes before
I don't quite remember this one
Only since Super Mario was the game about traversing the level
Yea, Super Mario was a side-scroll adventure game
Donkey Kong stayed exactly the same
True
Adventure? You know that one, don't you?
That's the one I know
Eh, what?
The level is over?
As expected from the Mario obsessed boasting Hosei,
Clearing levels without effort
I'm going to be playing this for ages you know?
That's fine
They're jumping now
Mario Brothers
Hosei
From here on, it gets more difficult
You have to bump them when they land
Only one hit, right?
Yea
Looking at this,
How could you guys lose to just turtles?
Mario Brothers
Hosei
He's so good at this
Really really good
He's not talking anymore either...
How dull!
Mario Brothers
Hosei
The devoted Hosei finally reaches the tenth level
It's already level 10, and he's been playing for almost 20 minutes
We could have just left and let him get on with it
Well done
There's no way I can beat him
Hosei 65840 points
That's impressive
Matsumoto's Mario Brothers Trial!!
Lastly is Matsumoto. How will he fare?
Honestly speaking, I've never played this before!
This one?
Mario Brothers
Matsumoto
You've not played this before?
Nope, not once
Get a move on
We told you don't bump them twice!
Uh-oh, you're in trouble
Are you for real?
I've never played it before, it's like an unknown world to me
Mario Brothers
Matsumoto
Without knowing how to play at all, Matsumoto was unfortunately beaten on level one
65840 Points
4850 points
3260 points
1610 points
900 points
Hosei
Tanaka
Matsumoto
Hamada
Endo
Mario Brothers Results
Hosei completely triumphs Mario Brothers
What did Hamada choose?
Shoving Sumo
Released in 1987
I don't know this one
What is he talking about?
I don't think there's a scoring system
Wait, what did you say?
There's no scoring
No score?
This is the first time in his life that Sakekan
looks so uneasy
But, seriously?
Let's give it a try then
Shoving Sumo
Hamada
Shoving sumo, you say
January Stage, day one
Which one am I?
Probably the white one
The one on the left
Yup, Tochiyama
That's it, Tochi
Use the d-pad or AB buttons to shove
Of course Tochiyama will be good at shoving
Or grab their loincloth
He's up near the edge
I won
Tochiyama won
You've won but I don't feel like you did much
How are we going to score this...
Just as Sakekan mentioned, this game does not have a scoring system
It's only about winning and leveling up over and over
The game doesn't end until attaining the yokozuna rank
You chose a bloody long one
The creators too must be in front of their TV
feeling completely ashamed
Begging you to stop
Released in 1984
Xevious
The retro game chosen by Hosei is Xevious
Shooting game: Use missiles to defeat enemies that
appear in the air and on land
Hamada's Xevious Trial!!
First up is the greenhorn Hamada
I remember playing this
Xevious
Hamada
Yea, this was very hard
My god, this game
I remember this, but haven't played it before
You're playing this for the first time too, right?
How about you, Hamada? Have you played this before?
Nope, never
Is this your first time playing this?
Yea, it is
But, you're quite good
Go further down a little
How do I go down?
Yup yup
That's right
If you stay at the center, you'll get hit easily
You should use the rest of the screen
The whole screen?
You sometimes have to go forward
You almost died
Tsk
This isn't Space Invaders, don't just stay at the bottom
Xevious
Hamada
What do you mean?
Go up and down
Then you can dodge the bullets
Now you're only moving horizontally
That's dangerous, so dangerous
Stop just going left and right
You're too simple, doing only what you're told
You're always like that, just like that time
Hamada 4330 points
Hosei 15750 points
Tanaka 9910 points
After that, Hosei and Tanaka both had a go at a high score
Matsumoto's Xevious Trial!!
Will Matsumoto be able to show off his Old Man Gaming skills?
The movement isn't as expected
Yea, it isn't
Xevious
Matsumoto
Good one
He's doing well
Good score
You've missed one of them
In the middle again
Can you get the next ones?
You've left one behind again
He's being hasty now
Watch out
Damn it!
I'm definitely not losing this one
Xevious
Matsumoto
When we all bought it at first, we struggled to do well at it.
I bet it was really fun though
There are also bonus ones, like ones hiding at the bottom apparently.
It looks empty, but if you shoot downwards, bases will appear
Sorry Tanaka, even though you went out of your way and told me to be careful
Matsumoto 7870 points
I already knew that
I was only trying to advise you
Xevious
Endo
Lastly is Endo. How well will he fare?
Pretend you're protecting Shikoku
Shikoku is in big trouble
Because Shikoku is in danger, you have to protect it
It's all up to you, Endo
How did Shikoku get neglected
until such a situation
Xevious
Endo
You should move horizontally
You have to focus on dodging the bullets
Anywhere you go is still dangerous
Your hometown is coming up soon
Nice nice
So bloody many are coming!
Woah, there's a lot coming, go go go
Avoid them, go go go
What the hell are these?!
You can't kill them
No way
You only can dodge them
They're not dying, you should already know that
Xevious
Endo
You're too far down
But it's too dangerous to go further ahead
Look and avoid the bullets, don't only look at a particular spot
Dodge the bullets sideways
Nooo!
Your sideways dodging was good
You can definitely get past this
Even though we've almost reached your hometown
Xevious
Endo
Ah, this...
Wait, what?
There's no way I can reach the boss
Don't think that way, keep going~ It's here again
If you can kill that, you'll probably reach the boss
What the hell?!
What should I do?!
It was difficult, suddenly so many bullets appeared
Endo 24530 points
There's no way
Endo put up a good fight in Xevious, surprisingly, he scored the highest
24530 Points
15750 points
9910 points
7870 points
4330 points
Endo
Hosei
Tanaka
Matsumoto
Hamada
Xevious Results
The next game chosen by Matsumoto, Wagan Land
Released in 1989
Wagan Land
Action game: Wagan fires sound from its mouth to stun enemies in order to pass
Matsumoto's Wagan Land Trial!!
First up is the Wagan Land loving Matsumoto
Like this
Wagan Land
Matsumoto
Wa wa
Wagan goes "wa~", right?
With this "wa~",
Use it to stun
You've killed.. It's still alive
It's not dead
When hit, enemies get stunned for a while
What?
Wagan got killed
Hang on a second
I don't remember it being like this
Wagan Land
Matsumoto
Even though he had so much confidence, he has completely forgotten how to play the game
Sadly, Matsumoto has been defeated
Matsumoto 6700 points
He was like 'Wagyaaaaaan'
Tanaka 30550 points
Hamada 8200 points
Endo 10800 points
After these three had their attempt, Tanaka managed to beat the first level and attain the high score
Hosei's Wagan Land Trial!!
Last up is the Hosei who is in peak performance today
Wagan Land
Hosei
He's good
You've probably gotten used to it by now
Hosei-san, is this your first time playing this as well?
Yea, it is
Awesome
Wagan Land
Hosei
Although it's his first time at the game, Hosei immediately understands the basics
Getting the invincibility power-up, he easily completes the first level
I'll teach you something about the game
Good job
What is this?
Wagan Land
Hosei
With great vigor, he gets another invincibility power-up and reaches the boss
It's the boss!
What's going on? I can't move at all
That was just a cut scene
What the hell... Shiritori??
It's supposed to be a quiz
Wagan Land
Hosei
Come on, beat him
Hourglass (Sunadokei) ends with "i"
"i", umm...what?
Ah, ink
Sol?
Such a word?
You've won
You've beat it
Hosei 69550 points
Nicely done
This was my first time playing this
Hosei is victorious in Wagan Land as well
69550 Points
30550 points
10800 points
8700 points
6700 points
Hosei
Tanaka
Endo
Hamada
Matsumoto
Wagan Land Results
Guys
Shall we try a game that none of us have played before?
Something that no one knows how to play
Something that no one has actually played before
Not even once
Released in 1985
Mach Rider
A new game for everyone, a racing game, Mach Rider
Hosei's Turn
First up will be Hosei
Mach Rider
Hosei
How does this work?
It's a racing game, you accelerate...
A missile is comi~ it got me
You got scattered
Sorry for not saying earlier but, you can shoot bullets at the enemies
Mach Rider
Hosei
What? There are enemies?
What? Why did I die?
There's a mirror for you to see
Really
Mirror
Mach Rider
Hosei
The enemy will be reflected in there, avoid them
Watch out for the puddles
Do they come from the front?
They approach from behind
There there, he's coming
This one isn't easy
Mach Rider
Hosei
I couldn't see it at all
"The End"
How much? 40 points?
Hosei 40 points
That's so bad
What if, whoever is last place gets flicked in the forehead by the others?
Wait, wait
We need some punishment for the loser
The last player will get flicked in the forehead as punishment
Special Rule
That's a good idea
Hosei, you got 40 right?
Wait, what? Don't just suddenly make something up
After this
Matsumoto's turn to play Mach Rider
Gaki no Tsukai news!
The newest production directed by Hitoshi Matsumoto, number 4, coming soon
Matsumoto's Turn Mach Rider Challenge!!
Will Matsumoto be able to do well in the difficult retro game, Mach Rider?
If only they didn't come from behind
Mach Rider
Matsumoto
Annoying isn't it
He's here
What the hell
There are 4 numbers which represent gear
Gear
Mach Rider
Matsumoto
How do you change gears?
Using the up and down buttons
I see
Look out for th~
He'll definitely hit you from the back
Mach Rider
Matsumoto
You don't die when you bump him from behind
What happened?
Wha?
How much did I get?
Why did it end?
Matsumoto 240 points
240 points
How much did you get again?
40 points
Tanaka 620 points
Hamada 520 points
Endo 2410 points
Although the remaining three others were struggling to play, in the end they all beat Hosei's 40 points
HOSEI PUNISHMENT!
Some people are awesome at doing this
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
I used to be good at it
He hurt himself...
It happens
It does.
If you're good at it, you're good
Sorry
As expected
Oy you!
What happened?
He used his knuckle!