Edited by:
Not_BigM
Original subs by:
Uzumakietana
Before the filming for Gaki no Tsukai starts,
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
the cast is relaxing backstage
However, one man is nowhere to be seen
Cocorico
Yamasaki Hosei
Tanaka Naoki
Endo Shozo
Good Morning
Excuse me... From Matsumoto-san...
Downtown Manager
Orita Naoya
What could it be?
Excuse me
Why isn't Matsumoto coming here himself?
Well, I was called to do this...
Um, sorry but you voice is so small, I can't here you
After all these years, why are you still like that?
Well, I was called. Yes
What is this...
I don't understand
Pretty long, isn't it?
The hell is this?
"People like yourselves"
"beings of low sexual experience"
"Your experience with women"
"has been postponed since birth"
"Your lack of swag"
"..is ridiculous"
"Therefore, the new technician of the ways of the bed"
"is to teach you how to become skillful"
This seems fishy
"You are to arrive at the place appointed in this map"
The map ratio is 1:2500
This doesn't make any sense, look at this!
Here
Chiba
Tokyo
Here's Chiba, here's Tokyo, and then it says "HERE!!"
Wow...
Here, if you would please
You can read this map?
Yes, it's fine
Huh, incredible
That's really amazing
Orita doesn't seem very enthusiastic to be doing this
Right
Where is it?
We've come quite far already
Yeah
Could you really read that map?
Yeah, really, amazing
What's this here?
Who..?
Matsumoto-San?
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hello!
Good Day!
So you've come, CHERRY BOY!
C'mere
He got everyone to come here..
Everyone's married...
The adult cherry boys have arrived!
Why are you so mad?
How is it?
Yes?
You @$!& your wife?
Guys who @$!& their wives, raise your hands!
What is the reason for Matsumoto's fury!?
Anyway, your, um...
Till now, have you seen a woman's #%@!
Yes
With this attitude
I've been working on this since last month
Eh, what so you mean by attitude?
Today, my technique is invincible
And I'm going to show you
Matsumoto today will show off his technique
The kind of spice
Am I Michael Douglas?
The Japanese version would be Hitoshi Matsumoto
There's a prize for the winner, right?
What is this? Don't speak to me with disrespect
Have a look at this!
That's a lot of mannequins
There are 30 mannequins with bras, waiting for you
Yes, yes, yes
This is a bra unhooking contest
That's @!#$
I'm 100% unbeatable
No, but...
You can't win!
That is, well...
$#%! doesn't have anything to do with this
It doesn't
There's a severe punishment for the loser
This guy's an idiot
Eh?
It would really suck to get this punishment
I'd want to go home
I don't understand the point
What do you mean "you don't understand the point"
Stupid!
This is the longest running program after Shoten!
I know that...
When you think about it, bra unhooking is a good theme for a competition
But I don't get it
I'm so good you'd think I'd win even if I was sick
What's the point?
No one can beat me with these 30 here
You're really confident?
I have confidence!
I'm confident, but.. Anyway, I...
But, because of the punishment I really don't want to
It's like that for everyone!
The contestants will single handedly remove the 30 mannequin's bras over 50 meters.
For the slowest time a batsu game awaits!
Rules
Well then, we'll start with Endo
No way!
It would definitely be you
Why Endo, of all people?
Being first is too much
You've been given this position
Are you any good at this?
Usually I... um...
Did I just say "usually I..."
With Chiaki's bra
Please stop!
It's bad to say her name, stop it
Let's stop
But how many times have you taken off her bra?
This doesn't concern her but you're making her look bad
We need to keep up the image for the kids
What kind of woman does that make her...
You shouldn't mention it
That's no good
No, are you usually one to take them off fast?
Well, since I used to be quite a bachelor...
I'm more like... "Take them off" kind of type
Endo who makes women take off their own bras
What is his true skill level!?
And so, Endo!
Yeah!
Are you ready?
All OK!
Then, Endo get ready!
Set!
I'm king of nervous!
Ah, that's bad
It's bad!
Slow, slow!
He's stuck there
He's getting stuck there too
He's freezing
He froze there too
The staff did this before
Around 30 seconds seems like the best
Oh, is that so?
So 30 seconds is excellent
His left hand is going to sleep
Right. Bad, bad bad...
This is not good
That's because he's used to just telling them to do it.
Exactly
Ah, no good
He doesn't take them off himself
He's loosening them with his fingers
He is
Ugh, he still hasn't done half, right?
He's getting a bit more use to it
Doing it one handed
Hm, but still...
I wonder why?
Oh, he messed up!
HE'S SLOW!
This is awful
It is, isn't it?
Isn't that kind of harsh?
I think this is pretty bad
Ugh, you're slow, slow!
And so the time is...
1 minute 17.69 seconds.
Endo
Isn't that too slow?
This is quite exhausting, isn't it?
Is it hard?
It's very hard
I must say, this is quite bad
Really?
Yes
But isn't it like that?
Really
I could take panties off faster
Seriously?
I could take them off with my feet like this
That's a bit extreme
Amazing
It's quite extreme
What kind of $%#@ do you do?
Next up is HAMADA MASATOSHI!
Go ahead
Oh, Hamada-san?
I'm second?
Second it is
Yeah but, well, this is...
I just have a feeling I'll be slow
Right?
Hamada-san's style would be more like ripping them off
There should be no ripping
The bra-ripping super-sadist Hamada!
What is his exciting technique?
Hamada, are you ready?
Sure!
On your mark!
Set!
Endo
I don't know about this guy...
Oh! Fast!
That's fast!
Fast, as expected
Super fast!
As I thought
He's fast!
As I expected!
"As you expected"?
That's impressive!
He's really keeping his pace
Well, this is..
Eh, what does this mean?
Ah, but he's fast!
What's the meaning of this?
Well, because after all...
*Kenken is a puzzle game
He's the best at kenken
He's stripping them so recklessly
Amazing
Have a look at that face...
Such an obscene face he's making!
With a perverted face... fast...
So fast all the time
He has no inhibitions
As expected
He got confident
He's the worst!
So very fast!
Looks like a Hannya mask
He seems happy
Wow, amazing!
He's really done it!
Incredible!
This is tiring!
48.67 seconds!
Ah, thanks!
Hamada
Wow, awesome!
I thought Hamada would be the second fastest, after me
Why would you think that!?
Somehow
You didn't know the technique?
I did it twice
the unhooking
The old guy from Wacoal is confused.
*Wacoal is a lingerie company
He's confused?
Even the emotionless mannequins laughed
He was just that amazing
That would make anyone happy
So, up next shall be... YAMAZAKI!!
Now I'm feeling kind of nervous
Zaki-San!
I think he's going to do the worst
You think?
Well, I somehow have that feeling
I see
You're right, I'm not that used to taking them off either
Oh!
I'm the Endo type as well
What do you mean?
Right
"Take em off"
Do you understand bras at all?
I'm fine with that
Yamazaki, who usually tells women to "take them off!" takes on the challenge
Ah, he's going barefoot?
He was wearing sandals...
He was
He took them off so it won't hurt
So, Yama-Chan, ready!
Set!
Hamada
Endo
Here he goes
Huh? Uh, he's slow
This is...
Slow!
Is this slow?
How is he doing?
Did he get the hang of it?
He's certainly slower than Hamada-san but what about me?
No, he's faster than Endo
No way! I must have been really slow...
Endo... That's right
Had he done one third...  ah, half of them already?
Half, maybe
Y'know...
So far he's been doing better than expected!
He might be faster than me even
It's true
See?
Huh?
He struggled a bit...
He is faster than me
He might be fast
Eh? Seriously?
Faster than me
Wait a minute!
Yama-chan, it's your time!
You did great!
Your time is...
48.10 seconds!
YES!
Yamazaki
Great!
Current leader!
Looking at this, it seems Endo is in trouble
This ain't good
Doesn't look good for you, Endo
Still, Tanaka is probably going to be really bad
Is that so?
I think Tanaka will do the worst
Really?
I'm the type to take them off myself
Oh, you are?
Yes!
It's just that I...
I'm sure liking to do it is enough
Experience is the difference
Different experience
Ah, I see
If Downtown is "heavy-speed" ...
I would be "minimum speed"
Tanaka, who in his own experience, is "minimum-speed" with women
How is he going to do?
So Tanaka, are you ready?
I'm OK!
If he gets more than one minute he's out, right?
What's up with Cocorico?
No, there's no such thing!
So then Tanaka, get ready!
Hamada
Yamazaki
Endo
Set!
Just now, Endo was...
Tanaka is...
Look!
But this...
There's no way he's going to get a good time
This is kind of good, its great! You're really skilled
This is, um...
Ah, he picked up the pace!
Yes, well... ah...
He's making up for a little
A little bit
With that start I wonder if it helps
But... but...
Finally he... hahaha!
But... Tanaka!
I won't be losing this!
Wait, what, how's this compared to me?
Looking bad for Tanaka, eh?
Tanaka is in trouble
Tanaka is heading towards danger
Tanaka... it's not going too well
Tanaka is doing quite badly
Tanaka, bad...
It didn't come off!
No good!
It might be he's lacking in physical strength
He's taking long!
I wonder what his time will be?
1 minute, 18.48 seconds!
Tanaka
Endo
The worst among the the group!
You had a really tight match there, Cocorico
Yes, well, but his legs did the weirdest thing back there
I've never seen a man sprain his ankle while taking off bras before
Did I seriously take that long?
There's no benefit to going through this!
But stripping them is cool!
Well, it is pretty manly
Manly and cool!
The first one was awful though
Well, the first..
You did it like "katakatakatakata!"
I didn't know how to approach it
I was lost on which approach to go for
No, no...
I was thinking of the entry
I'm sorry...
Yamazaki
Tanaka
Endo
Hamada
Results so far
Currently Tanaka has the lowest ranking. After this the moody Matsumoto will challenge them all in the field of bra unhooking!
I don't truly understand what you're saying here
Yes
It seems like I'll just do this so you will look up too me
Seriously?
I think that's how it shall be
How many seconds would it take you?
I think 30 seconds would be where I draw the line
Under 30!?
EH!?
Sorry, but I'm the technician
No need to apologize, really...
We don't have your result yet
This is a technician?
What that supposed to mean?
This is kind of embarrassing for Cocorico
There's something going on here
Did bra unhooking skills go down after our generation?
The hooks have moved to the front
We're the skillful generation
Let's move on
Is he really not kidding?
Matsumoto-san, get ready
Time to show us!
It is, right?
Alright, understood
Why this outfit, I don't understand...
I'll be going then
Good luck
Thank you
Ah, he just walked off casually
Matsumoto, with his 30 second limit, will now show his divine display of talent!
Alright, Matsumoto-san!
Yes!
What are you rolling your sleeves up for?
No-one's done it until now
Anyhow, I thought I'd show you my record
Ah, I see
Go ahead and show us then!
Yes please, go ahead
Matsumoto-san on your mark!
Get set!
His stance...
Yamazaki
Tanaka
Endo
Hamada
Isn't that just fantastic?
Indeed
Is he really that fast?
It's not that different from Yamazaki
It really is similar
What?
Oh, how embarrassing!
No, Ma-chan recovered
Well, yes
How can this be
Isn't this pure genius?
This is skill
He'll surely get first place like this
So it seems
Is he faster than Yama-chan?
NNNYEEEAAAH!
No, that is...
Yamazaki
Best time so far
Matsumoto-san's time is...
WOW!
47.02 seconds!
Mastumoto
YE-
That's kind of half-assed
Really, you!
It's true you're number 1 among us, but...
But that one...
What?
"That one"?
Anyway, I hate it.
It's a mannequin!
WHAAAAT!?
I've never done something like this
Here it comes
There was only that one camera over there
Yes
There was
It's normal to get super nervous there...
He's an idiot
Camera
I couldn't get it to work there
You couldn't
That was the worst among all 30 of them
True
We agreed to do out best
Aside from that one thing I'm number one, right?
No, but you did say you'd do it under 30 seconds
He did
So that would mean that Mastomoto-San...
Matsumoto-san should get the batsu game after all
What the hell?
Are you #@$!, you idiot!
No way in hell!
That's how it is
So this mean, with his pace, Tanaka!
Whaaat?
BATSU GAME!
No way, seriously? I don't want to do it
TANAKA BATSU GAME!!
Matsumoto-san, what is the punishment?
Well, the batsu game is, as the title suggests...
It's called: "aimsless journey by train"
"aimless train..."
The "burari" here means bra
It will have something to do with a bra
You will be boarding the Enoden train in the evening...
Enoden?
Yes, wearing a bra
*burabura = aimlessly
bura = bra
And you'll wander around
Are you serious?
It's a very crowded location
Exactly!
It is, yes
I really hate this!
It's crazy!
Why do I have to look like a total weirdo doing that?
Is this seriously for real?
When I think about it, I thought I did bad
I don't get the punishment but my time was still bad
They go together
That's right
On the other hand, Downtown is kinda giving off a pervy vibe
That is true
I've arrived in Kamakura
Incredible isn't it. There are lots of stores around here
Why do I have to do this batsu game?
I really do not understand
Since I was made to wear a bra...
I feel a  bit gross
But, a cuter bra would have been nicer
Cocorico Tanaka
Batsu Game
Well aside from this slight misfortune
I'm going to wander around
*He can't go on the train wearing just underwear
He's buying "pigeon shortbread" as a souvenir for 4 people
Excuse me, I'm looking for souvenirs for 10,000 yen
Hello!
This is a rickshaw, isn't it?
Feels great
What a wonderful feeling
Very nice
Here we have the famous bookstore
I think I want to wander further
Hello
Hello, good day...
Ah, thank you, thank you
Hello
As expected, it's the summer holiday
There are kids running around everywhere
This is a tasteful shop, don't you think?
How long has the place existed?
For three generations
Three generations?
What a splendid store
I'm feeling sort of nostalgic for the Japanese summer
How cute!
Cute, indeed
Hello there
I always watch you on TV!
Oh, thank you!
Thank you very much!
Hello
I wouldn't have thought this would be so sweet
"Kamakura Surugaya-san"...
It's a Japanese confectionery
You're doing good there
Oh, really?
Yes, really
Is it your first time?
It's my first time
You're good!
Tanaka's work
Chef's work
It's delicious!
*He can't go on the train wearing just underwear
Ever since I was small I've felt
being close to a big ocean like this
really makes you feel quite insignificant
After all, this isn't something I can do
take a punishment like this
just because I am slow at unhooking bras
Since I don't strip them off myself
A guy who is slow at taking off bras is really uncool
Doing it is just...
Taking them off your wife by force just seems bad to me
I just don't seem to be able to do it