TPF
TODAY, A CERTAIN MAN'S SPECIAL SEGMENT
Good morning.
Wait a minute.
Nobody told me we would start outside.
I'm only wearing two layers.
You're lightly dressed.
Very lightly.
There's only a slight breeze, but...
Endo isn't here, right?
Yeah, well, he wasn't here in the first place.
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Cocorico
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hosei
No, no.
He's here but...
Since last year and the year before that, he's been gone since then.
You weren't here for a while either.
I was!
I'm here.
All this time, the 3 of us have been waiting around.
All five of us are here today so...
Maybe he forgot.
Endo wanted to be Mori Shinichi once again.
Oh no, we don't need that.
He's really pushing it too far.
It had a short span.
He's pushing it so far that
Mori-san is going to get fed up with this!
Well actually, most of them are already dead.
Last Year's Broadcast
Pushing it forward Mori Shinichi Segment
Since last year, Endo really liked it and
has continued pushing it forward, the Mori Shinichi Segment
Starred in the popular talk show Uchi Iku!?
Last time, he starred in the popular talk show "Uchi Iku!?"
What will he do this time...?
This time, he wants to have a
dinner show as Mori Shinichi.
Mori-san has probably done dinner shows before,
Endo's Attempt
Fake Mori Shinichi will do a Dinner Show
we should just let the real one handle it.
Yes, that would be good, however,
We managed to do it at such an amazing hotel!
Everything is ready to go.
I know what this is.
This is some sort of tie-up with the hotel,
that's why we started recording outside...
Tonight, the Dinner Show of Dreams Begins!
And so, tonight, Mori Shinichi will take us to the world of dreams.
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents:
Down Town's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Translator:
Typesetter:
Proofreader:
J-Lan
Otviss
Christian
**We also have Facebook and Twitter.**
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
____________________________________________________________________
If you ever see this video being distributed online but not by us, keep in mind that on Youtube
individuals may make money off of sharing fansubs like this that are not their own. Please go back and
support the original creators. Fansubbing is voluntary and is not meant to generate profit. You can
download episodes on our website instead. Thanks for watching!
!!
The guests are already in.
By the way,
I actually don't have much
experience with dinner shows.
A while ago, I went to Seiko-chan's Dinner Show
A while ago?
Ah, over there.
So it's like this?
It's great, right? There's food too...
You're right.
Doesn't the show normally start after eating?
It's not while you're eating.
There's a lot of guests...
They all look like madams.
They're all very fancy.
All I see is women.
They're all women.
Then it was limited to women.
Everyone, we thank you for your patience.
Mori Shinichi's Special Dinner Show begins.
The Dinner Show Begins
Hey, old man.
One more.
Looks like this part is a play.
I think you're drinking too much again.
As usual, you run a gloomy place.
You say that, but aren't you the one coming here every night?
Port Town Blues
I stand straight and look across the strait
Today too, the steam whistle sounds in the distance
Give back to me the night I gave you
At the port, the port of Hakodate, it rains
Wait a minute, he's not singing.
He's just lip syncing.
He showed up rather early.
Mayai comin'?
Welcome, of course!
What did he say?
I couldn't quite catch that.
He's putting too much force on his face.
He can't pronounce things correctly.
I don't need anything right now.
As you wish. Hey, mister.
You don't look like you're from these parts. Are you a traveler?
Yes, I'm in the middle of a journey,
for a number of reasons.
Is that so?
In order to repent for your sins, you left your beloved daughter behind and decided to travel alone...
or something like that, right?
What? You're gonna ignore me?
Somebody!
Somebody help me!
What's wrong, young lady?
What is it?
Hey!
I knew you'd come here!
Get over here!
Hey miss, we're really bored.
Come play with us.
No, please stop!
Hey, you!
Stop that right now!
Shut up!
Hey, guys! Let's get her out of here.
Sdop!
Huh?
Shin-chan!
It's hard to make out what he says.
Can't you see this young lady doesn't like you?
Please let go of her.
I don't know where you came from but,
if you don't want to get hurt, shut-
No way.
I didn't want to get involved but,
pretending to be just a bystander...
will stray a person from the path of righteousness.
He missed.
Hurry up and
get lost!
Don't get ahead of yourself!
Amazing.
Everyone knows, the timing.
Here they come.
Kill him!
Yeah!
But...
His face stopped looking like Mori Shinichi.
Wait, he didn't hit him.
Argh!
His face is too much.
He's way too strong.
There's no feeling of danger at all.
I agree.
Could it be? Father?
What?
That sword looks exactly like the one my father used.
That kind of twist?
It's you, isn't it, father?
I do not...
have a daughter.
What are you saying!? Didn't you say you left your daughter behind to go on a journey!?
Father, it's me, Koyuki!
I went on a journey to find you.
Father...
Let's live together again.
Koyuki-san, I will...
continue my journey until I repent my sins.
However, if she found it in herself to forgive me one day, then...
I want my live together...
They're taking a lot of pictures.
with my daughter.
It's that kind of moment.
I guess it's fine to take pictures.
Traveler...
Could you at least tell me where you're heading?
Erimo...
The Cape of Erimo is where I'm headed.
Cape Erimo
Hm?
Shouldn't he be
doing this in the second half?
Yeah, I thought he would.
It wasn't just a play?
He's gonna sing now.
Everyone has their own penlights.
They knew beforehand.
Right.
At the northern towns they've begun using their stoves
This is when he actually looks like him.
He gets very close.
to burn away their sorrows, it seems
But,
if you listen to the real one it sounds completely different.
While worrying about meaningless things
His face is gradually starting to lose form.
we end up growing old and frail
All those months and years spent in silence
Very nice fan service.
Eh?
Let's gather all and warm them up.
It's amazing.
This is starting to feel like Taishu Engeki*
*A type of theater performance, there's a dance portion in the show and fans usually approach the performers to give them gifts such as money.
Spring in Erimo is just spring with nothing else.
He has loads of money.
What the hell...
He has too much money.
Lots of money.
Whoa, that's cool.
Even if we dislike the way we live, we continue living
Shin-chan...
So let's just keep smiling silently
Whoa, very nice.
Holding up your guard while only talking
Ah, what a coward it makes one look
He's lip syncing again.
Spring in Erimo is just spring with nothing else.
Hello, good afternoon.
Good afternoon!
I'm Mori Shinichi.
No he's not!
That's wrong.
You're not.
He straight-up said it.
He straight-up lied.
I made my debut back in
the year 1965.
Showa 40.
And this year, it's been exactly
51 years since my debut.
51 years is just right, don't you think?
They're loving him.
In the corporate world, it would mean I'm a section chief.
Except, instead of drinking milk, it would be sake.
They're making me laugh.
The people around us are making it funny.
However,
it's really taken
a long time to get here.
You did your best!
No, no...
It took a long time, but...
From now on, without losing my "ki" (spirit),
I will try to do my best.
That's because.
If I lost a "ki" (tree), I'd become Hayashi ("woods").
Lose one more "ki", and it's just "Moku" (wood).
Okay, that was pretty good.
Good afternoon, I'm Moku Shinichi.
I'm kidding.
He's kidding.
Tonight, please support me.
Now then.
Everyone, there's someone I want you to meet.
It's my son, please welcome him!
Good afternoon!
This is my son, however...
His name is Umi Wataru.
Hey, introduce yourself.
Umi Wataru...
Is everyone ready?
He's really excited.
Here we go!
It's wide and big.
The Pacific Ocean~
It's fierce and relentless.
The Sea of Japan~
Umi Umi Umi Umi...
Umi Wataru~
The World of Enka's Prince of the Stormy Seas
I'm Umi Wataru.
Pleased to be here!
Thank you, thank you.
Why are you getting more cheering than me?
Also, stop looking down on people like that.
It's only because I'm taller than you Mori-sensei.
Anyway,
at first glance, he might look like he messes around.
But he's actually a very reliable man.
Without real heart, you can't sing enka.
That's why I'm guiding him to become an enka singer.
As my successor.
He messed up with that pause.
If you want, go ahead
and sing to us.
I will, thank you.
Wataru's Banbara Beat
No, no, no, no.
Looks like this is gonna be lip syncing too.
I'm pretty sure.
Ban Ban Ban Bara Ban Ban Ban (Wataru)
Why are they showing us this?
The western sky is shining bright
The eastern sky is shining too
Winter's starry night sky is what those with dreams
(Breaks out in a completely different song)
What the hell?
What the hell...
Look up to see
How?
Is this a medley?
I don't think it's a medley.
That surprised me.
Only one song.
It just suddenly changed, right?
Thank you.
Umi Wataru...
Looks like the first part might be over.
So the first half is over?
I really just want to go home.
Yeah, since the very beginning.
The Dinner Show's Second Half Begins
Mori Shinichi's Dinner Show's second half begins.
Everyone, good afternoon.
Good afternoon.
From here on,
I, Tarajima Towako, will be your host.
No, don't know her.
She looks like she's real.
Let's get the fun started
with a special talk corner segment.
She sounds like a real host.
I agree.
It's Mori Shinichi, welcome.
Mori-san, thank you for being here.
He just casually walks out.
Well...
I've known Towako for a long time, about 30 years, right?
That's right.
She's just his woman.
At this year's dinner show,
I've been looking forward so much
to this meeting with Shinichi-san...
Last night, I couldn't sleep at all.
Oh, really?
Did you really not sleep at all?
No,
I slept about 8 hours.
You did sleep.
Now then, at last,
it's time to begin our Q&A corner.
Everyone, please
if any of you have a question, go ahead and
raise your hand!
A lot of guests raised their hands.
First, the lady with the red scarf, please.
Hello,
um...
Last year, the rugby player Goromaru had a pose
that was really popular.
Mori-san, just like Goromaru,
On that stage,
I wanted to ask if you could show us your routine.
I would love if you could show us.
Uh...my routine?
Yes, please.
Mori-san is a real big shot so he must have his own routine.
Just like when we did it,
he probably doesn't know
what they're gonna ask him.
My routine then...
This is all ad-lib.
I usually...
I do everything starting with my left.
Well then,
Could you show us what
"starting with your left" looks like?
Show you!?
Yes.
Alright, uh...
Show you!?
Show the left thing!?
Um...
He's not Mori-san anymore.
It would be...
Show it?
Something like...
With the left side.
Everything with my left side, I'm telling you.
It doesn't make sense.
While eating, I'm right-handed so as I'm about to eat...
I begin first with my left.
Since it's my routine, I start with the left.
After that, I continue with my right.
I do everything starting with the left side.
I want to see that.
What did you think, everyone?
This is Mori Shinichi's routine,
doing everything starting with the left side.
Now then,
let's have Mori-san go back to what he knows and
and have him sing...
that song that everyone loves.
If you please.
Winter's Riviera
8th Grade - School Field Trip
It's a slideshow.
Is that picture for real?
Why from the 8th grade?
8th Grade - School Field Trip
9th Grade - At the graduation ceremony
9th grade...
That's obviously fake.
He hasn't changed at all.
Age 20 - Coming-of-age ceremony at the public hall.
Why does he look so thin?
Age 21 - Getting his driver's license
He's in front of a Civic!!
Age 22 - Driving Trip - At Lake Akan
It was an important moment.
After just one year.
They're at age 22 but they haven't shown his debut.
Are they aware of that?
Age 23 - Driving Trip - At Kurobe Gorge
They were important.
There were many driving trips.
He drived a lot.
Yeah, it's all driving trips.
For real.
Age 23 - Driving Trip - At Kurobe Gorge
Age 24 - Driving Trip - At Gassan Ski Resort
Another driving trip...
They're all driving trips.
It actually doesn't look weird.
Whose pictures are these anyway?
Age 25 - At the office entrance.
No, no.
Enough with his 20s!
Yeah.
It's only about his 20s.
Age 26 - At the training with the office's baseball team
26 years old.
Why did they only show that?
When one is having so much fun,
time goes by very quickly.
It seems it's already time to say goodbye.
To finish, there's one more song, but before that...
There's one more person I want to introduce.
She's my cherished treasure.
Come.
They're mixing up people from different agencies.
Hello, nice to meet you.
My name is Kosakura Barbara Harumi.
I'm very happy to be here with everyone today.
Barbara is my cherished girl.
Her grandma was Hawaiian so
that makes her half-Hawaiian.
Mori-sensei,
it wouldn't be half, it'd be quarter.
Whatever it is, quarter, water...
Well, anyway, she's nice isn't she...
This will be the last one
Together with Barbara and...
everyone, please stand up.
I want to sing that song.
Mother Firefly
Why is Barbara singing too?
Look.
Umi Wataru is here too.
It's the Mori family.
It's a mix from different agencies.
When the sea calls out, a man's heart burns
He turns to drink to mask the fear
So, that was everything in the slideshow?
Yeah, looks like that was it.
It was only his 20s.
That's right.
Seeing dreams of fortune, he seeks a ship
Normally, you start with your birth.
It started when he was 12 years old.
Yes, when he was around 12.
"The reckless and foolish son"
Leaving nothing but harsh words
Holding a vigil at the shore
The mother prays for her son's safe return
At cape of Erimo, that wavering light is-
the mother firefly
Everyone, we thank you very much.
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
He really likes it.
He's getting all sorts of people involved.
It just happened.
Getting them involved.
I wish this would get riskier.
You want him to get angry?
I wish he would.
You want to anger him?
I think xxxxx will.
Yeah, xxxxx would.