Timer: GakiDave Translator: senor_wristband
First time on Gaki no tsukai ya arahende
1000 yen transvestite meetup!
I get what we're doing today.
This is a pain in the ass.
With a budget of 1000 yen, we will buy items from a 100 yen store
in order to become a beautiful crossdresser.
This isn't rude right?
And then finally, drag queen Bourbonne will decide who the prettiest one is.
This problem is, we only have 1000 yen to work with.
Yeah that's true, it seems undoable.
There's a lot of stuff you can get for 100 yen,
so we gotta manage with our 1000 yen.
Is the makeup included in that?
Everything is.
This time, it's not just us.
Let's introduce our guests.
Good Morning!
Viking and Heipo!
A beautiful crossdresser?
Yes exactly!
I understand this.
Last time we did some crossdressing stuff,
He was really good at it.
yeah uh Suga-san, Suga-san,
wait I'm confused!
He's got it in the bag.
Each member's 100 yen shopping text
What should I do ... Something Idol-ish?
But deciding - something Idol-ish is...
I have to decide on a clothing style.
This is...
Black garbage bag
Is 70 litres big?
In terms of the size
Let's make a costume with this.
What's this?
This nail ...
You put this on nails right?
Nail parts
Putting this on the ear lobes, like this...
...that would be good right?
It would work, right?
I have an image in my mind.
Something a little flashy.
I'm thinking of something like Britney Spears.
They have wigs! There's wigs after all.
500 yen ...
Are these the only wigs?
But the wig is essential
This is - Woah! Amazing!
It makes such a difference with the wig.
How should I go about shopping here?
I have absolutely no vision here.
What's this?
Stool covers...
This part could work for the head or something.
Look, this is good.
Wig
This with that hat,
I can have come down the sides like this.
I need two of them.
Is 1000 yen really enough for this?
I have this image of a masked beauty.
A flowery, kimono-style look
I want to wear a Hakama actually.
TN: Hakama are like traditional Japanese trousers.
On top of the kimono...
...somehow build on this.
Then let's do the Hakama!
Something, like a Gyaru or Lolita.
Easy to shop for.
Hair... I gotta do something about my head.
Pink knitting yarn
Yarn could be good.
Something flashy is probably good.
Will this be enough?
I think makeup is important.
A flashy woman would be good.
A cabaret style,
Eye shadow...
I'm interested in trying this,
Eye shadow
This has glitter in it.
Glitter is no good, for a flashy crossdresser.
Last time on a shoot, we had a very pretty crossdresser on as a guest.
I'm keeping that image in mind.
Table cloths
They have table cloths,
Ah, this is pretty, sort of...
...if I put two together it could work.
Do you have a theme in mind?
Something Latin, something bright and cheerful.
I don't know- AH this is a hat!
Seat covers
This is a mesh seat cover.
How's this?
Is it bad? Look, how's this?
What, what's wrong with it?!
Damn it, I don't wanna do this!
I have no idea.
Someone help me, what do I do here?
Is that a brassiere?
Crossdressers wear this often
Extra large ribbon
Eh? I'm wrong?
Just tell me! I have no idea.
After shopping, dressed in their finest, they head for a cafe.
What kind of crossdresser have they transformed into?
Cafe Meeting Spot
What is it?!
You're not that important.
Makes me so angry, honestly.
Tablecloths (x2)
Hairband
Eyebrow
Lipgloss
Color | Artificial lavender
Ah I just hate it
Could I take your ord-
Coffee of course!
Don't treat me like a moron!
Hurry up and get it!
What is this, seriously,
They just don't care about punctuality.
Just morons everywhere honestly.
I cannot believe this. I genuinely cannot believe this.
Sorry for the wait.
Ashtray. Bring an ashtray here, hurry.
They're all so clueless, honestly.
So late, honestly.
It's way cold!
You're late!
You're too early, you are!
What are you saying, I'm here on time!
Well you're supposed to wait for me.
Pink hair thread
Tote bag
Suit storage bag
Bath boots
Lip gloss
Black tights
Table mat
There was traffic!
Where did you come from?
Where?!
Where uhhh - Asakusa!
There's no traffic there.
Asakusa has so much traffic!
Don't go to Asakusa then!
I'm pissed off cause of the traffic!
Hurry up and decide on a drink.
Coffee of course!
Order it then!
Coffee please! Hurry up!
They're so late, honestly.
So late! Making us wait, honestly.
What were you doing in Asakusa?
Asakusa- that thing, you know...
I was looking at dogs.
You can look at dogs anywhere!
Askauksa has cute dogs.
The hell would I know!
What?!
You're late!
Wait a minute!
Only uglies here!
What the hell are these hags?
After all that time?
Shower cap
Wig
Fake Eyelashes
Ankle socks|Body Towel
Lip gloss
Hurry up and sit!
Hold on, dondake? DONDAKEEEE!!!!!
TN: Dondake is a slang exclamation like "SHEESH" is for zoomers now I think.
So bloody ugly!
What about you!
Wait a second
I don't want to be grouped in with you!
What are you ordering?
COFFEE OF COURSE! HURRY THE FUCK UP PLEASE!
Hurry up!
What do you eat normally?
What's your favourite?
I like corn.
I like CORN!
It's making me laugh!
What are you laughing at?
What do you like to eat?
Tsukemen (cold Chinese noodles)
Which is it?!
Hot or cold?
I like the hot tsukemen more.
That kind?!
You like shit noodles.
Yeah well
Hurry up and bring it!
You guys are slow godammit!
Don't mess with me!
I'll go home!
Sorry for the wait.
Seriously you...
You, raggedy ass.
You're the most rageddy ass!
Theme! What's your theme!
You can tell just by looking!
I'm traditional Japanese.
I'm from Kyoto.
That's dirty!
What are you?
It's Thelma Aoyama.
Thelma Aoyama.
What is that?
Seriously, it is pretty terrible.
Do you even want to do this?
Of course I want to do this!
You are just terrible.
What is it?!
What the hell are you wearing?
I left at bath time!
You guys are copying each other!
I came here straight from the bath!
You're the one copying me!
Wait, hold on wait,
Our tops are matching too!
You two!
You...
You guys are copying each other.
What, cut it out.
That's why they made come here third.
Is the variation GONNA BE OKAY?
What are they doing, so late.
They should hurry up, honestly.
I don't want to be with these ugly hags.
You're one to talk.
Welcome, good evening.
YOU'RE LATE!
What the hell were you doing?
Barefoot?!
Don't rush me, honestly.
You're late!
I'm not late, you guys are early.
Hold on, how did you use the money?
Where did you spend it?
You guys... Didn't set your hair?
Pink stole
Wig
Eyeshadow
Torn White Cloth
Eyelashes
We did!
It's terrible! What is that on your head?
I did this, I got this done properly.
Seriously what is that?
You're the odd man out.
What do you mean odd man out?
What concept is this?
Concept? Do you have a concept?
I do.
What is it?
A beautiful witch, straight out of the bathtub.
This person is terrible.
What!
What are you?
What are you, honestly.
Well I am,
A hot pants woman.
I don't understand.
Hold on, you came here barefoot?
I told you, I was in a rush!
What is this?  What is this? Kamui?
Kamui Gaiden?
No it isn't.
What's wrong with this?
Wear proper shoes
Your shoes?!
Are you two copying each other?
Yeah these are guys are matching.
Why?
The top is matching too.
That's why he's third.
The colours are matching too
Well if we want to be pretty, we might end up matching.
Hmm? Doesn't this gathering suck?
We told them this is the meeting place right?
We did, we did.
It is unacceptable to be so non-punctual.
I just hate that.
Welcome, good evening.
You're late.
I'm not late.
What are you doing? What the hell?
Don't say "What the hell"
Don't copy the same theme as your partner!
Only I should be Tradtional Japanese!
I'M the Japanese Culture!
Are you guys from a folktale?
Folkstory? I came from Kyoto
Where the hell are you from?
You're a grandfather from a folkstory!
Grandfather?! What do you mean grandfather?
Hold on, let me see your shoes.
Show them to us!
Why do I have to show them?
Faster!
It's like this
What is that?
Socks.
What is this?
Bicycle Cover (x2)
Tablecloths (x2)
Black felt hairband
Shawl
Lip gloss
I tied my hair up bunny style today.
It's all solid...
Are you messed up in the head?
What is this?
Amazing you walked outside like that.
What is this inside?
It's felt!
There's felt inside.
What is this? You guys have no confidence.
Let's sit down.
I just hate this.
Honestly so ugly.
So ugly, so ugly.
So ugly, it's amazing.
The old man smell is intense.
It's probably the person showing the most skin.
It's you isn't it?
It's you right?
Definitely not me.
Disgusting. What is this smell? I hate it here.
Are you trying to be a surfer?
I can surf, why?
I can skateboard too.
I just like that stuff.
This guy's concept is annoying.
This guys belly-
Don't look at my belly, seriously.
I'll work it off in the summer.
I'll definitely work it off.
I don't want to be invited to this ugly people party.
(various crossdresser noises)
I don't want to be bullied.
I don't want to be singled out.
You're one to talk.
You don't have a boyfriend!
I do have one!
I have one.
You guys broke up that last time.
I got another one immediately.
What kind of man? Tell us!
He works for TV Asahi.
What?
Let's ask about this!
Does he have any TV shows?
He has a bunch.
He's a reporter.
He reports the news.
No way someone like you is dating a reporter.
Well I am.
What the hell is that?
Who is your boyfriend?
Me? I'm free.
It's a pain in the ass.
You have a boyfriend?
I do!
He's a business industry worker.
Financial Relations?
I've heard of Financial Industry before,
But Business Industry?
It's business!
He's a generally a businessman.
I don't want to hear this from a single person!
That's true.
That hurts, stop it.
Honestly if I keep talking to these hags,
I'll become a hag too.
Sorry for the wait!
Get lost! Get the fuck out of here!
I'm here!
I'm telling you get lost!
There's only pubes here!
Aluminum two-top
Yellow wig
Eyeshadow
Sponge holder (x2)
Lipstick
Gold/Silver Origami
Just a bunch of pubes!
Sorry, what is that hair?
It looks grilled.
I got it done today
You don't know?
This new hairstyle?
What's it called?
This is uhhh...
...it's...Pearl White hair.
-  What the hell is that?
- What do you mean "What the hell?!"
You're weird all over.
Look who's talking.
I'm cute of course.
Only you are horrible.
Your...
Your hairpiece is offensive.
That isn't 100 yen is it?
It's not 100 yen.
What the hell?
We're all using 100 yen stuff.
The whole thing right? The total price.
And still, you're barefoot
You're barefoot?
You walked outside like that?
Barefoot?!
What's wrong with barefoot?
And your tits.
What are those tits?
This is gum tape,
and wrapped up tissues, what's wrong with that?
You spent money there?
I didn't!
That's against the rules isn't it?
I'm telling the truth!
It's true, I didn't use it!
This guy is so annoying.
If I think about I get angry.
Don't go and make a strange character all by yourself.
It's so cold out there!
What is that?
It's an old man.
It's freezing!
I waited so long too.
These boots...
...they're short boots!
My legs are bare, and it's cold!
Black trash bags
Giant ribbon | Rose cheek
Lip gloss
Fake nails
Feather Muffler
It's messed up!
A grandmother from Naniwa?
(Old name for Osaka)
The pants are amazing.
I'm from Kansai, I came from Osaka today!
You look the same as before!
You are unchanged.
You look pretty much the same.
What the hell are you saying, honestly?
What are those shoes?
Explain!
It looks so disgustingly hand made.
Perhaps that's why he took so long.
It took me some time, look!
Stop messing around already.
Wait, the material, what is this?
Oh no, oh no!
No! Not this material!
It's that thing from "Suna No Utsuwa!"
TN: A murder detective movie from 1974.
He's a vagabond.
You should work on your hair.
Your hair is just normal.
Enough, seriously just enough.
ENOUGH ALREADY!
ME TOO!
UWAHAHAH
NO!
STOP!
Say it already!
What the hell?
Why are you acting surprised?
I thought I might talk over one of you.
(Disagreeing Crossdressers)
What the hell...
I don't want to be associated...
I think I'm the most beautiful one here.
It's me!
I think it's me, seriously.
You've got some confidence.
That guy gets zero points, right?
That guy gets zero points.
It's really awful.
Why me?
You're all over the place.
He's in a trash bag!
Is that party spray? What is that?
It's not a spray idiot.
Is that noodles?
It's obviously not noodles!
Completed
Wasn't that too long?
That was so long.
Long, too long.
I feel so bad for the server.
I'm very sorry for saying all that stuff.
S'okay.
S'okay?
Our duo kind of copied each other, we're both the traditional style.
That's a tablecloth too right?
A tablecloth?
But look, I'm in high heels. See?
You made that right?
What is that?
This is, look...
That's a boot inside?
Cause it's a 100 yen shop.
So we all just got different colour versions of that.
Just different colours.
Yeah but I put the bag over it, look.
I've got the underwear too.
Show me.
Seriously?
You bought some?
Using the leftover material.
It matches huh.
So why then didn't you show us?
What if the conversation never turned this way?
What is the point?
You'd just be wearing that at the end.
I see.
Here, crossdressing performer Bourbonne chooses the most beautiful person.
A personal touch, something you thought of yourself.
So looking at all of us, which of us became the prettiest using the 1000 yen?
Everyone is very confident.
Could you first choose the worst one?
"1000 yen crossdresser meetup"
Who is the ugliest?
Seriously consider.
Hama-chan is last.
Well, because...
There's no need for explanation.
Your face? You put just enough to look drunk.
I was cautious of putting going overboard.
Something like this I thought is too far, it's lame!
What the hell is that?
It's cute!
That's cute?
Too much, too much.
So last is Hamada, first place please.
Going by total balance,
Kotoge-kun!
It looks similar to Lady Gaga.
If that's first place what can we do.
I think Hosei-san was really confident he'd win.
Yeah, he was way more into it than us. He was so confident.
To be honest I thought I'd win.
OK, thank you very much.
Here the shoot is over...
...but Hamada notices that man is not present.
Heipo isn't here!
Heipo is... at a prank location.
He's waiting by the streetside.
In women's clothes.
Where is everyone?!
It's freezing!
Hey! Please someone, it's cold!
I'm too bareskinned, please! Please just end this!
A 60+ old man, in women's clothes?
He might end up in danger.