Hot-blooded!!
Hamada's Cram School!!
Hot-blooded!
Summer edition
Tsukitei Hosei
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Football Hour
Iwao Nozomu
Fujiwara Kazuhiro
License
Inomoto Takafumi
Fujimoto Toshifumi
Haranishi Takayuki
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
students
Headmaster
Vice
Hot-blooded! Hamada's Cram School - Summer edition!
Awaiting for our eight students...
Headmaster rugby
There are loads of activities full of love
for the headmasters, set in a summer sandy beach
Pretend-scuba-diving
What is that?
Headmaster's drum touch & go
Come on!
Don't ever stop! The no-stop club!
Fujimon is doing great, huh?
Turbulent 2nd half!!
And this week, it's time for the turbulent second half!
The headmaster's guidance isn't over
An emotional ending
Hot-blooded!!
Hamada's Cram School!!
So, what's coming next?
- Let's see...
It's time for a swimsuit fashion show
- Ohh, I like that
Take a look at this
You might like or dislike some of them
But I want you to think of the headmaster's tastes
and pick the right swimsuit for the fashion show
Get out from there and walk all the way here
- That's right
Headmaster's favorite swimsuit show
Choose a swimsuit from 8 available ones and wear it for the fashion
show. Pick one the headmaster doesn't like and you'll be punished!!
Keep in mind that it's about
how you appeal to the Headmaster
So make sure you don't pick
something he wouldn't like
Keep that in mind
- That's right
They're so quiet and don't seem so lively...
- Huh?
Maybe you gotta move some more?
- I'm getting angry...
- That's not true
Wanna move some more?
- We're good!
Is there something wrong? Anything?
Nope, we're completely fine!!
But if you gotta pick one?
- Huh
Well...
That thing in which we had to keep on moving...
Just a bit, alright?
But I don't like it
You--
- I'd say
I hate it, maybe...
You---
What can they possibly hate about all this, boss!?
They should be glad about enrolling in this cram
school, what is there to hate for them?
You don't hate it, right Endo?
Nope! I don't!!
What was that?
"Nope! I don't!!"
What's wrong with your mouth?
My mouth is full of sand, sir
- I'm fine
Go get changed
- Got it
Get ready, students!
- Got it!
The students are ready to get changed
The students are changing
Remember: pick something the headmaster won't like and you'll be punished!
Headmaster's favorite swimsuit show
Counting on ya!
Oh, I see... so he thinks you like these red stripes
Fujimon is lookin' fresh
So, what do you think? It wasn't that bad, right?
- Yeah, I guess
He looked so confident
Maybe you like flower patterns?
Ehh... what is--
Or maybe he went for the one-piece suit?
Nice
Next up
Let's see-
Do you like this... frilly thing? How do you call that?
I see...
This is quite... audacious, right?
- That's right
Normally he shouldn't wear that underneath it
- Right
It's really small, this one
It just barely covers him
Right?
I wonder what do you think of the color blue
Let's see
We have another one-piece here
- I see...
A butterfly-pattern
What do you think of it?
- I wonder how am I going to judge this show
Can the next one be your favorite one?
- This one's so tiny!
An animal print, huh...
I see, headmaster, I see
This is really something, don't you think?
- It's small
You gotta be careful wearing those, or you're out
- That's right
I see... maybe he thinks you like it
when top and bottom don't match
Could this be it?
Let's see--
So irritating
Come on
Alright, let's see what we got
I see...
- This one is pretty bold too
I see, I see...
- A star pattern...
Stars are nice, I guess
Flat-chested, but whatever
An irritating body...
-I see
Here's our last one
How about a chic swimsuit, boss?
This is horrible
- Why wearing it like that?
This guy is an idiot
He's really a moron
What's his problem?
Alright, beauties
We're done here
So, headmaster...
- Yes
What do you think of them?
Well...
Can I just say the one I don't like?
- Of course
Who will be chosen as the most hated swimsuit wearer!?
It's Tsukitei Hosei!
What a shame!
I like them when they match
If they don't I really don't...
Makes sense
- Yeah
I think it's not something acceptable in our society, today
- Yeah, it's old stuff
It didn't last long
- It really didn't
I'm terribly sorry!!
- Huh? What's wrong?
And you're out
Out, out, out
Forgive me, headmaster!
- 100% out
What should we do with him?
Ah, let's see...
When I blow the whistle, start moving as much as you can
- This is hell...
I'll blow it again when it'll be over
Don't make that face
That's not the spirit
- You should be grateful for this
How do you feel?
Do you want him to forgive you?
Principal...
I'm terribly sorry!
- Nope, you're out
Alright, let's start!
Get ready...
- Oh my
Don't ever stop! The no-stop club!
Show us a new you
We've already seen that
That's--
Something new, please
We've already seen that
There's not a single new move
Another pattern, please
I feel like I've seen this one too
He has no idea what to do
By the way, principal...
- Yes?
Who was the second worst one?
The second, huh...
- Yep
If I have to say it, I don't like one-piece swimsuit...
- I see
Oh, yeah? I felt like you didn't like 'em
- That's right
So it could have been Haranishi or Inomoto
- Yeah, I think so
But they're safe
- Barely, but yes
If Tsukitei wasn't there, one of them would have lost
- That's right, lucky for them
I just saw something new
- Tsukitei is...
He just found a new pattern!
What face is he making?!
That's a face I've never seen on him
He's almost broken
Don't you think there could be more to come?
Oh my
My stomach hurts
I'm dying
- He's stopping!
A new one!
Oh my...
Your moves are too small
- He can't anymore
Go over there, over that tent!
Move towards it, come on
Just like that, these are the moves I want
It's a punishment, we can't help him
He looks like a pervert, principal
He's descending into madness
That's a full fledged pervert
Now--
Come back here, full speed!!
He just became Egashira-san
Move some more!!
I'm laughing so much it hurts
Keep on moving
He's moving his feet
That's the best he can do
That's incredible
- It's his last move
Come on!
He became a beached sea turtle
He's a turtle
He won't stop, though
It's over
We're done
Nice, huh?
- That was risky
So, anything else?
Of course there's still more...
But what do you think
About seeing the backside of a comedian like this?
this backside is what we're getting
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION
WEBSITE: shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
FACEBOOK: fb.com/shionnotsukai
TWITTER: twitter.com/shionnotsukai
KO-FI: ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
PATREON: patreon.com/shionnotsukai
Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Hot-blooded! Hamada's Cram School! Ep.2, 2nd half
He becomes a demon because of his love for them
Hot-blooded!
Hamada's Cram School!
Alright, vice
- Yes
What are we doing next?
- Our next step...
Will be a training with the sea
Oh, I see
Can you see that floating island over there?
Yes
For now, I want you to swim towards it
And then I'll tell you what to do
Alright, go to that floating island, will ya?
Come on
Let's overcome this summer
It's not really close, but it's fine
Don't be a slowpoke!
Quick!
Got it!
The students reach the floating island
The students moves towards the island, without knowing why
Ok vice, explain the rules
- Alright
We'll play a song
Who-mi-fa-bang
You have to guess the title and the singer's name of the song
You have to say your answer directly into the microphone.
If you know the title, you have to come here and say it
Come here and say it
Music: start!
Music:
Come here if you know it!
Quick!
Which one is it?
Come here, come here
I don't know it, what is it?
I'm drinking a liquor soaked in my inner pride...
What is this?
Huh?
The hell is this?
Come on, answer
I don't know
- Come on
What is it?
It's uh...
It's something by Itsuki Hiroshi
I wonder what's floating in my wife's eyes...
Something
- Itsuki Hiroshi?
You gotta say somethin'
You have to say its title too
The title, please
- It's--- uhhh...
It's "King" by Murata Hideo!
Wrong!!
Listen to the lyrics
What is it?
Which...
"My inner pride!"
At the end of this forgotten road...
By whom?
Uhh...
Mikami Hiroshi
On my homeland, Akita, in the Oga peninsula...
Come on
- Wrong!
Listen to the lyrics
Got it
- Say it
Fixed on my bed, with a drink before I sleep...
Kanto Heiya
Kanto Heiya, huh?
I see...
By whom?
Saburo Nishio
I see...
Maybe they don't know it?
Let's call it a day
It's over
We'll show you the answer
Who was it?
The answer was "Lonely Nostalgia Liquor", by Hitoshi Kuramoto
Who's that?
Hitoshi Kuramoto - Lonely Nostalgia Liquor
Never heard of him...
I'm sure you know him, if you listen to his songs
The lyrics didn't give any hint
What's that?
The title wasn't in the lyrics
Is him a real singer?
Really?    - Of course
Of course he is
He's a professional
Some of his popular songs are still around
So...     - Really?
Alright, maybe his name was too hard
Probably
But you should have guessed the title
Right
He's kind of famous
"Kind of"?
Let's move on
Go back
- If that's the standard, we're done for
Who the hell was that?
Let's go!
Music:
Play the track!
It started again! It's the usa ☆ usa ☆ time
One, two! Din don dan don din don dan don
What the?
Din don dan don!
What is...?
Hot-blooded!!
Hamada's Cram School!!
Let's go!
Play the track!
Music:
It started again! It's the usa ☆ usa ☆ time
What the?
One, two! Din don dan don din don dan don
Din don dan don!
Any clue?
You can sing it if you want to
Listen to it
I hurry back home as soon as the bell rings...
It's modern
Just like that, ok Yama-chan?
Come on! Let's run all the way down our usual spot!
"High school hubris"
- I see, nice one
This is a nice point, here
- Yes
"Afterschool Cinderella"
- Oh, I see...
That's what they're aiming for
- Nice
"Nostalgic Way Back Home"
Even pointless stuff is great with all of you!
Nah...
The other ones were way better
- True
"Highschool of Love"
Ah, i see...
Yes?
"When The Bell Rings, Ok? ♥"
Ah, nice one
Very girly
- Yes
I'm still a kid, and because of that I'm still hyped!
"That Guy I Saw Coming Back Home"
Still no answer, huh?
- Come on
"Smile Jr. HighSchool Student"
No way
And it's over!
Time to reveal the answer
Here it is
It's "Afterschool Usa-usa", by usa☆usa Girls Club
No way it's gonna say "afterschool usausa!"
What do they mean by "usa-usa"?
usa☆usa Girls Club - Afterschool usa☆usa
I don't know, you idiot!
- Usa? Like, in rabbit (usagi)?
It's not even a real word!
How could we get that?
But they said usa☆usa at the beginning
Did they?!
Yeah, they really said it     - They did
That's true
So, now...
Let's just play the track
Don't go swim around, just stay here
Music:
Play the next one
The principal is gonna sing!
- The principal?!
- Who is...?
I feel like I heard this
No way!
I never expected to meet you in such a place...
What's this?
You look so lonely...
What is this?
He's not singing at all!
Reiko, oh Reiko...
Reiko?!
He said "Reiko"
It's Reiko!!
Oh tear-stained Reiko...
- Reiko...
"Reiko At The Bar"
"Wait For Me, Reiko"
"Tear-Stained Reiko"
"Tear-Stained Reiko!"
So close!!
"Reiko With Tear-stained Eyes"
Almost there!
And now you're a couple with that guy...
I'm close
"Reiko's Stains"
We're getting close
Maybe?
We're done here
We're done
- Is it "Stains"?
We're done!
Stains?!
It's "Tear Stains" by Ryo Wakahara
- Damn, "Tear Stains"!
- That's right
Wakahara Ryo - Tear Stains
There was no "Reiko"
But he said "Reiko" so many times...
He even said that at the very end
- He said it
He focused too much on "Reiko"
We didn't need it
I think you should count "Reiko's Tear Stains" as ok
I agree
Let's go with our last one
- Alright, start the music
Music:
Maybe we'll get this one
Ah, feels like something I've heard before
I remember this...
What is this?
What is this?!
Recent?
- Seems old!
It's recent!
I think I saw through your lies...
It's not an idol, right?
Anything?
"Lies Lies Wow Wow"
And I understand it, 'cause I love you
What the hell was that?
"Wow Wow?"
Well, she said it.
A man can have two women at once...
Come on, guys
Just wait for it
Wait for that part and you'll get it
- You think so?
But that won't ever make you happy...
What can it be?
Aah, I wasn't that cute of a girl, but...
"He Got Me Cryin', Ha-ha"
Nice one
No way
"Two-timing Beep Beep"
But you're the only one I ever wanted...
Not even close
"Did We Break Up?"
Come again?!
- Huh?
"Did We Break Up?"
Correct!!
WHAT?!
It's "Did We Break Up?", by Kim Ranhi
Who's that...?
No way!
Kim Ranhi - "Did We Break Up?"
How did you know that?
No way you got it
She didn't say that in the lyrics...
She didn't say it...    - Is that it?
I'm very surprised
How did you...?
Did you peek at that?
I heard the lyrics...
I thought, it seems like she's talking about a break-up...
That's incredible
- Sure you didn't peek at it?
I didn't, I swear
You sure?
So, let's see...
What should we do, principal?
- Well...
Yama-chan got it right just now
But I 100% saw him peeking at this cardboard
- What?
Really?!
That's what we said!
- Are you kidding me?
The proof
Here's the proof Hosei cheated
Get ready...
Punishment game for you!
Please, wait... he kept on flipping that thing so I could see it
- Punishment time!
I didn't want to see it, but I couldn't help it!
He kept on flipping that thing on my face!
Nope, you're out!
Now...
Can't blame him
Be brave, Hosei
What should I do now, what?
Just tell me!
- Principal?
Alright, so...
- Spare me, principal!
Don't ever stop! The no-stop club!
Ready for the usual?
I can't...
I saw that before
That's all you ever do!
He's holding a baby!
You're right!
It's his baby!
Come on, switch into something else!
- Congratulations!
Congratulations
He's born
Congratulations for your newborn!
It's what you get
Cheating is the thing our principal hates the most
Yeah, that's no good
Here comes
- Maybe he'll come up with something new
Oh!
I can see a change!
It's the Moustache-dance!
A new trend?
He's running out of stamina
Maybe it's less tiring
Don't you think he just entered eco-mode?
I do       - Sort of...
This is the most basic type
He's thinking about the next move
Look at him
His face!
It's Ei-chan?!
It's Eikichi Yazawa!
Ei-chan!
So cool, such a cool face
It's Ei-chan
And it's over
Here it comes again
It's the backside of a comedian again
He's completely exhausted
Hot-blooded!!
Hamada's Cram School!!
"Once more, that incredible love"
lyrics: Osamu Kitayama | music: Kazuhiko Kato
From that day in which we vowed to stake our lives
We build up so many wonderful memories
But now that I see those same flowers we called beautiful back then
I realize how our hearts don't resemble each other anymore
Once more, that incredible love
Louder!
Alright, a little break now
That song for the red dragonfly we sang to the wind
Nothing has changed since then
But the two of us who chased after the sunrise
Our hearts have grown so apart since then
Louder!
Once more, that incredible love
Last one
How about you enroll
in Hamada's Cram too?
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION
WEBSITE: shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
FACEBOOK: fb.com/shionnotsukai
TWITTER: twitter.com/shionnotsukai
KO-FI: ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
PATREON: patreon.com/shionnotsukai
5-shot talk
"How to spend your summer break"
So, it's summer now
- Right, we're in the middle of the summer break
How do you plan on spending it?
I see...
Let's see
Are you going somewhere with your families?
I'm not
- Really?
'Cause it's gonna be crowded wherever we'd go
I'm going
I'll go to the sea
Who cares?
That's pretty standard
- Just go, who cares!
I will
- If you'll have time
Of course, if I can
And I also wanna do that, you know
I wanna do that rocket thing
- Ah, I see
That one!
- Yeah
You put it on your feet and it flies
It uses water pressure to make you float
Ah, the jetpack thingy?
- That one
I'm not sure...
photo: Afro
Flyboard
It uses the power of the water for a jet propulsion
And it sprays water, right?
That's right, it's very powerful
I never actually saw one of those
Me neither
Isn't there an ad for it?     - Yep
You wanna do it?    - I'm doing it in two days
Are they like boots?            - That's right
And from its side it sprays water, it makes you fly
I wanna show it to my family!
I wanna appeal to them
Flying like fwaaaaaaah!
That's it
- What's so funny about it?
It's really fun!
- Is it?
By the sea?
- Of course
You'll do it?
No way
Definitely, yeah
Are they going to film you?
Of course
- Perfect
We gotta see it, maybe we'll persuade Hamada into trying it himself
Please, do!
I wanna see him
- Please!
I really want to
- I want to see the principal fly
In Hamada's Cram School?
- Yeah
No way he'll do it
He doesn't even like to walk!
That's not true
I guess so
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION
WEBSITE: shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
FACEBOOK: fb.com/shionnotsukai
TWITTER: twitter.com/shionnotsukai
KO-FI: ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
PATREON: patreon.com/shionnotsukai