Gaki no Tsukai's Shichi Henge!
Put in rigorous situations which are too funny too fail,
this series displays the true worth of comedians.
And today's challenger is...
First time on Gaki no Tsukai - Kendo Kobayashi Shichi Henge!
Before that, congratulations!
Congratulations to Matsumoto on the birth of his first daughter!
Matsumoto Hitoshi has finally  become a parent
Matsumoto Hitoshi has finally become a parent!
Well, it happened finally around this episode's airing.
Honestly, about Koba's Shichi Henge today,
who gives a shit?
You want to go home to care for your new born.
Yeah, makes no difference.
But, all the comedians that performed here so far
who had promising futures
have become good for nothings.
Why all the ones that came here?
They have sort of given up, lost potential opportunities
and their future looks grim.
Let's welcome today's performer!
Kendo Kobyashi
Not your normal self.
- Something's a bit changed.
It's the usual me. Though I have
really sour feeling in my mouth.
Since you came here, I saw you sitting there by yourself
just staring at a point here.
Just staring there by yourself.
Up to 30 people have tried, and Koumoto is still on top.
T/N: Koumoto episode #753
This shows the money if you get on here.
That's some tight rankings. Gotta dream big.
I want to be around the ranks that are bold typed font.
Till here is bold typed.
Ah, so small!
Yama-chan, your typeface is so small!
We had less staff when I performed.
- It wasn't like that at all.
It was like 3 people, can't be helped.
That wasn't funny at all.
Typeset and Timed by GakiDave
Translated by Baumkuchen
This is a fan sub for fans
do enjoy :)
Alright, what should we do?
Project Meeting
These haven't been decided yet.
Gaki Tsukai Project Meeting
House Party at Matsumoto's place with food made by his new wife
Hamada & a Female Gorilla live togther for a week
Can't do standup talk! 20 years of experience Yamazaki re-enters NSC
First ever project of its kind! "Endo's live anguish til dawn"
Kokoriko Tanaka 24-hour four-legged marathon
Let's face off! Gaki no Tsukai vs Hayashiya Family
Heipo marriage hunting in the Philippines. "All relatives present. I'll take care of you all"
Angry King! ELT Ito Ichiro 1000 things
Where's Director Suga?
Variety General Director
Suga Kenji
Suga isn't here today.
Wait, who is this sitting here?
I was told to sit here since Suga isn....
Heipo
What did you say?
Since Suga isn't here, I was-
- Say it clearly!
What are you mumbling about?
Well, what to do about these?
Starting from the top is a good idea.
We can't do this live, can we?
First ever project of its kind! "Endo's live anguish til dawn"
My anguish delusional?
Forget the excuses, just do it!
This marriage one is interesting.
Heipo marriage hunting in the Philippines. "All relatives present. I'll take care of you all"
Philippines can be done.
In my 30s, I was with a Philippines woman and we dated.
You had one really?
You had your chance with a Philippine woman.
Yeah, I want to pursue someone else.
I went all the way to Cebu Island for her.
That really happened??
She must have been pretty.
- She was a dancer.
Dancer?
Please let me smoke a cigarette.
After the commercial break,
will Koba let out a puff like Nagira?
He's an idiot.
After the commercial break, will Koba
chug the leftover juice like Nagira?
My eyes are getting tired.
After the commercial break, Nagira tears up...
He really likes Nagira.
That was really close.
The money collected from this episode will be donated to the Nippon Television Kobato Cultural Agency.
T/N: Kabuto Agency provides for vision/hearing
impaired materials and supports cultural arts.
Source: NTV Holdings
Actually, he didn't even transform!
Yeah, lets tell him.
We'll address it later.
Not a transformation at all!
- Yeah, it isn't
He's just redoing his own gags.
Yama-chan, you're getting flack for this.
It's upsetting!
Can't do standup! 20 years of experience Yamazaki re-enters NSC
I can't do stand up talk.
Who wrote this out really?
Who came up with this?
I'm asking who wrote this!
I'm Yamamoto Kotetsu, you see.
T/N: Yamamoto was a famous pro wrestler, known for his unique
speech pattern, harsh training regiment and trained the likes of
Jushin Thunder Liger and Masahiro Chouno.
Source: wikipedia.org
Furutachi, you're r-really p-passionate today.
T/N: Ichiro Furutachi was a wrestling
commentator and now a newscaster.
Source: wikipedia.org
It's really hard to tell how old you are.
Might be older than 40.
You there, athlete Endo.
Your ambition is unwavering. Thats what I see in you.
Athlete Tanaka.
You're looking good, you see. Your wife is in good hands.
You know...
Athelte Hamada, you see.
You seem composed and cool headed.
But your words are explosive, you see.
Thats your reality, your knees and lips are overused a lot.
I don't have it in me though.
But still, your ambition is unwavering.
Well, that's alright.
I gotta go back and make sure my wrestlers are in shape.
You've changed, Furutachi.
Put it in.
Why was Matsumoto being treated as Furutachi?
Everyone else were themselves, why only me as Furutachi?
Heipo, stop with that kind of laughter.
- Such an enticing laugh.
Trickle trickle, your laughter is like
water being poured onto rocks
Like fine water on pointy rocks.
I'll end up laughing on that alone.
Yeah, laugh out loud.
It's 1000 Yen fine for a little smirk and for big laughter.
Let it out like a lumberjack.
I understand, I'll let out a proper laugh.
Tacchan!
T/N: Tacchan and Minami are characters from the
famous 80s baseball manga "Touch".
- Minami!
Be more cheerful.
I'm cheerful though.
Shouldn't a nice woman like you
give me a kiss if I am down?
That was Minami's first kiss.
Aim for it!
Tacchan! To Koshien!
T/N: Koshein is a National High
School Baseball Tournament.
Tacchan...
Invite Minami to Koshien this year.
Sure. I guess I'll go practice now.
Hama-chan! Take Minami to Yokohama Stadium with you!
- Thats not Hama-chan.
Take me there!
What the hell!
- Thats dirty!
Also, Koba just left in the middle of the skit!
Leaving that much of the skit. Thats no good!
Thats dirty, Koba.
There's context behind that famous line.
"Take Minami to Koshien..."
"Take Minami to Koshien late" is what she said.
After this:
Koba rides the momentum!! Penalty rush abound??
This is so grueling to watch.
Yeah, since he's not transforming.
Oh, come in.
Ah, we're going again.
Thanks for the coin.
What are you doing?
He's biting onto it.
Ok, all done.
Way different than yesterday.
Ok, go ahead.
Ah, that's a-alright.
MARVELOUS, MARVELOUS, MARVELOUS!
You won't get better doing it this way.
No room for potential.
You're just gonna keep doing that?
- This guy's an idiot.
Good. Good. Good.
I won't tell you that again.
You again? Go ahead.
Are you a pro out this?!?
Thank you for the meal.
That's my line. "Thanks for the meal" is for me to say.
Heipo and I got a front-row seat to all the licking!
Directly in front of us.
Ah, all the old dudes.
Directly head on. That's excessive!
Yes, just awful.
So gross.
- Gross af.
No one understood that scene just now.
I heard a rumor that you were
attempting Rakugo recently.
Really?
You said Rakugo is no big deal during Endo's anguish shoot last month.
Like are you really going to do it?
Before you said you were being forced to do it with our resident Baldy.
Our Baldy?
- What was his name, again?
Who is Our Baldy?
He wears some make-up wig.
Yeah, its Ounuma.
He's not Our Baldy.
Ounuma
Director
Stop this, it makes me laugh already.
We got to be serious here. Just stop it.
What the hell is with "Our Baldy"?
Naming a regular old dude...
I'm late.
Excuse us.
Are you Kobayashi Tomoharu?
Yes, that's me.
I'm Katagiri of Tokyo Police Search Unit 1.
7 years ago, were you working at uh-- Kanto um-- M-Medical Hospital?
7 years ago, were you working at uh-- Kanto um-- M-Medical Hospital...?
It's useless now.
You're aware of that, aren't you?
Yes.
Then, I'll get straight to the point. Will you come
with us to Tokyo immediately?
I understand, I'll be in your care.
Handcuff him.
Hey!! What are you doing?
Stop it!
Please don't be unreasonable with our doctor.
Our doctor didn't do anything.
He's a potential suspect
in a murder case a few years ago.
Don't do anything!
Everyone, its okay.
Detective, please, take me.
Take you where exactly?
I came all the way to this village chasing the culprit.
However, in this village, there's no murderer...
But, free of charge, you provide care-
- This is so shitty.
for the livelyhood of the people here that depend on you.
A caring doctor among the village folk.
Spending lots of money, coming to this village.
If you do something like that again,
I'll come find you.
T/N: Unsure of what is being said here. I did my best :)
Uncuff him, Fujimiya.
Get outta here! Leave!
The skit ended in the first half.
Was this even Koba?
We gotta tell him that enough is enough.
It's like this on all the skits.
It's been a while since I saw someone so stunned.
He's not even...
He's not doing anything on his own.
He only did Yamamoto Kotetsu skit. Everyone else does the rest.
Hey, come here!
Ace's Wakame, slurp it up quick!
Where's this Wakame from?!
T/N: Koba is mimicking an old Acecook
Wakame Ramen ad by Ishidate Tetsuo.
Where Wakame are you?
-Hollanda, California.
Its so old!
So old!
He left California.
Ohh, California!!
Ace's Wakame, slurp it up quick!
Where is this Wakame from?
Which you Wakame are you?
???, California.
T/N: I don't know what language he is speaking.
To me it doesn't sound like English. Perhaps EU?
He left California.
Well, if you listen closely, its California??
Go!
He actually does that.
Who the hell remembers that old ad??
He's gutsy pulling that off.
I wouldn't be able to.
After this:
Last skit and results
He only did Yamamoto Kotetsu
and Ishidate Tetsuo by himself.
- Yup.
The rest for that matter...
- Yeah, the rest
The detective skit was questionable.
- Yeah, he got away with a lot on that one.
That one was the most awful.
Ah, I'm so hungry!
- Yeah, so hungry!
Some sushi!
Looks delicious!
Gimme some too, Hirochi.
Here have some.
GUTSY
NEGO6
Eating sushi is the best feeling!
Delicious!
Koyamada-Senpai.
What are you doing?
Oh Golgo, I'm eating sushi, don't you see.
You're filling up quite well!
Ah, thanks!
Thanks! More importantly, Golgo...
...what are you here for?
Oh yes, Senpai, something's happened.
The hell do you mean?
Mr. Bure is throwing a fit again.
T/N: Unsure of what is being said here. I did my best :)
What should we do?
Oh Whatever!
Wait up!
Its Nego6 again, he's used him before too.
He appears often.
Lets just tally up just in case.
We'll address our concerns afterwards.
51,000 Yen.
You're joking!
3rd place. No, 4th place actually!
4th Place?
51,000 Yen?
Koba!
We have something that needs to be brought up.
Really, brought up?
Verifying authenticity.
- Objection of your work.
So far, 51,000 Yen.
Hell yeah!
You're in here.
- Somehow got in Top 5.
First things first, you didn't transform.
Wait, I did transform though.
You didn't when you had the camera closeups.
Trying to impersonate Nagira Kenichi.
On the last one, when Nagira cries...
...I synced with Nagira's style.
What about the Tacchan's skit?
Well, I transformed as Tacchan.
That granny did all the work though.
And yet you left, leaving her there by herself.
Does the laughs granny gets go toward you?
You can't have your cake and eat it too.
The worst one was the doctor and detective.
This one's hard to judge. What do you think, Koba?
I wonder if certain people in this world...
...might need to follow up on practice.
He told me he practiced it.
He did, didn't he?
- Thoroughly.
Also, he seemed like a respected veteran.
He causally turned me around during practice.
- Ah he did
Couldn't believe it that same person...
- Like a deer in headlights.
What will you do about that? You piled up lots of points there.
Everyone laughed.
- That was also derived from the results.
That was?
- I set it up.
But you also laughed as well.
Its no good if you laugh too.
It was derived from me.
We're thinking of not giving you the credit for the 5th skit.
(1) Camera before ad (2) Yamamoto Kotetsu (3) Touch
(4) Nipple Sucking (5) Doc & Detective (6) ACECOOK (7) Gutsy Nego6
Just the 5th one.
Doc and Detective?
If we omit this skit from the total,
how much is left over?
Well its 11 people, so...
In that case, the total is 40,000 Yen.
Since Koba laughed at his own skit,
you take out your own 1000 Yen too.
During the Doc & Detective skit.
41,000 Yen.
8th Place Total Amount 41000 Yen!!
On the contrary, you're gonna put in your own money.
What do you mean "on the contrary"?