[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]
My back hurts.
Huh?
You are both reading the same book.
-You two are close, huh.
- Is it a coincidence?
What are the odds?
This is strange.
It’s so scary.
Be quiet.
I chose this book too, so please don't be like that.
- You're ruining my best joke.
- You right.
That's blurred.
Mine was drowned out by an accidental joke.
[The person who draws the skull card receives the punishment written in the stand.]
[Shippe slap on both arms]
[Never speak out loud, as it disturbs people who are reading.]
There's no hair.
Did you remove the hair?
What's going on with you?
Let's all do it at the same time.
Ow!! Ouch!!
What's wrong?
Why?
Why didn't you slap him?
I slapped him.
Shut up.
Shut up, Tanaka.
Hide it.
[Beads scrape]
- What’s this?
I don't get it.
Hamada-san, please put the beads on both arms.
I will restrain him.
Shut up!
Is my ear still attached?
You are fine.
I’m so scared.
[Foul-smelling mask]
- I hate this.
It stinks!
Tanaka, you put it on him.
[Grilled kusaya]
It reeks!
What the hell are you doing?
Watch out.
[Four-year-olds beating and kicking]
What's this?
I don't get it.
Thank goodness!
What's this?
What the hell.
This is totally fine.
Why did he persist?
You're lucky.
I was heartwarming.
It was a heartwarming punishment.
[Shaved ice on the face]
Lie down.
This is scary.
Standby OK!
- Don’t  move.
- Here we go.
Tanaka, you restrain him.
Here we go.
Let’s start!
Quiet!
Do you know where we are?
Be quiet!
This is a library!
Follow the rules!
Follow the guidelines
That's enough, right?
There are more.
[Scratching the blackboard]
This is the worst.
I really hate this.
Ah, I see.
The screen will show an image of the blackboard, so watch it.
Your headphones are not aligned.
Fix the potition yourself!
It hasn't started yet, has it?
You heard him, didn't you?
Look at the screen.
I got chills.
I could hear a little.
I'm losing my mind!
Don't talk.
Don't talk so clearly.
This is torture.
Just how many more punishments are left?
[Nipple yo-yo]
We haven't got the punishment yet.
He's loosing his mind
- He's loosing his mind.
- His eyes are unfocused.
He's loosing his mind.
What's the nipple yo-yo?
Please lie down.
- Small nipples!
- Yeah.
Really small nipples.
Oh awesome!
No! No!
Be quiet!
Still no attack on the nipples?
Oh, no!
Oh, No!
What the hell is this?
- That was hurt.
- Because it's spinning.
That was hurt!
It hurts when it spins like that!
You seemed to feel good.
This side felt good.
But the other side was very painful.
I don't care about that.
Your nipples were erect.
His nipples were erect?
- I am embarrassed.
- “Oh, no”
Hamada-san and I have not yet been punished.
[ Too spicy water toothpick]
- I absolutely hate this.
Please go ahead, Matsumoto-san.
Really?
Go ahead.
Enough is enough.
My nipples still hurt.
Hey, what's this?
- I like how it's going.
- Yeah.
Please wear this.
[Water toothpick with too spicy salsa sauce]
- Now open your mouth and show me your teeth.
Be quiet!
He is out of his mind.
Earlier, he hurt his nipples.
My mouth and nipples are tingling.
My mouth and nipples are ...
I've had enough.
Two have yet to be punished.
Two should be punished.
I've had enough.
[Sweaty sumo wrestler press]
I hate this a lot too.
Go ahead.
I'm not sure anymore and I'm scared.
Then, I'll take the card first.
Wait a minute!
Wait a minute.
This can' t be helped, sorry.
What are the odds?
This is a very low probability.
- They're sweating.
- That’s gross.
That's the worst.
They stink!
I really hate this.
He's soaking wet.
And it wasn't even that funny.
I don't care about that.
You still haven't recovered from that nipples thing.
Someone please take over.
I really don't want to anymore.
If it's me again, I'll run away.
I'm really going to run for it.
The next one is the last.
[Punishment for 3 people]
So New York and Matsumoto should do it.
Let's open the cards one by one.
[Dick machine with face clothespins]
What’s the hell is this?
First let's decide who will get this punishment.
Is he deal the cards?
Eh, really?
- Who do you want to open first?
- Yama-chan?
Come on!
Is it serious?
Come on.
This is a one-third establishment.
Matsumoto-san should do this.
Let's open at the same time.
What are the odds?
[Dick machine and face clothespins x2 are linked!]
Three of you play rock-paper-scissors, and the winner gets to choose.
Two of them this, one of them that.
My nipples are no longer available.
This is serious.
My nipples are useless TODAY.
Your tragedy began with the nipples one.
You three play rock-paper-scissors.
This is also painful, though.
This is not good either, though.
Oh, you don't have to do it to your nipples?
Oh, you do that to your face?
Huh!?
This seems to do it to the face.
So this isn't a punishment that's done to your nipples?
You should do it to your nipples.
Put it on their nipples.
Ow!! Ouch!!
Here we go.
3, 2, 1...
What the hell!
Clothespins hit you in the face.
You're not lucky.
That pisses me off!
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]