TG
abyss of emotional suppression
An abyss of emotional suppression ...
TEAM Gaki presents:
Timing/Typesetting:
Slayeer (Alex)
Hinnerk
Kazuma
Inugami
Sacro
Alfred
Melty
Translation:
Michael
Melty
Half-San
DesertStarr(Jason)
Lei
Scion
Final checker:
James
Others:
Jordan & Rich
that is when people express tears of joy..
express tears of joy
Gaki no Tsukai best series
Gaki no Tsukai's best
"No Laughing Earth Defense Force"
Gaki no Tsukai best series
"No Laughing" series
This year they go beyond the Earth!
Secret
Attacked by laughter assassins!
Super Deluxe!!   Lineup
Secret
The best lineup of laughter assassins attack the five!
Matsuko
Shut up, you bastard!!
YOU BASTARD!
That's not okay, is it?!
Defense training
Special celebrities gather for the defense training!
Happy boy!
WOW!!
Happion!!
'That Horror'
Returns
The horror again ..
the howling and screaming
The Tag war returns for training!
The howl and scream-inducing tag war returns
the howling and screaming
The Tag war returns for training!
'Help~!
Stage Red Circuit
The stage is upgraded to a circuit
really cool guy
HAMADA SA~N!!!
prey
Even THAT super-famous actor also becomes prey
willpower of men
The willpower of men whose bodies are put to the test
OWWWW!!
You're a traitor! Hey!
HAMADA SA~N!!!
First time in the series!! An unbelievable situation
For the first time in the series ...
Tears
tears...
and the reason is ...
Only laughter! 6 hour special challenge!!
New Year's Eve special!
Absolutely no Laughing!
Absolutely no laughing!
Earth Defense Force
24 Hours
New Year's Eve Special
Absolutely no Laughing!
no Tsukai ya Arahende!
Gaki
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Alright,  Matsumoto-san
Tsukitei Housei
The day has finally come for this year.
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Yes, it has!
Is everyone okay?
We are okay!
Are you all okay?
Yes, that's right.
From here, we have a so much time, you won't believe it!
Yes
We really do!
Like forever!
It's enough time for a quick-blooming bud to bloom into a flower
We have that much time!
This year's theme is Earth Defense Force
Woah! It's here!
Defense Force
Protect the earth? We can't even protect our own arses
That's true.
Yours, right?
Yes, that's right.
You were defeated.
We were supposed to be a force.
We couldn't protect anything.
Your ass just finished, didn't it?
I literally heard my arse just 'end'.
It just went "PE~NNNNNN"!!
Yeah, really.
It said "pe~n"
My ass just 'ended'
At 50 years old my ass has just given up
I don't understand.
We are going to begin now, Matsumoto-san.
the cue for VTR
please!
Alright!
So are we ready? Let's go!
No Laughing Earth Defense Force
Dawn
When the sunrise colors the sky ...
the trees are awakening...
beginning
they symbolize a beginning.
Will there be a filming site?
I've heard that there will be rockets.
"Wait right here" is what it says.
Those signs pisses me off
Oh, this?
It could say "please wait" or "could you wait here".
Wait here!!
This is more of a demand
At this point, I've already lost interest in doing this shoot
My interest flew away.
You've started it by just moaning!
We all know that person will show up anyway.
Yes, that's right.
That person will come, won't he?
It seems like it.
HEE~Y!!
Ugh ... Something is coming.
It's coming.
Look at him, look at his speed.
Yes, I see.
He's not a celebrity.
Did he lose a little weight?
Yes, he looks a bit thinner.
Yes.
His face hasn't changed though
*we filmed with special permission
You stopped awfully far away from us
Downtown previous manager
Fujiwara Hiroshi
He can come closer
Yes, that would've been good.
Good morning everyone!
In the neighboring city's supermarket
there was an early morning time sale
I went to the sale by speeding on a mom's-bicycle
Hey Tanaka-!!
How many people do you think this food can feed?
We can't hear .. helicopter ..
Helicopter is flying very close by.
Mid-air distance
Can you please come forward?
Oh, you mean us?
The helicopter is right above us.
It's amazing, it's so difficult to hear.
Has this ever happened?
Hey Tanaka-!!
Yes.
How many people do you think this food can feed?
There's quite a bit ...
About 10 people ...
This is all for me
This food all of it is for me by myself
Why do you say that twice?
That makes me laugh!!
What the hell are you saying?
We're gonna do it this year, too!
What the hell ...
Hamada
Yes.
I came by mom-bicyle so
you may slightly feel something
What do you think this year's theme is?
You can't really tell..
Is it grocery store?
Hell no!!
This year's theme is Earth Defense Force!
Then don't ask!
That has nothing to do with the bicycle.
Newly Recruited members of the Defense Force
Challenge for 24 hours of duty!!
The five men are newly recruited Defense Force members
they endure 24 hours of brutal duty.
one person has a troublesome issue ...
But, there is one person who has a troublesome issue ..
Yamasaki  you went through a name-change
Yes.
Yamasaki you went through a name-change
Ah yes, thank you very much.
What was the name again?
It is  Tsukitei Housei
What the hell is that? No one knows that.
It hasn't become popular yet.
Yes.
Uhm ... That
....That
At an important time.
Seriously?
It's quick.
Should we try once more from the top?  (The script.)
His new name's unpopularity with the public
It makes me laugh a lot!!
the problem with Yamasaki's name change
even though recognition is extremely low, he will participate as "tsukitei housei"
I really don't understand.
Well we can't do anything about it
He makes me mad
The recognition really is low.
so you're gonna go as Housei!
Yes.
By the way, you guys ..
I told you that you're part of the Earth Defense Force
but why are you dressed like that!?
Isn't it weird?
What
I have your change of clothes
in those boxes over there
so I'm gonna have you change right now.
Ahh, we're changing clothes again.
Before Earth Defense Duties
Change into appropriate outfits
With that reasoning
they will change into the appropriate outfits.
Okay everyone, when you're ready
I'm going to have you come out one by one
Yes!
So cool.
Macho-Papa Soldier
Thank you.
It looks nice.
The titles are unnecessary.
Yes, that's right.
Housei!
Yes.
What is the point of it?
Selfishly changed his name-member
It's pretty cute.
Your legs are also showing.
Thank you.
Hopefully you'll be
a tasteful member.
Yes.
Yes!
You're definitely handsome and cool.
Handsome Baseball-freak member
Thank you.
You'll be well-liked by women.
Hopefully you'll be a very well-liked member.
Thank you.
Yes!
Lanky Pointy-Chin   member
You're so lanky.
You need to gain weight.
The pointy-chin was unneeded.
Hopefully you will be a strong-willed member.
Alright     Hamada
The only woman on the team   member
It looks good!
Why are you a girl?
It's nice!
I'm jealous!
Is that your own wig?
It probably has Hamada's name on it.
It looks so good.
That's definitely your own wig.
I'm going to explain the rules so
form a line up front
You have such nice legs.
You can work it.
You've always had
very nice legs   Hamada-san.
Hamada-san's legs really are pretty.
One! You are members of the Earth Defense Force.
You are newly recruited EDF members
going through 24 hours of training
For a whole day, you will do various tasks.
Cough!
Second!
While you are working as EDF members, no matter what happens - absolutely no laughing.
While working, absolutely no laughing
tirth
In the event that you laugh,
you will receive severe punishment on the spot.
that's it.
If you laugh, you will receive severe punishment
Got it?
I understand, but he hasn't been listening at all.
Hamada hasn't.
I'm so cold.
Are you cold?
Because, look-
wearing a garter belt ❤
You're wearing a garter ...
You've really done it.
It's very sexy.
You didn't protect at all
Yourself.
To get to the EDF headquarters
we will go by bus
Again, a bus ...
A bus.
And it begins when we get on the bus, right?
Ughhh ... I really don't want to.
Sponsors
Nissei Advance
Healthy Family
Is it really a bus?
Are we really going to do this?
We're gonna wait for the bus right here.
Tension    Rises
Finally the beginning
whether they like it or not, the tension is rising.
It's here.
Hey, it's here.
There's always Kurobikari.
Yes, that's true.
Of course, Kurobikari.
It's here!
Gaasuu Kurobikari Earth Defense Force.
This is the name of the place where you will be working.
Gaasuu  Kurobikari
Earth Defense Force
Isn't it cool?
Gaasuu Kurobikari Earth Defense Force
Gaasuu Kurobikari Defense Force of Earth
With importance put on the color red,
in this freshly-designed commuter bus
ölklöklöklöklöklök
Aim for the EDF Headquarters
they will aim for the Earth Defense Force Headquarters
Are we getting on?
We're gonna board
As soon as we board, we can't laugh, right?
the moment you get is when it starts
Oh well, can't do anything about it.
But it begins as soon as we board ...
So if we get on ...
I'm getting on!
It's starting, huh...
Wait... Why are you walking like that?
I was really cold.
Right, I'm getting on!
Lead the way!
Man, so cold...
Here we go!
Do Not Laugh
Earth Defence Force 24 hours
Wow, it's warm in here
Okay...
Right, let's go!
Okay let's go!
Here we go!
Okay, come on..
Some customers are already on
Man, it's so cold!
Yeah, it really is..
Your helmet will get in the way, so I am just going to take them from you
The helmet will "get in the way"?..
Hahahahahaha
So what is the point in giving them to us?
Judge didn't see... Therefore SAFE
Finally, the bus has
Off to the Earth Defence HQ - but what lies ahead....
departed for the Earth Defence Headquarters
but what lies ahead?
The bus is on its way to HQ
Laughter will NOT be tolerated from here!!
The 5 make their way for HQ
but their laughter will not be tolerated anymore!
Does the actual Earth
Defence Force look like...
well, like this?
Like the fact we're travelling with ordinary people is like...
Yeah...
You're right
Something's definitely not right...
Oh come on, it's not that cold...
He was moaning the whole time!
You guys
get to wear trousers..
You must be warmed up by now in here..
No no no, look at this
The woman gets a garter belt as part of their uniform
This was awful...
That is amazing...
That businessman over there just laughed...
That's way too much...
Fujiwara is laughing so much...
He's laughing like "What a Masterpiece"!
Literally his face is like that...
Haha...
You were never getting away with that
You guys were all laughing before me too...
Like 'he-he-he'
No no, I was completely cool...
I was safe
Black army will
4th Rule
smack you on your arse if you laugh
Oh... This again?
Shit, shit, shit...
Get him good...
BAM!
He got me  right in my face   just now...
HAHAHAHAHA
This can't be allowed...
This was properly...
Bloody hell..
And Endo is going to get another smack!
This was totally ridiculous...
I haven't done anything wrong!
This isn't right!
No, you're right Endo, it's not right...
You agree with me, right?
Ye, that was unfair...
That wasn't fair...
You got hit for no reason...
Yeah
Someone else gets punished and then that hits you in the face... I mean
Laughter from bad luck  is part of this show
After this  more traps will make them laugh
An unlucky start...
But that happens in this show
Man, it really has started...
And now the traps to make them laugh
will show themselves...
BUS STOP
The door has opened...
Wakabayashi Masayasu
Takaoka Saki
Cool guy
Madonna
Hey Saki
Yeah?
Have you decided which guy you want to be with?
Oh, he's a "cool guy"?
Those guys , they just don't
appeal that much to me
Hey Saki,
2 men are supposedly after Saki
You do realize that you are the brother of Rockabilly
The supposedly "coolest guy's" little sister
So don't go out with some loser
I get it, big bro.
But you know...
Those two guys...
They just don't appeal  to me enough
Ito Ichiro (from ELT)
Shark Crew
Yeah, it's just...
They've planned this well...
I was laughing at the length of his face...
They really put everything into it...
Yeah, they really had...
His appeal to Saki
A really cheesy chat up line
Hey Saki.
Today is the day I'm going to get
a good reaction from you
The only guy
God you can barely hear his voice...
capable of taming a woman like you
is me, you know?
The volume is...
If you could speak a bit louder...
This is tough, really tough
Oh shit...
It' a little hard to hear...
Well I guess he's not the singer of his band...
Please raise the volume a little bit...
Is it not hard for you
to hear at all?
The only guy who can tame a woman like you...
is me...
Don't be so stupid
I have no intention of going out
with an useless idiot like you at all
Even that guy  would be a better choice than you...
Tenryu Genichirou
Jet Crew
On we go...
Obviously we'll laugh...
He barely managed to get on the bus!
His knee is really dodgy nowadays...
Oh wow...
His appeal to Saki
A really cheesy chat up line
For real...
Hey Saki...
My nickname is
löälöälöälöälöälöälöälöälöälöä
And we're doing a dance off there.
How can we understand that...
What the hell is he saying?
and his voice is quite small too...
Saki prefers this guy?
Hey Tenryu boy, Saki's heart
ain't been strung along by you in the slightest, don't you have anything else?
On top of that,
about this cottage...
even Japan's famous people come there
like Takegawa Crystal...
and Takeshi-Gundan's "Downtown's"...
Umm Takeshi-Gundan's...
Downtown isn't part of Takeshi-Gundan...
Umm... Takegawa...
Oh
Oh.  Guadalcanal Taka as well
They just took over Downtown...
Okay both of you...
Next is... Whilst dancing
Give Saki your best chat up line
and win her heart over
Their appeal to Saki
Dance and chat her up with their best line
You have both prepared well for this, I hope?
Obviously...
How about you, Tenryu?
öä#öä##öäöääö
Ok Mister Ito, you're up first
Elvis Presley
Jailhouse Rock
He had a little glance at us there...
Like a kind of "are you okay" look...
'You're not pissed at me for doing this?' kind of look
Hey Saki
Um...
(sigh)...
Next time.. I will *&#(#*$#(*
He couldn't even say it properly at all.
And Saki's just laughing the whole time...
Saki was laughing so much.
She was laughing the whole time
Saki's been laughing the whole time...
Yeah she was
She was
Okay Mister Ito
Tenryu boy, it's your go now.
Ok, *(*#$&(#$&
Little Richard
Tooty Fruity
.Oh Tenryu boy..
Hm?
What was that dance?
Where's your chat up line?
Oh yeah...
Saki  Part 2
Saki, would you like to go have
a cream soda with me?
It just wouldn't go in at all.
Would you like to go have a cream soda with me?
Microphone wouldn't go into his pocket
Do it properly..
It's still not in his pocket properly.
No no no...
I'm not laughing at what he said
I know...
Yeah it's more the...
What about Yamasaki?
Sponsors
Hold on a second
He was the first one of us to laugh
No, I was safe
Okay Saki, did either of them appeal to you much?
Oh I can't decide
who's better out of these two.
Anyway, I...
found a really good looking guy
Excuse me there, sir
excuse me, sir
Saki likes Matsumoto
Excuse me, you sir
I have kind of fallen for you
Connie Francis
Stupid Cupid
Hey there, mister
These kind of things...
Tries to appeal by dancing with love
Watch my dance now
Seriously this situation was...
scary, I bet?
and it would be my pleasure
if we did something nice...
Hang on a second...
You there, the balding pervert!
What the hell, you
what do you think
you're looking at with that dirty look on your face!!
dgsdgsdsdg
You were looking at me, weren't you!?
No..part 2
No... I wasn't.
You were, weren't you!
...No, I wasn't...
You make me sick...
To Housei: The Pervert
She spits her gum at him
I feel sick now...
Let's go home!
Why did she do that?
Something flew, didn't it?
Hold on man...part2
The judges are being way too lenient
Yamasaki wasspared there
Yamasaki was spared there
He should have been hit like 3 extra times.
15 minutes since start
Fifteen minutes since they left the park
Already loads of  punishments!!
And the punishments just don't stop for the guys
But...
Obviously, ahead of them
And next
There are even funnier  traps awaiting them
are even funnier traps waiting to make them laugh
BUS STOP
Oota-san
If you don't sign the contract with us now..
our company will undoubtedly..be finished!!
our company will undoubtedly be finished!!
Salesman
Kakei Toshio
So I'm really begging you
You and I...We've been partners for a long time
You and I.. We've been partners for a long time
But this time...I'm really sorry
But this time... I'm really sorry
I have no time left
So I need to go
Let's go for a drink though soon, ok?
Wait... Oota-san!Oota-san!
Wait... Oota-san! Oota-san!
Please don't crush my company!Oota-san!
Please don't crush my company! Oota-san!
After failing one of his most important customers, the salesmen is in a dilemma...
There's no tomorrow...
"Ashita ga arusa"
Shozo I heard, at that age
You're resorting to use Viagra
Even now, I'm active
All I need is 'Aka Mamushi'
(Aka Mamushi = drink which contains lots of Vitamin C)
I like Shozo, I like Shozo
Shozo, I love you
When Shozo was becoming a teenager
I found your stash of porn magazines
The women in these magazines
were all the same age as me...
We like Shozo, we like Shozo
Shozo, we love you
On my 35th birthday,
my older brother got me a present
I opened the present, I was shocked
Inside was a radio control car...
I like Shozo, I like Shozo
Shozo, we all love you
At our graduation reunion, 20 years on
he tried to make himself look like Mr. Big Shot
He brought his junior, who wasn't even invited
What a dirty insecure guy
I like Shozo, I like Shozo
Shozo, we all love you
Endo-kun, you middle aged man
I found your hidden stash of videos
Son of honour, I will seduce
with a widow's mourning dress
I like Shozo, I like Shozo
Shozo, we all love you
I was worried about Ikue-san
after she watched last year's Gaki no Tsukai
This is just a lie but apparently
Endo also likes men?
I like Shozo, I like Shozo
Shozo, we all love you
Shozo, who was born in Toyonaka
He loves baseball, and loves women
He loves golf, he loves airplanes
He also likes the Kousou buildings
He likes his Benz, he likes kinako as well
He also likes pink clothes
I like Shozo, I like Shozo
Endo, we all love you!
Shozo is a really pathetic son but
All of us at Re:Endo Japan love Endo very very much
Everyone of Japan
Look at Kakei-san's knee...
Endo's Dad puts his hand on Kakei's knee
Let's all work hard together
Goodbye!
That was amazing...
Why did he put his hand on Kakei-san's knee?
I know, you're right
You're right, why did he?
Poor Kakei-san
Ye, really Kakei-sanpart2
Ye, really Kakei-san, I am so sorry
(My family) they came so early...
Yeah it was really early..
Morisaki Yuki
Testified against Endo last year
and therefore  is part of the family!
Morisaki-san...
She's not really part of my family...
She's teamed up with your ex wife and everything...
and like everyone close to you
I could never have imagined that
This is what happens when you fail to chat up a woman...
yeah... they get with your ex wife and...part2
Jeez, that was ridiculous.
Still a while to go on this journey
There are still more stops to come
45 minutes since the start,
The long and hard path to the centre still continues
Bus Stop
My first outing alone
Winter Adventure Special!!
Today the children going on a journey alone arepart2
Shota-kun, who is 5 and his younger brother, Yuto, who is 4.
Younger brother
Older brother
Yuto-kun (4 years)
Shota-kun (5 years)
The trustworthy older brother andpart2
the little cry-baby brother
They are very close brothers
Big bro...Are you sure we can do this, just us 2?
Big bro... Are you sure we can do this, just us 2?
Your big brother is here, so don't worry.
Ah, I get it!
Their Mum has asked them topart2
Go to the cake store and collect the cake they ordered and
go to the flower shop and buy some flowers
Big bro...Please can we get off the bus already?
Big bro... Please can we get off the bus already?
What are you saying?We just got on it, silly.
What are you saying? We just got on it, silly.
We aren't there yet.
WAAAAA~~~
Oh, is that so...
Oh deary deary me...part2
Yuto-kun is...
feeling scared and has started crying...
But look...part2
Look at the kind-hearted brother.
He got something from one of the trees before...
He gets the Kuwagata Beetle out...part 2part 3
and he is going to put it on his nosepart 3
in order to make his younger brother Yuto-kun laugh.
How this program works
Everyone must do as the narrator says
Don't worry little bro, watch this. Here I go...
No, it's no good. I can't do it...
Well of course he can't...
He might be a big brother, but he's only five!part2
Of course it's going to be scary.
When suddenly,part2
a man who happened to sit near the children
Luckily there was a kind old storytellerpart2
who asked "Are you okay?" to the children
How this program works
The storyteller asks them if they're okay
There's only one "storyteller" out of us
Yup, there's only one...
Are you okay?
The old storytellerpart2
will take the place of the older brother and
put the Kuwagata beetle on his own nosepart2
and will make Yuto-kun laugh.
Please can you do it for me!
How this program works
The storyteller will put the beetle on his nose
Wow...
How this program works
The storyteller will make the little brother laugh
Yuto-kun...
We know how much this shit hurts...part2
Housei-san knew as well...
Story didn't go to plan, kids are now crying
It's not coming off at all!
Like not in the slightest!
Wait, why are they crying?
Ow Ow Ow
That must hurt so much!
Ow Ow Ow Ow
They're both crying now...
RIGHT. CUT!!
WHAT?!
Our first outing
The Director
Chono Masahiro
Enters
Ow Ow Ow Ow
That must hurt so much!
They're both crying now...
RIGHT. CUT!!
WHAT?!
Our first outing
Director
Chono Masahiro
Enters
What the hell do you think you're doing? OY!
You've ruined my damn show on purpose!!
I was so shocked here.
Chono is angry because the story didn't go to the way it was narrated
Wait, hang on a second...
They told me to make them laugh.
What do you think you're doing?!
No-
Pick it up!
What are you going to do about my show?!
You've made the kids cry, I can't go on with this show!
This "situation" is just...
What is this situation?!
As a director, I am...
Hey guys, you okay?
They are crying so much!
Did that man make you cry?
Okay, come on, let's go home...
Who was the one who made you cry?
OY YOU!!
What the hell are you playing at?
Come here, now.
Ruined the show
the storyteller gets
PUNISHED
He came this year, way too early.
Yeah, so early on in the game!
I was shitting myself for
what was coming next...
I wasn't even ready mentally for it...
Like none of us were ready for that at all!
We just are not ready in the slightest...
Man, look at that...
Oi
It's my TV show,
do you get that?
What's the name of your show?
My first outing...
Because there are no kids, there's no show..
Okay...
How are you going to make up for it?!
Please forgive me!
Don't mess with me, you bastard.
Tsukihoshi...
It's Tsukitei...
This is out of order...
Isn't it?
Yama-chan... Do you really need to correct him now?
I know... Just
let him call you whatever.
Do you get me? You've screwed it all up for me...
You get it?
Yes...
Then you take responsibility for it.
What do you mean? How?
Okay okay, I get it...
What do you get?
I'm getting slapped, aren't I?
For crying out loud, I give up!
Don't just say it!
Don't like just say it so casually!
Jeez...
It is hard not to laugh when he just accepts the slap...
Okay, will you tell me your name?
My name is...
What is it?!
Tsukitei...
Housei!
Man that sucks for you...
For real? This situation...
We're still on the bus...
This was really tough...
This was the first time you got slapped on the bus?
Get out of my way!! God damn!
Doing that to my show, God damn!
What kind of face are you doing!?
OW!!!!!
My jaw... it's out of place...
Don't lie, you bastard!
Ow ow ow
OW!!!!!
How could you talk if your jaw was out of place!?
Man you got yourself into some shit there.
That was amazing...
Time on the Bus coming to the end
The GDFE Headquarters
is just ahead
The long journey on the bus is coming to an end.
The GDFE is just ahead.
Oh?
Are we here?
Yep, we are there in a second.
The earth... Kurobi...
We will be at the Gaasu Earth Defence Headquarters
We will get off there.
You really said it wrong at the beginning there...
Earth Kurobikari...
Finally the bus which carries the 5 showed itself to the Earth defense headquarters!
However
It is NOT
the goal
However, this is NOT the goal...
It is a new battlefield...
Man that was a long journey...
It really was!
Guys, we are here.
Guys, apparently we are here.
Finally we're here.
Wow, it's amazing.
Gaasu Kurobikari Earth Defence Force Headquaters
Do not laugh series:
Where the safety and laughter of the earth is the most important;
soon, a battle with the laughter assassins
will commence!!
Right guys, we're here.
Finally, yes...
Man that was long.
Shall we get off then?
Man that was hard.
Everyone, this is the Gaasu Earth Kurobikari...
Oh.. Gaasu Kurobikari Earth Defence Force..
The Headquarters.
The building is amazing, isn't it?
You're right, it's amazing.
Yes it is, I mean, we are the Earth Defence Force after all.
The prestige is on another level.
2nd floor of HQ
Okay, follow me guys.
We are now going to meet the head of this Earth Defence HQ.
So please don't insult him in any way, okay?
Okay.
Excuse us!!
Excuse us...
Excuse me.
Chief! I brought the 5 new members of the EDF!!
Here they are!
Oh it's you guys.
Big time celebrity
Hahahaha
I brought the 5 new members of the EDF!!
Here they are!
Oh it's you guys.
Chief of EDF
Matsukata Hiroki
I am FadeGaasu Kurobikari Earth Defense Force's Chief,
I am Gaasu Kurobikari Earth Defense Force's Chief,
Matsukata.
Do you guys have codenames?
No.
None.
No we do not.
As members of the Earth Defense Force, you can not reveal your real identity.
you can not reveal your real identity.
As members of the Earth Defense Force,
Therefore,
every member has a codename.
It seems as though you five do not have codenames,
so I will give them to you.
codenames for the newly recruited members
First is Officer Hamada.
He knows my name, he said it.
Gross!
It's gross!
Alright, I've got one.
Your codename is...
Male Gorilla.
Hamada's Codename
Male Gorilla
Just leave it as Gorilla..
Yes, we know he is male..
He's crossdressing.
That one really hurt.
Ouch
Okay.
It's Officer Matsumoto.
I've got it.
Your codename is...
Matsumoto-Kinnnikun
Matsumoto's Nickname
Matsumoto-Kinnikun
Matsumoto is in my codename.
Officer Endo.
Your codename is...
*note: Hirunandesu is a weekday show where Endo is MC every Monday..
Hirunandesu
Endo's Codename
He's been on the show before!
Endo's code name
Hirunandesu!
Thank you.
You appeared a lot there.
He really appeared a lot.
That hurts.
This is going to chaff real bad later.
You're right.
Finally.
Officer Tanaka.
Your code name is...
Chin Man.
Tanaka's code name
Chin Man
Isn't that the worst one?
That was the worst one.
That's impossible.
No, no.
Can you please change my code name?
Chin Man.
No you got to try your best as
Officer Housei.
Your code name is...
Ochiken.
Housei's code name
Ochiken
(Rakugo study group)
But he's a professional.
That's mean!
That's terrible.
He's a professional.
With this...
All your code names are decided.
Your
enlistment should be celebrated.
We brought our finest quality wine.
Celebrate their enlistment with wine toasting
And now
even though it's presumptuous, I want to lead the toast for this.
To celebrate your enlistment.
Cheers~! ♪♪
Why are you saying cheers instead~!?!
What's up with that guy?
But that was kinda cute.
Director Matsukata's manzai
Let's play around with the new enlisted soldiers~
Director...
What kind of a person is member Matsumoto?
That man there...
He's Officer Matsumoto.
I know!!
He's an American-born Sports Instructor, right?
Oh my God, it's Chuck Wilson!!!
That's right! He's Nigerian born...
Oh my God, it's Bobby Ologon!
You were aiming to be in Tokyo University and a beauty teacher, right?
No, you're thinking of Sakamoto-chan from Alkali the 3rd!!
What are you even saying.
Renaissance~!!
He even remembers that.
That's amazing.
No more, this hurts so much.
I can't handle more of this.
I don't feel like wine anymore...
Please bring that...
Supplying state-of-the-art ray guns
Go ahead.
I'm supplying each of you.
Cutting edge...
Ray guns.
Please don't use it yet.
Okay...
Shoot on my signal.
Okay, prepare yourselves.
Spread your legs more.
Yes.
Ready...
Our prank was a success you know~!!
Renaissance~!!
Just me?
Why only me..?
Isn't it all of us..?
Seriously, why am I the only one who got hit?
Really?
Wasn't that amazing?
That freakin' hurts.
They definitely don't sell these in shops...
Well, that's all from me.
Please carry out your duties now.
Dismissed!!
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much.
Let's go, everyone.
That surprised me.
That was amazing.
This is the newcomer's training room.
Training room.
Staff room for newbies
Get in.
Okay, well I'm off to the toilet again.
God he goes to the toilet a lot!
It's because it's cold.
My ass is already in pain.
1 hour 20 minutes since the start
It's been 1 hour and 20 minutes since it started.
They finally have time to relax a little
I'm just scared of opening anything...
You're right.
But they can't be too relaxed...
But seriously, electric shocks are really scary.
Even touching a weird object scares me.
FOR FUCK SAKES
It's that again.
Of course you would shit yourself...
Of course that would frighten me!
As I thought, there are traps...
CO2 emission from the coffee pot
Just as we're talking about it as well...
It seems like I always get shocked when I'm about to drink water.
OWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWW
I just twisted my ankle just now...
1 hour 30 mins since started
This laughter traps
are toying around with them
Since the start, the five are getting toyed around by the traps
OPENING OF THE DRAWERS! DEADLY LONG AWAITED
After this is the long awaited opening of the drawers!
Since the beginning until now, we've finally got to the room.
Yama-chan, right?
The bus scene was amazing, seriously
Chouno Masahiro
Hajimettenootsukai
13th January 2013 7pm start
Chouno will NOT be the director of the show so rest assured..
I had a feeling it would be me, since Chouno-san was there.
He's usually at the end.
I thought he would come at the end. But then he was just suddenly there...
My jaw was dislocated. Seriously
No it didn't...
For me, Endo's family appeared again.
Re:Endo Japan
Your dad's hand was on Kakei-san's thigh the whole time...
What was that? Was he nervous?
It's not like he had anything else to cling on.
I thought Kakei-san was like a hostess.
Maybe it relaxed him or something...
Oh, is it...
Even Chiaki was there.
Chiaki
Shozo, I love you~♪
She sang that.
Why did we divorce then? If she was going to sing that, we should have just stayed together...
If she actually loves me...
9:30 in the morning. The traditional yearly opening of the drawers...
9:30am- An hour and a half since the start
Do you want to rest some more or open them now and get it over with?
Eh, you want to pull it out ?
Well we don't HAVE to open the drawers...
No, they expect us to pull it after all.
Isn't that good, though? Maybe this year we just won't open them...
But the staff...
Maybe this year we won't open them
Maybe we should leave it to the person's choice if they want to open their drawers or not.
It's fine if you don't want to open yours.
Well I might not open it then...
Housei just ate a super hot rice cracker
Triple the spiciness of wasabi
Your face.
Ughhh
Why are you laughing?
Eh?
What's wrong?
Why are you posing like Mizuki Ichiro.
It's Mizuki doing his 'Zetto!'
Jeez, I'm crying. It's so spicy.
They've even set up traps like that?!
THAT HURTS~
You were like Mizuki Ichiro just now.
Yeah I saw...
Was it spicy?
What was spicy?
I think it was wasabi.
You got tricked again?
Which one was it?
The stuff that looks like rice crackers.
So, they're not rice crackers?
My ass is ending pretty early this year, it freakin' hurts. Maybe because it's cold...
Yes.
These clothes aren't even protecting us.
Why do they even call us the defence force anyway.
Come on, why don't you open it?
Should I? No use dragging it any longer, right?
Alright, I guess we should open them..
Please go ahead.
Almost every time, Tanaka's drawer will have a DVD in it.
And Endo's would probably be an object about something bad he's done..
Well, I haven't done anything bad this year...
Should I go first?
First up is Endo
Last year, you got a photo.
Yes. Anyway, I'm going to open it now...
Oh? There's something.
A mysterious panel and a magic pen
To Endo
There's a panel...
It says "To Endo"...
There's a magic pen.
Magic pen? What is this?
Okay here we go...
Hahahahahahahahha
It says, "Do this question in one minute..."
I have one minute...
You laughed just now, didn't you?
He was laughing.
I heard it too.
Endo's Draw
1 Minute Challenge
I only have a minute.
Solve the math problem in
1 minute
Problem:
Failure will result in
a wrestler headbutt
Uwaa! Seriously?!
Give it your best!
Quickly!
This is easy.
Hurry up.
Go, go, go, go.
Done!!
You're done?
I think.
INCORRECT
A headbutt from the wrestler will now be administered.
That's wrong.
It is??
HEADBUTT EXECUTION
No, no... why?
This is wrong?
You don't calculate it
just as it is like that.
You don't just add it like that.
Wah! He's here!!
This is bad.
Please, give me just one more chance!
Ah... I'm sorry!
Owwwwwwwwwwwwww!!!
He really went flying!
Wait a minute.
That was an incredible headbutt!
That's gotta hurt.
That can't be.
Your head must seriously hurt.
Endo...
It's a bit red.
It's not cut, is it?
It's not but... it's really red.
Everyone please be careful, ok?
This is a new thing this time around. The headbutt.
Owww.
I'm opening it now.
Yes, yes, yes.
Really? You're amazing, Hamada-san.
It might be another question.
You're right.
Yeah... but...
Uwaah... it's a question.
Not good.
Hamada Masatoshi
Mysterious Panels x 2
So it's this kind of pattern now, huh?
That looks different.
It's different.
So it's different.
There's no pen.
You're right.
What am I supposed to do with these?
Is it okay to flip them over?
Start with the first one.
I should do it like this, right?
Yeah, that's the best way.
Here I go
One, two...
Monster that greatly resembles Hamada 1
Garamon
[Ultra Q]
Appeared in episodes 13-16
Height: 40m  Weight 60,000t
They're being handled by the Earth Defense Force.
It looks like you.
It's not Pigumon but Garamon.
One, two...
Monster that greatly resembles Hamada 2
Model M1
[Ultra Q]
Appeared in episode 10
Height: 2m  Weight 180kg
Wow, this totally looks like him.
This kind of face is...
This is bad.
Model M1
There are times where his face looks like this
When he's in a bad mood
Yes, it does.
When there's a delay,
his mood turns like this
Although it's because he purposely comes in late,
it's totally his fault
You don't have to tell people that.
His face looks like this when they say, "Hamada-san is entering!"
"Hamada-san is entering~!" and your face looks like that
Seriously, why must you tell this story?
It's unintentional.
That is...
People don't care about that.
So something like that happen too.
It's the first time I've seen something like this.
It's your first time, right?
Me too.
He looks like this in the morning too.
Yeah, he does.
It's bad if you expand your power of imagination.
This is Hamada-san who just woke up in the morning.
You're right.
At today's hotel too.
When we went down the elevator
with his hands in his pockets...
He's like this during winter too
Wearing his handmade wooly jumper
That is scary. I'm so sorry.
Ah, that's scary. But woolen jumper...
I'm going to open the drawer
Hamada Family's Nameplate
A nameplate?
They really put a nameplate there.
It's hot!!
The Nameplate is Hot
It was sudden.
That was really mean.
Even I'm a victim.
You bastards should really stop doing things  that inflict pain to our bodies!!
You bastards should really stop doing things that inflict pain to our bodies!!
So this thing is hot.
That was really mean.
It's really hot.
If we had open it earlier it probably will be even hotter
Hot!
I don't understand why would you make it hot.
I don't know why too.
What are their intentions?
What the hell is this?
This thing is filled with evil intentions
Nothing.
I'm freaking out, jeez.
I'm so tired already.
But everyone, please do your best.
For today...
There's a lot of  physical punishment.
Seriously.
Quite a lot.
Can you flip back Model M1 upside down
Why are giving it to me?
That is really terrible.
It's bad.
Model M1.
This photo is not even photoshopped, right?
The actual appearance of a monster in [Ultra Q]
Are you sure?
He really does look like that?
It's not photoshopped.
He really does look like that.
The Gigumon.. I mean, Garamon is not photoshopped too.
No way, I didn't do anything.
You were grinning.
Grinning is not allowed.
You should know this by now.
Hamada and Model M1 are almost the same
[Ultra Q] episode 10 appearance
Boast a superhuman strength of 20 bulldozers
and intelligence of a 3 year old
What do you mean?
The description for the both of you.
Yeah, Hamada-san, maybe if you're reborn...
Boast a superhuman strength of 20 bulldozers.
Intelligence of a 3 year old...
That's really amazing.
Let's stop all the talk about Model M1
Talking about Model M1 is bad.
The destructive power is too amazing
Should we continue?
Here I go.
Nothing.
Huh?
Coke-bottle glasses
Some gag items.
Uwaaah, a wig.
Toupee
Is there more?
Can it be just this?
There must be a reason they put this in Yamachan's drawer.
That's amazing.
It's a Katochan set.
It does seem like it.
Mysterious Tiny Box
I'm opening it, ok?
Short mustache
Like I told you, it's a set.
Katochan set
It all makes sense now.
Well, then. Should I wear it?
I guess you have too.
How about putting on the glasses first?
Yeah, I'll wear the glasses first.
Ah, it's stuck.
The double-sided tape won't come off
Why?
You can't do that.
That was bad.
Why am I getting beaten for this!?!
That hair.
Something  smells bad.
It stinks.Seriously.
It stinks. Seriously.
Stinks!!
You can't wear that.
Maybe it's that.
Stinks!! What is this?
What did they put here?
It's smells really bad.
It's not the moustache.
Intensely smelly 3-piece set
It stinks!
What is that?
What is this smell?
I think it's your head.
Is it my head?
It stinks! It stinks!
Try taking off the wig.
But I just wore it.
It's not the wig.
Is it the wig?
It stinks.
It stinks! It was the wig!
Tanaka, try and smell him.
Wah, you stink!
That smells real bad!
You're really trying to laugh now.
But I'm not laughing.
Eh?
Just feeling really childlike.
I just feel really childlike.
I would hate that.
Man... what is this..?
That was really evil.
Really.
Now, Tanaka.
Okay.
I'm scared too.
Look. I knew it.
Mysterious DVD x 2
Yes, yes.
Every single time.
This is really...
Heh heh heh
What are you laughing at?
I'm not laughing at all
You guys have to look more properly!
No way... just now you did too!
You guys have to properly notice, the staff too...
You laughed just a minute ago too!
Like "HAHA!"
It was terrible. You went "HAHA!" just now.
Just now I was just trying to be childlike
Just trying to be childlike.
Stinks!!
It really stinks.
Seriously, it's bad.
But Matsumoto-san laughed too!
Come on, watch him properly!
You shouldn't try and frame others..
Man this stinks so bad..
How about the rest?
Maybe the box smells as well?..
There isn't anything..
Nothing?
Yes
So just a DVD?
there's nothingjust the DVD
there's nothing just the DVD
Matsumoto-san
Only Matsumoto left
Ye me too..
I'm really scared..
He's right.
Maybe we can just leave it...
No no, you have to open it.
Shit..
Mysterious letter
What is it
Just a small envelope..
I can't believe anything at all now
Eh?!
What?
Open Drawer No. 18
Order
Oh that's what it was
So that's what it was..
It says 'Open Drawer number 18'
drawer no. 18
Man there are so many more drawers than usual...
In the room, there are drawers labelled from 1 to 20
There is definitely something up here..
Please go ahead..
There's like loads more drawers now than there has ever been..
You're right..
Shit that's scary.
This is really freaky isn't it?
It's very scary.
It's very scary¡
It was very scary to.....
Is there something inside?
There might be another order..
A second letter
Wow, you're right..
Open drawer no. 4
Order
Number 4?
Number 4..¡ Oh oh, it's here
Number 4?.. Oh oh, it's here.
It's over here.
It's this one.
That was so scary over there..
They are just playing us like puppets.
Ye, there was loads of space in that draw..
This one is really wide..
It's really wide..
ohpart2
OH, again...
Man, they are just taking the piss now..
3rd letter
Open drawer No. 17
Order
Number 17...
Oh it's over there.
Drawer number 17
It's the one at the bottom
The bottom over there..
Man, they are just toying with me..
Trap in....
seconds
Oh hold on, this one is the smallest..
Ye, you're right..
AHHHHHH!
My back..clicked out of place..
My back, clicked out of place..
What are you doing?
For crying out loud..
I'm really sorry, my back just went..
4th letter
And again...
Because from all the way down there..
The drawer came out really easily
Oh something happened?
So the trap must have failed
Open drawer No. 7
Order
Open Number 7..
It's this one..
What is this?
It just goes on and on..
It's really annoying..
Oh.. again..
Again?
That's really weird..
wooaaaaaa!
They delayed it on purpose..
Totally delayed it on purpose
God he was so shocked..
ahhh tanaka as well..
Tanaka reacted so much as well..
Did you hit your elbow somewhere?
10:00 AM
2 hours since the start
Still not finished
I understand the troubles,
if we are dealing with everything that they set up
The DVD also comes under it...
DVDx2  haven't been watched
I'm scared of this really...
It's only Tanaka who hasn't sorted his thing out..
He's unable to handle it
I just can't go and just put it in...
There are 2, right?
Honestly, I don't think it will be just you Tanaka.
Do you think this year, finally, it could be different?
Thai Kick 4 years straight from the DVDs
Hotel
News
Airport
Teacher
Like you know...
Yeah, if we push him to do it too much, and then it ends up being us..?
Oh, that's true.
That could happen...
I hope not obviously...
Go!!
Seriously, um, please don't be me...
You know, when did this whole, like, "Tanaka Thai Kick" thing start?
It's been about 3 years
Seems like it will be drama
Was there one with a Drama?
There have also been songs...
Tanaka OUT Angel
People have feelings that they wish to tell...
Feelings of gratitude VIA Letter
This time, the appreciative feelings that want to be expressed
Living in Osaka prefecture, 11 and 12 year old sisters
Eh~~~~~!?
Even though he is always busy with work they say he always plays with them,  To their beloved father
Papa portrait sketched by the sisters
They will send their first letter ever to him
What kind of person is your Dad?
He appears on Television, that is his job
He is an interesting and serious person.
Eh~~~~~!?
How is your Dad a serious person?
He teaches us various things
He tells us how to act when we're older and when we have to get a job
Her dream is to be an actress. From the first daughter to Papa.
... Oh, so her dream is to be an actress too?
Yama-chan's face, hahaha
Thank you for always doing your best at work.
Thanks to Papa working very hard for us,
the family can eat food and be very happy.
I am truly grateful
But there was that time when Papa said, "We're going to Osaka."
I was very worried at that time if I could make friends
But because Papa chose a really safe place to live and a great school for us, I was able to make really good friends.
and that's thanks to Mum as well of course, but thanks to you Papa
and recently, when you took me to Aoi Shima... I was extremely happy you know
I hate it when you're drunk and all weird but when you play with us, it makes us happy.
You can't do this. It's totally ruining the mood...
received from his daughters
The times when Papa is tired from work, and Momo wants to talk to you..
when I have a fight with my friends, you teach me a lot of things
and Papa, you have taught me how valuable family and friends are....
from here on, even when you think you're tired from work, please continue to tell me things.
And let's hang out as a family and have fun.
Do your best, Love you Papa, Year 5, Class A- Yamasaki Momo
Her dream is to be a manicurist, from the second daughter to Papa
To Papa, for always doing your best at your work for the sake of your family, thank you.
Even though you're always tired due to work, on your days off you play with me and it makes me happy
Papa, I'm happy you're a storyteller now. I am really happy I have a Papa like that too.
Thank you for teaching and developing us so well.
I get to be fed by you,
and you buy me the things I need in life, and you try your best in your job, you make us really happy Papa, so thank you.
And also you protect our family as much as possible, thank you
I have so much gratitude that I just cannot express with words.
The things we do, admirable things, cheerleading, like Papa at work we will try twice as hard.
From now on, with cheerleading, studying also, I will try even harder.
Like Papa, even if it's a little bit, I want to make everyone a bit happier and treat my family well.
and my friends as well...
You can't do this. It's totally ruining the mood...
From here on... please do your best at work.
This was bad... It nearly set me off...
Papa, thank you so much, I love you. Yamasaki Ara
Momo-Chan
Rara-Chan
Do your best, Love you Papa
Yamasaki Momo
Yamasaki Rara
You held out well, didn't you?
Absolutely the wrong concept
What's this!?
I properly wept at that..
Yeah, I was close..
The second disc is just too scary now...
Ah, that might be
Yeah, we all have kids...
We all  have kids
We all have kids
That would be extremely weird
Has he gone for it?
I put it in.
It will be fine.
It could be something totally different, I guess...
Yeah that's true; we don't know that.
People have feelings that they wish to tell...
Feelings of gratitude via Letter
This time, the appreciative feelings that want to be expressed
Living in Tokyo Prefecture, A 9 year old Boy
9 year old Boy
Even though he is always busy with work he says he always plays with him,  To his beloved father
Papa portrait sketched by the son
He will send his first letter
What type of person is your Papa?
He does comedy and performances I think...
A Papa who plays with me.
His dream is to be a cartoon writer. From son to Papa
To Papa: On times off from work, you play with me
Papa I love you
But nowadays, you're so tired that even when you're at home,
you're sleeping a lot of the time. I'm sorry for throwing a football at your head when you're sleeping.
Wife Kohinata Shie
The time we went together to the park to play football was the best
You said that if I put strings around the ball and did normal kick ups like that
then I would get better at kick ups.
So when I was able to do the drill better than before, I was really happy.
Despite being tired you also came to my football match, that made me really happy.
And recently, when you came to see my match,
you told me I defended well.
And you complimented me and it made me want to try harder.
I heard from Mama, that Papa doesn't know a lot about soccer and you've never played it
but you asked your friends about the rules of football, right?
Thank you for studying about football for my sake
When you go abroad to work, you take the lucky charm I made you
Papa's protected treasures from his son
And you always put it in your draw which contains the most important stuff
On television, you always do weird things
the next day
My friends say a lot of nasty things and laugh at me a lot
but to me, when I watch Papa on TV, I think you are cool;
that's why the next time you watch my football match,
in order to look good in front of you, I will try my best.
Papa, thank you very much for everything.
I love you
From 3rd year red class Tanaka   Thai kick
From 3rd year red class Tanaka Thai Kick
His beloved son orders a Thai Kick
What the hell is this?!
Seriously, what the hell!?
Papa Tanaka, do your best!!
Man...
You have no choice but to just try your best.
Cry it all out
Must be having various feelings
Wow, so this is how humans react huh?
It can't be helped
They become like this I guess...
You must have been glad
Wait, you guys got nothing
the ending wasn't good
The ending was horrible
Endo also looked like he was crying
I was thinking about various things
Maybe it's because it was about your comedy partner.
The guy who kicked you might have a kid as well.
Quite unexpected happening
2:30 time since...
2 and a half hours since the start
Presented to the 5 is a mysterious spectacle
A "Showa" family preparing dinner
What was this again?
Dear! Dinner is prepared and ready.
After this
Matsuko Deluxe
Dear! Dinner is prepared and ready.
Terauchi Kantaro
Matsuko Deluxe
Kobayashi Assei Look-alike
They really look alike
Terauchi Kantaro I-kka
A drama about Terauchi Kantaro as the dad and his family
living peacefully in Tokyo in the Showa times.
Oh this is new
That's amazing
It was really similar to the original show
Right, let's eat.
Itadakimasu
Shuhei
Are you studying properly?
Yeah a little bit...
That's Hideki-san
Only a little bit? I am paying a lot of money...
Yeah Yeah
What do you mean "yeah yeah"? Is that how you should talk to your father?!
Dear please stop... It's my fault...
You're so miserable and particular
Typical day in the Teranai household
Father and son often fight
What do you mean? I haven't said anything!!
All you ever do is complain!
Your ways are so outdated.
"Outdated"? You bastard!
Yeah, it's really old
I dare you to say that again, you bastard!!
IT'S OLD!!!
Apologize, you bastard
Typical day in the Teranai household
Tantrum
That's dangerous
Watch out
Please someone help...
Someone who is tall, help!!
Please help!!
Tanaka is dragged into the fight
Who the hell are you?
Who are you?! You asshole!!
Seriously who are you?
You bastard, you just come into my house!!
I said who the hell are you!?
Typical day in the Teranai household
Pissed off Dad cannot be calmed...
Stop this at once!!
Hurry and die, you hag
Shit man...
Just made him fly across the room...
Man that is too scary!
Scary
There's still more?
Let's eat
Carrying on as if nothing happened
Please just stop...
Please don't fight anymore
Wouldn't it be better to put this to rest?
Every one is worn out
I heard you've got a girl now, you bastard!!
Yeah I do.
This little punk...
Not studying and just getting girls!
I am studying
Until you get into University
Stop doing dishonest things and be a good kid!
Why do I take advice about how to act from you?!
Pops' thinking is truly OLD I'm telling you!!
You ungrateful bastard!!
That's enough
Typical day in the Teranai household
Huge brawl
He is an genuine idiot
Help
Someone with muscles!!  Please help.
Matsumoto gets dragged into the brawl
Please come quick.
Old man with muscles
please help
Who are you!?
Listen to me...
Let's stop
Listen, Shuuhei
Watch this...  this is impurity
Watch this... this is impurity!
What do you think?
Let's go
Let's go now, I've had enough
C'mon let's go
You get it?
You too...
Do you get it?
When I talk about impurity...  this is what I mean
When I talk about impurity... this is what I mean
He's become quite admirable
That guy is amazing
As far as earth defense force  none of this has anything to do with it.
As far as earth defense force none of this has anything to do with it.
That was new.
If you said that (he) would be dressed as a man , i wouldn't have understood
He reverted to his true(original) look
He looked so much like the original...
11:00 am
3 hours since joining defense force
Lunch is served a little earlier...
Everyone, do you want some food?
We would like that
As part of the earth defense force in order to attain your meal  we will integrate a training method
Lunch will be received as result of the training
The training you will receive will be directed by this person here
Please enter
Good Morning
Not him again
Training Instructor
Shinagawa Hiroshi
Let's just eat normally
I want to eat normally
Okay, everybody listen part 2
You're going to compete for lunch and carry out this exercise...
praise
compliment
food improvisation singing contest!
Cuisine lyrics exchange rule
Shinagawa choose one of the five to
sing about the food written on the card shown
Rules as follows: Shinagawa shows a card to one of the five and they must praise the food in a song
Designated person following the melody
Improvise a song introducing and praising the food
They must sing about the food in a melody
and compliment the food in that song
Shinigawa judges who improvised the best and that decides
what lunch box they are able to eat
Lastly, Shinagawa will decide who did the best and worst and they get a lunch box accordingly
As an examplelet's get Fujiwara san to give us an example.
As an example let's get Fujiwara san to give us an example.
They sing to the tune of Momotaro
The example will be Momotaro. Here we go.
Music Start!
Momotaro
example
Shrimp chili
It's Ebi chili! It's Ebi chili!
with its enticing red color
puri puri consistency with a good texture
That's too difficult
I will give you the 'food' as we start
eh?
Who is out?
Huh?
Punisher comes out accidentally...
What the hell!?
ahh that was a hard one
What just happened?
The song is Under the big chestnut tree
Song they must sing to
Underneath the big chestnut tree
Let's just listen to the melody
Yeah, I'm not sure how the song goes again.
Musical piece:[♪Under the chestnut tree]melody used for altered song
The first assignment will be "Under the Big Chestnut Tree"
Under the Big Chestnut Tree
you and me
let's be friends and play
underneath the big chestnut tree
Ths is actually not that bad..
Not especially fast
Starting with Tanaka-san
Get Ready
Music Start
♪Underneath the Big Chestnut Tree
Subject
Macaroni Gratin
put the macaroni in white sauce
put it in the oven until it's brown
let's eat it with weiners
*NOTE: he meant to say together instead of weiner
the gratin
that's the cooking process
he's clearly laughing
he said weiner!
together ... (In Japanese Minna- everyone)
weiner?
"together"
on top of that wasn't his song turning into Momotaro-san?
on top of that, wasn't his song turning into Momotaro-san?
Oh yeah, it was
It was turning into Momotaro-san
It was a mess
(Inaudible)
Damn, this is difficult
He ended it a bit too short
Can we move on?
♪ Underneath a big chestnut tree ♪
Music Start!!
♪Underneath the Big Chestnut Tree
Subject
boiled tofu
There was boiled tofu
there was a big boiled tofu
there was such tofu
I ate with white tofu
What the hell?
You can't say much about boiled tofu
words just weren't coming out
you just introduced many tofus
You have to praise it!!
Rain rain pour pour my mom
la~ la~ la~
pitter patter drip drip
she came to pick me up with the umbrella, i am happy
Challenge song: "Amefuri'"s tune with different lyrics
The melody is changed, the song is now "Amefuri"
Please forget about "Underneath the Big Chestnut Tree"
if you remember it-
Oh! That's right
Are you ready?
ME?
Yes, from Tanaka-san
Wait a moment.
♪Amefuri
Subject
Potato Salad
Thanks...
His voice is so small..
Out!
I said to forget "Underneath the Big Chestnut Tree"
He was dragged (by the previous song)
the song is wrong
"Potato Salad thank you"
was what he was saying
He said "thank you"
to the potato salad
That was awful, Tanaka-san
He was only as loud as he was before his debut
Hosei-san, it's hard
That voice was pre-debut
Music Start!
♪Amefuri
Subject
Mabo-tofu
*NOTE:mabo-tofu is meat and tofu
Mabo-tofu and my mom
made a lot but
really delicious white tofu
What the hell was that?
That was so weird
Of course that was weird
I don't even know what I'm saying anymore
This is difficult!
Matsumoto's Challenge
Next, Matsumoto will make a parody of "Amefuri"
Music Start!
♪Amefuri
Subject
Goya Stir-Fry
Stir-fry stir-fry goya stir-fry
Stir fry of goya and my mom
Pitter patter drip drip stir-fry fry
Oh this is good! That was good!
I worked hard!
"Pitter patter drip drip" and
"stir fry" were connected
It was connected because the subject was fit for the song
Because it was goya stir fry,
you were singing kind of like an Okinawa Folk Song
Hehehe
You were just laughing   Definitely
Hamada-san it's your turn
Music Start!
♪Amefuri
Subject
Eel Bowl
Everyone likes eel bowl
you ngh hng pour from the top
*NOTE: Hamada choked
drink the sauce too, la~ la~ la~
Just, no no no.
Sauce
But that ...
that thing didn't come to mind
You mean eel liver soup?
It's eel liver soup
Hosei ... 2 points Matsumoto ... 1 point Hamada/Endo/Tanaka ... 0 points
Progress
What?! That was 1 point?
I 'm definitely not losing
to Tanaka and Hamada
All you did was say
stir-fry and tofu
he said to praise it but you didn't do anything
You didn't praise it, really
"Stir-fry stir-fry"
was all that you said!!
You too, all you said was "tofu tofu"!!
How many points?
It's 2 points.
Why the hell you're definitely wrong!
No, it's weird, it's weird-
You are jumping around and you are too excited
I think endo speaks here
But it's wrong!
Yes, it's definitely weird that he has points
All while he's jumping around in front of my eyes ...
Since the debut I have never seen anything like this
Since our debut I have never seen him like this
What's wrong?
Well, that's okay ...
Then go
Can I go?
No matter how many times you do it-
I don't think I will lose..
Music Start!
Amefuri
subject
Rice Omlet
It's good to break the egg
it's good to put it on the fry pan
and add ketchup, just like that, a fabulous meal
He did say fabulous ...
Your standards are so wrong!
Those were just the instructions on how to make it!!!
What's wrong with you, Hamada?
He's telling us to "praise" it but
But I was praising it
Those were the instructions, Shinagawa - his song
But he put "fabulous"
in the last part
I put it there
So, the instructions are okay?
I can say fabulous or good?
Progress
Hosei ... 2 points Matsumoto/Endo ... 1 point Hamada/Tanaka ... 0 points
It's okay to just repeat "stir fry"?
What happened, what are you saying?
What's wrong?
No no, don't 'what's wrong' me
don't you start taking their side you twat.
No no, don't 'what's wrong' me,
don't you start taking their side you twatpart 3
don't you start taking their side you twat
Ye he's right to be honest..
I felt so sorry for Hamada-san there.
Song: Sing to Sachan's melody
Next will be 'Sachan's melody'
Sachan's
Real name is
Sachiko
But because she is small
she calls herself sachan
How strange, Sachan
Hosei-san let's go. Music start!
Sachan
Subject
Hoicoro- Twice cooked pork
(szechuan)
Hoicoro is
meat and soup put together
it works my tongue a lot
you're very cute
coro
I will crush you!
Works your tongue?
And why 'coro'
The only thing I can think of is Jinsei Kourou
(Note: Jinsei Kourou = famous comedian duo back in 1950's)
Come on guys, let's concentrate
But...
He was able to finish the songso 1 point
He was able to finish the song so 1 point
Matsumoto-sanMusicStart!!
Matsumoto-san MusicStart!!
Matsumoto-san Music Start!!
Sachan
Subject
Chocolate Croissant
Choco Croissant
has chocolate in it and i love it
but it's expensive
so I can't open my wallet for it too often
you're so expensive
-oissant..
What the hell?
He's not complimenting it at all!
He's taking the piss
He is taking the piss!!
He's really taking the piss
No, I meant it's an expensive food.
0 Point
Well obviously!
I got through the whole song!
Obviously 0 points..
No way was that 0 point
No way that was 0 points, right?Oi
No way that was 0 points, right? Oi
Ahhhhhhhhhh!!!
Hey!!
'You're expensive'and Can't open my wallet'are all negatives
'You're expensive' and 'Can't open my wallet'are all negatives
'You're expensive' and 'Can't open my wallet' are all negatives
He's right
That's true
I should have said 'you are wonderful'..
Ye, that would have been better
Hamada's challenge
Are you ready, Hamada-san?
Next is Hamada. Can he praise it well?
Satchan
Subject
Shanghai Fried Noodles
Shanghai Fried Noodles!
It specifically says Shanghai, so ...
There it is!
It has a lot
of vegetables and it's soft
but some people like it
and some people dislike it ha~
there is division
I like it
Shanghai
He's just talking about the place!!
Is it a song about China?
Are you talking about the name of the city?
In the end, all he did was go to the city!!
It's not related to fried noodles
You should have said "noodles" instead
"I like it noodles"
That would have been better
Ah yeah!
"There are people who dislike it" was included as well
"There are people who dislike it"~
You could have stopped at "there are people who like it"
He ended it with the city
It became a song about where you're going for New Year's.
Yes.
Wow, how amazing!
Improv Food Parody Results
Endo Shozo
Tsukitei Hosei
1st place
2nd place
Tanaka Naoki
3rd place
Matsumoto Hitoshi
4th place
Hamada Masatoshi
5th place
The result is, with the worst parody, Hamada is in last place.
3rd place seaweed lunchbox
Ittadakimasu.
1st place 3-course lunchbox
With this lunchbox, I can work harder from noon.
2nd place traditional lunchbox
Ittadakimasu!
This was good, wasn't it?
4th place Old Lady #1 Character Lunchbox
It really looks like her!
5th place cooked sweet potato
There it is.
After lunch, the five get ready for their next task
Is everyone okay?
He comes so often...
He's here again
Now you will go through the EDF's training for new recruits
fight against members of rival branch
participate in joint-recruit training
Really...
That's right.
So joint training...
Joint training...
Joint training
You got to be kidding me...
I wonder what teams will be there
Yeah, me too...
Is everyone ready? This is a special training, so laughing is OK.
Joint-training rules
During training laughing is OK
Combined Recruit Training Center
Please have a seat!
Okay
Earth Defense Force
Osaka Neyagawa Branch
KABA. chan
Animal Hamaguchi
Fujiwara Fujimoto
Anjashu Kojima
Kano Eiko
Kyai~n Udo
Peace Ayabe
The people that will participate in the joint-training are
members of the Osaka Neyagawa branch
and the person who will conduct the joint training is...
Ladies and gentlemen it's a team battle training!!
MC's for this training are these two!!
Happy Girl
Takahashi Maasa
Happy Boy
Okada Keisuke
Babio~n!!
Even though it's early babio~n has come!!
This time's team battle training
MC is Happy Boy!!
My pin-mic kind of gets tangled with my accessories, so
Could you do something about it... IDIOT!!
Am I a sound-check person!! IDIOT!!
Happy Bo~y
WOW!
For Happy Boy, that~
Happy Boy's strong assistant! This person, Happy Girl!
My father is Momotaro Samurai!!
Tonight, I am serving as Happy Girl and I am Takahashi Maasa!
Is this a "Naruhodo-the-World" special investigation? Am I Kusuda Eriko? Idiot!!
Happy Bo~y!
WOW!
I don't get it...
Thank you very much! Thank you!
Earth Defense Force Headquarters
Tsukitei Hosei
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Ogi Mama
As a helper to the EDF headquarters, Ogi Mama is participating.
Also,
For the headquarters, a special guest member
We have prepared an assistant!!
It is this person! Please,
come on!
Kemon?
Isn't it a fighting force?
Come on!
Special Guest Member
Maeda Kenta
Hiroshima Toyo Carp
It's baseball player Kenta!
We ask for your help!
The special guest member is
somebody that everybody knows and he is an ace who represents the Japanese baseball world
Maeda Kenta of the Hiroshima Toyo Carp
Hiroshima Toyo Carp's Young Ace
Maeda Kenta
Hello, Maeda Kenta here!
My nickname is "Matsuken" but am I "abarenboushougun"...
IDIOT!!
Happy Bo~y!
WOW!
Alright, Kenta-san is your assistant!
What?!
Amazing!
I want to do a little interview
Do you believe in ghosts? Or not? That's all!
I don't believe in them
That's all, thank you. With that, please go to your seat.
Don't you have more things to ask him?!
Will and Pride put at risk
Crushing Training Battle!!
Headquarters Team
Osaka Neyagawa Branch
Will and pride are put at risk in the hot, crushing training battle!
It will begin now!
Will and pride put at risk
Crushing Training Battle!!
Headquarters Team
Osaka Neyagawa Branch
The men's pride and will are risked in the crushing training battle!
The first task is...
Happy conveyor battle!
Conveyor Battle!!
With the explanation, here we go, Happy Girl
Because within the EDF teamwork is essential,
Happy Conveyor Battle!!
5 Representatives
face various challenges
5 team representatives will face various challenges on the conveyor!
If one person fails, then everyone receives punishment
Mission Failed
Everyone Punished
so please work hard together!
It is teamwork!
SO, the first obstacle is...
Sneeze!
SNEEZE!!
joint training #1
Sneeze!
several "tissue straws" stream on the belt
rules
The rules are simple
straws made of tissues will stream down on a conveyor belt
cleared if they sneeze!!
they take turns sticking them up their noses. if even one person sneezes, they're clear.
Seriously, what the hell kind of drawings are those?
Earth Defense Force
Osaka Neyagawa Branch
Sneeze!!
First, these members from Osaka Neyagawa Branch will go.
You have to sneeze!
I got it!
It's a sneeze!!
IT'S A SNEEZE!!
What the hell
With that, folks
conveyor... START!
Good luck, everyone!
Yes!
Get one!
Yes.
Within your own time, right?
It's not good to rush him.
Oh it's here!
Give up! Give up!
*choking*
No, no
You can do it!
Yes!
Work hard!
Further, further!
Even further up!
Oh, it worked
Ah, no!
Come on, you can do it
Seriously, what the hell?
You can do it!
He has it, he has it
Little Kitty, break a leg
That's a lovely sight
His finger is stuck out so much.
Further.
Further, further!
Further!
How elegant
No good!
You can do this.
It's coming! He can do it!
It's over!
He's the last one!
He's stuck it so far!
Papion!
No way...
Oh, it came out.
I sneezed, I sneezed!
I sneezed!!
What a mess.
But "papion"!!
"Papion" came out.
That was a shameful display; you fail!
MISSION failed
EDF Headquarters
their training task ... ?
Next, the headquarters' turn. What will their task be?
Avoid the extremely smelly nose spray
Dodge the extremelly smelly nose spray!!
Happy Girl~  the rules
Yes the rules
Combination Practice 3
Avoid the smelly Nose spray!!
Rule
6 Nose sprays will emerge
1 by 1 the nose spray will arrive in order, spray 3 times
Each person will try a Nasal Spray
1-2-3, do it 3 times
of course entirely within your nostrils
Please make a nice face!
There is only 1 smelly Nose spray bottle
However if only once the smelly nose spray
You can't be serious
is chosen and used
If you can avoid that smelly bottle, Clear
That's going to be deep in your nostrils
We won't be able to get the scent out of our nose...
This, of course, is luck
Well, is everyone prepared!? Okay, let's start!
Let's get it
Yes!
Conveyor ~ Start!
Mr. Maiken
It's all luck, huh?
that's true
Remember to spray 3 times
Remaining
6 choices
Spritz 3 times
More like, this is truly luck, right?
Pure luck
What kind of smell I wonder
This is scary
Going
Yes
Safe
5 choices
Excellent, keep it up
okay, this is it
Okay here we go...
Choose carefully...
See how lucky
look for what looks familar
I'll understand when I see it
So the result
okay I'm going
3 times
4 choices
Good job Kenta
will you put such a (strange) thing in your nose?
2-3
He's enduring well huh?
did he make safe choice? SAFE? SAFE?
What is it?
Safe oh!
3 choices
You're okay? You're okay, right?
Safe? safe? safe? quickly say if you're safe
eh it smells...
It smells?
It Stinks!
wait a minute
What's happening?
There is a serious stench
That's amazing
He said he was safe
So with this, the mission is a failure
Mission Failed
That stinks!!
Headquarters Team
Osaka Neyagawa Branch
So neither won any points in the first round, to the second round we go
What will they have to do?
5 word shiritori
5 Word Syllable match game
New Year's food
Fusion practice
5 word Shiritori
Rule
Written words on sketchbook will stream out
The words you have written on the sketchbook
will proceed out on the conveyor belt
Key Word 1
New Year's Food
Word Game
Osechi
If the written word can't be connected
Science
Word Game
Bonito
Science
New Years Food
If you fail to match, move on to the next word
Key Word 2
Armor
Sketchbook will proceed to
Word Game
Science
Bonito
Chocolate
Mission is cleared after the 5 word is used
Game
Science
Bonito
New Years Food
Watch
5 Word Shiritori
Earth Defense Force
Osaka Neyagawa Branch
Pioneers Osaka Neyagawa Branch
Everything is fine, Mr. Animal?
OK!! I'm good.
AChaChaChaChaCha
No one is laughing...
So, anyway, let's begin now...
Starting from 'Ri' Part of Shiritori
Start the Conveyor
Umm Ri..
Shiritori(Word Game)
Keyword 1
Roulette
Shiritori
Word Game
Risu
Squirrel
Shiritori
Surume
Dried squid
Shiritori
Risu
Mezashi
Dried Sardines
Shiritori
Risu
Surume
Shikoku
Japanese island
Shiritori
Risu
Surume
Mezashi
Kuma
Bear
Shiritori
Risu
Surume
Mezashi
Shikoku
Mari
Mary
Risu
Surume
Mezashi
Shikoku
Kuma
Ri-ru
Real
Surume
Mezashi
Shikoku
Kuma
Mari
Ru-letto
Keyword 2
Pineapple
Shikoku
Kuma
Mari
Ri-ru
Tokei
Watch
Kuma
Mari
Ri-ru
Ru-letto
Inu
Dog
You can do it
Mari
Ri-ru
Ru-letto
Tokei
Numeri
Slime
HUH!?
Ru-letto
Tokei
Inu
Rinpa
Lymph
Tokei
Inu
Numeri
Painappuru
Keyword 3
Truck
Inu
Numeri
Rinpa
Ru-to
Root
Numeri
Rinpa
Painappuru
Torakku
Keyword 4
Rhinoceros
Rinpa
Painappuru
Ru-to
Kusai
Smell
He didn't need the 'I' at the end!
Painappuru
Ru-to
Torakku
Inu
Dog
Ru-to
Torakku
Kusai
Nurui
Lenient
Ru-to
Torakku
Kusai
Inu
Ikaku
Menace
Torakku
Kusai
Inu
Nurui
Kusai
Smell
Do it right!!
Kusai
Inu
Nurui
Ikaku
Inu
Dog
Nurui
Ikaku
Kusai
Nurie
Coloring book
Nurui
Ikaku
Kusai
Inu
Esa
Bait
Ikaku
Kusai
Inu
Nurie
Sai
Keyword 5
Brakes
Kusai
Inu
Nurie
Esa
Ibu
Authority
Inu
Nurie
Esa
Sai
Bure-ki
Mission Success
Clear!
Kusai(smell) became its own hell
Kusai
Earth Defense Main Branch
5 Word Shiritori
Now will be the Main branch's trial
the results
From the Ri in shiritori
Beginning with Hamada
Yes!
Very good, Let's Begin!
Conveyor ~ Start
Keyword 1
Horse
Shiritori
Risu
Squirrel
Shiritori
Suika
Watermelon
Shiritori
Risu
Kaba
Birch
Shiritori
Risu
Suika
Banto
Bunt
Shiritori
Risu
Suika
Kaba
Tonma
Fool
Suika
Kaba
Banto
Ma-chi
March
Such a sorrowful old man!!
Suika
Kaba
Banto
Tonma
Chiri
Dust
Kaba
Banto
Tonma
Ma-chi
Rika
Science
Banto
Tonma
Ma-chi
Chiri
Kaba
Birch
Tonma
Ma-chi
Chiri
Rika
Basu
Bus
Ma-chi
Chiri
Rika
Kaba
Suika
Watermelon
Rika
Kaba
Basu
Karintou
Japanese sweet cake
Kaba
Basu
Suika
Ushi
Cow
Ehh?
Using this is fine! Right here is okay!
Ushi! Ushi!(Cow)
Oh, we're finished man!
Basu
Suika
Karintou
Shimauma
Zebra
This type of horse is no good? Ma-ma-ma
Suika
Karintou
Ushi
Mari
Mary
Karintou
Ushi
Shimauma
Ringo
Apple
Ushi
Shimauma
Mari
Goma
Sesame
Shimauma
Mari
Ringo
Mausu
Mouse
Shimauma
Mari
Ringo
Goma
Suika
Watermelon
Mission failed
That was horrible
You are Ogi MaMa  right?
You are really him right?
I didn't actually understand the rules
Main Branch
Osaka Neyagawa Branch
Fill in the Translation
Next Practice method is
Happy Monmari kiss battle
Monmari Kiss Battle
Monmari Chair
Joint training 3
Monmari Kiss Battle
Rule
Team representative showdown from all places and ages
The team representatives
The kiss target will get closer as random questions are missed
Secret Character
If you get 3 subjects wrong ♥ Kiss
After 3 incorrect answers
Monmari machine will  be in range for a character kiss
Monmari Kiss Battle
Main Branch Team
Hamada Masatoshi
Osaka Neyagawa Team
Ayabe Yuji
Peace
Hamada Rep Vs Ayabe Rep
And finally the the characters
With that, those making their appearing, Present yourself
Women androids
Barbie
Grandmother #1
So we will have 2 androids
Okay let's get the ball rolling, will everyone please get ready
Who will be with which android?
There are only two to choose from?
What shall we do Hamada-san?
Are you participating?
How about your preferred?
Isn't the hag good for you?
The 'cougar' is right there she can hear you
It's your choice
'He chose Barbie !!' is sort of what your face is saying
Anyone would say they prefer Barbie(in this situation)
Monmari
Barbie
The final results of the pairing
Representative
Hamada Masatoshi
Monmari
Granny #1
Representative
Ayabe Yuji
And the questions the two will get are as follows
Talent who write their name in Katakana
Katakana is a system of letters used to denote foreign influence or origin
Let's begin with this one
Talents' names which entered as Katakana
With that all ages topic, from Hamada
Kiss Monmari Start
Magi Shiro-san
Yuusuke Santamaria-san
Completely in Katakana
That is how it's written
He doesn't have many names in his head...
Ai George
You can just tell he doesn't have that many names left can't you!?
They're already running out of names...
Izumi Pinko-san
That's a good one...
Celebrities with Katakana's in their name
Stops doing that "um~~~" (thinking aloud)
Like he's blown a fuse...
Oh, Maggie.
Terakado Jimon-san
That was quick
He's giving names with ease.
Our one is struggling already...
He's cracking...
The cracks...
There are loads, you know?
Calm down, calm down...
You have to be kidding me...
He's gone...
Rola, Rola, Rola...
Time up!
Unfortunately, you ran out of time...
Celebrities with Katakana in their names
Odagirishou, Utada Hikaru, Tamori, Piko
Wada Akiko, Korokke, Shibasaki Kou
And because you ran out of time...
Hamada-san's android... Come on...
Monmari Start!
How close is she going to get?
She's hungry, really hungry!
She's coming really close...
Oh man, she's getting closer...
This is bad...
This is just...
Right now... She has come quite close already...
Are you okay?
Tokyo Metropolitan Areas
Shinjuku
good...
Edogawa
In the next round, both did very well...
Shinagawa
and gave a lot of answers, but...
Oh, he's struggling...
He's definitely struggling...
Shinagawaku!
The two guys were at a tie
The distance between them and disaster evened out...
Right, let's carry on...
National Holidays
First up, Hayame
Kiss Monmari, Start.
Sports Day (holiday)
Oh you have gotta be kidding me...
Labor Thanksgiving day
Oh, good.
They're starting to struggle...
Marine day
Hes taking way too long...
Wait, wait, just wait a second...
What do you mean "wait, wait"? Can he do that?
What kind of time do you need?
(morning of) New Year's Day
That, unfortunately, is not technically a "national holiday"
National holidays
coming of age day, National Foundation day, Vernal Equinox Day, Day of culture
What Hamada said is only the morning, therefore not a national holiday.
And that means...
And that means, Hamada-san's android, go!
Monmari start
What's wrong?
Oh this is dangerous
You're in serious danger now!
not able to hear anything
The next one is going to...
Right, next, we have...
Groups which are part of the Janeez (pretty boy groups)
groups which are part of Janeez
You should know a lot of them...
Right first, Hamada starts...
Right, Let's... go!
that's obvious...
Arashi
Okay good, keep going...
He's keeping up...
Oh dear...
Groups part of the Janeez
Shounenbu, Kinki Kids, Takki and Tsubasa, NEWS
Kan Janee 8, KAT-KUN, Kis-My-Ft2
Deary deary deary me...
I didn't hear it... Did he say Tokio?
he did say it...
Yes, I did say Tokio.
He said "Tokio-san"
And that means, Hamada-san's android...
Come on!!
Monmari Start
Grab him hard...
I can't watch...
Go on, keep going...
This is so much worse than an "android"...
After the training, they want to rest now but...
That was harsh...
The next trap has already started...
The next trap has already started now...
Is it really safe?
For crying out loud...
It's on Hamada-san's desk
yep, that's right...
Mysterious button
It has nothing to do with us...
Yup...
There is definitely something going on...
Because I'm wearing thick socks...
I'm really hot...
The trousers as well...
Yamasaki-san was just casually laughing
Yamasaki-san was just casually laughing...
I know...
Yup...
Is it like a Barbie
personalized flavour?
Yeah...
I don't really need to push that button...
But it was on Hamada-san's desk...
It was there from the start.
We haven't moved it or anything.
It says, "Whatever happens, do not push."
Yeah yeah, we swear.
Man, it was so cold...
responsibility of pushing the button
Hamada
Endo
It says, "Whatever happens, do not push."
Exactly...
So I don't think we have to push it...
It's just a button, we don't have to...
Don't bring it here... come on...
Hamada
Housei
Well usually the person who pushes the button... has to be... Tanaka
Eh?
If you say button, it has got to be you...
Hamada
Endo
Tanaka
I honestly haven't had buttons in my drawers... like ever...
I don't think it will be like "because you pushed it, you get punished"...
Yeah, it was orginally on Hamada-san's desk...
I don't think it will be a punishment to the person who pushed the button...
Come on, push it...
Emmanuel (Webster)
Natually they look at the monitor
Wait, what is this?
After the break
She's back!! Matsuko deluxe
Emmanuel (Webster)
Natually, they look at the monitor
Wait, what is this?
How many times are you going to come out?
Emmanuel (Webster)
Matsuko Deluxe
You've come out too much on here, surely?
How many times are you going to come out?
He's working too hard...
The screw moving him falls off
Look at that...
The screw came off...
What are you doing?
The screw came right off...
How long are you going to do that?
What kind of face is that?
Surely you need the screw to move...
I get it Matsuko... Please forgive me
Giving a lovely smile
Look, we were totally in the wrong...
Like seriously...
She's amazing...
She's here the whole time!!
Like the whole time!
come on guys...
So she wasn't done yet...
Push button
Emmanuel comes out
So there's no point pushing it...
No, no point at all...
Just annoying...
There's no point, no point...
If we press it again, will she come out again?
Oh just leave it...
I'm not sure, she might not...
Emmanuel
Emmanuel returns again
She's back...
As we thought...
It fell again...
Screw moving her falls off
It fell off again
Seriously, leave it out!
We've already seen this...
Why does that screw always fall off?
I know, and she still moves...
Your screw came off...
Here she comes...
Giving another lovely smile
She's massive
Why did they cast her to do it?
The original kid was no where near that big...
He was so cute...
And that screw thing sticking out of her back creeps me out...
It's just like...
Well obviously...
Again...
So if we press it, she comes out...
Okay...
My butt is likenearing its end
My butt is like nearing its end
Yeah, my butt is as well...
Same here...
If we press it one more time, I wonder if she comes out?
Emmanuel
For crying out loud...
Will she actually come?
This will be the 3rd time
Surely not...
No way...
Press the button and she WILL come
She has come!
She's coming!!
The screw falls off again
So however many times...
Cannot hear
It's the face she makes as she comes out...
Seriously, enough...
She is kind of cute...
Let's go our separate ways...
yeah, let's move on...
Emmanuel confiscates the button
She's telling us to give her a break
Okay we get it...
You want to rest, right?
We are sorry...
That was fun...
Seriously...
My butt is like...
Seriously, my butt is quite...
My butt is in trouble...
Those foundation materials aren't really...
Yeah they are a bit...
Isn't this a little bit hard?
I'm worn out
I want to take a shower
Guys,  you've started to look more like an Earth Defense Force, don't you think?
Guys, you've started to look more likean Earth Defense Force, don't you think?
Guys, you've started to look more like
an Earth Defense Force, don't you think?
Not at all!!
We still have a long way to go...
Where were you looking?
Starting from now,
we will move to the Earth Defense Force's training center, of course, in order to undergo a special training. Shall we go?
In order to further skill up the members,
they'll go to the Earth Defense Force's training facility
Let's do this
Where are we going? Outside?
Obviously we're going to reach it by going outside
You gotta be lying...
Seriously?
By bus!?
It's freezing!
They enter the bus a second time
It means that, naturally,
It will be a severe journey
it will be a severe journey
On those who waited before...
A new battle curtain is rising!
1:30 PM
5 hours and half since the Earth Defense Force's training began
The 5 are having an eye on the bus which is taking them to the training facility
There is no need to say that the journey won't be easy
Yeah we got this, let's move forward
Isn't that the same bus as before?
Really?
Arrived at the stop
It stopped again...
You've got to be kidding me...
This one stops too?
Crap...
Catwoman: Anna Tsuchiya
Joker: Yuuki Himura
Whoa, that was...
That's totally impossible
What the hell do you mean by
"Totally Impossible"!?
"Totally impossible"
I wonder what
Move
It's impossible to take a position
Really impossible
Yeah, it's bad
Awesome, huh?
Crap, that's regrettable
Regrettable!
Yeah, we did
But we tried with everything we had, right?
Because we can wear these suits and still casually
Uh...
make the audience laugh
Yeah you're right...
The two are sluggish comedians
We usually can
What I think is that
The outfit can't be wrong, right?
What the?
He's so fat!
Should we show those people  our jokes?
uh..?
Should we show those people our jokes?
Should we?
Um, excuse us
Hm
Being comedians
Right
We would like to perform our skits, would you like to see our jokes?
Yes of course, please
Very well
Tch!!
Sorry, we need your help
Let's do this!
"School"
Here we come
Double Cheesecake is presenting this short comedy skit
"School"
Short skit: School
*opening the door*
I'm here
Are you serious?
I'm on duty... and so are you!
Ah, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I literally did all the work by myself...
I'm sorry
Tell me, is there any remaining work to do?
I must move this desk to the science room
Ah, I got it
It doesn't matter, I'll do it by myself
Huh?
Oy oy, wait, what are you doin'?
Because you're a woman
You must leave this kind of
strength-based work
to a man like me...
I FRIGGIN' FELL IN LOVE!
That's the story
of the people!!
It's not even rare
It's not even baked
Yeah
Double Cheesecake!
They made it...
Those guys are idiots
Source of their sluggishness: Basically, their stories are rip-offs
They stole the skit (from other comedians)
Right
Totally...
Next is a short comedy skit brought to you by Double Cheesecake
"Big fan"
Ah~ let's do this one more time
She said "one more time"...
A short comedy skit brought to you by Double Cheesecake
"Big fan"
"Ahaha" I can say
Oh, wrong!! It's not that skit
I'm sorry
Source of their sluggishness: The female comedienne acts too freely
What the hell?!
Too much freedom!
Could we stop this at once?
This is getting our butts slapped, you know...
Why am I getting slapped for this?!
That's ridiculous
What the hell...
I'm sorry
Himura is overwhelmed at this point
That's a useless round
One more time?
A useless round
Because I can set the switch
A short comedy skit brought to you by Double Cheesecake
"Convenience Store"
Convenience Store
Welcome!
*beep*
If you please
Should I warm you up the boxed lunch?
Oh, yes, please
Ah, sorry, one more thing: two meat buns, please
Meat buns?
It's prohibited
When I seeeeeeeeeeee~~
...Eeeeeeeeeeeeee~~
A man who's buying a meat bun at the convenience store
I feel like I can make it!
Or that's what I think
You're so annoying and noisy!
No one see that one coming
Enough of this
They're not allowed to laugh, right?
***the worst
Will they not get angry at me?
Source of their sluggishness: The female comedienne is also way too carefree
Wait, hold on...
I was trying really hard not to laugh...
Don't talk please
That's right, stay quiet
If you speak that's no good
We tried our best
I've been told that I am not allowed to laugh...
A short comedy skit brought to you by Double Cheesecake
Are they starting over?
Wait a second... Okay.
"Surgical operation"
I wonder how they'll...
Surgical Operation
Okay then
Let's start the surgical operation
You can't laugh, ok?
Okay
Response?
No~~!
He's out!
Yeah! DON DON DON!
Out out out
DON! DON! DON!
OOOOOUT!
That's the story
of the people!!
It's not even rare
it's not even baked
wertwer
Double Cheesecake
Go back home already!
Hey!
Do it properly, you're just messing around
Yeah, seriously, I think...
I think having accepted this work... It is itself a mistake.
Then you should do it properly, having accepted it
But I couldn't help it!
I already told you to do it properly, it's your fault you don't!
You're noisy!
What are you saying?!
Shut your trap!
What the hell is you problem, you bast-
What kind of situation...
No way!
Source of their sluggishness: Kissing is really embarrassing ♥
Not even rare
Not even baked
Double Cheesecake!
Thank you, thanks!
Farewell!
Seriously, I didn't mean to laugh when I was doing it...
Get out, jeez!
You don't have to tell us!
They said "farewell"!
I ended up laughing...
That was amazing...
Indeed
Awesome
We're free, right?
You get those kind of people...
Carefree people, right?
Yeah
Yeah those kind of people...
I'm a bit envious...
One thing after another
The bus journey will get worse and worse...
Again...
Arrived at the stop
That's enough, seriously...
Enough with those...
What should we feel once the bus stops?
Earth Defense Force executive staff:
: Itao Itsuji
Itao Itsuji
Deep fat executive staff: Itao's wife
She looks strange!
These two again?
Her form changed way too much, ain't I right?
You think so?
She looks the same to me
His wife has not appeared for a while due to maternity leave.
She gained weight after her pregnancy.
Wife long time ago
Of course not!
You sure?
Deep-fat
Must have been after the maternity leave
I heard about that
That's right...
Right?
Those people are, you know, the Earth Defense Force's big shots, a married couple
Those people are, you know, the Earth Defense
Force's big shots, a married couple
They also gave birth to a baby recently. They are in the midst of happiness.
They also gave birth to a baby recently.
They are in the midst of happiness.
What the hell?
What was that speech?
It was nothing!
What kind of situation is this?
Well, they love each other
Well, yeah
That's strange, though
Very passionate indeed
They're loving each other
I don't get what she's doing though...
I wonder if that's different from our culture...
Their mutual love is unstoppable
Don't do this, don't
Stop with that!
They're holding so firmly!
What is the point of that?
What the hell, man
It's a little weird to do that here, come on...
Wait a second!!
He spotted something outside the window
Not fair...
What's that? Over there
Dating agency with Suga from 25 years ago when he was a model
Wait, that's a dirty trick.
What the hell?!
I can see it
What the hell is that?
Eeeeh?
Huh?
Jeez!
What does this mean?
Suga...
We don't need this right now!
What does that mean?
Was that being there just a coincidence?
It's called "Sugakuru"
What's that ad for? That's a young Suga-san
Something for dating and such...
Oh, I think you're right
Because Love is even written on it.
The advertising car is chasing them
Good Morning, Everyone!
Listen to our wonderful rendezvous features
Number of members: 3 million! Frauds: Zero!
That's exaggerated
Japan's biggest match making site for long-established relations, Sugakuru!
Sugakuru is perfect for you if you want to find a real encounter!
Uh? What?
Providing you with the best we can! Enjoy our service!
The advertising car also stopped
The typical song of Itao's wife's dance
You're going to do it?!!
Strange Itao dance
I thought his wife would...
Don't do this!
He's not dancing at all
That's not even a dance
That character of his...
Looks like he's mimicking something!
He's nimble
He's nimble!
These moves...
Looks like a mime though, that's so intense!
He has the moves
He's not following the rhythm at all.
True
Uh, yeah
His wife is...
His wife, uh?
Is it the wife's go now?
Well obviously his wife had to do this.
Fat but sharp: Distinguished
Please, not this!
That's bad
Watch out!!
That's...
That's dangerous!
Well, I must say it was amazing
Really, this
She's teasing us
It appeared, uh? Her former step
Well actually her moves haven't really changed at all, right?
They haven't!
Careful!
Whoa!
Landed
That person completely changed, don't you think?
Well, kinda, she got fatter
She's still doing it
No, wait...
They are still doing it
They have such a good relationship!
Still doing it...
Looks like it
They're so resolute
I understand...
It hurts...
Ah, what a relief
Ah~ They're still doing it.
They're running!
They're reaching us by running!
Wait~
That's not even his character...
After their time of migration with the bus has ended,
the training center draws nearer, right before their eyes!!
Guys, you'll soon start your next training
You should now be able to see the Earth Defense Force training center
The setting of this "Absolutely do not laugh" that rises under Mount Fuji:
Gasu Kurobikari Defense Force of Earth Training center
And inside the facility's field
There's even a circuit track
In this huge training facility for this elite group,
A new battle against the assassins is going to begin!
Members will undergo  training
This is so freaking huge...
Yeah
We arrived, guys. Let's get off, okay?
That's the place where we're going to train?
It is
Training...
Shall we go?
Are we getting off?
Before me, please
Go, please
Getting off?
Inside the facility, the sound of the brake echoes
Come on, we arrived
I could hear a "kikikiki"
That was~
That freaking sound!
Its timing was lethal
That's, without a doubt, not good!
That's DEFINITELY going to be something bad for us
You're right!
Why that sound?
We were even able to hear it to that extent
Of course we know already, we're not stupid...
What's with that sound?
I got it now, I got it...
I had already enough...
The smell of trouble is strong...
Right?
That's the training facility.An amazing place, right?
That "kikiki" keeps going
Oh, this way
That's the center where, as occasion calls, the trainees undergo training
Earth Defense Force: Training Center
So
Awesome!
Wow
Unusual
Interesting
Amazing, though
Yeah
I wonder how it is inside...
I think that  I probably won't be good at this...
I think that I probably  won't be good at this...
What's with this hugeness?
Training Center - Second Floor
It's ridiculously enormous!
Uh huh
This way
Wow, it's amazing...
I wonder how this time will...
Whoa!!
Guys, that's the training facility's
Rookie's training room
Rest here for a while until we come and get you...
We have to go through this again?
There are even drawers again and some of them have numbers on them
Whoa! You're right!
There's already everything, everything, everything
Everything is present
You know, I can't trust anything anymore...
It hurts, it hurts
Looks like the usual room
I have a cramp on one of my ass cheeks, it strikes me more occasionally, recently
I have a cramp on one of my ass cheeks,
it strikes me more occasionally, recently
when this side cramps up, it's bad...
I'm going to the toilet for a sec
That's bad
It is
Men's Toilet
A previous visitor is using the toilet
The user was LiLiCo
Housei is not here
What happened?
Something must have happened over there, right?
He went to the toilet
For sure
I'm afraid...
It surprised me!
What the hell?
What's he doing?
What kind of movement was that?
Once Yama-chan is back we should probably start opening the drawers
You're probably right
Those with the numbers...
Something must be in those
I was surprised!
What just happened? It said "Housei Out" once you went to the toilet
Yeah
What?
I went to the toilet and on the other side there was someone
emitting this absurd "bububu" sound
And the person who came out was...
That person...
That woman...
I think I forgot her name
Don't say it, if you can't remember the most important part!
What the hell, man?! You have to say that part quickly!
Don't talk if you don't know the main topic
Why? You just met her before!
I really forgot it
You forgot it?
Well how did you...
It was that person of mixed race...
Mixed?
Well, there are a lot
There are several of them
A woman of mixed race from recently, a rough person, a bit of a granny character. Some time ago she kinda~
LiLiCo-san
Yeah, right, LiLiCo-san!
LiLiCo was taking a sh*t?
She was taking a sh*t
I swear, she was!
And emitting sounds
That's kinda a bad thing to say
right
Well, if this was real I would be laughing
You're laughing, though
Are you being honest?
Yeah I am!
Ouch
Ow!!
I was really surprised the moment she came out
I would like it if they stop setting traps in the toilet
Enough with those, really, stop
2:30 PM
6 hours and half since the Defense Force training began
Once again, they face off with the contents of the drawers
Ow ow ow
Shall we start opening with Tanaka?
Yeah, I guess we have to, huh?
There must be something inside, look
Look, there's  a DVD player
For real... damn
It doesn't matter if we look at them sooner or later
Right...
If something happens, then it might be a different pattern...
There's no doubt
If it contains something, it's troublesome
I agree
Tanaka is the top batter
Please, be anything but the gas spray
Look
Mysterious DVD
a DVD
One DVD
Only one, huh?
The other is surely where you are
I want to think there aren't any
Right?
But...
What are you doin'?
Sorry
Nothing, just a DVD from him
I'm going next, if you don't mind
Uh!?
Mysterious Letter
What does this...
Ahh, there it is
It's going to be the same...
Ah! That's Matsumoto-san's...
Matsumoto-san's pattern, right?
there it is
Wait, there's more on this desk
Uh!?
Oh, there's something inside
What's that!?
Eh? That's a bit scary.
Mysterious Box
Wait, let me check the rest
Nothing!!
Nothing
There was a single one
ugh...
Which one should we look at first?
Yeah...
It's an envelope, right?
Let's read this at least
We can make some link from that, probably
A link, probably
Right?
Yes
Written Instructions
Open
drawer
number 7!
Number seven...
Here it is
In the rookie's training room there are drawers from number 1 to 20
Ehhh, no more 'POKAN' sounds (loud sounds)
Pokan?
pokan...
I'm opening number 7
Uh?! Wait a sec.
Um?
There's something~
Uh? Is it stiff?
It's stiff
It opened normally...
A second letter
It was stiff, I was working hard
That's because you were scared, right?
I was
He totally was
Number one
Written Instructions
Open
Locker
Number One!
Ah! There!
Is it this?
Scary, scary...
Indeed scary
This pattern is no good...
Terrifying
Wait a sec, wait wait wait!
I'm opening it!
Got it
There's something inside
It's obvious it was there
Again, it has something
Jeez...
It will continue for a while...
Enough...
It was obvious!
They truly don't give up on this prank!
From where did it came out?
From the inside
That gas spray from before was bad
Ouch!
He slapped my stomach!!
That must hurt
It's such a... tender spot!
What's wrong with you?
Cut it out!
Me?
Uh?
Uhuhuh
Endo was slapped by mistake
That was too funny
Enough!
Okak it's a Batsu, but...
Careful!
I didn't even move from before
You stood still
OK
Uh? This keeps going, right? Look, it says "locker number three"
Written Instructions
Open
Locker
Number 3!
Again? Has this not ended yet?
Looks like we have no choice but continue
Scary, scary, scary, scary!
W-wait, that thing is huge!
It is!
So scary!!
That's so scary!!
Secret!
That's scary!
Whoa!
An alien in the locker
Whoa, what's that?
That's kinda creepy
Whoa!
Ugh!
help... me...
help me
please
please!
The alien is complaining about something.
He's talking to you
Go Yamazaki
No, he wants Matsumoto!
That was incredibly creepy!
Creepy indeed!
pleeease
please!
This?
I'm hungry...
Huh?
Why am I the only one who is OUT?
I just smiled...
Just a little smile...
I just smiled
Ow!!!
As expected you couldn't have a dignity, right?
H-he-He said "Hungry"?
He said "hungry"?
Give him some sweets!
Hungry?
He's hungry I guess...
Hungry
Oh he said hungry...
If that's the case
I wonder if a Baumkuchen would be okay...
Why am I doing this?
Stop with painful things and such, please
Please, stop with painful things and such
Matsumoto was attacked by the alien
HOLY SHIT!
WHY?!
Holy shit!
Violence isn't allowed!
Ow ow ow!
What the hell? Since I came here only bad things happened!
Violence?
I am hungry
Enough with this stuff...
Shh, look
Crap, he's coming coming coming here...
Careful!
He's hungry, remember...
Take this Yama-chan! He's hungry!
He's famished!
No, he's saying to feed him something else...
Is it no good?
He has become attached to Housei-san!
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
He seems to like him
It's definitely an alien...
Yeah...
It's definitely an alien
I'm sure this will go fine
Thank you~
What is your name?
Aaah, it went nice, thankfully
Housei
Housei     my friend
That's hilarious
Proof of the friendship between Hosei and the alien.
That's good, that's good
Everything went fine
You're good Yama-chan
Amazing
He was angry because Matsumoto gave him something?
Looks like it
He wanted Yama-chan to feed him...
That's a little...
A situation where the alien wanted to be friends with Housei
That situation was...
That was great
I'm sorry
You think so?
It was really hilarious, I'd say
When he did this
I didn't know aliens were so primitive
He hit me
End of the day...
other planets act the same way huh...
Violence is everywhere...
Are we finished with Yama-chan's drawers?
We have this
This box
It's a rice cake
A graceful salted rice cake for the exhausted body
It's a rice cake stuffed with jam
Don't say it!
You shouldn't have talked!
We figured out by ourselves!
Just by looking at it, we got it
Ouch
Oww
My back hurts...
Is it possible that
this rice cake was placed in order to give it to the alien from before?
Ah, you should have opened the box
And then give it to the alien
That's possible from you, though I gave him a Baumkuchen
And I was almost beaten up by him
It's your turn, Matsumoto-san
Ah, right. I wonder what's inside mine...
It could even come an empty pattern
Well, that's right
Just stop with gas sprays
I'm ready
He's eating so much...
Nothing here
Empty
I seriously don't want the spray!
Enough with that
Seriously, the spray should be banned
Uh?
Looks like a cellular phone...
It's a mobile phone!
What, that's kinda...
Mysterious cellphone
Scary, uh?
Scary, scary
That's one heck of a strange item
I agree
Whoa!!
There's something inside
Hmm?
There is something inside
What's that?
Magic Balloon Kit
Err
A balloon
It's one of those long balloons with which you can create dolls
Aaah, one of those?
uh-uh
Hmm?
Do you know those?
Uh?
Did it bring back some memories?
Uh? What do you mean?
What's that?
Well...
I have no idea...
Well, why would it be in your drawer?
Doesn't this brings up any memory at all?
Uh...
None?
Matsumoto is hiding something.
Uh?
If there's something
Please tell us...
Are you practising it?
Well, this is...
you are practising it?
Yeah, this...
You're practising it?
Well, that's... wait, what do you mean... I mean, what are you asking me to do?
Wait~
We just don't know!
Please fill us in...
What is this meant to mean?
That's great...
What do you mean?
So for your kid...
You went to a balloon class
and going through it?
What the hell
is a balloon art class?
Like how many of them are there?
How much do  the classes cost?
How much do the classes cost?
No seriously, it does exist...
Yeah...
I think it's a really beautiful story
Yeah it really is...
I think it's a really good thing
Maybe it's telling you to do the one that you've specifically learnt
It's in a brand new packet...
Go on, please make it.
Yeah, can you?
Make the one that makes
your kid the happiest...
It's not really about my kid to be honest
It's just a coincidental thing...
If your kid wasn't involved, surely you wouldn't do this...
Oh so you just do it for yourself?
I bet there are just mountains of balloons in his house...
It's not really for myself or anything...
Bloody hell, I can tell you have practised loads
Yeah he's a pro...
What do you mean?
What?
An amateur wouldn't have known to do that first!
He looked so comfortable handling it...
I didn't know "first you have to pull the balloon apart... etc."
Everyone knows that, surely...
No, you wouldn't know that...
Balloon Art 1
In order to not burst the balloon, you stretch it out first
Looks like you have to...
I didn't know...
Oh so you stretch it...
So what are you going to make us?
Jesus, look at how good he is!
Balloon Art 2
Inflate balloon with a handpump
Wow that is amazing...
I didn't realize you had to pump air into it with that...
You don't do it with your mouth...
Please, just shut up
You don't do it with the mouth, you do it with the pump...
You don't even need
to look at the instruction book?
You do this every day, don't you?
No seriously, what the hell?
What?
What's he doing?
He's doing something to the tip...
He's probably doing it on purpose, he knows what he's doing...
Balloon Art 3
Blow the right amount of air in and then tie up the opening
What are you making?
I swear, anyone can do this...
No no, we have normal lives...
I've never...
None of us can make it...
No seriously, I don't know...
Balloon Art 4
Grab the opening of the balloon and twist it into shapes
Please make us something then...
Hang on, do you ACTUALLY do this at home as a hobby?!
Like this...
What a dad... He'll do anything to make you smile...
Balloon Art 5
Bend the balloon to keep its balance and
twist accordingly, making sure air pressure is equal
So when you do it like this...
well, this is in the end... is basically...
a rabbit...
Rabbit has been created!
Very well done
That's amazing!!
Your child would be so happy!
Amazing!!!
This is  so cool!!
This is so cool!!
This is really cool
No seriously, this is like not...
you know...
not for my kid or anything like that
I coincidentally just found it
I coincidentally just found it...
and like umm...
just started doing it...
Oh yeah, if you put on stickers, it looks better. Oh that's so cute!
Put stickers on, and it is KAWAII
Your kid will be so happy
so happy
Matsumoto-san does balloon art, huh?
Matsumoto-san does Balloon art, huh?
I didn't know...
I never thought...
I really didn't know...
So when he's alone, this is what he does...
I guess...
No, everyone does it, right?
No...
I've never done it
Okay, teach me later...
I'm going to open my drawers now...
It's so cute...
Go for it, Hamada-san
Go for it
Go...
nothing...
Maybe there isn't anything...
Oh, there's nothing...
There's a possibility there won't be anything
Maybe there's nothing...
Hang on...
WOW!!
Shit, it's huge!!
That scared me...
Man, that is very made well!
Model M1
It looks so damn funny...
The Model M1...
It's the big version of the M1
Model M1  let's stop playing with it...
are there like loads of other goods you can get?
Does it move?
No, surely not?
It's really unbalanced...
There's something here...
Maybe there's a switch somewhere...
Yeah, I think it moves...
It definitely will...
Oh...
There might be something  somewhere
There might be something somewhere...
There's definitely a catch to this!!
Oh I see, I see...
Maybe it's just meant to stand up?
You're right...
It's amazing
Oh, it moved!!
What the hell...
What's it doing?
What's going on?
wow... wow, wow,wow
hang on...
It stood up!
Wow, amazing!
Stands up on its own and greets them
amazing...
What is this?
I think the switch was...
like...
around here...
probably...
no?
Hang on, it's still moving...
What's going on!
Shit, he's amazing!
greets with 'Sansannanabyoushi' dance
Wow, that's amazing!
It's doing it so fast!
Wow that's amazing...
This is so funny!
How many times am I going to get hit over this!?
It's still reacting
Yeah it is...
Oh, it reacts to sound!?
It could be...
It's reacting, it's reacting
When I held the hand, it suddenly started moving...
Oh, was there a switch?
I don't think I flicked anything though...
Heavy Rotation
Are you kidding me?
For real?
Jeez...
Why?
I don't know if I can laugh at this...
It can dance to "Heavy Rotation"
It's amazing, it dances properly.
Wow, that's amazing.
It just stood on one leg!!
This is amazing...
I don't know if it's like a laughing matter or...
I am touched
What kind of world is this?
This is no good...
It's going to keep on going...
Eh?
It's resting...
yeah...
It's resting in the weirdest position...
It's resting...
When the charge runs out, the body stops...
NOT ABLE TO HEARRRRRRRRRRR
It fell asleep...
It is sleeping?
Shall we like... leave
it over there?
Yeah, let's do that
It is Hamada, after all
No no no, no it's not...
In a few years' time,
that's what you're going to look like...
That's how you look when you're just
chilling at the office, right?
Okay, I'm going to open it...
Well yeah, obviously it was going to be...
you know...
Like we're returning to basics...
They wanted us to open that one first I guess...
This is where it really starts...
What's in there?
oh?
What is it?
That's the same thing as Housei-san's...
Same box as Housei's
Nothing...
Housei-san, what was in yours?
A rice cake...
Yeah, a rice cake
It says, "Please eat for your tired body."
Why does this one have two?
There are 2 rice cakes...
I guess you're meant to eat it...
Yeah, Yama-chan ate his...
It's just rice cake...
A nice salted rice cake for his tired body
How about the other rice cake?
Could it be?
Just a rice cake...
They went so easy on you
They went so easy on you.
Thank God...
You laughed Endo...
No, it got caught in my throat...
Hold on...
Because the staff
didn't put effort into the traps in his drawer so he's...
Yeah to be honest, I'm disappointed.
They didn't put any effort into it at all...
They're just being too easy on me...
Wow...
There was like a hidden message in that hit...
That was hard...
For crying out loud...
the bloody Model M1 is...
Model M1 in the fridge
He's here as well...
He's being frozen...
the Model M1...
M1...
This Model M1 is amazing...
Oh, Tanaka... the DVD
I know right...
DVD hasn't been watched yet
It's still a mystery...
It is...
I personally think this DVD...
one of you three...
one of you...
The DVD at HQ
Housei's and Tanaka's kids sent letters to them
I think it will be something like that...
But...
I don't think so to be honest...
Like even if it is...
It wouldn't just be about me...
you know...
Let's watch it anyway...
I'm putting it in...
I think it could be the same as before...
The whole "feeling touched" thing...
We, at the Gaasu Kurobikari
Earth Defense Force
It is definitely different
because we endure extreme training
we are much stronger than everyone else...
We have the 'Elite Member'
Elite Member
Ebisu Yoshikazu
And that man is... Ebisu Yoshikazu.
This Elite Member's secret mission is...
And today, let's watch the Elite Member's secret mission...
Secret mission
Staying in a sauna for 20 minutes
Staying in a sauna for 20 minutes...
Usually the sauna is set to 90 degrees
Rainbow Sauna at Shinkoiwa
However...
To get the best out of this mission...
It's better to raise the temperature up to 110 degrees
to succeed, he must get great results
as it will get better results...
10 minutes in...
15 minutes in...
Ebisu is sleeping...
What?
I dont' want to see it...
Why does he push himself so far?
To produce  Elite DNA
The reason is...
to produce Elite DNA.
A lot of sweat
Out of Ebisu, comes
a lot of sweat...
And we absorb that
in a high absorption towel
and we squeeze it into the measure cup
and collect it all...
Lots of DNA
We now have a lot of DNA
inside the sweat and then...
We heat it up to purify it
We heat it on a bunsen burner...
and to get rid of all the impurities.
Elite salt is born
and what is created is
100% Elite salt
and with that salt...
we use it to its fullest...
and create the ultimate food...
The Gaasu Rice cake
That's right...
You're kidding me!!!
You've got to be fucking kidding me!!!!!!!!!
That is disgusting!!
That is so disgusting!!
I ate the whole rice cake!!
You had 2!!
You're kidding me!!
For real?!
Elite salt...
That is disgusting!!
Are you serious?!
They weren't going easy on me at all!
I like properly scarfed it!
You really did...
I had 2... 2!!!
Both scarfed it down
That is disgusting
It's really sick, just sick...
The staff gambled on that working
You're right...
If we watched the DVD first you wouldn't have eaten it
That's right
That's so true!
On top of that I opened mine first
Amazing...
That is amazing...
That is so scary...
Never...
They weren't going easy on me at all...
Elite salt... apparently
Ebisu's...
Elite salt...
You'll never get it out...that elite salt
You'll never get it out... that elite salt
I feel sick...
Did it taste good?
Yeah it tasted fine
It was a bit salty...
It was Elite salt after all...
They're shocked by the Ebisu situation...
Earth Defense Force's Training Center    7 hours since starting
but...
they can't be shocked about it forever...
when this gets aired to the public
that will be really popular I bet
But do they sell this?
No way, they definitely don't sell this...
I don't think so...
They must have taken ages to plan and make this!
The fact it's called  M1 is also
like amazing, isn't it?
M1...
MASATOSHI is his name after all...
Like... Masatoshi 1
It's just like...
too much of a match made in heaven...
it's just coincidence...
It's got to be...
It's fate
Definitely, it's fate
Your dad and mum just like
loved it so much they named you after it
loved it so much, they named you after it.
They said, "I hope our son becomes like that in the future..."
That was their wish...
to become just like M1...
So they took M1and got Masatoshi from it, tha'ts what you're saying?
So they took M1 and got Masatoshi from it, that's what you're saying?
That's the only explanation...
I wonder if the faces were similar?
Of course they did, right from the moment he was born.
It doesn't look like me...
The fact that your faces are so similar makes me want to laugh...
However you look at it, out of us five
That's you
It sounds ridiculous if you say it
looks like me, right?
What? Is it ridiculous?
Absolutely.
They should put Suga-chan in it
If Matsumoto-san put that forward as an idea
I reckon they will make it, seriously
like a little Suga-chan kind of thing...
No one would ever stop laughing...
A wig...  that's what I want...
Like loads of different ideas
Like a bobbed haircut
It would be absolutely perfect
That would be...
Not... perfect.
So have Suga-chan wearing that kind of thing...
and next to it, stick someone like Komuro-san
Tanaka...
That was good...
That was hard...
This is seriously like H Jungle
Right?
Yeah...
This is when he was a baby  right?
This is when he was a baby right?
a baby?
He is so stupid to do that...
M1...
You can clearly see the whole development
That one was like when he was a newborn...
and that one is during shichigosan right?
Shichigosan: A traditional rite of passage and festival in Japan for three and seven year old girls and three and five year old boys,
Shichigosan...
5 years old huh?
So he's 5 there...
5 years old...
That one is when it was 5 years old...
How about the picture of when it was born?
Hang on
You're full of it...
Isn't that picture the worst out of three?
The picture...
It was the worst
I agree
The picture...
You were laughing
I didn't...
But seriously, that photo, untouched...
could be Hamada's driving license,  no?
could be Hamada's driver license, no?
Tanaka, you're always getting away with laughing...
Do you think so?
I really do, as his driver license
like if he's with the police?
When he gets asked "please show me your license"
seriously, I think you can get by
If you just casually showed it
Like obviously
if it's sunny during the day then it might not be possible
If it was a bit dark or something and
the policeman flashes a torchlight on it...
he would just say, "Oh okay, thank you"
No way in hell would that ever...
I'm serious, it would happen
That's going too far...
No seriously, it would happen...
If there wasn't light...
Seriously...
He wouldn't just casually say thank you
I'm not joking here...
He hit me on my tender spot  just now
He hit me on my tender spot just now
I'm happy he hit you there...
like if you  just came out of a tunnel at midnight
like if you just came out of a tunnel at midnight...
I think so too...
The policeman will say, "Sorry, excuse me..."
Naturally, he will go "Hold on..." when he sees Hamada's face
anyways,  he would have to check his driving license
anyways, he would have to check his driving license
if he just  casually hands it with that picture...
if he just casually hands it with that picture...
he would just normally say,  "Oh, okay... thank you"
he would just normally say "Oh, okay... thank you"
No no no, that would be ridiculous...
He definitely wouldn't say like "Oh thank you..."
It's really  extreme
You see similarities?
Holy shit...
Hang on a second...
WOW...
Can we please take a photo?
It's like brothers next to each other.
You're so annoying...
This is amazing...
I'm really sorry...
This was a really funny time for us...
I want a picture...
I really wish I brought a camera with me...
would you
please sit next to it?
This is going to be priceless...
That's amazing...
Don't mess with me!!!
Like in all seriousness...
We're really serious
You can't be serious...
We are literally like serious in all seriousness
We are being serious
Sorry but can you do it once more?
Yeah, please...
Why the hell??
It literally looks identical...
This is seriously amazing...
It looks like a family portrait
Oh yeah, you're right.
Hamada is the mother...
It's amazing...
It really is...
Because the baby is such a newborn
his tits are still big...
Come on now...
You're right...
Because the kids sucking on them...
Oh, that's why...
Because they suck on it...
the tits are like pressing right against the shirt
Okay, let's stop...
Let's stop, seriously...
Yeay, let's stop...
Seriously, it would never happen...
M1 is so scary...
That is amazing, Hamada-san
There shouldn't be a
look-a-like monsters...
No way...
If you look for some, there would be
I honestly don't think we look alike at all...
but I'm sure there is a monster for everyone...
Was it originally a gorilla
Was it originally a gorilla?
It's some sort of  fucked up monster
It's some sort of fucked up monster
It doesn't say anything about that...
But you know...
Appears in casual clothes
Gekidan Hitori
I will say this, but...
Hi there...
Hey there...
Hey guys...
What's up?
Have a seat...
Okay, excuse me...
Today... um...
I need to apologise about something firstly...
This year  I was called onto Gaki no Tsukai
This year I was called onto Gaki no Tsukai
and I wanted to do something funny
for them but...
I couldn't think of anything funny to do...
I got to...
I got to attend loads of meetings with the staff...
But...
but still...
I came empty handed...
you know?
and I thought about it loads...
this is my graduation album of middle school
well about this...
If I rip this to shit, would that make you laugh?
He'll rip the album to shit just to get them to laugh
No no...
No, no, you don't need to...
Don't do that...
Definitely don't...
You don't need to do that...
It would really make us feel awkward as well...
Yeah, let's not do that...
Don't do it, don't do it...
It's fine!
Come on, stop it...
It's your memories right?
It is my memories!
Then don't do it!
My whole youth in this book
Seriously, we won't laugh if you tear it up...
If I rip this to shit
all of you will definitely laugh for me
No we won't, we really won't...
Look...
Ridiculous...
Look, please look at this...
Look...
There he is... there..
Hitori (young)
Look...
There you are...
That's great
I  loved Downtown so much
I loved Downtown so much
that I even
had the same hairstyle as Ma-chan!
Even had the same haircut
I wanted to be like him so much...
But I just can't be like him...
no no no...
So I know this is the only thing I can really do...
Wait, what are you going to do?
Wait, wait wait!!!
Please don't stop me!!
It's something really precious
Please don't stop me!!!
It's your memories man...
It's really precious...
I really want all of you to laugh!
We won't laugh at that...
Yeah, we won't, so stop
We won't laugh...
Here you go everyone...
please laugh to your heart's content...
No no, stop...
Stop him...
Don't, don't!
Please stop it!!
Ripped his middle school memories to shit
Stop it you idiot!
This is the real one...
It's funny, right?
This kind of thing is no good
This kind of thing is no good...
It's really bad...
No no, seriously...
It's not good...
This is wrong...
This is so wrong...
3:30 PM
Earth Defense Force training     7 hours 30 minutes since the start
The real Elite training starts here...
Alarm suddenly goes off
What the hell is that...
Announcement
Oh no!!  Right now, in this building
Right now, in this building
there is an intruder
there is an intruder apparently.
So you guys be careful.
Oh dear...
Why do things like this happen...
But how?
Surely you shouldn't be able to get into the Earth Defense Force training centre...
Surely you shouldn't be able to get into the Earth Defense Force training center...
The intruder enters
Wait, what, what?!
What's going on!?
There are loads of them
Hang on a second!!
Why me!?
Man... that surprised me...
Well we can't do anything about it...
Yeah we really can't...
Oh well...
Nothing we can do...
Weren't those people  familiar?
Weren't those people familiar?
Everyone don't worry
Everyone, don't worry
The truth is  we're doing a special training{\c\4c\3c now
The truth is we're doing a special training now
so I had one person get caught on purpose
as training...
Well we are going to start the training,  so can you changed into this?
Training?
Well we are going to start the training, so can you change into this?
To do this "special training" we have to get  changed?
To do this "special training" we have to get changed?
When you finish getting changed, I will return...
Before the training starts
the guys get dressed into something appropriate
Before the training starts,
the 4 get changed into something a little more appropriate
Okay, shall we?
I'm actually quite scared...
What will the special training be exactly?!
Now...
What will the special training consist of!?
Right guys, can you all line up here?
Shit... I saw it...
What, here?
Hamada-san, please look behind you...
Oh shit...
Are you fucking serious?
Okay guys
the training you're about to do is this!!
There it is...
Shit, that's the worst!!
I really hate this thing...
Oh come on, no more...
During this training, you can laugh...
but if you get caught by an ONI  you will be
severely punished on   the spot!!
DO NOT GET CAUGHT - SPY
3 years ago
The nightmare from 3 years ago - "No Laughing" Spy
If you get caught by an ONI, you face hell...
If you get caught
you get punished according to what it says on their chest!!
You will be punished severely, according to what is written on their chest.
When the training starts, there will be 3 ONI.
When it starts, 3 ONI will appear
Special Training
every 20 minutes  more ONI will appear
every 20 minutes, more ONI will appear
Do Not Get
Caught
Earth Defense Force
A training which will occur across the whole area
Do not get caught Earth Defense Force
You guys are all
such low life comedians, the whole lot of you
I've prepared a more upper class comedian
just for you
Please come out now.
For real?
Other person
Mizobata Junpei
What the hell are you doing here?
I love Gaki no Tsukai
I've been saying, "I really want to go on it"
I've been begging Suga-san for ages
Japanese producer
Suga Kenji
This isn't something you want to be part of...
They will properly fuck you up!!
This is really like harsh!
The EDF depends on this!
The 5 men are given an important mission!
And so...
Including Misobata, the mission given to the 5 is...
THIS!
Special Training
Find the treasure chest which contatins a map
showing where Matsumoto is
find the treasure chest containing a map which shows where Matsumoto is...
and rescue him.
I was so cold there...
However...
sfshjkhjkhjkhjkhjkhjkdfsdfsdfsdfsdf
every 20 minutes Matsumoto will be punished
Until he is rescued...
Matsumoto will be punished
every 20 minutes.
This is really horrible!!
Like really horrible!!
Okay, are you guys ready?
Shit, I'm scared
Special Training START!
Slipper
Shit, he's quick!
[Hamada]  Oh, shit, shit
[Hamada] Oh, shit, shit
[Hamada] Oh, shit,  shit,
[Hamada] Oh, shit  shit
They were so fast
This really hurts
[Hamada] my head's making a "kin~~~" sound
[Endo] Have you ever seen Hamada-san get hit
that hard by a slipper?
2nd ONI COMES OUT
[Hamada] Another one's come out.
[Endo] There's two of them...
[Endo]   There's two of them.
I could hear the sounds of them hitting you
Oh I see...
Massive paper fan
That is ridiculous...
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry...
It hurt so fucking much
Of course it would...
[Hamada] He went over there  right over there
[Hamada] He went over there, right over there
He got hit like SO hard
I hear sounds going off in my head when I got hit...
Housei doesn't look like a comedian anymore...
Shit, I'm scared...
3rd ONI COMES OUT
That's a bad look you got there...
All fours
He's got a bad look on his face
Look at that, he's got a bad look on his face
This is hard, so hard!!
They are so fast, you're right
They were so bloody fast
That's fine but...
What the hell was this?
What is he doing to you?!
What the hell is this?!
Say something!!
The 5 meet up
You don't want the paper fan, whatever happens
Leave it out!
Whatever happens, you don't want the paper fan!
The five meet up
What did you get?
I got slapped four times and then 100 strikes.
Eh? 100 times?
Don't lie!
Let's look for it: the treasure box with the map in it.
No way.
That paper fan is dangerous!!
PAPER FAN
That paper fan is a no-no!
That paper fan is really bad.
Your head really makes a sound
This one really hurts.
Stop! Stop! Please stop!
Tanaka with his disgusting running form.
The way he ran...
That running form is seriously...
Aaaa~n!!!
Why?
That was tiring.
Something is coming!!
Getting closer
All fours
It's all fours.
What is up with this?
That hurts!
This pisses me off.
It really does, huh?
They should hit him harder.
They really don't go easy on you.
Slipper
Time quickly passed by, but soon it will be the punishment rush.
All fours
Endo's... butt... is getting slapped.
Poor guy.
All fours
Slipper
Tanaka is being flanked by two ONI!
You gotta be kidding me.
That was quick. I was quickly caught!!
It's a double. It's the worst two punishments, look.
That hurts!
It hurts! That hurts...
That was the worst. Man, I can't deal with that.
Wait a sec...
Let's go over there; this place is bad.
They come out from here. This spot is bad.
That's right.
If we stay here, we'll always get punished.
Let's search for it.
Let's look for that treasure map.
This is really hard.
It's amazing... Variety shows...
This is not a variety show anymore.
It's a documentary.
Tanaka hiding himself
Oy! OY!!!
All fours
There! There! Over there!!
Housei selling out his friend to the ONI.
Ahahahaha~!!
That guy has gotta be kidding me.
Housei got what he deserved
If you sell out your friends, of course that's going to happen to you.
That guy really sold out his friend.
I was spared so I'm fine but...
That really shocked me...
"Over there! Oy oy! He's over there!", he said.
I thought we were friends.
Tanaka, believe me.
Tanaka, believe me. You're mistaken.
I've always thought we were friends!!
Please give me another chance!!
Alright, let's go up.
Give me another chance.
What is up with that guy?
The treasure map!!
What kind of chance did
he want?
The 20 minute mark has just passed.
A total of seven ONI is on the site.
Punishment time
Stop! Stop!
Stop! I seriously can't stand this!
They were really tickling me.
Are you done yet?
That was tiring.
That was really tiring.
Even my head was spinning.
Searching the 2nd floor
I don't think it's here.
I don't think there's anything here.
SLIP
Is there a step there?
He slips even when there's no steps.
No way. You stumbled here?
It was slightly raised...
Getting closer
Honeymoon
Why did you run ahead and not tell us, you fuck!?
What's "Honeymoon"?
I can't take this already.
That is too scary.
I got caught.
I got caught because of Hamada-san.
It says "Honeymoon" there.
It's not "Harisen"? (Paper fan)
You'll be exposed!
You're definitely gonna be exposed with all that loud noise.
Don't come here!!
Even though you say I'm gonna be exposed...
This is all fixed, I can't help it.
Then you just stay here on your own.
Definitely don't come near us.
Let's go find it quick!
The abandoned Housei
Four of them went back to 1st floor
This won't end unless we find it.
Housei-san is just utterly useless to us now...
Just clattering as he goes by.
It's because you would know where he will be.
It's gonna be dangerous for Yamachan; an ONI is coming; slipper.
Because of his noise.
Slipper could hear the noise
He's gonna be exposed easily.
It's here!
Slipper
Hamada is rejoicing in the misfortunes of other people
It's really funny watching someone else gets hit.
It can't be helped.
Can't be helped.
Housei escapes to to 1st floor
Housei's tin can gets entangled
That's hell.
A hellish time.
It's a really hellish time.
I got entangled!!
You're just bait. The ONI is gonna come here!
Paper fan ONI could hear the noise
What should I do?
Wait... Junpei-kun!!
No no no wait! This is scary! Stop! No!
Paper fan
Wait...
Wait a sec...
Someone save me!!!
Someone please save me!!
Matsumoto's reaction to the screaming
HAMADA-SAN!!
ENDO!!
JUNPEI-KUN SAVE ME!!
Ahahahaha...
Handsome actor can't stop laughing
TANAKA!!
SOMEONE!!
SAVE ME!!
The shameless scream of an abandoned man
SOMEONE!!
You could really tell where Housei-san is immediately.
Paper fan
Getting closer
Hamada who is not hidden at all
That is so easy to figure out!
Ha ha ha!
I thought it would run pass me
But it saw me
What's with that face?
Your face pisses me off.
What is up with that face?
When the punishment was coming, did it not occur to you to help me?
I saw it from the beginning til the end.
You were like this.
My collapsing senior.
A new ONI slowly draws closer to the two.
Only Tanaka notices it.
Getting closer
You are really playing dirty!!
Tanaka abandoned his senior
Looks like he abandoned you
Wait a moment! Seriously wait a sec!!
Tanaka feels sorry and watches his senior...
Elvis
That hurts.
Making the hideous Hamada even uglier by vandalizing his face
It hurts.
Elvis?
What the hell?
It hurts. My face hurts.
You look like Elvis Presley. Ah, that's why "Elvis" was written on him.
Oh is that so?
I think so. You look really...
You look like Presley.
He doesn't look that much like
Presley though...
But the sideburns...
I've been hit so fucking hard and they're turning me into Elvis...
Tanaka!!
You... seriously...
The moment you realized the ONI is close, you just ran away and didn't warn me.
Oy~!!!
Housei-san is calling.
I could hear him there.
What happened to him after the incident?
Yes!
Wow, that's amazing.
He's still stuck?!
What's wrong?
I'm stuck.
What do you mean you're stuck?
Elvis
Alright, you just got caught by Elvis.
That hurts.
That seriously hurts! That hurts!
He drew more stuff.
Is that Elvis?
Junpei-kun, be careful. Otherwise you'll become like that...
Tanaka, remove this.
This is impossible for me, Housei-san.
There doesn't seem to be anything you can do other than just be quiet.
This is gonna lure them in.
Because of the noise...
Junpei, you guard from outside.
There are too many and not enough time. We can't save Matsumoto-san like this.
Housei gets abandoned once again
What is this?
Housei attempts to escape
Why is he sweating from this?
You managed to escape?
See, you can do it if you try.
Can you walk quick... Actually, can you stay away from us?
Yamachan, you're so noisy.
You're gonna expose us.
They will find us.
That senior is really noisy. Man.
Let's have 2 people look around the 3rd floor.
Divide into 2 groups to search for the treasure chest
We went to the 2nd floor before, so go to the 3rd floor.
Finally, we got an order from above.
Maybe we could finally find it.
Wha!
Call the other guys!
We found it!
Treasure chest discovered
We found it! The treasure chest!
No way!
He is so noisy.
Man, you're so noisy.
We found it!
Oh, they did.
We immediately found it.
It's good that we found it.
We're counting on you.
The map is in here, right?
Here I go.
Get the map.
Trick mechanism is too much for this 50-year-old's hips
Don't mind.
The 40 minute mark has just passed.
4 more ONI are now added
Victory
This is the worst!!
The number of ONI keeps increasing...
I'm so wet.
BICYCLE RIDE
The severity of the punishments also increase...
It's the next one Tanaka, the next one.
Victim of a 130kg giant
Even a 130kg giant appears.
Pole Fishing
It's Model M1!! Model M1!!
It hurts!
Chinko machine
They don't go easy even on newbies.
The handsome actor got his balls whacked
Matsumoto continues to wait alone
And of course this guy too...
What was the point in this?
It was really rough in there.
It hurts! It hurts!
This is tiring. I'm really worn out.
ONI continues to multiply
Furthermore,
a more powerful ONI
descends!!
And a more dreadful terror appears.
Egashira 2:50 appears
There he is!
This is bad.
This is really bad.
Egashira 2:50 appears
This is bad.
This is really bad.
Just wait a sec!
Tanaka!
Hamada-san! Hamada-san!
GOT YOU~~~~~!!
I CAUGHT YOU~~~~~!!
I can't do this...
Ega-chan, stop this.
Please stop this.
Stop!
Egashira-san, please stop this.
Tanaka, stop looking with those eyes.
He has a really serious look just now. That Ega-chan.
Ega-chan, what are you planning?
What are you doing, Egashira-san?
Egashira-san, you're joking, right?
What is that syringe for?
How much are you gonna put in?
Egashira injects powder into himself
He used quite a lot.
Egashira-san, this is your fourth one.
And now it's 5.
For real?
Tape change
You're changing the tape right now?
Egashira-san, they're changing the tape now.
Please stay still.
An unexpected turn of event!
Egashira's tortured expression!
Poor guy!
He's gonna continue.
His 6th one, how many is he going for?
Egashira-san...
I think there's quite a lot already.
This is his 8th one.
Egashira-san...
You don't have to force yourself. Are you alright?
This is frightening.
It really is frightening.
I sense something dangerous is gonna happen.
For this Earth Defense Force
I'm gonna cause a revolution!!
HERE I GO!!!
Ah! It's time for my part-time job!!
Are you alright, Tanaka?
You must have really hated getting that much on your face.
Why are you looking at Hamada-san like that?
He's your senior.
What is he doing?
I would never do such a thing...
You caught me and tried to sacrifice me to him.
And then when I turned around, all I saw was... "UWEI UWEI!!"
What is that "UWEI UWEI"?
The 1 hour mark has just passed.
3 more ONI are discharged
Matsumoto continues to wait for more than an hour
This was seriously...
Must be tiring to wait
Enough already.
Man...
I'm tired. I'm seriously tired.
What the hell is this?
It was really...
It was seriously...
Just do it already.
No more! No more!
Searching everywhere in the facility
Have we looked here yet?
We didn't search here yet.
Should we go?
Try looking up there.
Ah!
There's something!!
No way!
There's something up here!!
Treasure chest discovered
Ah, it's true!
Let's open it.
The opener should be...
Junpei-kun. Officer Junpei.
There's such thing as this?
We really thought the map would be in there.
This is kinda amazing... There's absolutely nothing.
Something is coming!!
That's scary~
Drive
You found me.
What's "drive"?
What the hell is "Drive"?
He has been caught!!
He got caught!!
I got caught, I couldn't hide from him...
It said "Drive"...
Mizobata is getting taken "somewhere"
Being captured by a "drive" ONI, the place Mizobatawas taken to was...
Being captured by a "drive" ONI, the place Mizobata was taken to was...
Is that person with the umbrella
a race queen?
Hold on, is he
going to be put in a car?
Wow!
A black Race Queen...
Even in their world
there's a race queen, huh?
Wow, this is really amazing...
Stop this...
Wait, what is this?
What's going on?
You got to be kidding me...
Something's coming
It's totally black...
It's a really cool car
So cool!
You're kidding me...
He's going to get put into that?
What? This is really scary, man...
One of the best in Japanese Motor Sports
3 times winner of the Super GT
The Driver
Wakisaka Juiichi
Junpei! Get ready!
I would definitely hate this
Shit, this is fast!!
Ow oww oww
Are they coming?
Holy shit, here they come!
Shit ShitShit
Shit shitshitshit
Shit shit shit shit
This is so messed up...
It's that fast, huh?
Hold on, they're coming back.
You're kidding me...
They're coming this way.
This is...
Are you okay?
Junpei!
Junpei!?
I feel so sick...
I might throw up...
Who's driving this thing?
Jesus, it's Wakisaka Juiichi..
Why did you hit him?
He is amazing...
I wonder how much this car costs roughly...
40,000,000 yen ($383,480; £233,520; €283,400)
40,000,000 yen...
You got to ride something amazing...
You're so lucky...
And you got driven by a big time racer...
Another ONI appears!
Umm, excuse me, what?
You're kidding me, no come on, are you serious?!
Driver
You're kidding me!
No seriously...
I don't want to!! I really don't want to!!
Are you serious?!
I really don't want to do this...
Please go find that treasure chest.
I'm obviously not going to!!
You never know, search for us.
Seriously, pay attention
Okay, have fun!!
Did you do a "key lock"?
Do you not want to shut the window?!
You mean "door lock"...
Does it really go that fast?
No no, it goes way~~~ faster.
Can cars accelerate that fast?
In one moment, Housei's face looks like a ghost...
I guess it just happens naturally...
Yeah, you really do...
Oh, here they come!
They're coming this way!
Watch out...
This is amazing...
Please stop!!
Drive normally
Please drive normally
Iiiiiiiiihihihihihihihihihihi
Ahhhh No no no !
ZUUUUU
ZUUUU
Here they come
They're coming...
Here they come!
No no no no no no no no no no
This is not good!!
There's smoke everywhere!!
There's smoke everywhere!
Please stop!! Please stop already!!
This guy's amazing...
Amazing!!!
Is this really happening?
You got to be kidding me...
Are you alright?
It was amazing, huh?
Isn't your body just really tired?
Like you have to hold your body, especially at the turns...
Otherwise, it's really like...
Yeah, your neck just kind of drags away...
He didn't drive normally at all...
What a shitty driver...
The training now leads them to the building
As the sun starts to set, they head to the building
Shall we look over there somewhere?
That was amazing...
Hang on, there it is!!
The colour is also a bit different from before
You're right
They discover a treasure box
This has got to be the real one
There can't be any more...
Jeez...
I'm opening it then...
Look, we found it!
There it is, there it is, the map!
They found the map
It's the top floor...
The 3rd floor, the 3rd floor
Let's go!
The top floor.
I'll take the map
The map shows Matsumoto's location
Matsumoto is on the 3rd floor.
The 5 look at the map and rush to his rescue
The five arrive at the 3rd floor
So he was on the top floor...
Like near the end on the top floor.
Yeah, looks like it...
I'm so tired...
We did well...
What?! Bazooka!!
Bazooka
Why is he here?
What the hell is "bazooka"?
Hold on, what is "Bazooka"?
Wait, what is "Bazooka"?
Here comes "bazooka"..
Wait, what what what?!
What is this?
It's coming Junpei-kun...
This is so scary...
I bet he will never come on this show again...
That would be horrible
The pretty boy gets dirtier and dirtier...
Junpei...
Even after everything from before...
I'm regretting coming on this program a bit...
Jeez...
To be honest,you're getting the full course.
To be honest, you're getting the full course.
You're enjoying this.
You're standing out the most...
They head to the room Matsumoto is in
Finally they get to the room Matsumoto is held hostage
I'm opening it...
And...
The time to rescue him has arrived
Oh Matsumoto-san!
Oh, he's here, he's here.
Thank God, thank God.
Man, I'm tired.
What kind of face is that?
You took bloody ages...
That was so fucking long...
I sat here for so long...
It was, it was, we're really sorry...
He's locked by a key...
Yeah, I got locked by a key...
Wait, so what do we do about the key?
Um...
You don't have the key?
No we don't...
No, we haven't got a key...
No, we seriously don't have a key...
Wow wow wow, what's going on?
Holy shit!!
No no no, seriously...
Everyone gets tickle attacked!!
What what?!
Stop!
Get off me...
They were so persistent...
This was so tough
Training finished
That hurts...
What the fuck are you doing!?
Even Fujiwara is tickling Matsumoto
What the hell are you doing?
What does he think he's doing?
He's treating you like a kid
What the fuck, you had the key?!
They rescued Matsumoto
The training of horror finished!!
Finally they rescued Matsumoto,
the training horror finishes...
However...
Once again the temptation of laughter is back!!
Once again, the temptation of laughter is back
and will attack the 5 guys
Man that was long...
From the point where we got into that room
and opened those drawers...
You're right...
I love Gaki no Tsukai so much and
I want to be on it
After it finished, he said to me
Mizobata Junpei
I'm never coming on again!!
Honestly, he said that.
Never again...
I thought so...
He did...
He did say that, I don't blame him
He got the full course...
But seriously, Hamada-san's...
M1...
Oh yes, of course
M1
M1 came out and just...
Seriously, he doesn't...
What is with that?
Seriously...
Are you and
Tsuburaya in some sort of agreement?
(Editor note: Tsuburaya is a special effects studio)
Yeah...
There is a connection for sure...
Like a collaboration...
Why the hell!!
You need to speak to the head office if you want
to do that kind of thing!
Shut the hell up!
He's right though...
I haven't agreed with anyone...
For me it's got to be...
The salty rice cakes... that was amazing
Yeah, the bloody salty rice cakes
Ebisu Yoshikaze
That's right!
That was so sick, wasn't it Endo?
It's disgusting...
Like seriously, from the beginning...
I felt sicker and...
When I think back to it now, I feel sick...
Matsumoto-san the last imitation please
No one laughs at all...
7:00PM...
Earth Defense Force       11 hours from the start
During your long Earth Defense Force missions...
troublesome things can happen...
Everyone there's trouble.
Everyone, there's trouble.
2 of Earth Defense Force's maritime divisions are arguing over operation area
Not again...
Seems like they are having a dispute at a nearby base
You got to be kidding me...
Will you guys go and sort it out?
Every year, they just fight...
Really, then I got to like...
Heading to the Marine Members
The 5 go to improve the situation!
A fight has broken out between the two divisions
The 5 are just going to improve the situation
What is it that awaits the five!?
Earth Defense Force
Marine Division
But what is it that
awaits them?
Marine HQ Entrance
This is the place.
Wow this place is huge
Oh look, they're arguing
A very dangerous mood
Excuse us
Excuse us, is there no way we can just talk and sort this all out?
Excuse us, is there a way we can just talk and sort this all out?
What are you going on about, asshole?!
Get the hell out of the way and just watch and listen!!
Shall we just sit until it concludes?
After the meeting I will return
Don't get in the way, assholes
Bunch of dumbasses
Don't joke around, you bastard!
If you truly are that serious let's put our bodies on the line in a match
If you truly are that serious, let's put our bodies on the line in a match
Let's do it!!
Breakdown of Negotiations! Conclusion will result in a battle of bodies!!
In the end, the clothing has no relationship, huh?
Changing into combat uniform
Unlike you guys who have no guts,
Degawa Division will show you that we will go to any horrible extent!!
Go on then, let's see how far you're willing to go!!
Willpower is what Urashima Division is all about!
Alright bring that out
Degawa Division Staff Officer
Hosshan
Wait isn't that too close?
It is close
close
We train our groins more than any  other part of our bodies.
We train our groins more than any other part of our bodies
Show you what it means to have a crotch as strong as steel
Iwao! Show 'em!!
Degawa Division
Iwao Nozomu
Are you sure you can do it, you fool?
Show them what it means to be truly strong willed.
What is this?
A rocket will be fired
Degawa Division's Spirit
Firework rocket will be stopped via crotch
and he will stop it with his crotch
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming
Alright
Wow he's being tough.
*Out of concern and safety, reformed fireworks are used. Please do not imitate.
The practice of my village since birth
Urashima Division Staff Officer
Kendo Kobayashi
Since birth, the people of my village don't feel any heat in our groin area.
Since birth, the people of my village  don't feel any heat in our groin area.
What the hell is he saying?
Carry it out
Urashima Division's Spirit
3 times the fireworks will be stopped by the nether regions
There are 3 of them
So since birth his crotch isn't affected by heat...
That is quite amazing
Come on!!
Is this for real?
I'm calm and relaxed
Come on then!!!
Was so scared he pussied out
You felt something in your crotch...
What the hell man?
He obviously felt the heat
One shot and he was gone
He was born in a village where no one feels heat between their legs
You ran away didn't ya?!
Well in my division...
It doesn't matter whether it's his groin or anywhere else.
Bring it out!!
Degawa Division's Spirit
Firework will fly diagonally then will be stopped by his nether region
He will show that he can do anything
Commander, please proceed
Degawa Division Commanding Officer
Degawa Tetsurou
Hell yeah let's do this!
Hosshan come take a look at the position!!
What do you mean?
Come take a look at the position!!
It's nothing really!!
Are you ready to start?
What is the meaning of any of this?
Here we go!
Bring it!!
Watch right here
Hosshan's brave
You better watch
It was nothing at all!!
*Out of concern and safety, reformed fireworks are used. Please do not imitate.
It really was nothing!
It's not hot, it's not hot.
Im not scared!!
Next we will show you something even more amazing
Our Kuro-chan will now
Degawa Division Staff Officer
Kuro-chan
He's trained his nipples
So we can put a clip on his nipple, get a bat,
hit it off really hard and he won't feel a thing.
Degawa Division's spirit
Swing a baseball bat at a washing clip attached to his nipple
This guy is like half beast already
Wrong section to hit
Is it going to be that sort of feeling?
It definitely won't hurt
Definitely won't say anything
It huuuuurts!!
He said it hurts!!
Why would he have a reason to say it hurts?
Didn't you just say it hurts?
Home Run
Whats up with your hand?
What's wrong?
Isn't it a breach of regulations to be getting a tattoo?
No, I don't even had one.
Bring it on!
Starting again - Challenge retry
Make it fly
Oh really? He has one?
Ow!!
It hurt, didn't it?
You said "Ow" just now
I swear you just said "Ow"
There is a cold sweat coming from your head
Water vapor!!
Starting now, let's settle this in one go
We'll show you the standard training we do
Oh jeez!!
This is much harder than anything you do
I bet you losers wouldn't be able to handle this...
This is amazing
Training Machine
Sword Cut Noodle Robo
Urashima Division's tradition
Urashima Division's training machine
Sword cut noodle robo
A very High Tech Machine
where it automatically cuts noodles into the hot water
This machine was created...
to cut ramen one after another into hot water
Our Yoshinobu
can eat straight from this amazing machine
and he can eat loads of noodles straight from the nabe with his bare hands
I doubt he could do that.
Urashima Division
Nakamura Yoshinobu - Producer
Hang on a minute.
The producer...
Our Haranishi will
Shall I finish this?
Degawa Division
Haranishi Takayuki
Go for it, go on!
Only take a minute
That's why I said it
What the hell is he doing?
So freaken noisy
10 seconds left
What is Yoshinobu doing?
What are they doing?
That guy with the glasses didn't eat any!!
If I'm not mistaken they said it was hot
Degawa Division won't back away;
we will show you our training method
Bring it out
You... This is...
Machine's name Wedgie High
Wedgie High
Wear some briefs really high up
and get swung around as if on a swing
They will wear briefs uncomfortably high
and whilst being pushed as if they were on the swings, they must kick the balloons.
What the hell?
All the weight will go to the crotch
A very good machine to toughen up the crotch
As their whole body weight will be on their crotch
They sure love doing things to their crotches
this is a fantastic machine to toughen it up.
With this training, Degawa Division's Iwao will show his spirit
We'll show ya!!
I get it, it's a huge swing
There's a pin at the tip of the shoe to burst the balloon
It hurts! It hurts!
Stretch out your legs!
Are you okay?
Because it's too hard, he needs a rest
What the hell...
This machine could be dangerous if you don't rest in between...
I will burst it.
I will burst it straight away!!
You can't do this, can you!?
Give me a break!!
That's enough
What the hell...
Seriously, enough...
You're so pathetic...
Nice fight!!
Tanaka's willpower
Riding it like a swing  he will burst three ballons
Now, Ueshima Division's
Tanaka will try and burst three balloons
Widen both legs!!
Time...
Okay!!
AAAAAAGGGGHHHHHH
Quick! Please give me energy!!
Try and rest without any help!!
I was able to rest without any help...
This part is so sadistic...
I'm just really tall...
I will put an end to this once and for all
Bring that in!!
Uh-oh!
Don't shit yourselves  you guys!
Don't shit yourselves, you guys!
There it is...
What is this?
Candle wax...
Degawa's willpower
how many times can he be spun around in a tanker full of melted candle wax
Watch me, you marines!
Ryu-chan was laughing the whole time!
Don't be nervous you guys!!
He just couldn't contain himself.
Watch and learn what willpower really is!!
Amazing...
He looks like Pinocchio...
This is nothing!!
This is nothing you fool!
That's enough!
*We have taken safety precautions, please do not try this at home.
He looks like Mask-man...
There is genuinely a Mask-man that looks like that
Let's settle this in the final battle
Bring that in!
Is it "that" thing?
If you look at it, you should already understand
There it is...
We put gas up the guy's arse and they arm wrestle!
Whoever farts first is the loser
That's so fuckin stupid...
What kind of rules are those?!
Can you just explain the rules once more..?
So we put gas into our arse till we can take no more and we arm wrestle
and whoever farts first loses...
You don't need him to explain twice
It's weird because you're speaking in Osaka dialect in that last part as well...
This is the final battle
The final battle
They put gas up their arses and arm wrestle and whoever farts first loses
We're getting our strongest member out
We're getting our Leader to go!
Your leader is so weak...
Do not fart arm wrestling competition
Degawa Team
Kuro-chan
Ueshima Team
Ueshima Ryuhei
That is Hosshan, isn't it?
It's okay if it's Hosshan?
Okay, I'm putting gas in now.
Both sides put gas in at the same time
AAAAAGGGHHHHH
It's in!!
Kuro-chan has been filled with gas
Still?
Wait, not yet? You're taking ages!
Ueshima, hurry up!
Kuro-chan will release everything!!
Make sure everything is done at the same time!
They calm down and get ready again
You're like sumo wrestlers right now...
The first part is really important
Oh!! Wait!
Sorry wait!
Ueshima runs into the back room
I don't think this is possible, is it?
Until Ueshima returns, they practice putting air into Kuro-chan
*clan*
What happened?
Something is stuck in me
The nozzle is inside Kuro-chan...
It's just stuck in you...
It's not good
The nozzle is gone
We were able to get the nozzle out
You put too much air in. Just let it all out
Get set and...
Oh
it's coming
A real one is coming out...
and substitution...
What is over there?
What the hell man!?
There is not going to be a match...
What are we going to do about this?
You're amazing Ueshima
You guys are awesome, aren't you!?
Ends with them making up
You got to see the will power of the marines, huh?
They were able to be friends again
This year was also amazing, huh?
I'm off to the toilet
9:00 PM. As soon as they get back to the training centre...
Since the start - 13 hours
First time in japan! The monkey who went to space
They're now heading to his return ceremony!!
The first time in Japan!
To celebrate the monkey who went to space
They will attend his return ceremony
The stage
Pfft...
Executive Astronaut
Choushuu Riki
Asaoka Yukiji
Executive Astronaut
Umezawa Tomio
And now...
The genius astronaut monkey
returning ceremony is about to start
Genius Astronaut
His returning ceremony START
Without delay
Introducing to the stage the genius space monkey Ken-Kun
Welcome
Entering the stage Ken-kun the Genius space monkey
Genius Space Monkey
Hourichi Ken
Astronaut
Maeda Gin
Ken-kun
The experiment was to determine whether monkeys could survive in space like humans
and in order to test this
after a year of preparation, he got in a rocket and traveled to space
and he successfully survive out there.
Starting to get irritated in this quiet situation
During his time out in space,
he was able to find a true partner
who is this man, the astronaut, Maeda-san
Let's quickly get to the anticipated questions
Astronaut Maeda    What was Ken-kun like up in space?
Umm yeah, let's see
Inside the rocket Ken was healthy and all
Ken-kun likes to prank
when we got up above the skies, he started to get excited...
He was really loving the zero gravity
He was adapting...
He was adapting much quicker than us, because he's a monkey.
What the hell is he doing?
I can't deal with this
Have affection
So you're saying you needed to be strict while showing him love...
Top Leadership become target of pranks
Same as humans
That's terrific... next...
Ken-kun's Prank
Puting hair mousse on glasses
What was Ken-kun's diet in space?
His favourite: bananas.
Like us, he also got a variety of meat and vegetables
it's something I realized while we were in space
Ken-kun's Prank
Sticking oranges into mouth
When we started eating the same things out there...
He got much healthier
So maybe, the diet had a part to play?
Ken-kun's Prank
Pushes orange rind into nose
Well then, the space station and the headquarter on Earth actually had a video feed between the two.
We could see what was going on up there.
They said that Ken-kun was great and he was popular among them
Ken-kun's Prank
Blowing into ear
What do you think about that?
I honestly didn't think he would ever be this popular
Ken-kun doesn't actually think of himself as a monkey.
He thought of me as a rival, like an enemy
So if he didn't like something
He would get angry with me
Oh, so like a fear almost?
Perhaps, yes.
Ken-kun's Prank
Drawn in permanent marker
He really does understand everything I say.
Okay then... To all the kids who wants to be astronauts...
Ken-kun's Prank
Hair style by hand
Do you have anything you could say to them?
Well you know, Ken-kun here was able to do it, so
it is possible for anyone who really wants to do it.
Okay well this is a little bit of a strange question but...
Oh yes,
For someone really active like Ken-kun...
EEEEK
Ken-kun escapes
Thank you for your time
That is the end of the Return Memorial Service thank you very much
Return Memorial Service Closing
Alert Level 5
Emergency Announcer
The Earth Defense Force confirm
that we have had an intruder inside our base
Emergency Announcer
All members of the Earth Defense Force
get ready for combat.
Oh no! We have received
a video message from the aliens!  Please show it on the screen now!!
Dear earthlings, we are the Drago people.
We will start the destruction of the Earth.
First, we will start by blowing up the Earth Defense Force.
Well then, I will press the button now
Goodbye
Earth Defence Fo-
How?How was our plan?
How? How was our plan...
The transmission ends
Special Unit enter the room
GOD
DAMN!!
Commander of Special Unit
Chono Masahiro       2nd time today!
GOD
DAMN!!
Commander of Special Unit
Chono Masahiro 2nd time today
Earth Defense Force members, be happy!
We have prevented the Aliens' attack on Earth
We were able to capture an alien who sneaked intothe Earth Defense Force HQ.
We were able to capture an alien who sneaked into the Earth Defense Force HQ
Oy!! Bring it in!!
The captured alien is brought on
Inside of here is an alien
Oh yeah, him...
Is there any one here who recognizes him?
One thing that concerns me.
He said, in the middle of our investigation,
that he has a comrade inside the EDF!!
Someone his heart connects with!!
Isn't that a remarkable expression?
So this is how it is
If the traitor is in here
or anyone knows who is the traitor
Immediately show yourself!!
So that means this alien has been telling us lies
But!! Let's see if he recognizes anyone
This Alien
Only the one his heart connects with
Meeting finger to finger and there the light will show
Everyone will do it!!
If his finger lights up, it proves friendship
Find the traitor!!
I thought you would be okay...
What a remarkable expression Yama-chan
He had already been slapped in the morning...
Will we be okay?
It is the second time
I have faith that everyone
I trust every single one of you
From you
You mean me?
Yes you
Touch his finger
Be careful
Heart doesn't connect so no reaction
Let me see
We should just fast forward this part...
Okay
Thank you, I was mistaken
It's fine. It's fine.
Well surely, not twice in a day.
Okay it's good thank you
I thought I was in trouble...
I was fine
Okay
Can you do it?
Hey!!
What is with your face?
Don't you think there is a chance you could be saved?
Okay, it's up to you
Alien's finger instantly lights up
Well that was to be expected
Traitor Discovered!!
Hey!! What's your name?
It's Tsukitei Hosei
I don't know you
You're a traitor!!
You're wrong!!
So what this guy is saying is a lie?
Before me, the person on my left  gave him some goods
Before me, the person on my left gave him some goods
Goods...
Goods, haha.
He totally sold him out just now...
What are you saying?
He really is a bad person
Totally...
Really?
No doubt in the slightest...
That's not the problem
Why is that?
His finger lit up
Your hearts are connected.
The information was transferred
I don't like him; I hate him
He's not my friend; he's not anything!!
Why the hell are you so dramatic?
Damn...
Oh well, whatever.
I don't like how you're speaking
What character is that?
He's saying something
Wait, the alien is saying something
Hosei my friend
Would you really say
it at that time?
Get up now
Get up, damn it!!
Hosei-san, stay strong
For the traitor: a punishment slap!!
I've already been slapped once today...
What are you talking about?
This morning I already received a punishment
I told you that my jaw was dislocated!!
I forget that kind of stuff!
Tsukitei Houtei
It's Hosei.
Shut up!!
He got it wrong in the morning, too.
In the morning it was your last name
It was "tsuki".
It was the "tsuki".
He just won't remember my name...
Would you really do it twice?
You're always like this
Why do you stab your friends in the back? This is the EDF!!
I didn't stab them in the back
You didn't stab them in the back?
Then why did you give him information?
I didn't give him  any information
I didn't give him any information
Did I actually give you any information!?
Then talk!!
Hey Alien
Did I give you any information!?
I hate you!!
You're my enemy!! An enemy!!
Hosei my friend
He's awful
Hm... That alien is the worst
I wonder what happened to make him like you so much
You guys are friends!
You are not an ally of the Earth Defese Force
You're a traitor!!
Wait...
What the hell are you doing?
What the hell...
Wow
So noisy...
I wouldn't want that to happen to me
Alright, stand up!!
Why?!
I don't want this! I really don't want this!!
Get up!!
Get up man!
Get up man...
I can't do this anymore
His mannerisms are awful
He really didn't help us
This is your last chance; get up!!
Hey you, what are these?
Those are oranges
The genius monkey brought them
EAT IT!!
I don't want to!!
Eat it, damn it!!
I don't want to do this anymore
This is tough, so tough.
I don't want to do this year after year
Just get it over with
Do you understand?
Yes
Don't step  on the oranges!!
Don't step on the oranges!!
Stand on one leg! One leg!!
It's dangerous
You will fly
If you stand on one leg
Stand up right!
I can't!
Close your eyes!!
Not my eyes!
Not my eyes!!
Normally... Normally
If you escape, you know what will happen hey
Yes
That was a bad face just now
Why is he acting like they're mates?
Let's go!! Ready?!
Tsukitei Hosei
Let's do it again this year!!
HEY!! Are you okay?!
ALRIGHT!!
You traitor!!
He was wrong...
What the hell is that
What the hell...
What happened
Now his personality
His personality has been messed up
It's finijjed...
Wow
Let's go...
As much as the alien said that you were his friend, he didn't help you at all
14 hours and 30 minutes passed since their duties began
we don't forgive those who mess with the order of the earth
Protection Department Conference Observation!!
They will participate in a conference among the EDF officers
And what they find waiting for them is...
Right now I would like to begin reporting findings from the EDF protection department
The order of the Earth is not disrupted by only evil aliens and criminals, but...
EDF safety department conference
conference for reports about
suspicious celebrities with negative effects on people
there are suspicious celebrities on TV who have negative affects on the Earth
So, does anyone know of any suspicious celebrities? Please tell.
Can I talk about Tsukitei Hosei?
Um well, Tsukitei Hosei, well,
Tsukitei Hosei Secret Information
with a certain TV program...
Since he was Yamasaki Hosei, there was a TV program important to him, called "Drive A Go-Go"
Since he was Yamasaki Hosei, there was a TV program important to him, called  "Drive A Go-Go"
So, recently he met with some people who are connected to the show
so everyone knows what "Drive A Go-Go" is
Male celebrities and female celebrities drive together and enjoy the travel
It's scripted, but most of the parts are left to them
Because the celebrities have an ability to work and report
but,
concerning Tsukitei Hosei, there are many problems!!
Something happened at exactly the last filming location
before he was entering the inn, the director said
"the spa nearby has a lot of steam so can you please touch it?"
After Hosei said, "Wow! The spa's steam is amazing!" The cameraman took the shot, right?
After Hosei said, "Wow! The spa's steam is amazing!" The cameraman took it, right?
And when the cameraman returned to him, Hosei was already in the inn
What the hell?
Why would you do that?
You wouldn't think he would do that
He didn't get used to it! (being on TV)
Tsukitei Hosei Secret Information
with a certain TV program...
In the program, celebrities enter outdoor spas
and they report how good the temperature of the water is
and the most important thing to report is the view from the spa
they have to report the beauty of the scenery
but as soon as Hosei gets in the spa he closes his eyes
No no no no, Hosei-san
That's kind of bad, isn't it?
Amazing
That's kind of bad
That's not good
It's amazing he's still on TV.
A story about Tsukitei Hosei
Tsukitei Hosei Secret Information
History of career is hard to explain...
He's gotten tired of explaining his career's history
He became a Rakugoka
Rakugo is a form of art/comedy through story telling
while he was getting into Rakugo there is an order from beginning to end
and in the Rakugo world,
Tsukitei Hosei Information
Horrible attitude
In the Rakugo world, he is  an opening performer.
In the Rakugo world, he is   an opening performer.
And you know, I thought he might be finding it a bit tough,
so I went to his show, and when I saw him,
the presence he was giving off was like a master's.
the presence he was giving off was like  a master's.
It was really like powerful and everything.
And after the show,
he comes up to me and  and goes like "How are you doing lately, mate?"
he comes up to me and goes like  "How are you doing lately, mate?"
Really?
Yeah, he was so casual...
Hosei once said thathe gets the "Ding Dong Ditch" prank done to him
Hosei once said that he gets the "Ding Dong Ditch" prank  done to him
Hosei once said that  he gets the "Ding Dong Ditch" prank  done to him
and apparently there are kids who ring his bell and  shout "Yamasaki OUT!"
Tsukitei Hosei information
"Ding Dong Ditch"
and apparently there are kids who ring his bell and  shout "Yamasaki OUT!"
But I've been past his house once before...
but you can't Ding Dong Ditch him   because of the location of his house...
but you can't Ding Dong Ditch him because of the location of his house...
That's NOT COOL man!!
You can't do that!
Don't lie...
You really shouldn't lie...
I've got a story which has got to do with his Rakugo...
Basically...
Hosei-san's stylist wasn't sure what exactly a Rakugoka was  so he asked him
Tsukitei Hosei Information
Rakugoka is...
Hosei-san's stylist wasn't sure what exactly a Rakugoka was so he asked him
So you know, he explained it to him and his stylist said
so it's like an adult's version of  a "picture story show"
And he replied, "Hm, I guess, kind of."
And the next day, Hosei-san was getting interviewed by some magazine and his stylist was present
and the interviewer asked Hosei-san what exactly is a Rakugoka and he answered,
"It's basically an adult version of a picture story show..."   He basically stole exactly what his stylist said   and made it his own words...
"It's basically an adult version of a picture story show..." He basically stole exactly what his stylist said  and made it his own words...
"It's basically an adult version of a picture story show..." He basically stole exactly what his stylist said and made it his own words...
How horrible...
Shall we go for someone else?
This isn't important,  but you know  Shouhei's story about  Tsukitei Hosei's episode?
This isn't important, but you know  Shouhei's story about Tsukitei Hosei's episode?
This isn't important, but you know Shouhei's story about  Tsukitei Hosei's episode?
This isn't important, but you know Shouhei's story about  Tsukitei Hosei's 'episode'?
That wasn't funny in the slightest!
But he should report it...
Well yeah, I guess...
We are a "reporting society"...
You want people to know...
Can we move onto stories about Hamada?
Hamada Masatoshi information
Can't handle foreigners
From what I've heard, Hamada
really can't  handle foreigners
He went to a restaurant when he was abroad and he was starving
and he was saying that
he wants to eat a lot so   he wanted to take his time, relax and eat
he wants to eat a lot so he wanted to take his time, relax and eat
but when the foreign waiter came over and asked, "Are you finished?"
he replied immediately, "Yes."
Man he really can't handle them...
He's so useless...
I don't want him to go abroad anymore; how embarrassing...
I've heard some news about Hamada as well.
Apparently, the other day, it was about a mask...
Hamada Masatoshi Information
A strange story
He was banging on, saying "Where's my mask, where's my mask?"
and he was looking everywhere for his mask  but it was on his chin
and he kept on looking for it, and his juniors didn't want to embarrass him
so they couldn't bring themselves to just tell him, but eventually
they said, "Sorry Hamada-san, but it's on your chin." And he replied
"I ain't got any feeling in my chin"  or some rubbish like that
What a stupid reason...
I heard something too, that he's the type of guy
who worries a lot, even though he looks like that...
I actually heard this from his wife
Supplier of information
Ogawa Natsumi
Hamada Masatoshi information
About him worrying
When he went out with his son,  he called her and said,
When he went out with his son, he called her and said,
"He wants to go to the park...  Is that okay?"
"He wants to go to the park... Is that okay?"
"He's just gone on  the jungle gym...  is that okay?"
"He's just gone on the jungle gym...  is that okay?"
"He's just gone on the jungle gym... is that okay?"
And when he got home, apparently they have 3 poodles,
but one of his poodles' ears is droopy, so he said to this one...
"Only your ear is droopy...  is that okay?"
"Only your ear is droopy... is that okay?"
You're taking the piss!
But that's information from his wife, right?
That obviously isn't true!!
It must be true if she told you...
That must be true.
I guess that's his nature...
Tsukomi people are meant to be the ones who make   things right so they shouldn't really be like that...
Tsukomi people are meant to be the ones who make things right so they shouldn't really be like that...
About Jinnai Tomonori...
I've got some information about him...
Apparently he took up jogging up for a while.
He was running with Yagi (Masumi) of Savanna (comedy group), who's his junior
Jinnai Tomonori information
Spontaneous moment
and together
they were running in Osaka Castle Park
But as soon as theystarted, he said, "My knee really hurts"
But as soon as they started, he said,  "My knee really hurts"
But as soon they started, he said  "My knee really hurts"
And they're wondering, "Why does it hurt? We've only just started running."
When they looked down at his feet, he was wearing leather boots
When they looked down at his feet,  he was wearing leather boots
For real?!
Right, who's next?
It's about a man called Endo Shozo, is that ok?
He really loves  his sex toys
He went around loads of shops looking for sex toys
Endo Shozo Information
Loves his sex toys
He went around loads of shops looking for sex toys
But lately...
He found out that the stuff at Donkey Hote   are really good
He found out that the stuff at Donkey Hote  are really good
So he buys his sex toys there, and he buys so much; he's really embarrassed about it
so he puts the goods in  among his golf stuff
so he puts the goods among his golf stuff
so he doesn't get noticed at the checkout counter
and he goes  3 times a week!!
and he goes 3 times a week!!
What a bad habit...
Are there no more stories?
I have one about Matsumoto...
Matsumoto Hitoshi information
When I go to the dressing room...
There are a lot of times, when you know...
I'm on a program with him so I go and just greet him
but usually...
He wears a white shirt,  V neck,  and his muscles are just amazing!!
He wears a white shirt, V neck  and his muscles are just amazing!!
He's hench (buff),and because he's got dark skin and he's got a white shirt on
He's hench (buff), and because he's got dark skin  and he's got a white shirt on
He's hench (buff), and because he's got dark skin and he's got a white shirt on
He really looks like a porn star about to do a video
He is really dark though...
I don't look like that, you dick.
He really does look it...
It's about like,
before he got so big and hench...
He wanted to go to the gym basically, and he had a bit of muscle...
Matsumoto Hitoshi Information
A Macho story
I asked him, "Bro, when do you go to the gym?"
And he answered, "Well, basically...
when I fight with my wife, and I'm annoyed,  then I go to the gym in my house."
when I fight with my wife, and I'm annoyed, then I go to the gym in my house."
when I fight with my wife  and I'm annoyed, then I go to the gym in my house."
And you know, he's massive now, right?  They're going to get divorced, aren't they!?
Well yeah, if he trains that much!
It has got nothing to do with his muscles, but...
There was like a house party  at the Matsumotos...
It was about 2 years ago...
Matsumoto Hitoshi information
At the House Party...
There was a conversation about Matsumoto-san and his wife...
It might just be hilarious for me but...
basically his hands were di.rty..
He said, "Do we have any like moist hand towels?"
and his wife replied "Sorry" and he said, "Yeah, just anything like a moist towel or something..."
so she was like "A moist towel?"... so he replied "Yeah, you know, something wet, I want to wipe off my hands."
and she replied, "We don't have any moist hand towels..."
"No no, not like that, just something to wipe off my hands with  a towel will do..."
"No no, not like that, just something to wipe off my hands with,  a towel will do..."
"No no, not like that, just something to wipe off my hands with, a towel will do..."
We don't have any  moist towels,  sorry
We don't have any moist towels,  sorry
We don't have any moist towels, sorry.
and he was like "Grrr..." Anyway that's what happened...
It was so funny...
I thought he was going to get really mad
Yeah, me too...
I can understand if it was towards a junior...
I was scared for her but he just kind of accepted it...
Obviously, he's going to go train his muscles then...
Yeah, if that happens, all you can do is go to the gym
I can't really explain this next one but...
It's about Tanaka Naoki...
When we're on the same program and our dressing rooms are like next to each other...
Tanaka Naoki Information
In the dressing room...
When he comes to greet me, he gets so happy  when I'm standing really close to the door
When he comes to greet me,  he gets so happy when I'm standing really close to the door
When he comes to greet me,  he gets so happy  when I'm standing really close to the door
So every time we are
on the same program,  just for Tanaka...  I stand really close to the door
on the same program, just for Tanaka... I stand really close to the door
on the same program, just for Tanaka...  I stand really close to the door
You shouldn't encourage that kind of behaviour...
But he gets so happy...
He goes, "Oh you're so close to the door" and he gets so happy
About Tanaka Naoki, basically...
He really loves  Mitarashi Dangos (type of food)
You don't need to tell people that...
Are we all done?
Okay guys, we are running out of time...
I have information on Miyasako Hiroyuki...
It's about Miyasako Hiroyuki...
So basically Matsumoto Hitoshi and Miyasako Hiroyuki were on the same program...
and after they finished with their show,  we agreed that I would come with them  to dinner
and after they finished with their show, we agreed that I would come with them to dinner
Matsumoto Hitoshi asked me "Mimata, what have you  done on TV lately?"
Miyasako Hiroyuki information
When they were drinking...
Matsumoto Hitoshi asked me "Mimata, what have you done on TV lately?"
It's not really amazing, but for the first time,  they let me be a chairman
It's not really amazing, but for the first time, they let me be a chairman
Miyasako Hiroyuki information
While drinking...
So he asked me "Wow, which program was it?"
So I answered  "The National Squirting Competition"
So I answered "The National Squirting Competition"
So 3 female pornstars came and you know...
I was there with my stopwatch and...
I had to see who could squirt the most times in an allocated time,  that's basically what the program is about
I had to see who could squirt the most times in an allocated time, that's basically what the program is about
and he (Matsumoto) answered "Jesus! Is there such a program on TV?!"
Anyway, eventually Matsumoto Hitoshi went home
So it was just Miyasako Hiroyuki and I now...
and he said, "I was laughing before because big bro was there and all...
but being on some program called  'The National Squirting Competition'...
but being on some program called 'The National Squirting Competition'...
like taking a job like that... I mean...
The money might be good,  but you've got to have courage to say no to those dodgy programs"
The money might be good, but you've got to have courage to say no to those dodgy programs"
and so you know, I felt bad and apologised to him
anyway, the atmosphere got a bit weird so Miyasako was nice and said
"There's no point just us drinking alone;  I'm going to call up some girls"
"There's no point just us drinking alone; I'm going to call up some girls"
30 to 40 minutes later, a girl appeared...
Coincidentally, the WINNER of "The National Squirting Competition" came
Coincidentally,  the WINNER of "The National Squirting Competition" came
Is there such a thing?   A miracle like this?
Is there such thing?  A miracle like this?
You idiot!
Just my name being in that story hurts...
16 hours since the start...
The atmosphere had changed...
and the 5, who were past their limits now...
could not even salvage a conversation...
We were a mess...
Well yeah, by this time...
When suddenly...
Gasu Earth Defense Force
Nursery
At Gasu Earth Defence Force
A nursery for all the female team members  with children
there is a nursery for all the female members of the force with children
and a lot of the children are taken care of here by our nurses
The infants  are taken care  by the
special nurses
There is an expert member
who knows everything about infants!
And out of them, there is someone who knows everything on the development of infants, and that is
Expert Member
Mother Jimmy
Mother Jimmy-san...
There are a lot of children today  who require your attention.
There are a lot of children today who require your attention.
I understand. Well then,
let's get to work!
BWEEEEEEE!!!
OEEEEEEEEEE
OEEEEEEEE
Po-Chan (Heipo)
*COUGH*
Task 1
Cleaning the belly button
First, we will clean the belly button
This properly stinks...
This is a ridiculous scene...
Those two have finally   combined together...
Those two have finally combined together...
Buweeeeeeeee
Ah Ah Ah
Ah Ah
AhAh
Bweeeeee
For crying out loud...
This is bad, huh...
This is really bad...
Task 2
Sucking the snot out
Next, we will suck out the snot with our equipment...
Bweeeee
Ufufufufufu
Bweee
Ufufufufufufufu
Ufufufufufufu
This is ridiculous...
This is so ridiculous...
What the hell are they doing? Just stop this...
I hate these two together...
This is tough huh?
This is really...
They're not matching dialect at all...
Task 3
Changing the nappies
Last of all, it's time to change the nappies.
Oeeeeeeeeee
What the hell  is this?
What the hell is this?
BWEEEEEEE
UWAAAAAAA
What the hell!
As expected of an expert, Mother Jimmy-san,
Expert Member
Mother Jimmy
The mothers at the EDF
feel safe with you there
the mothers working at the EDF, feel safe with you looking after their infants.
They were like a dream team...
It's the first time they were together in something, right?
Yeah, it was.
Is it?
Two big stars...
Everyone...
We've finished with the training  at this facility
We've finised with the training at this facility
Let's go back to headquarters.
Finished, eh?
Finished their training
Again, they return to  Headquarters
Their long training is now done
The 5 make their way back to Headquarters
They can't see the end yet
When they get to HQ,  it will all continue
However, their duties as Earth Defenders has not finished
When they get back to HQ, their job is not done yet.
1:00AM; they are back at the Headquarters...
Wow..
Nice to meet you...
I am the leader of the invading army, Kyoko
Invading army boss
Kano Kyoko
It's all a bit sudden, but I have taken your friend,  Fujiwara-san
It's all a bit sudden, but I have taken your friend, Fujiwara-san
If you want to save him, find a weapon in the armory,  which is somewhere in the building and save him
If you want to save him, find a weapon in the armory which is somewhere in the building and save him
If you want to save him, find a weapon in the armory  which is somewhere in the building and save him
If you want to save him, find a weapon in the armory, which is somewhere in the building and save him
I say, "Fuck it..."
First up, Tsukitei-san, Kokuriko... ko... Cocorico-san
First up, Tsukitei-san, Co...  Cocorico-san
First up, Tsukitei-san, Co... Cocorico-san
Oh, by the way
You can laugh now, but  if you get scared, you are OUT
You can laugh now, but if you get scared, you are OUT
Ho Ho Ho Ho
She made a few errors there..
So we can laugh freely now, yeah?
It's here again...
Every bloody year...
The one that Tanaka hates the most
I really hate this part...
The special rule of the night time
DO NOT GET FRIGHTENED
EARTH DEFENSE FORCE
Do not get frightened, Earth Defense Force
Get the ray gun in the armory and save Fujiwara!!
First up is Hosei and Cocorico
They go to find the ray gun which is needed to save Fujiwara
and head to the armory...
Okay we're off
We're off
Make it so that  we don't have to go
Okay, we will save him
We will do it all
You guys sort it all out, ok?
If we can...
If you combine our ages, we  are 100 years old!!
If you combine our ages, we are  100 years old!!
Yeah, seriously...
We understand...
What are you laughing at?
We're not laughing
We would never...
The game might allow you to laugh but  we don't allow you to!!
The game might allow you  to laugh but  we don't allow you to!!
The game might allow you to laugh but we don't allow you to!!
Matsumoto-san, you're so strict...
You're only just 100 years old together, you know?
Just 100...
Oh God, here we go again...
Oh jeez... This is bad...
Scenery has changed
I think you should go to the front...
Tanaka is so...
You go to the front...
I guess...
You'll fall on us otherwise...
You know, when something happens, you fall like this...
I really don't want to hurt  the either of you
I really don't want to hurt the either of you
There are signs telling you which way to go so...
This is too much...
2nd floor
Secret trap
What was that, I felt something...
Yeah, you're right...
Rubbish bin
What is that?
Holy shit!
The rubbish bin exploded
What the hell?
No way... no way!
Obviously I'm going to be scared...
This is   too intense!!
This is too intense!!
There's another one here...
They've gone full out from the start..
Tanaka, it's dangerous here,  let's go
Tanaka, it's dangerous here, let's go
Wait a second, wait a second, wait, wait
Wait a second, wait a second,wait, wait
Downtown alone together
Meanwhile, Dowtown were...
It's ridiculous how I'm the only one who has to  wear a bloody wig
It's ridiculous how I'm the only one who has to wear a bloody wig
I think if you really hated it that much, you would have told the staff by now?
I think if you really hated it that much  you would have said it to the stabb by now?
I think if you really hated it that much, you would have said it to the staff by now?
You know, if I told them something like that
It's like I'm saying a selfish thing
On the other hand, you say whatever you want to  about other stuff, right?
I mean, about that skirt and that wig... you don't say a thing
It seems like you accepted them...
So if this had been prepared for you to wear?
I think that's probably impossible
Right?
Yeah...
That's not my character, duh!!
That's actually
The message is completely different
What are you on about?
The arrival of the three wanderers at the armory
Armory
Isn't this?
Isn't this the armory?
Yeah, it is
A ray gun... Ah! Here it is
Ray gun taken: proceeding searching Fujiwara
Having grabbed their ray gun, they leave the armory
Skit in ... seconds
Ugh... That's creepy...
Are you okay, Tanaka?
Morohoshi Kazumi during a live?
A mysterious masked group attacks
The Live performances also strikes the training room
What the..?
Enough!!
This startled me so much!
They piss me off...
No, again?!
Ehh? Wait a second
Are we  hostages again?
They have been taken to the confinement room
I hate this part...
Huh!?
Enough of this!
Ugh, this again?
A giant piece of paper is placed
~Origami~ Shouji Tomoharu
Wow, Shouji was there?
Just do it normally
You can just do it normally, right?
There's something ghastly in him
Wow the Origami suddenly  skipped a few stages...
This must have been so tough to watch...
It was so long...
Ye I bet...
I bet it lasted ages...
It was awful
I guess he thought about this long and hard...
Mhh...
Abenomics
You're an idiot, aren't you?
The crane he made couldn't even stand up
Let us free!
Louis Kurihara's dance...?
"Because the next performance takes some time to be prepared, please enjoy Kurihara Lui's dancing in the meanwhile."
For real?
Eh?
I wonder if he can dance
Can you actually dance?
~Original Dance~ Kurihara Lui
An Original Dance
Creepy creepy creepy!
Scary!!
What kind of dance is this?
What's this?!
This dance is quite creepy...
Creepy!
Lui-kun, Lui-kun
Lui-kun, what's wrong buddy?
Woah! That's scary!
What just happened?
That's how he moves, huh?
The three, who were meant to find and rescue Fujiwara
The three are imprisoned...
End up being caught themselves
You two from Downtown
I have some bad news for you two
Tsukitei-san and CoCUrico-san have been
taken as hostages by my subordinates
It's a task for you two from Downtown
to go find the other three
Reunite and all together
Go and try to save Fujiwara-san
Well then, Good Luck!
Oh... ho... ho... ho...
She said that CoCUrico-san has been caught too.
Shall we go?
Stopping by the armory, then to the rescue of the three prisoners!
Now is time for Downtown to head to the armory
And after that
They're going to rescue the other three!!
This is so bloody annoying...
..seconds to CO2 gas spray
Woah!
I wish they would stop doing that
Defense Force - 3rd Floor
It would be nice if they would stop selling CO2 gas to the staff here
The company themselves, right!!
Right, right, right...
.... Seconds to next prank
Stay close to me...
Defense Force - 2nd Floor
What's that?
Remote Controlled
Kyouko Doll
Kyouko doll just exploded
These kind of things
really piss me off
It stinks.
Next Prank Countdown
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scar-
WOAH!!
Amagasaki unofficial character:
Making fun of "Little Old Man"
Why?
It surprised me!
Downtown brothers, come and eat at our store
You're noisy.
It's no good if you forget about Amagasaki!
Move, you're noisy
Shut up!
Come back to Ama(gasaki) some time, alright?
We're all waiting for you there!
Okay...
We got it...
Just before the Armory
Wait a moment...
I don't want this!
What's that?
Fingerprint authentication system
"place your hand on the mark for the fingerprint authentication system, one person at a time
starting with Matsumoto", uh
Announcer: Place your hand on the icon, please
Here?
Scary...
Announcer: Fingerprint authentication in process...
Fingerprint Authentication System
Monitor Screen
Fingerprint Authentication: Completed
You're Matsumoto Hitoshi-san, correct?
Yes!
Choose which is is between the two
Oh, it's "YES"
YES
Authenticating now...
I guess it's your turn?
Announcer: Place your hand on the icon, please
Announcer: Fingerprint authentication in process...
Monitor Screen
Fingerprint Authentication System
Fingerprint Authentication: Completed
You're Sato Gajiro-san, correct?
A 69 years old dude, uh
Choose which is is between the two
That's not the best fingerprint scanner
I said it's "NO"!
Couldn't authenticate.
Next prank in ... seconds
Please, authenticate one more time
Place your hand on the icon, please
I kn-
Bzzt
OUCH!
Authentication system gives him a shock
Authentication: complete
Armory
One more time...
The staff in here must really like those electric shock pranks!
The staff in here must really
like those electric shock pranks!
Damn that hurt!!
....Seconds to trash can jet propulsion
What ray gun should we take?
Which ray gun is ours?
W-wait
Oh, these!
Next Prank in 3 seconds
Next prank in 3 seconds
Here here here here here!
Scary, kinda scary
These, these, these
That electrical shock prank is scary!
thud
The mannequin attacks
...Seconds to next prank
That was unfair
Friggin' scary!
Sex appeal personnel Kano Mika + Pillars of fire
Fucking scary!!
Mika-san?
I didn't look at her at first!
What the hell?
Something is coming!
Where? There?
This way!
Where should we go?
Aah! Mika-san!
Why is she saying that?
Scaryscaryscaryscary!
We're safe! Safe!
It was Mika-san, right?
It was her, right?
Man this is crazy...
Woah, there's someone there
Oh! Here they are
Oi! You're there!
The three have been found and rescued safely
Downtown safely reunited with the other three
And they plan to exit the room at once
Some amazing stuff happened there...
When suddenly...
What should we do?
Wha- Uh?
Splendid, I must say, that teamwork of yours
Let me tell you where Fujiwara-san has been confined
He's in the storehouse of the sports ground
However, don't even think that you cou- can rescue him easily
How many mistakes does she want to make...
They could have just recorded it again...
You will taste the true fear in here
You're right...
They should have just recorded it again...
Going to the sports ground' storehouse to rescue Fujiwara!!
The five head towards the sports ground's storehouse, in order to rescue Fujiwara
So we are going to save Fujiwara?
Defense Force - 2nd floor
Yeah, we are
Uh...
I don't even understand what we're doing...
Uh? It's here?
The elevator in which they must hop in
There is something blocking their path...
The thing blocking their path is...
But before it
The thing that is blocking their path is...
Uh? Where to go?
Ah, here it is
It was just there
3 Seconds to the prank
This way...
We must go by elevator
Did you see that?
King of skits 2013 display - TKO Kinoshita's character
I learneddy to speaky speak!
Are you finished?
Because I talky everyday
I learnedy how to speaky!
Creepy!
That was creepy
Hop in!
He's moving!
Scary!
He's coming!
So creepy!
Aah! He's coming!
Me coming too!
Why are you here?
Why are you coming in?
Matsumoto-san saidythat my skit scoreded 920 pointies. (king of comedy 2013)
Matsumoto-san saidy that my skit scoreded 920 pointies! (king of comedy 2013)
Oh, did he? That's nice.
How many points do you thonk it was worth, Hamada-san?
You talk way too much!!
Defense Force - First Floor
Do your best! Do your best! Do your best!
Do my best?
Just go, go..
Come on, go...
Let's go...
You can do it!
He's funny...
He looks good
Awesome!
That surprised me!
Morohoshi Kazumi reappears
What the- Woah!
Bang
He has been shot!
Why things like that..?
Ka-kun... when it was his moment to shine..
Ka-kun... when it was his moment to shine...
He got shot...
He was just about to start singing
He was just about to start singing...
This way
Ehh? Enough of this...
Here, right?
Looks like it
I hope it's near
This way, come on
This year's is so long!
Ugh... there it is
Here's something!!
A representative must enter the phone box and wait for instructions!
"A representative must enter the phone box and wait for instructions!"
Waiting for orders, uh?
Pay attention to Hosei
No way, no way!
But you're our leader...
I don't want to, it's so scary!
The Junior's opinion: "Matsumoto should enter"
It's really scary, leader!
Do it for us, leader!
Please!
Please, leader!
Do it for us!
What the hell!!
Is it okay for you to go and wait for the instructions?
I don't get at all why I'm the one who has to go
Should we decide by rock-paper-scissor?
No, but-
Let's do this, shall we?
That's what I said
Yeah, that's right
Just like I said!
We don't know what could happen...
You're right...
Well, okay okay okay...
Choosing the person who will enter by rock-paper-scissor
I guess this is a bit...
Right, Rock Paper Scissors then...
That's scary, though
Ok?
Yeah
Shall we start?
Matsumoto Hamada Endo Tanaka Hosei
Sweet!
Ah! Endo!
Endo has been chosen!
Endo, you're going?
No no! I won, I'm out!
I'm out from this!
Don't be a party pooper... Are you really a member of this Earth Defense Force?!
Don't be a party pooper... Are you really a member of this Earth Defence Force?!
Don't be a party pooper... Are you really a member of this Earth Defence force?
What the hell!
It's so cold in here! Plus, we have to rescue Fujiwara!
Yeah, yeah, we have to save him!
I understand. After all, we are the Earth Defense Force, right?
I understand, After all, we are the Earth Defense Force, right?
Please, enter!
Ok, I'm going to wait for them!! (the instructions)
Scary...
... Seconds to prank
Ask for instructions!
Yes?
Strong Wind from the receiver
Woah!!
A large quantity of white flour fell
Thank God!
I was so close to going in as well...
This is the worst...
You just became covered of pawdur!
What about the instructions?
What are the instructions?
There was nothing about instructions
Eh?!
I guess we just follow this path ahead then...
That was incredible, check this smell
Woah, awesome!
That was great
Wait just a sec...
He became covered of pawdur
The way he removed the flour...
Incredible, this high tension
You must not liked this, uh?
Sports Ground
It's ridiculously pitch black in here!!
What is that?
There are 5 of those...
Crucifiction standfor 5 people
Crucifiction stand for 5 people
Yes?
Ehhh?!
Eh? Enough of this!
Mysterious masked group attack
whatwhatwhatwhatwhatwhat
This has never happened before, what the hell?
The 5 have been crucified...
What is this, what the hell!
What's that for?!
Did we do something bad to deserve this?
What the-?!
Eh?!
... Seconds to prank
This is way too cruel!
Really, too cruel!
Uhhh?!
Hey!
What is that?
What the-
Wait a second, what the hell...
Did we do something bad to deserve this?
What is that!
Eh?
... Seconds to prank
This is way too cruel!
Really, too cruel!
They're saying something...
Eh?
Scary!
What is that thing?
What is coming out?
It's a rhinoceros beetle robot!!
Invading Army's Combat Weapon:
A giant rhinoceros beetle robot
What appeared unexpectedly before the eyes of the five members....
Is a 11 meters long and proud
Big, enormous rhinoceros beetle robot!
Woah, awesome!!
What should we do?
Ah! Mika-san is riding it!!
Woah! You're right!
Is this safe?
It's not Mika-san, it's Kyouko-san
That's amazing!
I'll crush you!!
Make it stop from doing those random movements!!
You idiot!
That's dangerous!
You're going to hell!
Can Mika-san actually see?
Yeah, seriously, can she?
This thing is drawing near!
The Rhinoceros Beetle Robot draws near
A desperate situation: they're in a big pinch!
The rhinoceros beetle robot draws near
Hey, Shozo!!
Yatta-man? Is that Yatta-man?
Sorry we kept you waiting!!
We came from Toyonaka!
Endo~
Endo-man!
The peace of our world is something Endo-man has to protect!
Toshihide (67 years old)
Endo Toshihide, 67 years old
Endo Kiyomi, 63 years old
Kiyomi (63 years old)
Endo-men are called on!!
How many bloody times do you want to appear?
What are they doing?
How many appearances are you going to make this year!!
Seriously, how many bloody times?
Endomen rescued the 5 prisoners
At least we're free to go
Thanks, Endoman!
An awesome setup, really
Endoman is 67 years old, wow...
This way, let's go this way
Got it
Here
Haven't they appeared too many times this year?
Really...
You Endomen guys, wait up!!
She said 'wait'
What?
Let's run away, guys!!
Roger that
... Seconds to prank
Wait! I won't let you escape!
This is hard!!
I wonder if they're okay..!
Wait up!!
Fujiwara's whereabouts are...?
What about Fujiwara?
Oh! You're right!
That's true!
We were supposed to save him
Ah! Fujiwara!
Hmm?
Guys!
Good job!
Ah!
I was somehow able to escape from the storage by myself!
By yourself?!
Yeah, that's true Matsumoto-san
19 hours since Earth Defense Force training started
Late in the night, 3:00 A.M.
After becoming part of the Earth Defense Force
Five men have completed several harsh tasks
The two red marks on his nose...
Finally, they face that moment...
Guys...
Your long Earth Defense Force task is ending here!!
Thank God!!
We made it!
You did a great job
Thank you!
Ok guys, shall we go?
Thank you so much!
Thank you
Much appreciated
It was harder than any other year...
Hamada, don't you need to take those with you?
These
It's Model 1-M
Why should I take those?
We think it's really important if you take those with you
You should decorate your house with these
Whilst you three were off doing your part of the 'do not get frightened'
Hamada was caressing them like his children
I wonder if when alone with Hamada  it will come to life and talk to him?
We're into the new year huh?
Really?!
It's 2014!
I crossed a year holding this thing? (Model 1-M)
We don't even get to wear any jackets.
We don't even get to wear any jackets...
Yeah, you're right
In the past, when he came to tell us we're done,  he brought us coats as well
In the past, when he came to tell us we're done  he brought us coats as well
Right!
Happy new year!!
Thanks for your work!
Happy new year!
Legendary Captain: Suga Kenji
This year is the year of the horse
Right...
We have a teacher (of Rakugouka) here
Using the word "Umadoshi" (year of the horse) I'll make a compostistion using...
Did you bite your tongue?
Sorry?
It's too cold and Suga Kenji's mouth won't work properly.
Don't bit your tongue
We know it's cold and everything!
Yeah, it's cold
Of course it's impossible
Topic: Horse Year
U-MA-DO-SHI, it goes like this
Umadoshi, right?
"U"
The road of no lies
"MA"
The road of seriousness
"DO"
I want to walk it, rapidly
"SHI"
I wanna walk it with Shelly!!
What the...
I... I think that's...
Why that outcome?
Why are you saying that?
Whatever
Couldn't find anything else, right?
That's because I'm going to do my best cooperating with Shelly for a whole year
Guys, I wish the best regards for you for this year!
Thank you!
If you excuse me..!
I couldn't understand not even a bit of what he said!
Everything was soooo messed up
He spoke so fast...
Everyone, huh?
Well, this was for sure
No, I think he should be OUT
Ouch!
Owowow
It hurts!
It hurts, geez!
Okay, everyone, we can get out of here this way
Once you cross this line your task comes to its end
Looks like we made it through the end!
Yeah!!
It's over!
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tsukitei Hosei
Hamada Masatoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Endo Shozo
Okay!!
I wish you all a happy new year!
Happy new year!
You too!
"I want to become kind"
Kuzayoshi Saitou
As the clock turns to 8 o'clock, I get ordered 'protect the earth'
Fujiwara is laughing at Masatoshi's wig
From behind Itou, draws unnoticed Gen Ichirou
Morisaki is now part of the nostalgic family
Chouno is not fast. His slap is not fast.
It's not something intended to end just with nicknames
It's not like he's just crap at Maths
It looks like you, this ugly Model 1-M
That's actually very funny.
It's not like I want to cry, with that letter to dear Papa
Words can't come out, I want to sing properly
The low dining table flips over, but Asei comes out, after this
And Matsuko, who doesn't want to get out, dance thanks to a clockwork motor
Okada would probably say... "Looks like you! WOW!",
If you can meet Maeken, it's all good
I don't want to laugh, I don't want to laugh
By Anna's freedom or Itao's dance
It's not like I want to eat Ebisu's rice cake...
Or dance to a song, or to create a rabbit...
It's not like I want to destroy a precious album
This one, huh?
I don't want to get caught; I want to escape from the ass spray
The wax waterweel is spinning, a stench comes out by farting
Horiken, who runs away, please don't snap at him...
It's not like I want to receive those slaps without any love
I want to be part of the disclosure, and Shouhei, I can't laugh at your jokes...
It's not like I want to accept this loveless explosion
I'm not young anymore, my joints hurt
I'm already over 50, but I want to be interesting
I want to be smiling, I want to live laughing
We hope that laughter fulfills your year...
Looks like it's finally ended!
It's over!
Greetings for the new year!
Greetings to everyone!
Happy new year!
Happy new year
We crossed a new year
Yeah!
That's right, uh? We've crossed the new year by now
Yeah, we did
What are we going to do now, seriously?
This is our 8th year I believe...
Now that I think about the Kouhaku...
Kitajima Saburou didn't show up this year, right?
Yeah, right
Really, uh?
Let's get the Kitajima family to do our jobs from next year??
With his family?
Yeah
Like all of them?
Just go get Saburo-san and everyone and just...
we just need to talk to the heads of Yamamoto...
Ye, that way, we can just go on Kouhaku
But seriously, this is so tough...
well, we'll leave it at that for now...
I know, right? Really...
Sorry, but really, viewers of Gaki no Tsukai ya Arehende
I hope you'll keep on watching us this year!
Thanks!!
Please continue to support us! HAPPY NEW YEAR !!
This Story was a fiction. Every organization name etc. that appeared in it is fictitious.