Tofu Panda Fansubs presents:
Down Town's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
TPF
Ah. So, according to the staff,
Endo opened a safe.
You three were talking about this.
We talked about that in the taxi.
Yeah, it was the other day.
In the segment where we didn't use phones...
Tanaka didn't hear about this.
I haven't heard anything about this.
Yeah, when we were doing
the "without phones" thing, us three were in the taxi...
That's when we were...
It was you three and Tanaka and me.
Okay.
I don't remember what we were talking about but,
he started talking about his safe.
There's a safe that I've always kept in my house.
But I forgot the combination
and I lost the key.
So it just sat there for over ten years.
I started getting curious about it so I decided to open it.
So I called a locksmith company
and had them open the safe.
There was actually something inside.
But it wasn't money or anything.
It was a handwritten letter
that Tanaka gave me before he came to Tokyo.
That was in the safe?
I must have put it in the safe
because it was important to me, and it had stayed there since.
That sounds like a nice story but,
That's a nice story.
Who would wanna steal that!?
Putting it in a safe...
Seriously...
But really, that was the only thing in there.
And around 20 years later, I read it again.
That's what we were talking about.
Ah... while you were in the car.
The thing is that,
right now.
Endo's wife let us borrow it.
We asked her to
You're kidding, right?
Endo's wife let us borrow it.
Hey, why? Why?
1992...
Do you remember?
I'm getting a really bad feeling about this.
This is something that Tanaka wrote...
Why?
This was just a nice story...
"To Endo Shozo-kun" It says.
Not only that. Tanaka.
What's with this handmade envelope?
It's stapled together.
That looks really bad.
What were you doing?
It looks really bad.
It looks like it's from back in the war.
Seriously.
Well, it's from 1992 (24 years ago).
It's from 1992.
It's from back when we came to Tokyo.
You still weren't famous.
It's from around our debut.
Departing to Tokyo "Do Your Best" Edition.
No, no, the "Do Your Best Edition" is just...
So lame
Edition? Now it's some special edition?
"Do Your Best" Edition?
Let's stop this, come on.
I'm serious.
Departure to...
This was just...
Tokyo, "Do Your Best" Edition.
Departure to Tokyo Do Your Best Edition
No, this edition thing was...
How many editions were there?
Please don't do this
You know, at the time...
I was serious.
"Do Your Best" Edition.
Look at the name,
the name on the back was weird.
Tanaka Hidemitsu?
What is that?
Okay, this is...
Back then,
when we were in elementary school,
there was this funny, quirky kid.
His name was Hidemitsu,
and that's probably why Tanaka...
Let's just stop this!!
Sit down!
That's not funny at all.
It wasn't about being funny.
This whole "Tanaka Hidemitsu" thing.
Seriously.
Look inside.
Inside.
Look inside, Matsumoto.
It wasn't meant to be funny.
*The names in the letter all have the kanji character translation.
Why does his name have the pronunciation written on top?*
That despite being an adult,
maybe he couldn't read the characters...
Uhh...
So it's a joke?
Maybe I thought it would be funny?
That's where it's supposed to be funny.
I don't know.
Making him seem like an adult
Please sit down.
who couldn't read his own name.
The real problem is inside.
There's no way this is gonna funny.
The outside is pretty awful too...
This is all just...
Well, you really got me with this...
Why didn't you buy an envelope?
Actually, at the time, Tanaka was
I think it there was some kind of reason.
going to a vocational school...
For a designer course at the school
So with his handy skills,
he always made a lot of things himself.
Phh...
So it's completely handmade.
So it's not like, um...
Eh, wait...
Do you remember writing this before coming to Tokyo?
Yeah, I remember writing it and giving it to him.
Hey, what are you pulling out?!
Be careful.
They found something in there.
What the hell is that? That's so creepy!!
That's disgusting, what is that?
Really, what's up with that?
What are you talking about?
What is that?
That isn't a letter...
He drew a portrait of him.
It's making me feel really sick.
Why?
I don't understand the reason for this.
No, no, this is...
Why? Why this?
Even I'm not entirely sure why this was there.
It must have been some trend at the time.
I don't know but...
He traced it.
He traced it with a pencil.
The shocking letter is revealed
Next
Alright, sit down.
This is not good.
This is an advertisement to ride the bus and experience the No Laughing Batsu segment.
Show what's inside.
Wait...
Let's just stop this.
I'm serious.
The writing is really small.
This is...
He couldn't have read this without reading glasses.
We brought in an announcer for this.
Let's have him read it.
Wait...
Hello.
I'm Sugaya, NTV announcer.
Nippon TV Announcer
Sugaya Daisuke
Well then, with your permission...
Can you read it?
The writing is really small.
Yes, it's fine.
Please excuse me while I read on your behalf.
Wait, seriously, wait...
Just sit down!
Please wait...
Wait a minute, please! I'm serious!
I'll seriously do anything!
I'll do anything so,
Please don't read it.
No, it's better to read it.
Let me just say this,
This isn't gonna be funny or anything.
Right, that's it.
It's just a letter between friends from 24 years ago,
That's right.
when we were together...
You came to Tokyo together?
We did.
We didn't come together.
There was just a little delay.
Endo came first.
I came to Tokyo
and Tanaka came two months later.
An "I'll be waiting for you" sort of thing?
I was like "I'll wait for you" so...
In response to that, Tanaka wrote this letter.
That's the reason for the letter.
That's why he wrote it.
Right.
No, wait, wait...
It's not funny, this won't be funny at all.
This won't be funny, I don't care about that.
It's stuff from 24 years ago, anyway.
But actually,
I think it's gonna be sort of disgusting.
It's not funny, really.
It's obviously not gonna be funny, but that's fine.
I'm actually okay with it not being funny...
But more than that,
I think it's a creepy one
That's what I'm afraid of.
I think I'll actually be very moved by this.
You don't know...
There's no way
you will.
Let's just be quiet and listen together.
For now, please sit down.
Why did you write a letter if you were gonna follow two months later?
He actually hadn't decided to leave two months later.
He'd just been thinking about it.
But you know, this is...
This is the title.
This isn't something we should be showing everyone.
Let's read it right to the end.
Of course...
Let's just listen.
Better to not stop every few seconds.
Right.
Do it right.
To Endo Shozo-kun,
Departure to Tokyo. "Do Your Best" Edition
Dear Endo Shozo,
At last, it's here. The day of your departure.
Today, Tuesday February 2nd,
Is a very important day for you. Let's remember this day.
For now, please go ahead and keep an eye on the situation for me.
I'll be following you soon.
Let me say this clearly.
What's with this weird writing
I, your partner Tanaka Shinichiro, alias
Stop that, we can't read it like this.
Sit down!!
Sit down, Shinichiro!!
Let us listen!
Shinichiro, sit down!!
I'm sorry but this is really...
Sit down, Shinichiro.
Enough... stop this...
Don't do that again.
This was something between friends.
Let me say this clearly.
I, your partner Tanaka Shinichiro, alias Tanaka Takuya
That was another joke, I guess.
That was a double joke.
This is...
Something that only I could understand.
Only I would think, "Hey, who's this Takuya?"
It's fine if only you understand it...
Yeah, it's okay that I could get it.
Okay then.
It's directed at me.
I'll be heading there on the 1st of April; I'll be waiting for your retort.
It's something only I could understand.
It's a retort with a time lag.
The retort for the fake names, right?
Yes
In 2 months when I arrive, please retort.
"Thanks in advance."
Anyways, for now let's light a cigarette and take a puff.
And then, we shall offer a cigarette
to the old man sitting nearby.
What is that?!
Something like that probably happened though, right?
It probably happened.
I don't know
Since we just turned 20, we could finally start smoking
and something like that happened, I think.
Something like that
Parenthesis "By 8000 Kei"
"By 8000 Kei"?
"Parenthesis"?
"Parenthesis 'By 8000 Kei'"
This is, this is just...
The Hankyuu
"B a y"
This is about  The Hankyuu Railway'snew trains
This is about the Hankyuu Railway's new trains.
The ones at the time.
As long as I get it...
Do you get it?
I get all of these...
But still,
Why did trains suddenly come up?
Well, sudden and random
Exactly
Suddenly writing random stuff
can be funny, right?
Who's speaking? No idea
Suddenly...
Random stuff.
Completely random
Changing it up, huh
I can feel the amateurishness
There is one thing I feel I have to apologize for
After coming back from Kagawa,
The precious time we had together before you left Osaka
was spent helping me with my project.
*Aritou is close to arigatou, meaning thanks
Aritou.
➦Former Lotte Mariner, Number 8
Michiyo Aritou
Wait, hold on
As long as I think it's funny, it's alright.
Hey. hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
You're not
even laughing
I am laughing
Hey. hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Sit down, sit down!
Sit down already.
As long as I get it.
Only I have to get it.
He's really packing the jokes in tight.
He really is
In such a short letter...
He's packing the jokes in so tight.
So it's not a serious letter, huh.
He really wants Endo
to think that he's funny.
It was really funny to me.
That's probably what I was doing.
No, no, Aristotle. That's not right!
Really, Sasshūnada Nada. (Izutsu Stable)
...sorry. But really, thank you.
I'll show you once I graduate.
And now, a haiku.
Stop!
"And now, a haiku" can't be good
No wait, seriously please.
Just end the letter there!
Enough, already!
Unbelievable
What's wrong with you
He won't stop with the jokes!
He's really showing off his talents
It's overflowing
This is bad
"And now, a haiku"
This isn't good.
And now, a haiku.
At least for today thoroughly and completely $#!&$#!&$#!&.
I'll stop writing pointless sentences now, but
Will you look for a place for me when you have time?
I'm counting on you.
Suddenly so serious.
I know that Endo Shouzou has probably known this for a while,
He used his full name
We'll cause a lot of problems for a lot of people. However
we're going to Tokyo to try and
make our dream a reality, so
Let's go after it as hard as we can
with no regrets, kaykay!?
It's almost over
Isn't he reading it in a bad way?
No, he's not
Really?
That was normal.
Correct
He definitely read it that way on purpose.
As long as we're together, we'll definitely be successful.
I suppose soon, your beloved
eastern Japanese soil (red clay) will be under you.
Or maybe you're still in Kyoto?
Or maybe, you haven't even got on the train yet?
This makes no sense.
To Toshirou, the stupid Japanese giant salamander
I'll be headed there in April,
so tell him to wash his **** and wait for me.
What the hell are you talking about?
He's confused.
That's not normal.
Then, I'll suck it for him.
Did he really write that?
Are you kidding?
It was that kind of...
Something Tanaka would never say.
This is crazy
No more.
This is gross.
I'm so happy.
So, relax and wait a bit.
Sorry for the pointless letter,
but be sure to take care of yourself.
Tuesday, February 2, 1992. 9 AM, 32 minutes and 2 seconds.
from your partner, Tanaka Naoki (Whale species)
He joked to the very end.
Thank you very much.
Bravo!
There were so many parts that we don't understand.
Parts that only Endo understand...
Wow, that was somethin'.
From twenty something years ago...
That was somethin'.
You even made this?
Here it is.
24 years ago,
When I...
was about to get on the
train at Shin-Osaka station he gave me this.
Oh, I see.
We thought it would be more serious.
Like "Let's do our best"
or something like that.
In April, I'll...
This part is rough.
"I'll head there in April,
so tell him to wash his **** and wait for me.
Then, I'll suck it for him.
I'm so happy."
That's...
He just...
It's a $#!& letter.
That's not true.
That's not what it was.
It's a $#!& love letter.
What the hell is this!!
After that we worked hard and...
It's crazy that you found this.
So now, I think
Next it's time for Endo
to write a letter back to Tanaka.
After all, you really should or it will feel unfinished.
A conclusion, huh.
After all this time...
Hold on
It's too big of a wall to climb for me.
Writing back after 24 years...
I'm really bad with these kinds of things.
It's just a response to this.
24 years later...
I see.
No no no no no no,
I think you should.
That would be so...
You have to fill it to the brim with jokes.
That would be so hard.
Talk Scene Recording Finished
Following their dreams,
they headed to Tokyo.
Endo's Feelings towards Tanaka
His feelings that he never expressed...
until now.
To Tanaka Naoki (Whale species),
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
At the time of receiving this letter 24 years ago,
We never dreamed that it would be read
on Downtown's show that we both admired so much.
It was all possible, because you came to Tokyo with me.
I am truly grateful. Ariga Satsuki.
Former Fuji TV Announcer
In the future,
Let's continue to work hard,
and do our best on the show-n Connery.
And now, a haiku.
Eastern Japan is once again today, fertile layered soil.
July 31, 2016. 11:55 PM
from your partner, Endo Shozo
(by Airbus A380)
Translator:
Typesetter & Proofreader:
Jose
&
Callanse
Otviss
**We also have Facebook and Twitter.**
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
____________________________________________________________________________________________
If you ever see this video being distributed online but not by us, keep in mind that on Youtube
individuals may make money off of sharing fansubs like this that are not their own. Please go back and
support the original creators. Fansubbing is voluntary and is not meant to generate profit. You can
download episodes on our website instead. Thanks for watching!