"Shozo Endo's quiz - Maa Maa Maa!"
TN: "Maa Maa" is a word similar to OK. It can mean something is mediocre or so-so, and can also be used to calm people down (like "now now" or "Ok ok")
Maa Maa Ma Ma Maa Ma Maa Ma
Maa Maa Ma Ma Maa Ma Maa Maaaaaaaaaa
So it's begun, this is the Maa Maa Maa quiz
So this segment is my idea,
I can't believe they let you get away with this
Now now Hamada-san now now now that's Maa Maa
You sure do say Maa Maa a lot
Well, I entered the break rooms of male comedians,
And I just said "Maa Maa" until they let me kiss them
Who the hell cares
Hamada-san, Maa maa maa
So I went out and kissed some guys and filmed it, and that's what the quiz is gonna be about
Quiz?
They didn't know anything about this right?
Yes the other comedians didn't know anything
It's just a test to see if I can kiss them by just going "Maa Maa Maa"
Matsumoto-san what do you think? If I came in with a camera going "Maa Maa" and tried to kiss you?
That would be "Maa Maa" I guess
Well you said it
Timed & Typeset by: Kedomas
Translated by: senor_wristband
In this quiz, the members guess how long it takes Cocorico's Endo to kiss male comedians by saying only "Maa Maa"
They will win "Maa Maa" dolls for coming the closest
Well let's begin, this is our first target
London Boots - Tamura Ryo
Situtation - In front of the studio after recording
Ah Ryo?
It's Ryo from London Boots. We're the same age, but he is my junior
So I was waiting for him after an NTV shoot in front of the studio
Damn that's amazing actually
So, take it away!
Everyone reveal your answers please!
Matsumoto: 21 seconds - Hamada:  5 seconds  Yamasaki: 30 seconds - Tanaka: 3 minutes
Did that thing just go Maa Maa?
This is what you mean right?
Ah yes around 21 seconds?
I think after 21 seconds
I see
Hamada-san 5 seconds, thats quick
He's gonna go "Why? Why?", but the camera is there and you're his senior
I feel like he'll kiss you a bit, and then immediately pull away
5 seconds is quick though
It could be even quicker
5 seconds is quick indeed
Hosei-san?
Similiar to Matsumoto-san's guess. He'll go like "Wait what?" in the beginning, but yeah 30 seconds really
Tanaka-san, oh that's a long one! 3 minutes you wrote
Yeah I think on the contrary it's gonna take a while
I think you've stretched it too long
The correct answer will be revealed now
Man so many small details
Waiting for Ryo's recording to finish
Woah
Yeah I was waiting out here
This situation
Yeah not sure how this'll turn out
Here it starts
Ah, it's the time until the kiss? I thought it was how long
Yes, until the kiss
Now now, now now (he only says this)
Why?
I made it seem like I want to talk
Yes
What is this?
Now now now now now now...
Wha-What?! What are you doing?!
NOW NOW NOW
What?
He's not really resisting
Oh, he saw theres a camera
Yes, he just checked
What are you doing?
There it is, almost there
Alright alright alright
I don't understand
I was checking to see if he'd bring his face closer
Damn! Tanaka,
I think my guess was close
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
WHAT-
Ok...
Wait!
No this is not Maa Maa (Okay)
Why'd you do it again?
Why'd you do it again? It has nothing to do with this
That's not necessary! What's the point of that
It's already over
Right?
That was too much
Eh? hold on please
Eh?
It's like I'm the one who did something wrong. What is this, seriously?
What is this?
Alright, the closest answer is Yamasaki-san!
He wins 2 dolls!
Thank you very much
I just got it
I thought it was the length of the kiss
And we've got a woman - A rather Maa Maa (not bad) woman
You can't say that man
Thank you very much
She seems Maa Maa (fairly) angry!
Incidentally, the kisses in the videos,
I want to know what you think, there are these Maa Maa buttons. If you think it was a pretty good kiss please press it
Is it possible to not understand someone this much?
What are you saying?
Well just try it out
Maa Maa
If you think its a Maa Maa (decent) kiss then press it
If I think that then I'll press it
Moving on, the next target is;
Miyagawa Daisuke
Situation - Backstage after recording
So here we go
There it is
Daisuke-san...
I think his switch flips on quicjly
This is a tough one...
It's possible that Daisuke will be very eager
I see. Well please write your answers!
I don't think he won't do it
I think he will do it
Yes indeed
It's a question of how many seconds
I think I got it now finally
Please guess the time until the kiss, if you think he'll do it
So, let's reveal the answers!
Matsumoto-san says 17 seconds. So faster than Ryo?
Matsumoto: 17 seconds - Hamada: 20 seconds
I think, Daisuke would do it even faster if there was no camera
Yamasaki: 15 seconds - Tanaka: 6 seconds
For real?
Daisuke is OK with men and women of all ages
So no camera just going Maa Maa?
Daisuke-kun is OK with anything except old men
So if there was no camera and someone like Tanaka went in?
Yes he would kiss him
I think this is the fastest possible time
Daisuke returns to his break room after recording
Please relax in here
Ah, he's smoking. But Endo still has to kiss him right?
Yes exactly
Endo smokes too right?
Ah yeah
Alright it's begun
Yup he's gone in
If it was 6 seconds then it would be here
Ahh here huh?
See, this situation...
What do you mean "Maa Maa"?
Yeah of course he would say that
Oh dear!
Eh?
What is this?
Maa Maa Maa. Maa Maa.
What the hell is this?
Seriously what is this
No not "Maa Maa"!
How many times are you gonna do it?!
Seriously, how many times?
Where are you going?
Hold on, what?
Who is this?
What is this?
So Hamada-san wins!
Thank you
It was 24 seconds!
As expected, Daisuke's switch flips quickly
Yeah it did
So how was the video? If you think it was great please press the Maa Maa button!
Maa Maa. Maa Maa.
I'm the only one who looks like an idiot
So let's keep on going. The next target is;
Ogi Hiroaki
Situation - TV Station Parking Lot
Well basically I haven't really worked with him before,
I see
I've barely ever talked to him either
And well I just wanted to say this now,
He's wearing glasses right? I think that's something to consider
But Daisuke was wearing them too
Maa Maa. Maa Maa.
You're pressing it for that?
Matsumoto: Doesn't -  Hamada: 50 seconds  Yamasaki: 25 seconds - Tanaka: 1 min 25 seconds
These are the 4's guesses. So, just what time will it be?
This is not good!
Ogi arrives at the NTV parking lot
Here we go
There's someone else
Yeah
After he gets out...
After he gets out
Maa Maa Maa
This is so scary
What is this?
What is it?
You scared me, what is this?
No not "Maa Maa"
He's going to make this difficult
Yeah
It's a matter of whether or not he even does it
Here we go, here we go
Alright
Hosei-san's 25 seconds is coming up soon
C'mon do it!
Do it!
What is it? (x2)
Sorry I don't understand
Endo hurry up and move in!
Yeah
Hold on!
He almost went for it there
Yeah
What?
I think Tanaka got it
Yes
Ah there he goes
Wasn't that too long?
What?
Wh- What?
Why do you do it twice?!
It's always unnecessary!
You don't have to do it twice!
His glasses are coming off too
He's really going at it
What is this?
So Hamada-san wins!
Thank you very much
You win 2 more Maa Maa dolls
But Endo, Ogi leaned into it once
It's a difficult thing to handle. If I do it too soon he might back away, so I have to wait a bit
It's something that does happen
You don't know until you try it huh?
Yes, not until you try it
Well I'm not gonna do it though
That was quick
Maa Maa
So there's still more-
YOU HAVE SO MANY
How can you be so good at this
# 4
Irie Shinya
Break Room at Yoshimoto HQ
The target this time is Yoshimoto's Irie
These are their guesses. Hamada who won twice in a row wrote 30 seconds. How will this turn out?
Matsumoto: 43 seconds - Hamada: 30 seconds Yamasaki: 52 seconds - Tanaka: 32 seconds
Irie enters a room at Yoshimoto HQ for a meeting
OK Start
Good morning!
He saw the TV, he saw the camera
He saw the camera yeah
He's looking around, he thinks he's gonna get hit maybe
What is this
What is it?
So quick!
That was so quick!
This is bad!
What is this?!
GOD DAMN! What are you doing?!
Too quick
You've got your mouth open!
I'm just creeped out
Hamada-san continues to win!
Some more Maa Maa dolls for you
3 in a row is impressive
What kind of talent is this?
#5!
Himura Yuki
Situation - At a pub after work
The target this time, the #1 kissing comedian, Bananaman's Himura
The 4's guesses are as shown. Will Hamada win a miraculous 4th time?!
Matsumoto: Doesn't do it -  Hamada: 46 seconds
Yamasaki: 53 seconds - Tanaka: 1 min 15 seconds
Ah this kind of place
Himura arrives to have a meal after work
Ah his manager is there
Doing this would surprise him
He was super surprised
I see
Maa Maa Maa Maa Maa
That's a great face he's making
Maa Maa Maa
What?
Certainly, as Endo said...
What is this seriously?
It's hard to time this
It's so difficult to decide
It is, he can't close the distance at all
If I do it too quickly he'll run away
Ehhh what what what is this seriously
Yeah this is still not the moment
Yeah he can't do it now
Yeah
Eh?
I see, it can turn out like this too
I see
When it gets like this...
You go all the way
Oh my, he's crying!
He did cry
He cried?
What is this?
So Tanaka won this round!
I see
Thank you
Everyone else please try your best
Why did he cry?
I don't know. He said he didn't have any emotions of anguish or happiness or sadness or anything, he just started crying on his own
Then he's pregnant
Crying with no emotion
Is what he said
Alright, lets move on to the next target
The next target is this
Kaneda Akira
Situation - In the washroom of Yoshimoto HQ
Hanya's Kaneda
This one is super serious
He's really quite a germaphobe
He doesn't really kiss women either, even though he's a comedian
This time I headed to Yoshimoto's HQ
I waited for Kaneda to enter the washroom, and then barged in with the camera
The washroom?
The washroom
Matsumoto: 3 min 15 sec - Hamada: 3 min 32 sec
Yamasaki: Doesn't do it - Tanaka: 1 min
This time it's the germaphobe Kaneda. Will Endo be able to kiss him?
There he is
Kaneda heads to Yoshimoto HQ for a meeting
Kaneda who knows nothing
I think this is gonna be a difficult one
Everyone seems to smoke
Oh right, you'll wait for him in the washroom?
Oh right, the washroom
He's moving!
He's going to the washroom I think
After he finishes peeing?
No I enter right away
Oh right away?
Good morning
Maa Maa Maa Maa
Man this is scary, it's in the washroom too
Eh?
What is it?
What is it? Wait wait wait what is it?!
Hold on! What is this, seriously!
Look!
Nobody has resisted this much before
Wow!
AHHH WHAT IS THIS
You're just forcing him!
OW!
He's trying so hard to escape
STOP WAIT WHAT IS THIS SERIOUSLY
AHHH SERIOUSLY
Seriously
Woahh look
Amazing
Interesting
This is amazing
He ran away
Maa Maa!
He went inside?
Yeah
I was so surprised by this
Maa Maa Maa!
Hold on! What is this?
"Maa Maa Maa"
This could be Yama-chan's win
Yeah it's gotta be mine
What do you mean "Maa Maa"?!
It's like a studio apartment
What is this for real?
It really is! It's like a studio!
Stop! Honestly!
What's he gonna do now?
OW!
He ran away!
What?!
He ran away for real
He did it
Unexpectedly, Kaneda escapes!
He's looking for him
What is this
For real, this guy...
He really doesn't wanna do this
Oh he's there
Wow
This guy...
He really did run away
Maa!
What is "Maa"?!
He didn't kiss him
I see
Ahh I see
Yamasaki-san wins!
Unexpectedly, he didn't do it
Even though his senior walked in with a camera going Maa Maa
I really did think "The young people these days don't get it"
He really hated it
He made me work so hard
He hit the camera so many times and still ran away
I see
The last target is this
Sekine Tsutomu
Break room before recording
Sekine-san huh
Damn Sekine-san...
You all know Sekine Tsutomu-san of course
Matsumoto: 8 sec - Hamada: 1 min 22 sec
Yamasaki: 1 min 30 sec -  Tanaka: 1 min 40 sec
Their guesses are as shown. How will Endo kiss his important senior?
Sekine enters the break room
Oh it's curry
Good morning
Maa Maa. Maa Maa.
He's eating curry too
Maa Maa?
Mmhmm
He's so cautious
What is it man
He pulled back
Of course he pulled back
You want some?
What is it?
What (x2)
Hmm?
That was rather quick
That was really rather quick
Are you an idiot?
How long are you gonna do it for?!
As expected!
Well done!
Brilliant
His switch flipped
I wanted to see this
I wanted to see this!
The mount
Amazing!
It really was amazing
Maa Maa
Like "We can still do it"
Yeah he was giving off that vibe
So Hamada-san wins!
Of course!
The winner this time is Hamada-san!
So the winner Hamada gets a portrait drawn by mangaka Yaku Mitsuru-sensei
I think he'll be Maa Maa happy
I think you'll be Maa Maa happy. Congratulations
Thank you very much. Thank you for this.
So that was the Maa Maa Maa quiz
Is there a part 2?
No way
I asked if we should do it again, and the staff said go for it
They're making the preparations?
They are
Some strange preparations...
Timed & Typeset by: Kedomas
Translated by: senor_wristband