"Are their hearts connected?" No Smartphone Meetup!
The Rule: They head to a location using the hint card given to them
The challenge doesn't end until they all meet up
The first hint; A place with a lot of pigeons
However, they ended up seperated
The second hint; A theater
It's gotta be Honda Theater
Hamada headed to Honda Theater ...
... and had a splendid reunion with Endo!
Tonight, let's see if they can all meet up!
Subbed by senor_wristband
Currently, Endo & Hamada are in Shimokitazawa
Hosei's in Shinjiku
And Tanaka is in Shibuya
Matsumoto is a little farther away in Ginza
Time for the next hint!
Here we go. This is the next theme,
A large shoe store?
Eh? Are there really large shoe stores?
Oh, like Shoe Distribution Centre?
I've never bought shoes at a shoe store ...
Where else would you buy them?!
I have a feeling that place would be good,
Wasn't there one near that intersection in Sancha? It might be gone now
Matsumoto-san heads to a shoe store near Sanjengaya
I think it's a pretty big shoe store, considering it's in the city,
Hamada-san, you have some idea?
I don't know the name of it though
A shoe store you can't name?
In Sancha, near that police station and the McDonald's,
Isn't there one there? Like you always see it
I don't know the name though
At the intersection?
Yes yes yes yes
Like a huge one
I'm totally fine with that
Then let's head there
They both head to a shoe store in Sanjengaya, like Matsumoto
I think there are other big shoe stores in the city, but I don't know any of them
Like for example, is there a Nike Shop?
But that's not just a shoe store though
Oh, right
In Harajuku,
The Nike store
Nike store?
It's pretty big, that "Nike Shop" I think it's called
Hamada-san, and Endo, they wear Nike shoes often don't they?
They do... they do
Right?
In fact today, Hamada-san was wearing some Leopard print Nike shoes
Oh yeah
Since those two Nike shoe wearers are together,
it's totally possible they might go "Let's head to that Nike store"
It's possible. In fact, I can't think of anywhere else.
What about ABC Mart?
Oh yeah, ABC Mart is an option
There's also the Shoe Distribution Centre
I think it's near Ikejeri Ohashi
Let's head to [!@!@$!@]
Alright
Hamada, Endo, and Matsumoto have a chance of meeting
Hamada & Endo are the first to arrive
Look, that there,
Oh, HERE?
This is a big one!
What is it called?
Oh Chiyoda, that's right
It even says "Shoes" so clearly
See, there's so many
It's very big
If you look at it from here you can see,
Woah, it's huge!
This is a big store, so huge!
Last time, for the Tsutaya thing, Tanaka definitely walked past here
Yes, he did see it
You know, I want Tanaka to come here
Yes I want him to come
I really do think Hamada-san & Endo will come here
Both groups were thinking of each other,
Tanaka chose the Harajuku Nike Shop
There's a lot of people
I think Hamada-san & Endo will for sure come here
Matsumoto reaches Sanjengaya, where Hamada's group is
That's also pretty big shoe store huh?
That one is really big!
That sign is really big
Hamada and Endo's location
Well still, that's not the point though right?
It's not the one I thought of. The one I thought of is here.
See, that one. Right?
Matsumoto is just one station away from Hamada's group
He chose the Shoe Distribution Centre in Ikejeri Ohashi
It's gotta be here. Look, it's so big
Alright, c'mon come here
Any time now
Alright come on
However, time's up!
Tanaka-kun, where are you?
I, Tanaka, am at Harajuku-
Harajuku?
Yes, the Harajuku Nike Shop
Nike Shop?
That's not a shoe store
Yeah, Tanaka I think you've got the wrong idea
There's so many, there's 150-
Enough already
Limiting it to Nike is wrong,
They make their own shoes!
That is just so irrelevant
Who cares if they make their own shoes
Where is Hosei-san?
I'm in the middle of Centre Gai in Shibuya,
ABC Mart
Matsumoto-san where are you?
Listen ... In Ikejiri Ohashi, Shoe Distribution Centre
No way ... the Centre?!
I should've gone there!
It's the only answer
I should've gone there
Well, we're close, not that far away I mean
Wait wait hold on hold on
Wait, Hamada & Endo, you two,
You guys need to react to my "Shoe Distribution Centre" a bit more
Don't just move on, like"Anyways, we're at..."
Just the flavour, taste it for a second
Very sorry, I didn't taste it
Matsumoto-san you're not that far from us. You're pretty close
Where?
We're at Sangenjaya's ...
Chiyoda
It's called Chiyoda
That place with the "Shoes" sign...
When I was taking a U-Turn there, I said "Woah, that place is pretty big!"
Oh, you did a U-Turn here?
Ah, is that so?
So close
But I never thought of that place though
I just said that when I saw it
Ah I see, I see I see
I didn't think of that place
Tanaka you should've known this place!
I really really wanna smack Tanaka
I want to slap his glasses off
Even if he isn't wearing them
He doesn't wear glasses
This is the only place I could think of
The next one please everyone, let's finish this
This time, they're all close by, which should help their chances
Time for the 4th hint
The next hint,
We should get this one at least
Let's meet everyone
Oooh? A "Gyoza no Osho" location?
But Shozo, this one,
If we consider what everyone might think, there's just that one answer
Isn't this one really hard?
How many branches are there in the city?
There are 66 stores within the city,
However, there's only 4 stores within reach of the members
Furthermore...
Last time, wasn't there that place Matsumoto-san said "Let's eat here!" ?
There was. That happened.
There was right?
It's just there (Shimokitazawa)
This is something that happened on a shoot in Shimokitazawa 3 years ago
Hmm, where was that Gyoza place again?
Let's eat Gyoza
Gyoza ...
They went to this Gyoza no Osho in the middle of the shoot
I think this one is not bad,
If we're all thinking the same way,
That's the only answer
And, it's near Matsumoto-san right?
Yeah it is. He'll already be there
It is close by
There's only one answer to this question,
This is it. This one is definitely it. Let's go
"That one!" - That's what I think, "That one!"
As for any other answers ... I don't know
There's one in Dogenzaka as well
Dunno!
The three groups have a desired location in mind,
Just the hesitant Matsumoto is left
Incidentally, there's one there right?
There is, there is. But, I don't think that's the one
It's gotta be [!)(@!&$] hasn't it?
I think at least one person is bound to go there, right?
Alright, let's go
What "Gyoza no Osho" did he choose?
Tanaka is in Harajuku, which isn't that far
Endo and Hamada aren't that far, they're just behind me
Wait, I think this is the end here
You know,
It's amazing, after 30 years of this,
This "bond" that brings everyone together, we start to understand it
I think there's no doubt we're right
Yeah
Tanaka is the only trouble maker
That's true.  Tanaka ...
After making it this far, I can say Tanaka is the biggest trouble maker
They're at Ikijeri, Sancha, Shibuya ...
So distance wise this is perfect
I wanna meet them
I hate being the last one left
Will they all be able to meet at Shimokitazawa?
Hamada & Endo reach their destination,
They should already be there
I think so
Considering the distance, Matsumoto should have arrived earlier
Just where though?
There's no sense that they're here already
Look, look, look - Eh?
You're joking?
Ah! What if Matsumoto-san got hungry and went inside for Gyoza?
It doesn't seem that way
He's not here...
He isn't here
There's no way ... No way
No way, is this possible?
This is not good, this isn't good
Where did Matsumoto go?
I'm hungry~ Maybe I'll eat Gyoza while I wait
Next, Hosei arrives at his destination
You know, I almost want to run to everyone-
Let's run then?
Oh, shall we? Let us leap into our comrades' chest!
Are you very confident?
I'm just pumping with confidence!
Eh? Is there? Huh?
Somebody! Huh? They're gathered over there!
They've gathered!!
Yama-chan's here!
Exactly! Exactly!
I'm so glad!
It's gotta be here right?
This is the only answer!
This place is closest to Matsumoto-san
Yeah, we thought he'd be here before us
He's not here though
I have a memory here with Matsumoto-san too
You've been before right?
Manager Fujiwara, before he got married,
Him and his wife, they had all these dishes laid out, laughing and eating
And Matsumoto-san and I happened to be there too
Oh, coincidentally?
Coincidentally
We've got that memory here
What a cheap performance!
Cheap ...
But it was amazing though, all that food
Even though it's for 2 people
How could they finish that?
Enough food for 4 people
But this was an easy question though
Eh? We need Matsumoto-san at least to meet us here
Oh, we're so close by
Momentarily, Matsumoto will arrive to his destination,
Alright
I don't know if everyone's here,
But it'll be a great ending if they are
Was Matsumoto heading towards Shimokitazawa?
Then Tanaka also arrives,
I think considering everyone's locations, this is the best choice,
I really want to meet them, for real
They're there!
See, they're there!
I did it!
I told you right? It's gotta be Shimokitazawa
Yeah, if Tanaka didn't come here I would've punched him
Yeah, really,
It's gotta be here right?
Its gotta be here
If you got this wrong I was gonna hit you
There's no doubt
It's hard to think of anywhere else really
And we ate here recently
We came here on a Gaki shoot
Yes
But, Matsumoto-san was the closest, and he's still not here,
In Ikejiri?
It's gotta be here! This is it!
Eh really?
Like, you can't think of anywhere else!
Where did Matsumoto end up?
Matsumoto headed to...
I think Yamasaki is walking to here
Gyoza no Osho - Dogenzaka location
Damn I wanna eat that!
I straight up want Gyoza
No, come on this is the end
Like,
There's no sense of celebrities approaching
I think it had to be here, considering the flow. There is a flow after all
Time's up here!
Just what is this
Matsumoto-san, where are you right now?
It's obvious, it's gotta be the Dogenzaka store
Dogenzaka?
No, no, no
It's, there's one in Dogenzaka,
What a pain in the ass
Fine, where are you?
Well, all four of us have assembled
There's 4 of us here
Seriously?
You're kidding right?
Nah for real
For real
We're all here
Do you remember on that shoot, you said "Let's go get Gyoza .. everyone agree?"
Do you remember that?
Where?
In Shimokitazawa
That's not it!
It IS it
It's totally it
Nobody would think of there
This is the only answer
no no no its gotta be dogenzaka
The distance too. I thought Yamasaki was gonna walk here!
But listen, the answer to "a Gyoza no Osho store?" is Shimokitazawa
And Matsumoto-san, we've all eaten here before
Don't care
You don't care?...
I've never really talked to you
What do you mean we've never talked?
Well whatever there's 4 of us here
You're there by yourself
No no no, think of the flow!
We're here BECAUSE we thought of the flow
Tanaka, you should say something, you've gotten the most complaints
You know, I,
I never thought you were such an incapable person
I'm sorry, I'm very sorry. I'm just startled
I'm capable, i'm capable
I am, I am, I'm actually really capable
Forgive me, Senpai
Alright, that's enough, it's time for the next one
God this is annoying
We're counting on you
I'm definitely not in the wrong here, but whatever
The quantity decides!
Going by quantity, this is it
How many times are we gonna have this argument about quantity?
And now Endo's using words he doesn't understand
I can understand quantity at least
This is the first time Matsumoto's been left by himself
They want to decide this with the next hint
"A place with Tokyo in the name"
This is another hard one!
There's more choices than you'd think
Let's just go with the cliche?
What place is a cliche?
A super cliche place? I think it's the same place
Alright, super cliche
Let's go with super cliche then
Tokyo Tower
Tokyo Station
Tower, tower ...
Station, station
Ah we split up!
I'm sorry, you're right. It's Tokyo Tower
Right?
It's the Tower
Right? It stands out
Let's go to the tower then?
Yeah, the station is out
We're alright then?
I think so
And if he doesn't come, we have to think again
Meanwhile, Matsumoto ...
So difficult!
Let's think while eating Gyoza
What do we do if we don't meet him?
yeah honestly
A troublemaker has been discovered
He certainly has!
If his choice turns out to be dumb
He's changed positions with you
It's been passed down to the next generation
It's gone backwards actually
What did Matsumoto think of while eating Gyoza?
Hold on, Tokyo Station?
Or hold on, Tokyo Tower?
Whatever! Let's go to [@!$!@@$!]
Shall we?
Let's go and see
Did Matsumoto pick Tokyo Station? Or Tokyo Tower?
The 4 head at Tokyo Tower
I guess only Tanaka would understand how Matsumoto feels right now
It feels very tragic,
Like, have I really been left behind by society?
I guess you would right
You'd think "Do I have bad taste?"
This is the first time I've been by myself this long
That's true. It's also very rare.
Those guys are just deviants, there's nothing I can do
It's so frightening being a deviant
He's probably by himself right now, and we'll see this on TV
He's just complaining the whoooole time
Yeah, he probably his
Yeah
Like, complaing the whoooole time
I guess it makes sense,
Making a TV show with morons like them is really tiring
I guess they just have bad intuition. They have no "sense"
I just think, it's really tiring making a show with idiots like that'
Oh yeah, I just remembered
You said that picture of bird shit looked like me
What happened?
Oh yeah, when the "Photos Resembling Hamada" episode aired
I didn't,
I didn't know anything about that
You said "This is Hamada isn't it?"
Everyone found it funny, so I let it go
It was pretty funny after all
Pulling out that picture ...
It was um, it was a mirror image
The 4 reach Tokyo Tower
Considering the distance, Matsumoto would have arrived first
If he isn't here already, that's not right is it?
Eh? No way, he isn't here?
You're joking
If he isn't here already, that's not right is it?
Eh? No way, he isn't here?
He's there!
Oh he's there, thank goodness!
You were alone the whole time!
The whole time!
Piegeons live in Ueno, it's a fact. In Ueno Park
Pigeons!
It should have ended with Gyoza
Yeah with Gyoza
Yes, Shimokitazawa should have been the end
no no no no. No.
No no no
But you felt that regret right?
"AH! Shimokitazawa!"
I was talking with the staff
When you make a show with people who have no "sense", this is how it turns out
Thank god though!
Yes, thank god we met here!
If we couldn't get this one, what could we get?
Even if it was like "Where is Yoshimoto's Headquarters"