Gaki no Tsukai recording day
An usual recording day
But on this day, things will be
settled with a certain character
We just... have to go, I guess
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
I don't think we're wrong this time
Excuse us
As nervousness takes over their faces, they pay a visit to that certain character
Their faces became unusually stiff
The person they'll face...
Shoji Murakami
Is Shoji Murakami
The man in charge of the "class" series
Responsible for countless rating drops
For Shoji, who had a bad influence on this show,
He'll make a remonstrance about how he's going to move on from the show!
The time has come to move on!
So, what's goin' on today?
Well...
Sorry but I...
Cocorico
Yamazaki Housei
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
My hips aren't really ok lately, so...
How are you now?
I'm quite ok by now, I think
Isn't it good?
Oh, thank you
So, err...
About what we originally planned
I mean, about the "class" series you've been doing
We had to skip one episode of it
It's fine, 'cause this was, like,
you know, I mean it's just for once
Sorry but I have no idea what you just said
What was that?
I mean, that was one week ago, right?
- Yeah...
We always made em until they were good
- Yes
But now you're telling me this
Yeah, I'm sorry we had to
cancel it because of my condition
You want me to start a new one now?
'Cause we co%$&"#@!" a class %$£!§ !!
I mean, if we have time
What?
I'm all in for the class series
We have no idea what you're sayin', big bro
Has your articulation always been that bad?
I can't really understand
what he's saying, today
Yeah, I have no idea
So, I'm really sorry, but...
You see...
We tried something about the class series...
We actually had one
Mh?
I mean, your series
We had our own episode of your class series
Without me and just you guys?
No, it's...
We had a different teacher for that
With another teacher?
Yeah...
On the contrary, isn't it good? I mean
I mean, lessons could become more
interesting with another teacher
That's nice, 'cause it----
YOU FUCKING IDIOTS !!
You know there can be only one teacher, right?
I know but...
A teacher does one thing, another does another one,
of course two teachers can't teach the same thing!
Of course we're aware of that
But why don't you at least take a look at what we did...?
Well I guess that...
Not looking at it would been weird
Things will be settled tonight!
The person who will take Shoji Murakami's place
as their new teacher is going to be...
Who will be the one to take over Murakami's place?
Translation & Subtitles by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
facebook.com/shionnotsukai
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Want to support my works? consider donating @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
CLEAR WEATHER
Appointed day of the class series
Weather,
temperature,
humidity level...
aren't they perfect?
It's the best, it feels nice
How is this even possible?
(the times with Shoji)
It was always cold as heck and nothing more
There were times when it rained, even thunders sometimes
Look at this sign, it's so stylish!
It surely is!
note: on the sign: "the ninja class is here"
I'm getting excited for real!
Yeah you're right
Makes me really wanna pay the monthly fee
It's making us wanting to do this
Now we just have to wait for our teacher
- Yes
Ciao
Ciao!
So cool!!
So friggin' cool!
He's even wearing boots!
Looks like I made it in time
How do you like my chest hairs?
The pioneer of wild-look
Girolamo Panzetta
Pioneer of fashion
Girolamo the dandy will be their teacher!
So today, we're here...
We're here to have ourselves a ninja class
Thank you!
Thanks!
You know, there was another one
before me, but wasn't that popular...
pin pon pan pon
Isn't he italian?!
- Yes...................
We're first of all supposed to have fun here
I think that
After all we italians are all friendly
In Italy, the word for "friend" is "amico"
Amigo?   - Amigo...
It's amiCo!
Amico!
Say it again
Yeah! I'll teach you lots of things today
His sunglasses are pretty cool, aren't they?
Are you ready? Shall we start?
Let's do this!
Yeah!!
Training 1
Aim to be a wild-looking cool ninja
The training will begin
By remodeling the old-fashioned ninjas
Sudden change: style change training!
Yeah!!
Sudden Change!
Style
Change
Training
What the f-?
Don't you think the image of
ninjas is outdated by now?
I mean, just black
You're right
We'll try to make it more fashionable
Training: use the fashionable items and make your own wild-looking cool ninja
More fashionable...
You can see lots of items here
This is amazing!
So many fashionable items!
Just pick some of them
And make it cooler
We'll start from Hamada
But ninjas aren't supposed
to be spotted by the enemy
Oh! Hamada    - Hamada-san!
Are we choosing them ourselves?
Next up is Abe-san
I'm Endo by the way
Oh, sorry
It's ok
Amico, right? Amico!
That's amico
That's a weird mistake
ENDO'S CHALLENGE
Endo will be the first challenger
Tokyo Ninja Collection!
Yaaaaay!
So cool!
Amico!
Looking good, Endo!
Pretty cool, right?
As expected from Louis Vuitton sunglasses
Louis Vuitton Sunglasses
Thank you!
Maybe it's a bit too hot today for this
Even this scarf color is amazing
This is so popular
Silk Scarf
This is cool but
It's probably lacking something to be cooler
I don't know much about it
He does look incomplete
A black diamond
Black Diamond Ring
Woah, this raises the bar!
The hell is this!?
It will stand out when throwing shurikens
More than for battle, this is for being popular with girls
I'm giving them all to you
For real?!
- It's ok, leave it to me
Amico!!
Endo receives a (around) 700'000 yen worth set of items!
Hamada too changes into a wild-looking cool ninja
Rayban Sunglasses
The hell is this shit?!
This will make you look badass
Bottega Veneta Gloves
He's not gonna wear them
How is he supposed
to wield that?!
With sunglasses and gloves his style got upgraded
Amico!
Pretty good, huh?
What the fuck!!
These are all presents
Hamada receives a (around) 150'000 yen worth set of items!
THE TEACHER'S EXAMPLE
Lastly, here's the teacher's example
Is that a ninja?
Leather Coat & Belt by
This is just bad
Amico!!
I don't get the
meaning of this!!
As expected by our teacher!
Leave it to me
Amazing!
- Fashionable!
After the ninja are done with their job they go have fun, right?
Listen to me, what's our hobby?
Our hobby?
It's to make good use of women
The hell is he
talkin' about?!
Is he an idiot?!
Amicoooo~
He's cool, right?
- He's amazing
In a way, yeah...
His point is that ninjas are outdated by now
But that's not the issue
Does he even know what "ninja" means?
Besides
Why are you guys like that?!
Acting as if your boss threw a dining party
And he's like "I'll pay your taxi home"
And you're like "Wow, thanks boss!!"
Are you idiots?
To be honest...
Aren't there plenty of dark affairs
Involving you directly, Shoji big bro? Let's talk about those
Like, a lot of stuff
I think he thought the same
As he was talking about it before
Wait a sec
That has nothing to do with the class!
That's true
I'm talking about this class
You're right
Also
My daughter is attending college now, it'd be awful
I see that
If you start talking about that thing,
I think this episode would just end right here
Back on our topic...
Our staff decided to do something about this situation...
And so
And did a sort of street interview
That's right
You know, about the teacher from before (Girolamo)
And you, Shoji-sensei
A sort of comparison
Of course I'm better than him, I mean...
Is it a survey about who's the funniest, right?
To be honest, I don't really know it myself
Shall we take a look?
Gaki No Tsukai Image Survey
Who would you rather sleep with?
Girolamo or Shoji Murakami...
Girolamo Panzetta
Shoji Murakami
Who would you rather sleep with?
Girolamo
Murakami
Girolamo vs Murakami:
Who will you choose?
Gaki no Tsukai image survey
Girolamo
'cause he looks like a man who knows how to treat a woman
Isn't he a "ladies first" type of guy?
Girolamo
Murakami
Girolamo vs Murakami:
Who will you choose?
Gaki no Tsukai image survey
Of course
I'd pick Girolamo
Is there a reason for why
(staff)
You didn't choose Murakami?
He kinda...
It'd be creepy if he would touch me...
Girolamo
I guess
I'd go for Girolamo
Murakami
George
.
(staff)
Is there a reason why?
Let's see...
What does this person do?
Girolamo
Girolamo Panzetta
No way I'm choosing him (Murakami)
(staff) Why is that?
No way! I don't like him
Girolamo
Girolamo is ok
Girolamo Panzetta
What kind of survey was that?
That was something the staff always liked to do, so...
Wait a sec, regardless of that
This is
The "class" series, you know
You're right
I got mad at 'em myself too
And told them like "this is unrelated to it"
"Who would you rather sleep with" - geez!
Also, there was one of them...
what the hell?
I mean, what's the deal
With that old lady?
She wants you     - You were chosen
They found her on the street, we don't know
Isn't it strange it was not a survey about something like
"who would be funnier in a ninja class episode?"
The staff probably got it wrong
A mistake
Yes. Hey, you guys.
What was that?
- That's no good!
Must be that
- It's our staff
Dontcha make this mistake again!
Got it!?
Don't be mad
Also, that was all about...
This whole "wild-looking dude" thing but
But I don't have any qualities like that
Even though back then I used to
Eat and run away without paying or such
But such things are bad!
They're not worth praising!
It's not our fault
you were like this!
Alright, whatever
Let's get over this
- Yes
Is there still some recording left?
Yeah it goes on
Yeah, there is
It's not so long, so, please...
Wiggling Kunoichi Twister Training!
note: kunoichi = female ninja
Wiggling
Kunoichi
Twister
TRAI
NING
So, don't you agree balance is important for a ninja?
Oh yes
But...
Do you like surfing?
I never did it before      - You did not?
Oh don't worry about it, ninjas don't do surf
It was just an italian joke
Amico!!
I've prepared Twister for you
Training: make good use of the Twister game to increase your balancing skills
But it's no fun if only dudes are playing
Here are some cuties!
Come, please
They're beautiful, right?
Kunoichi?
Their partners for Twister
Will be the sexy "Kunoichis from the World"
Their helpers for this training
Will be the sexy "Kunoichis from the World"!
"Kunoichis from the World?!"
MATSUMOTO'S CHALLENGE
Our first challenger will be Matsumoto
Ok, let's start!!
- Let's go
Roulette: Start!
Countin' on ya, Abe-chan
Ok, both of you
Right foot on
red
green
yellow
or blue spots
on the board, please
Right foot, huh      - What?
Abe-chan?
I think I didn't understand the rules
How can you not?!
I'm sorry
- Right foot yellow, right?
He can only
understand baseball
Here?     - Anywhere is fine
As long as it is yellow
Ok, moving on!
Go, Abe-chan
Right hand on blue!
Right hand blue
- Right hand blue?
You should aim to the closer one
Nice
Sorry for this
You've found a nice spot!
The training's toughness increases...
The balance of their bodies is steadily crumbling down...
And finally, a conclusion on the 8th round
Left foot red
Red
Alright, you did it!
MATSUMOTO: VICTORY
What the-?
This was good
Amico!
Following up, Yamazaki performs several tricky balancing techniques
Right foot yellow
YAMAZAKI: VICTORY
What the...
This is the best, isn't it?
It is
Let's move to the next one
Was it?
Yaaa~y!!
So, that was a balance training
Right, balance
A balance training is fine
- Yes
But you didn't even know the rules
I mean, Twister's
- Well that...
Was my first...
- Even those who did it
Balance my ass, you didn't have any
All you showed me was bad balance
We're sorry
It was because of the kunoichi...
Do they have anything to do with this?
Well, they were the Kunoichi from the World, so...
He said it clearly
I didn't really get that thing about surfing
You know, that joke
Girolamo told us...
Where was the joke?
He's such an unfunny old dude!!
I'm 100% sure you would
have made fun of me if I said that
And yet you were all like "yay yay"
Sayin' "amico" and shit
The hell is wrong with you?
So, you know...
Our staff did something for this episode
So it did another street interview, a survey
Or something like that, I don't know I haven't watched it
Of course not about which of you
to have sex with or nonsense like that
Not like that
I think it's different this time
So, shall we...?
Gaki no Tsukai image survey
Tell us your impression on this person
"Tell us your impression about this person"
Girolamo Panzetta
Let's start with Girolamo Panzetta
He's really cool and
He looks like he's really
good at dealing with women, he looks skilled
He seems a honest person
Like the type of person who never lies, kinda
I've seen him before on a cooking show
And he's pretty good at cooking, you know
It made me think how good it would be to have an husband like him
He really gives out this grown-adult image
I think that when I'll grow up I want
To become a refined man just like him
Shoji Murakami
What about Shoji Murakami's image?
I have no idea who this person is
I guess his image...
Is in the category of
"people I don't like or dislike"
He doesn't seem to be a knowledgeable guy
Whenever I see this guy on tv, I always change channel
He's the guy who does "doooing!"
note: a gag by Murakami
(staff)
Do you get any other image from him?
Mmhh...
"Doooing!"
I have no idea what this guy does because I've
never seen him before
His face kinda...
I've never seen him before, so I have no idea
(staff)
You really don't know him?
No, I don't
I think he focus his comedy on unfunny stuff
To be honest, I don't like him nor hate him
It's more of a "I don't care" for me
Bring those people here
What's with this "image" thing?
That's right, we're not dealing with this
Girolamo Panzetta
- kind to women
- honest
- fashionable
- good at cooking
- "I want to be like him"
Murakami Shoji
- "Never seen him before"
- Not knowledgeable
- "I change channel"
- "Doooing"
- "Who cares"
What's that?
Hey, what's this?!
This is new
Bad staff
I wonder if this stuff is going to be broadcasted on tv
Maybe it won't air, who cares, but there were
People sayin' "I don't care" talking about me
I mean, they even said "I never saw him before"
I think we're now about to look at the last VTR
for today's episode
Ninja class:
final act
Yes, it's our last one
Take a look, please
"Buono buono" training!
Yeeeeah!
BUONO BUONO TRAINING
Buono buono!
Buono?
Buono, it means "good"
Buono
And so
The image of a ninja
Is something really though, isn't it?
I mean, you have to endure even your hunger
Right
Let's get rid of this image
Training: satisfy your hunger by eating something delicious
Let's bring you something tasty, here
Today for all of you guys
Yes?
I've brought you a delicious pizza
Really?
But first, a quiz
What type of pizza is inside?
Girolamo's Quiz
Q. Try to guess which type of pizza is inside the tray
Woah... I really have no idea
Tanaka, give it a try
Maybe anchovies...
Anchovies
are stinky, aren't they?
If you eat them, then you can't kiss anyone, right?
Must be something easier
It's something lighter
How was that popular one called?
Margheri...?
Margherita!!
Urrà!!
note: italian for "hooray"
You got it in one guess!
I'm impressed
CORRECT ANSWER
That's what you say for guessing it right?
As expected from ninjas
CORRECT ANSWER
This has nothing
to do with ninjas
I'm impressed, as expected from ninjas!
It looks delicious
Feel free to dig in!
Can we eat it?!
Of course, of course
That's just... eating
We never were offered anything to eat before, I mean...
Tasty, right?
In our previous classes
Not even once
Those were just so shitty
So good!
Buo~no~!!
You know, I had a friend come from Italy to make this
You can tell, it's nothing like our
delivery pizza, this is buono!!
The "Kunoichis" join them for the training's gran finale
Remember the cuties from before?
Let's make em join our group!
Bambina!! (baby)
Bambina~
The hell is this?!
This is too much, I mean
Our previous teacher was pure shit!!
Yeah I think so too
This is really good!
We never got to see this
type of ninja before, right?
Eat, eat, that's passion
So, how was it today? Did you have fun?
We had fun!
It was the best!
I had fun too, let's do this again one day
Yeah, let's do this again
Thank you guys!
Our previous teacher is a turd, isn't him?
Amico~!
Sorry for my late introduction,
my name is turd
The hell is that supposed to be, you morons?!
We all said that...
You think you can call
me that because of this?
Why should ninjas do that?
I mean havin' a banquet for no absolute reason?!
That's not the way you praise a ninja
You'll just spoil him this way
Ok, you could have been
enjoying the moment, I see that
But calling me "shitty teacher" or "turd"...
Yes...
Let it down
Let that panel down
So...
What do you think about it?
I think this class had a different feeling from the others
It felt like something new
See, I know by seeing you that you had fun
Cause you were part of it
So you had fun and everything, but what about
Our audience made of
big fans of my class series?
I mean, even the big ones from Lumine or Gap
They'd be like "Where's the class series?!
I'm about to go crazy!"
Don't laugh at me, it's true
They'd be like "What the hell is going on?!"
They would be like that?
It's true, I have to say them "just wait"
"It's cause Macchan is like that, he told me"
You know, that thing...
'Cause your crotch got weird lately
So I'm like "his crotch got weird, you have to wait"
Is that so? I see
Leaving that aside
Why did you take part on such thing, I mean
My intention was to train you, not to loiter around
Yes...
That was total crap
Anyway, I still think that
You took good care of us in all the previous classes, big bro
I mean, we can't just deny that
So, in order, starting from Cocorico, we...
Some presents...
You took care of us all the time
So I want you give you this
'Cause Tanaka loves animals
note: "children picture book: bizarre & surprising animals"
He really loves em
It's extensive
What's going on..?
Next up, Endo
- Yes
Those are coupons for gyoza
We got them for a Gaki shoot
We got quite a lot of em
That's a lot
- It is
You like em
- I do
You're not giving all of them?
Yes, those are enough
The members give their farewell gifts according to their tastes
Each of them gives him gifts full of memories
It's an headcover
That's nice
These are popular
I'm giving you this ticket case
You can use it for passes
Useful
Passes or Suica
Thank you for everything
Thanks for this long time
Are you idiots!?
Let's go
Hey!
Wait a second
Hey
Thanks for everything
"Thanks for everything" my ass!
Wait!
What was that?
Endo!!
Translation & Subtitles by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
Thanks for everything
Wait---
- Thank you
Ha--- Hama--- Hama-chan? Macchan!
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
www.facebook.com/shionnotsukai
Can I just take my lunch and leave?
Want to support my translations? Consider donating @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
Wait
I'm not
quitting this yet!
That was very Yama-chan of him
You're right
Who is him, Yamazaki?
I thought so too
find more Gaki episodes on www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com