First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende
Hollywood Zakoshisho Shichi Henge!
Here it comes again
Although Hamada is not into it at all
You are the one who said that
Oh, is it?
But we've had it up to here
It's been 8 months since the last challenger Tamura Kenji
The 45th challenger after Tamura Kenji
And I think this challenger and Tamuken
Are Douki (debuted at the same time), right?
What about Cocorico?
We count as Douki
And Yamasaki is junior, right?
No, I'm not
I'm the senpai.
Let's welcome today's protagonist, Hollywood Zakoshisyoh
Thanks for having me
You don't like this kind of gag?
When Hamada-san doesn't know how to entangle with you, he will not entangle with you at all
It was only until recently that he started to entangle with Lytton Chousadan
Oh, I see, I see, no wonder why
What do you mean "no wonder why", dude
Because I am Lytton-ish too
Which position are you aiming for?
Your name will be smaller if you don't get a high rank
Well, for me, it's probably either here or there
It must be one of these two, here or there
Dude, it's cunning to say that
Even if I try to put in a Tsukommi
I feel I like I'm going to bomb too
And if I ignore it
"Huh? Matsumoto can't handle this?"
That's not what I meant, that's not
Well, so you just have to aim high
Many of my colleagues are here too, so
I want to at least win Kenkoba and Tamuken
Tamuken's ranking is quite low, huh?
Why did you quit Yoshimoto, when there's so many Douki?
Well, actually, when Yoshimoto closed down Nichome Theater
They said to me "you are fired too"
So, as usual, what should we do for the next episode?
Let's decide the theme
I wonder what does the first line means?
Here comes Spring! Let's look for Matsumoto's favourite tank top!!
The tank top that suits you best
They are definitely making fun of you
Okay, well, I see
So I became someone that they can make fun of, huh?
It's not a bad thing to become a broad-minded person though
It's a good thing, honestly, it's a good thing
We should aim to be like Sakata-shisho, right?***
*Sakata-shisho's nickname is "Sakata the idiot"
Even the juniors can make fun of him
He's the god of Owarai, Sakata-shisho
Hamada should be like him too
So our duo can become double Sakata
It's incredible to have double idiots, right?
It's so much fun to have a after-party, right? So much fun
It's really nice to have these parties after doing live performances, it's just so much fun
Huh? What?
The party is ending? Eh?
It's ending already?
I just arrived!
And it's ending already? Come on, what do you mean it's ending?
3,000 yen? Eh? 3,000 yen?
I need to pay 3,000 yen?
I was here for 30 minutes only, and I need to pay 3,000 yen?
That's so expensive, isn't it?
I'll pay it
I didn't say I won't pay it
I didn't say I won't pay it, I'll pay it
I'll pay it
I didn't say I won't pay it
All I said was it's so expensive to pay 3,000 yen for 30 minutes
Expens...but I'll freaking pay it
I'll pay it
It's so expensive to pay 3,000 yen for 30 minutes, isn't it?
After-par...but I'll freaking pay it
I'll pay it...30 minu...I'll pay it
It's so expensive to pay 3,000 yen for 30 minutes
I'll freaking pay it
3,000 yen for 30 minutes is definitely...
I'll pay it, I'll pay it, I'll pay it
I'll freaking pay it
3,000 yen is just...
Expens...but I'll freaking pay it
I'll pay it, I'll pay it, I'll freaking pay it
That was an amazing voice he had.
The volume of his voice is amazing
What the heck is going on with that voice volume
Hey, no, no, no, Matsumoto-san
Don't try to muddle through
Well, yeah, I laughed
But, well, he's really persistent
He almost got me when he came back and took a seat
"The anger of our Tanaka! Storm in Shukan Bunshun (news magazine)!!"
Hahh...I really dislike it...hahh...
Recently...you know...recently...
At places like Shibuya...
Those young people...
Always wear their pants below the waist, right? They call that sagging or something?
That's really pissing me off, you understand me?
After all, if you are a man, you should wear your pants...
Above the waist!!!
After all...
If you are a man, you should wear your pants...
Above the waist!!!
After all, if you are a man
You should wear your pants...above the waist!!!
After all...after all...
Just leave, dude
That guy is so persistent!
Tanaka, you (laughed) so quickly!
He's going all out for each of his gags
There's still 5 more to go, can he make it?
Sorry for keeping you waiting
We shall start the 60 minutes one-point match
The red corner, 210 pounds
Tigerrrrrrr Maskkkkkkk!!!
He's pissing me off
He's seriously pissing me off
What are you even doing?
That's enough already.
That's enough, honestly, that's enough
This is a waste of time
What the heck? He's doing nothing
What the hell's up with that guy?
He did absolutely nothing, but it got many of us, huh?
He's just behaving like a XXXXX
He won't leave until you pay up, that's what he's trying to do
He'll go round and round until you pay up
What's this about Hamada-san?
The journey to meet Hamada's favorite omelette rice!!
To meet his favorite omelette rice
Why omelette rice?
Because they think Hamada-san likes it, right?
But I'm not really that into omelette rice though
He likes ketchup
Oh, really? You like tomatoes?
But he hates tomatoes
I hate tomatoes, but ketchup is good...
We've been working together for so long
And yet you know nothing about Hamada
Did you guys even know he likes ketchup?
Yes, we know that
No way, you must be lying!
All you know is (that he likes) Yakisoba!!
You're so mean
He can even eat a mini car with ketchup on it
Why the heck, dude!
♫Bakufu Slump
Runner♫
Is that it?
*The singer of this song, Sunplaza Nakano-kun, is known for his trademark bald head, suit style and especially dark sunglasses
That's enough
That's it. Matsumoto-san.
Well yeah, I somehow laughed
He's always moving
I wonder if he can stick it out
Here it is.
Hello everybody, hello
I'm sorry for being remiss in not introducing myself
My name is...
Huruhata (Ninzaburo)
*Furuhata Ninzaburo is a police detective drama, and was one of the most popular television dramas in the history of Japanese television
I heard that an incident has happened, so please allow me some time to investigate
-Huruhata speaks in a halting, mumbling tone and hums while thinking.
-Huruhata has odd "tics", like poking his forehead with his forefinger when thinking.
-Huruhata always thinks aloud in a distracted, stream of consciousness manner.
I know that feeling*
*Huruhata always say "I know that feeling" to suspects
I know that feeling
SAFE
It's unbelievable that he bombed out on his most famous gag
One of his most well-known gags
Endo Chiaki...........
Endo vs Chiaki's remarriage partner! Head-to-head Sumo battle!!
You two remarried almost at the same time
Well, yeah, within just half a year
And they ask you to...
Endo vs Chiaki's remarriage partner! Head-to-head Sumo battle!!
Do a Nipple Sumo
Not a nipple sumo, the word nipple never appeared
All it said is head-to-head sumo, not nipple
♫Mr.Children
Shirushi♫
I am...
Sakurai from Mr.Children
Sorry, sorry, please excuse me
I'm Sakurai from Mr.Children
Sorry, I'm sorry, I'm a bit too excited
I'm just so happy to see so many people here today
Let's take a look from this side first
A beautiful girl here
And here's another beautiful girl
And then...skip this person
But remember to skip that person
That's all from me, Sakurai
Last one.
This is Zakoshisho...
At his best
And it didn't take long
Yeah, it didn't
For him to prepare
He's coming out immediately
That kind of person could actually be very earnest in real life
"I can't let them wait, that's impolite"
Are you guys still doing it?
Well, well, it's about time
It's about time to take a bath
I just want to take a bath here, please excuse me
Please let me take bath here
I need get changed before taking a bath
I'm really sensitive to the cold
Okay, okay, I'm going to take a bath now
AHHHHHHH HOT HOT HOT HOT HOT
It's too hot, dude
It's too hot
I'll have a Kanpu Masatsu (rubdown with a rough towel) instead
The temperature should be just right now
Arghh...arghhh...too hot...
Kanpu Masatsu again, I need a Kanpu Masatsu again
Arghh...I'm so tired
ARGHHHH...SO HOT...
Ah...starting to feel good
What was up with that face?
His face look different
Good work
I laughed for 6 times
Really? Really?
The only one that I didn't laugh was...
Your most well-known gag, Huruhata
I did that for the audience
Do it just in case
No one was laughing when I'm performing, so I was actually terrified
But well, that was quite a lot
27,000 yen (about $270)
Tied with Waraimeshi Nishda (episode #945)
and Kimura Yuichi (episode #597).
It's a tie for 29th place.
You won Tamura (Kenji)
That Sakurai one was quite interesting, but no one else laughed...
Oh, really?
I laughed too, that got me
That's definitely not how Sakurai will behave like, right?
That's the Sakurai-san when he's talking nonsense like me