Translation & typeset by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
- more episodes @ shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
- like my page: fb.com/shionnotsukai
Show your support by donating on ko-fi:
ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
Second time on Gaki no Tsukai
downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
How far can we go with Cold Noodles?
HIYASHI-CHUUKA
Let's find out the limits of "Hiyashi-chuuka"!
Thank you
Have I seen this setting before?
Yes
We did this before
"Second time", right?
This time is different, it's more complicated
How?
Last time we only did "ice coffee", remember?
Today we're doing "hiyashi-chuuka"
See?
Not so different...
Last time, they tried to order an ice coffee by saying
words such as "ice mohi" or "Ouyang Fifi"
I'll have an Ouyang Fifi
Excuse me?
Oh, an Ouyang Fifi, please
An Ouyang ice coffee
Ice--?
Ice coffee, right?
You said it
And today, they'll research the limits of hiyashi-chuuka
COLD NOODLES
Translation & typeset by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
more subbed episodes @ shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
like my fb page: fb.com/shionnotsukai
Do you enjoy my translations?
consider making a small donation:
ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
@ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
So, let's take a quick look at it
Our first one is
Miyashi-chuuka
"MIYASHI NOODLES"
This shouldn't cause many problems
It's our first one
Third one:
"Higashi ni-chuu ka"
"CENTRAL-EAST No.2?"
- It's already too much
Why you think so?
Here's our fourth one
"Chuuka hiyashi-hiyashi". This one is...
"NOODLES COLDY-COLDY"
This is... listen to me, ok?
If this option was one of Ultraman's brother, it would be Ultra 7
I mean, it's different from the others
But I personally wanted to make it happen anyway
Sixth one:
"Hikkoshi shiyouka"
"SHALL WE MOVE AWAY?"
No way this one can do it
This is where it gets hard
Number seven:
"Oyaji chau ka"
"I'M NOT A DAD"
Let's just cut this one out
Here's number eight:
"He get sea Check car"
"???"
It's nonsense, right?
Yeah I just took random words with similar sounds
It's just a list
And our last one:
"Nenchuu mukyuu ka"
"NO HOLIDAYS THIS YEAR?"
And that's how we're doing this
We told you the same last time
But the trick is the way you say it
This time I tried to say them just like "hiyashi chuuka"
Like mumbling
Last time you said them way too clearly
- Yeah, I know
Did they scold you?
- The staff? Yeah
Aren't you a bit old to be scolded?
How far can "hiyashi-chuuka" go?
Yamazaki Hosei
investigation reporter
I'm going to check that out
Hiyashi Chuuka's Limits
COLD NOODLES
~study results~
Miyashi-Chuuka
"Miyashi Noodles"
I'll have ramen
- One ramen, ok
I'll have...
Miyashi-chuuka
"MIYASHI NOODLES"
Hiyashi-chuuka, got it
"COLD NOODLES"
Here they are, my Miyashi-chuuka
"MIYASHI NOODLES"
No problems at all  - Easy
O Miyashi Chuuka
"Miyashi Noodles"
Higashi Nichuu Ka
"Central-east No.2?"
I'll have higashi nichuu ka
"CENTRAL-EAST No.2?"
Hiyashi?
Higashi nichuu ka
"CENTRAL-EAST No.2?"
Higashi nichuu ka? Sorry I'm asking...
Which is it?
He's stuck in a loop
Higashi nichuu ka
"CENTRAL-EAST No.2?"
Oh, you meant cold noodles
He got through it somehow
- Yeah, kind of...!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
O Higashi Nichuu Ka
"Central-east No.2?"
"Noodles Coldy-Coldy"
Chuuka Hiyashi Hiyashi
Alright, I'll have some chuuka hiyashi-hiyashi
"NOODLES COLDY-COLDY"
Oh, hiyashi-chuuka, got it
"COLD NOODLES"
Why should they have that?!
O Chuuka Hiyashi-Hiyashi
"Noodles Coldy-coldy"
Oh, you got that
Yeah, it was quick
"Shall we move away?"
Hikkoshi Shiyou Ka
Alright, uh...
That's not enough, right?
One hikkoshi shiyou ka
"SHALL WE MOVE AWAY?"
Didn't catch that
She has no idea
Hm? What is it?
You only had gyoza, right? One more serve of this
Plus...
A bowl of hikkoshi shiyou ka
"SHALL WE MOVE AWAY?"
What is that?
They still don't know
what you said
They're just ignoring you
I'm sorry, sir, I didn't catch that
I'll have one hikkoshi shiyou ka
"SHALL WE MOVE AWAY?"
You're saying it too clearly
One hikkoshi shiyou ka, please
"SHALL WE MOVE AWAY?"
Heard that? Too clear
You're moving away? Where?
They're having a good time
X Hikkoshi Shiyou Ka
"Shall we move away?"
Oyaji Chau Ka
"I'm not a dad"
Excuse me!
Coming
I'll have...
Let's see...
Oyaji chau ka
"I'M NOT A DAD"
What's that?
Her face is scary!
Hiyashi-chuuka
"COLD NOODLES"
Hiyashi-chuuka?
Alright,
coming up
You said it normally
One hiyashi-chuuka
Yamazaki ordered it normally
I got stuck, it didn't sound natural to me
X Oyaji Chau Ka
"I'm not a dad"
I think I'll have...
"He get sea check car"
Eh?
What?
Come again?
Don't know that, what is it?
Wait
Yamazaki doesn't really know what to do
Man, it's so hot in here
Oh boy
I get what he's doing
By saying it's hot, he's implying cold noodles
Sorry for that
Would you please say it in japanese?
Sure
"Sure", he said
"No holidays this year?"
Nenjuu Mukyuu Ka
I'll have a nenjuu mukyuu ka
"NO HOLIDAYS THIS YEAR?"
No holidays all year...?
Nenjuu mukyuu ka
"NO HOLIDAYS THIS YEAR?"
Are you asking me when are we closed?
We're closed on weekends
Nenjuu mukyuu ka
"NO HOLIDAYS THIS YEAR?"
What a bad situation...
May I suggest you our tantan noodles? They're very good
Ok
He went for tantan
As suggested by the waiter
Yamazaki ends up getting his order chosen by the waiter
He said "yes" too
X Nenjuu Mukyuu Ka
"No holidays this year?"
Why did you say "yes", dude?
Non-aired ones:
2 - Miyashi Jouka (MIyashi Purge): 〇
5 - Hiyashi Chocopa (Cold Chocolate): 〇
As you can see, it starts with lots of circles but then it's all crosses
It means they were perfectly ordered
Man, I'm so good at explaining stuff
And so, for our grand finale
Let's push hiyashi chuuka's limit to this:
COLD NOODLES
Suzuki Kyoka
(japanese actress)
That's our arrival point
This won't work
I don't know that... I mean, we had "Ouyan Fifi" for "Ice Coffee"...
And to be honest
It was kind of forced
But this one...
I think this one can do the job
You think so?
I think it can, yeah
Alright, it's time to disguise
▀
Will they be able to order hiyashi-
chuuka by saying "Suzuki Kyoka"?
Again?
Can't be helped, we're doing it
You'll end up crying again
Not today, I swear I won't cry today
What kind of disguise is that?
Flawless, isn't it?
Downtown enter the shop with a flawless disguise
How is it flawless? It barely works
Here we go again
Let's just do this
What are we taking?
Excuse me
Coming
Here
Is this the menù?
- Yes
I'll have...
Suzuki Kyoka
Sui...?
Sui gyoza? You meant that?
STEAMED DUMPLINGS
Suzuki Kyoka
Sui-kyou-ka...?
Four of those
You said sui-kyou-ka, right?
Suzuki Kyoka
You meant sui-gyouza, right? Or not?
STEAMED DUMPLINGS
Ok, sui-gyouza
"STEAMED DUMPLINGS"
You straight up ordered dumplings!
Come on, man!
What do you want for real?
Ok, what I really want...
Is chuuka-hiyashi-hiyashi
"NOODLES COLDY-COLDY"
Cold noodles? You sure?
Give me a break!
You two are incredible
What's this about?
I'm gonna talk about this on 4chan, you know!
We got exposed
He easily figured out they were
actually Downtown, despite of their flawless disguise
Cold noodles, one serve
What the hell, dude?
Chuuka hiyashi-hiyashi...
"NOODLES COLDY-COLDY"
X Suzuki Kyoka
I see, I made a mistake
What?
I didn't consider there was "sui-gyoza" on the menù
"STEAMED DUMPLINGS"
Even so, there's no way "Suzuki Kyoka" would ever work
Yeah but... we also know that chuuka hiyashi-hiyashi perfectly works
"NOODLES COLDY-COLDY"
Satisfied now?
Can I...?
Oh, sure
Downtown got a sign request by an employee
Here
Translation & typeset by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
Thank you so much
- It's nothing
You suck, man
more episodes @ shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Let's finish this with a sign
- Yeah...
like my page: fb.com/shionnotsukai
Here
Thank you very much
Show your support by donating on ko-fi:
ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
Thank you!
I hate this
Turn that off
He's crying again