First ever Gaki No Tsukai Chiki Chiki
100,000 yen prize Kushikatsu Tanaka marathon
Tokyo 23 wards - 23 stores competition!
Didn't understand a word you said
C'mon, I said it very clearly
This is the 6th eating marathon
The 6th?
Last time we did Ikinari Steak
And at the 14th store out of 37,
Unfortunately Hamada-san...
In a nutshell, this is a segment where we get mad at Hamada
A national chain restaurant where you can eat Osaka specialty Kushikatsu at the table
TN: Kushikatsu is deep fried meat and vegetables on a skewer
Kushikatsu Tanaka!
The rules: From a menu of 34 items, each person has to eat 2 skewers
From Tokyo's 23 wards
they will visit a chain in each one, aiming to complete 23 stores
We're counting on you, seriously, till the end
No listen, last time I gave up cause I was thinking of you guys
I want to hear the details, what do you mean?
Matsumoto's face just looked so fed up
Who cares what our faces looked like, right?
I thought "I should stop this right here"
I was reading the room
You care this much for your partner?!
A prize of 100,000 yen if they complete all 23 stores
But the challenge ends if one person gives up
And whoever gives up, has to pay for all the food eaten thus far
Will they be able to finish?
Subbed by /u/senor_wristband
Everyone, before we head to the first store,
You will draw cards to see what Kushikatsu you will eat
Wait, we don't pick?!
Yes that's right
What?
From the line up-
I can't eat the oysters
Oysters?
It's fried, so you'll be fine
The raw ones are no good for you, right?
The fried ones are no good either, umm, my doctor told me
Your doctor?
Hold on, what did you say?
I can't eat oyster either
I can't either
So what if you two get oyster?
Cause somebody's gotta eat it
Someone needs to eat it,
So we need to keep that in mind
If Housei or Tanaka gets Oyster, they'll exchange with one of the other three members
Deciding the first store's menu
Starting from Hamada-san
Huge, kinda
Chicken Wing
So big
Chicken wings huh
That, and ... Cheese
Oh Cheese!
Seems pretty easy
How big are they?
I've heard the wings are pretty large
Oh really?
Seriously?
So Housei-san?
Mine is, wah
Kushikatsu, and ...
Banana
That's very nice
You can eat that right?
Bananana already?
So the dessert is the main
Yeah
Matsumoto-san?
I got, these are good
Asparagus
Asparagus is good, yeah?
But the yam...
That's no good
A risky one
So Asparagus and Yamaimo
Then Endo got Pork Shiso and Clam,
And Tanka got Shishito pepper and Ginan (Ginko Seed)
Wait so you can't eat fried Oyster?
Oysters are just, no good
Oysters are no good right?
The taste of oyster ...
You don't like it
I got sick once
But it wasn't fried oyster right that got you
It was a raw one right?
It was raw
Right
Yeah and this is fried
Yeah but still ... it's scary
That sort of thing
That sort of thing getting you scared is unacceptable
But it really sucks when you get sick
I've gotten sick too, so many times
That was raw
No way
It's true
I think oysters have gotten me sick the most
How many times?
Like 7 - 8 times seriously
That means you're a goddamn moron!
They were raw though
Seriously, getting sick that many times and still eating it.
That pisses you off right?
Who would get pissed off?
Right?
What's with you today, you're so abrasive
Right? He sort of is
Being so abrasive
Cut it out
The first location, in Kagurazaka
So you'll get the two skewers from your cards
Got it
Yup
Since you're all from Kansai region you might probably know this,
Double dipping is not allowed,
Of course, of course
Second dip use the cabbage to get sauce
Yeah
We all knew that I guess
There's also a side menu
So whoever wants something can pay for it
Who the hell would order something
But first-
Excuse me
This is Asparagus, Yam, Clam,
Pork Shiko, and Chicken Wing
This here is Bandana, Ginaan,
Cheese, and Shishito
So you can have the Asparagus with sauce or mayo,
For the Banaan, if you like,
you can enjoy it with this chocolate sauce
Okie Dokie
And this?
And that?
Pork
So soon, Hamada-san
It's good
It's not as big as you guys think
You can go for it?
Itadakimasu
Curry sauce would be good too
It's tasty
Sauce is tasty too
Tashty, tashty
It's kind of annoying we can't dip the Asparagus twice
This from one dip, right?
The asparagus is big
The size
I can dig into this
You can dig in yeah
Absolutely
Wouldn't Babana taste better with chocolate sauce?
Should I be using it?
It's up to you,
Maybe just try it
I'll try as is
How is it?
Oh, it's tasty
I can totally eat this
Without chocolate?
It's already sweet
You gobbled that up
Tanaka-san is quick
Easy, this is easy
The other members finish one after another
Hamda-san is done too
Eh, the sauce, on the Banana?
Hold on
Not the chocolate?
It's sweet, too sweet
The banana
Is it sweet?
Does it go together?
It really doesn't
In the end it tastes bad
In the end
Excuse me, I'm done
Alright
The first store is cleared!
It was easy huh?
Piece of cake
Finished before they realised, on to the next store
Deciding the menu before heading over,
Eggplant
Banana
Shrimp
Tsukune (Chicken)
Tomato
Monaka (Mochi Wafer)
Asparagus
Nitamago (Ramen Egg)
Everyone but Tanaka got the following
Tanaka's menu?
Pollock roe, and ... oyster
Pollock Roe?
Oyster!
How do we deal with this
No helping it
If Hamada-san has one he wants to swap,
I will swap one also
I'll swap the Banana with you
So Hamada-san is swapping Banana, Matsumoto-san?
The Tsukune
I want to swap the asparagus
Asparagus?
...yes
Why
Downtown-san, both of them...
Why did you two react like that
I don't understand a man who would trade asparagus
You made Downtown-san go "WHAT?!" so loudly
Tanaka what will you do?
I will, after all, sorry, ummmm
I'll go for the asparagus
So Endo-san has egg and oyster
I will take his oyster
You've really helped me out
The 2nd store, the Edogawabashi location
They're ready
That was quick
Brilliant
That looks big
Hmm?
So this is Eggplant, Banana, Shrimp, Tsukune, and Tomato
Those two are huge
You're right
Really big portions
The size of the Eggplant and Banana...
You greedy bastard
Hamada-san has a lot
The Banana and Eggplant aside, comparing everything to a wiener, everything is a large size
Finishing just one will be quite a task on its own
Eggplant
Matsumoto-san has good ones
I can dig into this easily
The pollock roe is a small portion
How is it?
It's good ... huge though
It is tasty though
So hot
Tasty
The Monaka?
Straight up delicious
Totally
So good
It's good?
It's so good
No sauce or anything
It's good by itself
How's the ramen egg, Endo-san?
Tasty, it's tasty
You're shoveling that down
It is pretty heavy though
I can't handle this
He means cause it's so tasty
Half the Banana would be good
But still, it seems like everyone is really digging in
This guy is so slow
The guy with the Banana will definitely take the longest time
Like Hosei-san earlier
It's pretty hot inside
The eggplant is hot too right?
Yeah exactly
He's finished!
Deciding the menu for the third store,
Endo-san?
Tsukune, and ...
something something Dengaku
TN: Namafu seems to be like a wheat gluten mochi
It's Namafu, you can't read it?
It's Namafu Dengaku
What, you're joking
You can see what it says right away
... something something Dengaku
I've never learned these words
Tomato                 Monaka
Hanpen                  Shitake
Lotus Root                  Mochi
Namafu Dengaku               Tsukune
Ham Cutlet                     Quail
This is what the other members got,
This time the sizes are easier to eat
But you've had Namafu before though?
I haven't
.... I've never eaten it before
You definitley have
Even if you haven't eaten it before,
you should have at least read those words before
It's a different problem
The next store is the Suidobashi location
Thank you
The Namafu has sweet miso on it, please try it as it is
This is hot too
Shitake
It's hot?
But still...
Tasty, the Ham Cutlets are good
Ham Cutlets look delicious
Endo-san
Endo-san, the Namafu
This is Namafu
This is?
Without dipping in sauce right?
I think you would've eaten this before
You've seen it before right?
No it's my first time seeing this
There are no people like you Endo
How is it?
Oh, it's good
Eaten it before?
Nah I haven't
What, really?
My first time
Seriously?
The 5 are merrily finishing their kushikatsu
I can totally dig into this
Mochi
They're still commenting that this challenge is easy
Time for the next menu
Hamada got Spring Onion and Onion
Shitake
Ham Cutlet
Yamaimo (Yam)
Asparagus
Matsumoto got Mochi and Namafu Dengaku
And Tanaka's items?
Osaka Specialty, Beni Shoga
TN: Pickled Ginger Root
It appeared!
Finally!
Osaka specialty, and ...
... Oyster!
There's the Oyster
You keep on getting that
Does anyone want to swap with my Oyster?
For the Mochi, absolutley,
Oh for the Mochi?
Mochi is uh.......
The worst,
This guy is the worst
You're turning me down?!
It's up to him
The Ham Cutlet!
Ah Endo-san's
Again?
In the end, Tanaka switches his Oyster with Endo's Ham Cutlet
I'm not sure we've solved the Oyster problem
Yeah the rules...
Let's decide on something then?
Ah! I got it!
Just pull two cards
2 cards 1 person?
I mean like ... an alternative to the Oyster
If those two get Oyster, they will eat 3 items
Ahhh 2 cards for that
So 3 items in total
3 items
Let's do that, it's the best solution
Take another card then!
I see
No no no, that's-
That rule is for next time
There's plenty of time before we arrive there, like 20 minutes
That much time?
Ok then take another card
The odds are amazing here
If you get the same thing again
You'll go from 3 items to 4
Wiener!
What's with that triumphant tone?!
"WIENER!!  :^D"
Like, like he won a prize or something
It's like, his triumph over the villains at the end of the story
Like we're super evil guys or something
"WEENAH! 8^D"
"WEEENAH!! ~(˘A˘~)"
It's not like that at all
He exclaimed "WIENER!" didn't he?
It's not like that
Like he won
So Tanaka will have Beni Shoga, Ham Cutlet, and Wiener to finish
The 4th store in Arakawa Ward, the Nishinippori location
Tanaka-san if you will,
He gets it separately
3, for the first time
Three, three huh
Cause you kept going on about the Oyster,
This is like God's wrath
I don't think this is God's wrath
But still this is ...
Beni Shoga
Hamada-san's is huge huh?
Right?
Beni Shoga is delicious!
Yeah Beni Shoga is good
Beni Shoga is nice yeah
That looks tasty
I can totally dig in
You can go for it?
This is really good, the Namafu
Ah it's not what I expected
Ah, it's not?
You're kinda slow aren't you?
No I can eat it, but
But the portion is kinda big
Ah, what is that?
Yamaimo
Yamaimo?
The Onion is huge huh?
Big portion sizes, but they still gorfle it down lickity split
That looked easy for you Hamada-san
Yeah I guess
Then they decide the 5th menu,
Shishito                                       Ginnan
Chicken Wing                                  Wiener
Hanpen                                       Liver Cutlet
Monaka                                       Oyster
Spring Onion                        Namafu Dengaku
Tanaka got Spring Onion, will he be okay with the size?
So Tanaka? Are you full after eating 3?
No I'm still fine
How full are you?
How are you? Still easy right?
I'm still, totally fine
Totally fine
But last time, what was it,
At Ikininari Steak you were already full, right?
By the 4th store
Yes, yes
You were already done by the 4th store?
By the 3rd store
Really?
That soon?
I was on the edge
On the edge?
Kushikatsu Tanaka Marathon; 5th store in Taito Ward, Asakusabashi location
Chilly
Yeah
Okay!
Shall we play some Chinchirorin? (Cee-lo)
Let's do it!
Chinchirorin!
Kushikatsu Tanaka attraction; Chinchirorin High Ball!
If you roll doubles, you get one highball!
An even roll gets you half price
An odd roll gets you a double size Mega Jug!
Matsumoto will play this game
What outcome will show off my talent power?
Doubles
Doubles of course
Doubles,
If I get two 1's that'll show my talent power
Observe
Here I go
Seriously
two 1's
Two 1's would be amazing
Hold on, I can hear some yawning
Yawning?
Just when I'm about to display my talent power,
My partner is yawning off to the side?
This is diminishing my talent power for sure
No you'll be fine
Here I go, for real
Six and Five - That's an odd roll
A Mega Jug!
Okay! Talent Power!
There it is
I got an interesting outcome!
So interesting.....
Before the Mega Jug highball, it's time for Kushikatsu
This spring onion is huge
Damn that is huge
Finally
It's big, and also heavy
Very heavy
The weight too?
Yes
Your highball sir
Huge!
It's here Matsumoto-san
So big!
It's here
The chinchirorin prize
Wait hold on
Cause you got odd
Nobody else is doing chinchirorin?
Any others?
Right?
Talent power ...
He ignored you
So freaking huge huh?
Still I think it's good have a little bit
The still easy going 5 have eaten their 10th skewers!
5th Store Complete!
With this everyone has eaten 10,
Tanaka-san 11
I can still eat
The 5 are in good spirits; The next menu?
Hosei-san?
Ah, Garlic!
Oh, first time someone's got that
That, and ...
There it is, there's the Spring Onion
There it is
That thing is huge
Why do you have such a foul expression?
That is pretty rude actually
OK, so Tanaka-san,
Quail
Wait a second I got Oyster again ...
You keep getting that ...
Seriously?
So that means, 3 alternates for you
Oh, really?
Yes
3 of them
Ah man
You are like an Oyster magent
TN: Apologies, I might not be translating this line correctly
After that, the two cards he pulled?
He will have Quail, Pollock Roe, and Cheese
Hamada; Nitamago (Ramen Egg), and Liver Cutlet
Matsumoto: Yamimo and Beef Kushikatsu
Endo: Chicken Wing and Tomato
Does anyone want to play Chinchirorin at the next store?
Uh Yamasaki-san wants to
No no no
Hosei-san?
No no
Looking at Tanaka last time, I don't want to be like him
A face full of despair
I was just feeling sick that day,
It didn't have anything to do with Sake
But still,
It'll be like I'm in a Hell-Zone
Hell-Zone...
Should we do a Hell-Zone contest,
whoever can say it the scariest
Oh yeah
Starting from who?
I'll go, Hell-Zone
Do it super scary
What do we say?
Hell-Zone
The words Hell-Zone?
Here I go
You're so quiet
It's not scary then
Ah, really?
Who's next?
Then...
I'll go
Here I go
Wait a second please
The banging
It kept getting louder all of a sudden
That's a wrap
Not like he can do it now
That was the beginning and the end
Only for that moment
Kushikatsu Tanaka 6th store; In Sumida Ward, Ryogoku location
Liver Cutlet
Okay
I'm gonna dig in
Okie dokes
I can totally dig in
Woahhh, that's nice
The size right? It's Nitamago after all
Like Humpty Dumpty
Hosei-san too
Spring Onion
Actually eat it, Ok?
Of course, of course
Who the hell do you think you're talking to?
Saying "of course" with a full mouth is no good
Apart from Hosei and his Spring Onion, the other 4 are finished their skewers
Hamada-san finished the Nitamago
It seems we're always waiting for the guy with the onion
Yup, the onion
The guy with the onion takes a long time
We had a good tempo going here
A little slow pace
Are you OK?
Like, we have another store too...
Don't want to stay here too long
It took him a while, but Hosei finally finishes his Garlic and Spring Onion
Oh! He's finished
Finished
Brilliant
Next, deciding the menu for the 7th store
The menu Endo got?
I got Lotus Root, and ...
Finally got it ... Spring Onion
Oh dear!
Someone will definitely get Spring Onion
This is a pain in the ass
Monaka
Ham Cutlet
Chicken Wing
Shishito
Mochi
Yamaimo
Onion
Wiener
Hosei got Yamaimo, Tanaka got Onion,
A large size menu
They head to the 7th store, in Chuo ward,
used for employee training, the Kodenmacho location
Tanaka-san are you gonna do it?
I will
Chinchirorin
Now Tanaka will take part in the Chinchirorin challenge!
Get a good one
You've got the same name after all
It's odd
It's here
Your Kushikatsu
Use the cabbage and enjoy please
The Spring Onion ...
The Spring Onion is small now
Oh wow
Oh yeah
But the regular Onion is huge...
The Onion is massive
The Spring Onion was a lucky item then
Right?
Sorry for the wait, your Mega Jug is here
So big
So goddamn big
Thank you very much
Go ahead,
Pretty amazing
Hamada-san, Ham Cutlet?
Yes
Ham Cutlet is just straight up delicious
I guess so
It's something you would order
That's big
It's big right?
Last time I had this it was like super thick,
Did you guys tell them to give me a thicc one?
We did not tell them "Make Hosei-san's Yamaimo a big one"
I still smell something fishy,
Sorry, I just don't trust you
Still so slow though
Despite the complaining, he finishes his Yamaimo and Mochi
Spectacular
Next, deciding the 8th store's menu
Oh he got it
Oh Tsukune?
Hell yeah
Hamada got Yamaimo, Matsumoto got Eggplant;
They are concerned with the size
Yamaimo
Pork
Eggplant
Clam
Tsukune
Quail
Ginko Nut
Nitamago
Potato
What store are we going to?
Monzen Nakkacho location
Ah I see,
Finally near the end huh?
I see
They've already started recapping
Hamada-san said "I see"
Looking back, we've been through a lot together
We sure have
We worked hard though, I thought it was gonna be impossible
There's a total of 23 stores,
we've just been lollygagging around the middle
NEXT WEEK, KUSHIKATSU AAANTA AFUCK AFA