TPF
The first annual Gaki no Tsukai Chiki Chiki, bet your life on this one bite for 100,000 yen, Kiki Anpan!
Come on!
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
You know, I think we are all in serious trouble today.
Serious trouble?
Well you know....
The cruel staff here...
That's true.
So it must be seriously difficult to get correct!
Usually, we have 12...
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hosei
Yes, 12 usually.
Correct, 12 usually.
But this time...
Because we are just not winning at all in recent times...
They took our age into
consideration, thinking that our tongues are just not functioning anymore.
They're worried about us, and that's why they've decreased it to 10...
Oh, is that so?
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents
DownTown's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Translator:
Typesetter:
Proofreader:
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
**Follow us on Facebook and Twitter!**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
Mickstar
(Team Gaki)
Otviss
Christian
Kiki Anpan
Choose the correct one
chosen for you out of the 10 anpan
Kiki Anpan!
The rules are simple. Find out which anpan out of the 10 you tasted at the beginning.
Get it right and win 100,000 Yen!
Who will win the prize!?
Get it right and win 100,000 yen. Who will win this prize!?
First Challenger
Endo Shozo
The first challenger is Endo, who has not gotten a Kiki right in eight years.
The one chosen for him:
I see...
Tezutsumi Tsubuanpan
The red bean has been put into the bread by hand and baked, a delicious anpan.
Well, it can't be helped.
There's no point in eating it in a clean manner...
Damn, this is tasty.
The grains in this are quite big.
They are quite big and firm, that's one of the clues.
The size?
Yes.
The bread...
Don't do that on camera...
People don't really want
to look at that kind of thing on their 4K TV's.
You know...an old man licking the crap out of some anpan...
Endo's Challenge
Remaining
10 / 10
The prices are from 91 Yen to around 130 Yen today.
All around the 100 yen mark.
Yes.
This Oginopan, Tanzawa Anpan
Oginopan
Tanzawa Anpan
130 Yen for 60g (without Tax)
He's gone for the one that
it's most likely not
Currently Tasting
Oginopan
(Tanzawa Anpan)
Correct Answer
Dai-ichi Anpan
(Tsubuanpan)
just to increase
his on air time that little bit.
It's his only way.
That's his usual way of thinking.
So easy to read the younger ones.
It really is.
I'm going for Oginopan.
Damn, that's tasty.
Maybe he really loves Anpan.
Damn, is anpan
really this tasty and delicious?
Who the fuck are you asking!?
Of course he would snap at you.
No no, don't get me wrong.
I genuinely don't know who he is asking.
But anyway, the taste is different anyway.
It's wrong?
It's wrong.
The red bean tasted simple.
They should've gotten a better red bean for this Japanese confectionary.
I'm not really sure what he means...
The one I ate
was NOT Oginopan's Tanzawa Anpan.
Correct!!
Yeah, I was sure about that one.
So the taste was different.
I could tell that the taste was different.
Maybe the size of the grains was just for that bite.
Watch
Yeah, was it just a one off thing or are they all like that...
Some of them are also sold nationally...
I'm really sorry.
This guy was yawning so much that literally
half of his face became a mouth just now.
Can you believe that?
Senpai, please get a hold of yourself...
What are you on about?
I'm really trying my best, here.
If you were a coin purse, you would have definitely just broken.
From opening too wide, right?
I'm going.
Endo's Challenge
Remaining
9/10
I'm going to try, umm...Itouseipan?
Itouseipan
[Ogurapan]
115 Yen for 126g (Tax Not included)
Made in the Kanto prefecture.
Endo can't read the symbols.
He suffers from bad vision due to old age and the fact he can't read it anyway, it's a double whammy
He suffers from bad vision due to old age and the fact he can't read it anyway...it's a double whammy.
Even if he can see it, he can't read it.
And he can't see the hiragana because of his poor vision.
It's a double whammy.
Currently Tasting
Itouseipan
(Ogurapan)
Correct Answer
Dai-ichi Anpan
(Tsubuanpan)
He's stooped in silence.
Can I just say one thing?
This is so hard!!
It's hard?
The things you're looking out for...
they're kind of there, but like even the size of the grains is just...
How about the taste?
It's so tough to say.
It's basically the same?
But I think it's just a little bit different, just at the end.
There's this little bit of saltiness at the end...
I think it was a bit sweeter before.
The one I ate was NOT Ogura-pan.
Correct!!
But seriously, oh man...
I really want to get this right.
You keep saying it's difficult, but...
You're getting them right.
Currently Tasting
Yamazaki
(Ogurapan)
Even though he says it's difficult, he distinguishes the sweetness of the red bean taste correctly and gets six in a row correct.
Currently Tasting
Family Mart
(Anpan)
Currently Tasting
Megumihi
(Anpan)
Currently Tasting
Ikedapan
(New Jumbo Ogura-pan)
6 in a row correct!!
But man, you are just...
Endo's Challenge
Remaining
4 /10
Yeah, only four left now.
I'm doing well.
Come on, you're so close so just go for it.
Oh man, give me a minute...
This Kobe-ya's Tsubuan... I've actually eaten this one before.
Kobe-ya
Tsubuanpan
118 Yen for 128g (tax not included)
Currently Tasting
Kobe-ya
(Tsubuanpan)
Correct Answer
Dai-ichi Anpan
(Tsubuanpan)
Ok, touched!
Oh man, this is close.
But I don't think the red bean
was this sticky...
I mean, it kind of was,
but I don't think it
was this sticky.
So it was that sticky...
You just said it wasn't that sticky.
Oh man, oh man...
But I guess he's
panicking a bit because there are
no parts we can use for the final edit.
I see, so he's really grinding it out.
He's panicking but he's not that stupid, he knows there's nothing that will get into the final edit.
He has done it 38 times, after all.
Indeed, 38 times.
Have a look...
He's really going for it now.
You really need courage to do this.
How pathetic.
So pathetic.
But I think this is actually
too sticky, so it's wrong.
The one I ate was NOT Kobe's Tsubuanpan!
Correct!!
Sorry about that.
You're doing amazing!
Only three more!
Isn't he!?
I'm going for this Aeon one.
Endo's Challenge
Remaining
3/10
Aeon
[Ande Gozaru Tsubu]
31 Yen for 121g (Tax not included)
Currently Tasting
Ande Gozaru Tsubu
(Aeon)
Correct Answer
Dai-ichi Anpan
(Tsubuanpan)
"The grains are very refreshing and sweet." (Reading from package)
I mean, it was refreshing...
But no!
It was too refreshing.
The one I ate was NOT Aeon's Ande Gozaru Tsubu.
Correct!!
He's done it!
One of these two!
Please!!
It's been so long!
I think it's the first time in ages this has happened.
Let's go.
Endo's Challenge
Remaining
2/10
Whichever one he picks here is really important.
I think it's this one.
Shikishima.
Shikishimapan
[Tokachi tsubu-anpan]
110 Yen for 121g (Tax not included)
Currently Tasting
Shikishima
(Tokachi Tsubi-anpan)
Correct Answer
Daichi Anpan
(Tsubuanpan)
Hang on...
The taste wasn't this light. Which means...
it's this one, Daichi-ya.
I can't eat this other one now, right?
Of course not.
I honestly thought it would be Shikishima pan, but
when I tried this one
the taste was too refreshing.
So...
I think it's this Tezutsumi Anpan.
If he gets it wrong he gets punished, but get it correct and get money...
I'm begging you!
The one I ate
WAS this Tezutsumi-Anpan!
Correct!!
YES, COME ON!!!
Wow, amazing!
Amazing, amazing!
That was amazing.
He went through them all.
I'm so happy!
It's tough on us now the first challenger got it right...
Producer's dance
Nakamura Yoshinobu
Kobayashi Hiromitsu
What the hell...
Thank you very much!
Endo 2007: Oolong Tea was last time he got it right
Wins 100,000 Yen
Get in!
Thank you so much, seriously.
He got it.
You were moaning the whole time, saying how hard it was.
Yeah, saying "I don't know, I don't know..."
"It's impossible."
But seriously, it is, please try it yourselves, it is really difficult.
There isn't one where you'll say, "Oh, this is wrong" straight away.
Second Challenger
Hamada Masatoshi
Next up is Hamada.
It's fine if we ALL get it correct.
Yes, if all of us get it right we get a total of 500,000 yen.
Let's make them shit themselves.
The one chosen for Hamada:
Kobe-ya, Tannenjyukusei, Tsubuan.
It's very soft and moist
and the refreshing sweet grains make it a perfect combination.
Well, you know...
There is no other way.
You're right, in order to get it right...
He's eating it like this so that he can get it right.
In order to find out information about it.
This isn't that sweet, you know.
But I wonder...these days
red bean isn't that sweet anyway.
Oh, really?
You're right though, the grains are quite firm.
And it's not that sweet.
Those are your hints I guess, huh?
Who the fuck do you think you are, talking down to me like that!?
Hamada's Challenge
Remaining
10 /10
You really do just end up looking just at the red bean paste.
I know
I guess it really is all about that...
Okay, I will go for this simple looking one.
Correct one  Kobe-ya
Tannenjyukusei Tsubuan
118Yen for 128g (tax not included)
This 'Kobe-ya' one.
Currently Tasting
Tsubuanpan
(Kobe-ya)
Correct Answer
Tsubuanpan
(Kobe-ya)
I haven't got a clue.
It is hard, and that's why they've shrunk it down from 12 to 10.
Actually, I do get what you're saying Endo, but the one I ate before...
I don't think it has this many grains in it.
You know, in the red bean paste.
Then you should know the answer...
So I'm right, this is wrong?
Umm no, I don't know.
Then don't say anything!
You know, I actually
don't look at the correct answer when choosing.
I'm pretty sure the one before
had one or two grains, but this one has
loads everywhere.
It's wrong.
The one I ate was NOT Kobe-ya Tsubuan.
Incorrect!!
What are you doing!?
It hadn't even reached the bin yet!
It literally hadn't!
It hadn't even left his hand yet!
You're kidding me!
It was.
Why did you go for the Kobe-ya first!?
Man, that was quick.
It was totally different, though!
Eat Anpan,
fart, then sleep!
It was the first one!
I'm happy though that we didn't have to spend too long going through all of that.
Yeah, he would never have gotten it right.
He would never have gotten it right.
Third Challenger
Tanaka Naoki
The third challenger is Tanaka.
The one chosen for him is the same one as Hamada, Kobe-ya Tannenjyukusei Tsubu-an.
Everyone except Hamada needs to get it right.
By all means, please do.
We really will.
Which one is it?
What do you mean by that?
The one I just ate.
I'm not sure if it's sweet
or not sweet.
Then you're screwed.
You're just screwed.
Right, let's just try to get it right quickly.
Tanaka's Challenge
Remaining
10 /10
Right, I'm going with Yamazaki Anpan.
Yamazakisei-pan
Ogurapan
98 Yen for 115g (excluding tax)
Currently Tasting
Ogurapan
(Yamazaki)
Correct Answer
Tsubuanpan
(Kobe-ya)
It's not called Yamasaki Pan, is it?
No, it is Yamazaki Pan.
No, it was more refreshing before. The one I ate was a bit less sweet.
That's right.
Why are you saying
it like it's your catchphrase?
I didn't
actually talk about this before,
but I sniffed it, right?
When I did that
I thought the scent of red bean would hit me harder,
but instead the scent of bread hit me hard.
So that is one of this episode's,
my kind of,
that thing,
I think.
What the hell, man?
That's the important part.
You were so close!
Let's say that part properly!
The one I ate was NOT
Yamasaki's Ogurapan.
Correct!!
Right!
Currently Tasting
Tsubu Anpan
(Pasco)
He uses his sense of smell to distinguish the scent of the bread.
Currently Tasting
Tsubu Anpan
(Dai-Ichi Pan)
3 in a row correct!
3 in a row correct!!
He goes and gets three in a row correct!
Let's go, let's go.
I'm just going for it now.
Tanaka's Challenge
Remaining
7 /10
Kobe-ya san, Hamada-san's one.
Correct answer Kobe-ya
Tannenjyukusei Tsubuan
118yen for 128g (tax not included)
Currently Tasting
Tannenjyukusei Tsubuan
(Kobe-ya)
Correct Answer
Tannenjyukusei Tsubuan
(Kobe-ya)
The taste is
definitely close, but
I've managed to see through the difference
in the scent of the bread.
The one I ate was NOT Kobe-ya's Tsubu-an.
Incorrect!!
You didn't "see through" anything after all!
I honestly thought you were going to get it!
Yeah, he stopped for a second to think and everything.
You couldn't tell anything about the scent.
You're existence is about as much as red bean paste!
You small balls comedian!
Okay, Tanaka-san.
Small balls comedian...
Yep, small balls comedian...
What does this mean?
Is it hard after all?
So hard, so hard, it's so hard.
It really is hard.
Fourth Challenger
Tsukitei Hosei
Fourth up is Hosei, who has not gotten a Kiki right in 11 years
The one chosen for him is Ito-pan's Ogura-pan.
It's not too sweet, and the bread is soft and moist.
Damn, it's hard!!
That's so bad!
Just eat it, man.
The bread is so soft.
Oh, so the thing that is hard is the red bean paste?
Yes.
I'm just going to eat the red bean paste.
This is so disgusting.
You could never watch this on a large screen.
Yamasaki's Challenge
Remaining
10 /10
Yamazakisei-pan...
Yamazakisei-pan
Ogura-pan
98yen for 115g (not including tax)
This is the one I most often eat.
Currently Tasting
Ogura-pan
(Yamazaki)
Correct Answer
Ogura-pan
(Ito-pan)
Okay, let's go for it.
There's no point taking that one!
Get a hold of yourself Hosei-san, please.
You have to get the bread sample.
Oh man, it's totally different.
It's totally different.
It was much sweeter.
Leave it behind!
Jeez, I was about to...
He's doing everything the wrong way.
Everything, he's doing it all the wrong way.
What's wrong with you today?
However, he is able to distinguish the differences between the anpan.
Correct!!
After that, he is able to distinguish the taste with confidence and he gets six in a row correct!
Currently Tasting
Tsubu Anpan
(Pasco)
Correct Answer
Ogura-pan
(Ito-pan)
6 in a row correct!
Yamasaki's Challenge
Remaining
4 / 10
Yes!!
Only four more!
YES!
Hold on a second...
It's very rare that two people get it right on the same show.
Let's go with this one.
Chosen to try Family Mart's
Hokkaido's Tsubu-anpan
100Yen for 91g (not including tax)
Currently Tasting
Tsubu Anpan
(Family Mart)
Correct Answer
Ogura-pan
(Ito-pan)
Wait...
It feels like...really dry.
The bread.
Well I mean, it has...
Quite a lot of time has passed.
But it's so dry that I have no idea at all!
The bread would be hard either way.
No no, that's not true.
The taste is the same.
What? Wait, give me a second.
This...
Is it because it's dry?
Damn, you're stubborn!
If you keep saying that, the other ones will dry up too.
Exactly.
That's what happens when you're up against
time itself.
You need to go quickly.
No, it's wrong!
I beg you!
The one I ate
Was NOT
Hokkaido's
Anpan!
Correct!!
Damn!!!
That was dangerous!
Damn, he's having fun!
Currently Tasting
Tsubu-an
(Kobe-ya)
He gets over the huge wall and distinguishes the next one with ease.
Correct!!
It's one or the other.
We have finally arrived.
It really depends on which one you pick.
After the break
Will Hosei  get it right for the first time in 11 yeaars!?
Yup.
Yamasaki's Challenge
Remaining
2 /10
He can look at them all he wants.
Dai-ichi Sei-pan
Tezutsumi Anpan
105 Yen for 116g (tax not included)
Oh, he touched it.
Currently Tasting
Tsubu Anpan
(Dai-ichi Pan)
Correct Answer
Ogura-pan
(Ito-pan)
This is the one...
This one...
COME ON!!
It's been 11 years!
It's been so long.
It's been 11 years, but
the one I ate
WAS Dai-ichi Seipan Tsubu Anpan!
Incorrect!!
You're kidding me!
Just...
Your jokes
are more amateurish
than red bean paste!
So true.
What he said was correct.
Fifth Challenger
Matsumoto Hitoshi
The last challenger is Matsumoto.
The one chosen for him:
Family Mart's Hokkaido's Azuki Tsubu Anpan
From Hokkaido, there is azuki in the bread, which is mixed with a strong tsubu-an in a moist bread.
The bread...
I'll try that.
This edge here...
This guy, this guy...
This division in the bread.
7:3 okay!
It's a 7:3 ratio.
I'll try the bread first. If you try the red bean first,
the bread will lose, so I will just try the bread first.
It's good to just shove the bread into your mouth first.
And to be honest, if my intuition is right,
I don't even really need to try the red bean paste...
That bread you say is so important just flew out your mouth.
After the break
Will Matsumoto get it right!?
Matsumoto's Challenge
Remaining
10 /10
I will get it right, however!
I will get it right, however...
JUST GET ON WITH IT ALREADY!
What the hell, man!
Currently Tasting
Ogurapan
(Yamazaki)
Correct Answer
Tsubu Anpan
(Family Mart)
Oh man, have I really done it again?
This here, it's been split 7:3.
Before, I just ate the top part first.
What should I do?
This is cruel!
I'm in trouble, however...
Oh just cut it out!
Seriously, that's enough!
Just hurry up and decide!
The red bean paste is a bit different.
It's too sweet compared to the one I ate.
Damn, that was a close one!
The one I ate
was NOT Yamazaki's Ogura Seipan.
Correct!!
Man, that was dangerous! It's the sweetness.
The sweetness?
Matsumoto's Challenge
Remaining
9 /10
This is the one that Endo was saying was definitely different from the others.
Okay, I will try this one.
Anpan Ebi
Ogura-an
112yen for 60g (not including tax)
Currently Tasting
Ogura-an
(Ebi)
Correct Answer
Tsubu Anpan
(Family Mart)
But man, this isn't that different. Oh, hold on!
It doesn't have that split I was talking about!
It's definitely wrong, then.
Using his sense of touch and distinguishing the sweetness of the anpan
Currently Tasting
Anpan
(Oginopan)
Currently Tasting
Tsubu Anpan
(Pasco)
he gets five in a row correct!
Currently Tasting
Ande Gozaru Tsubu
(Aeon)
5 in a row correct!!
Wow, you're half way there now!
Matsumoto's Challenge
Remaining
5 /10
I can do this!
I do want him to get it right.
Me and Endo, me and Endo.
It'd be great if there were two winners.
Ito's Ogura-pan, this is the one Yamasaki got wrong.
Ito Seipan
Ogura-pan
115yen for 126g (tax not included)
Currently Tasting
Ogura-pan
(Ito-pan)
Correct Answer
Ogura-pan
(Family Mart)
Umm, oh damn, this one has the 7:3 split.
Well this area is the same, they both have the 7:3 thing.
Oonuma, what the hell you looking at?
Producer
Oonuma Akihiro
You look like
you have a huge interest in this or something...
you have a huge interest in this or something!
Currently Tasting
Ogura-pan
Ito-Pan
Correct Answer
Tsubu Anpan
(Family Mart)
Is this a sign of his confidence? After this, he distinguishes the differences easily and gets two more correct!
Currently Tasting
New Jumbo Ogura pan
(Ikeda Pan)
2 in a row correct!!
Only three more!
Matsumoto's Challenge
Remaining
3/10
I think I'll start with Family Mart. Get Family Mart out of the way, go for one of these and I'm pretty sure I will get it right.
Correct one Family Mart's
Hokkaido Tsubu Anpan
100yen for 91g (not including tax)
I'm not going to do it the way Endo did.
I want to shout, "It's this one!"
And I'm going to receive 2,000,000 yen!
2,000,000 yen!?
Currently Tasting
Tsubu Anpan
(Family Mart)
Correct Answer
Tsubu Anpan
(Family Mart)
As if they'd pay you that much!
I think it's wrong.
It wasn't this sweet.
Yep, yeeeep!
The one I ate
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
was not Family Mart's Hokkaido Anpan!
SO FAST!
YOU GUYS, YOU CAN'T BRING IN FAMILY MART ON THE LAST GO!!
THAT'S SO OBVIOUS!!
There's such a thing as a pattern!!