A certain library in Tokyo
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tsukitei Hosei
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Guest
Katayose Ryota
It's a library, so...
Right, I'll be quiet
So thick...
Skull card: the person who draws it is going
to undergo the punishment as displayed
Kendama on forehead
Oh, come on...
topic:
Mh?
Kendama on forehead
One, two and...
Endo
Shh
Kendama on forehead
Really?
Are you kidding me?
That can't be true
Gimme a break...
It happens
Wait, this is not safe
This...
In order not to disturb the other readers
they absolutely can't raise their voice
Woah, wait---
Can you say a countdown?
Like, two, one...?
Please...
That--
I'd hate that
It hurts so bad
It still hurts
You have no idea
I'd hate it too
Right in the middle
It hurts
It's getting red
Yeah...
Hamada's cushion
What's this?
topic:
Doesn't seem like anything good...
Hamada's cushion
I hope you get it
No way
One, two, and...
Hamada
Shh
Hamada's cushion
What's this about?
That's your cushion
This is my usual...
It reeks!
Hamada's favorite cushion soaked in something with a strong smell
It stinks!
Huh? What now?
It stinks so much...
It's unbearable
Rugby kick
topic
One, two and...
Hosei
Shh
Rugby kick
I'm glad it wasn't me
Stand up
What now?
I'm glad I'm safe
I really am
This looks bothersome
Huh?
Scary
He's gonna do it?
Just like the World Cup
This is so scary
He must stay still
If he moves he's dead
Stay quiet
I'm glad it wasn't me...
Yeah, I agree
It stinks
You stink
Did you poop your pants?
Hosei, 51 years old, pooped his pants?
It really stinks!
Try to smell him
Huh?!
He pooped himself!
It stinks!!
Eh? Poop?
He pooped himself...
Poop?
Are you kidding me?
Really?
It stinks so much!
I won't deny I farted, but...
But it smells like poop
It really stinks
Sniff it
Just to make sure
You liar!
Be quiet
In front of our guest?
Quiet
I had enough already...
Garlic galore
topic
No idea what that means
Please God...
Garlic galore
One, two and...
Katayose
Shh
Garlic galore
Here it comes
Finally
What is--?
This one sucks
What should --- are we moving?
Step forward
There's an old dude
When you say ramen, I'd say garlic a-go-go
This is incredible
Such a strong smell
He's basically eating only the garlic
Yeah...
I can smell it
It's all over
It stinks so much
Oh man, the smell
It reeks...
I bet it does
Directly on your face
Yeah, that's it
It stinks so much...
I could smell it from behind you
It came like a wave
It still stinks
It smells
Unbelievable
You can't avoid smelling that
There was too much garlic
Yeah
It stinks...
Spinning rubdown
Huh? What's this?
topic
Spinning rubdown
One, two and...
Alright
Tanaka
Shh
Spinning rubdown
Glad it's not me
What does this mean?
Hole
Oh, I see
This isn't good at all
Isn't this dangerous?
It is
He might bleed
Holy shit
Nice shot
Shut your trap!
It looks painful
Is he bleeding?
He's gonna bleed
That was amazing
People can bleed from that
I bet it hurts, doesn't it?
I think that's the worst one yet for me
That guy was good
Yeah, incredible
Shabu-shabu drone
What is this now?
What the hell?
topic
Shabu-shabu drone
One, two and...
Endo
Shh
Shabu-shabu drone
Again?
Why always me?
One after another...
What is that?
It's for shabu-shabu
You have to place your chin here
Huh?
Whaaat?
Is it hot?
Place it properly
More than that
Scary!
This is freaky
Eh? What?
Woah!
That hurt
What the?
What the hell?
What just happened?
The hell was that?
What was that?
Ouch
It made no sense
Straight on my face
It could have gone bad
We gotta make sure Katayose gets more
No way
We can't know about that
Super hot bazooka
Here it comes
What the-
Super hot bazooka
topic
I don't like this one
Super hot bazooka
You go first
Ready and...
Hamada
Shh
Super hot bazooka
You gotta be kidding me...
I can smell danger from a mile
Woah, this is freaky
Eh? Come on, man...
Would you please...?
He's asking you to move
He's--
Be brave
Hurry up and go
Be a man
Come on
Look at him
Man...
Geez, I've had enough of this
Why are you doing this?
Piping hot T-shirt
What are you doing?
The fuck is that now?!
What's this for?
You really like hot stuff, don't you?
That's too hot
What are you doing?
He's pouring a lot of hot water in it
I bet it's gonna burn like hell
It's gonna be so hot
Maybe too much
What are you going to--?
So scary
This is horrible
I'm getting scared
Wait--- I'm freaking out!
I'm seriously afraid
Three...
Two...
One...
Shit!
His face---
This isn't fun at all
It felt like a punch
It almost hit your face
Maybe that was the plan
Such a nice impact
Granny bike seesaw
topic
Ready and...
Katayose
Shh
Granny bike seesaw
Alright alright
Ok ok
Katayose Ryota's manly scream!!
Downtown's combo face destruction
Katayose Ryota's real deal scream!?
TYPESET & QUALITY CHECK BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI.......I.......IS
TWITTER.COM/FGRNDNOISESASD'''
OTHER EPISODES & NEWS:
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI.....1
DONATIONS & STUFF:
Katayose
Shh
Granny bike seesaw
I'm scared
He's gonna die
Is this safe for him?
Granny bike seesaw
Really, is it safe?
I'm freaking out
I swear
Hang in there
This can't be happening
Relax
Here he comes
Wha-?
It's the guy from before
Huh?
His sworn enemy
He's his nemesis
My darling is waiting for me
Noooo!
- Gotta go now
Noooooo!
Nooooooooo!
Nooooooooooooooooooooo
La la la ♪
La la la la la ♪
- Shit
They're a duo
Sworn enemies
They always meet in the end
Matsumoto is the only one left
That's why I'm scared
Liquid nitrogen
topic
One, two and...
Hosei
Shh
Liquid nitrogen
This one sucks
Oh crap
This is bad news
Sit down, please
Yonemura Denjiro's disciple
Professor Genki Ichioka
Do I have to sit down?
Oh my
Be gentle, ok?
Ok
Terrifying
Are we gonna do this?
They'll fill the cups with liquid nitrogen and throw it directly at him
I'm scared myself
Woah
Holy crap
What?
It's undiluted
Are you sure this is going to be fine?
Doesn't seem that way
What happened?
You ok?
What?
It's kinda cold here...
Just that?
I have a bad feeling about this...
We gotta flip this first
Here I go
Pro wrestling (☠x2)
Look
Oh!
It's for two
Pro wrestling
topic
Sounds horrible
Pro wrestling
They'll need 2 skull cards for this
The punishment is for two people
I'm taking this one
I'll go with this
Why did you...?
No reason
Just for fun
Ready?
Ready and...
Matsumoto & Hamada
Shh
Pro wrestling
The hell have you done?
Splendid
Just perfect
It was meant to be
Gimme a break, please...
Best outcome
We're finally getting it
You gotta be kidding me
What the hell is this?
Finally
This thing?
What's this?
That's what I wanted
You're kidding me, aren't you?
Eh? What?
What's that for?
Ouch
This is heavy
On his lips too
This hurts...
Eh? Whad de--?
It's pro wrestling after all
What is--?
No way
It hurts
Ow ow ow
It hurts already
It hurts
Here they come
Wait--
No way
This is gonna hurt so bad
Ouch
Stop it
Here we go
No!
Let's do this
Am I bleeding...?
Is that a thing?
Great, huh?
That was incredible
Satisfying
As expected
This is gonna be our last one, right?
Yes
Here we are
I want him to go
Yeah, he deserves to
We don't know what we'll get
Mh? You're handing em out?
What?
No way
Can't be helped
Like this
Electric shock mixer (☠x2)
Oh, stop please
Electric shock mixer
topic
Let's flip them one by one
Hosei
Alright!
You got to be kidding me...
Tanaka
Please not me
This can't be
Please no
Hamada
Shh
Electric shock mixer
Don't shout
Who's next?
Please
Be one of you two
May I...?
Please don't...!
No way
Endo
Shh
Electric shock mixer
This is so messed up
You got it
It should
Should have been one of them
I know, right?
I agree
It had to be one of them
Can't be helped, dude
You gotta accept it
Why me? Why not one of you two?
You're talking so friggin' much
One of you would have been
way more suited for this than me
Static electricity machine
I know for sure this is going to hurt
Geez...
What is...?
Come on man, quit it...
Ehh? Come on...
Is it fine now?
It's not running?
Share the same one
Come on, are you kidding me?
Gimme a break
Didn't my lips get weird?
From before?
Kinda
They do, right?
A bit, yeah
It feels like they're swollen
Yeah, a bit
They're a bit swollen
They're redder than usual
Red and swollen
But you're fine
Yeah
They have to eat it?
Are they eatin' it?
Slowly
They're slowing eating it
Calmly...
It made a zap sound
You heard that?
This sucks so bad
I'm done
I'd hate it
It hurts
This isn't ok
No friggin' way
Enough of this
It hurts
Holy shit
We can do it again, right?
Yeah
Eh?
It can be used again
It stores electricity
Of course you can
How about the other 4...?
Oh, you're right
Excuse me?!
I don't get it
Between the remaining 4 members, 2 of them will go for it
What do you mean?
Sit down, you four
Why?
But--
You sure I haven't fucked up my lips?
I wanna pick it up myself
I don't like being given one
But we don't really know, I haven't seen them
Here
Katayose, please!
Alright, go on
One by one?
Starting from you, Tanaka
Go Tanaka
Let's see what you got
Alright!!
Tanaka
Shut up, Tanaka!
[drum roll]
Hosei
Shh
Electric shock mixer
Now I'm confused
Please not me
Spare me
Alright, let's do this; this one's yours
What?
It has to be the guest, come on
It's him
Right is our guest, left is Matsumoto, let's go
Guestguestguest
[drum roll] ready and...
W-wait---
Uugghhh
Katayose
Shh
Electric shock mixer
Fuck!!
Can't be helped
That's how it is
Are you kidding me?
Give up dude
Shit...
Not our fault
Hosei and Katayose's KISS!?
Katayose & Hosei
Shh
Electric shock mixer
Come on
You do your job and then you go home
Yeah...
Really?
Welcome to Gaki no Tsukai
Electric shock mixer
It was a pleasure
Thank you
Now they even know what's gonna happen...
Everything's set
That's right
Huh?
What the-?
So irritating
Are you kidding me?
I felt something--
Oh, come on
I swear
It made a sound
It's still charged
Really?
I heard it
I'm seriously scared
Oh man
Here, take this Yama-chan
It's still fine while you hold it
Yes, you don't feel it
That's true
Incredible
Now he's gonna charge it
Are you good?
Eh-- what's--?
We're not done yet
It made a zappy sound just now
Keep on charging it
Let's go
Hold it with your mouth, it's still safe
It's fine
Now start eating it
Eat it
Start eating it
Ah-- enough, please
Oh my oh my
Now that we're done, how was it?
Tell us
It went---
It went to my nose
Your nose? I see
Woah, incredible
Which punishments did you--?
That old man...
Yeah, those
Ah, the garlic thing That one
Garlic galore
Granny bike seesaw
Electric shock mixer
Ah, the garlic thing That one
"Granny bike seesaw" too That one too
All of them revolved around old dudes
Till the end
Even with him at the end
Of course you'll be surrounded by
old dudes if you come to our show
TYPESET & QUALITY CHECK BY KEDOMAS | TRANSLATION BY SHION
FIND OTHER SUBBED EPISODES: SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FOR NEWS & UPDATES HIT LIKE: FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
OR FOLLOW ME ON TWITTER: TWITTER.COM/FGRNDNOISES
WANT TO SUPPORT? YOU CAN MAKE A SMALL DONATION
ON PATREON: PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
OR ON KO-FI: KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT FANSUB MADE BY FANS FOR OTHER FANS
NO COPYRIGHT INFRINGMENT INTENDED
(HEY I LIKE THIS SONG, IT'S BABY BABY BY GING NANG BOYZ!)