Let's play with table games from around the world~!!
SECOND HALF
On today's Gaki No Tsukai
We'll see the second half of the previous table games episode!
It's time to have a good time playing
several games from different countries!
Just as last week
They'll play with lots of tabletop games from different countries!
Translation & Subtitles by Shion
facebook.com/shionnotsukai
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
This one
We'll have to play it in front of the table
Roger       - Ok
Use your turned-down card as a pillar to rise a building!!
Captain Rhino (huge version) - Germany
The game Tanaka chose
Is "Captain Rhino", from Germany!
You have to use face-down cards as pillar
to gradually build a tower, it's a balance game
Cards will start piling up
And the one who tears it down will lose, that's the game
I see
Germany -  Captain Rhino (huge version)
First you place your "wall-cards" in the position showed on the base-card
Then you place a "roof-card" from those you have in your hand
note: narrator voice = same as text
CHANGE ORDER
SKIP ONE PLAYER
THE NEXT PLAYER
ADDS AN EXTRA ROOF CARD
ROOF CARD
PLACE AN EXTRA
THE NEXT PLAYER WILL PLACE "CAPTAIN RHINO"
OVER THE DISPLAYED MARK
This 5 marks appears over the roof cards you can place
The players will stack em up while following their directions
THE NEXT PLAYER WILL PLACE "CAPTAIN RHINO"
OVER THE DISPLAYED MARK
This mark is the most important between them
One thing
If a player places a roof-card with the Rhino mark
The next person in order must
Place Rhino over it and keep on building
Rhino
So is it a special card ?
In a way this one has a special function
So it's special, right?
'Cause you can't just move it
monster
Where do we have to place this monster, then?
It's not a monster!
It's Rhino     - In the middle?
Rhino is supposed to be a loveable character!
Let's try a bit to... that's right, we have to try it
If I don't try it I won't get it
Maybe while you explain it...
Ok so...
Let's start from me
First of all place it
Following the directions
Which directions?
This is, uh... it's
The illustrations
down here
And now
I'm placing this
You place it-- oh, there's Rhino
Here's Rhino
Rhino already?!
So now Endo-san
Has to place Rhino before the cards
THE NEXT PERSON MUST PLACE RHINO ON TOP
Wait a moment, already?
So I guess it's here?      - Place Rhino there
Placed     - Now the walls
Two cards for this?
Yes
Is it always two cards?
Nope, could also be a single card
Who knocks it down
Yes?
loses
That's right     - Got it got it
Now Endo-san
Has to choose which of his card to use as his roof-card
Ok ok ok
I'm going then
It's a Rhino card again
Ok, Hamada-san is next
You have to take that Rhino first
Make sure to take it first
Right
So are we reusing
this thing?
Rhino
Could you stop calling it "thing"?
Let's avoid this abusive language
It's Rhino-chan
I mean, I guess it's still bearable at this height      - Yes
Right, but things won't be that easy as it gets taller
After that, Hamada safely clears a round
Hamada then proceeds to safely place his wall-cards
Matsumoto too easily clears a round!
After him, Matsumoto too clears it easily
And next one is Housei
Housei is next
Place Rhino first
Oh, Rhino-chan first?
Yes, Rhino-chan first
Then I place this      - Place it, right
This is...
This is a bit...
Ok, done      - Alright
Woah!
This one kinda
Gives me a bad sense of stability
It's scary, yeah
This-- Oh, you used that?
This is a reverse card
CHANGE ORDER
Flips the order
And now it's Matsumoto's turn
Got it
Can you see
The way he's trying to create
this sort-of-fighting mood?
It's like those rival dojo in comedy manga, isn't it irritating?
Suzuki Yoshiji
It's like those of Suzuki-sensei or...
Kaminaga Ichiro
Or Kaminaga-sensei
Yeah that's the setting he's aiming at
We're gonna need tons of lawyers for that
Yeah, right
Alright
What should I do?
Which is it?
CHANGE ORDER
That one...
It's reverse again
Back to Housei-san
Have I forgot to mention "rival-relationships are old fashioned"?
As long as it is
Funny, it doesn't matter that much
We're back to Yama-chan      - Your turn, Housei-san
This is pretty harsh
Now that we end up to this
Watch out
This is risky!
Seriously
Ok
This one was risky
Yeah
I've made it
It would suck to get Rhino by now
What if we pull out Rhino now?
CHANGE ORDER
You have to place it     - Matsumoto-san
You're next
It's reverse again
(staff)
It's not that hilarious, man !!
I guess two turns were enough!!
It got old already      - What, wait a moment
Matsumoto, Hamada and Endo too clear their rounds splendidly!
After that
Matsumoto, Hamada and Endo perfectly make it through
The building reaches the tenth floor!
And the building
Reaches its 10 floor!
Tanaka, this...
This is... we're pushing it to its limits
I really want to add a floor to this
Of course you want to
One, two, three, four, five...
This is the worst part
If the game would end here
it won't be funny at all
I guess you're right
Even if you say so...
If this ends here
Tanaka is the worst
Concentrate, concentrate
Concentrate, you're doing it
It's fine
This is nothing good
Which card is it next?
This
SKIP ONE PLAYER
Skip one player?
It's on Matsumoto-san then
Rules are rules
His choice is right
Dude that's so sly
He can but please
Please don't fail on this one !!
Come on Tanaka, you don't have to go that far to stop me
He made it
He did it
Ok
Yama-chan will be skipping this turn, so it's on Matsumoto-san
Ok, Matsumoto-san
Matsumoto-san...
If it falls right now
it's not going to be funny at all
It would be the worst
It's really the unfunniest distance
I mean height
I really have no idea how's up there, I can't see anything!
Right
That's true
It's too high
I don't know its shape
Woah, here we are...
Which shape is it?
It's a single one
A single one?     - Just one?     - One...
A single "V" on its center
If you manage to get through this, the next player will be pressured
Yeah, right
Pretty high...
This is a bit too much...
You can do it, Matsumoto-san!
He actually made it
See?
Are you for real?
This is impossible by now
Speak louder!
I have a really bad feeling about this
This is a bit too much...
It's on, it's on, it's on!
Ok, ok, ok, ok, ok
That means
Hamada-san is next
This is impossible by now
I don't think I can see its top from this stepladder
Let's do it with a taller one then
I think you can do this
Yeah but it's shaking like crazy!
This should do it
Yeah but
Shouldn't we let Hamada place it?
Man, it can't be that near
This is scary
If you please
Scary !!
That's 'cause you placed this single card here
Why the other side?
Nnnope !!
The other side! The other!
It's not a matter of sides---
You suck
Moreover, it happened without him realizing it
Yeah it was like "I have no idea what's goin' on"
He really had no idea it was happening
He ignored it!
As soon as I placed it
I suddenly got it back cause it was shaky
Alright, you're no good!!
Matsumoto snaps playing a occupy-the-base game!?
Coming up
Matsumoto's outburst with a battle game!?
Blokus - France
Link together the pieces with your color and line them up!!
The next game Tanaka chose
Is "Blokus", from France!
France -  Blokus
It's a game about occupying the others' base, in which 4 players,
in order, has to connect the pieces with his own color
4 players, in turns,
While connecting their own pieces
Must place them on the gameboard
However
There's a single rule...
You have to line each of them up one after another
As a rule, at least one spot of each piece must adhere
It must touch, right?
To that of another piece you've placed
Just one spot, right?
You have to make sure their edges touch
The edges?
But you can't make them touch like this
We can't?      - Is it not good?
Yeah this is no good
If the sides are touching, it isn't ok
Edges only?
Yes, it's only the edges
You do like this with just the edges...      - I see...
And gradually connect them
By doing that you widen your own field
You also have to think on how to block your opponents' invasion
That's hard!     - I see
You have to
Use your head
The player who thinks he can't go further than that, is out
I see, I see
Keep on playing until the end with those who still can
Woah you can't really...
Win this game if you don't corner the others
Pretty much
Starting from Endo
Lots of them have edges... Ok, I'm going
Ok
Nice choice
Next up is Hamada
Choose which one to use between these
upper right corner: in-game color of the players
Endo → Hamada → Matsumoto → Housei
Alright
Good
Like that
Alright
Back to Endo-san
Yes, yes, yes, just like that
Why pointing that out? I can see it
'Cause the rules are surprisingly hard
Let's see...
Alright, alright
Ok
Yes, that's fine
I have no idea what to do, though      - Yeah me too
You can't do that!!
'Cause the sides are touching right here
But it wasn't touching over there
Yeah but
Even if it touches just one side is still not ok
So like that?      - Yeah, that's fine
The four of them easily place their pieces
However, the space on the board is reaching its limits
However, the space on the board
8th round
Give me a second     - Ok
Should I do a countdown?    - Ok
You ignored it
You're all cornering me
Good, good
Is that good?     - Yeah
Alright
Matsumoto-san, you're next
What?
It
It just took you a long time to realize that
Its' just that...
You were just going 3, 2, 1 to us
It's just that none of you
Reacted to my countdown at all, so I wonder why
It backfired just at me
Ok
Alright, good, good
Ok, ok, ok
It's about time for a drop-out
Yes, it will slowly get more severe
So someone will surely lose soon
I see...       - Yes
Ah!! A side is touching there
How many times are ya doin' this?
You're the only one who did this
countless times
Shut the hell up!!
What the hell, man
This piece is long
Tanaka, shouldn't we use a penalty system?
You've made the sides touch again !!
Can you do this more seriously?!
Alright, alright
Hurry the hell up!!
Say what you like but I'm always hurryin' up
I have this big one
You just wanted to say that, don't you?
I've found a pretty good spot
He's right, that's ok, alright
What are you doin'?
You said it's not ok to touch sides, so...
Don't check their length
The situation quickly worsened
Alright Endo-san, that was good
Can I snap one of them in half?
You can't
That's obvious
You just want to tear them all to pieces
Oh!     - Ok, ok
I see
Am I the one who's screwed after all?
Well...     - Seems so
YAMAZAKI!!
YOU DID IT, YOU FUCKER!!
He's right
This is pretty bad for him
I think he's done for      - Yeah pretty much
Probably      - This is...
I wonder if I can overcome this
Right, right, right
After that, Housei
Endo
And Hamada place their pieces easily
And it's Matsumoto's turn again
Alright
Up to you, Matsumoto-san
Man
The situation got pretty harsh for me
Do I have fitting pieces for that?
Am I done for!?
I think it's impossible
Get the hell away from me!!
There must be a spot!
Yeah but... not much left
Oh! This one!
He found one!
Alright!
He did pretty good!
His range got really wide
He did a great move
He made his comeback
This felt so good
An unexpected turn
You can't place that over there
You really want to stand in my way, don't you?
Can he do that? I'm not sure
This is 100% illegal
And on top of that you are a friggin' unpleasant presence!!
They were completely attached        - What the hell was that?
Endo's situation is going to...
At this point
Things don't look good for Endo
I think I've just run out of free space
Probably
Of course this was impossible for Endo
'Cause baseball
Is the only thing he ever did in his entire life
Looks like
Endo-san has
I'm done for, right?
no space left
I have no space left
Do you have a 1x1 square piece?
Have you used it already?       - Yeah I used it
If only baseball
Wasn't the only thing he ever did to this day
That's what made him waste his 1x1 square
This all happened 'cause I did nothing but baseball
Yup, I can't do anything      - You're out then
ENDO DROPS OUT
Leave your pieces here, we count them later
It's Da-Hama's turn
Now it's battle between 3 players
I think Da-Hama-san too ran out of space
Yes, the situation got really strict by now
(staff)
If he hasn't any 1 or 2 square pieces left, he's...
Well, he doesn't have any of those, so...
Nothing left for me to do but snap them in half
Giving that you can't do that, it means you're out
HAMADA DROPS OUT
Alright
So now
Now it's a 1 vs 1
Matsumoto vs Housei: the unexpected conclusion!?
So, it's a 1 vs 1 now
Oh but
I still have the 1x1 square piece left
He's right      - Incredible!       - I see
It could come in handy
Yeah but he has to widen his range
I think this is the only place left...
There's nowhere but here, right?
Tanaka-san?
This...        - Matsumoto-san...
What the-
That isn't attached to anything
If that was ok, it would have changed the whole course
Anywhere would be ok
I see, there...
That is so satisfying to watch!
It felt so good
Yeah, it did
Matsumoto vs Housei - they both only have 5 pieces left...
After that
The battle between Matsumoto and Housei continues
And both their pieces are down to five
And now it's Matsumoto's turn!
This one? No, maybe it's wrong..?
I'm going home !!
See you, then
Why is that? Just play this
Come on!!
Why do you want to go home? Hurry up and finish this
It stinks!!
Come on, he's just messing around
I bet you just felt the urge to say that giving the moment!
Come on, man
Found it
Woah, Matsumoto!
And now...
The situation has become sort of numb by now
It's the legendary duel
That's true
Alright, alright, alright
I should have make it reach that other side there...
I had no idea at first that it would turn out like this
Whatever I do isn't ok
This is not good
This too won't do
And even this move
Does it mean
Is this a stalemate!?
I think you just have to use the 1x1 square
Yeah I think you don't have anything left
I'll use it and hope for a chance of winning
Right
You just have that corner left
Where?
Like here, this part
You mean here?
I think that's the only thing to do
He did it!
Can you still go on?
I'm probably done for
You're probably done for
I think I am
You can't with those pieces
I think it's impossible for Housei-san too
We gotta measure them
Yes, we have to     - Wait a moment...
This two are the same
Same goes for these two
It's on these two
1, 2, 3, 4, 5... 1, 2, 3, 4, 5
They scored the same
Same points...
You fought that much just for a draw
So, is it a draw in the end?
It's a draw in the end
No winner in the end?
Maaaan, just look how it turned out...
An hard fight playing a game from Korea!?
This game was really fun to play
Yes, it's a brainy one
Let's strike down the tree bark and make it fall!
Korea -  Click Clack Lumberjack
The next game Tanaka chose
Is "Click Clack Lumberjack", from Korea!
Korea -  Click Clack Lumberjack
In order, each player hits the tree with the axe 2 times
The player who collects more fallen bark, wins!
Rules are simple
In order, each player hits the tree 2 times with the axe
The player who makes more bark fall down, wins!
Let's start from Endo-san
From me?     - Yes
Ok, here I go
Nothing fell down from it
This is harder than you'd expect
So friggin' violent...
So crude...
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry
Even if we're playing, it's not funny at all with this guy
I'm sorry, I'll fix this
At least scream an "AAAAAAAH!"
That was harsh      - I'm still learning this!
Such a rough character
That' not it, that's not it
It's just hard to set the power      - Right
Let's continue from me then, this guy is no good after all
Going back to square one, they'll start again from Matsumoto
Here I go
AAAAAAAH!
Come on, Downtown-san...
So strong!
Ok, real talk now
I had no idea how hard I should have hit it!
I know, right?
You don't know at first
I didn't know how it felt, I'm sorry!
You wouldn't think of it as being that light
Really?
This bitch is way more unreliable than I thought
It's weak
It's better to go soft on it
They'll start again from Housei
I'm going
Ok
Yeah, that's how you do it
That's 'cause we aimed to get a point at the very start
Yeah, that's right
Something like this
I guess that's it
It's pretty hard to get points in this
They're not fallin'
He's so gentle now
That was without a doubt way too weak for a hit!
Who are you, an old shoemaker?
Geez, this
This is pretty hard
Yeah it's hard
Oh, I see
Awww, but it's possible
Yeah
I think it's here
What is there? You can do it?
See?
Alright, one point
I guess we'll make some points from now
I see, I see      - 'Cause it's crumbling
3rd round
Look at this one!
It came out with a click
(staff)
Doesn't count if it doesn't fall
This could be a chance
You're right, it's easy to take off this piece
Why is it a chance ?
'Cause this...
Maybe it's better not to say it
Right, don't say it
Are you kidding?
He chickened out
You can do that?
Look!
Does that one count?
(staff) Yes, it counts
You should have told me that
He took two
I see
Why are you telling me this only now?
I didn't know side hits were ok too
Yeah, right?
He's good!
Yamazaki is scoring a point after another
I bet you already have this game at home!
Yeah I mean, it's strange
You can't be this good at it!
That's the first time I saw it!
Are you sure?
I don't have one myself!
He's secretly trained
Tanaka & Endo too failed their round
Following Housei
Tanaka and Endo try to score points too
But they're not able to make any bark fall
So...
If I use my axe
and swipe
it this like this am breaking rules?
No, you can do it
I can?     - Yes
Only the bark
As long as you hit it
So good!
He's suddenly so good at it !!
I bet you have this game at home!!
But Hamada
Wouldn't it be better to end this round with one hit?
Nice idea       - You can if you want to
In the end the most unnecessary thing has been said by me
That was sweet of you
You can strike 1 or 2 times?
On this next round
I'm gonna be screwed
No doubts on that
This isn't easy
Why don't you try to place it back upright?
He's right
I have to study this
I can hit it as if I'm scraping it off, right?
Oh, you' wanna take that down?
I'm sorry
Was that even something?
It's this way! I got this
It kinda went back
The top got risky
He's right, watch out Housei
Right, one strike
I think if it goes well now there's no way we can reach his points
Push it back
Right
That was risky!
He's a prodigy
There's no doubt he got this game at home !!
You have it, don't you?
That's so strange
That's amazing!
So strange
I'll try to place it back
Nice one
Maybe placing it back won't get you points
It makes you bring out your character
I see
It brings out your character
Man
Tanaka sure likes to return it to its uprightness
"Its uprightness"
I guess I like to do that
But I guess you managed to get 1 point after all
Endo isn't
thinking of anything anymore
'Cause he's really an
idiot
, that's why
See?
That was no good at all
Translation & Subtitles by Shion
Are we done?
Are we?
You cleared it by smashing it
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
You're really the worst!
The worst!
The one on top is so light!
www.facebook.com/shionnotsukai
Of course it is!
It's like smacking down the Daruma first in Daruma-Otoshi
The game wouldn't be fun at all!
Want to support my translations? Consider donating @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
Of course it's light, it's on top of them!
But I wanted it to make this fall--
We all did our best not to do that!
I'm sorry... I'm sorry