Gaki no Tsukai ya arahende, chikichiki!
"Aim at making quick money!
Ass Work grand prix!"
Today, please make interesting works with ass.
the prize is paid this time.
Really!?
First of all, please choose the course.
And five judges whom Producer Suga leads...
Gaki Menz
If you can have four or more of this five laugh,
we will pay the amount of money that you chose from the program (Gaki no Tsukai).
If four or less, you must contribute
the amount of money that you chose
to "Ai no Kobatobokin Jigyodan".
- Campaign finance that Nippon Television
Network Corporation manages -
Why!?
Out of own pocket?
Of course!
We offer a prize. So if you fail,
you must contribute your own money.
I don't know why, a strange guy is in comedians.....
Onuma participates?
- Yea.
(※ Mr. Onuma is a director.)
Evangelist of beauty, Onuma.
Hey Yamazaki, decide your turn.
The first!
Really?
First?
- Yea!
This guy wants to advertise CD.
Wants only to say "Yamazaki ichiban"
※ Yamazaki released CD titled "Yamazaki ichiban".
ichiban means the first.
Well, choose the course.
3000 yen course!!
Shit!
Contribute more, shit!
You purchased Benz?
This guy owns Benz.
Shut up!
Purchased new Benz, shit!
All right!
50000 yen!!!
50000 yen course!!!
Well, we'll see how things go.
Let's work out countermeasures
after see his action.
Well now, entry No.1
Mr. Hosei Yamazaki's "Ass Work"!!
Finish!
Oh my God!
Mr. Motoichi and Yoshinobu laughed.
Only two!
and so Mr. Yamazaki failed!!
Whew!! Having 4 men laugh is very hard!!
- risky!
How's it going?
Motoichi and Yoshinobu laughed,
but other 3 guys didn't laugh.
Whew!! Really?
Mr. Yamazaki, please contribute 50000 yen.
Thank you!
Well, next challenger is Mr. Shozo Endo.
Hey Mr. Endo. Did you see?
- Yea!
The first challenger's 50000 yen course.
He has dropped admirably.
Well, which course do you choose?
5000 yen course.
5000 yen?
- Yea, 5000 yen.
- Yea!
Whatever?
- 5000 yen whatever.
Ok.
Mr. Endo. 5000 yen course!
Entry No.2
Mr. Endo's "Ass Work"!!!
Finish!
Motoichu and Suga chan were close.
Well,
5000 yen
Please contribute.
- Whew!!!
I could hear no laughter at all in the box.
Well, next challenger come on!
Third challenger is Mr. Tanaka.
Did you see?
Yea, I feel very hard... at all...
What??
I see.
Oh my god! What will I do!?
The first is 50000 yen and second 5000 yen.
Well, which course do you choose?
2000 yen...
All right! All right! All right! All right!
30000 yen!!!
I'm confident!
Really?
Of course!!
"Fuga Fuga" is coming.
There isn't no laughter.
"Fuga Fuga" was coming to the first and second.
Next is
"Boooooom!!!!"
"Hyahhahahahahahahahahahaha!!!!"
There is a possibility enough.
Well,
Mr. Tanaka's "Ass Work"!!!!
"Tamori, Center"
※ This mark means positioning on the stage.
※Tamori is a veteran comedian.
His comedy show is broadcasted everyday in Japan.
"Tamori, Center"
Finish!
Oh! Very hard!!
Impossible!!!
Mr. Tanaka,
30000 yen,
Please contribute.
My face was showered with your massive juice.
Thank you very much!
Next challenger come on!
Well, Mr. Onuma
What will you do?
I thought Tanaka's was funny.
I am not confident, so...
25000 yen.
25000 yen?
- Yea.
Entry No.4
Mr. Onuma's "Ass Work"!!!
Nice bust
Finish!
Mr. Onuma selected 25000 yen course?
Yea
25000 yen
We offer the prize.
But yours is very ordinary.
At last! The last challenger come on!
Did you see?
- Yea.
No.1 to 4
The thing can be said through the whole,
all is unsatisfactory.
4 men are unsatisfactory?
- Unsatisfactory!
They are useless at all.
But Mr. Onuma got 25000 yen.
Huh! That's evil!
Very evil!
That's very evil! And...
I am very mortifying.
Till now, 50000 yen, 3000 , 30000, 25000
well, Mr. Matsumoto,
of course,
I shoulder the signboard named DOWNTOWN,
I have walked from the pass for a long time.
From the pass??
70000 yen course.
Half-sum!
But the highest amount of money.
Well, please prepare.
70000 yen course!
The last challenger.
Mr. Matsumoto's "Ass Work"!!!
"Kadokawa Horror Paperbacks"
Finish!
Even if xxx is put out...
Mr. Matsumoto.
You selected 70000 yen course?
Yea yea!
70000 yen.
Please contribute.
Please pardon me!
I've done my best!!!
But only 3
Only 3!?
You must think more!
The bookmark is put in!
Someone reads again later!
Open my ass
All please on the stage again.
But Mr. Onuma got 25000 yen.
Amazing...
The results was the worst.
Contribution was 155000 yen.
We have a favor to ask you...
Please let us challenge again!!!
We select one of us, and challenge 155000 yen course...
155000 yen single-game match!!
Are you quite sure!?
Oh, I think it's not.
Ummmm.....
But I don't want to pay.
I worked hard but must pay,
It seems that maid has broken high-priced vase...
Shut up shit!
Only amateur Onuma got a prize after all.
So, by comedian's pride, they challenge again with Yamazaki's ass!!
Well, betting 155000 yen.
4 men's "Ass Work"!
Finish!
You four....
Please contribute.
Well, total 310000 yen.
I'm not involved.
I'm not involved, not involved, not involved
I am not involved.
You said! shit!!!!
You said let's challenge!!! shit!!!