Piece of trash.
Gaki no Tsukai's Best Series!!
"No Laughing Enthusiastic Teachers"
Broadcasted on New Years Eve was Gaki no Tsukai's greatest series
Translation:
GodzillaRadio
Typsetting/timing:
Hinnerk
DsupremeR (Jonko)
Slayeer(Alex)
Absolutely Can't Laugh Enthusiastic Teachers 24 hours.
Modern school and Edo times
Powerful Assassins Constantly Attack
Spanning from modern to Edo times, powerful assassins of laughter attacked the five.
Shes here!!!
These are the funny traps that we showed on New Years Eve.
However, this was not all of them.
There were this many tricks that we tearfully had to cut!
For the people who missed it
We condense 6 hours worth of laughter
Tonight, we unleash it with a condensed version of the 6 hours from New Years.
101st
101st Proposal!
101st  Proposal!
Unreleased scenes that
We will show you all of the unreleased set-ups.
couldn't be broadcasted on New Years!!
Not good! Seriously, get lost!
Mysterious  Band of Heroes
A mysterious band of heroes appear on the bus!
What the hell is this!?
Grim  incidences
Grim incidences encountered in Edo times!
We're OUT?
He's the one that's OUT!!
{\fscy120He's the one that's OUT!!
Secret
He's the one that's OUT!!
Don't Laugh Enthusiastic Teachers Complete!!
The incomplete "Enthusiastic Teachers" will be completed tonight!
You can't do stuff like this!
You can't do stuff like this!!
Absolutely No Laughing Whatsoever
Enthusiastic Teachers
24 Hours
Missed parts and unreleased parts all unveiled SP!!
New Year's Eve Special
Gaki no Tsukai Yaarahende!
1st broadcast of the New Year.
Please continue to support us this year
Downtown
So it's the complete version of the New Year special!
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Yes, that's right.
Yamazaki Hosei
It's inevitable Matsumoto-san, that we couldn't include everything in the New Years run.
Kokoriko
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Could you please stop me from doing this Yakko-dako kite soon.
You can keep doing it.
Really? Alrighty, I'll do some more.
A yakko dako joke!!
So we'll show everything today!
People that appeared as guests might have watched on the 31st
The five of them will finally watch the complete show.
and be like "Huh!? Didn't I appear on this".
Claudia didn't appear though.
Umemiya Claudia
No she didn't.
Apparently she's busy doing business.
Yes, business.
Yama-chan, please cue the video.
You know, since you're Tsukitei.
You're in charge after the new year starts.
From January 1st
Yamazaki Hosei will be
Tsukitei Hosei
Yes, from tomorrow you're Tsukitei!
You'll be Tsukitei Hosei now.
So then!
Heeeey!
Maeda (Time Keeper) saaaaaaan
Roll that VTR for meeeee!!!
This is the art of Tsukitei Hosei.
So let's take a look at "Absolutely No Laughing Enthusiastic Teachers"
from the beginning.
No Laughing Enthusiastic Teachers
suitable attire for the job as teacher
Changing into
This time, the 5 were to work as teachers
and were forced to dress as Kinpachi-sensei.
This one! This! This one! This!
The taste of the Kinpachi wig is different
The moment they enter the bus laughing will not be tolerated
The moment they enter the bus, laughing will no longer be tolerated.
Oh! He went!
Absolutely no Laughing
Enthusiastic Teachers
24 Hours
Absolutely no Laughing
Right now, only Yamazaki will get punished if we laugh...
If we laugh... it'll be totally fine...
Pfft hahahahah!!
See, he laughed!
Hey! Why aren't you guys on board!?
Rules only apply to Yamazaki
He looked at Hamada from inside the bus and laughed.
Rule
It was a start full of commotion, with the rules only being enforced on Yamazaki.
Black Army  will
Spank their bottoms
Towards the assigned school they   depart
The first assassins of laughter were...
Band Guitarist
Itou Ichirou (ELT)
Two-Timing between band members exposed
Two band members clash in competition for the band manager.
I'm, seriously in love with you.
Female Manager's Request
Get a stag beetle to clamp your nose and show your true love!
So the female manager asks them to clamp a stag beetle
on their nose and show her their true love.
UWWAAAA
Isn't he a bit pissed off?
The next assassin was a movie critic
The next assassin was that movie critic.
I'm sick of this shit
So fed up...
Movie Critic
Osugi
(Sekine Tsutomu)
I loathe being mistaken for piko (his twin clothing critic brother)
Just really, recently it's...
In regards to "Nihonkai", a movie that Hamada starred in 20 years ago...
Released in 1991
Introduction to Hamada's starring film
I saw your movie! This one!
By Osugi
"Nihonkai" Starring Hamada Masatoshi
This is a very shocking tale, and if you ask why
The star, Hamada Masatoshi, does a splendid job of portraying the dark yakuza world and yet...
I can't get over the fact he looks like a gorilla
Breaking promises or shooting guns, no matter what he does he's a gorilla! A child-faced gorilla!
Whatever he's doing he's still a gorilla! Even though its a yakuza film, it's become an animal film!
Anyone who doesn't watch this gorilla flick will be trampled!!
Critiques with harsh comments
He critiques the movie with some harsh comments.
And now, for the unreleased footage! There were other jokes set on the bus.
45 minutes passed since start
Haven't we reached the school yet?
Maybe the train would've been better.
Arrival at bus stop
Which one is the opening?
Pardon me.
Just walked a little bit and my legs are already tired.
Shoots for Ikushima Hiroshi's  "Lunch Time Everyday" Show
(Fake)
Basically, the problem is how we cut scenes to here.
In any case, let's just start with this and...
Trip Guide/Actress
Akikawa Sumiko
(Tomochika)
Tsuyoshi & Reiji
(Nakagawake)
Director & Cameraman
Let's just hurry up and shoot this.
So I link it with "Treat every encounter like your last"
Okay, I understand.
Begin the shoots with a punchline
Should we start with a shot of the scenery?
Should we?
I think it'd be good to start with scenery.
5 seconds to go, 4, 3, 2.....
Cue Card
Treat every encounter
like your last
So it's been a while since I've rode a bus during a trip
but I've got to say that it's a leisurely feeling.
Isn't she gonna say the show's title?
Akikawa ignores the arranged lines
No, you should be saying the title.
It says "treat every encounter like your last" on the cue card.
I can't take anymore!
Isn't it like a title call?
Treating every encounter like your last is a great.
I think that relationships with others are important for people.
Weeell but I suppose, for me, the best thing are hot springs.
I'm still going, so get outta the way! I need to get into here!
I have to say it again!
Yeah, right...it should be fine.
Yeah, don't worry.
How many times are you going to make me say it.
Err yes, sorry.
Don't ask me that you idiot.
Why is she holding a persimmon?
That persimmon is so annoying!
Dunno what they supposedly did before this.
The persimmon won't....make the scenes consistent.
Persimmon given by a passerby.
In the location just before....
It's reversed.
It becomes reversed.
You gotta explain this...
Can we take take that persimmon for a bit?
Yeah, we don't have time.
Apparently it's seedless.
Oh really.
Now rolling, okay, yes...go.
In my opinion, hot springs are the things...
that make people feel warm inside most.
Ha, hahahaha
Cameraman forces a laugh
The hell was that?
Nothing was funny about it.
There are people like that though.
Alright! That hit on Endo was great!
Keep destroying Endo!
We'll have to go with that.
I understand.
I'll just go film the outside of the bus.
We should just ask again outside.
Ask someone on the street.
You want the persimmon? Should I take it?
Stop asking me the same question over and over again.
The persimmon will link to the next scene.
Let's just film her wandering around.
You know how she entered while saying "My legs hurt from just walking a little bit"?
The 5 guys faced  troublesome happenings
You laughed at yourself saying it!
In no time, the 5 faced troublesome happenings.
Your's is that all girls school!
I know right? It's full of cuties!
Delinquent students occupying seats
Excuse me, I've got bad legs...
...so could you please give up a seat for me?
HELL NO!!
So friggin' annoying.
Bus arrives
They're gonna come.
See, here they come.
Mighty Sou
Oowada Shinya
I am the Dragon God exiled from the land of Gods...
Mighty Sou!
Ahhh
Hock Eye
Terence Lee
I am the world's greatest marksman.
Sorry.
Next
A bill....billionaire and a genius scientist.
Ironmarn
Umemiya Tatsuo
A genius businessman who punishes evil.
Ironmaarrn!
We are...
We are
Arvengars!
What is this poster?
Well, I was expecting something like that to come.
Arvenjars
Go on grandma.
Go? Didn't she wanna sit down though?
Saves elderly lady from delinquents
This is lame, let's go home!
Take care on your way home.
Fucking geezer what?
Pheww...those guys are lucky to keep their lives.
Besides, it's because you guys
don't offer your seat to elderly people.
That's why all this even happened!
Anger gets aimed at the 5
Don't be silent and answer me.
I said answer me, damn it!
Hold it!
Black Window
Agnes Chan
The world's most skillfull....
Assassin! Black Window!
The cast has laughed, but may continue to watch
I'm the legendary warrior possessing wild physical ability!
Captain American
Sugi-chan
Captain American!
Incredible Hulks
Umezu Kazuo
Ahahaha!
Anger changes my appearance...
You're totally different people.
I'm a genius scientiiiiist!
I have no idea what you're talking about.
DAAAAAHH!
Jeeez...
That's enough already.
These guys look even more like CG.
Huh, you're gonna sit down?
Jeez, why are you gonna sit?
Mighty Sou
Don't get so worked up.
They're just civilians.
Mighty. I told you not to get so worked up.
It's obvious that these people aren't bad.
Oh, my bad. I  just can't stand how they left the lady to die.
Who's next?
.....hey.
Get your act together! Jesus!
Do it properly.
Surely it's not that hard.
Seriously, come on!
You're Tatsu-nii
You're definitely Tatsu-nii
Don't check now.
Your didn'....didn't say but...
I understand what you want to say but
Hahahaha
Please do it properly.
They haven't said their side of the case yet.
Argh, seriously...seriously..seriously
There contagious laughs were...
Maybe you should have practiced it a bit earlier?
I understand what you guys want to say
We haven't said anything.
but we are the Arvenjars.
Shut up you fucking hag.
Oh...
You just said something, didn't you?
I don't understand the story.
You didn't
call me a hag, did you?
There's no way you would, right?
This is crazy.
There's no sense of tension.
Get into character.
Script?
No, I heard him clearly.
Everyone is following a script
Mighty Sou definitely called Black Window a "hag".
And....you guys
when I got called a "hag"
weren't you laughing?
If you make fun of the world's final hope...
What is this half-assed rubbish.
Your neck....
What the hell is this!?
What the hell!?
It's not finished yet.
I don't understand anything.
What the hell, it's long too.
Just do it properly please!
It's so long too!
What are you doing?
Choking his neck.
I was told to "Choke it strongly".
Is it this bus?
I'm to busy to deal with random idiots.
Policeman
Koyabu Kazutoyo
What are you people?
Arvengars!
Arvenjars
Ave...
You make me feel like crying.
You cocky bastards.
Questioning commences
Let's start with your real names.
Hey.
Name....
Ironmarn.
This guy's going senile.
Your age?
What's with the half-assed lie?
I really am 45...
You got
a crap load of wrinkles on your face.
Your skin's rolling inwards.
I ask for you age and you give me this bullshit.
Name...
I'm talkin'! You shut up!!
Don't come forward like that.
But you told me to say my name...
Agnes stop it.
I wonder what's up with her? Nothing is done right.
Please get more into your character...
Say your name. Your real name.
Black Window
Age?
I wonder how old I am?
Umm...
Basically around 25
Around 25.
You're a friggin' old lady.
25 years is lower
than half my age.
Ufufufu
Fufufu
Stop laughing about your ages. This ain't a snack bar.
Snack?
You don't need to ask again. You sure like attention.
Woah, what is this?
What the?
It's a snack. Snack as in snack bar.
This isn't a snack bar.
Mighty Sou.
Age?
Might Sou is amazing. He has lived thousands of years.
Cut it with the snack bar talk.
Tiny bits of manzai that aren't funny at all.
I'm a God so I have no age.
The hell are you laughing about? What's with those eyes!?
It's like you're constantly shocked.
How rude. It's my real face.
You two only give lame ass responses, assholes.
Man this guy is rude.
Koyabu, you're rude.
Haven't they been doing this for about an hour?
Next old guy.
What's your favourite song?
Cold dawn (Samui Yoake).
Eh？
Cold Dawn.
Who's song is that?
Go Hiromi.
Mr. Policeman I'm cold.
yeah.
This policeman's having a rough time.
Okay, you're coming to the station.
Arvenjars arrested
You're going together?
Go. Be careful, don't jump out.
Farewell.
Gong!
Ouch!
That was dangerous.
Ahhh that was a shock.
Even before reaching the school,
Travel show filming team
Defenders of Justice Arvenjars
the 5 were facing this many assassins.
Saint Kurobikari School Building
and so, they reached the Gasu Corporation's Saint Kurobikari School, where they will be posted.
The first assassin to appear here was....
Madonna Teacher
Manda Hisako
I'm Manda, the school nurse.
The Madonna teacher lightly checks Hamada's profile.
Check Hamada's profile
Well usually I just wear jeans and a casual shirt.
Manda-san sees this and doesn't laugh.
Hmmmmmmmmm.....
Hisako here...
HAMADA...
was once
the name of an incredibly lame company
incredibly
owned by this very man
, who was once considered to be a fashion leader...
Now he's...
wearing a weird perm
weird
with hairs resembling
that of disgusting pubes...
disgusting
He's so ugly...
So ugly...
He's such an ugly comedian...
Manda-sensei!
Let's stop here!
You're talking too much!
Manda-sensei, let's stop here, please!
Headmaster's Office
When the new teachers go to introduce themselves to the headmaster.
Headmaster of School
Takenaka Naoto
PANG PANG!
HOM CHICA CHICA!
PIYAKO PIYAKO!
SIT DOWN!
That's your desk?
Don't mess with me, you fool!
From beginning to end, he was a high tensioned headmaster.
New Recruit Training Room
Customary jokes took place at the recruit training room where the 5 standby.
What is it this time?
Mysterious panel
A mysterious panel came out of Hamada's drawer.
Composite photo of Hamada+Gorilla
Baby Gorilla
This thing.
GET a luxurious prize with 100 medals
In the corner of the room was a slot machine.
It was a chance to get a luxurious prize but...
Tanaka...
It might come?
Oh nice!
TANAKA
THAI KICK
What! Why!?!
Why! Why!?!
It was set up so that when the faces line up, you are prey to a thai kick.
Black part and the
Red part of the announcement!!
Tanaka!!
Scary, scary, scary!
Don't struggle or it will just hurt more, ok?
OOOUUUCH!!!!
NO MORE!!
Oouchh
Oww
OUCH
OWW
Ouch!
What are you doing rolling around like that?!?
After this!!
And after this...
...was an unreleased event.
A genuine kind of school function begins
Attend the anniversary ceremony for the school's foundation.
The first function that the new teachers attended
was the school's foundation anniversary ceremony.
Let's go everyone!!
The weather's not that good though is it?
It seems a bit cold.
Grounds
Oh, they're doing it.
School students also attend the ceremony
Guidance Officer
Kawashima Akira (Kirin)
And now, we will hold the Gasu Corporation
Gasu Corporation Saint Kurobikari School
Ceremony to Commemorate 100th Year Anniversary
（川島）　これから…。
Saint Kurobikari School's 100th Anniversary Ceremony.
Such a nice voice.
We'll start with
the school's anthem.
Sant Kurobikari School Anthem
Anthem's lyrics feature peculiarities of the founder, Ninomiya Sugajirou
The anthem's lyrics focus on the peculiarities of the school's founder
Ninomiya Sugajirou, a man who suffered from greasy skin.
I would like
to ask our
school's music teacher
to sing this song for us.
When you're ready please.
Singing of the school anthem.
It's totally rock.
This is the school anthem, right?
Giant trailer appears
Huh?
School anthem sung with a live band
Music teacher appears
Music Teacher
Diamond✡Yukai
Yaaaaay!
Nimya Sugajirou
Round faced guys
are never bad guys
Gasu Gasu Corporation
Saint Kurobikari
School
What kinda song is this.
Girls flock
towards
He's totally looking at us.
Suga's grease.
We'll get our hands on
an oil
He looked at me the WHOLE time!
harlem.
Suga's
grease
is 10 times that of a soft-shell turtle.
His face
What is he saying?
is a red mamushi.
Gasu Corporation
Saint
Kurobikari School
Kobayashi Producer
(Sugajiro's habitual phrase)
Kobayashi
when are ya gonna come!
Otomo Producer
Otomo
Hahaha!
Didn't I tell you to cut that!
Uchino
Otomo
Desk Worker Uchino
What's today's soup?
Hahaha!
Nakamura Producer
Sure ain't no match for Yoshinobu!
Yeaaaayyy!
That was long, wasn't it?
(Suga's grease) 10 times that of a soft-shell turtle.
Yeah, the lyrics are properly....
That was an incredible school anthem.
Appearing next is
the school's no.1 Madonna
Haruka-chan
leading the Idol Research Society
who will grace this ceremony
with a song and dance.
Well then, when you're ready.
One, two, three, four!
Heavy Rotation
Things like this are cute.
Woah.
This is what they mean by Haruka-chan?
Waaah!
I want you
Idol Research Society President
Umihara Haruka
I need you
I love you
Inside my head
He must have practiced this heaps!
The blaring music
He practiced properly.
Heavy Rotation
What an idiot!!
Just thinking about your face and voice
You can't
hear his voice at all!!
Makes me go crazy.
I'm so lucky
He put feeling in it.
He put feeling in it!!
to be able to feel this way
I want you
I need you
I love you
He must have practiced hard.
This love that overflows
in around my heart
is on heavy rotation
Heavy rotation
He's an idiot!!
He sang in the end.
That's the worst Haruka it could have been.
He had practiced that a lot.
I wonder why
he sang at the end?
Haruka-chan is currently
receiving offers from
5 different talent production agencies.
However
as she wants to concentrate on school
she has
apparently rejected every single one.
OOOOIII!!
This shows that a student's main duty is to study.
I hope you all put your schooling first, like Haruka-chan.
A drunkard crashes the ceremony
Ya bloody doin' it ay!
Oi suit man!
○△□×☆※…！
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
Old Drunkard
Reiji (Nakagawake)
Bring the guy in charge here!
Umm...mister, mister. Excuse me.
I always
sleep here damn it!
We're in the middle of an important ceremony...
The sky
is my roof, I say!
Please hold him back! Get him out!
○△□×☆※…。
I've beeeen drinkin'
all day long!
Hey you there
watch me prowess at drinkin'!
BWHAHAHAHA！
He didn't drink at all.
What? What?
Nothing.
Ahhh man, my bum hurts.
You guys!
The outdoors sure are good, innit?
'Cept, why you guys
blarin' and bangin' and
playin' all that music
I always sleep.
This old man is tired
I'm gettin' old recently
but I used to work at that trading company, long ago.
But you know what!?
I've ended up like dis before I realised
BWHAHAHAHA！
So he ended up like that before he realised.
Maybe
you should get this guy out of here?
Let's get him out.
Hey, someone get him out.
Hm, yeah. Hm.
It's better if you get him out...
So any o' you guys married yet?
It must be tough bein' married.
Cuz' you gotta go
to IKEA and Costco and stuff aye!!
That place is huge innit. The space.
And even when you go to IKEA
you only end up buyin' this tiny place mat!!
For 1 hours or 2 hours
you walk around there and ya get nothin'!!
How could you after walking around that much?
What do you want!!
Please go back now, my bum hurts.
Have you had enough?
Whaddaya mean "Have I had enough"!?
Only people related to this event are allowed here.
Who do ya thinkk I aam!!
LET GO DAMN IT!!
Somethin's comin'
You're getting arrested.
Here they come.
Patrol car arrives
Here they are.
Here comes my taxi.
I'll go ride this taxi now.
You called one for me?
He'll be like "I'm yo taxi driver Inoue"
??
EAAGHH! EAAGHH!?
Drunk geezer is taken by police
UUGH!?
Eeaarrgh you guys!
Calm down!
Whaddya mean calm down!?
DAMN!!
DAMN!! STOOGE!! IDIOT!!
STOOGE!!
IDIOT!!
DAMN!! STOOGE!! IDIOT!!
There are some strange people.
Yeah, you're right.
Sorry about the disturbances.
I will now read a
congratulatory message sent by a graduate.
Announcement of Congratulatory Message
I congratulate the school for their 100th year
anniversary, and at the same time
I will wish that...
you develop greatly and..
More intruders at the ceremony
Intruders at the ceremony
Hey hey hey hey!
Yes?
What do we have here hmmmm?
What is their objective!?
Female comedians intrude the ceremony!!
Who are you people?
Don't ya know about us?
What?
We are, the delinquent group from the Takarazuka Revue!
Female Comedian Gang
Sumida Hooligans
We're the Sumida Hooligans!
So you're the rumored...
Sumida Hooligans!?
Please go away!!
SHUT UUUPO%∆□#
SHUT UUUPOӾ∆□#
WE'LL CRUSH THIS DAMN SCHOOL!!
Huh?
What did she say?
I have no idea what she said.
Sumida Hooligans
Tsubaki Oniyakko
What do you want?
Sumida Hooligans
Kurosawa Kazuko (Morisanchu)
What the hell are you guys lookin' at!?
Oh for real?
Sumida Hooligans Leader
Sumida Miho (Asian)
Hahaha snot...
This one was tough.
Snot
This is disgusting.
What the hell?
The combination is just too...
You got snot hanging out.
It's stuck on your nostril hair.
Fu Fu
This ain't cool
Of course you'll laugh.
It's gross.
It really is on her nostril hair.
Isn't it on her real nostril hair?
Mm hmm, yes it is.
Seee, Sumida-senpai
They're shit scared!!
I bet you guys have
pissed your pants, haven't ya?
Man, her character is frustrating.
Sumida Hooligans
Barbie (Fall In Love)
Who the heck are they?
I understand. Here I go!
Ohh
Blows breath on his face
I'm sure I held that one in!
You did.
Yamazaki notices something strange with Barbie
Ohhh come on!
Raw ass from cut out shapes
What are you doing?
Stop bein' scared!!
Ohh man, pleeaase!
It's impossible I totally held it in!
I really don't like this.
This is reverse sexual harassment.
It is.
This is totally sexual harassment!
Stop bein' scared!!
I bet they're all virgins!
Surely that's enough
Please leave us alone.
The hell are ya sayin'
We're nowhere near finished!
Sumida orders something to Kurosawa
For real!?
We're gonna use that!?
You guys have made
our senior quite angry it seems!!
In this world, there~
Orders were to give a performance on a mic
was a pole!
OI! BRING THAT POLE, DAMN IT!!
OI, BRING THAT POLE, DAMN IT!!
BRING THAT POLE,  DAMN IT!!
BRING THE POLE!!
Matsumoto Speech
What the hell!!
How many times is she gonna say that?
How many times are ya gonna say that!!
Man she's annoying.
Bring the damn bat!
Clamp the bamboo poles together and go back
TAKE THE POLES BACK  DAMN IT!!
TAKE THE POLES BACK!!
TAKE THE POLES BACK DAMN IT!!
What the hell!?
Even after watching again, I still don't get it.
Her voice isn't that loud either.
The five had attended a 100th year anniversary ceremony full of intruders.
School's 100th Year Anniversary Ceremony
Just a little thinking and leads to this skill!
5-6-5
Instantaneous food praising senryu
They return to their training room and begin a
food praising senryu game to determine their lunches.
Here you go, "Hamburger"! (Japanese meat patty)
Example
Instantaneous food praising senryu
Hamburger
The hamburger with
It was a game where you praise food with senryu poems but...
its dripping meaty juices
it's supreme
Matsumoto....
Here we go!
Example
"Gratin"!
Gratin
Even if I'm sick
I can totally
eat it all
Gratin should be an easy one! (?)
Here we go Hamada-san!
Hamada-san!
"Omurice"!
Omurice
Sitting on the plate
sti-sticking up
it's the omelet-chan
OUT Downtown are horrible!!
Next was Yamazaki's turn at the challenge.
Here we go, Zaki-san!
"Fried Oyster"!
Fried Oyster
When it's deep fried-ied
let's eat loads and loads of it
all together, yeah?
Did you say "when it's deep fried-ied"
When it's deep fried-ied,
let's eat loads and loads of it all together, yeah?
Lunch with bento according to grades
As a result of these strange senryu poems
they have lunch according to how they ranked.
Last place
Rice and takuan (pickled daikon radish)
You can't do stuff like that!
Please sit down and eat it Tamago-Chan
Also, they watched a video that will help students to form a career pathway.
Text
Taxi Driver
Hey driver, can you go
to Roppongi for me?
Did you say Roppongi?
Taxi Driver
Uchida Yuya
Roger that.
Did you say Roppongi?
Yes.
Roger that.
Uchida Yuya makes an unexpected appearance.
Furthermore...
Dear customers...
the captain wold like to give his greetings.
Captain
Uchida Yuya
Thank you for boarding World Airline flight 61.
Assistant Pilot
Shin Onii
I... In foreign countries
various... various... vari... mmmm...
An unexpected collaboration becomes reality
An all too unexpected collaboration became reality
and lead the five to laugh.
And after this
there was another unreleased scene after this.
We, at Gasu Corporation...
have developed an Education Center
Gasu Corporation
Education Center
to aid students leading a better school life.
Ahh this was bad.
Yeah this one.
Let's take a look at their day
Now then, let's take a look at a day in the life of a counselor.
Counselor
Suzuki Akiko
Cooperating with us today will be Suzuki-san and...
Ohnishi Hideko-san.
Counselor
Ohinishi Hideko
Here at Gasu Corporation
we have developed an education center
Gasu Corporation
Education Center
to aid students in leading a better school life.
Ahh this was bad.
Yeah this one.
Let's take a look at their day.
So then, let's take a look at a day in the life of a counselor.
Counselor
Suzuki Akiko
Cooperating with us today will be
Suzuki-san and...
Counselor
Ohinishi Hideko
Ohnishi Hideko-san.
This is the Education Center. How may I help you?
(Guardian)
I will be transferring my son
to your school but...
Yes.
(Guardian)
Could you please
tell me
Yes
whether your school
follows the yutori education method or
the cram schooling method?
Guardian's Question
(School's style of teaching)
At my place
ummmm
it's yutori education.
(Guardian)
What exactly is
yutori education like?
Yes, umm...
We
errr
provi...
provide service to
the yutori people.
(Guardian)
What sort of service is that?
Errr
well
executive
massages and stuff like that.
(Guardian)
What specifically
do you do during that?
Yes.
Umm
we use talcum powder (baby powder)
and
errr
put it on their backs and
trace
trace our fingers along it.
Haven't heard that it a while....talcum powder.
Ahhhh shiiit!
Ouch!
Arrrghh!
I was hoping to get through with out laughing with Jimmy-san.
Hello, this is the Education Center.
How may I help you?
(High School Senior)
I'm a third year senior approaching tests next year
Yes.
and I can't help but feel anxious about these tests.
(High School Senior)
Can you send your feelings
so that I can pass my tests?
Yes.
Question from Student
(Prayer to Pass)
Bura bura bura bura bura bura bura bura bura bura bura bura~
BAM!
Swaaaboon
Zuuubang
Zubang
ZuBAMM
ZzBAMM
ZWUAAAN
BONNNNG
ZUBOING
BUAAAA
GAAAANG
BAASCHAAA
DONGGG
BRIANG!!!
WWYYUUUN
HYUU!!
BONG!!!
That's enough.
HYUU!!!
That's enough...
That is enough, right?
Yeah, enough...
Ow...
What the heck....
Jimmy Ohnishi's VTR
has passed but in no time at all...
Having only just finished with Jimmy's video
the next temptation to laugh came.
You alright everyone?
At this school
there is a teacher who is very popular with the students
and he said he'll let you
amateur teachers observe his class.
So we're gonna go look now.
Observe the class
of the teacher who is popular with students!!
What is this class that is highly rated by the school's students?
3rd Year Group 3 Classroom
There are seats prepared for you at the back.
Teacher not present
Make sure you properly study him okay?
Yes.
Japanese History Teacher
Nakayama Kinni-kun
YAAHH!!
He's way too enthusiastic.
That voice is coming straight from his stomach~.
Japanese History Teacher
Kusano Hitoshi
It did come from his stomach.
Oi
Oi!!
Now then
are you really
going to 'being'
doing a class
or are you not?
SO WHICH IS IT!!
I'LL DOO IIIIIT~!
He said going to 'being'.
Slightly nervous Mr. Nakayama.
Kinni-kun's face.
So, today we'll introduce
how to make udon, a food that
Introduce how to make udon
many people of the Edo period liked.
Yes.
Pot and Katsuo-bushi on standby
What are the doing?
Well apparently
they're popular teachers.
YAAHH!!
You are the most
popular teacher, aren't you?
Ouch!
Jimmy Ohnishi's video and
Jimmy Onishi's VTR (Education Counselor)
Observing a very popular teacher's class
the 'muscle' class was being conducted.
Attending a
staff meeting
The five were also attended a staff meeting.
Vice Chairman
Chariman
Hataka Daikichi (Hakata Hanamaru · Daikichi)
Suzuki Sawa
All the complaints are extremely self centered and unreasonable.
The teachers announced the current news of their class and
among them were teachers with unclear speech.
This is class 3-1's home teacher Tenryu speaking
This is impossible! Impossible impossible impossible!
Homeroom teacher of 3-1
Tenryu Genichiro
And an unexpected event followed after
Gorillaimo and Tekkamen was brought in for fighting.
Goriraimo
Oshima Miyuki (Morisanchu)
Take that Iron Mask off
at once!!
That's right! Hurry up and take that thing of you fool!
Why you!
How dare you do that!?!
Why you! How dare you do that!?!
BAHAHAHA!!!
Eh!?!
Tanaka's wife enters
Tanaka's wife appeared for the first time as an assassin of laughter.
What a shocker!
You two,
what is the meaning of all this fighting?
Tanaka's wife
Kohinata Shie
This bonehead was talking smack about my man.
Huh?
If he's gross and I said he's gross,
then what is wrong with that?!?
He's not gross at all!
Even though he has such thick arm hair,
his head
is still going bald!
What's up with that???
Shut up!!!
It's true that when my man
gets out of the bath,
his head is so bald
that I wonder if he's sick!
But that's fine with me!!
Hey, what are you doing???
What are you doing?!?
Red part of the announcement
Black part
Next, when they visited the school's baddest delinquent
Delinquent student
Matsuko Deluxe
The prize is a rice ball filled with love
Matsuko, who took a great liking to the five
ended up gifting them rice balls.
I'm making this one for you (Yamazaki)
Ah, actually...
You don't want it?
No no no...
You don't want it?!?
That's not it...
Who will be the one...
that will understand my feelings...
Huh!?!
Will you be the one that understands my feelings?
What is this!?!
Come on now!
It kinda felt like it ended a moment ago!
I really thought it was over just now!
Do you guys really think it's THAT funny
to see a bunch of old guys hop around?
A competition event with teachers of rival schools.
A competition event against teachers from rival schools.
OK to laugh but losing representatives will be punished!!
Competition event
Although they were allowed to laugh
the losers of a jumping box battle were to be punished.
Competition event
OK to laugh but losing representatives will be punished!!
He's not that heavy, is he?
His butt touched the vault!!
Endo, who dragged the team down got the Thai kick
In the end, Endo, the member who was expected to be most reliable
dragged the team down to defeat.
A Thai kick was given as punishment.
This is really scary!!
WAAAAAAHH!!!
WAAAAAAHH!!
That really is
"The Asshole Crusher"!
Must be, yeah.
It must indeed hurt badly right now.
Going to a field trip
Finally, the five go to a field trip.
Naturally, traps were set as they traveled.
Arriving at Bus Stop
Eh?
Again?
Why are we stopping here?
Actress
Kimiko Ikegami
Reading a script of a
suspense drama
with Matsumoto as her partner
When Ikegami entered the bus she began to read the
script of a suspense drama with Matsumoto as her partner.
From the back of the bus....
When from the back of the bus...
Sister!
Please stop it already... Let's just give it up!
* Enjoy the show even though they laughed already
We can't defy our destiny even if we run away...
Little sister Kanae
Nakayama Shinobu
Kanae, what are you talking about?
Do you honestly think you could be happy?
Prosecutor
Toyota Maho
...actors continuously appear.
It unfolded just like a real drama.
Detective
Kawahara Sabu
And in the end...
If I build a house one day
Singer for the credits
Akiko Kosaka
...Kosaka Akiko appeared.
She sang the ending song, and the suspense drama concluded.
Suspense drama concludes.
From here is unreleased footage. There were more assassins on the bus.
One danger ends and another begins.
The bus ride becomes even more harsh
The bus ride becomes even more harsh.
Arriving at Bus Stop
That was kinda quick~.
Maybe we arrived?
Arriving at Bus Stop
Hurry up and get on.
Hurry up
Come on, this way.
Okay, quickly quickly.
Gaki no Tsukai - New Face-
Takei Tokuji
It's the "New Face".
Ouch!
Indeed
there was this guy.
Forgot about him.
What are they doing?
Acchan, Toku-chan...
Mom
Koumoto Junichi
Daughter
Acchan
Son
Toku-chan.
today you have an important audition for a drama.
If you succeed at this, you'll be stars of the child acting world!
Auditioning today to be child acting stars
Okay? Did you read the script the director gave you?
Are you okay, Toku-chan?
Speak up honey.
...mmm.
Not good!
His voice barely came out.
Owee ow!
Ow!
I don't get it
a child actor?
Let's try and restrain ourselves.
Firstly, Acchan. Acchan you are
the school's madonna, okay?
Acchan's role is the school's madonna.
And Toku-chan could you please act as
the school's gym teacher who is loved by everyone?
Toku-chan's role is an idol teacher
Ha...ahhh.
These two people fall in love and...
Story of a student and teacher's forbidden love
and they run away together.
A female student and a high school teacher enters a bus.
Ready, start!
Female student
Hey sir
I bet the school
is probably
making a huge fuss now because of what we've done.
Look at that grandpa's face.
And in response to that
the teacher, Toku-chan says...
...I dunno the lines.
Fufu...
I wasn't given the script.
Arrrghh!
Argh!
That hurt.
He said "I wasn't given the script".
Shouldn't you start from there?
You did get the script, right?
I DIDN'T!
Mummy has it and
even Acchan has it too.
Why is it that only Toku-chan
ended up not getting one?
Isn't that strange?
Yeah, that's why I said
"What the hell's going on".
To who?
Oh man, this is getting to me. Crap, crap.
We gave Toku-chan a script one week ago.
Argh!
Ahhh!
He's friggin' lying.
Basically,
this is the situation.
I'm not a professional talent, okay?
I'm working casual as an extra, okay?
"You don't have to do much"
is what they say to me.
How am I supposed to capture what he's saying?
It seems that Toku-chan was directed
about this shoot by his management agency.
That's enough, seriously!
Ouch!
Maybe that's what he was told?
But we live together.
Female student
I was really happy, you know.
Just hold it there Acchan.
Wait, wait.
Hey mom. Mom.
Mom.
That's enough.
Acchan's just continuing on.
What I'm saying is exactly according to the script.
We can't go to the audition like this!
Quickly get off and try once more.
Toku-chan quickly come here
we'll remember it from scratch again.
Come here!
Hurry up and come
practice!!
They didn't end up coming back in.
They left, didn't they?
Yamazaki kept loudly making noises
like "Fuga fuga" next to me.
Did you get hooked to it?
I was hooked with Acchan.
25 minutes pass since departing school
25 minutes pass since departing the school.
The next assassin
to assault them was again a formidable enemy!
The next assassin wasn't
easy to deal with either.
Huh?
What is that!?
Student finds something towards the front
Stop for a second!
Please!
Wait, wait! Stop for a second!
Someone stops the bus...
Up we go.
Jeez,
Akira
Mom!
Chinese restaurant delivery
Maeda Bibari
You forgot your lunch didn't you!
That was totally on purpose.
Delivering her son something he forgot.
Here!
Thanks.
For pete's sake!
Huh? Crap!
I forgot an important text book at home as well.
Well Mom is busy delivering food so bring it yourself.
I'm sorry.
Come on, hurry up!!
Seems like...
...seems like there'll still be another trick.
Hey look, isn't that the lady from the noodle shop?
Maeda Bibari zooming off with a delivery
Huh?
Hahaha...
She was following us all along.
It's the lady from the noodle shop.
Whoa!
Whoaa!
That's dangerous!
Bike explosion accident occurs
What the?
Eh?
Man that scared me~.
What happened?
Whaat?
So was she in an accident?
This is scary.
Despite the horrific accident, she returns to deliveries
Eh?
Bibari-san?
Isn't that Bibari-san?
It's blown right off.
Are you okay? Seriously, your helmet....
Arrrrrghhh . . .
Hahaha...
* Enjoy the show even though they laughed already
Oh arrrghh...
Ow ow ow....
Heaaaahhh....
There's blood dripping out.
Ahhh....
Isn't it better if
you go to the hospital?
I think it'd be better to call them.
Informing shop about the accident
Excuse me...
This is Maeda Bibari but...
(Boss)
What's up Bibari, what's wrong?
I crashed
while on the bike and...
(Boss)
What are ya doin' IDIOT!!
I told you so much to be careful!
(Boss)
You didn't hit anyone did you, you fucking bastard!!
It's solo.
A solo accident.
"It's solo"...
Well yeah, it was solo but...
You should go to the hospital.
I wonder who she's talking to?
Probably the store's boss?
Ouch!
Her boss is scary.
I don't think the boss realizes how hurt you are.
(Boss)
Customers are waiting for their food.
Hurry up and deliver it you IDIOT!!
Yes.
*peep* *peep*
Sigh...
Recommence delivery
They had been pitted against this many
Family heading to a child actor audition
A noodle delivery becomes a traffic accident
assassins during the bus ride.
Whaa~! We're going back through time!
And the five time slip back to the Edo period.
Time slip to the Edo period
Whaa~! We're going back through time!!
The next stage was the world of Edo
A new battle began!!
The man who welcomed the five to the world was that warlord.
Whoa!
Hamada, Matsumoto and Yamazaki.
Everyone, look at this.
This is
the 16th Tokugawa Shogun
Tokugawa
Kogemitsu.
Tokugawa Kogemitsu
16th Tokugawa Shogun
He's the 16th shogun.
Kogemitsu was 'that', you know.....errr...
a great shogun who left his mark on history.
He was a grand shogun who etched his name into history.
For example.This is just an example but,
For example. This is just an example but,
He defeated an army of  50,000 peopleall by himself
he defeated an army of 50,000 peopleall by himself
He defeated an army of  50,000 people all by himself
They call it the Battle of Kogehazama.
(Kogehazama means "Burned Valley" alluding to Suga's tanned skin)
and is a reference to the Battle of Okehazama
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Battle_of_Okehazama
Tokugawa Kogemitsu's Achievements
The Battle Of Kogehazama
In order to protect those who are tanned, he made
In reference to Tokugawa Tsunayoshi's "Law of Compassion",
which protected humans and animals against cruelty.
Check here for info: http://www.jstor.org/discover/10.2307/2384718?uid=3737536&uid=2129&uid=2&uid=70&uid=4&sid=21102414035667
the Laws of  Compassion For Tanning Salons
Tokugawa Kogemitsu's Achievements
Law Of Compassion For Tanning Salons
And errr.... that other one.
Sorry um.... that thing. that thing.
Sorry um.... that thing. That thing.
Come on!
Can you at least stop waving your arms around?
At least the arm waving.
Rule
Additional
In this era an army of ninjas will
come and smack their bottoms.
Woah! You're right!
They're ninja!
Ninja Ninja
Please tell us properly.
And that one err....
Law Of Compassion For Tanning Salons.
It's
that...
um...
...
well
grease...
Sorry.
Just stop your arm waving!
I have no idea what that waving is meant to mean.
It's so pointless!
Cough
And that thing... is what people used when they had problems regarding greasy skin
They put their problems in the Gleaming Box.
Tokugawa Kogemitsu's Achievements
In reference to the "suggestion box" that was used by
Tokugawa Yoshinobu to collect opinions of commoners.
It's a "Gleaming/Shining box" here because of Suga's reflective tanned skin.
Gleaming Box
Impressive, isn't he?
In order to blend in with the Edo Period
They change into appropriate clothing.
Once the five finished changing into clothes that suit this period...
The First Assassin
Appears
...the first assassin duly arrives.
Shimizu no Jirocho
Shimizu no Jirocho is a famous gangster from this time. Check link for more info (if you want)
http://tinyurl.com/pap57sc
Endo Toshihide
Shozo
So you had come to play in Edo as well then?
Him again!?
Jirocho Family
Endo Kiyomi (Mother)
Endo's parents and young brother came
in the guise of the Shimizu no Jirocho family.
fdgdfgdfg
Endo Junji (Young Brother)
My surname is Endo, and given name, Junji.
Suddenly...
When suddenly, the father, Toshihide said...
OhI had forgottenthere is one more person.
Oh I had forgottenthere is one more person.
Oh I had forgotten there is one more person.
Huh?
HeeyCome on out!!
Heey Come on out!!
What?
Who is it?
You gotta be kidding.
Eh?
I really have no clue.
Mori no Ishimatsu
Chiaki (Ex-Wife)
She's here!!
Mori no Ishimatsu was an assassin, and a follower of Jirocho.
Oniiit has been a while since we last met!
Onii it has been a while since we last met!
Miraculous costarring of ex-wife and husband's family.
Endo's parents and his ex-wife, Chiaki,had miraculously co-starred together.
Onii it has been a while since we last met!
Terminator Comes To The Edo Period
The next assassin...
...had come in pursuit of someone who had time slipped to Edo, just as the five had done.
He was, the Terminator.
Prohibitted
Terminator
Itao Itsuji
You're too old to be doing this.
Introduction of Tokugawa Kogemitsu's bronze statue
Shimizu Jirouchou Family
Itao Terminator
Drawer ・ Sugar Cup
Drawer ・ Money Box Explodes
Drawer ・ Ventriloquist Doll (Hama-chan)
And from here is unreleased footage. The five had encountered a gruesome incident.
Huh?Everyonethere's a bunch
Huh? Everyonethere's a bunch
Huh? Everyone there's a bunch
of people gatheredover there.
of people gathered over there.
Finally, we see some people.
Yeah, there they are.
Seems like they pulled out a drowned body.
Was it suicide?
Maan, I don't wanna see that.
A drowned body is quite...
Thisera must have had
This era must have had
things like this happening.
They must have.
My, oh, my, you were right.
Drowned Bodies x 3
Tanaka, Endo, Yamazaki, Hamada and Matsumoto. Can you line up in that order?
?
ddfhdfdfhdfdfh (they're just yelling)
Magistrate Court Officials Appear
Tragedy befalls the drowned bodies
while being checked for life
Who Is The Identity Of the Court Official!?
Playing Games With Geisha
The Shogun, Tokugawa Kogemitsu Appears
They're drowned bodies.
Wawawawa
Gosh, three bodies?
Huh,Is it moving?
Huh, Is it moving?
?
Magistrate Court Officials Appear
Move, move, move, move!
Magistrate Court Official
They pulled out three corpses?
Do you know their identities?
We've been told that they have no clue.
You're unfamiliar faces but
you guys might know
these drowned bodies so
could you check their faces once?
I understand.
Checking The Identities Of Drowned Bodies
I'm don't think I'll know.
We'll start with this guy.
Drowned Body 1
Ebisu Yoshikazu
Crotch Is Visible
Prohibited
Please stop that.
It's poking out.
(Your dick) is poking out!!
Ahhhh ouch-ouch-ouch
You're moving too.
Prohibited
(Your dick) is showing!!
He's the one that's OUT!!
He's the one that's OUT, not us.
This guy is the Edo's most
dullest manga artist.
It's no surprise that he's dead.
Prohibited
And, this guy...
Drowned Body 2
Sakai Toshiya
He's Edo's most untalented traveling actor.
He tried selling himself as a funny bald man character but
that ended quite miserably.
She's rude.
Drowned Body 3
Yamane Yoshiaki
Oh this guy is...
He's Edo's most boringtraveling comedian.
He's Edo's most boring traveling comedian.
His comedy partner also has a creepy face but
this guy's creepiness is just plain insane.
These guysdon't even move a muscle.
These guys don't even move a muscle.
What's with this guy?
It was the part where
you shouldn't move the most.
Be a professional.
What do you find so funny!!
Isthis guy dead?
Is this guy dead?
Checking For Life Of Drowned Bodies
Life Checking Item
Jutte
Are you dead?
Are you dead!?
He doesn't move at all.
Prohibited
Crotch Is Clearly Shown
This ain't cool.
That's enough!
You can't do that!
Not to a dead body!
You'll be cursed.
You're going to get cursed.
He doesn't move at all!
He doesn't move at all.
Neither do you.
Prohibited
You can't do stuff like that!
Jutte In The Ass
Poor guy!
Are you dead?
Isn't asking the question
"Are you dead?", strange as well?
Asking, "Are you dead?", is just strange.
They are dead.
They're dead.
They don't move at all.
Yeah, cuz they're dead.
He's shivering.
Why is his butt like that?
Is he cold?
He's cold andscared and...
He's cold and scared and...
It's every typeof shiver a human can do.
It's every type of shiver a human can do.
They don't move at all.
Bring THAT thing!
What the hell?
Life Checking Item
Cold Water
They don't even budge.
It's cold there so...
Here I go
He's obviously alive!!
He revived!
He totally just revived.
He'sdefinitely alive.
He's definitely alive.
Thanks for your help, guys.
Prohibited
He hasn't stopped shivering.
Look at his bottom.
We witnessed something awful.
Nobody shoulddrown themselves.
Nobody should drown themselves.
Intro To Tokugawa Kogemitsu's Bronze Statue
Shimizu no Jirocho Family
Itao Terminator
Drawer ・ Sugar Cup
Drawer ・ Money Box Explodes
Drawer ・ Ventriloquist Doll "Hama-chan"
The five had tastedthe anguish of drowned bodies.
The Three Dead Bodies
The five had tasted the anguish of drowned bodies.
Edo's New Recruit Training Room
The training room existed even though the era changed
and, of course, so did the drawer tricks.
A Ventriloquist Doll
Resembling Someone Familiar
In Matsumoto's drawer wasa ventriloquist doll resembling someone familiar.
In Matsumoto's drawer was a ventriloquist doll resembling someone familiar.
You can ask him anything you want!
How old are you?
SHHHUT UP YOU BASTAAARD!!
Where did you come from?
FUCK YOUUU!!
You're cute.
I'LL KILL YOU!!
Your favorite food.
BASTAAARD!!
Scary!!
Edo's City Center
In the middle of exploring Edo's city.
Oh?
It's a Daimyo's procession.
Hey, it's a Daimyo's procession.
Daimyo's Procession
They encounter a Daimyo's procession.
You Cannot Cut Across A Daimyo's Procession
It is a law that you definitely cannot cut across a Daimyo's procession but...
A Small Girl Cuts Across The Daimyo's Procession
Insolent fool!
Young girl!
A child who broke the law was about to get punished
and her father hurriedly ran over
Girl's Father
Musaka Naomasa
and bowed for forgiveness.
Shut your mouth!
Behead both parent and child!!
Sudden Separation of Parent and Child
The sudden separation of parent and child...
enveloped the scene with a mournful air.
Keep on living, my girl.
When suddenly...
Daddy!
CARNIVAL!!
SHOW TIME!!
Happy Boy (Daimyo)
Okada Keisuke
Hey, I'm here baby!
That's enough of him!
Appears On An Anachronistic Robot
Happy Boy appears on an anachronistic robot.
Comedy  is all about timing of pauses!
Comedy is all about timing of pauses!
Please excuse me  for the slightly slow paced sense of things!
Please excuse me for the slightly slow paced sense of things!
Court of Law
At the court of the magistrate's office...
Takeuchi Riki
Toyama Saemon no Jou
...they witnessed three grand trials.
Doctor Who Repeatedly Sexually Harasses Oiran
Villains of Edo, Number 1
Trial number 1,
involved a doctor who repeatedly sexually harassed Oiran.
Bandit Thai Kick Punishment
Judgment Towards Perv-Doctor
The seemingly remorseless perv-doctor...
...was sentenced to receiving a bandit's Thai kick.
This would hurt!
Ahhh God damn it!
That one would have hurt!
This would hurt!
This is too funny!
Fake Ikkyu Who Cons The Townsfolk
Criminals of Edo, Number 2
Trial number 2,
involved a fake Ikkyu who conned the townsfolk.
A Real Ikkyu Should
Be Able To Reenact Various  Famous Scenes...
If he's the real Ikkyu
he should be able to passionately reenact various famous scenes.
The scene in the noodle shop where Goro,
as played by Tanaka Kunie, yelled his famous line.
Kita No Kuni Kara
The scene from the drama, "Kita no Kuni Kara",
when Goro
The Children
Are Still In The Middle
Of Eating, Aren't They!
as played by Tanaka Kunie, yelled out that famous line.
Kita No Kuni Kara
Famous Line Said At Almost Closing Noodle Shop
The air's coldness and the noodle's warmth.
Noodles sure do taste great when it's cold, don't they!!
Is he angry?
Also...
101st Proposal
The Scene Where Tatsuro, played by Takeda Tetsuya
Jumps In front of A Truck And Yelled A Famous Line
That scene from the drama, "101st Proposal",
I
Will Not Die!
when Takeda Tetsuya jumped in front of a truck and yelled that famous line.
101st Proposal
Famous Line Said After Jumping In Front Of Truck
That's dangerous, dangerous, dangerous
That's dangerous, dangerous, dangerous.
101st Proposal!!
He said the show title.
The Next  Man...
Who'd have guessed that the next one was...
Guard
Eh!?
Crouch!
Crouch down!
Person To Be Put on Trial Was Endo
To his surprise, Endo was to be put on trial!
Endo, Who Continued To Send Messages To Lady He Co-Starred With
Criminals of Edo, Number 3
He was alleged to have continued to persistently
send mail to a lady he co-starred with.
The Content Of Mail Was Revealed
With Family And Ex-Wife Present
The content of those mails was revealed in front of his family.
send
Received Mail
From: Kokoriko Endo-san
"Hey, I want your photo
Can you send me a recent photo
of you??"
"Awwww!
a little naughty pweeese! Hurry uuuup"
Endo Shozo
Misa-san
Hey, I want your photo, just for me, pweeese.
Can you send me a recent photo of you>>>
Awww! Your photo pweeeese.
I'll be waiting for it.
I want something a little naughty pweeeese.
I haven't heard about this!
Naturally, Endo received divine punishment.
Endo ReceivedDivine Punishment
Ass Cannon Punishment
Judgment Towards Endo
He was sentenced to the "Ass Spray Cannon"
Guard
What?
Today I'm gonna cause
Egashira 2:50
Text Top
a revolution in Edo, baby!!
HERE I GO!!
Aww hell no!
I'd rather die!
That'd totally suck.
In this way, Endo's evil doings were punished.
Fire Fighting Groups Get In A Confrontation
Working As Teacher
13 hrs 30 mins
A confrontation erupts
between fire fighting groups of Edo.
The five
go to them as teachers, in order to mediate. However....
....they were unable to.
Negotiations Breakdown It Becomes A Clash Of Bodies
It became a clash of bodies, with their honor and pride on the line.
They attempt to eat Miso flavoured udon
while sitting on a cushion that suddenly explodes.
It looks hot.
He's not eating very successfully.
Scary!
Until Explosion
Come on! Guzzle it down!
They then meet Terminator for the second time and...
Terminator'sTarget Becomes Clear
...the identity of the person he had pursued to Edo became clear.
I'll be Back
Oh!!
Henmi Mari
Villager
He was looking for the villager, Henmi Mari.
Pursues Henmi And Fires Gun Wildly
What's happening?
He's shooting somewhere totally different.
Time it properly!
It's not in sync at all!
Dang, he sucks at shooting.
And after this was unreleased footage!
Finally...
...the shogun had appeared!
Finally, Tokugawa Kogemitsu Appears
They Experience Ozashiki Games!!
The unreleased footage
involved them being summoned by the shogun
ruler of this era, Tokugawa Kogemitsu
Are people who time slipped here allowed to meet him?
Ozashiki
This is the ozashiki that Master Kogemitsu always comes to enjoy himself.
Please sit in the order of Tanaka, Endo, Yamazaki, Matsumoto and Hamada.
Who art thou?
Umm...we've come to meet with Tokugawa Kogemitsu.
Wakabayashi Masayasu
Audrey
Chief Retainer
So ye art
the people rumored to have come from the future?
That's right.
Master Kogemitsu has been greatly looking forward
to meeting all of you.
Well then I shall now
call Master Kogemitsu for you.
Master Kogemitsu Master Kogemitsuuu!!
This is the 16th Shogun, Master Tokugawa Kogemitsu
16th Shogun
Tokugawa Kogemitsu
Suga Kenji: Nihon Television Deputy Chief Producer (Concurrently) CP
16th Shogun
Tokugawa Kogemitsu
Suga Kenji: Nihon Television Deputy Chief Producer (Concurrently) CP
It is an honor to meet you today.
As a token to symbolise our friendship
We have something called a swim suit photo album, featuring
naked girls from the future...
Bring it over.
Master Kogemitsu is  pleased about this!!
Master Kogemitsu is pleased about this!!
When this top knot stands up
it means his highness is in good spirits.
No, no, no.
Then...
...the princess of the Kogemitsu clan makes an appearance.
Kogemitsu Clan's Princess Appears
Popular Actress
Just who is the princess's identity?
The Princess's Identity Is That Popular Actress
Terminator Returns!!
She is Master Kogemitsu's princess.
I will now be calling for her
but be careful not to offend her.
Princess!
Kogemitsu Clan's Princess Appears
Mizuno Miki
Princess
This is her royal highness, Princess Miki.
Beautiful, is she not?
Well then.
We shall now get you to play some
Geisha games that Master Kogemitsu loves so much.
Geisha ladies enter!!
She's here.
My name is Naomi-yakko.
Watanabe Naomi
Geisha
I am pleased to make your acquaintance.
I am Haruka-yakko.
Minowa Haruka
Harisenbon
Geisha
I am pleased to be able to meet you all.
I am Haruna-yakko.
Kondo Haruna
Harisenbon
Geisha
Thank you for coming to visit us today.
Rola
Geisha
I am Rola-yakko
Fu
fu
My charm point
Heeheehee
I am Maji-yakko.
Urgh!
My charm points are...
Majima Shigeki
Geisha
...my lips!
Please enjoy yourselves at your leisure.
Yes!!
Why did you say "Yes"?
Why did Rola say "Yes"?
Well then let uscommence the geisha games.
Well then let us commence the geisha games.
Could the geisha please sit behind the men from the future.
Fu fu fu fu
Well then...
...in his game that you will now play with the geisha,
the most dismal player will receive a special punishment.
Geisha Games
Most Dismal Player Will Receive Punishment
Let's begin with impersonations!
Impersonations From Any Time Or Place
Princess Miki Joins Too, To Play With 11 Members
Princess Miki joins as well
and they play an impersonation game with 11 players.
We shalt do our best!
Theme
Kuwata Keisuke Impersonation And Saying Something Red
Say something as Kuwata Keisuka that is red
The theme was to say something red with a Kuwata Keisuke impersonation.
Princess Miki's turn.
Say Something Thing Red As Kuwata Keisuke
Theme
Ready....
begin!
Che Cherryyyy
This is from the song "Ellie My Love" by Kuwata Keisuke's band, Souther All-Stars.
Well then, next person please.
Say Something Thing Red As Kuwata Keisuke
POST BOX!
What did you say?
"Post box".
Say Something Thing Red As Kuwata Keisuke
Theme
Well then, next person.
*&^%*
What the hell is that!!
A "Louisiana Craw Fish"
Next person.
Say Something Thing Red As Kuwata Keisuke
Theme
Chouchin
You're good!!
Whoa!
What did you say, Yamazaki?
Chouchin
Oh, a chouchin (Japanese paper lantern).
Say Something Thing Red As Kuwata Keisuke
Theme
Tomato
Sorry, what did he say?
He said "Tomato".
I can't understand!
We didn't even...
We didn't laugh.
Say Something Thing Red As Kuwata Keisuke
Theme
"#@#%@"
I said "Sun".
Say it again like you did before.
Fu  Fu Fu
Whatever you said had 5 letters!!
Surely I was fine!
Surely I don't need to be hit!
Did you say "Sun"?
"Sun", correct?
Say Something Thing Red As Kuwata Keisuke
Theme
I could not catch that.
I said "Torii".
You said "Torii"?
Say it so that we will understand.
"#$##^^&"
Chili powder? Indeed it is red.
Once more.
"#$@@@&*"
I said "Paprika".
You totally changed it.
I did not change it.
Didn't you?
Next person.
Red Pickled Ginger
I heard that one
I heard it.
That's fine.
It's not about whether it sounds like it or not.
That one would've hurt.
Say Something Thing Red As Kuwata Keisuke
Theme
The next person, Rola-yakko.
Ketchup.
You could've tried harder.
That was completely just Rola.
I will now announce who will be punished.
Tanaka!
Chosen For Punishment!
Tanaka
The punishment will be the Shaolin kung fu expert,
Princess Miki's Thai Kick!
Kung Fu Expert ・ Princess Miki's Thai Kick
Punishment
Come to the front.
I'm sick of getting Thai kicks all the time!!
Seiya!
AHHH THAT HURTS!!
AHH THAT HURTS!!
THAT HURTS.
THAT HURTS!!
My ass has been hurting all day.
Master Kogemitsu had appeared
Tokugawa Kogemitsu's Geisha Games
and some strange geisha games had taken place.
Next up...
Work As Teacher
Hours
GOD DAMN!!
Magistrate Court Official
Chono Masahiro      Barges In
Hey!
Tragedy befalls Yamazaki while observing the Oiran's dance.
So you won't come voluntarily huh!?
Nezumi Kozo's Portrait Picutre
The Magistrate's Court Official, Chono,
appeared with the portrait of the great thief, Nezumi Kozo, in his hand.
What's your problem.
Let
go of this!!
Crap, that hurt!
With no way to escape, Yamazaki....
Here I go!
Yes!!
Punishment Slap Unleashed!!
...became prey to Chono's slap again this year.
His face is all twisted.
GOD DAMN!!
Let's go.
And now for unreleased footage.
That man returns!
Owww...
What does he mean?
"Do something funny"?
Oh!?
Excuse me!
I'm being chased!
Henmi Mari Changed Costumes
What's wrong?
Why're you dressed like that?
I'm being chased by the Terminator!
Oh, wha..what?
A motorbike is coming.
Terminator Appears
Oh!?
Excuse me!
I'm being chased!
Henmi Mari Changed Costumes
What's wrong?
Why're you dressed like that?
I'm being chased by the Terminator!!
Oh, wha..what?
A motorbike is coming.
Terminator Appears
Everyone get onto the bridge!
Oh no! What should I do!
This way.
Everyone go up here!
She ran away.
Is she okay?
Henmi Escapes Into The River
No way!
Oh maan...
That's gotta be so cold!
What's she doing?
Henmi In A Life Threatening Pinch
Wow.
Wait, wait, wait...
Where is he shooting?
That wasn't even close to hitting.
He sucks at shooting.
He can't hit her at all.
So she's gonna come back out, after all that?
It hit him.
Henmi's Shots All Hit The Target
Oh wow.
He doesn't get it on target at all.
That Terminator doesn't hit her at all.
On Screen Text Part 1 On Screen Text Part 2
He got beaten?
Terminator Fatally Wounded?
Huh?
Whoa, that's dangerous.
Terminator Is A Fireball
What the? No way!
What are they doing?
Terminator Dies
Mari ran away.
What the hell!?
Look at them all come.
Terminator-san died, didn't he.
He parked his bike quite far away too.
The five had witnessed Terminator's shocking death.
Itao Terminator
The Excursion Ends
They Change Back Into Appropriate Attire
The excursion came to an end.
The changed back into clothes appropriate for a teacher
Ride The Bus  And Time Slip To Modern Era
and time slipped from the Edo Period, to the modern era!
Since Beginning Work As Teacher:  17 Hours
As soon as they returned to modern times,
they attended a PTA meeting that included the staff.
Attended a PTA Meeting
Please begin.
Everyone
May I speak about Hamada?
Oh yes, sure.
Hamada Masatoshi Secret Info
Story of his stupidity...
They then begin to talk of and episode of Hamada's stupidity.
Hamada and Higashino do a show in Osaka
Info Provider
Higashino Koji
Ah yes.
called "Gobu Gobu", where they wander around towns.
Well Hamada was being egocentric
and said "I don't want to walk very much".
So the staff carried him to the location of the opening scene
by station wagon.
Then they open the doorand Hamada gets off.
Then they open the door and Hamada gets off.
and then they shoot the show.
And at the end of the shooting
a station wagon will come and Hamada will get on.
Every time  he gets off and gets on the car
Every time he gets off and gets on the car
he bangs his head,  apparently.
Every time!
Can't Be Scared Enthusiastic Teachers
The final trick was the
"Can't Be Scared Enthusiastic Teachers"
A fairly  big lady with long hair
A fairly big lady with long hair
may be here so be careful.
What are you on about?
Secret Prank in..
No idea.
You don't make sense.
This was really creepy.
Gigantic Sadako + A Gang Of Sadakos
That was scary.
Successfully Rescued Fujiwara
This was everything from Can't Laugh: Enthusiastic Teachers 24hrs.
Newspaper Company
Hotel Man
Spy
Airport
Sunplaza Nakano
Tsunku
Daiji Man Brothers
Okuda Tamio
Every year, a big guest sings our ending theme.
Last Year December
This time, it was this man who volunteered to take on this job.
Fujii Fumiya
Year
His famous song, "True Love" will change its shape and feature at the end of the show.
Does He Enjoy The Show?
However...
...how much does he know about this show?
I watch it every year but...
I watch it around when it's time for flower watching.
Around April.
He looks at the lyrics
and says the he is slightly disappointed to have the jokes revealed to him.
However...
...the color of his eyes change as he stands in front of the mic
and that great song was born.
TRUE LOVE: The Gaki no Tsukai Version
When
I
look
back
you
were
al
ways
lau
ghing
With
on
ly
that
wig
on
all
the
time
I
on
ly
be
lieved
Far,
far
dis
tant
leng
da's
out
burst
was
a
must
laugh
ther
year
has
pass
ed.
We
must
al
ways
dream
of
a
fu
ture
fill
ed
with
laugh
ter
It's done.
Recording Finishes And...
My wife was worried.
Saying "Is it okay? To do something like this."
I'm quite comfortable with it now  so I'm fine.
I'm quite comfortable with it now so I'm fine.
Well.
Yes.
We had quite a lot this year.
Yes, you're right.
Yeah.
Yes.
If you see this
you can understand that this wasn't cut because it wasn't funny.
Oh, yes, yes.
Yes.
So, Matsumoto-san. This year...
No, no, I'm not worthy.
How are you gonna end it?
That's Great Lord Hamada's job.
Why the hell!?
It's not my responsibility!
The Nihon TV staff all moved in closer.
No, that's his role.
They call you the God of Yoshimoto though.
You're called a God.
You idiot!
Whatever, wrap up the show...
...Tsukitei-san.
You gotta be kiddin'!
Please wrap up the show.
STARTING FROM THE MORNING!!
NEXT YEAR!
I'LL DO MY BEST AGAAAAIN!
Piece of trash.