Are their hearts connected? Meet up without smartphones
The rule: Think of a place using the hint on the card, and try to meet up
I'm in Sancha
Sancha? ...
He went to the Tsutaya in Sancha
The first time, despite Tanaka's dawdling,
they were able meet up in 3 hours 43 minutes
The 2nd time, Downtown met up after the first hint
The challenge ended in 3 hours and 32 minutes
And now they do this again for the 3rd time
Will they be able to meet up?
5 seconds till start
5, 4, 3, 2 ...
3rd ever Gaki no Tsukai CHIKI CHIKI
Are their hearts connected? No smartphones meet up!
Even the count guy was too loud
Hamada's a bad influence on him
And he's a bad influence on Hamada
This is the 3rd time we're doing this
I thought we could make this one "The Movie"
That would be a pain in the ass
Perhaps even in 3D
Tanaka has to try hard this time
For real man
Even if it's on purpose, he sucks
Yup
Nobody thinks it's funny
I'm not
I'm not fooling around, I'm trying my best
It's really lame dude
This series, and the "I Think This Suits You",
I really hate them
I take both of them seriously
But it's great, how you draw in the audience like that
That's how you got the job on 'ZIP!'
This October Tanaka will be a ZIP! regular panelist
That's how?
Congrats, congrats
What's Endo gonna do when 'Ougon Densetsu' ends?
TN: Ougon Densetsu is a program hosted by Tanaka & Endo
Tanaka I'm counting on you man
I'll do my best
My next gig is at the Kokura Horse Racecourse
You're going there by yourself?
Yup
Can I come with you?
Why? Just why?
Can we know the first hint?
The hint for the first place, is...
This
A Shop With A Long Line
There's so many places that fit!
Really?
Yeah, yeah there are
Please don't go to some far off place for the first one
That's what messes up
You know, just yesterday,
I saw a place with a huge line while driving through
And it was a famous place
It's been on different TV shows
You probably have experience from hosting 'Hirunandesu'
I have no idea
Well then, let's get in our taxis
They begin at 3:05PM
They all head to a store they think has a long line
Matsumoto has been the fastest to meet up in the past. Where will he go?
Musashi
Let's go to the Musashi in Shinjiku
Matsumoto heads to the famous Ramen place Musashi in Shinjiku
You know, probably...
Like Tanaka, actually,
Tanaka and Hamada ... probably have no idea
I have no idea
As expected
What's that supposed to mean?
Honestly, I can't think of any definitive place
As Matsumoto expected, these two can't think of a store that fits
And Endo, being informed, might go to place we have no idea existed
Towards Ometosando, there's this really, like famous, Pancake store that you line up for
And as expected, Endo picks a place popular with youngsters that other's probably won't choose
The one I have hope for is Yamasaki
Since I live in Osaka, whenever I come to Tokyo I usually make a choice,
Either somewhere in Shinjuku, near NTV, or Jinbocho
Usually somewhere near those places
Within those, in Shinjuku there's this place that you always have to line up for
In Shinjiku?
Like Matsumoto, Hosei heads towards Shinjuku
Will these 2 be able to meet up?
Meanwhile, Tanaka...
He was still at the Kojimachi studio
When we had that shoot for Ryuchell,
There was like this Sweets shop near there
That's the one place I can think of
I don't know where it is though
Tanaka heads to a shop in Omotesando he remembers from a shoot last month
Do you think you'll recognise the area when we get closer?
I think so
But ... I don't remember what they sold
Cause, there were young people lining up,
I think it was a Sweets shop
So in that case, I think Endo, maybe he's been there for Hirunandesu
Maybe he though of that place, or he's been there on location,
I think it's that sort of place
I think it's probably a sweets shop
Will Endo and Tanaka meet up @ Ometosando?
Meanwhile, Hamada still hasn't thought of a place to go
Last time,
Last time, on some shoot we did,
Maybe it was in Roppongi,
After we ate sushi, wasn't there a line at some place outside?
There was
What was that, what store was that?
In fact, on location in a previous episode,
There's so many people lined up
Woah, it's packed
What is that for?
Coincidentally, all 5 members saw a store with a long line
It was a shaved ice place
Shaved ice?
That's the only place I can think of
We all saw it
Roppongi
Head to Roppongi please
There was a line there, right?
Yes there ... was
What was that?
What was that reply? Now I'm doubting myself
There was a line though
There was right?
Finally, all 5 have decided on a location
Mastumoto - Hosei, and Endo - Tanaka could possibly meet up
However, there is one unsure member among them
If this was Osaka I'd be sure
There's a pancake store,
Hawaiian pancakes
A huge line for it
Eggs.. Eggs something
I waited 1.5 hours with my wife to get pancakes
I didn't get it at all
1.5 hours just for pancakes
I don't get it honestly
We're heading towards Shinjiku though
I mean I don't know what the pancake store is
You know just now, I thought of a place,
They line up outside [REDACTED] right?
Oh that's true
Let's go to [EXPUNGED]
I think I've been there with Matsumoto
Yeah, sorry, let's go to !@#!$!@#
Meguro, let's go to Meguro
I'll meet someone at this place
Hosei changes his location to a famous Ramen place in Meguro
In fact, Matsumoto also ...
There's one place ... One place that interests me
Yup,
In Nakame, I think it's Nakame
[*******], that place
There's huge lines outside there
He's already said that famous ramen place,
They're still headed towards Musashi in Shinjiku
There is one more unsure member
What should I do?
If I go ... to the pancake store,
Like most people would say that's the right idea
But it's about the other members
Let's go to a place where guys would go
Endo changes his destination
From a youthful choice, to a guy's choice
What is the store he chose?
Will any of them be able to meet?
I thought you guys would understand this!
subbed by senor_wristband
There! Somebody's there!
Exactly right?!
Matsumoto was the first to arrive
He waits and prays for someone else to come
I guess that's right
TN: Matsumoto did an ad campaign for Yu-Pack; That's him in the poster
TN: His slogan was "Baka Majime" (Stupdily Serious)
It's cause I'm Stupidly Serious
Those guys are just stupid
Thank you
Hamada then also arrives
Look at the line
See!
The line is so long
That's a line
It would be weird for them not to show up
Hosei and Endo both arrive to their destinations
Only Tanaka, the one who doesn't know his store's name, is left
I don't properly remember it
I might be wrong, It might not be here
He wandered around looking for the shop
Ah there it is. Here, here
Eggs ... Eggs & Things
This is it. See, look at the line.
And? There's nobody here
There's nobody here
Time's up
Time's up, of course
Time's Up!
There's nooobody here
The 5 call each other, to see where they're at
Hello, this is Matsumoto
Hold on, Tanaka. Tanaka where are you?
I'm in Urahara, at a pancake store, Eggs & Things
You'll get a Double Hand Slap later, alright?
Double Hand Slap?
Who the hell would go to Urahra?
Pancakes, you idiot?
Hamada and I would never go there
How am I supposed to know stuff like that
In my entire life, since birth, I've eaten at most 4 pancakes
So little
Just 4?
Alright alright, Matsumoto where are you then?
I'm at the head store for Musashi in Shinjiku
There's always a line here!
I see...
Yeah, I did say that. Matsumoto-san and Musashi
The thing is though not a single person is lined up here
I had the same idea as you Matsumoto-san
I thought of a ramen place too
Eh? Where, where?
I went to a ramen place. [!@#%] in Meguro
I knew it!
You went there after all
Eh? You thought of here too?
I did for real
Hosei-san, Hosei-san!
I'm at [EXPUNGED], near you at [REDACTED]
That place is really popular yeah
Hamada is the problem here
Uh oh. Uh oh.
Where are you?
Well first off, I'm in Roppongi
I couldn't think of a place at first. Remember we went to that Sushi place for that episode?
After we left we saw that huge line, remember?
Oh yeah, they were lining up
The shaved ice place right?
Shaved Ice place
There's no way we'd think of that
What's the name of the store?
What's the name?
Eh? "yelo" "kakigori"
"yelo"
Nobody knows it
He's definitely made it up
It's the first time you've been there isn't it?
It's gotta be a ramen store! Hamada! Tanaka!
Young people are good too
We've all been to this place
I totally get Yamasaki's idea
Right?
There's also the distance. We had to start in Kojimachi,
I thought you guys would understand this!
You guys really are clueless
We're all clueless
Let's get the next one, let's do it
Let's meet at the next one
That shaved ice place, from last time ...
I don't know if that's the right idea
If he doesn't even know the name, why would anyone else go there
They told me "No way!" after all
"It's gotta be a ramen place!"
58 minutes from the start
They gather themselves, and look at the next hint
Hotel
This is .. It's too general
There's over 2000 hotels within reach of the members
This is a pretty tough hint
The key is to consider how the other members will think about this
Those ... impoverished comedians can't stay in nice hotels anyways
Hotel Yoko!
Let's go! We'll meet at this one
Why did Matsumoto choose Hotel Yoko?
The people watching TV probably won't get this,
Akasaka Yoko,
Yoshimoto was located in that neighbourhood,
Pretty much everyone stayed at that hotel
It became an Ibis after
I've stayed in Akasaka Tokyu a lot in the past too
Matsumoto chooses Akasaka Yoko, a hotel many comedians stayed at in their youth
This is so hard!
However. However,
Back when I entered Yoshimoto. I think 20-25, maybe closer to 30 years ago,
There was a hotel that every comedian that came from Osaka stayed at
This is a hotel DownTown would really remember.
Alright, let's aim for DownTown.
I've got 2 ideas
1 of them,
When DownTown came here from Osaka, when they still didn't have a place in Tokyo,
there's a hotel they stayed at often
I've heard a lot about Akasaka Tokyu
Wasn't it Yoko?
Oh yeah Yoko. So Yoko, or,
In Roppongi, what was that place called,
Ibis
Well let's head towards Akasaka
Hosei and Endo both head towards that historic Yoshimoto hotel
What about Hamada and Tanaka?
When we were in Akasaka, I pointed out that place that changed names
Akasaka Tokyu
I think the first big hotel I stayed at when coming to Tokyo was that one
Either that, or Yoko
We stayed in small places
But should I use these memories? Cause I think perhaps, in Roppongi,
the Grand Hyatt
Let's go to !@#!
What hotel did Hamada choose?
Considering the distance, I say Westin
Tanaka ignores using memories as a hint, and heads towards Westin in Ebisu Garden
I think I have the right idea
I'll definitely meet someone
I'll definitely meet somebody
Seriously, Westin in Ebisu Garden Place
I'll meet up for sure!
Seriously, if they go to some cliche place like Hyatt, or New Otani,
If there's nobody here I'll be shocked
Seriously if nobody comes,
I'll have to rethink my relationship with these guys
Everyone besides Tanaka has a good chance of meeting up
Matsumoto arrives near his location
There's gonna be someone here
However ...
There's no celebrity aura here
There would be a crowd if a star was here,
But those guys can't do this, in the first place
Oh there's someone there! There is!
There's someone there
Exactly, right?!
This is it right?
There was some distance between us
Oh thank god
This is it right?
I knew this is the place
If you're a Yoshimoto comedian,
Hotel Yoko
Eh, but why are only you here?
I had the same confidence
This is the only answer for a Yoshimoto comedian
Seriously
Even Nishikawa Norio stayed here
Everyone, all the seniors,
Hanshin Kyojin-san stayed here
Everyone's stayed here
I don't understand why they aren't here
I think because Cocorico are from a different generation
Those guys got their break in Tokyo, so they don't really have experience with hotels
I thought DownTown-san would be here
Isn't Hamada scary?
Time's Up!
Eh? Where did Hamada go then?
Hamada?
I just gotta say
Yamasaki and I have met up
Of course we did
Listen, Hamada,
What's your agency? Where are you from boy?
Where are you from? Jinrikisha?
Are you from friggin Hori Pro?
Where?!
My, my agency is Yoshimoto
Yoshimoto right?
So then,
What hotel have you stayed at?
So you're at Yoko then?
Yes!
It was Yoko after all
Where are you, actually
Where I'm at right now?
The Grand Hyatt
Why?
What is that? What memories do you have there?
We've never even been there
Is the summer fatigue getting to you?
Just hold on-
Did you not have this idea at all?
I did have the idea, but I'd heard Yoko was demolished
It's standing proud right now
That place, Ibis,
Oh yeah, I've heard Ibis was demolished too
I'm at Hotel Ibis
Right? What's with that choice?
Endo, oi, Ibis is no good
The Ibis is gone, and next year it'll come back as a different place
I mean, that's still,
You guys think you're hot shit cause you met up right?
They said "Hotel", so you have to consider a lot of places. Right Tanaka?
Yes, I agree
Where are you?
I'm at the Ebisu Westin
Ebisu's Westin?
Why Westin?
Why? Why Westin Tanaka? Why?
I'm gonna get you fired from ZIP!
Your turn idiot
Please, not that,
I was thinking about the distance, how far you all were
That's why I thought it was the Ebisu Westin
This is a shock
I wish you at least went to the Marudo Inn next door
That was another place too
Then we could've gone "Oh wow we ended up next to each other!!!", and then cut to commerical
That's what the director was hoping probably
What's wrong with you people? Are you guys idiots?
Next week - Meet Up Without Smart Phones - finale
Their idea for the 3rd hint?
3, 2,
Dogenzaka
There's a big XXX in Ginza
Or in Shinya
There's no other answer but Nikotama
There's someone there!
Will all 5 be able to meet?!