Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende presents Episode 1 of Duo Fight: Bus Tour Full of Pink Ladies!!
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
So, Matsumoto.
Yes yes yes.
We’ve done this 3 times in the past.
Kogal, S&M queen, anime character
That is indeed correct.
Those are the cosplays we’ve done.
We’ve done a lot of cosplaying.
For the bus tour.
Yep, that’s what we did.
This time, it’s Pink Lady.*
*Translator’s notes: Pink Lady was a J-Pop duo from the 70s.
Indeed, Pink Lady.
That’s what the decision came to.
Rules:
The games will take place inside the bus. The duo who loses 3 times must be dropped off in the middle of the city and they must sing and dance like Pink Lady.
Yes, when I heard that we’re going to be doing Pink Lady, I knew I definitely had to be Mie-chan.*
*Translator’s notes: Real name is Mitsuya Nemoto, but went by the stage name, Mie-chan.
That was the case so... I was graciously given the role of Mie-chan.
Oh is that so…
Well, that’s okay with me, I don’t really care.
Let's bring out the participants,
the first duo is the following!
Yamasaki is partnered up with Director Komurasaki, commonly acknowledged
Yamasaki Hosei
Komurasaki Kozo (Director)
as Yamasaki’s most trusted friend at the moment.
Competing as “Wanted”!
They’re competing as Pink Lady from their hit, “Wanted"!
What the hell is this.
This is a duo fight, why the hell are you two together?
Well, Komu (Komurasaki)…
Where’s this confidence coming from?
It’s like you’re saying, “Feel free to praise me.”
So creepy…
Thank ya.
Cocorico wraps themselves in a blue one-piece dress and
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Competing as "Nagisa no Sinbad!"
enters the battle as the million-seller hit, “Nagisa no Sinbad”!
Last week, you let Heipo ride on your shoulders
And you were hospitalized for a day.
I didn’t think that Heipo would be such a heavy guy.
Heipo of the World.
That man is like 70kg! (About 154 lbs)
Sounds about right.
Endo says he doesn’t know anything about Pink Lady.
Oh really?
I don’t have a bad back or anything but…
I can’t dance or sing, at all.
Our guest duo is Cream Stew.
Cream Stew
Ueda Shinya
Arita Teppei
After taking elaborate dance lessons,
Competing as "Carmen '77"!
they will be competing as “Carmen ‘77”!
Hello hello.
Alright, let’s hurry up and battle and then just go home.
Why are you treating us like a rush job?
You guys were part of the Pink Lady generation
I loved Pink Lady so I was extremely excited to go with this song.
The Chihara Brothers make an appearance on Gaki no Tsukai for the first time.
Chihara Brothers
Chihara Koji (Jr)
Chihara Seiji
Competing as “UFO”!
The tall duo will be cosplaying as the big hit, “UFO” for this occasion!
This is hideous.
You two are huge.
Our sister looks like this.
Everyone, I hope you understand, this is supposed to be a batsu game.
Yes, yes.
Don’t be shy.
Well, it only sucks if you lose. If you win, it’s fine.
Yeah, alright.
Okay, we have everyone gathered, let’s get this started.
Downtown’s Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Oolong - Translator
DuckToaster - Typesetter
typesoshee - Proofreader
Subbed by DTR Subs
http://dtr-subs.tumblr.com
All right, I’m going to present our first game!
Yes!
Mie-chan, Kei-chan game!
It’s very simple. For example, I say “Mie-chan” and point.
Mie-chan, Kei-chan Game Rules:
Yell, “Mie-chan” then “Kei-chan”, in which you must point at a person after the name. The two people sitting next to the person who gets “Kei-chan” must say “UFO” and pose.
And the person who gets pointed at says
Kei-chan.
And then that person is Kei-chan.
And then next to Kei-chan on both sides have to pose and say, “UFO!”
Alright then, Mie-chan, Kei-chan Game, START!!
Game Start!
Nope! No good!
Cream Stew:
Ueda is OUT
That was just strange.
Let’s start with the one who messed up, Ueda!
First to make 3 mistakes gets a batsu game!
Cocorico:
Cream
Stew:
Downtown:
Chihara
Brothers
Yamasaki
& Komu:
Chihara Brothers:
Junior is OUT
First to make 3 mistakes gets a batsu game!
Cocorico:
Cream
Stew:
Downtown:
Chihara
Brothers
Yamasaki
& Komu:
Alright, let’s start with Junior.
Okay.
Oi!
Cocorico:
Endo is OUT
Oi!
It’s because it’s here and here.
Wait then…
Watch carefully! Director Komurasaki hides his mistake.
Okay, we’ll start with Endo.
First to make 3 mistakes gets a batsu game!
Cocorico:
Cream
Stew:
Downtown:
Chihara
Brothers
Yamasaki
& Komu:
Downtown:
Matsumoto is OUT
What the hell!
Yes!! Woo hoo!
Hold on a minute!
I SERIOUSLY wasn’t paying attention.
I’m gonna pick up the pace.
That’s fine.
You’re going to increase the tempo?
Yup, faster tempo.
You didn’t say it!
He definitely didn’t say, “UFO”!!
What does everyone say?
Out, very out.
Cream Stew
IN DANGER!
Wait, does that mean for the both of us?!
From here, the development heats up with the Chihara Brothers continuing into the danger zone right after Cream Stew.
And following that, Director Komurasaki messes up, which brings the Yamasaki and Komu duo also in the danger zone!
However, Tanaka makes a mistake and now Cocorico is in the running for the batsu game!
So Downtown is still safe.
Wait, so everyone is in danger except for us?
Everyone but Downtown in danger!
Cocorico:
Cream
Stew:
Downtown:
Chihara
Brothers
Yamasaki
& Komu:
Shit shit shit shit shit
Okay, starting with Tanaka.
Here I go.
You didn’t say it!
Downtown:
Matsumoto is OUT
No no, I said it all at once!
Downtown
IN DANGER!
I said, “UFO! ...You know.” I even added “you know”!
All in. Going all in.
Everyone in danger!
Cocorico:
Cream
Stew:
Downtown:
Chihara
Brothers
Yamasaki
& Komu:
You didn’t say it!
Damnit!!
Cocorico
Batsu Game!
It was you!
Daaaamnit!!
You only said, “FO!”
Only “FO!”
You only said “FO!"
You only said “FO!”
Why is it bad if I say only, “FO”?
It’s been decided, it’s Cocorico!
No! I don’t want this!
I’m sorry! I’m really sorry!
I don’t want this!!
But really, Tanaka, you were weird the entire time.
When someone points at you, you’re just like…
Alright, for Cocorico, go to Big Echo in Hibiya, the karaoke shop located along the main street.
Go to the second floor to sing and dance on the terrace.
It’s a place where people will pass by the immediate vicinity.
Batsu Game Location
Big Echo in Yurakucho on the second floor terrace
Isn’t that it right there?
Where?
That one, it says Big Echo.
Get going then.
On your way there, there’s tons of people waiting for the light.
You're right.
*Translator’s notes: Miracle Type was a variety show that Cocorico hosted.
Be sure to tell them that this is “Miracle Type”*
I’m just gonna say this is for “Gaki”.
Why can’t I just say it’s “Gaki no Tsukai”!
Why do I have to do something so embarrassing?
Oh geez, it’s so cold!
Wow, really cold.
This is no good.
Let’s finish this up and go.
Yeah, seriously.
This is so sad.
Oh wow, it’s outdoors.
Yes indeed.
Hey, it’s looking kinda cool with the lights.
Oh yeah, true!
I’m a bit jealous.
It's starting.
“Nagisa no Sinbad” (1977 - One-million copies sold)
Vocals: Cocorico
They look cool!
As if!
They look like they’re representatives of the city.
You’re right.
If you were going to do this, this was the ideal spot.
Yes, that’s true.
Doing this at eye-level would be difficult.
Right.
Good job, guys.
Good job!
I know how you feel.
Well, it was good, wasn’t it?
It was amazing though, being exposed like that, just to let you know.
Yeah, it was no good to be walking through there.
We were caught at the traffic light.
Alright, well, that’s enough of that.
Continuing on, the next game is
Dandy Sakano Game!*
*Translator’s notes: Dandy Sakano is another Japanese comedian, known for his catchphrase, “Gets!”
Dandy Sakano Game Rules:
Yell, “Dandy” then “Sakano”, in which you must point at a person after the name. The two people sitting next to the person who gets “Sakano” must say “Gets!” and pose.
This is just like the previous game.
Dandy, Sakano, then both sides say, “Gets!”
Ugh.
Hold on, shall we shuffle then?
Our seats?
Yeah, let’s switch seats.
Switch seats and game start!
Hold on a minute!
Hey, everyone!
Cocorico, what do you think of this?
Wait, Komu, do I have something stuck here?
What the hell! No way. So cliche.
You totally raised your hand!
Yamasaki & Komu:
Yamasaki is OUT
When you put your hand to your throat and say, “Komu, do I have something stuck here?”
That was no good.
Awful.
That was the bad part.
That was really cliche.
Arita of Cream Stew still can’t seem to grasp the rules of the game.
In addition, Chihara Junior breaks his concentration and the guest duo are back in the heat of battle.
Downtown is very strong.
First to make 3 mistakes gets a batsu game!
Yamasaki &
Komu:
Cream
Stew:
Downtown:
Chihara
Brothers:
Alright, let’s go!
Starting with Junior!
No, not me.
Yes!
Pointed at Endo who is already out.
Downtown:
Hamada is OUT
I can’t even laugh, he’s senile. Senile in his forties.
Then we shouldn’t be laughing.
First to make 3 mistakes gets a batsu game!
Yamasaki &
Komu:
Cream
Stew:
Downtown:
Chihara
Brothers:
Hamada, please start.
Hold on right there!
Wait a minute, wait!
Before that…
How about this guy!!
No way!
He didn’t say “Gets”!
He didn’t say it! He didn’t say it!
You didn’t say it.
Downtown
IN DANGER!
The hell, why are YOU saying I didn’t say it!
You didn’t though.
No, no, I thought, “What’s the point in me saying it?”
Out!!
Downtown is in danger!
Senile people everywhere.
Downtown
Batsu Game!
Wait, what? Did he point at him?
You just had this dull look on your face.
Downtown
You’ll be dropped off in the middle of Roppongi in front of Don Quijote where there are plenty of people there to go shopping.
Hold on, I still can’t get over his mistake.
He points at Endo, then he does absolutely nothing.
He’s just there as if he didn’t do anything wrong.
Roppongi Intersection
We’ve arrived.
Look at all those people.
Don Quijote Roppongi Branch Entrance
Right here?
This is gonna suck.
Oh man, this will be hard.
Alright, Downtown.
Your performance, please!
Senile duo!
So embarrassing!
“South Paw” (1978 - 1,460,000 copies sold)
Vocals: Downtown
Oh wow, they’re really doing it well.
They’re not even staying to watch!!
No reaction.
No reaction at all.
You aren’t kidding.
They won’t even laugh for them.
Maybe they’re creeped out?
Yeah, they’re probably creeped out.
No one’s watching.
What’re they doing right there?
Good job.
Good job back there!
That was amazing…
I knew that no one was laughing.
The people walking by didn’t care either.
They didn’t watch, huh?
You know, you actually don’t feel the cold out there.
Yeah, you don’t feel it.
When we first went outside, we were like, “Wow, it’s cold,” but yeah.
Because your body was burning with embarrassment?
That was good, right?
If that’s how they’ll react to Downtown, we’re screwed.
Okay, I’ll be presenting the next game!
Alright!
The next game is Antonio Inoki Dahhh!* Game!
*Translator’s notes: Antonio Inoki was a professional wrestler. He’s well-known for yelling 1, 2, 3, DAHHH!
Antonio Inoki Dahhh! Game Rules:
Yell, “Antonio” then “Inoki”, in which you must point at a person after the name. The two people sitting next to the person who gets “Inoki” must say “Dahhh!” and pose.
You already know the rules, right?
Antonio, then Inoki, then both sides say, “Dahhh!”
Switch seats and game start!
You’re not saying anything!
Cream Stew:
Arita is OUT
Come on…
What are you, an orangutan?
First to make 3 mistakes gets a batsu game!
Yamasaki &
Komu:
Cream
Stew:
Chihara
Brothers
Hold on, you’re way too slow!
Too slow.
You’re just like, “Dahhhh…”
It should be more like “Antonio, Inoki, Dahhh!”
That’s too fast!
We can’t do that!
We can even do that! We can even do it, right guys?
Then show us an example.
You guys were all messed up!
At this point, Yamasaki, who seemed to be good at the game, makes an unusual mistake.
In addition, Chihara Junior slips up which brings all three teams into a big close match.
First to make 3 mistakes gets a batsu game!
Yamasaki &
Komu:
Cream
Stew:
Chihara
Brothers
That’s enough!
That’s enough.
Are you guys the bus’ engine?
Is that what this bus is running on?
Even at this stage of the game, Chihara Junior can’t follow the rhythm and gets 2 mistakes in a row.
Chihara Brothers are in danger!
First to make 3 mistakes gets a batsu game!
Yamasaki &
Komu:
Cream
Stew:
Chihara
Brothers
Wasn’t that too slow?!
What the hell are you doing?
Why are you stopping?
Why did you stop?!
That was just fine, wasn’t it?
That was fine!
Chihara Brothers!!
Chihara Brothers
Batsu Game!
That was totally… Totally off! Wasn’t it?!
No no no, that was not off.
Ehhh? How was that off?!
What is up with your phrasing?
It’s all your damn fault.
I’ll apologize if it makes you feel any better.
You don’t need to apologize.
In fact, you should be pissed off. He’s just accusing you.
For Chihara Brothers, go to Japan’s #1 fashionable area Daikanyama* and sing and dance at an outdoor cafe.
*Translator’s notes: Daikanyama is a very chic and trendy area in Shibuya, Tokyo.
I wouldn’t want that!
Batsu game location
Cafe terrace “Lloyd Cafe” in Daikanyama
It’s this place, here, here.
This is harsh.
It’s completely empty.
The people inside the cafe are really staring.
Do your best!
Just hurry up and go.
Oh hell
So cold!
Here they are!
They’re hesitating.
These guys, you know, they’re brothers.
This must suck.
“UFO” (1977 - 1,550,000 copies sold)
Vocals: Chihara Brothers
This is grossing me out.
They’re causing a disturbance.
They’re brothers, you know.
I can’t watch this.
Me either.
Should we just leave?
Start driving!
Get the bus going!
Let’s go, let’s go.
What the hell are you doing?!
Chihara Brothers
Left behind in Daikanyama while still dressed as Pink Lady!
What the hell are you doing?!!
What the hell?!!
Bye bye!
What the hell!
Alright, we’ve only got 1 game left and for the last round, it’ll be Takeda Tetsuya Game!
*Translator’s notes: Takeda Tetsuya is an actor and singer, most well-known for his role as Kinpachi Sensei in the Kinpachi Sensei J-drama series.
This is a standard one.
In the last round of the batsu game, there’s only 2 teams competing. Arita, still unable to get the hang of the game, is out!
Continuing on, Yamasaki makes an unlikely mistake and the game alternates the losses!
Furthermore, when the game switches over to Senda Mitsuo*...
Translator's notes: Senda Mitsuo is a voice actor who has been voice acting in many major animes and dubbed for big Hollywood movies.
Cream Stew
IN DANGER!
Cream Stew is in danger!
Alright, the game might or might not end here.
Cream Stew in danger!
Cream
Stew:
Yamasaki &
Komu:
Next is Shimura Ken Aiin.*
*Translator’s notes: Shimura Ken is a comedian who usually plays the foolish character. Aiin is a nonsensical phrase that he made up and became popular in Japanese media.
What the hell!
Cream Stew
Batsu Game!
Get a grip, goddamnit!
Arita, it’s a miracle that you even made it this far.
Alright, now for Cream Stew.
Location is Odaiba.*
*Translator’s note: Odaiba is a city in Tokyo, built on an artificial island. It is a major commercial and leisure area with accessible seashores.
Odaiba is a tough one…
Not only that, it’s at the beach.
Why the beach?
There’s no way anyone would be there, right? Geez!
It’s pitch black outside.
We’ll just look like we’re having a normal Pink Lady practice.
In such a place, in such a situation.
What’s going to happen? The bus stopped.
It’s right there. Right there.
Batsu game location
Sandy shores of the Odaiba Beachfront Park
There isn’t even one person around!
There really is nobody around!
Oh god, it’s so cold!
So damn cold.
Do your best.
Please do your best.
It’s so damn cold.
So cold!
Why is it only Ueda who keeps saying it’s cold?
You’re right.
So cold!
There must be something wrong with Arita.
Something’s wrong with his bodily senses.
“Carmen ‘77” (1977 - 660,000 copies sold)
Vocals: Cream Stew
Fast, very fast
This is pretty good!
Whoa, amazing!
Oh, people are actually passing by.
(Hamada also singing along)
Arita is really tone-deaf.
Something ran by, a dog ran by!
We did it with all of our strength!
Where?
We were right over there!
Huh? We didn’t notice.
We were there, if you just looked to the left!
Sorry about that, we were discussing what to do next week.
You don’t have to do that now!
Someone better confirm that we did the entire song.
Like someone saying, “They did it!”
Just leave it, don’t say any more.
Then, pardon me, please watch it when it airs.
It’s fine, just leave it.
Why are you siding with them?
Well, it was… The first time singing with the ocean behind me, and it was kinda refreshing.
Really though, Ueda, something’s wrong with you.
With me?!
Yeah.
He’s the host, the host. It’s fine.
I mean, this show is going to keep continuing and all.
I don’t think we’ll be back on this show again.
I really doubt that’s the actual reasoning.