Ignore this line
TPF
Gaki no Tsukai usual recording
Hey
What?
What's up with this guy?
Tsukitei Hosei
Hm? Is something wrong?
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
What happened?
"What happened"?
You mean the all back hairstyle?
Everyone said that it would suit me
Downtown
Cocorico
Matsumoto hitoshi
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
It seems like a makeover
It has sort of a Rakugo actor vibe
You mean that?
Yeah, that's why I've put my fringe up and exposed my forehead
You really seem to admire Shinosuke
Tatekawa Shinosuke
*Tatekawa Shinosuke is a rakugo performer. He has helped to popularise rakugo among young Japanese people
You really seem to admire Shinosuke
Like the Master
Compared to Shinosuke-san, the volume is...
That's rough
Rough?
There's no volume
Is that so?
With that, Peyang won't choose you*
*Tatekawa Shinosuke did a commercial once for Peyang noodles
Speaking of volume
How about making it an all back only when you do rakugo?
Sort of a Yazawa Eikichi* mindset
*Famous japanese rockstar
In order to get into the mood
Yeah yeah yeah
What's with this song?
Who are they?
Who?
I have no idea. I really don't know
I'm crazy in love with you
No no
Matsumoto, behind you
When I found out that we couldn't be together
This is quite amazing
He's not even in sync at all
Exactly, it's good and all but,
I will never let you go for you are my everything
This woman...
Yeah yeah, it's great but,
Who is it?
What's this from?
I don't know what this is from
What the hell is this?
Exactly, what the hell is this
It's so long
What the hell is all this, Itao
Lip sync part 2, shall we?
Itao Itsuji
What?
Yup
Still remember that?
Yeah, I remember
Yeah, I remember that
But before that,
Who is this person?
Um,
She's my new wife
New wife?
Do you just keep changing wives like this
Let's just say that she is my new wife
Your ex-wife then?
We've divorced
You guys are divorced?
Bringing along his new wife Itao's purpose this time is
Passionate lip sync rendition of popular songs
The second Lip sync ballad event
Held in April last year
Which lip sync singers will be performing this time?
This time around,
So it looks like we're doing a part 2?
No no, because
There's a lip sync boom coming
It's coming?
Are you really going to do a part 2?
What do you think?
You would ask me that?
The second
Lip sync ballad event
Itao presents
3 hours prior to their performance everyone was in a hurry
To fully train themselves for the songs chosen by Itao
The winner will be rewarded
In this lip sync competition,who will stand victorious!?
Late night
Hit songs
Studio
Lip sync
Returning again
The Late Night Hit Songs Studio
Host
Assistant
Itsuji Itao
Wife
In order to fulfill the audience's passionate love call, this TV show is renewed and brought back
And so, let us welcome the first lip sync singer
With a voice that unites Japan with the world
By Haruo Minami
Greetings from the world
Was the japanese theme song for the world expo in Osaka year 1970. Since then it has been played numerous times at big events in japan.
Greetings from the world/ Haruo Minami
Lyrics: Yoko Shimada  Composer: Hachidai Nakamura
Greetings greetings
From the countries in the West
From the countries in the East
Greetings greetings
To the people of the world
In the country of Sakura
Greetings in 1970
Greetings greetings
Let's shake our hands
Thank you
Please come over here, Hamada-san
Okay
As the first to perform
You had a really great smile on your face
No, I was actually nervous
Is that so?
Let's see what my wife thinks
How was it?
Would you ask me that?
Well that's all there
Thank you Hamada, please have a seat
The next lip sync singer
The bittersweet duo will sing
Promiscuous night of adults
Suzuki Kiyomi with Rats and Star, Lonely Chaplin
Go ahead!
A popular 80's song and still a popular duet karaoke song till this day.
Lonely Chaplin/ Kiyomi Suzuki with RATS&STAR
Lyrics by: Fumiko Okada  Composer: Masayuki Suzuki
The wind reflected in your eyes looking afar
When did that happen
He's mocking the singer
You leaned your face against the window sill
A sadness that you can show only me
Lonely Chaplin
Even if you disappear for a long time
I will definitely wait
That melody that binds us together
From wherever we hear it
We will know it anytime
The limits of unfulfilled dreams
Thank you
Please, if you two will come here
The two of you had such alluring voices
What an amazing degree of perfection
He's making fun of the original singer
From the great Haruo Minami earlier, you've renewed
this stage with a sexy atmosphere
Stop mocking him
Enveloping it completely, haven't you
We're glad to hear that, right?
It was very mature lip syncing
Mature lip syncing?
Yes, thank you very much
Tofu Panda Fan subs presents
Down Town's Gaki no tsukai ya arahende!!
Translators:
Typesetter & Proofreader:
Hans
Lei (Team Gaki)
Otviss
**We also have facebook and twitter.**
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
Special thanks to:
Nozomi
(Independent)
Oolong
(DTR Subs)
Hit Songs Studio
Late Night
Lip sync
Returning again
The return of famous song lip syncing by the Late Night Hit Songs Studio
Producer: Onuma Akihiro
A somewhat famous cover song initially and has been covered by many bands and singers since it's original release in 1975.
The Last Snow/ Iruka
Lyrics/Composer: Shozo Ise
Next, producer Onuma will perform Iruka's hit song
After the annoying seasons have passed
Now that spring has come, you've become so beautiful
This guy pisses me off
He does look a little like her
He really does look like her
Yeah, he does
The Exciting the Lip Sync Competition has become a close match
The next performer will be...
Theme song for the comedy/action film of the same name.
Sailor Costume and Machine guns/ Hiroko Yakushimaru
Lyrics by: Etsuko Kisugi  Composer: Nakao Kisugi
He looks so enthusiastic
That preparation
He's fully prepared
His face is ready too
He's betting his life on this song
"Goodbye" does not mean farewell
You'll be scolded if you keep doing that
He's pouting
The distant promise of meeting again
So annoying
Although it exists only where dreams linger
You're only being distant
It's gradually getting worse
I want to stay like this, embracing you for hours
This guy really
Pisses me off
His stubble is so thick
His face looks somewhat chubbier
And his stomach...
I want to stay like this, warming up your cold cheeks
He only sometimes does the mouth thing
What the hell?
Having finished singing, how do you feel?
Um,
I was very nervous, I wonder if I did well
There's no need to act like Yakushimaru
Which part did you pay most attention to?
The gun is very heavy
You mean this
You can act like Yama-chan
I was afraid I couldn't hold it up
You can go back to being Yama-chan
I see. Thank you
Please have a seat. So, the next lip sync singer..
Don't pass in front
That passion is exactly like a revolutionary soldier
With a voice that could change Japan
By Kaientai, "You're the boss"
Sitting there silently while drinking is fine
Hit song by Keintai. A three man band featuring "Takeda Tetsuya", an actor and singer who has been imitated several times in other GNT episodes. (You may recognize him from Kinpachi Sensei or from Prison Batsu during the 101st Marriage Proposal skit.)
You're the boss/ Kaientai
Lyrics by: Tetsuya Takada  Composer: Toshio Nakamuta
You started your story, there might have been many hardships
His entrance is on point
Producer: Yoshinobu Nakamura
We can't win this
Your boasts are too long, only counting the women you've made cry
His entrance was perfect
Boasting doesn't increase the value of being a man
Did he look like this?
You're the boss  You're the boss  You're the boss
You're the boss  You're the boss~
Sing with me!  You're the boss  You're the queen  You're the shareholder
You're the leader You're the general You're the president You're the genius
You're the gang leader  You're the boss
Thank you, come over here please
It's bad if it's too long
That was amazing, thank you for that
Matsumoto, having watched it through, what do you think?
The "You're the boss" part went on for a while, didn't it
Probably because that was the punchline
By dragging it out
You could see how inexperienced he is
After this
Endo will passionately perform that song!
The next lip sync singer
Japan's music might not have evolved to what it is today
Perhaps, if Japan did not have him
By Shinichi Mori, Winter Riviera
Mori Shinichi is a famous folk song singer (The Gaki members imitate him in many of the batsu games because of his particular looks and way of speaking.)
Winter Riviera/ Mori Shinichi
Lyrics by: Takashi Matsumoto  Composer: Eiichi Otaki
Already his face
Just the face already
The first line
He's about to make the face
Is he?
She kindly tells me
That she should already be asleep now
You're mocking him
He's mocking him, right?
I think so too
Don't mock Shinichi Mori
If she cries, turn on the radio by the window sill
He shouldn't mock Mori Shinichi because he's so famous
It's a little bit different from exactly impersonating him
This is good
You should sing a cheerful song for her
That's right
That's good
But any more than this
Any more is too much
That start feels like it'll lead to
An American freight
a good run
Waits on the pier
That's good, even the subtle things
He will peak at the hook of the song
Winter Riviera, a man
He held back
Yeah, he held back
He managed
He's held himself back
Like a ship leaving the harbor
Ok Endo, this time is fine
The sadder it gets
Don't do that
Stop it, that's too much now
I become more silent
Ok, it's good now
Ok ok
Stop it, stop doing that
It's good now
He just barely made it through
Yeah yeah
He managed to hold himself back
Thank you
Come over here, please
That was a really magnificent lip sync of Shinichi Mori
Even the people behind me were highly praising you
This time was good
Yeah, it was good
He tried to restrain himself
If you overdo it...
That's not your limit, right?
Then could you do it one more time as much as you can?
No no that's not okay
That is definitely not ok
It seems like, if you overdo it then it'll slow you down
My mother really likes it too
To mention your mom is too much
As expected of Shinichi Mori
Why does he say mother so politely?
I wanna see him
Japanese men are bewildered by her voluptuous charm
The one, the only, Cool Beauty
Akina Nakamori's Desire
Award winning hit song which has also stayed on best single charts. Won best Single of the Year for the first annual Japan Gold Disc Award
DESIRE/ Akina Nakamori
Lyrics by: Yoko Aki  Composer: Kisaburo Suzuki
A creep has appeared
Director: Kenji Suga
This is really infuriating
A strange person has come down the stairs
That's disgusting
Sometimes I feel so bored that it is unbearable even when you are around
I wonder if he'll do that
If it is some prate I want to dance now
This is gross
The glass discotheque
Yes, everybody are fallen angels, instead of wings, sweat is spattering
It's perfect
Yep, perfect
It's Ok to adhere to anything, lovers in an era
Where love is absent
Here it comes
It's about to start
Here comes the hook
Falling head over heels, Desire
Burning like a blaze, Desire
The "Dance, Dance" part is coming
Even love, to the extent of dance, dance, dance, dance
There
If you can't in it you will be isolated
His body is barely moving
He's not moving at all
You can hear his bones creaking
Old man
What an old man
Thank you
Please come over here. This time which exact part did you most concentrate on?
This time was extremely difficult
He's out of breath
Last time, um, what was it again?
TM Revolution
Don't purposely overdo it
It was TM revolution, right?
Akina Nakamori
Akina's
Suffering was portrayed really well
However, we, as the audience suffered way more
He barely moved at all
That's why I said this old man is creaking
With a prize on the line, in this heated lip sync battle
Which performer will stand victorious!?
I will now announce the winner
Here we go... The winner is...
Shinichi Mori's Winter Riviera. Congratulations!
Hit Songs Studio
Late night
Lip Sync
Shozo Endo
Victor
He did a good job restraining himself
That face
He looks more like Takeshi now (Takeshi Kitano)
Now, there is a reward for the winner, Shinichi Mori
To sing along
With just the instrumental of the song
My actual voice?
After this
Endo will perform MAX Shinichi Mori
I wonder if I can do well
Acquiring the competition
What do you mean "acquiring"?
It should be winning
You "acquire" license, not competitions
Pardon me
So,
The winner of the competition
Performing Winter Riviera
Winter Riviera/ Shinichi Mori
Lyrics by: Takashi Matsumoto  Composer: Eiichi Otaki
Here he comes
Here he is
So far, he's almost the same as before
He started fine
She kindly tells me
That she should already be asleep now
Endo Endo
That's not bad
That's fine
If she cries, turn on the radio by the window sill
Endo, that's good
That part was really good
I will even sing a cheerful song for her
He's redeemed himself from earlier
There it is
An American freight
An American
Samba
*Endo mixed up the words. "Pier" is Sambashi in japanese. That's in the next line.
Waits on the pier
American Samba?
Winter Riviera, a man
An american midwife is waiting
*Sanba is midwife.
He won't be the winner like this, we were mistaken
Like a ship leaving the harbor
The sadder it gets
This is exactly like Endo
Yeah I agree
He's not doing it properly
I become more silent
That's such a forced grin
Oh man, so close
Just that one part...
Thank you
That was amazing
It was really good wasn't it?
I thought you were actually Shinichi Mori
How was it?
An american midwife is
waiting on the pier
Having made this error
I'm very sorry
It's hard to say that he's the winner
Well, I guess
There should be another winner
Another winner
It should be DESIRE
Tsk!
What a last minute change
There's a clicking sound from back there
Director Suga
Revised Victor
The winner, Director Suga will perform with his voice
So, the winner of the competition, Akina Nakamori's
Desire
DESIRE/ Akina Nakamori
Lyrics by: Yoko Aki  Composer: Kisaburo Suzuki
Good luck
Director looks different
It's not an easy song
Yeah
That's to be expected
Sounds like an ordinary old man
He isn't voicing out at all
Sometimes I feel so bored that it is unbearable even when you are around
But, the real Akina's voice is also quiet
This is scary
We can't help watching until the end
Exactly
This video was brought to you by tofu panda fan subs
This is hell
It's torture
This is hell for everyone
The singer and the audience
Because it feels like hell and no one will benefit from it, he is forced to stop
How was it, singing with your actual voice, director?
*Whisper whisper*
I can't hear anything