w[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
The First Gaki No Tsukai Arahende Thorough Search Project!
Let's stroll around town until we find a celebrity!!
[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
The First Gaki No Tsukai Arahende Thorough Search Project!
Let's stroll around town until we find a celebrity!!
Nakameguro Edition!
We're here!
Let's go!
Nakameguro Edition!
We're here!
This is our second time doing this.
-Yes!
-Yes.
We visited Daikanyama last time.
Right, right...
But we found absolutely no one!
Yeah, it was deserted.
I think it was also because of the heat.
Right, that was another factor.
No one was on the streets.
But today's a bit cold.
-That's right, this time it's pretty chilly.
-It's completely different.
Last time, this program was recorded under the scorching sun.
Thank you for having me at "Hey! Hey! Hey!".
She's been on Hey! Hey! Hey!
Although they did meet a few famous people in the Daikanyama area...
-Ah, Ms. Repro.
-You're from the agency Repro, right?
...they didn't manage to name a single one of them. Could this be due to a generational gap?
So to get their revenge, the guys have moved to another area this time around.
They will try their hand at Meguro Wards' Nakameguro area!
The area around Meguro River.
It's a trendy town, surrounded by popular restaurants and famous stores!
Will they encounter any celebrities in this town full of talent agencies?
But, the very guy that said,
"Since we didn't find anyone last time I wanna get my revenge", is not here because of a tummy ache.
-That's right.
-He's resting.
Does he have a stomach ache?
I mean, I don't know the exact cause...
He's just feeling unwell.
Yeah, he's feeling unwell.
But I mean, what's with that?
You know, just last week at the waiting room he bragged to me and said, "You'll never get sick if you keep eating yogurt.".
-He told me that last week!
-For real?
He told me this the other day too, "I'm never gonna get a cold and won't be getting one anytime soon".
And now we're here.
I was so shocked when I heard!
-It was last week, wasn't it?
-Yeah, it was!
He told me all of that last week!
Just like last time, these are the rules.
We won't stop until we find someone.
They have to be on their personal time.
They can't be in a shoot or anything like that.
We didn't even see anyone filming the other day.
That's right!
Right! No one was even filming!
And this rule is the harshest, don't you think?
Yeah...
You have to say the person's full name.
And all of us have to say it, right?
-Yes, that's right.
-That's right.
Lastly, if their agency doesn't consent to the filming then it's no-go.
Will we complete the task this time?
How do you guys feel?
We're in Nakameguro!
Yeah!
Have you guys met anyone famous here?
I said this before, but back at Don Quixote, I met husband and wife, Kaera Kimura and Eita.
Whoa, marvelous.
-That's right.
-Isn't that great?
-It is!
It really is amazing.
You know, I am really hoping to meet Yoko Kumada at the Nakameguro Don Quixote.
Didn't you meet her before?
-Yeah, I did!
-Oh, right back then.
-Yes, I've run into her before.
-I see, I see...
-Yeah, I did!
-Oh, right back then.
-Yes, I've run into her before.
-I see, I see...
So I think we'll run into her today as well.
I also ran into someone at that same Don Quixote.
Everyone's at Don Quixote!
I had the pleasure to run into Nenji Kobayashi.
That's amazing!
You ran into Nenji?!
I had the pleasure to run into Nenji Kobayashi.
What was he doing there?
He was doing some shopping.
For real?!
I gave him a proper meeting and we chatted for a while.
We'll be fine today.
Yes, we'll be fine!
What about you? Have you run into anyone around here?
In their off time, I mean.
Not on their off time, but while I was on a shoot, I saw Saburo Tokito on his bike riding out of the gym next to Don Quixote.
-I wanna meet him!
-That's so great!
I really wanna run into him!
I'm so jealous!
That's a great encounter!
He was going home after a gym session, I think.
The hour is 3:39 p.m.
Unfortunately the sky is riddled with clouds...
But let's get started!
Someone is bound to be here!
Yeah... Maybe...
We'll find someone, won't we?
First off, we'll be aiming for the heavily trafficked Yamate Street.
But then, Hamada immediately blurts out something negative.
Isn't the EXILE office right around there?
That's right.
If we meet one of the E-girls I'll never get their names.
I've only ever met them as a group.
You're totally right.
I'm never even sure if I'd be able to name them.
There's just too many members, right?
I'll never guess their names if they come at me one by one.
You never know, we might meet one of them.
Oh, there’s Don Quixote.
We're finally here, huh?
I'm 100% sure we'll find someone there.
-I hope that's true.
-I'm certain.
But we can't go in with the cameras.
Oh, it's fine.
You're gonna get fired, man!
-Huh? Can we really go inside?
-Really?
-Yes, we can.
What?!
Then it's gonna be an easy shoot.
What? Really?
The shoot's gonna end so soon.
Then it's gonna be an easy shoot.
What? Really?
The shoot's gonna end so soon.
-Is it really okay?
-Can we really go in?
Of course.
I mean, we've only been walking for a few minutes...
We won't fill the full run time!
Yoko Kumada is gonna be there, you know?
It's just around the corner so we'll be stopping by.
We won't fill the full run time!
It'll be a short episode!
It's just around the corner so we'll be stopping by.
We won't fill the full run time!
It'll be a short episode!
Right?
The four guys have an unwavering trust in Don Quixote.
Will they run into someone famous?
Alright then, let's go in.
Let's go.
-There's bound to be someone.
-Let's go.
Yoko Kumada is on the second floor.
Should we go up?
I think there's a better chance upstairs.
-They should be up there.
-Let's go up then.
Huh?
That girl looks like an actress.
That girl, the one getting money at the ATM.
Isn't she a celebrity?
Maybe...
I saw her face but I don't think I'd be able to say her name.
Huh?
-I saw her face but I don't think I'd remember her name...
-You don't remember her name?
But she really looks like a celebrity.
-She was pretty cute.
-Yeah.
Just drop it, we're already upstairs.
Yeah, you're right.
Isn't that one of the EXILE guys?
Oh, I guess not.
-He looks like a famous magician.
-Right, a magician.
Sorry about that.
The other day... Was it Reina Asami that I met?
Yes?
I ran into her here.
But this place is empty.
You're right.
There's no one here.
Wait, wait...
What's going on?
What time is it? Around 4 p.m.?
-Yes, it's 4 p.m.
-That's right.
Huh?
I guess it is a bit of an odd time.
Is that so?
We should have come by a bit later.
Yeah, they usually come through here before having dinner.
-Oh, I see...
-Yeah, before dinner.
Huh?
Endo, what's going on?
Your calculations were wrong.
Endo?!
Your calculations were all wrong.
There's not many clients because of the time.
And a wave of disappointment washed over the guys.
You guys told me we'd definitely find someone here.
-I mean, it's an odd hour...
-That's right...
We better suck up some of that outside fresh air for now.
In the end, Don Quixote was a swing and a miss.
-I am so disappointed about that...
-Wait, wait...
I can already see our future...
Hold your horses! This is only our first stop!
Just be patient!
I can already see our future...
Hold your horses! This is only our first stop!
Just be patient!
It's all because you set up such high expectations.
It's just the time...
It really is the odd hour...
We can still make it a short one.
Isn't that Bobby Ologun?
He looks like him, but it's not him.
It's not him, it's not.
That was close!
-Meeting Bobby Ologun here would be amazing.
-Yeah.
It really would.
Yeah.
Sorry...
Isn't this the gym you were talking about?
Yes! That's right, this is it.
He came out of here.
-I think Shoji from "Shinagawa Shoji" is also a member of this gym.
-Oh, really?
Look, look, she's wearing a mask.
Yes, yes, yes.
You're right!
I wanna talk to her...
Looks like it could be someone.
-Someone has to go talk to her.
-She really looks like a celebrity.
She's gotta be famous!
For sure.
-Hold on, should we just go?
Should we?
-She came from over there.
Let's go then.
-Let's try.
-Should we?
-Yeah, let's go.
Let's seize our chance.
-Let's try.
-Should we?
-Yeah, let's go.
Let's seize our chance.
-Let's go.
-You guys go ahead.
I'm tired.
Is the girl in the mask a famous celebrity?
I'm almost sure that girl is famous but I don't think I'll ever remember her name.
Right, Yama?
Huh?
I'm almost sure that girl is famous but I don't think I know her name.
Well, I don't know about that...
She might be part of one of the EXILE groups.
Excuse me, would you mind talking to us for a bit?
It's you, right?
It's that girl from earlier!
-He's going in!
-Okay!!
But it all comes down to the name!
But they really found someone, look!
Tanaka is cracking up!
-Really?
-Yes.
If we know her name it's over then.
Maybe it's Yagu-chan?
(Mari Yaguchi)
No way!
Is the masked girl a famous celebrity?
Kokoriko is on the hunt.
Excuse me, do you have some time?
I'm from E-girls, E-girls.
Right?
It's you, right?
Aya?
-Aya? Right? Aya? Aya?
-What's this? What's going on?
Hamada!!
Aya, hold on...
Sure...
But it all comes down to the name!
But they really found someone, look!
Tanaka is cracking up!
-Really?
-Yes.
You're E-girls'...
-I'm the leader, Aya.
-Aya!
Yes.
-I'm the leader, Aya.
-Aya!
Yes.
Right?
Yes, I'm Aya.
Nice to meet you.
This girl is E-girls' leader! Aya!
Are you working right now?
Or is this your off time?
I'm on my off time.
Are you working right now?
Or is this your off time?
I'm on my off time.
-It is, isn't it?!
-You were buying some bread, right?
I'm on my off time.
-It is, isn't it?!
-You were buying some bread, right?
I was buying bread!
-It is, isn't it?!
-You were buying some bread, right?
I was buying bread!
She was buying bread!
Come one, please...
Do they really know her name?
But I can already tell from Tanaka's reaction...
Come one, please...
Do they really know her name?
But I can already tell from Tanaka's reaction...
He went like, "Whoa!!".
Right, I know that expression.... Like, "Whoa! I've met you before!".
And then you go like, "Who?".
"What was your name again?", or something like that.
We'll see if Hamada can name her once he gets here.
We're waiting to see if Hamada remembers her name, right?
He won't remember! There's no way! No way!
You never know...
We're waiting to see if Hamada remembers her name, right?
He won't remember! There's no way! No way!
You never know...
I'm scared!
If Hamada can't say it, then it doesn't count.
Okay then.
Hamada! Could you come over here?
She's a celebrity...
-She's a celebrity...
-I told you!
Right...
So, we have already explained what we're doing here.
She's a celebrity and we know who she is.
Tanaka and I, we both have worked with her.
You guys worked with her?!
-Yes, she was a regular at our show.
-What?!
I know her face but not her name.
So... Hold on...
She's on her off time so she's eligible.
And one of the rules... I mean, Tanaka and I already said it...
But they'll give us a pass if you can say her name.
That's outrageous!
Right?!
No way!
It's only a pass if everyone can say her name.
I already said it.
No way! One person is enough!
-Tanaka already said it, right?
-Yes, of course.
-And I also knew her name.
-Right.
So it's up to both of you.
What?!
Hamada is enough, no?
No way! I don't know her name either!
Right? I knew it...
Does it count if I just say the group's name?
Just say it then.
Go ahead.
Isn't she one of the E-girls?
-Yes, yes, yes!
-Amazing!
Yes!
-Right?
-She's one of the E-girls.
E-girls'...?
-Right?
-She's one of the E-girls.
E-girls'...?
I don't know...
There's like 20 members in the E-girls!
I've met them a couple of times.
But I don't know.
There's just too many of them.
Is there that many?
Of course, there's lots of them.
We're 27 now.
-Isn't there like an almost-there-girls kind of group?
-There's like 3 different teams, right?
-They make up 3 different teams, right?
-Yes, yes.
-Is she not one of the almost-there-girls group?
-But who are you?!
I really don't remember her name.
-So, everyone has their own name, right?
-Yes, we all have names.
Of course they do!
In the end, they couldn't come up with her name.
Task failed!
Alright then.
But I recognized her right away.
That was quick.
We've only just started.
Oh, is that so?
Have you seen any celebrities around here?
There's tons of them walking around here.
-Walking?
-Yes.
-Right, they're walking around.
Like, Shizuka Fudo.
-What? Really?
-Whoa, amazing!
-But this area is full of E-girls.
-Let's keep looking.
-Oh, really?
-Is that so?
But we can't name them!
-We can't remember a single name!
-What are their names?
After splitting ways with Aya from E-girls, they boys head to a more crowded area around Nakameguro Station.
Isn't there anyone around?
I wish Tatsuo Umemiya would just walk in front of me.
Mr. Umemiya...
-Oh, this is new...
-I haven't eaten here.
Isn't this a famous pizza place?
-Oh, this is new...
-I haven't eaten here.
Isn't this a famous pizza place?
It looks fancy.
But Hamada, you were on point back there.
-Right?
-You spotted that girl.
She was wearing a mask.
They always wear masks.
A mask... Huh?
A mask and some sunglasses.
Or a hat.
A hat...
It's only been three minutes since they started searching again...
Just minutes ago, Hamada spotted Aya from E-girls...
But he's about to make another miracle.
Ah...
I gotcha!
Huh?
I found her!
Awesome!
-Hello!
-That's amazing!
-And we all know her name!
We all know her!
-By the way...
-What are you up to right now?
-What are you doing here?
My husband is at the convenience store...
Alright!
So, are you waiting for your husband to come back from the store?
Yes.
-This is your off time, right?
-That's amazing!
That's right.
Let us check.
-Hamada!
-Hamada, you're amazing!
-Hold on, that was unbelievable!
-That was incredible!
-Hamada, you're amazing!
-That's crazy!
You're on your off time, right?
-Hamada, you're amazing!
-That's crazy!
You're on your off time, right?
This is completely your off time, right?
You're just shopping, right?
You're not working?
Oh, right...
Hold on, we're just checking with your agency to see if you can appear on the show.
A famous person who has worked with the guys many times in the past.
Of course, everyone knows her name.
-Let's go all together.
-Alright!
-Yes.
One, two...
Akiko Hinagata!
Is that correct?
That's correct.
Thank you so much!
Alright!
Incredible!
-Sorry for startling you.
-If your agency doesn't give us the okay we have to go searching again.
That's the only part left.
-Sorry for startling you.
-If your agency doesn't give us the okay we have to go searching again.
That's the only part left.
I think it'll be fine.
Alright, how long has it been since we started?
It's 4:17 now...
So about...
-About 30 minutes.
-30 minutes?
-That was so fast!
-That's great!
We're still trying to contact her agency.
No way...
If her agency says no, I'll jump in her car right now.
It's been 8 minutes since we contacted her agency.
We couldn't get a hold of her agent so permission has not been given yet.
The guys will keep searching for famous people while we wait for confirmation.
Hmm... There are too many people around here.
-Right.
-Yeah...
-Right...
The more normal people, the less celebrities.
Right.
-But we're at the station already.
-Right...
Right.
-But we're at the station already.
-Right...
They are being careful.
They won't be around here.
Right.
Yeah...
You know, there's plenty of restaurants by this side of the Meguro River.
Right, right...
And I've heard there's a lot of famous people around there.
Oh, really?
But it's still early.
-Right...
-It's still only 4-5 p.m.
It's about to start.
Right.
What are you guys eating?
-Looks delicious!
-What a cute couple!
Are you in high-school?
We're in third-years in middle-school.
Middle-school!
Oh my...
That must be their first date!
How do you know that?!
Stop making stuff up!
Yeah, don't do that!
Do you think someone's playing Pachinko?
I don't think they would play Pachinko...
Pachinko?
One of you, go have a look.
-I'll go then.
-Sure.
-Tanaka, go have a look.
-I'll be back.
Is he gonna find something?
Tanaka will be searching the inside of this Pachinko parlor alone.
-Finding someone playing Pachinko would be so funny.
-That's so true!!
Who would be the funniest?
How about Tamao Nakamura?
Right, she does like Pachinko.
Akko! (Akiko Wada)
She also loves playing.
There's a chance...
She really does love it.
Tanaka has been searching the inside of the parlor, but what has he come up with?
No one was in there.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Tamao wasn't there?
She wasn't.
Actually, I was also thinking of her.
I was like, "I wonder if Tamao is here".
Let's go then.
-Yes.
-Yeah.
-The camera man that followed you inside said he saw someone.
-What?!
-Who?
-Huh?
Just now?
Come on man! Go have a good look!
What?! Hold on!
-Are you serious?
-Huh?
Was it a celebrity?
-A celebrity?
Yes, but I don't know his name.
Hold on...
Come on, man!!
Are you serious?!
For real?!
Yama, go with him!
It's only been 8 minutes since they parted ways with Hinagata.
Have they found another famous person?!
-Look!
-There!
Who?! Who is it?!
What?!
Come!
Come here!
-What?! Are you serious?
-Look! Look! Look!
You're kidding me!
Who is this celebrity at the Pachinko parlor?!
What?!
Come!
Come here!
-What?! Are you serious?
-Look! Look! Look!
You're kidding me!
Are you serious?!
For real?!
No way, no way!
What's up!
Let's go, over there.
What?!
What are you doing there?!
This is your off time, right?!
Yes, it's my day off.
Alright! Let's go!
Sorry to bother you.
Can you be on our show?
We have to contact your agency.
Of course.
-They won't refuse as long as it comes from you, Hamada-san.
-No way! No way!
-Then we'll contact your agency.
-Alright.
This is amazing! What are you guys doing?
What were you doing today?
-Well, I am on my off day...
-Right...
Yeah... And I was playing some Pachinko...
Pachinko?
How long have you been here?
About 2 hours.
Have you been making money?
-Just a little bit.
-Right.
-Did we catch you right as you were about to win?
-Yeah.
That's too bad.
I mean, I don't get to come here often.
I'm so glad.
I just finished playing.
Do you come here often?
Yes, I do.
Your house is over there, isn't it?
Yes, it's pretty close by.
-I see.
I've run into a lot of people around here.
-Oh, is that so?
-Yeah.
-In your own time?
-Yes.
Like, Maki Carrousel.
She's coming such a long way!
I wanna run into her!
Right? I wanna meet her too!
Who else?
Well... Masato Hagiwara.
Right? I wanna meet her too!
-Oh!
-Right, right!
Hamada, do you know his name?
Of course I know his full name.
Let's go on three.
Alright.
One, two...
Masaya Nakamura.
Thank you.
Alright.
Of course we know him.
-We're just checking with your agency, we'll use the footage if we get the okay from them.
-Sure.
Alright, sorry about that.
-We're just checking with your agency, we'll use the footage if we get the okay from them.
-Sure.
Alright, sorry about that.
-Thank you!
Thanks!
Hang in there!
Thank you!
Hope you win the big bucks!
Just like with Hinagata, we couldn't get through to Masaya Nakamura's agent.
The guys will head forward toward the Meguro River in search for their next celebrity.
Let's avoid the train station.
We might run into 10 more people later at night.
At this rate?
You might be right.
We can make a special.
A special?
I can't believe Masaya was at that place.
It's amazing.
It was incredible.
But I guess, celebrities... Right...
I mean, a lot of them like playing Pachinko.
-You're right.
-But is it normal to play like that?
-There might be someone doing some shopping inside that store too.
-Probably...
For real...
But you know, supermarkets are Yama's specialty!
My specialty?
It was like that last time!
That's true.
I was just cooling off last time.
I knew it.
Look at this trendy joint.
It's very fancy.
That's where the gym is.
-Oh, Hiromi's gym?
-Is that so?
That's where the gym is.
-Oh, Hiromi's gym?
-Is that so?
Is that so?
And Masaya's place is just down there.
Hmm...
At this hour... Is it around 5 p.m. now?
5, huh?
I feel like they could be anywhere around here.
But this is definitely better than Daikanyama.
Of course.
It's completely different.
Matsumoto was the one vouching for Daikanyama.
He said all the celebs hang out at Daikanyama.
Right...
But I didn't find anyone.
While all of us were secretly thinking Nakameguro was the place to be.
But we couldn't say anything.
We were overwhelmed by his presence.
Ah... Damn it...
The Meguro River was empty!
Once again, the guys head back to Don Quixote.
Alright, we're back.
We have arrived at Nakameguro's promised land.
We walked for ages... But we're finally here.
The place all of you so admire, Don Quixote.
-We're bound to find something.
-And there's bound to be someone, since it's just before dinner.
-Definitely.
-We've come back.
-Yes!!
Look, that's crazy!
There's already tons of people inside.
Wasn't that quick?
Ah! Who's that?
Let's hang around here.
See? Hamada?
See? I told you.
Huh?
Wasn't that quick?
What do you mean by "see?"?
We still haven't seen anyone.
Have they found a famous person right at Don Quixote's front door?!
No way, we don't know her name.
Could I talk to you for a minute?
Ehm...
Are you in the entertainment business?
No, not at all.
Oh, you're not?
Are you normal...?
Do you have a normal job?
Oh, I see...
-Sorry to bother you.
-If the camera wasn't there, Tanaka would be just a dude hitting on that girl.
Oh, I see...
-Sorry to bother you.
-If the camera wasn't there, Tanaka would be just a dude hitting on that girl.
She said she didn't work in the entertainment industry.
Right...
-An normal person?
-Yes.
Completely?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
She was so annoyed.
Did she tell you off?
Although they came up empty, the boys' spirits are up.
Huh? Are you famous?
I'm not.
-You're not?
-Huh? You're not?
See? Look at all the people.
You can ask anyone, "Are you famous? Are you famous?".
You're right.
But we're just asking, aren't we?
She wasn't famous, was she?
Will they run into a famous person?
Look.
Huh? Ah! Ah!
Look!
I remember! I remember!
Hamada-san!
You go.
Nice to see you!
I know him, I know him.
Can you talk for a moment?
Ah! I remember! I remember!
I remember! I remember!
We're so close.
I forgot, but now I remember his name.
I know, I know, I know.
It's nice to see you.
You too.
By the way, are you on your off time?
Yes, I am.
Ehm... I just stopped by to get some hair products.
-Oh, you came to get some hair products?
-Yeah.
Alright!
We did it! We did it!
Awesome! Awesome!
We did it.
Amazing!
We're doing Gaki No Tsukai Arahende today.
Oh, really?
Amazing!
Please check with his agency.
-Do you know his name?
-Of course.
One, two...
Mandy Sekiguchi.
-Thanks you!
-Thanks!
By the way, have you seen any other famous people around?
Oh...
I just came out of the hairdresser and as I was walking out...
-I saw the slapper, Chono, from "God damn!".
-Huh?!
What?!
I wanna see him!
Let's stop!
No way! No way!
-Let's go search for him!
-No way! No way!
-No, no, no, no...
-Chono, huh?
-It was down at Omotesando.
-Omotesando?
Really?
-It was down at Omotesando.
-Omotesando?
Really?
Omotesando!
Omotesando?
Over there?
Ah... I'm so glad.
He was apparently going to Gold's Gym.
-I see...
-Oh, I see...
We got through to Mandy Sekiguchi's agency immediately and got their confirmation!
After that, we also got the approval of Akiko Hinagata and Masaya Nakamura's agencies.
Everyone, thank you!!
With that being said, the guys walked a total of 1 km and 868 m.
With a total time of 1 hour and 38 minutes.
It was a complete success!!
Where are we going next time?
We can just leave that up to Matsumoto.
He'll have to go alone.
Alone? That'd be great!
He said he wanted revenge but didn't show up today.
Next time we'll force him to go alone.
He'll have to go to Kamata or somewhere like that.
Where there are no celebrities.
Great idea!