So, today our master painter
Downtown: Matsumoto Hitoshi (master painter) - Hamada Masatoshi
Yes yes yes
Will be Matsumoto
Exactly
To put it simply...
We'll try to find out whether or not you're good at drawing pictures
That's the plan
So pretty much today
It's not like we're going to see who's more creative
All of us will try to draw the same theme
This week, they'll all draw with master painter Matsumoto
a certain theme decided together and compete together
Then Matsumoto will review each one of our works
And lets us know
Got it
Just like that
Well, what I'll be looking for is what you've got there
Are you looking for our @#&$% ?
I'm talking about your spirit
Ooohh
So it's not just the appearance
What do you mean?
It's the feelings! - That's it that's it!
I'm not saying this about his artistic skills
But I must say, he really does look good dressed like this
World Famous Heipo
Saito Toshihide
I didn't realize there was such a big artist in here
Translation, subtitles & encoding by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
More clips? Subscribe to this channel: Shion (ガキの使い用)
Find all my other subtitled clips on this channel or on my wordpress:
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Okay, with that being said, our first topic
Look, if I were to choose
I would go with what I'm good at drawing
Right, you'd choose what you're good at, makes sense
How old are you again?
Oh, here comes, go for it Yamazaki
Yamazaki Housei
I really like DisneyLand a lot
So I'm choosing "Mickey Mouse"
Theme:
Mickey Mouse
I see
"Mickey Mouse"
I'm really good at drawing him
Got it
I think it'll make a real challenge
Ok everybody, let's draw Mickey Mouse
Currently Drawing
It's important that you draw pouring yourself into it
Would you like to see master painter's one first?
Yeah, sounds good     -      Good idea
Without any warning?
As a starter, I see
I see, so it gets curvy in this point
Most likely
At this point it's also a challenge of mental pictures
Let's see the others!
I want to see his work
You mean Hamada's?
Ok, let's take at look at his Mickey Mouse
It's completely messed up!
Children would run away if they saw this!
That's anything but Mickey
You
That's the theme you brought up
Yeah I've suggested it
You're in trouble if yours isn't the best one
Show us yours, please
I'm not saying I nailed it, but that's the idea
Whaaaat?!
You-- that--
What the hell is this?
What about this?   -   His ears...
- How many ears are in there?
Why does he have two pairs of ears?
I made a mistake
Should have been just two
His nose too
Your turn, Heipo
Why is everyone turning Mickey into this?
It's freaky!
It would be terrifying to play with your Mickeys
I'd like to choose the worst one if possible
Sure
And that would be yours
Why? What about Yamazaki's?
No no, yours is the worst
You can't even tell that's Mickey!
"Seahorse"
Writer
Takasu Mitsuyoshi
A seahorse huh...
Theme:
Seahorse
I must say, I really am a master painter
Is that so?
It sucks!   -    The hell is this?
No way
I'm sure the viewers would give their consent to this
Its proportions are weird
That's no good
This is how it turned out
I guess that's how the tail is supposed to roll
Let's just look at his, shall we?
We know he's the main star, let's just look at his
Come on
TERRIFYING!
You're a monster, aren't you?!
What is this? What is this?!
I-it's his face
WHAT?!
See? The eyes...
Hold on a second
This one should be its mouth
It also seems to be smiling
You're right, it's expressive
It can experience human emotions
Show us yours, Suzuki
I think I got its body structure a bit wrong
Writer
Suzuki Masaki
What?!
Scary!
What the heck, it looks like a katana
For now, just tell us which one is the worst
About the worst one...
Maybe it's Heipo's
Or maybe Suzuki's
This game is harsh
Yours were pretty bad
But this!
This is something serious!
And it's also scary
I think I'm starting to like it a bit
Director
Yanaoka Hidekazu
Let's go with a character
Elvis Presley
Theme:
So
This is the master painter's work
Presley, isn't it?
Yes
It's good!   -   Cool
I know, right?
To be fair I've just drawn his face
This is...
How is this supposed to be Elvis Presley?
What's with this hairstyle?
I thought that's how--
It's nothing like that
You can tell the one you've drawn is japanese
You're right
Director
Sakamoto Hidenao
I wonder who this is
Heipo
You suck!
We can agree this is the worst
Yeah it's really bad
Why did he draw him with glasses?
Picture them as sunglasses
They make it look so lame
I think it's about time for our idiot-master painter
So japanese!
Are you for real?
Why, what's wrong with it?
It's terrible
I've even drawn his chest hair!
To be fair the worst one
Is this
You couldn't even get the hairstyle right
Producer
Kenji Suga
I know it will be a self-portrait for Hama-chan
But I'm choosing "Hama-chan's face"
Theme:
Hama-chan
Alright
Show us your work, master
Sure
It kinda
Looks like a dumb ogre
But I guess you can tell it's him   -   Yeah...
Director
Tsutsumimoto Yukio
So sweet!
Looks like the guy who will take the thing you accidentally dropped before to you house
Ok, Suga-chan
I made it a bit chubby
It seems to lack style
He's saying "nandeyanen"!
He clearly wrote it
My version is...
I think it's ok this way
I guess I can see you in this
Well I'm drawing myself after all
Duh
Giving that Hama-chan just came out as a theme
I was thinking of having Macchan as our last one
Theme:
Macchan
This one's hard
Scary!
It's an old man!
Really
I think I've nailed it
They eyes are spot on    - They are, right?
Yamazaki?  - It was hard
What a goofball
A generic goofball
So sweet
Looks like a reliable guy
I don't see much difference from his previous one
They're all good guys
He really do have the face of a nice guy
He's the type of guy I'd ask to take care of my chickens during Summer break
Ok, it's time for our idiot-master painter
Well, I think mine's the most resembling
Yeah?
Well it's a bit...
Yeah but you can tell that's him
Why don't you line up all your works here?
Why do we have to do this?
Why do I have to be the focused one?
Alright
Now we have gathered the entire collection of the idiot-master painter
Idiot Master Painter
Hamada's Collection
Are we having this corner for real?!
He was having a tough time when he drew this
You can sense it   -   I guess so
I know we would have got to this eventually
Since we were halfway through it
Let's send those as presents too
I mean, the idiot master painter's works
We'll have a lottery between those who want to get
Hama-chan & Macchan's illustration and send them!!
We could send them as presents to the viewers at home
Read more details at the end of the episode.
We could sign them
And send them as presents to our audience
Translation & subs by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Oh, that's nice
Oh, right, th-- for those
Who have just turned on the TV
That's not a panda
That's Mickey Mouse
I think it's important to make it clear