Subtitles: Godzillaradio
http://jburogu-godzillaradio.blogspot.com.au/
Editing: Hadin
What!?
Yes.
Seriously?
Shozo, where's Tanaka?
Oh, well.....I'm sure he'll be here soon.
Do you want to go scare him?
What do ya mean?
Oh yeah, take a cameraman with you and...
Idiots!
Yamazaki's finally turned over a new leaf and started to come on time.
At least an hour and a half early...
Stop friggin' lying!
I'm seriously traumatised from that, you know!
Idiot!
He gets scared as soon as the elevator opens
and can't stop sweating from the trauma.
He thinks I'll be there, does he?
Yeah he thinks Hamada might be there.
Good morning.
Who the heck are you?
What? We're License.
Ahhh, right. License.
There's something about Tanaka-san we'd like to talk about.
He's not here yet.
Yes. That's right.
You know how you did the "100 Things About Matsumoto" sketch the other day?
Do you remember how Matsumoto-san said
"I wouldn't want to be reborn as Tanaka-san"?
The issue pertains to a remark made during "100 Things About Matsumoto".
Here is the answer.
Errr....Tanaka.
Whaaat? It's Tanaka?
Furthermore, when asked for his reason....
(His life) seems boring!
Was I meant to be choosing from one of us?
Because, I actually meant that out of all Asians.
Ever since around then, Tanaka-san has become a bit crazy.
But that was sort of just part of a joke, ya know?
He was also saying stuff like "Maybe I won't go to Gaki anymore".
I really doubt that.
That's an immense character change.
He's not the type to say stuff like that!
And what else?
Anyway, we asked some Gaki staff to record him on film.
Of Tanaka?
Tanaka's recent activities.
Would you mind watching?
Yeah, let's watch it.
Oh we can watch it here?
Yes, we can.
That's weird, he never was that kind of person.
Yeah, out of all of us I'm sure Endo knows him best.
I'm not really sure how exactly he'd change.
Should we really release this footage into the open?
After much debate, we decided to bring it out to the world.
1st Day Of Shooting A.M 9:06
We followed License, who had been called by Tanaka to meet him.
Please film everything until the end.
OI!
Good morning!
LICENSE!
Please film everything until the end.
OI!
LICENSE!
WHAT'CHA DOIN'?
We'll be right there! Hold on.
You can undoubtedly sense a strange difference to Tanaka.
Please explain it to him properly.
About us.
Oh yeah, of course.
Good morning.
You took a while.
Yes, sorry.
Today we've got Gaki's cameras with us today, is that okay?
Why?
I don't really mind but....there's nothing interesting here.
You eat these Super Cup noodles so early in the morning?
This is what I always eat for breakfast.
Oh really?
Yeah. It's freakin' tasty, right?
Woah that's scary.
That is scary.
It's freakin' tasty, right?
His teeth are dirty.
What's wrong with him?
Humans have a light and dark side.
But there are few who so openly show their dark side on camera.
And all while sitting outside the entrance of a convenience store.
The familiar sight of the man who smiles shyly was no longer there.
Something is wrong.
Yeah, something is wrong here.
You got married, huh.
Yes, thank you.
Do you boink her?
Pardon?
My wife?
Well yeah, we've got to make babies so....
Are ya gonna do it today?
Today!?
I won't be doing it today but...
Do you often talk about that sort of stuff?
About what?
In private....do you talk about those sort of dirty topics?
Oh yeah, I'm totally erotic.
Yeah.
I really love threesomes in real life too.
This isn't like Tanaka at all.
He's not used to sitting like that, so his ass touches the ground!
This change within Tanaka must stem from....
(His life) seems boring!
So that's how I seem to you, is it?
The heck is that?
Could he have been deeply hurt from Matsumoto's words?
Not at all, Eraser (Staff's nickname).
I'm starting to feel responsible for this, Endo!
(Matsumoto-san) said that from what he imagined about my life, right?
I mean, of course I love him (Matsumoto-san)....yeah.
Uh-huh....for sure.
But this is what I'm actually like usually.
We were confused. This was definitely not the Tanaka we knew.
He should be such a pure hearted man that
even cries after being intimidated by Hamada.
Oh man this is scary. I don't wanna see Tanaka like this.
An optician's store.
Look!
Woah, cheap.
Ahhh...that's nice.
Oh really?
Yeah.
Tanaka's two juniors sighed as they revealed that they are
now always made to wander around town with him like this.
Difficult choice!
It's so cheap!
It is very cheap.
What!? What are you doing?
What?
That's dirty.
I'm suuuper thirsty.
We'll buy you water then!
No, no, that's fine. Look what's written here.
"Please freely use this ultrasonic wave cleaner"
Well yeah, it says "Please use freely" but...
Ain't it totally funny though?
Ain't it totally funny to drink from the washing basin?
No, stop! Just stop!
Without concern about people seeing him, he quenches his thirst from a washing basin.
They had no choice but to smile awkwardly.
I drank three tubs! HAAHAHAH!
There was no goal to his wanderings.
Just a sec.
Sure.
Hello?
Yeah.
WHY THE FUCK!?
WHY THE FUCK DO I HAVE TO START SO EARLY!?
EHHH!?
WHAT DOES IKUE AND NAOMI AND SHIT HAVE TO DO WITH ANYTHING!?
YEAH! I AIN'T GOIN!
I SAID I AIN'T GOIN'!
SO FUCKIN' WHAT!?
TOO EARLY IDIOT!
They're seeing him going berserk.
We couldn't help but gasp.
We even contemplated stopping the camera.
I'm so pissed off.
Did he have some trouble with his manager who just phoned him?
Tanaka was terribly angered.
When suddenly...
You gotta be kidding?
Is it okay for a comedian like this to exist?
Is this okay for a comedian?
No way, he's finished.
We were left speechless from shock.
But, this is what Tanaka is like now.
He kicked it in a weird spot too.
Is this kind of thing normal for him?
Only recently....
Sorry!
LICENSE!
Sometime when my switch flicks, I think I get like that.
Is it a bad thing? I dunno but...
I do think "I want to be audacious".
He does stuff like this recently!
There was a senior like that before though.
Yeah, I hated him.
His eyes were shining suspiciously.
2nd Day Of Filming
The next day, we were witness to another unexpected side of the man.
It was Tanaka Naoki absorbed in a game of mahjong amidst a choking haze of smoke.
Recently, I'll come twice a week if I can.
Sometimes I finish work and go straight to a mahjong house and...
sometimes I finish work and go straight to my mistress's place.
He has never even used the word mistress before!
I don't wanna see Tanaka like this!
It was one surprise after another.
The smell of trouble had become even stronger than before.
See, he's distressed right?
3rd Day Of Filming
Yeah he is.
The next day, Tanaka himself invited us to meet up with him.
Sorry, since it's your day off.
Uh yeah, no problem.
(Staff) This is your car, Tanaka-san?
Yeah.
(Staff) The much rumoured about car.
(Staff) Have you had it for quite a long time?
No, about 7 years.
Tanaka's driving was surprisingly calmer than we expected.
In addition, he was very cautious.
You're always following me now.
(Staff) Well, we heard that you had changed, Tanaka-san.
I guess I can be a bit messed up.
Speaking of messed up, see his dirty hands....
(Staff) Don't you clean your hands? And your teeth.
That smile is like Matsuda Yusaku in "Black Rain".
Tanaka turned his attention to in front of him.
A German made car is blocking the entrance to a parking lot.
(Staff) Should I ask him to move?
Just hold on a second.
No, stop, stop!
He has such a short temper.
The nightmare from the shopping centre was revived.
No one can stop an angry Tanaka.
What'cha doin'?
You're in the way.
OI!
Where the heck are you parking it, you f**k?
Oh, sorry.
YOU'RE IN THE WAY!
Yes, sorry.
WHERE DO YA THINK YOU'RE PARKIN'!?
Sorry.
OI!
GET OUT!
Yes, I'll go now.
GO!
ARE YOU AN IDIOT!?
Even we were terrified at his intense rage.
I can't forgive shit like that.
Tanaka currently has no control over his emotions.
I guess, I want to be like a "dangerous man".
(Staff)  Don't you worry about your public image as a talent?
Why? Do you?
Tanaka doesn't look at these things.
(Staff) You seem to like erotic things, don't you?
Uh-huh, I'm always thinking about erotic things.
His rage and eros seems to be spiraling out of control.
There is not even a shred of the old Tanaka from Cocorico.
5th Day of Filming
His erratic behaviour was even present when we met him in Shinjuku.
OI!
ERASER (STAFF)
(Staff) Good morning.
Tanaka had arrived in a hearse.
So sorry I'm late.
(Staff) What's going on?
I realised I was running late so I caught a ride with this guy, who happened to pass by.
Thanks! Sorry.
Looks so cool doesn't it?
Wanna go then?
At the sushi store he just takes the sushi and leaves the plate.
Oh man this tastes awesome.
The store owner could do nothing but grimace.
6th Day of Shooting
While in town, he found a drink machine.
"Idiot"
I do this every time I find a poster.
Are you serious?
When we asked his reason for doing this, he kept his mouth closed.
Oh man this sucks. I wanna turn back time!
7th Day Of Shooting
It is apparent that this comedian, who should make people laugh,
is carrying a considerable amount of stress.
But it should be strictly forbidden to show this to the public.
(Staff) Who is this?
None of your business.
And yet, Tanaka has shed his self restraint and is revealing his raw nature.
Just where did that Tanaka of old disappear to...?
8th Day Of Shooting
License were called to come to a small shrine.
Wanna feed them (pigeons)?
Oh, can we?
Yeah.
The animal loving Tanaka experiences
limitless joy from feeding the pigeons at this shrine.
Quite a lot gather, so it's fun. Plus they're cute.
<Staff> Do they come if you throw food?
Yeah usually they do.
But this day....
They ain't comin' at all.
Yo pops.
Where're the pigeons today pops?
Hey I'mma take some of this food.
OOOOOOIIII!
(Staff) The pigeons are c...
Animals possess qualities that I don't have so...
They're really impulsive, and they're all so different.
They're so cool like that. Totally different.
This is actually the real size of a poodle.
Quite a lot of people don't know that.
Most people think that Toy Poodles are real poodles.
The only time he doesn't show anger, is when he is with animals.
10th Day Of Shooting
We wanted to see what was going on inside his heart.
(Staff) Do you often come to this park?
Yeah, I guess.
I come when I'm frustrated and stuff.
Yeah, like when I'm frustrated or...
Tanaka, who invited us and the camera, was frustrated for some reason.
Something was irritating Tanaka.
But, what is it?
Cheers!
12th Day Of Shooting
The duo from License were worried about Tanaka.
You're chugging it down today.
Are you ok about your hands?
He devours a spare rib with his dirty hands.
You're eating a lot today.
He shows an uncharacteristically large appetite, and a layer of grease on his lips.
It was saddening for License to see their beloved senior, seemingly deteriorate each day.
It's fine, it's fine. They're not fighting over there.
I'll totally go over there, you know.
Why're you getting excited?
OWW that hurts!
License didn't want to cause any trouble.
And so, they just kept on drinking.
Perhaps sensing his juniors anxiousness, Tanaka didn't go wild.
I'm beginning to feel drunk.
Oh really?
We began to notice the sombre expression on his face.
(Staff) How do you feel about License as your juniors?
I like to look after them. Yeah.
They come calling "Tanaka-san, Tanaka-san" for help too.
It's fun right? Everyday.
Yes.
That's what I'm like everyday.
Even when alone?
Mm-hmm.
I'm worried about when you're alone though. It's fine if we're with you but....
What's wrong?
Is he crying?
He finally snapped.
It's fun being with me everyday, right?
Yes it is.
I'm sorry if we said something to upset you.
Sorry.
Take a look at that.
His face is like a Hannya.
It's interesting, right?
It's fun, right?
Just how many times did he repeat those words?
Something that was niggling Tanaka inside, was now tormenting him.
But we don't know the truth behind Tanaka's tears.
Sorry.
He snapped.
The next day, we were unable to contact Tanaka.
13th Day Of Shooting
We were worried about Tanaka.
His manager revealed to us a location where Tanaka often visits.
It was an entertainment district covered in colorful neon lights.
Apparently, there is a store he recently frequents.
There, we found Tanaka spilling with lust and desire.
(Staff) Tanaka-san. Excuse me.
You guys again?
(Staff) You go to brothels?
I do, I do, I do. I go quite often, actually.
I probably go the most out of the Gaki members.
(Staff) Matsumoto-san says he often goes too....
Ohh yeah he does say that.
I reckon I go more often that Matsumoto-san though.
Mmhmm..
We witnessed him putting up a front, and trying beat Matsumoto-san.
What's this?
Got it from a girl.
From Ayumi-san?
Yeah.
The Tanaka Naoki we once knew, is now nowhere to be found.
This is pretty serious stuff.
It wouldn't feel strange at all if you switched Tanaka's face with Hamada's.
That's his everyday life.
But I only said that because I was asked though.
It's part of a joke.
But I only said it because I was asked.
He's not here today either.
Good morning.
Put that away now.
His hands a dirty too.
It was my bad. I'm really sorry.
It was really my bad.
I really feel that way.
Hey listen! He's trying to apologise!
I'm not saying this lightly okay?
I'm not upset at all about that.
I really am like this everyday.
You're not like this!
This isn't Tanaka!
I'm thinking of appearing on TV like this from now.
That's not possible.
There's no energy there at all.
There's no energy because you're not comfortable doing this.
I'm going ahead to the studio now.
Yes.
I'll go on ahead.
You can't be on TV like that!
Do you want an apology?
TANAKAAA!
Wow.
It's over. It's all over for us.
Did I really say something so bad?
Well for him, it must have been, I guess.
He's not listening to anything we say.
More importantly, is he gonna appear on other shows like that too?
STOP CHATTIN' AND HURRY YO ASSES UP!
We'll go.
I'VE BEEN WAITIN' ALL THAT TIME!
AND YOU'RE JUST DILLY DALLYING AROUND!
Let's go, let's go.
LET'S GO!
DILLY DALLYING THE FUCK AROUND!
This is the last time I'll work together with him.
LET'S GO!
Hey Tanaka, let's break up.
I can't take it.
This footage of us following Tanaka is fiction
every item that Tanaka used
and every person Tanaka came in contact with
were all priorly prepared for this act.