Oyakoukou tte nani? tte kangaeru
What is devotion to parents? I wonder
Demo sore wo kangaeyou to suru koto ga mou
But trying to think about it
Oyakoukou nano ka mo shirenai
Could be devotion itself
Kodomo no goro tama ni kazoku de gaishoku
When I was a child,
my family would sometimes eat out
Itsumo tanonde ita no wa CHIKIN RAISU
I always ordered Chicken Rice
Gouka na mono tanomeba nido to tsurete kite wa
I thought that if I ordered the expensive one
Moraenai you na ki ga shite
They wouldn't take me out anymore
Oya ni ki wo tsukatte ita anna kimochi
The way I considered the feelings of my parents
Ima no kodomo ni rikai dekiru kana?
Could kids these days understand?
Kyou wa KURISUMASU
Today is Christmas
Machi wa nigiyaka omatsuri sawagi
The town is lively with festivities
Shichimenchou wa yappari tereru
Turkey feels too awkward
Ore wa mada mada CHIKIN RAISU de ii ya
I am just fine with Chicken Rice
Binbou tte nani? tte kangaeru
What does being poor mean? I wonder
Hekonda toko hekonda bun dake warai de
With depression upon depression, laughter
Mitasu shika nakatta ano koro
Was the only way to fulfill those times
Mukashibanashi o kataridasu to kimatte
Whenever I start talking about my past,
Binbou jiman desu ka to iu kao suru yatsu
They say "Bragging about how poor you were?"
Demo are dake binbou dattan da
But I was that poor
Semete jiman gurai sasete kure!
Let me at least have some pride about this!
Saigo wa warai ni kaeru kara
Eventually, I will laugh about it
Ima no kodomo ni iyagarareru kana?
But will kids these days dislike it?
Kyou wa KURISUMASU
Today is Christmas
Machi wa nigiyaka omatsuri sawagi
The town is lively with festivities
Dekai KEEKI motte koi
Bring me a big cake
Demo maa zenbu tabekireru SAIZU no na
But make sure it's small enough to finish it
Akasaka PURINSU o osae toke
Forget the Akasaka Prince
SUIITO to made wa iwanai ga
I am not calling for a suite
Shichimenchou motte koi kore ga shichimenchou ka
Bring the turkey, is this it?
Omotteta yori dekai na
It's bigger than I thought
Yappari ore wa CHIKIN RAISU ga ii ya
I am still alright with just Chicken Rice