Uwaaah!!
TL: DCSUBS
TM/TP: BQ00
I pulled my ass!!
Famous Series
Silent Library!
Tonight's Gaki no Tsukai is the famous series, Silent Library!
For the guests, Chidori,
Powered up punishments!
The punishments have been powered up for our guests, Chidori!
DOWNTOWN
RECIEVES BACK TO BACK
AND WHY DOES DOWNTOWN LOOK SO DEFEATED!?
PUNISHMENTS!
Extremely Rare!
DOWNTOWN'S REACTIONS!!
RARELY SEEN DOWNTOWN'S PUNISHMENT REACTIONS
A LIBRARY IN THE CITY
It's fine to go home now right?
Why would we go home now?
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Tsukitei Housei
Endou Shouzo
Tanaka Naoki
Sorry...
Chidori
Tl Note:Nobu is the Tsukomi and Daigo is the boke.
Nobu
Daigo
It's like it's already over
This is much is in there
The person that draws the skull card
Has to take the punishment written on the paper
Daigo, Pick first.
No thank you...
Shoehorn
Forehead
Slap
Punishment
Shoehorn Forehead Slap
Why's it gotta be that... It hurts...
It's so scary!
Phew, My turn...
Three... Two... One...
HAMADA
SHHH
Shoehorn Forehead Slap
What a good start!
Seriously?
Alright!
What the hell!
They can't scream or talk loudly
Because they have to think about the people around them
Just stop it...
Seriously?
We can't do this..
I already want to quit!
Please... No more!
It was only the first one.
Stomach
Pinching
Punishment
Stomach Pinching
Who is it going to be
Go ahead.
My hand won't move.
This is really hard
Three two one...
Yes!
DAIGO
SHHH
Stomach Pinching
Who's gonna do it?
Hamada
Hamada will grab and twist the sides of his stomach
Why you?
He's a crazy person...
He's not a crazy person...
He's a completely crazy person when it comes to this
It's common knowledge
It's common knowledge?
After you Hamada.
It hurts!
That wasn't pinching
That was stabbing with your nails!!
What the hell...
Scary...
Here we go.
Stinky
Air
Canon
Stinky Air Canon?
Punishment
Stinky Air Canon
I don't want this...
After you, Daigo.
We'll start from Daigo.
Three... Two... One..
ALRIGHT!
DAIGO
SHHH
STINKY AIR CANON
This is good!
Please wait!
I might puke from this!
It's fine!
I actually might puke from this....
Just wait!
Is it alright if I throw up?
No... What the hell are you saying...
He did eat before this though...
Genki Ichioka
Denjirou Army will be operating it
This is it?
It smells...
Stink Extract has been soaked into the socks
Wait it's-
Be quiet!
There it is!
Why the hell did I get punished!?
To check the smell
Disgusting worn socks are being put into the air canon
Alright, Let's do it.
Put it in.
3,2,1...
I'm gonna puke
It stinks
Don't you dare throw up!
Damn, It stinks.
Let's continue
Alright.
Loan Receptionist
Shock
Stapler
Punishment
Shock Stapler
What does that mean?
This is terrible
Endo! Change with me?
You want to change?
You don't know the cards
I don't know but
We'll switch
Alright
Housei. Change with me?
Change?
This is kind of scary now
Is it fine with you?
It feels like it's gonna be one of us three
No clue
Three, Two, One...
MATSUMOTO
SHHH
Electric Shock Stapler
SERIOUSLY!?
Alright!!
IS THIS FOR REAL?
Things like this happen!?
If you just left it alone it would have been Housei.
Seriously?
I seriously hate electric shocks...
Go ahead
I'm not that kind of person!
Doing this wasn't the reason for my debut...
Everyone's the same
Holding it's fine right? Once you press it'll shock.
When you squeeze you get shocked. Squeeze whenever you want
Squeeze it.
I've gotta do it myself?
Doing it by myself is worse!
Well, We can't do it.
Go!
Do a countdown!
A countdown!
Here we go!
From three!
Three!
Start from eight!
That's long.
5,4,3,2,1 go
I pulled my ass!
He just got so stiff
This is bad
Stand up
Give me a minute
It hurts
Enough already...
I'm thinking I was set up for that one!
Well with the card change
You clearly switched them
I'm done with it! I'm not changing cards again!
I'm fine with whats left
Scalding
Hot Swim
Cap
What the hell...
Punishment
Scalding Hot Swim Cap
I'm still feeling it...
It's still in me...
I'm still shaking from it!
It's still in me!
Three, Two, One...
MATSUMOTO
SHHH
Scalding Hot Swim Cap
It was so close to Daigo
MATSUMOTO'S HOT REACTION!!
Please!
Please...
No!
MATSUMOTO
SHHH
Scalding Hot Swim Cap
Make him sit!
Scalding Hot?
Enough...
Scalding Hot Swim Cap?
Bathed in Boiling Water, They'll put a swim cap on his head
It's boiling
Wait...
Why is there so many...
This is bad!
This is no good.
Did you guys do a simulation?
Hot!
Did you do a simulation?
What the hell are you doing?
What the hell?
Come on!
Please don't freak out!
You didn't do a simulation did you?
They did.
Come on! Please!
Hurry up.
IT BURNS!
That was fast
He took it off so fast...
Enough already...
Your hairstyle is so cool now!!
Your hair looks so good!
Like a Paris Fashion Week designer!!
He's a Paris Fashion Week designer!
Give me a minute
Isn't this more than enough?
I agree
There's still more...
How many?
Sweat
drenched
Old Man
T-Shirt
This is terrible...
Punishment
Sweat Drenched Old Man T-Shirt
This is one that'll make you puke
Matsumoto would go well with this Old man thing
You're right
If I get out on this one...
I'm gonna be suspicious of all of you!!
Something is off about this
How about you take a card first
This and... this...
Which one!?
I'm gonna divide them alright?
Why the hell?
You have this
It's fine like this?
Three, Two, One...
TANAKA
You got it! A really bad punishment!
SHHH
Sweat Drenched Old Man T-Shirt
This is gross
You're gonna be put into it.
How does this work?
A box with a lid on it is put on the head
Why?
He's got a lot of sweat
This old man again?
The Old man has gathered a lot of sweat from wearing a Sauna Suit
He only took off his jacket
Old man Sweat+Stink Extract
I can smell it already
UWAAH! IT STINKS!!
Because they have to think about the people around them
They can't scream or talk loudly
What the hell are you doing?
Working with you is scary
The smell...
It's still there?
It's not leaving...
Just calm down
Ah! The last one!
Housei still hasn't gotten one
That's right
Mouth
Water
balloon
Explosion
Huh?
Punishment
Mouth Water Balloon Explosion
I'm getting a mouth ulcer from this
He's talking normally!!
The Kanji is scary
I've got a bad feeling about this guy
Three, Two, One
Housei still hasn't gotten one
NOBU
SHHH
Mouth Water Balloon Explosion
Here we go
This is a new one
A new one!?
A new one!!?
I've never seen it before
Don't try new things on people!
Open your mouth
The balloon in his mouth will fill up with air and water and explode!
Breathe through your nose
Don't open your mouth
I'm gonna die!
I was right before death!
The top of my mouth closed my nose
I was about to die
After a quick fix one more try
Gaki No Tsukai is gonna kill me
It's fine
It's good here right?
This one is pink
Pink huh?
The pink colour is pretty cute
It is
Don't spit it out
Another Failure
What are you doing!?
THE STAFF NEED TO TEST IT OUT FIRST!!
The water was just flowing out
It broke
This?
Rapid
Nipple
Strikes
What the?
What does it mean
I've never seen a 4 Kanji character word like that before!!
I'll pick first
Punishment
Rapid Nipple Strikes
Which one
Three Two one
Here we go!
HOUSEI
Finally!!
SHHH
Rapid Nipple Strikes
He goes on standby laying on top of the table
It's Takahashi Meijin
Takahashi Meijin will strike his nipples rapidly
Takahashi Meijin!
So that's what it means
I get it now
His hair is incredible
Don't be laughing!
Hold him down
Alright after you
What the hell is this?
That was fine
This!?
This is surprisingly better than the others!
It's embarassing
You weren't even hit hard
It was embarassing because he talked about my hair
It was incredible!
That's embarassing. Stop it
His nipple hair?
It was incredible
Current Punishment Count
Just take the next one Endo
Ah. Endo hasn't gotten one!
It's fine!
Just take the next one for us
We're paying you money so do it
Ass
Canon
What is this?
I hate these ones
Enough with the ass stuff
Punishment
Ass Canon
I hate these ones
It'll be fine if its Endo
Three, Two, One!
ALRIGHT!
MATSUMOTO
SHHH
Ass Canon
Enough already!
Spare me please!
I'll pay money!
I'll pay for this to stop!
No way
This is bad!
This is so scary
What is this?
Is this really fine?
Put your feet there
This is fine right?
The angle is the most important!
Match the angle!
Match the angle!?
I don't know anything about the most optimal angle for this!!
Up more!
Up!
Did you not hear me?
His ass will be hit by a canon
Here we go
This is scary!
My ass hurts already!
Here we go!
Three, Two, One!
AH! I TORE IT!
It was really pretty
I tore it
Tore it!?
It was really pretty
Apparently he tore his ass
His ass got torn
It was pretty huh?
Really pretty
Take the next one Endo!
I don't want that
Here we go.
Thigh
Bamboo
Sword
Machine
No way!
Punishment
Thigh Bamboo Sword Machine
Let's take and flip it one at a time
Alright, You start.
No, I'm fine. Yamazaki
Alright!
Pick one Daigo.
This is great!
Hamada's Thighs will
be hit by a bamboo sword machine!
Hamada's thighs will be destroyed by a bamboo sword machine!
Uwah!
Can you lie down here?
Lie down!?
Yeah, right here
It's gonna be quick
He goes on standby after lying on the machine
Lie down!?
He's talking normally!
I've never heard of this one
We've never had to lie down for these!
I haven't heard of this before too
This is no good!
He's talking so loud!
That's good
You're serious?
Here we go!
No! Wait a minute
Three, Two, One, Go!
I still want to use my thighs!
Ah, Thank god thats it
That wasn't - OUCH
Embarassing!
Nice try!
So embarassing!
The lamest thing to see on TV.
Punishment odds level up!!
Now we've increased the skull cards increasing the odds for a punishment!
Enough already!
Lip
Weights
( X2 )
Look!
Why now...
Punishment
Lip Weights ( X 2 )
There's two skull cards
This will be incredible if I survive it
Start from me?
You had the last punishment
It'll be perfect if Hamada gets the lip punishment!
It'll be fine if it's all you
And if Endo gets it too...
Come on Endo!
ENDO
SHHH
Lip Weights
It'll be nice with Tanaka
Alright! Safe!
REMAINING SKULL CARDS  1/3
Today is really incredible!
What are you three going to do?
You pick one Nobu
Pick one, Nobu
Pick one!
The closest to Matsumoto was this one so I'm going with this
Three, Two, One
So close!
The punishment goes to MATSUMOTO or DAIGO!?
It's either Daigo or Matsumoto
Please go ahead Matsumoto.
It's too much for me
So close
This is so scary..
Please pick one Nobu!
Daigo!
Ah! Not Nobu!
You really mixed them up
Daigo!
Please pick one, Daigo!
Honestly pick one.
Then this is yours
You flip yours
Endo and Matsumoto's Lip Punishment
It's real.
ENDO AND MATSUMOTO'S JOINT LIP WEIGHT PUNISHMENT!
Matsumoto&Endo  get the lip weights!
They're joined together
They place a clip on their lower lip while a laundry basket hangs from it
Give me a second
It's fine if you do it alone!
Ah, I get it now
Place heavy items (water bottles) in the basket
You let go of it here
I'm putting the first bottle in!
Here's the first one!
There.
The second one!
It hurts
Enough already
Hamada did it
It'll be good if Endo gets one by himself
Why?
Let's do Endo's..
The last one will be Endo
Bamboo Sword Nipple Strikes
What do you mean?
Let's just check the next one
Let's just check
Face
Compression
Bag
( X 2 )
One that kills
That'll kill you
It's like they want us to die
It's fun and all but you're just trying to kill us at this point
Especially on air
Punishment
Face Compression Bag ( X 2 )
If we don't do this they'll be pissed
Let's just get this done
Then Endo will have the last...
As a special
As a special?
Sorry but  we're relying on you
You're relying on me?
He's only saying that because he want's to see it
I kind of want to see it
Is it going to be on air?
No it won't.
Honestly
Really?
Is there a point in doing it then?
Who got the last punishment
Then you can pick first
I mean I still don't want to
Enough already
Take yours Tanaka
Seriously, What the hell is this?
Alright, Housei
HOUSEI
SHHH
Face Compression Bag
I had a bad feeling about this
Just take the punishment Nobu. You only had one so far
This is tough
Pick one
Go Nobu.
Flip it
NOBU
SHHH
Face Compression Bag
Die!
It ended really well with this
Good luck Nobu.
Oh, They put a balloon in it.
Now I get it
A Nylon Bag covers their heads
So that's how it works...
They put that in and it inflates
A balloon is put in and inflated
The balloon is in the back
Go ahead!
Stop this!
Stop this already!
It's coming!
I COULDN'T BREATHE!
Dangerous... So dangerous...
We would of died in another 5 seconds
That was really interesting
Then let's do Endo's now
Huh?
ENDO'S SPECIAL PUNISHMENT
Thigh Bamboo Sword Machine
Rapid Nipple Strikes
Special Version PUNISHMENT
Endo's special version, Taking on both at once
You should take your shirt off
Alright
Please come here Takahashi Meijin
This is...
Takahashi Meijin will be here. We don't need the mic
MIC
Wait a second
Right?
It hasn't started it but it's already scary
Well, The mic was in the way
Scary...
He has some nice points to him
This way
Wait a second!
Here we go.
Alright start in 3
Here we go!
Make sure
you look pretty
Really pretty!
His face...
So pretty!
Come on Endo!
Give us a prettier face!
He's making a good face!
What are you talking about?
You did it real prettily
SPECIAL TREASURE!!
Translation: DCSUBS
Timing + Typesetting: BQ00
HAMADA'S THIGH BAMBOO SWORD MACHINE