The First Annual Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende, Chiki Chiki
Never lose your childlike heart!
8 Years Old Contest~!!
What a title again, Matsumoto-san
Well, Gaki no Tsukai started today's show just for this
-8 Years Old Contest?     -Yes
What's happening to people nowadays?
when it comes to the emotions that we once had as a child
or simply a childlike heart,
-aren't we losing those emotions     -I see
So today we're going to challenge a bunch of things as a 8 years old kid,
and whoever behaves like a 8 years old kid the most wins
umm...Anyone can do it!
Everyone must have experienced it!
So just do it!
Competing against others to become the most realistic 8 years old
8 Years Old Contest
The judgement of whether its a 8 years old
will be decided by Matsumoto pressing the button in front
The one that becomes the most outstanding 8 years old
will be awarded with some plentiful prizes!
Well, we're going start the challenge now
Matsumoto will be responsible for being the judge     -Thank you
Okay, let's welcome our first 8 years old kid!
Welcome!
Please introduce yourself
Yamasaki Housei and I'm 8 years old!
We heard that you have some special skills, can you show it for us?
Yes! Come out Rizadon!
Pokemon Gotcha!
Judgement: Housei, 8 years old!!
So the judge decides that he's 8 years old
Cute, cute, very cute
Okay, let's welcome our next 8 years old!
My name is Tanaka Naoki!
and I'm 8 years old!
You also have some special skills right?
-Yes!     -Let's see what you can do
I have a special skill
Let's see what you can do
I do sport fukiya (Japanese blowgun)
So I'm good at fukiya!
Then can you show us please?
And because I've been doing sport fukiya for a long time
So now I can blow fukiya in whatever position
-Sounds good     -So can you show it for us?
Not just blowing it normally
Say it all at once in the beginning!
-Well, well     -Yeah, he's just 8 years old
Ah, looks awesome
-I'm ready to start!     -Yes please start
Judgement: Tanaka, 8 years old!!
-He just failed though     -That's exactly why
No way! No way!!
Let's welcome our next 8 years old kid!
Okay, please introduce yourself
I'm Osaka from Fujimoto! Oops...
I'm Fujimoto from Osaka!
I'm 8 years old!
Judgement: Fujimoto, 8 years old!!
Do Fujimoto-kun also have some special skills?
Yes!
I can say the number's digits very quickly!
Then please show it for us
Yes!
Units, Tens, Hundreds, Thousands, Tens of Thousands, Hundreds of Thousands, Millions, Billions...
Oh yes!
Judgement: Fujimoto, 8 years old!!
Could that be 8 years old?
That was awesome
Okay, let's welcome our next 8 years old kid!
Where are you going?
Ah...it's here
-Please introduce yourself     -What are you doing!
Please introduce yourself
I'm Komoto Junichi from Aichi prefecture Nagoya city
He's so nervous
So he seems to be quite nervous
Yeah it's his first time to be on a TV show
Is this your first time to be on a TV show?
The first time was when shopping with my mom before...
Don't cry, please don't cry
There's no need for you to cry
Do you have any special skills?
Umm...I can flip my eyelids
Be careful okay, are you good?
No need to overdo it
He did it?
Is he done with it?
Ah, he did it?
-Not at all     -Not really isn't it
Not in a good condition today right?
Not good
I can do it!
Oh really? Then give it a try
Everyone please give it a try
Yeah please try it everyone
Let's start from the ones that did it
Raise your hand please
Raise your hand and Matsumoto-san will judge
Ah Yamazaki-kun, let's see Yamazaki-kun
Ah Housei-chan looks good
Judgement: Housei, very 8 years old!
House-chan is awesome
Enough, it's good enough
It's starting to hurt right
Your eyes are starting to hurt right
Yeah, so let's stop, let's stop
It's fine
No, I actually did it
Well, well...
Ouch!
Hey, what's happening over there?
Chill out okay
What are you guys doing!
Judgement: Kawamoto & Fujimoto very 8 years old!!
Very 8 years old... So what's going on over there?
Okay, let's welcome our next 8 years old kid!
Please introduce yourself
I'm Yamamoto Hiroshi, 8 years old
Hiroshi-kun do you have any special skills?
I can clap hands very loudly
Eh, what's that
Then please show it to us
Awesome, very awesome
Everyone give it a try
Awsome, very awsome
Judgement: Everyone 8 years old!!
Okay, thank you all
So they won't stop until you say so
So now let's get started
Beginning with the 8 years old quiz!
What's 8 years old quiz
Matsumoto-san will ask questions easy enough for you all 8 years old to answer
If you know the answer please raise your hands up vitally
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yes these kids are full of energy
So let's get started, please ask the first question Matsumoto-san
Okay!
Who is the president of America?
I know! I know! I know!
Kawamoto-kun please
My mom told me before when watching the news
My mom told me before, and my friends talked about it too
And my mom told me before as well
-Oh, oh     -This kid talks a lot
Eh... what was it... what was it...
I know! I know!
So what did your mom say? Do you remember?
My mom said do not do anything naughty
Judgement: Kawamoto extraordinary 8 years old!!
What kind of 8 years old is that...
He just forgot about it, it's fine
Then Housei-kun please
You mean the King?
Yes?
So the King right?
What about the King?
Pokemon Gotcha!
Judgement: Business 8 years old
Donald...
-Donald...     -Donald
This is a hint, the name comes up in card games
Yu-Gi-Oh!
Judgement: Kawamoto 8 years old!!
Ah! Hanafuda is it? (Japanese playing cards)
Donald Hanafuda president
Judgement: Fujimoto uncle!!
-Let's go for the next question     -Okay
What did you dream last night?
That's a good question, what did everyone dream about last night?
Fujimoto-kun please tell us your answer
I got eaten by a huge dick last night
Judgement: Fujimoto very 8 years old
What about others, Housei-kun?
Pikachu became really big
and then I got surrounded by a lot of them
and Pikachu then started to poo and poo...hahaha
Judgement: Housei 55 years old!!
The dirty joke there is a bit inappropriate
Yeah you're right, it does feel inappropriate
Yes!
What's going on?
This is the Goodnight time
They're probably feeling tired
So you can take a nap if you want to
Well, yeah they're 8 years old
Yep
So here comes the Goodnigh time
Please take your time to rest
Naoki-kun... Naoki-kun fell asleep right
Naoki-kun feels more like a salary man
instead of 8 years old
Housei-chan dreamed about something just now right?
You dreamed something right, Housei-chan?
Yes, I saw a dream
What did you dream in this short time
What do you think I've dreamed of?
I don't know, please tell us
I just saw a dream...
Then?
I ate some Manju (Japanese confection)
Judgement: Housei 55 years old
Let's go for the next question
What is the most difficult phrase you learnt recently?
A difficult phrase for a 8 years old...
What happened Yoshi-kun
I made...the table lower
Judgement: Yamamoto very 8 years old!!
These things do happen
Eh, no way
Yes! Yes!
Naoki-kun
Adjacent buildings
Judgement: Tanaka very 8 years old
Well, good enough
I just learnt it at school
Yes! Yes!
Junichi-kun
Hercules beetle
Judgement: Kawamoto 8 years old
Hiroshi-kun
Fjord
Judgement: Yamamoto 8 years old!!
Yes!
Fujimoto-kun
Kashima Antlers
Judgement: Fujimoto extraordinary 8 years old!!
Okay let's keep going, Housei-kun
Konjac jelly
Judgement: Housei 55 years old!!
You're 55 years old, you're always 55 years old
The tempo was good just now
and Housei-kun messed it up
Sorry, sorry, let's start again from Naoki-kun
Holiday traffic
Judgement: Tanaka very 8 years old
-Yes, yes!     -Junichi-kun
Tokaidochu Hizakurige (Shank's Mare)
Judgement: Kawamoto 8 years old!!
-Yes!     -Hujimoto-kun
El Niño–Southern Oscillation
-Such a difficult word     -Judgement: Fujimoto very 8 years old
Istanbul
Judgement: Yamamoto extraordinary 8 years old!!
Ootori Ran (Takarazuka actor)
Judgement: Housei 63 years old!!
Stop playing around!
I'm 63 years old?!
Oh! So starting from here!
What happened?
3 years old time!
-3 years old time?     -It's now the 3 years old time
What's that?
While they've been 8 years old for now
They'll again be younger for another 5 years
-and become 3 years old     -Awesome!
3 years old time!
That's hilarious!
So this happens when people are 3 years old?!
Really?!
Fujimoto-kun,
you didn't want to hurt your hands just now didn't you?
Well, well
Hosei-kun, what's going on with you?
I found this thing... It's shining...
It's going to explode, it'll explode
It's dangerous! Run! Run for your life!
Hey, what are you doing!
Finish
This part will be cut
Please go back to your seats
-That was too awful     -Please return to your seats
They're probably a bit tired right?
Oh I see, then let's have a break now
Please take your time to rest
Can I pee? Can I pee too?
Yes of course you can pee
Pokemon Gotcha!
No, you shouldn't say Gorilla!
You said Gorilla just now!
He's saying Gorilla! He's saying Gorilla!
Who is the one that said Gorilla?
Teacher!
Who? Toshifumi said it? What did you say!
Okay, let's have a rest
Yep, let's have a rest...
Are you okay?
Go to rest now!
It's so scary!
During their rest
Having some snacks and comfortably enjoying their rest
Soon, the 8 years old contest will become a hell for them...
Reacting as a 8 years old
Matsumoto-san, what is this about?
So now, there's a box in front of everyone right?
-Yes!     -Yes!
The box is filled with all kinds of different items
Please react as a 8 years old after seeing the thing inside
Each box is filled with different things
Oh, I see I see
But before that...
3 years old time!
There's a bird! There's a bird here!
Okay, it's enough
Finish
Okay, please go back to your seats
Please drink some water
Because they're at this age, their body needs water
And they still need to show their reactions next
There's no water?
Are you okay?
Yeah there's no water for me...
Oh there's no water for you? Then never mind
Pocari...
Yes? There's obviously no Pocari...
Matsumoto-san, who's having which box is not decided yet right?
Yes of course
You can choose whichever box you like
Oh yes! So I can choose any box?
Yes, but there's different drawings in front
Which one will you choose?
How is it?
-Oh a car!     -Car!     -Car!
My dad has a car so it's gonna be mine
My dad has a car too!
Everyone's dad has a car
My dad has 100 cars though
Which one is the 3 years old time button?
This one
I like animals instead
3 years old time
Finish
It's finished
5 years old time
Give me boobs! Give me boobs!
3 years old time
Hold on to 3 years old time for a while!
Okay 10 more minutes
Goodnight time!
Good for you all
So tired, so tired
What a lovely Goodnight time
Naoki-kun fell asleep while standing
He must be very tired
Naoki-kun don't even need to lie down
He still looks like a salary man though
Is it?
Okay, finished!
Well, well
Choose the box that you like
Please hurry up though
Don't let me ask you too many times
Komoto-kun are you having a heartache?
Yes, yes, it hurts
So you hurt your heart?
Not that I hurt my heart
But my heart is just not feeling well
Okay I see
Just a bit tired right
So can you continue?
No, I can't do it anymore
What? What did you just say?
Uncle Hamada just now
asked can you continue and you said?
No, no more
While being stressed by Hamada's traumatic requests,
the members still try hard to react as a 8 years old
Wow, what's this?
Ginseng Wine ->
I saw this in my grandpa's house
Not something that makes you happy
Ah, yeah it is
Judgement: Yamamoto 8 years old!!
You thought it was a car didn't you?
I thought it was going to be a car
You should behave as a role model for being the first one to present
Judgement: Fujimoto uncle!!
The next one is Komoto
The box was placed with the kid's favorite beetle
Awesome! So lucky!
Are you even able to catch it?
Aren't you actually scared of it?
Of course he can, he's a 8 years old kid
Judgement: Komoto 8 years old
No way, he asked me to open my mouth
-8 years old!     -Ouch, ouch, it hurts
Ouch...Hey, it really hurts
Judgement: Komoto 55 years old
Open up!
That's scary
Cockroach!
Judgement: Fujimoto stinks
Judgement: Fujimoto business 8 years old
Here comes Tanaka's reaction
It stinks!
Judgement: Tanaka business 8 years old
He actually got a chance
Housei-kun, please open your box!
So cute
Judgement: Hosei 63 years old
Everyone has been exhausted
Who is the most outstanding 8 years old?
So now the contest comes to the end
Matsumoto-san, please announce the winner of this content!
The winner is...
Hosei-kun!
Congragulations to Yamasaki Housei!
I did it!
The winner can get a plentiful prize
What is it?
So an amazing guest came to today's show
Please welcome our surprising guest!
Who is it?
It's Tora-tora-kun!
So cute! Tora-tora-kun so cute!
It's the Tora-tora-kun that everybody likes!
Are you really feeling happy?
Thanks for coming today Tora-tora-kun!
Did you really wanted to meet Tora-tora-kun that much?
Yes! Yes! We wanted to meet Tora-tora-kun!
Okay, then let's dance together!
Can we?
Awesome!
Dance with joy, dance with joy you guys
3 years old time
Really?!
It's like going to Hamada study centre
He keeps making some strange requests