First Gaki no Tsukai ya Arehende bet it all on one
mouthfull for the 100 thousand yen prize.
Kiki Castella!
Matsumoto-san, this is the 32th entry.
I'm surprised we haven't done this already.
It was about time already.
Why the hell are you laughing?
-Why are you laughing?
No, I was surprised we haven't done this already,
it's what I thought... Sorry.
Here it comes!
The staff wanted us to try 12 kinds of castella but...
Idiots! They only found 10 types!
-Really?
Who will be first?
Everytime Endo goes first...
-Every time.
How about Hamada-san?
Should I?
Hamada-san could win this right away.
If this guy wins they won't know
where to put the star.
Because he can't do anything else!
He couldn't even build with lego!
www.gaki-no-tsukai.com  -  subs by H
Kiki Castella, first up is the six time winner Hamada.
The one chosen is Izumiya's Nagasaki Honey Castella
Ah, Well... This...
His nose is so bloody clogged, huh?
For some reason I'm getting a cold every year.
He ate it.
How about it?
Somehow, there is this firmness, right? This...
It had this quite firm feeling, like, springy.
I'm not sure that makes sense.
The last part of it tasted quite sweet.
So maybe I'll focus on the bottom sweet part.
I see. Quite sharp, huh?
-But aren't all like that?
Yeah, all he did was say the most basic thing about it.
This is my intuition but it's either one of these two.
Just the two?
-One of these two.
Why is that?
Because there was a sweet bottom... feeling.
Sweet bottom feeling?
-Sweet bottom feeling.
I wonder why he narrowed to those two.
-Amazing.
First I'll try this one.
Japan's best Nagasaki Egg Castella.
I don't know, as I thought they are identical.
Try to remember, wasn't there various things about it?
-The sweetness in the end and so.
I know that, now I want to try this one!
It's gotta be one of them.
One of the two?
-Why only the two?
Which one is it?
He said "which one".
-Amazing.
No, no, I'm sure.
Because of the bottom part.
Bottom part?
-The crunchiness of it.
I should just go for it.
Really? He's so confident.
It would be cool if I got it right, huh?
Very cool.
-Would be awesome.
But I could go "Maybe it's that one!"
and turn out to be right...
Well, there are still nine of them to choose, so...
When I said "One of these two"
weren't you surprised?
You narrowing down to only two
was the reason we were surprised.
I see.
I'll go with this one, then.
The one I ate was...
Japan's best Nagasaki Egg Castella...
Wrong!
You should have tasted some more.
-True, you should have.
But I said-
-Look, a man from Holland.
Only to the castella... It remains... $%&@!!
What?
-I didn't understand.
That works I guess.
-It's a punishiment after all.
Wait! Scary! Scary!
Did it hurt?
-The impact is very scary.
Which one was it?
-This one, the other one you chose.
The one I said?
-Yes!
How did you know?
-It's easy.
I just looked for the ones with crystal sugar.
The others didn't have it.
-What!? How did you know yours had it?
What? It's there.
-But this one also has, and this one...
So those the only two that had visible sugar.
Here, see? It's sticking out.
I'm so thankful for this!
I see...
I think we can do this!
Now the staff will start looking out for this.
You all win we'll take 400 thousand yen from them.
I haven't looked yet to see how the staff faces are.
They don't look so happy.
Next is Tanaka.
Found on convenience stores,
Sweet Factory's Moist Castella is selected.
Is it fluffly?
-Yes! And there is no crystal sugar.
Ah, sorry!
-You're the worst.
We can't pick it up for you now.
-That's the rule.
That rule was just created.
I kinda feel bad for him.
First of all,
I'm trying to figure out which
one to choose, by their looks.
Is that so?
-Yes.
Should I go for the most expensive one?
The one in the golden box.
-Yes, it costs 3800 yen.
Here I go.
Completely wrong!
Maybe because of the hint I can tell,
but it's completely wrong.
It was way fluffier.
Also moist.
Somewhat... Heavier.
Because this is different, immediately...
I can say it is different.
You said it already.
"Because this is different
I can say it is different."
The one I ate was...
...not Nagasaki Honpo Castella!
Now the opposite!
The cheapest one, 150 yen.
It'll be completely different.
Huh?
Which kind was it?
-"Which kind was it?"
Is this it?
The smell and feel...
Are exactly the same.
The entire feeling when eating it...
Even the taste is the same.
This nice feeling...
Was it honey?
It was honey!
The sweet flavor I felt
was from the honey!
Well, that's obvious.
It's how they make castella.
This is it!
Until now, when we did this,
a lot of times I went "This is it!".
But honestly I knew I could be wrong.
But this time,
this is really it!
I really think so.
What confidence...
-There is no doubt!
The one I ate was...
Sweet Factory's Moist Castella!
Dancer Producers
Nakamura Yoshinobu  -  Kobayashi Hiromitsu
It's been a while we haven't seen this, huh?
-True.
Thank you very much!
Did you really know?
-In the end I thought:
"This is it, it's exactly the same!"
Just with the flavor?
-Just the flavor.
The third one is Endou, chosen for him is:
Bunmeido's Slice Castella.
What are you doing? Geez...
That is just wrong...
-No, no!
I'm trying to keep it
in my mouth to see the
absorption of the sponge.
That joke sucked.
Sweet... This is very sweet.
There was no crystal sugar so...
I'll look for that.
You can feel it's crunchy when it does.
In the world of comedy it is said
that Endou is the #1 idiot.
I'm not stupid.
The one who said that is the real idiot.
Should I try this Nozomi one?
Should I try this one?
-Sure, go on.
I don't know if I said this but,
I did a blood test just today.
-Is that so?
So, in a sense, I'm doing this like Endou would.
This is not sweet at all,
completely wrong.
The one I ate was not
Sera Rouge's Top Quality Castella!
So fast.
-Yeah, I can do this.
It was not Moist Castella.
Feeling like it's homework, using sweetness
as guide, he splendidly clears 4 brands.
Bunmeido is very popular isn't it?
-That's true.
So I'll try this one,
Bunmeido's Castella.
Man, this is close!
The one I ate was not
Bunmeido's Slice Castella!
That was lame.
-What a shame.
This is hell isn't it?
You have no discipline, train your taste buds!
Right!
-Understood it this time.
Ugh, I'm sorry!
Next is the man who missed
eight years in a row.
Chosen for him is
Sera Rouge's Top Quality Castella
There!
-Did you chose it?
Crystal Sugar
Which one is it?
Here!
We chose one.
What's wrong?
Thank you very much!!
What's wrong Housei-san?
-Surprise!
This is the first time you were kind to me!
Thank everybody.
-Thank you everyone!
You sure laughed a lot.
Is this real? I'm so happy!
Did you eat enough?
-Yes, enough!
Like this it will be impossible
to get it wrong.
That's true. Thanks to the
kindness of the people.
Well, just like Hamada-san said, it has to be
either of the ones with crystal sugar
I'm going for the one Hamada-san didn't choose!
How about the crystal sugar?
There are lots!
Crystal sugar, check?
Crystal sugar, check!!
This is it...
The sugar is completely...
Wait a moment...
The amount of crystals is wrong...
But it's exactly the same sugar.
Just like this, the sugar.
This is it!
Please be this one!
The one I ate was...
Izumiya's Nagasaki Castella!
You're joking, right?
You have no sense for words or for taste!!
Wait... Let me try again.
Nothing you can do now.
-This part is scary.
Yama-chan, it was this one.
What is that?
This was it. Nozomi Castella.
We chose that, and when we
gave it to you, we realized,
There was one more with crystal sugar.
"It's there!!" We all thought.
You knew I would never
choose that one then?
With me all happy there.
We knew you'd focus on the two...
-And me saying "thank you!".
When I said I was thankful,
what were you feeling?
Last is the man hoping to get it right
after seven years, Matsumoto.
The one chosen was...
Ah!
I heard you go "Ah!"
You found crystal sugar!
For sure you found it!
You said "Ah!", man...
Then Hamada goes "What the hell are you doing?"
Specially chosen for Matsumoto, is the one
with crystal sugar, Nagasaki Honey Castella.
Here I go.
Matsumoto bites the side without crystal sugar.
You bastards...
At this point you give me one without sugar?
Ah!
What did you find?
Crystal sugar!
Crystal sugar!!
That went great.
Ah, sweet!
This is so common...
Well, seeing how things went so far,
I know I should not rely
only on the sugar, right?
I'll go for Bunmeido's Slice Castella.
Eh?
Crystal sugar!
There is crystal sugar!
Do you know what this means?
That there can be sugar in any part of it!
That was a hell of discovery.
I have no choice now, do I?
There was no crystal sugar.
You were wrong then?
But I can see it.
You can see it, right?
I couldn't feel it in my mouth!
Can this happen?
The one I ate was not
Bunmeido's Slice Castella!
I knew because there was no sugar.
Looking for the crystal sugar,
he clears 4 brands!
I can definitely find the right one.
Here I go.
There is a load of sugar!
Based on the crystal sugar,
and softness of it,
Perhaps this is wrong.
This is not it.
It stinks!
What are you doing?
It is not my partner!
That's too harsh, it's not that bad.
-It stinks!
Not disturbed by Hamada's gas interruption,
he clears 3 more brands!
Both of the two left have sugar on them.
I'll go for Sera Rouge!
Here I go!
Just kidding!
You really had no good reason
to laugh, I know.
It's really stuck in there...
Is this wrong?
The sugar wasn't arranged
all crowded like this.
Try eating it then.
Yes.
Yeah!
Maybe...
This could be wrong.
Ah!
I have to chose one, right?
No matter which one,
I have to go forward.
Man, I'm so nervous.
What should I do?
Maybe it's this one.
Maybe this.
After this:
Will Matsumoto get it right after seven years!?
It is really amusing. It was funny playing it.
Please have fun playing it!
Heipo-san, please talk to this camera.
-Ah, this one?
Get it over at the show's homepage!
2 left
What do I do?
How many years have it been?
Seven years!
It's been a while...
It has finally come...
What's with that laughing?
What is it you guys?
Hurry up, do it already!
This is taking too long, you say,
that laugh and feeling, what do they mean?
As the remains caught in my back teeth,
the way of that laughter,
who on earth is that?
What do I do?
I can't decide it, it's impossible!
Here I go!!
I'm going for the opposite of
the one I wanted to.
The one I ate was...
Izumiya's Nagasaki Honey Castella!
Impressive! Really impressive.
This really was...
Trusting your hunch no matter what may not work,
somehow I was able to betray myself.
You thought it was that one, right?
I did it!
I'm so happy!