TPF
Right then
Yep...
Today...
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Things will be a different to usual, it's
a special episode...
Yamazaki Hosei
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
And you know, us 4 coming out
text
Tonight's episode will broadcast
Hamada Masatoshi's batsu game
is a bit weird to be honest...
Don't say that
Well Cocorico are getting there
Thank you so much
That's true though
Oh really? We'll keep going
Yeah
But you're ****
Please don't say I'm ****
Today though... we're not important
The main man is Hamada
That's right
Let's introduce Hamada-san
Hamada-san, come in
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents:
Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Translators:
Typesetter:
Proofreader:
Mickstar
(Team Gaki)
Otviss
Nemesismode
**We also have Facebook and Twitter.**
____________________________________________________
**tofupandas.tumblr.com**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
If you're unhappy about anything regarding the episode, please send us feedback at: tofupandahost@gmail.com
Last year in October, when Hamada went against Team Matsumoto in golf
Hamada lost
And because of that, it was decided he would do a Batsu Game
And that Batsu game would be...
Currently, NTV do a 3 second advert 'NTV is now broadcasting'...
And Hamada would have to do this for 24 hours live on TV...
A few days ago, a press release was made for this Batsu Game
And Hamada told everyone how he felt after doing it
The next day, it became a huge thing in the newspapers
The advert gets aired 32 times per day on NTV
And Hamada must do all of that live...
24 hours- Hamada Masatoshi- Now broadcasting
I bet you only saw a few...
19th April, early in the morning
Through the rain, the car carrying Hamada arrives at NTV
Morning...
This way, please...
I'm going to fuck around in the first one for sure
And then go home and sleep
Hamada waits for the first advert, when the phone rings
Staff
A phone call from Matsumoto-san...
Whadd'ya want...
Matsumoto:
Hello
Voice of
Matsumoto Hitoshi
What do you want...
Aaahh~
You going to be alright?
What do you mean?
What you mean 'what you mean' you...
I'm begging you
The first one I'm going to fuck around and...
Hey you...
Stop saying such lame things
What you mean?
You are really, you're just really
you're just so fucking lame...
What the hell do you want?
So umm...
We're going to make you dress up loads
But you'll still
be a lame fuck
Yeah, I know that I'm going to be changing into different costumes...
There's loads of fucking wigs and stuff here...
I'm going to fax
Voice of
Matsumoto Hitoshi
and tell you which costume
to wear
I will be sending you orders
The costume for the advert
will be sent by Matsumoto via fax
So do it in the costume I choose
Okay, I got you
Got it?
Okay
Right then, you will now
say Ganbanbi!  'I will twy my bwest'
Ganbanbi (Twy my bwest)
Hey you, cut it out you fool, that's so lame
Just hurry up and say it
Ganbanbi!
The first fax arrives from Matsumoto
Hamada-san...
A fax has just come through
Look at this, is that seriously the writing of a 35 year old man...?
MISS S&M
Is this seriously the writing of a man who's going to turn 36 in September...?
What a lame ass this guy is...
His first costume is Miss S&M...
The time for him to appear closes in, so he gets ready...
4 minutes to go...
You really are an ugly piece of shit
Here?!
Even though it's this fucking cold?
First advert is 15 seconds long
Woah woah woah...
It's so cold!
Please read this...
Are you for real?
Look at that...
Walking like a fucking crab
Damn it's cold!
24 hours, Hamada Masatoshi broadcasting
I will be doing the 3 second
adverts for NTV
doing it live all day long
Today it's raining, so everyone please
take an umbrella. Gaki no...
It finished...
You really don't have time to say what you want
A fax from Matsumoto-san...
10 minutes...
The next fax arrives from Matsumoto
This is the fax
Pink Lady...
Please get going
The next costume is Pink Lady
He only has 10 minutes until the next advert
so he gets changed in a hurry in a special box
Surely if a car passes, you won't be able to hear?
5 seconds
Damn...
Sekai Marumie is also being broadcast...
Okay...!
Is this actually being broadcast on TV okay?
Sekai Marumie is also being broadcast...
They really can do this kind of stuff, huh...
Wait, this isn't the time to be amazed...
I want to go home for fuck's sake
1 hour since the start
A 3rd fax from Matsumoto arrives
Muscle Man
Will I be able to talk in this...?
Yes...
Why the fuck do I have to dress up as Muscle Man
I just don't get why...
This time, he enters the studio for the show "Jipang Asa 6"
NTV TV announcer
Kazue Sonomaru
By the way Hashimoto-san,
this guest right here has been standing right beside me since before we came back
Downtown's Hamada Masatoshi-san has
come to the studio. Good morning to you...
Good morning...
Really great work...
Next is the 3 second advert
Jipang Asa 6 is also
broadcasting
Jipang Asa 6 is also being broadcasted!
Thank you so much for stopping by
I never knew that you were that big but...
But anyway Hirashi-san, about today's weather...
It is as expected... rain...
Oh fuck, I shouldn't be here should I...
Right, so looking at this morning's weather...
It went straight to the show from the advert
and Hamada got in the way...
I was just thinking, 'Why am I still on the TV'...
Over 3 hours since the start...
Female shell diver
The next fax from Matsumoto said 'female shell diver'
Why the hell do I have to be a diver...?.
We've only done 3 so far...
Why do I have to go here of all places...?
Over here please
Oh shut the hell up...
Don't tell me like it's normal...
Oh man, something's coming
Super TV is also being broadcast
And yes... the wind is getting stronger...
There's only 4 minutes until the next advert
Hamada rushes to get changed
Matsumoto's fax says 'Stan Hansen' (wrestler)
Stan Hansen
45 seconds...
I had no time here...
Yeah...
I don't get it...
NTV announcer
Fukuzawa Akira
So you will say 'Zoom in Asa' also
People on TV must be thinking, 'What the fuck'...
Who the fuck am I meant to be...?
Zoom in Asa is also
being broadcast
Okay, thank you very much
It's 9am, and 5 adverts have been completed
You can just cross out a few more as well, you know...
Bunkin Takashimada
Next fax from Matsumoto says 'Bunkin Takashimada'
I just read your horoscope and...
It says, 'People from the Year of the Bull will be forced into doing something annoying and dull'
Hamada is born in May which is the Year of the Bull
No way...!
You will be forced into doing something annoying and dull...
If you do this properly
You can make that step up
This time, he will be on 'Look Look', so he heads for the studio
It's just news in the morning after all...
Hamada waits to do his commercial shoot
After the commercial, we will go to Wakabayashi-san's news corner...
Please come over here
Great this didn't become news on this day, eh...?
Must be very tough...
TV announcer
Masako Usui
Fumio Matsunaga
Yes it is, I don't know why I have to dress up like this
15 seconds...
Yeah, why do you have to dress up like this?
I know, right...?
Like, what's that all about...?
Look Look is also being broadcast!
Main headlines, what's on the newspaper!
You just don't know what to say...
Only 14 minutes until the next commercial, they go downstairs and wait...
Speed skater
That was a bit of a shock...
Really...?
He gets changed into a 'speed skater'...
Why am I dressed like this...
So what do I have to do...?
Tuesday Suspense Drama is also being broadcast
5 hours gone, we start to see fatigue on his face
And his next costume will be...
Warette Koraeta is also being broadcast...
Miniskirt police woman...
Miniskirt Police woman
Okay...
11am, that man comes to visit
Mornin'...
Mornin'... You working hard...?
It's so fucking obvious that you've just woken up
Yamazaki Hosei
No, no... not at all
You haven't been watching, have you...
No no no... anyway, here
Don't you 'anyway, here' me... You've just woken up!
You haven't been watching, have you...
You working hard...?
I've been thinking of a lot of ideas, too...
And like about the
costumes and stuff...
Oh, just go home...
Oh, it's come...
Dango 3 Kyoudai
Hamada-san
Dango 3 Kyoudai has come through
You do it for me
No no no...
I'll let you do it once, how does that sound...?
I mean, in all seriousness I do really want to do it
Dango 3 Kyoudai, right?
I've got 3 ideas...
So first off, I want you to be REALLY enthusiastic
Dango 3 Kyoudai is also being broadcast
Go ask the line I have to say next or something
What does he have to say?
Sanma Goten is also being broadcast
'Sanma Goten is also being
broadcast' whilst laughing and then at the end
Show it to the camera or they won't understand...
Do it like this
Like this?
Damn, that's an annoying face
That's great, let's do that!
Sanma Goten is also being broadcast!
Okay
That was great
Wasn't that really lame?
No no no...
I mean you looked really ugly...
But it was good
And another fax came from Matsumoto...
The next costume is 'stewardess'...
Why does that guy not sleep...?
That's true...
Uta no Daijiten is also being broadcast
God, that's an annoying face
9 hours since the start
Gakideka
His fatigue is reaching its limit but he's not even half way
He gets himself together and heads to the studio
This is the one I hated the most...
Literally...
Old women looking at me the whole time...
Look at that...
That would be awful
The guests behind you are clueless as to what's going on...
I know...
Only person who's got a clue is Mino-san...
Omoikiri TV is also being broadcast!
Old women everywhere...
That is tough
Omoikiri TV is also being broadcast!
Mino-san reacted fantastically to it...
Poor him...
Seriously, Hama-chan...
After Gakideka is Onigawara Gonzou
Onigawara Gonzou
As he doesn't have much time, he gets changed quickly
5 minutes...
Yeah...
Heipo, do it for me instead
World affiliated Heipo
Toshide Saito
Romance is also being broadcasted...
He's starting to get into it...
The next costume is 'Kusano Hitoshi's clothes'
Kusano Hitoshi's clothes
Kusano Hitoshi
We're literally shoving everything around the waist back
so I look okay but these clothes are huge
Barachiemon is also being broadcast!
18 minutes until next commercial
Great work...
3 faxes come at once...
Butcha...
Security guard
First up is Yatsu Hakamura
Kamaitemo is also being broadcast!
Kusano Hitoshi
NTV announcer
Mori Fumi
Only 10 minutes until he must do a commercial dressed as Butcha in a cafe. Hurry Hamada!
Butcha
He runs dressed as Butcha and gets to the cafe just in time
-ryori Show is also being broadcast
Damn it, they didn't get all of it in...
Next is an NTV security guard
He walks in the restrictive Butcha costume
Security guard
Hang in there, Hamada
I've had enough
It's seriously enough
This time, he will stand in front of the NTV main entrance and do the commercial
A lot of fans come to watch, and Hamada arrives dressed as a security guard
Why the hell do I have to protect NTV...
Downtown Deluxe is also being broadcast
Okay, great
Now, we have done 16 commercials...
It's been 12 hours since he arrived at NTV
and Hamada is reaching his limit
So cold...
As soon as he lies down, he falls asleep...
You've got two minutes...
2 minutes, 2 minutes!
Yeah...
Nandarou-kun
Next is a 15 second commercial
For the next one, he must dress up as Nandarou-kun and do a 15 second long version
I'm Hamada Masatoshi doing the 24 hour broadcast
I've just gotten to the half way point, another 16 times
I'm going to raise my spirit and do it!
NTV broadcast, Gaki no Tsukai broadcast!
Ahhh!!!
Hamada finally gets to the halfway point... What lies ahead for Hamada...?
Damn...
That was seriously something
It must be really tough to meet the other celebrities
And the other people are like 'what the hell is he doing'...
Yeah...
And give me horrid looks, right?
Like when you went to that one in particular...
That must have been really tough
Those old women don't know anything...
Did you guys actually see any?
How many? Surely not many...
1...?
So they just had the TV on and coincidentally saw you...
Anyone could see you once...
You see him just as much on a daily basis...
Yeah...
Wait, is there anyone who watched ALL of them?
Yeah, that would be amazing
No way...
You know, like
if it said like, 'what time I would be on TV'
Yeah, that's true
That's true
So they could just switch the channel then
Otherwise, you have to have the channel on the whole time
And plus, this wasn't about Ma-chan, it was only Hama-chan...
I really got the whole 'but it's only Hama-chan' kind of feeling...
I really felt that... you're just such an incomplete person
I don't feel that...
I see... so no one watched all of them...
Obviously
But sometimes, I did it outside so some people came to watch
Oh yeah, but that was for the Janiizu
Oh, so they actually wanted to see someone from Janiizu
And coincidentally, Hamada-san was there
What the hell are Janiizu doing at NTV?
They were saying 'who's that, who's that?'
No they weren't!
They didn't know it was you
Not at all?
They didn't have a clue
Seriously?
Even when they see him?
I swear he's really famous...
They call him the 'smaller one out of Ichan Nanchan'...
What...?
Is that all...?
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
The 2nd half starts... only 16 more commercials to do
Just when he got past the half way mark
he gets 3 faxes from Matsumoto
here he gets 3 faxes from Matsumoto about his costumes...
Hamada, who cannot hide his fatigue, lets out a large sigh
They move to the NTV Talent Cloak room and he dresses up as an 'eccentric young boy'
Eccentric young boy
City Hunter...
I have to talk about fucking City Hunter as well...?
I think for this one, I'll look to the side...
City Hunter is also being broadcast
Chaplin
He only has a short time, and next up is Charlie Chaplin
The next thing you will say is 'Itouke no Shokutaku' is also being broadcast
Itouke no Shokutaku you say...?
Why the hell do I have to say Itouke no Shokutaku is also being broadcast...
Oh, hello there...
Came to record for his program 'Itouke no Shokutaku'
Ito Shiro
I heard some bad mouthing about my program...
Like 'What the hell is Itouke's...'
No no, not at all
What are you doing?
Well, what are you doing?
What you mean what am I doing? I'm here to record my show...
Oh, you're here today for a shoot?
Well I'm advertising for you today...
Oh really?
Actually, would you please do it with me...?
Since you're here, I've been
doing it alone the whole time
please, just once, go on...
No...
It's just 3 seconds!
15 seconds before we shoot...
Wow, there's 15 seconds worth of advertising...
No no...
Countdown from 10
Itouke no Shokutaku is also being broadcast!
Thank you very much
White Swan
The next one is in 8 minutes, and he must change into a white swan quickly
That's great
Sekkai Marumie is also being broadcast
Hahaha!
That's hilarious
Brilliant
That was funny
You now have a bit of free time...
You have some time off now
Great work
Hamada goes to sleep
SHUT THE FUCK UP
HEY
He finally gets some rest... Even though it's only an hour, Hamada sleeps deeply
This isn't right
Yeah
You shouldn't be allowed to sleep
Excuse me, we need you to start getting ready
If you would...
Matsumoto's next order...
Tamori
Damn man...
You look so old...
He will now go to News Plus 1's weather report to shoot the commercial
He will do the commercial next to the "News Plus 1 weather report"
Look, they're shouting 'who is that'...
Like hell they are...
Te-...
What the hell was that?
They screwed up
It finished...
However, due to a mistake from the staff, came the first failure...
Another order from that man...
When he returns, another order from Matsumoto
Sorry... but that one doesn't count.
So you'll do it again
I've got to do it again...?
What the hell man...
So he will do it as Tamori again
Romance is awesome again tonight...
Was that okay?
Yup, that was brilliant
You just changed the wording...
Next order is to borrow Takeshi-san from Sekai Marumie's costume
What kind of costume will he go for...
Something Takeshi-san
has worn
Damn, this is amazing
He has so many...
Can I borrow this one, then?
Yes.
Takeshi wore this in his program
called: Momotarou Zamurai
Beat Takeshi
The one chosen was Momoratou Zamurai's costume...
Labyrinth is being prepared
9pm. Only 8 more to go. Here, those two guys arrive.
Hello!
Great work
Hello
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
So we are here to */$£&$*
Oh man, we don't understand what you're trying to say
You do realise you're not funny at all, right?
We wanted you to do
this 'Yasugibishi'
No, no, I'm fine
That's like... Tanaka's thing
You know?
It's no one's thing...
Get him a tissue
That's great
Don't be ridiculous
That's perfect
You know what they do, right?
I don't know
You know what I'm talking about
Like this
Yasuki-...
Like this... put your shoulder into it
Your shoulder, like this
And then pretend you found something...
Wait... It's only 3 seconds long
No, you'll be able to get to that point
True
So search for it like this
The bum is important here
Please try it, Hamada-san
And then you find it...
So you find it, and please go and get it
I said it's only 3 seconds long!
What do you have to say next?
It's
Labyrinth is also being broadcast and that's fine but
No, it's 'being prepared'
But since you're doing yasugibushi
So let's say 'Yasugibushi is also being broadcast'
But it's got nothing to do with this...
We haven't got much time so let's practice
Yasugibushi is also being broadcast
That's great
So find something
And approach it cautiously
Go towards it
And pick it up
It's great
Hamada-san, you look terrifying
YASU*&*$& IS ALSO BEING BROADCAST...
That's great
Wasn't that shit...?
That was brilliant
It was definitely lame as shit...
Here, he has 2 hours rest
He has 2 hours rest and it passes midnight
He had 2 hours rest and is recovered
It's a new day now...
What is it...?
Kogyaru
Kogyaru...?
This is better than some of the other ones he's written
Ah- man...
I can't be doing this shit...
seriously, I might just say it here
****** is also being broadcast
And then go home straight away...
Maybe dress as a nun...
Yeah, as a nun
Labyrinth is being prepared...
Matsumoto here sends 4 orders at the same time
Matsumoto sends 4 orders
at once
Seriously, why the fuck is he still awake
Bakatono
First up, Bakatono
Im bored, shall we go to a convenience store...?
Hamada says he wants to go to the convenience store
Get the palanquins...
Great work so far
The palanquins, the palanquins I say
What the hell...
I'm going to buy all of them
Could I get a receipt
under NTV...
Let's go back
Ah for fuck's sake, I shouldn't have come
That was a failure
I bought way too much
15 seconds
Ok
I'm not doing it
I said I'm not doing it
I SAID I'M NOT DOING IT
HEY YOU FUCKE-...
&*£&£*& is also being broadcast!!
8 minutes until the next one
Okay, please get changed quickly
Hamada is getting a bit impatient
This is the tough part where he has to keep getting changed quickly
Who the hell am I...?
First up, Suzuki Sonoko
Suzuki Sonoko
5 minutes to go...
Wait, what? After this one, I have 1 minute?
90 seconds...
Are you serious?!
Damn my face is hot!
10 seconds
Suteritsumorimo is almost... Damn my face is hot!
Okay, 90 seconds!
Next one in a minute
This is a really quick changeover. Suzuki Sonoko turns to Trampman...
Trampman
45 seconds...
That was easy...
Tenshaishingo is also being broadcast...
Okay, 14 minutes until the next one!
14 minutes
I can see through this...
Demon Kogure
And the last one with white paint on his face will be Demon Kogure
This isn't Demon...
Who am I even!?
Labyrinth is being prepared...
Next one in 2 minutes!
Wait, what?
No, 29 minutes
I will smack you man...
29 minutes, you're right, apologies...
The staff who are getting tired make an error...
Shinora-
It's already 2am
Including being dressed as Shinora, only 3 more to go
Yomigaeru Kinrou is also being broadcast
Next one in 2 minutes
What is this...?
Kaminari-san
Next one is Kaminari-san
That was Shinora-...?
Hamada's patience is coming to its end...
I'm wearing tiger striped pants...
You're just mucking around...
Finally, only one more to go
Hamada Masatoshi's 24-hour broadcast...
Finally, only 1 more to go
Right, the last one
What?
Misora Hibari
Misora Hibari...
I see...
This is the last one
The last time he has to do makeup
The staff prepare for the last one too
This is so funny
You look so tired...
You look quite cool though, right at the end
Hamada heads to do the final commercial
24 hours of pain...
He heads to do his final commercial
Final will be 15 seconds
What kind of finale will he show us...
5 seconds...
Sakura fubuki no
Sarai no sora wa
Mabushii Shiho-...
Aoku Susunde
WE'RE ALREADY FUCKING FINISHED!
Great job guys
Great job
They're going to think I'm crying
You know...
We need to change the rules and have a re-match
24 hours, Hamada Masatoshi, let's watch all of them in one go!
NO MAN, WE DON'T NEED TO DO THAT
Damn that was amazing...
WE'RE ALREADY FUCKING FINISHED!
Great work...
Umm, we just saw the Batsu Game
and all but ovewall...
ovewall...?
You were mucking around...
Like too much...
You're taking the piss out of the TV industry so...
let's go apologise to the President...
What...?
Right guys...?
Don't you agree...?
Aren't you going to back me up!?
Oww...
Honestly, I thought he did really well...
Well that's fine, reply then...
Don't just sit there quietly!
But you got to sleep right?
No, I was just lying down and..
We don't know if he really did that over 24 hours you know...?
He cheated?!
Don't be ridiculous
He did
He definitely did, right...?
SAY SOMETHING!
No, I just don't think he cheated...
So what, again...?
We'll battle again
For sure...
I will just say
you want to do golf again?
Wait a second...
The rules are so fucked up
You've always said that, like you're obsessed...
'The rules are so fucked up', 'The rules are so fucked up'...
He does, right?
Since middle school, he's been saying that
Really?
That's a long time!
But... the rules are so fucked up
He just said it again...
But no seriously, the rules are fucked up...
He said it again...
Seriously, how many more times are you going to say that?!
You like baseball, right?
Yes, I do...
Shall we do baseball?
That sounds good
And how exactly are we going to do that...?
Like we have to get him out once, he has to get us out 4 times...
Oh yeah, that sounds great
Wait, what the hell?!
That's great
Are you stupid?!
That's brilliant
I agree
Yeah, those rules sound perfectly reas-
The rules are so fucked up!
That's fair
Stop saying that!
It's like a habit
You just say 'The rules are
so fucked up'
Tennis?
Oh yeah, tennis sounds great
Yeah, with tennis we can do 4 vs 1
Wait, why the hell is it 4 vs 1
That's perfect
Did I ever say anything about being good at tennis?!
But it could be harder for us to be in a foursome...
Yeah
Like we'd get in the way of each other
No no no, I ain't getting tricked
Why the hell not?
Because the rules are so... no, you know what, it doesn't matter...
DON'T YOU FUCKING DARE SAY IT AGAIN
He's quite good at bowling
Yeah, I've heard you're quite good
You are
Shall we do that?
Our balls have 4 holes in it...
Okay
but yours only has one hole
Great...
No, wait...
Be careful, or I will break your finger...
No but don't you think it's fucked up...?
Why do I always have some huge disadvantage...?
If that's the case, you should...
Okay, okay I know
I thought of something brilliant. I will give one person
to you
Okay
2 vs 3...
so 2 vs 3...
Wow wow wow, hold on a minute...
What?
Why him...?
Well I mean, that's probably about what you're going to get...
No man...
It depends on what we do I guess...
He's about to cry...
I don't know then...
You want to do sports though, right?
Well yeah, of course
You used to play football...
Yeah at junior school...
He was quite good
Football?
You're good at ball games, aren't you?
Can we do it though?
You're good at handball, right?
Oh yeah, he's awesome at it
Handball...?
He used to like represent regionals...
For real?!
You do love sports, don't you!
If I went over there, we would win, I'm sure.
Do you want to go over there though?
No, if Hamada-san
chooses me to come over, I would happily...
Then I want to go too...
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
Then I would like to come too...
Yeah, let's do that then!
Yeah, we're coming to your side
We're going to win...
We are young after all
True
Right then, what are we going to do, eh?
What we playing?
Come on, what?
Tell us!
What we going to play...?
ha-.....
What kind of sigh is that!