Tonight's Gaki no Tsukai: The 3rd installment of the Nostalgic Song Drive!
Whenever ANYTHING happened they would make us all sing this song
In this series, they drive while listening to songs they have memories about
However today is a rainy day
It's rare isn't it? There's usually no rain on Gaki
That's true
Yes, Gaki is rather lucky when it comes to weather
On the "No Laughing Series" too
On "No Laughing", there's a lot of trade professionals right?
There's some messed up folks in their ranks too
Rain Men
TN: Rain Man means someone unlucky who makes it rain when they show up
There's a lot of rain men
Messed up?
There's gotta be like 70 of them
There's like 100 staff members right?
I think even more
More?
Hamada, are your hemorrhoids alright?
I haven't gotten the surgery yet
Actually I too, I've got a straight up reserve army waiting
Both of you have hemorrhoids?
A straight up reserve army in waiting
If they break out, I might have to get surgery too
What do you mean "a straight up reserve army"?
They're not hemorrhoids right?
Nah, they're almost, they're becoming like hemorrhoids
Oh really
When you get tired they break out?
Yeah
So on "No Laughing" there must be a lot
I've heard there's actually a lot of hemorrhoid-comedians
I've heard a lot about hemorrhoid-comedians,
But the top of the pyramid is Hamada-san
I'm at a rather low position
Please raise your rank
It's so annoying
TKO Kinoshita, and I think Kosugi from Black Mayonnaise too
Oh yeah Kosugi too
I've heard when it gets really bad he places a napkin there
Kosugi is known for hemorrhoids
His pants chafe him so he places a napkin
I thought "I wanna avoid that"
They say it looks like the crest of a chicken
Woah, really?
No no, that's a different type
They're an anal fistula
Anal fistula?
They're not the same as piles or fissures
They happen in a different place
Seperate from the anus?!
Yes, in inside the anus
It's a hole in a different place,
Inside the anus!
So there's like a tear there
Around the anus
Ow!
Why does that happen? Lack of hygine?
That's pretty rude
No
Well I do think it's rude, but,
That's not why idiot
It's cause they worked hard for Yoshimoto
It's cause they worked hard to grow Yoshimoto from a tiny little agency
Matsumoto-san. Today we're on a drive
Yes
Yes today...
Last time we listened to everyone's nostalgic songs, but this time is different Matsumoto-san
That's right
This time, everyone will record themselves at home, singing the song acapella by themselves
Recording using those nostalgic cassette tapes, really singing all by ourselves
They gave us really difficult homework this time didn't they?
For this drive, they'll listen to acapella renditions of songs they recorded by themselves at home
"Because of this digital age, listen to my analog recorded song"! Music Memory Drive Start!
So everyone sang a song they liked,
Well speaking of songs we liked Matsumoto-san...
Most of us recorded 4
Yes, I did 4
That's true, I did too
Look at this please!
There's so many
They gave me the big one, the case is different
The case is different!
Is that from a past first date?
He's very enthusiastic
He's very enthusiasitc
Someone put a tape in when we get on the highway
Should the driver put his in?
Ah should I start then?
Let's listen now
Even putting the casette in...
Very nostalgic
It was nostalgic recording it
It was!
Enough to make you die....
So serious all of a sudden
Suffering and Sadness, Two or One of those feelings
This is Nagabuchi Tsuyoshi right?
Everyone, from here or there, burdens themselves with it
Stay Dream, it's a famous song
It's not a single right? It's from an album
Yes, from an album
The album Stay Dream
Yes I've heard Stay Dream
Even if you sit down and try to block, the answer is Nothing
He's good
Ah, thank you
Enough to blow it away
Anger or Frustation, one or two of those things
We have to listen to this?
That's what this episode is about
This is what it's supposed be like
It's supposed to be like this
We're not saying this song is bad, but you could have picked a more upbeat song for the first one!
That's true
It may be a famous song, but maybe something more up-tempo would be better
Ah, that's true, actually
Don't get so glum
The voice is really coming through
You're at least singing loudly. You were by yourself too.
That's true, I did this in the living room in the evening I think. Around 5pm.
I thought it would be bad to sing so loudly at night,
So I did it in the evening
We're all stuck in this endless maze
He's got the voice down
Did you...Look at the lyrics while singing?
Yes, I was looking at the lyrics
What the hell is this
Yeah, what is this
And it's raining too...I'm gonna get depressed!
It's a bad atmosphere
Ah it's over now. That was Nagabuchi-san's Stay Dream
When I was in high school and doing my best playing baseball,
It was my senpai's last match ever, and we lost, because of my mistake
So when I was really down about it, like "I really messed up"
That senpai brought a tape to me, and said "Listen to this". And it was Nagabuchi's Stay Dream.
He said "Listen to this, and do your best again"
And I cried
You cried?
I cried, as expected
It was your fault?
It was my fault after all
I felt bad about it, and this song expressed that
I get it
That is...
Enough to make you die....
Enough already
I said enough
Let's listen a bit more
We're listening after my story?
I thought you told him to play it
Ah, so we listen to it again taking to that story into account? ... I, I think I've heard it enough times
Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Timed and Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband
Listen to my singing voice!
Nostaligic Song Drive!
Alright
Yama-chan you go
Please do
You have so many you can't find it, can you?
Give me a sec
Keep in mind, please become a Director
Take the current mood into account
Alright, for now, I guess this one
Alright, go ahead
Alright, let's listen
Let's listen
You recorded this in Osaka?
I did this in Osaka, in my house, while the kids were at school
The cheap sake I drank last night
Listen ...
I told you!
Be a director!
Maybe it's the cheap gin that gave me this headache
It's copying Endo's kind of
The vibe is the same
You bring a hot coffee to me in bed
Asa no Sillouhette - Igarashi Hiroaki
My white shirt hanging over your shoulder
What do you guys think?
This half-assed impression he's doing...
Please don't be gentle
I think he got it wrong
It's not supposed be an impression
It's supposed to be you singing acapella
It's difficult to say "Goodbye"
Like the basics I guess
It was a good thing you said that
Oh really? I'm singing normally though
No no no no
Listen to it
Why does a man try to get a woman?
He is good at this though
Please don't tell me your telephone number
But still this is...
Cause I know too well how sad the end of love is
This is a less well known song right?
Yes, from the album Sand Castle
But like, a more famous song could be better
But I have memories of this song
When are these memories from?
Theyr're really from, when I was in Osaka, before I came to Tokyo
Well it's exactly as the song says, "The gin I drank last night" and then "My head hurts" the next day
And the exact same thing happened to me while I was listening to this
And the girl I was dating at the time, well I didn't really drink coffee
I got her to bring me tea, while she had my white shirt hanging off my shoulder
I got really turned on
You got turned on?
Yes, it was that,
She was wearing just my shirt, my oversized shirt
I'll go then
A woman, something a bit more cheerful
All we've had are sad songs sung by men
Right, of course, I apologise
We're on a drive after all
I thought my song would be good because it's raining
Ah the mood right now?
So Hamada-san's...
Right after we kiss, don't say anything
Your voice is so quiet
Sakurada Junko!
I might break out in tears, that's how much my heart is shaking
Hold on, this song?!
Hajimete no Dekigoto (The first event) - Sakurada Junko
Even if you don't care, I do
So creepy
This is like...
He's singing like he's about to die
Like he's about to die, his last words
Yeah really
It was an act big enough to change the world
His voice is so quiet
It really is
I've been pretending to be mature, following you all this time
Yeah, I couldn't really get my voice out
It's a woman's song after all
He's not singing in the correct key
I thought this song was more passionate
I was singing right after I woke up, so my voice was still gravely
I see, you weren't prepared
The overwhelming tears make me dizzy, and I don't get angry because I love you
Why did you sing first thing in the morning?
Oh no
You were being too considerate to your wife
No no no
You should really loudly
Was your wife sleeping?
You should sing loud enough to make your wife barge into the room
This was the song of our first idol
This is one of her most famous songs
So Tanaka-san?
This one please
How should I say, "The First Experience?", sorry right "The first event"
I'm counting on you Tanaka seriously
I'm kinda worried about Tanaka-san's
Honestly, he's not very good at singing
Oh, really?
Oh really? Tanaka is a bad singer?
And it's acapella too
You could count happiness on one hand
Eh? What is this?
I think Endo knows this one
You need more than both hands to count sadness
This is kinda creepy
Sachiko - Banba Hirofumi
It's not creepy!
This is creepy
Like a haunted tape
Isn't this too quiet?
No matter how clean your heart is, you can still believe in ugly things
Even if you cry now, one day this will be a funny story
Man you're so quiet
It's hard to sing, even though I picked this song
Sachiko, I remember that street
There it is
Sachiko, live on
It really does
His voice really tapers off at the end
Even if it's a sad love story, when you forget the laughing good times,
He SUCKS
He's too quiet, and he sucks
You really are super quiet
He hasn't improved at all
See his voice is breaking
I'll stay by your side until you remember
Hosei-san has told me that many times
It's been consistently bad so far
Just pick a song with a key you can sing!
That's true, I tried so many times
Why did you go and make up rules for yourself for no reason, just sing acapella
Back in Year 2 or 3 of middle school, at an event for appreciating music
At the neighbourhood Toyonaka Civic Centre, Bunba Hirofumi-san actually performed this song live
So that was the first time I ever saw a professional singer live
I was really amazed by a pro singer's awesomeness.
His presence?
His presence
That was really impactful to me. Even now this song,
It was a popular song
I can't forget this song
Man you suck at singing
Matsumoto-san, your turn please
You're right
It's gotta be, this one, I think
You suck at singing
Next, what nostalgic song will Matsumoto sing?
You know of it, Yokohama Harbour
Ah yes
What kind of memories do you have of this?!
Isn't this a really old song?
Oh you know this song?
I've heard the first phrase before
He sucks!
No no listen
His voice is all over the place
A dream sprinkled in the lights of Isezaki
Isezakichou Blues - Mina Aoe
This part, from here\
His voice is breaking
Passionate love,
Dooby Dooby Dooby Doo-ahhh
The light stops
So goddamn passionate
Very passionate
You guys should be this passionate!
Like a dad singing
My memories of this are with my father
Yeah
My dad loved Aoe Mina
This is Aoe Mina-san?
My dad liked her
At the time, she had slightly blonde hair, and had that erotic atmosphere
So my dad would always get excited about Aoe Mina, and my mom would get pissed off
I thought "So creepy"
My excited dad creeped me out, and my angry mother creeped me out too
I really hated it when I was a kid
I get it
Your mom's jealousy
My mom would go "What is that crap? So indecent!"
Don't show your spouse those feelings, right?
I would say mine was the most powerful singing today
No no no
Well there were other powerful ones
What do you think? We've done one rotation
What should we do?
Yama-chan are you going?
Yes
We haven't listened to a cheerful song yet
Yeah
The harbor light changes in the morning
You're going at max tension right away
At the moment, the first seagull flew
Your voice is really strong!
He got us with this one
He's really belting it out
The Day the Gull Flew - Watanabe Machiko
Which number song was this?
This was like the 9th song I recorded
Yeah makes sense
You really got into it
He went off right from the start
Do you think the tears will disappear?
I'm still in love with you
He's very loud
Who was this again?
Wataname Machiko
An off season harbor town
The Gull?
The Day The Gull Flew
AAaahh moi shadow only
"Moi", he's saying moi
The gull flew, the gull flew
Amazing
Amazing right? It's flying
It's flying
I want to clap for this, amazing
Nobody's sang so loudly until now
Yeah, very impressive. He was really into it
He really was
I was totally into it
Is the 2nd chorus in there too?
It's in there
Wow
Only good men have a fondness for the harbor
His voice is really strong!
I was dancing too
I didn't expect to break up
I can see it, moving like this
This one, yeah,
I didn't expect to break up
You gotta have this much excitement
Yeah you're right. Once you try it you figure it out
Only the view of the harbor
You're right, once you try it
The bitter scent of the tide
Shut up
He got told to shut up
You kind of need to go all out when you sing
That's true
So now, the past mood was the worst
I got it, I understand
No more sad songs
This is really, this one is cheerful
It's cheerful right? That's all we want to hear
Yes please, play it
This one is pretty nostalgic
It's nostalgic?
Oh I know this
I already got it
Yeah I know this
Oh Endo you got it?
I got it
You're not a side piece, Baby don't cry
I said that to my friends as a joke, Baby I was kidding
Counting the stars by the beachside
Zokkon Life - Shibugakitai
There's been no improvement
Seriously?
Is this the extent of your vocal range?
What do you mean, c'mon cut it out
No no , my voice isn't monotonic!
Yeah seriously, you sing at one pitch
Seriously?
I thought I sang this well
You make my heart sting so good, more than anyone else
Listen!
Well you are getting into it
Don't give it over, Don't give it over
Yes yes
I guess there's no pitch variation in this song
The best romance, ZOKKON!
Zokkon? Zokkon Love
Yes Zokkon Love
I have 2 older sisters, and my oldest sister loves Shibugakitai
Ah, that generation
She had posters all over her room,
Could you turn it off Matsumoto-san?
Well keep going
He doesn't wanna hear himself singing
Please listen to me
It's hard to understand him or his singing
So this is just a song I've heard a lot, that was my memory
Oh really?
Maan Tanaka sucks at singing
You all suck at singing, generally. That pisses me off a bit
I think this is a song everyone knows
The love between 2 pen-pals
What a somber singing voice!
Yeah for real
This singing style
This song gets you excited
That's true
This is a great song isn't it?
It's a great song
Under a Big Onion - Bakufu Slimp
Yeah this is kinda dark
No, the lyrics are just like that
Cause we're too young, Too far apart
This sounds like a buddhist chant
Why are you singing so somberly?
But it's supposed to be like this!
It's a more cheerful song than this
Cause, I think I got it,
Cause this is a song you sing with other people, it has a different feel
But I was alone singing by myself for a while,
So in terms of excitement, this somberness is inevitable
This mood...
Starting from here, this part it changes
The photograph in the card holder
It's the same!
It hasn't changed at all
It'll go up a bit, just wait a bit more
Cause this is a famous song isn't it?
That smile doesn't waver
See, I'm getting into it
Under that big onion, was the first time I met you
He's trying to hit the note
Listen to the hook, that's what I want you to listen to
Get off at Kudanshita station, and go down the hill
This is like Enka
It's turning into Enka
It is, didn't he say it gets better?
He fuckin sucks
He made it depressing
Yeah, acapella makes the song depressing doesn't it?
I got it. It's depressing
Next Week
Next week: Music Memory Drive finale
More nostalgic songs in acapella!
Don't miss the passion of the soul!
Timed and Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband