TPF
Gaki no Tsukai
Recording Room
Thank you for recording on New Year's Eve.
Thank you.
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hosei
Endo Shozo
I think it's inconvenient but anyway...
License
Fujiwara Kazuhiro
Inomoto Takafumi
That's right.
This show has run for a long time,
but even this show doesn't show
but even this show doesn't televise
all the videos that are recorded, so
This time, we thought we could show
everyone one of those unseen videos.
Every year.
We record too much.
We don't need that much.
2015 Broadcasted on New Year's Eve
Absolutely No Laughing
Detectives 24 Hours
2015 Broadcasted on New Year's Eve
Absolutely No Laughing
Detectives 24 Hours
Last year, on New Year's Eve, 24 Hour Absolutely No Laughing Detectives was broadcasted.
There's a never before seen video that wasn't shown during the program
What will that video be?
At the time it was recorded, there was a video that wasn't shown.
Endo's Verification Prank Video.
My prank video?
Yes.
Eh?
They recorded that?
Yes, they recorded that.
You can feel how the mood changed...
Wait a minute...
What's this about?
The mood really changed.
My prank video?
You have no idea?
I have a faint idea.
I remember there was one show where I felt
something was wrong.
At the end of the year.
Yeah.
It was before the end of the year.
Between October and November?
It was around October, right?
Well, I don't know if that's it.
I really tried my best in that show.
Nico Nico Douga. You had a show, right?
There was Nico Nico Douga.
With Nico Nico Douga, we had
Something like a big discussion.
It was a show.
And they had you?
I was a part of the show, but I thought it was strange.
It was a bunch of super smart people and a super dumb guy!
He straight-up said it.
I kept wondering why.
That was the point.
No, I mean, it was...
The place was just...
I didn't know what was going on.
Something like that.
Well, Endo...
You felt strange?
It felt very strange.
But we're watching it today so,
it couldn't have been that bad, right?
Ah, we haven't watched the video yet, but...
What what we heard from some of the staff was that
there were very few laughs,
Wait a minute.
that's what they said.
Let's just stop this right now.
This is gonna bomb.
But they're not zero, not zero.
I don't want to go through that.
So this is my fault!?
It's your prank video.
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents:
Down Town's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Translator:
Typesetter:
Proofreader:
J-Lan
Otviss
Nemesis-mode
______________________________________________
**We also have Facebook and Twitter.**
**tofupandas.tumblr.com**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
______________________________________________
If you ever see this video being distributed online but not by us, keep in mind that on Youtube
individuals may make money off of sharing fansubs like this that are not their own. Please go back and
support the original creators. Fansubbing is voluntary and is not meant to generate profit. You can
download episodes on our website instead. Thanks for watching!
Let's just see what kind of video it is.
Play the video!
Every day, they conduct all kinds of investigations in order to get closer to the truth.
Closer to the truth
Gasu Kurobikari Detective Agency
A certain man's investigation!
And this time, a certain man's behavior will be examined.
The target is...
Cocorico
Endo Shozo (Age 44)
Cocorico's Endo Shozo. Age 44.
Speaking of Endo...
*The three duties are: tax liability, military service, and compulsory education.
Write down the "three major duties of the citizens".*
Citizen's Three Major Duties
Just that?
Just the three major duties.
Is something so easy really fine?
The three duties that Endo wrote are these.
Life, Meal, Home
Meal?
His idiot character was exposed
He was exposed as the dumb character in Gaki no Tsukai.
However
However...
Guest appearances in Kansai News Programs
ACTING SMART
Lately, we've heard he's made guest appearances as a commentator on Kansai news programs.
He's been acting like he's smart.
I wasn't acting smart.
Is that information correct!?
But is this information correct!?
How far can Endo keep acting smart!?
Thorough Verification
So this time, we'll conduct a thorough verification to see
how far Endo can keep acting smart.
Talking about Japan's future
A Fake Discussion Show was prepared
Without delay, we cooperated with Nico Nico Douga and prepared
a fake discussion show that would talk about Japan's future.
Former NHK announcer
Former METI member
Athlete
Underground Idol
Former Hostess
NEET
Hori Jun
Kishi Hiroyuki
Takei So
Sakurayuki
Hojo Kayo
Kimura Masaki
These six collaborators were tasked with confronting smart Endo.
I see.
Recording Day
Clueless Endo enters the Green Room
No problem.
Excuse me.
The green room was really far.
Quickly going through the show's script
we could have a little meeting?
Excuse me, do you think
Ah, sure, please.
Our accomplice, the director will
ask him about a certain social problem
First, one of our accomplices, the director, will ask him about a certain social problem.
I think I'd like to talk about the TPP.
Well, there's (all kinds of) other points of view
It's a big problem for farmers,
for everything made in Japan.
Like people buying things from overseas
because they're cheaper.
They were expensive because of taxes but,
without taxes, people will buy those instead.
People who think "I'll buy Japanese products"
will now think "maybe I'll buy Japanese products."
Endo starts acting smart using
all the knowledge he has.
As expected, Endo uses all his knowledge on the subject,
I'm not acting.
I'm not acting smart.
and suddenly begins acting smart.
I wasn't trying to act smart.
So that's how it's gonna go.
Kishi, Endo, and Takei,
You're all used to being on TV
so you'll be fine, however
There's the NEET guy and the idol,
and the former hostess...
There's gonna be things they won't know so
we might switch (the subject) over to you.
Right, it's fine.
Masked Idol
Former Hostess
NEET
Sakurayuki
Hojo Kayo
Kimura Masaki
However, there's something Endo doesn't know.
These three collaborators are actually very smart members.
The Masked Idol is an idol enrolled at Todai
The masked idol is actually an idol enrolled at the University of Tokyo.
Now I get it.
Former Hostess is a Kyoto U graduate and social studies writer
The former hostess is actually a Kyoto University graduate and social studies writer.
That's how it is.
The NEET is a young man knowledgeable on social problems
And the NEET youth is very knowledgeable on social problems.
What about this guy?
I see.
Gradually, the three will reveal their intellect
How will Endo react!?
As the show continues, they will gradually reveal their true intellect.
What will be Endo's reaction when that happens?
Clueless Endo heads to the studio
Clueless Endo heads to the studio where the recording will take place.
The Fake Show Starts!
At last, the fake show starts.
Politics, economics, medicine, sports
All kinds of topics are discussed here at "Gendai Nippon"*
*"Gendai Nippon" = Modern (Current) Japan
We begin the year 2016.
We've gathered controversialists who will talk
about Japan's troubling future.
A passionate discussion with our seven samurai of the future.
He's trying to...
Host
Hori Jun
I'm your host, Hori Jun. Thank you.
put on a smart face.
Thank you.
Looks like it.
Raising his mouth like that.
Now,
I'd like to introduce all of our samurai of the future.
First, a former member of the Ministry of Economy, Trade and Industry,
who has recently made appearances in news and other kinds of programs as a commentator.
Former METI member
Kishi Hiroyuki
Professor at Keio University's graduate school,
Kishi Hiroyuki.
Thank you for having me.
There were many things to discuss about 2015, but...
First thing I'd like to ask is,
is Japan's future bright or dark?
I've come to the conclusion that it's dark.
Economics is my specialty, I know that
to make the future bright, things like
"Increasing the rate of economic growth" and
"Figuring out financial reform" are both needed.
Abenomics depends
too much on monetary easing,
and such an important thing as
raising productivity can't be done.
We have financial reform and many consumption
You're acting smart.
tax increases but no results or reductions at all.
He's just nodding.
With the way it is,
I can't say the future is very bright.
Right from the start we have somber comments.
Representing the sports world, a former track-and-field decathlon athlete and record holder,
Athlete
Takei So
The king of the jungle, Takei So. Welcome.
Is Japan's future bright or dark?
I think the future is bright.
Once athletes become part of society,
they should promote young people
to use their energy and make the world a better place to live
Japan would be able to
become a much brighter place, that's what I'm hoping for.
We've had dark and bright outlooks so far,
Now, the tsukkomi half of the comedy duo Cocorico who's very popular in variety shows.
Lately, he's been participating in news programs as a commentator.
It's Endo Shozo, welcome.
Happy New Year.
What will Endo say about Japan's future?
Following Kishi and Takei, what will Endo say about Japan's future?
Ah, what did I say?
I really can't remember.
Endo,
is Japan's future bright or dark?
Well, I've always lived here in Japan,
and I've been doing this job for a while now.
And well,
Of course, my daughter is here too.
Thinking about all those things,
it absolutely needs to be bright.
That's how I feel.
Conversely, is there anything that makes you feel uneasy?
Makes me uneasy?
Well, my everyday life makes me uneasy.
But I think that struggling with all your might,
is something that feels very human.
I think it's fine to struggle from time to time.
That way...
As a person...
What Endo thinks about the future of Japan
Sounds like
Aida Mitsuo.
Struggling with all your might,
Please stop this.
is something that feels very human.
This is the same as the
"Hamada's wise sayings"
episode!
To give Endo a sense of security
we begin the discussion with a friendly topic
I hate this.
In order to give Endo a sense of security, we begin the discussion with a friendly topic.
Here we go...
The future of idols.
Idol Group Masked Girls
Sakurayuki
A current idol, Sakurayuki, is part of a group
Yes.
The Masked Girls, it's really amazing, have you heard of them?
They're idols but they all wear a mask.
Wouldn't it be better if she kept her mask on?
It just doesn't feel complete.
If you take it off, you're not complete.
Endo feels comfortable talking about a friendly topic
Endo feels confortable talking about such a friendly topic.
We throw the following question at Endo
We throw the following question at Endo.
Endo,
What kind of requirements does an idol need to meet
in order to survive in the world of show business?
What kind of requirements for popularity will Endo mention?
In the ebbing and flowing world of show business that Endo knows,
This isn't something to
struggle with.
what will be the requirements to become a popular idol?
Well, if you ask me that...
The Hello! Project idols are the
strongest there is, right?
Everyone who wants to become an idol
want to get in there.
They want in,
but from those rejected in auditions, there's people
who don't give up and think, "We'll do it by ourselves."
Well, these people are also idols, fine idols.
If you asked every one of them to describe
how they see themselves, they would say things like:
Rebellious spirit
Endo really
knows...
Not an elite
But also:
about feelings.
With a firm belief
Like the one ideal they will always keep.
They should be people like that.
Here our accomplice Kishi
will interpret what Endo wanted to say with a smarter explanation
Kishi is really amazing.
There's a very important thing that Endo mentioned just now.
What is really needed in the idol world
and the sub-culture in general is innovation.
Idols are now similar to say, AKB48
they join big groups and
Endo quickly begins taking notes
What?!
they wear matching uniforms.
You're even doing that?
Why?
Idols have started evolving,
What are you writing down?
making something that...
Doing that...
Who are you trying to look like!?
Comedy too,
involves constant innovation, so there's a lot of variety.
It's similar to that, right?
Yes, that's what I think.
Endo agrees completely with Kishi's opinion.
We checked Endo's note after the recording
And after finishing recording, we checked the note Endo took while Kishi was talking.
They checked that?
You took a long time.
Hello Project
Mask
Like
He didn't write down anything
What the hell?
about Kishi's comment.
What the hell were you doing?!
You should have written down the "innovation" thing.
Now then,
let's move on to the main topic.
TPP's future.
Do you know what it is? TPP
TPP is rather...
Basically, it's something that has
That's just...
Endo talks down to the idol.
been planned for many years.
TPP, the Trans-Pacific Partnership,
is a trade agreement between America, Japan and other countries in Asia and around the Pacific Rim,
with the purpose of liberalising trade by providing measures for tariffs, intellectual property and investments, among other things.
Tariffs, intellectual property, investments, etc
Trade Liberalization
Meat, vegetables and other imports will become cheaper
Merit
This will allow imports, such as meat and vegetables, to become cheaper.
It's very good news for some companies.
Japan's domestic products won't sell
Demerit
On the other hand, Japan's domestic agriculture will suffer a big blow.
There's a big concern about its demerits.
Regarding Japan, the TPP has
many kinds of merits, however
there's also many demerits and risks to consider.
You're twisting it.
You can do it.
Everyone, please use your notebook to write
whether it's a merit or a demerit.
That's difficult.
He was about to write his own opinion, but then...
It's serious.
This was meant to bring down smart Endo by making him write his own opinion, but then...
It's pretty hard.
This is important.
Our eyes caught him in the act!!
Our eyes were able to catch this suspicious behavior.
He's gonna copy it. Ah, he cheated!
Kishi's answer is copied by Thief Endo
He just cheated.
He's very quick.
Now then, everyone...
He copied it!
Raise them up at the same time, please.
Demerit, demerit, merit, merit, merit, merit...
Looks like this side is all merit.
Idol Sakurayuki will begin discussing the TPP in detail
Now, the idol Endo looked down on will suddenly
begin discussing the TPP in detail, showing off her knowledge.
How will Endo react!?
Now then, Sakurayuki?
Yes.
It's a merit.
Yes, joining the TPP will place
four of the world's nations
with the highest GDP together,
forming a new economic bloc, right?
That way, these countries will have free trade
That was sudden.
and thus little to no tariffs.
Too sudden.
Foreign trade will improve a lot, don't you think?
After becoming aware of the idol's intelligence, Endo tries to laugh it off.
You asked her before.
I thought she was on my side.
You asked her if she knew...
Furthermore, the former hostess too
It's been said that the tariffs on car parts
will be promptly eliminated, right?
However, most of Japan's car makers
don't even have domestic production.
So it doesn't actually provide any benefits there.
At this unforeseen development, Endo can only look downwards.
That just...
I didn't know what was going on.
How did you not figure it out.
At last, Hori asks Endo for his opinion
I wonder.
This is when Hori asks Endo for his opinion.
We knew this
was coming.
Endo, what do you think?
But this is really, um... uh... this is uh...
I'm a consumer so, um... cheaper things are a benefit.
But if I thought Japanese things were better,
I could just buy Japanese things.
Being able to choose, I think that's pretty nice.
That's how I see it.
Endo on the TPP
Cheaper things, that's pretty nice.
I hate this.
Endo isn't able to hide his surprise at this unexpected development
Endo isn't able to hide his surprise at this unexpected development.
I really hate this.
We're gonna keep going like this to corner him
What's more, we're going to keep this pace in order to corner this man.
Talk Topic
100 Million Active People
Our next topic is the "100 Million Active People" Plan.
With Kikuchi Momoko's appointment as a member,
it became a much-discussed  topic, the 100 Million Active People Plan
Prime Minister Abe explained it as
"the creation of a society where anyone, at home,
at the workplace, and in their region, can play an active role in their society"
No definite details have been explained
However, there haven't been any clear details, which has raised discomfort and concerns with the public.
A sense of discomfort can be felt
Right, here's the question for everyone,
The "100 Million Active People", do you think it can be implemented?
Look at your face.
If you think it can, then write can
If you think it can't, then write can't.
Please write down your honest answer.
100 Million...
Active People.
There's no way
you can do this.
After copying once, he faces another binary question
He decides to take the risk and do or die!
Having just copied an answer, he's faced with another question with two answers.
However, this time, Endo decides to take the risk and do or die.
Now then, are you all ready?
The 100 Million Active People Plan,
Can?
Can't?
100 Million Active People
Can? Can't? Raise them all the the same time...
He took too long.
Yeah.
Go!
"Can't"
Endo, you're the only one who wrote "Can"!
Yeah.
Endo is the only one who writes down "Can".
You added something in parenthesis.
Not to mention,
I wish they do
he wishes they do implement it.
You backed away.
This line is his insurance.
It feels like you're in a gray area.
You didn't commit.
Everyone said it can't be done, so
Kishi, what's your opinion?
Well, the citizens need to feel safe about their future.
If you have that security, then everyone can
begin taking an active role in society.
That sense of security is important
but the government didn't do enough to foresee our future.
You're not looking up.
Just telling them to become active makes them think,
"Isn't that a bit arrogant coming from them?"
That's right.
You're right, you're right.
"You're right"!
They need to present it in a much more specific way,
otherwise we won't know if it's an actual policy
or the government is just telling us
You're right.
to keep trying to do our best.
Looks like you're
apologizing.
I don't think they can do it this way.
I wish they could tell us something more conclusive.
Endo, you're nodding.
It's exactly as they said.
It really is
as you're all saying, you're all correct.
However, I really wish they could do it,
that's how I feel about it.
He goes with the opposite opinion
He goes with the opinion that is opposite to his own,
You switched sides.
And yet, despite being a discussion program
And yet, despite being a discussion program...
I had no choice.
You switched.
that's how I feel about it.
Endo mentions an unfounded idea based on a feeling
He contributes with an unfounded idea based on a feeling.
You're all over the place.
Endo can't keep acting smart, so we ask him this
Endo can't keep acting smart,
so we ask him this kind of question:
Individually, in order to make Japan's future
brighter, what exactly do we need?
If you could appoint a historical figure as our prime minister,
who would you decide to appoint?
A leader, this is interesting.
Everyone, please write it down.
He only needs to write down a person and explain why.
Endo's answer is completely unexpected!
He only needs to write down a historical figure and explain why.
However, Endo's answer is comepletely unexpected.
Raise your answer at the same time, please.
There, ah.
There's a lot of variety, between all of you.
Hanshin Tiger's Manager
Kanemoto Tomoaki
People from very different eras.
You really like him, huh?
Endo will try to overcome this once-in-a-lifetime mental lapse
Endo will have to try overcoming this once-in-a-lifetime mental lapse.
But first...
Kishi.
I chose England's
prime minister during World War 2.
This person's leadership skills were obviously amazing.
He really inspired
his people and helped to encourage them.
Embarrassed, Endo hides his answer.
Put it down!
You did put it down.
He gave so many speeches,
Churchill put a lot of importance
They told you
not put it down?
on using the right words.
Probably.
How about you, Kimura?
I chose Ino Tadataka.
He's the person who created so many maps of Japan.
The studio's staff orders Endo to pull up his answer.
His vitality was amazing, being able to walk all over the country.
Pull it up, pull it up.
Endo?
I chose Kanemoto Tomoaki.
Starting this year, he became the
Hanshin Tiger's manager so...
Yeah.
Well, it's said that even if he broke his arm,
he would still be able to achieve a hit, right?
So, that sort of leader with a strong character.
That's right, for a prime minister.
The question made me think of Kanemoto.
Well then, we've been broadcasting this special show
live on Nico Nico Douga for over an hour.
With our seven samurai of the future.
To finish, everyone will answer.
What are we missing that will make
Japan's future brighter?
Tell us your plan to make Japan better
using a four-character idiom.
Next
Shocking! Endo's four-character idiom!
We've been broadcasting this special show
live on Nico Nico Douga for over an hour.
With our seven samurai of the future,
To finish, everyone will answer,
What are we missing that will make
Japan's future brighter?
Tell us your plan to make Japan better
using a four-character idiom.
You're doing it again.
Really makes one think.
Anything is fine,
it doesn't have to be kanji.
Like if you have a catchphrase.
Can you tell me
how to write this?
"Surrounded by"...
Endo ends up asking about a kanji he doesn't know.
Right, let's go everyone.
Raise your four-character idiom at the same time.
Ah, we got many different ones.
Ah, very complicated.
"Surrounded by enemies"
He just laughed at
the staff's reaction.
I was really surrounded
by enemies.
Once again, Endo hides his answer.
It's the only one
that came to mind.
Again.
Hide it, hide it!
...everyone has their assigned role,
but they could solve it by becoming more flexible.
I think it would be great if society would become aware of this.
Next, Kimura.
It's "Unite in a common purpose".
From an organizational perspective,
it could mean to get together
Once again, the staff orders Endo to fix it
to be able to fight a common enemy...
Endo, you wrote "Surrounded by enemies".
That means everyone around us is our enemy.
Hori is laughing at you.
Why is that?
This is the only one I know... the four-character idiom.
Sorry, that's all.
That's it.
Well, in a way,
Frankly, I'd say it really describes Japan's current situation.
We're in a deadlock.
Is it considering the US-Japan Security treaty and the like?
Yes, yes, considering everything.
Well then, we really got all kinds of comments.
With all your help,
let's do our best to make 2016 a good year.
Let's meet again. Now then, goodbye.
Thank you.
Verification Results
When he can't pretend to be smart,
Endo begins to deceive
I see.
And that was the end of the video.
Endo, why did you write down that note?
Yeah, that thing.
I was wondering too.
Normally, you would have written down the "innovation" bit.
Yes, in the idol world.
I thought you'd made a note of that.
I was thinking that taking notes
could make me look smart,
Yeah, makes sense.
"Ah, that's good".
I was thinking that nobody would look at it.
I didn't imagine it would get exposed like this.
I couldn't act smart with all those people.
Well, yeah, that happens.
That masked idol that was sitting next to me,
at first she kept her pace with me.
With that girl here and the hostess over there,
At first I thought that I wouldn't have any problems answering.
But halfway, that happened.
We watched it, so we know!
That was so slow.
What the staff said now makes sense.
In the video, you used the idiom
"Surrounded by enemies"
For the year 2016, tell us about your expectations, Endo.
Of course, using a four-character idiom!
Eh?
Nice.
Write it down.
He can't use "Surrounded by enemies".
What?
A four-character idiom?
About your expectations.
We'll wait for you, we'll wait 40 minutes.
It won't take that long.
10 minutes per character.
Uh, what about...
Wow.
Are you ready?
Ah, yes.
Endo's expectations for 2016,
as a four-character idiom, let's see it.
Alright then.
My expectation for 2016 is this...
"Once-in-a-lifetime experience"
Endo, this is just...
This is very...
I think this isn't really an expectation.
This is just a phrase.
Actually,
I don't actually understand what it means that much.
What it means?
You don't know?
You should know what it means.
I just kinda know it.
Then how do you understand it?
You should have an idea, otherwise
you don't actually have any expectations.
Right.
I know it uses these four kanji.
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
Like with the last idiom.
And you understand them.
Sort of, like...
Something like "one meeting per semester"?
One semester?
What are you gonna do with one meeting per semester?
That hurts.
So dumb it hurts.
There's the movie "Forrest Gump" that uses this.
Yes, that's right.
It's the movie's subtitle.
It had that subtitle.
I haven't watched it though.
That hurts!
You're so dumb it hurts!
Why mention a movie you haven't seen?
My tooth hurts.