The 4th time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arehende!
Let's Play World Tabletop Games!
Tanaka was really looking forward to this
He's seriously enthusiastic about it
Am I totally in charge of this series now?
Matsumoto            Hamada
Hosei                      Endo                     Tanaka
I mean you came in at a totally different time
I heard you went to the Kojimachi studio early
To Kojimachi?
I went there from my house because it was nearby
Tanaka learned the rules from experts already
I arrived early to learn the games
There's new games again?
All new games have been brought in, they'll be fun
If Tanaka's so stoked for this, let him do it by himself!
I'm really not that stoked
A lot of them are from cold places aren't they?
A lot of European games...
A lot of indoor games
They're all games you can play in your home
I want to play some outdoor games
There's a Japanese one too
There's a lot of card games too
That's true there's a lot of cards
I've actually bought some of these games
Eh? Do you play with your family?
Yes
Eh?!
Eh?
Doesn't your family hate you?
What? No, they don't hate me
Really?
I heard your daughter doesn't talk to you
That's just because of puberty
Oh really?
That can't be helped
She must not play with you then
Actually I've managed to get her to play
She listens to music while we play
She's not focusing on the game at all!
But she's still playing with us
This sub is provided as is with all errors
This is a non-profit sub by a fan for fans
The first game is from Canada "Bellz!"
There's a magnet inside of this
You use it to pick up your color's bells
It's a pretty simple game
The larger side's magnet is strong
While this side is weak
Alright lets go around the table in order
Endo: Gold
That's bad
You got them all
I'm pretty sure that's wrong
You can't take other color bells
What the heck, you got three too many
Are you an idiot?
You didn't even use the big side but
The magnetic force was still too strong
It's surprisingly difficult
I'm green?
Hamada: Green
Is that one really okay?
It's fine isn't it?
The first one is pretty hard isn't it
Ahh, one's stuck in the middle
Is this even possible?
It's possible, it's definitely possible
Oh it's my turn
So I'm pink right?
Matsumoto: Purple
Is it even possible to get a pink one?
Look this is how you do it
Yep, no good
But I was pretty close right!?
Well, yes, I suppose so
Is this even possible?
This is really hard
Is this possible, seriously
It's possible
Can I try now Tanaka?
Housei: Blue
Go ahead
Well we won't get anywhere if we don't try
Wow, amazing!
He actually did it?
Now what?
Now it's Endo's turn
Okay
Those are yours Hosei
Do you play this every week?
Endo: Gold
Ooh, not bad
Like this right?
But if I don't take it I can keep going?
Yes, you can take it or keep going
For now I'll just take it
Wait what color am I again?
Hamada, you're green
Oh green
That's definitely no good
How many times will you repeat the same mistake!
Are you an idiot!?
No I thought I could do it
What color am I again?
Matsumoto you're purple
Matsumoto: Purple
Ah okay okay
That's pretty lucky
There's one on its own
Of course
Why don't you try for another one?
That one's definitely possible
Oh well done!
That one's probably possible too
Ah
That was scary
It just turned towards me
It was just like "Eh?"
You can do it, you can do it
It just turns towards me
And it's like "What!?" but I was going for a different one
This one's big
Is it possible?
Whoa!
Okay okay okay
That was pretty skillful
Alright I'm stopping here!
Three is good I think
Now I'm winning right!?
No it's a tie
No look, Hosei's are smaller
Oh you're right
Eh, is that how it works?
The size of the bells matters?
No they're worth the same points
Ehh??
The point is controlling the magnetic force
I can get these two probably
Well done!
That surprised me...
The four of them kept getting bells
Amazing!
What the heck
Cool!
You could probably do it with the bigger side
The bigger side?
Ooh Nice!
Oh I want to do that, that was cool
That one is definitely possible
Which one? This one? Really?
You're right it's separated
Here comes a fugly one
An uninvited fugly is coming
Amazing
He did it
Alright this is enough for now
Suddenly he's back in the running
It's pretty hard for me now
You can get that one over there
That one right
It wants to come too
A fugly is trying to come too
I didn't even ask for her
"Let's go back together"
You go back first!
She can't read the mood
"My place is pretty close by", that's not the point!
That's how it is
JUST GO HOME BY YOURSELF!
Geez
Endo, you're going for another? That one's pretty dangerous
That one huh
It looks like she'll come over by herself
Try calling her over by herself
You won't do anything bad anyway
Just do it quickly
I mean honestly
In times like these, I'd never doing anything improper
There's not enough magnetic force
It's cause the bell's too big
Yeah that's why
Eh? You're ending your turn?
I'm ending it
But that's still pretty good. He's got 7
This one is okay right?
Alright, nice
Hamada's pretty fast at this
Uh oh, that's looking a little loose Hamada
But the other side is still fine
You say the other side, but this is impossible
With your talent power it's possible
No way, no way
Now you're in the lead Hamada
Hamada, Endo, and Hosei are all in the lead with 7
This one's possible too
You can do it
I've met up with this girl several times already
Then she should come to you real quick
Can we stop this conversation!?
You're the one who started it!
This is definitely bad
This is just a game about getting bells
I'm sorry but it's just a game about getting bells
It became a nasty game while we were playing!
You can't play this game with your family!
No it's just bells
I can't play this with my daughter!
No it's just a game about getting bells!
The final results are in, Hosei wins!
The next tabletop game is from Germany: "Grab It!"
The objective is to take the cards matching the dice
A simple game except for one thing...
There's a lot of interesting games from Germany
Yeah, kinda similar to Japan
So small!
Damn these are small, I can't really see them
You can't see these?
I'm a bit worried
It's fine
You're just messing around though
Tanaka sorry but, I can't see the dice
You can't see these?
I'm worried about those too actually
I'm worried, y'know the colors are kind of
If you can't these then this game is
Pretty much impossible
It's pretty much impossible
Seriously?
Is being unable to see bad?
If you can't see then none of the games will be fun
Oh really
Alright then, let's play is like they do on the show Arashi
Yeah, all five of us playing it together
The fire mark means that you can't take any cards
Let's start
I can hardly see
I don't see the green one
Is that all of them?
How many cards are there?
Oh there's five
There's five cards
Wait why are there five cards?
Ah, there's two heart cards
This is fine
So the round is over?
Yes, now we roll again
It's gonna heat up from now on as there are fewer cards
Okay, you're out!
Why?
Because there's a flame
What does that mean
You're an idiot
Such an idiot
When a flame is rolled you can't take anything
None of them?
It was the first thing you were told
I already hate this game
Ehh, hang on a second
Why did you take it from me
What is that
What even is that
Which one
The pink one, what is it, a pig?
The pink one I already grabbed
That was the one you tore out of my hands
No I didn't tear it out
I don't think there are anymore
That's all of them
That's it right? They've all been taken right?
Are you even looking to see if we made a mistake?
I'm looking
You're definitely not!
You're not checking at all, seriously
You're frantically checking the cards right now!
The next game on Let's Play World Tabletop Games is-
"The Mind" is a German game
It's a cooperative psychological game
You play the cards from 1-100 in ascending order, "The Mind"
In addition, there's one important rule, that is-
You can't talk
You can't say what your card is but
For example, if you had the 100 card
You're not going to play it any time soon
You'll hold on to it until the end
So you can wait for a while
And signal that you're going to hold
Alright let's play
It's subtle but difficult
Can we look now?
Yes
Aaand start
If you think it's okay you should just play it right?
Well of course
Just play that immediately
It's still so low
He's still worried?
It goes up to 100 so
This is good, this is good
Remaining are Matsumoto Hamada Endo
The eye contact is very important
Yeah, that's true
I want you to sense what I'm feeling
I want you to read my expression
Probably if I played my card it wouldn't be right so
Are you serious?
I mean it goes up to 100 right?
100. From 1 to 100
Alright, if that's the case then
Did that really just happen?
Such a small difference
I didn't realize this could happen
This is pretty unbelievable
You wouldn't play it
Matsumoto and Hamada, off by one, fail the challenge
2nd Attempt
Now then
Let's start
Remaining are Hosei Matsumoto
He's serious huh
We just have to have to believe him
If he's gonna go that far
The Mind - 2 Card Version Challenge
That was good wasn't it?
The Mind - 2 Card Version
2 cards is pretty tough
There's 100 cards so there's 90 cards in-between us
Without further ado, let's start
Play that immediately!
There was a chance, there was still a chance!
No there wasn't!
There's always a chance in this world!
What the hell!
There's no such thing as 100% in this world!
There is! This was 100% certain!
The deck starts at 1!
He got me so concerned about the first card
My heart was pounding
If this bit failed
it wouldn't have been funny at all
The timing was really difficult
I got so scared when he slid the card
Ah right, wait a minute
Well this stuff happens too doesn't it
Amazing
I was worried
You're already done
For now we're safe, incredible
Again?
Off by one again?
You should've played it!
Well I kinda understand
45 is way too big
You should've played it
The tension had risen so high
But I was waiting for something around 30
Let's go again
Again? Another go at the 2 card version
It was going so well
Yeah, starting from 1
2nd Attempt
Will they clear it this time?
This is so simple but it's fun
Now, let's start
It took some courage to play that
Indeed, to play an 11 at the start
There's no way right?
This hurdle...
We've overcome this hurdle
This is good, well done
Let's go. Have some courage
I've done it. We're clear
It's here, he's in the zone
He's entered the master state
The order is even stranger now
He's in the master state but...
Being unable to speak is tough isn't it
Just go
Have some courage
You passed
What about the master
He's still focused
He's still in the master state
He's been focused the whole time
I really want us to win
The master still isn't ready
I hope this is okay, I'm doing it
It passed, he's through
Okay okay okay, only 3 more cards
It's like he's sitting, waiting for his make-up
He doesn't have make-up on
and he's waiting for it to be applied
He changed much faster this time
Right? He changed much faster this time
It's just these two
Yes, it's just them
Alright then, I'm gonna surprise you a bit
Did it pass?
Come on!
Master!
Translation - Tekno        Typesetting - Teknova
Timing - Teknonavi         QA - TeknoProasheck
Consulting - fubintien
I still had these, I totally should have been the master
I didn't think he had two cards in the 90s
It's absolutely possible
Two cards in the 90s, why would I think that
That's why I said that I should've been the master not you
Then you should've just become the master
I was totally the master
Midway you guys started saying master master,
I didn't understand at all
And then you started talking about make-up
But we got pretty close