First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai
What's with that voice?
"Absolutely Tasty - I've always wanted to try this": Tapioca championship!
I didn't like that at all
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Endo Shozo
Tsukitei Hosei
Tanaka Naoki
He spoke so softly
There was no passion in it
You just told me last week I'm too loud
You sounded like an average man in his fifties
If I speak too loud it's gonna echo all around
A typical man in his fifties
You know, people watching this show are expecting a man in his twenties
He's right
Today is a new Absolutely Tasty episode in a while, about Tapioca
Tapioca became really popular lately
Last year, a record-breaking tapioca boom surfaced
Now that it's fading a bit, it's time to observe its new possibilities
Today, our members will try 2 new Tapioca recipes each
How much tapioca have you had till now?
I had it before
Yamazaki seems to enjoy it, am I right?
The one I like the most is tapioca milk tea
That's the most clichéd
They call this "tap'ing", right?
You don't like tap'ing?
I don't like it that much
You're such a geezer, dude
Translation: Shion
Typeset & QC: RIDDELL
more eps @ shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
FB: fb.com/shionnotsukai
TW: @FGRNDNoises
Let's start with Endo's new tapioca ideas
Let me show you my first ingredient
Here it is
It's a tapioca-paella
A paella, huh?
he plans on replacing rice with tapioca pearls
As you know I've been doing this show "hirunandesu" for a while
So we always wonder what's popular at the moment
We get all the info we can and try to catch each trend
And I was thinking, we haven't hit this yet
And I think the most important thing is to have girls like it
If they don't, it will never get popular
It's not like we plan on starting a shop, you know
It's not about that, it should be what you wanted to try
Yeah but, I wanted to try it
But if I had to do it in the first place, I wish it would get popular
Shut up and do it
Well, he's right
Man, I really hated the Endo during this timespan
Time to start cooking
First, he'll fry some chopped onions until they become amber-colored
[SFX: glance]
Alright...
It's time to pour our main ingredient inside
What are you glancing at?
add the previously boiled tapioca pearls and stir-fry again
You can tell he's not doing this for himself
That's not true at all
Such a bad attitude
It happens to AV actresses too
You know? When they glance around 'cause they're uncomfortable
I hate when they do that
Just focus, goddamn!
He used the tapioca pearls instead of rice, then added saffron, turmenic and consommé
Lastly, he adds olives and seafood such as squid and shrimp
Thank  you
Now, we place the lid
And we wait for roughly 2 minutes
Endo's second recipe is an extremely simple one
What I had in mind is to have this accompany the paella one
And here it is
Brown-sugar tapioca beer
Previously I told Yamazaki the milk tea is a cliché
But if we add this sweet tapioca to a beer...
Don't you think... it's going to be a perfect match?
Is it going to be sweet?
Sweet, you say?
It's really simple
What's with this color?
It's brown sugar
It seems Instagrammable enough, though
Yeah, girls would love this
Just like a tapioca milk tea, you enjoy it with a straw
Tapioca Paella
Endo's Idea
And now it's time to taste Endo's first idea, "Tapioca Paella"
I must say, it smells good
Not bad, huh?
It smells the same as paella
There are some crispy ones too
Let's try this
They kept their shape nicely
I don't hate it that much
It tastes nice
I must say, onion...
Was a really good choice here
Yeah, I put in a lot of it
This can be a thing
It's not bad, I agree
And together with this dish
Tapioca Beer
Endo's Idea
This one?
You can drink your brown-sugar tapioca beer
Maybe it makes it more easy to drink
It's so good!
Don't you think it's good?
It's just beer
Not really that good
Are you kidding me?
To be honest, this sucks
It sucks?!
It takes away that desire you have to gulp it all down at once
It's an obstacle to the beer itself
How should we judge this, guys?
They'll score each dish by discussion, with 10 points as the highest score
Well
Seven
Thank you
That's pretty high
I think it's around seven
You think so?
He placed it in front on me with such confidence, I was like what?
But when he told me to eat it, I dug it
Even still...
I think it's around 3 or 4
Tapioca Paella
3 points
Four, yeah
That low?
This time I'm supporting you, Endo
I think it can be higher than that
But it seems today everyone's condition isn't that good
Did something happen at home?
What about the beer?
I'm not lying, this one is a two
Really?
I agree, two for me too
Tapioca Beer
2 points
We can all agree to this  - It's an insult to beer
Really? I could easily get drunk to this
Next up we have Hamada's ideas for tapioca recipes
My first recipe is going to be a very plain one
Plain?
Here it is
note: a pickling method, usually done with vegetables (tsukemono)
Asazuke?
An asazuke-tapioca
Tsukemono?
He's making a tsukemono
I'm gonna pour 'em inside this bag
I'm looking forward to the crispy texture, if asazuke works
It's simple, I'm adding this too
That's the standard method
Looks like you're making some nasty stuff
That's one heck of a vision
I'm not, dude
I mean, the way he's doing this...
I wonder if he's gonna be okay if the police see this?
Hamada's second idea is a tapioca-filled hamburg steak
First off he'll chop some onions
I've been told if you cut it this way, it's easier to chop
Who said that?
Someone...
Not your wife?
Right, my wife
What a complex way to phrase it
I mean, you asked me "who", so--
What's wrong?
Don't point that knife at me
Knives are bad
- That was scary
He said "someone"...
I know that
How can we eat that?!
No way
You have to cut it properly
He's not even trying
How can we eat that?
The knife isn't reaching the board
Look, it's not touching it
Feels like he's worried about damaging the cutting board
When he doesn't give a shit about damaging people
Next up, he's going to add minced meat, breadcrumbs, egg, and salt & pepper to the chopped onion
And lastly, I'm adding tapioca pearls
How will this turn out?
I'm worried about its texture
Yeah, me too
I have no idea
There's a lot of them
I've added lots of them
More than expected
Oh, he's ready
That's the sound
Lastly, he covers it in flour so it won't crumble, and it's now time to cook it
Make it firm
Hot!
What's hot?
He touched it
He touched the frying pan?
Yeah, his fingers
What are you doing?
He was making sure it wouldn't jump out
Yeah
Let's see how his first dish "tapioca-asazuke" turned out
The asakuze was prepared ahead, rested for one night
Don't say it
If my wife would bring this to the table at dinner, I'd snap
What's this?!
That's too much
It's just asazuke
Let's eat up
What's this?
It's so sticky!
It's lacking salt
Feels like the salt has been completely sucked away
This tapioca
Tapioca asazuke
1 point
Sucks so bad
It feels like...
Chewing a vinyl figure's finger
You've done it before?
Tapioca Hamburg
Hamada's Idea
Next up is Hamada's tapioca-hamburg
Let's eat it as it is at first
Simply
Yeah, don't add any sauce
Let's eat it
What do you think? Isn't it far from tapioca?
It's not bad...
Really?
What do you think?
I hate it
I don't really like this
Endo-kun, you seem to be enjoying it
Yeah, I love it
Don't call him "Endo-kun", you'll scare him
I like it too
Really? Nice
It depends on how much tapioca you get in a bite
I see
I think kids would really like it...
But we're not doing this to satisfy kids
Why is he so angry?
We're a bunch of old dudes
We're all old dudes and we're all sayin' it's good
But my old-dude-self disagrees
Ok, Matsumoto-old-dude says no
But every other old dude is saying yes
We old dudes liked it
I hate to say it, but it's good
Tapioca Hamburg
8 points
I just thought...
It could also work as an hamburger
Of course it does, it's an hamburg
You just have to insert it between buns
I mean, its texture...
The tapioca's tapsture----
And now it's time to reveal Tanaka's tapioca ideas
Here's my first dish
There's a load of 'em
It'll be a tapioka-kake-gohan
note: tamago-kake-gohan is steamed rice with a raw egg mixed in, usually with soy sauce too. A simple yet tasty dish.
But with no rice?
We'll use it instead of rice, simple as that
Tapioca instead of rice?
Tapioca instead of rice
This will be our "rice"
So it's basically kake-tapioca?
It's time to boil it
You're boiling it?!
Not like that?
Not raw?
We had to cook it first
This is reckless
Is it gonna be ok?
How much water?
I made it so it matches the pearls' quantity
After it's done, we can enjoy it like a kake-gohan
You like tamago-kake-gohan, don't you?
Yeah I mean, everyone does
Now we just press the "cook" button here
And we just have to wait until it's done
30 minutes later
I'm not sure myself how it's gonna turn out
How is the tapioca cooked inside the rice cooker going to look like?
Here I go, let's open it
It's the same
It's exactly how it was before
There's just less water
See? It became shiny
Don't say that as if it's rice
Is it rice?
It was shiny to begin with
The freshly-cooked tapioca is placed in bowls
Now just add the raw egg and it's done
Tanaka's second dish is a risky attempt
Here's my second dish
What's that?
I added food coloring to tapioca powder
And I mixed them
Now I'm gonna make some tapioca pearls with each of them
You're going for a party feeling?
You do it like this
Are they gonna be round?
Yep
Stupid question...
One by one, like this
I don't wanna eat those...
They're being given birth to on an old dude's hand...
Before recording this episode
Tanaka prepared a lot of colorful tapiocas
And how they look once boiled...
They changed quite a bit
They look really pretty
Now these are really Instagrammable
I know, right?
That's something Chad would eat
Chad Mullane would eat this
What are you gonna do with them?
I'm making an omurice with them
I'm---
This is too much, man
When the egg isn't solidified yet...
Pour the colorful tapiocas in it: then wrap it up and you're done
This looks really bad for your health
It's so pretty
Tanaka's Idea
Tamago-kake-tapioca
Let's see how Tanaka's tamago-kake-tapioca is going to be
Feel free to pour soy sauce on it
Over the egg
Just like a normal tamago-kake-gohan?
Yep, just like it
It looks disgusting
Eat it first, feel its texture
I won't say I hate it so much
Feels like your mom cooked the rice for too long
Ah, you mean when there's too much water in it?
It's the thing you eat when you catch a cold
And you don't have much of an appetite...
His second dish is the "rainbow tapioca omurice"
Rainbow Tapioca Omurice
Tanaka's Idea
Ready for this?
They came out, look!
Is this that german tabletop game!?
It's the game we played on Let's Play With Tabletop Games
It's flashy
They're kinda hard
It's not so bad...
Maybe it needed some more salt and pepper
How is it with ketchup on top?
It just tastes like ketchup
Rainbow Tapioca Omurice
3 points
You like it, right Hosei?
This kind of flashy food?
No
It sucks
And now it's time for Hosei's tapioca dishes ideas
Here's the first one
Here it is
Tapioca is made of cassava, which is a tuber
And we have its powder here
This has been mixed with curry powder
And this one is mixed with salt
So, what am I going to do?
We just take it as it is
He makes some curry & salt tapioca balls around 3cm in size
It's gonna change its texture as well
My tapioca pearls are going to be huge
I don't think they're that huge
And once you boil the freshly done tapioca balls for 20 minutes...
I'm gonna fry them
Fried?
I love potato fries
So I've been wondering what if I did the same?
Just like this
Gonna drop 'em all like this
And here they go
Shit
How are Hosei's tapioca-fries going to look like?
His second dish is a sweet made by using a banana
It's sweet to begin with, after all
Tapioca? Yes
First off, we peel the banana
You peel it off, ok
You have to be careful at this point
Why?
'Cause we're gonna reuse it later
The peel is important?
It is
So make sure to be careful at home while making this
As if anyone would
Then he mixed the banana with tapioca powder in the mixer...
Mix it up good like this
Then forms it into a banana shape
This is the point
When it's the most Instagrammable, so make sure to snap a pic
"It'S tHe MoSt InStAgRaMmAbLe, So MaKe SuRe To SnAp A pIc"
If I had to choose between saying that or dying, I'd pick death
And it's not over: he also makes some smaller tapioca worms
Then he boils all of them together
Get ready to see Hosei's special arrangement!
Let's start by tasting Hosei's first dish: tapioca fries
They don't look bad
Kind of
Let's eat em as they are
Bon appetit
Fried-tapioca
So hard!
Delicious!
It's a mochi
Really
It's like a mochi
They can work as a sweet
Man, this makes you hyper-thirsty
Their flavor is too strong
Feels like eating curry roux
Tapioca fries
2 points
You're right
You have to drink a whole water dispenser for one of these alone
Here's his second dish: how is it going to look like?
Here goes
Hosei's second dish is a sweet made of banana and tapioca powder
How is it going to look like?
Here it is
What the hell is this?
Grotesque banana
But it's delicious
Grotesque Tapioca Banana
Hosei's Idea
What's with the grotesque image?
You know they have those gummy worms in America, right?
So kids eat them and their parents are like "what are you eating, bugs?!"
That's how they play pranks on their friends' parents
So I want all of you to go back to your child self
So you can surprise your parents with these
Surprise our parents? At this age?
How old are they?
I think around 86 years old
86 years old, huh?
How is this a good idea?
It tastes great, trust me
It really doesn't make me wanna eat it
But it's good once you eat it
You can't cut it at all
This is not ok
It's gonna chip your knife
It's so stiff
It really is
What's this?
Its elasticity is impressive
This is really something
So bad
Horrible
Disgusting
It's horrible
Tastes like the valve on a beach ball
It's just like that
Grotesque Tapioca Banana
Skull Mark
This is the worst
This is no good
So bad
And now we get to see Matsumoto's tapioca idea
First, I want you to see how it's going to look like once it's done
Here's how it looks like
- No need to cook?
Tapioca gunkan maki (salmon roe sushi)
This is...
Instead of salmon roe?
Of course there's also rice in it
I'm wondering if it's okay to put some wasabi on it
There's no need for it
Are we going to eat only this dish now?
Let's go to the table then
Take a look
Yeah, yeah...
We've seen it
→
wasabi
We're looking at it as we walk
Tapioca gunkan maki
Matsumoto's Idea
Let's jump right in into his first dish, "tapioca gunkan maki"
Here goes
Man, this is so gross...
This is the best
Maybe adding some soy sauce could make this stronger
Is that it?
Feels like eating salmon roe
Hear that?
He said it!!
I mean, the texture is the same as salmon roe
He clearly said it!!
I also thought of a hybrid, half salmon roe and half tapioca
Maybe it gets harder to tell which is which
Is there some roe?
Maybe it'll be hard to tell
Oh, but...
See? Like this
Like this
Real salmon roe and tapioca
This is surprising
"Sworn enemies, same boat"
I took a bite of just the salmon roe half, and it tasted delicious
Of course it does
Tapioca gunkan maki's score is 5 points
Now, it's time for our last one, and I...
I chose to do something different from the usual, more party-themed
I prepared something you could enjoy at a festival
Matsumoto is going to show us a fun way to eat tapioca
Our last one
Is a simple one
That's a tapioca milk tea
But I thought it may be nice to have it this way
Huh? That's--?
Here's nagashi-tapioca-milk-tea
note: based of nagashi-somen, noodles running down a water-filled bamboo log
Are we gonna suck 'em up with straws?
Exactly, each one of you is gonna suck them as they flow down
Isn't this really fun?!
I don't really know about that...
Guess we have to try it first
Let's go
Oh, here comes
This is milk tea, right?
Is it flowing down?
Having fun?
I don't know
Here they come!
Isn't Gaki no Tsukai fun?
Subtitles & editing by  Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
I got so many of them
Yeah
Typesetting & QC by  RIDDELL (springmanRIDDELL))
I got way too many pearls
This is so good
Find more episodes  @  shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
I think this could be a hit at parties
They just keep on coming
That's enough, Matsumoto
Like my FB page:  facebook.com/shionnotsukai
Get them, quick
There's too many
Want to support? make a donation on ko-fi: ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
You end up eating too much
This is a blast, isn't it?
Unbelievable
I think I ate like 100 of them
They won't stop coming
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TWITTER.COM/FGRNDNOISES
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
SPECIAL THANKS TO RIDDELL FOR TYPESETTING THIS EPISODE!!
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT FAN-TRANSLATION MADE BY A FAN FOR OTHER FANS. ALL COPYRIGHT ARE RESERVED TO THEIR RESPECTIVE OWNERS.