Translation by Shiabatabread
Re-sub by Shappuri Agemasu Subs
If I Were An F1 Racer...
F1... F1... what the hell is up with that?
What's so cool about F1?
This is all they do...
Seriously
I believe they're a bit more focused than that
I'm totally faster than them
Can you drive like this though?!
At speeds of like 300 km/h?
Huh?
I'm pretty sure I can handle that
300 km/h??
And their heads get banged around like this
But everyone's driving about 300 km/h right?
It's not just one guy, right?
I wouldn't want to waste energy going that fast by myself
You're missing the point!
I don't think you can handle that speed
But it's the car doing all the work
No, it's the driver's technique moron!
Listen, when I was in driving school...
Don't compare your stupid driving school
to racing a car!
Did they teach you to ride like this at driving school?!!!
Were you changing gears like this?!
But it's much easier to drive that way
Get the hell outta here!
You fool, you don't know what I'm capable of
My instructor even said,
"You drive too fast"
But that's...
You're an idiot
Those are two completely different situations
You're talking about driving a school vehicle
But I was told "You're driving too fast!"
But this is from your driving instructor
You were doing 40 km/h tops!!
Well, the instructor was stunned at my speed for sure
But you're not to exceed 40 km/h during your class
I mean, I failed once because of that
I only went up to 42 or 43 km/h
But you went over
Yeah, I did
Then you might have the right skills, too...
Get outta here!!
We're talking about a mere 40 km/h!!
We are far from being skilled!!
What do you mean?
This one time,
I was too poor to put any gas in my tank
And I had maybe this much gas left
But I managed to get home safely that night
How the hell does that relate to anything we're talking about ?!
Those racers don't think about the gas in their tanks
They do, too
They need to make a pit stop to refuel and stuff
But are they paying??
Why do they have to ?!!
That's their freakin' job!!
You expect them to pay out of pocket?!!
♪ And that'd make a whole lot of differeeeence ♪
You're not making any sense!