Gaki no Tsukai's First Jimmy Onishi 24 Hour Long Interview!
Hitoshi Matsumoto    Hamada Masatoshi
Tsukitei Hosei     Endo Shozo     Tanaka Naoki
I wonder if this guy is gonna be alright.
It's 24 hours.
The first time I saw him I thought
he came straight out of Tensai Bakabon.
He jumped right out of volume 8.
So far, both Tsukitei Hosei and Drunk Dragon's Suzuki Taku
24 Hour Long Interview
have challenged the 24 hour long interview.
I've broken a lot of people's bones.
Talk about their life nonstop for 24 hours
During this segment, one has to talk nonstop
about their own life so far for 24 hours.
The one who will challenge it this time is...
Tonight's special guest is Jimmy Onishi, welcome!
Jimmy Onishi (52)
You just pulled the red curtain right over you.
You've probably been hiding back there since yesterday.
Recently you've been in all kinds of TV shows.
Well, since you let me show up here every year.
Yeah, at the No Laughing Series.
That has really helped me out.
But you've shown up at all these popular shows
that suddenly wanted you as a guest.
Shows like Golden and Gan Gan, right Jimmy?
Have any of those appearances left you anything good?
Well, maybe 1 good hit out of 10 swings.
It's not that many...
It's only 10 percent.
I think that's too many swings.
Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende
Jimmy Onishi (52)
24 Hour Long Interview
Jimmy Onishi's 24 Hour Long Interview
Taito Ward, Asakusa
Tonight's stage is a certain hotel in Asakusa.
Look at the snow.
How do you feel about the 24 hour interview?
There's a few breaks here and there, right?
There's no breaks.
Nonstop?
It's nonstop.
It's fine if I sleep a little bit, right?
No.
Good morning.
The 24 hour long interview will take place in this room.
Two interviewers will be on standby at all times to be shifted during the interview.
Jimmy Onishi's 24 hour long interview begins.
Birth
Kindergarten
Elementary School
Middle School
High School
Performer Apprentice
Popular Performer
Switch to Painter
Return to TV
During this interview we will be using this time-line
to go over everything that has happened in Jimmy's life.
Today I'd like to start our 24 hour interview with your birth.
Sure
Jimmy, when were you born?
I was born on January 1st, 1964.
On New Year's Day.
You were born on New Year's Day.
Yeah.
The interview starts with some personal questions.
What's your real name?
Um, Onishi Hideaki
So your name is Hideaki.
Can you explain the meaning behind your name?
Onishi...um...the Onishi...well,
there's nothing I could do about that.
You don't need to say that.
You couldn't do anything...
The "Hide"came from Toyotomi Hideyoshi...
because he was born on January 1st.
And then the "Ake" came from the phrase for "Happy New Year".
That's the meaning behind "Hideaki".
So there was a meaning
behind the name.
How many people were there in your family?
My family was...
My dad, my mom...um...
Say it quickly!
My older brother and me for a total of four.
Wow, that's scary.
Jimmy was raised in a family of four.
Why didn't you remember your brother?
But what were his parent's personalities like?
I'd like to know what kind of people were your parents.
My dad was...
an alcoholic... so he drank all day.
What kind of father was he at home? Was he scary?
He had a lover so...
He didn't spend much time at home.
When did you learn he had a lover?
Some time before my dad retired...my mom...
found a letter from his lover inside his suit's inner pocket.
When she opened and read it, it said... um...
I've been by your side for
35 years,
That long?
Yeah.
thank you for making me so happy.
I thought he did a really good job hiding it.
Next, an episode about his mother.
What kind of parent was your mother?
She used to work at the cafeteria of what is now NTT.
"You won't be able to speak on the same level as your parents
until you start bringing your own money to the house."
She used to say that.
That's why I started delivering newspapers since the 4th grade.
Really?
Yeah.
I was a young worker.
I see.
I'd like to learn about the influence your parents gave you.
First, what kind of influence did you get from your father?
My dad taught me...
"Imagine everyone around you is a thief."
My mom taught me...
"Don't touch other people's belongings."
Something like the shield and the spear.
Opposite...
they're opposite.
Complete opposite.
Growing up in that family, what kind of child was Jimmy?
I'd also like to ask about kindergarten.
Do you remember anything about kindergarten?
According to things I've heard from others...
I was always alone... um...
playing with wooden blocks or pretending I was a train.
I guess I didn't mix too well with everyone else... um...
I wasn't able to speak at first.
My mom said "I'll take him to the hospital."
My grandmother said "It won't do any good if you take him."
"He'll learn to speak eventually." And well...
In elementary school there was a girl I really liked.
So the first word I spoke was "like".
I liked a girl called Maki.
After saying "Let's play together during summer"...
she got some kind of disease and...
she passed away in September of that year.
What kind of relationship did you have?
Well, rather than a romantic relationship...
it was more like a little love.
What are you even talking about?
Were you able to make friends during elementary school?
During elementary school...
Between 3th and 4th grade I made more and more friends.
What helped you make so many friends?
I guess it was thanks to me telling Maki I liked her.
Everyone was surprised that I could actually speak.
And from there I began to slowly learn how to speak Japanese.
What the hell?
Things like being able to say my own name.
You sound like a kid
returning to Japan.
That makes me angry.
You couldn't have spoken anything other than Japanese.
He experienced his first love
and his first farewell during
his elementary school years.
Your face hasn't changed at all.
What will he say when asked about his earliest memory?
What is the earliest memory you can remember? If you can.
I can't recall anything.
Just that there was this big stone over me.
A big stone?
My body was laying under a big stone.
That's the only thing I can remember.
Are you Goku?
Are you Son Goku?! (Sun Wukong)
What do you think about that big stone?
It was a rock. I was under the rock.
That was Goku.
Definitely.
I couldn't knock the rock off me.
Being trapped by a rock.
That's when Sanzo
Hoshi helps him.
And after that...
It's size was about from there all the way over here.
I couldn't knock it off so I tried to slip out like this.
The story of the mysterious rock continues
So then...
Let's say this was the rock, I was just stuck going like this...
Because I couldn't knock the rock off me.
Enough about the rock!
He's been going on forever about the rock.
Once again we try to identify the real identity of this rock.
In your opinion, what exactly was that rock?
It was a rock.
Yeah, you've made that very clear.
That's seriously all I can remember about the rock.
Time: 1 hour and 23 minutes
Jimmy Onishi's 24 Hour Long Interview
We're still at the beginning of Jimmy's history.
Now I'd like to ask about your elementary school years.
How well did you do in school?
I didn't do well at all.
Every time I brought my report card home,
my mom would...
she called me Hide-chan.
"Hide-chan, your report card is like a marathon."
"It goes 1, 2, 1, 2."
Did you learn any skill during elementary school?
Yes.
The abacus.
Using the abacus?
Yes.
But I didn't earn a grade for learning it.
I got an award for my effort.
You didn't get a grade?
Why did they give you an award for your effort?
No matter what, I just couldn't earn a grade.
So in the end they just gave me the award.
How long did you practice it?
3 years.
And you couldn't get a grade?
After 3 years they should have just given you a grade.
Jimmy was really bad at school, but...
along with the abacus, he practiced something else...
You practiced baseball, right Jimmy?
Yeah, I uh...
When I was younger...
I would do things like XXXXX and XXXXX.
You did bad things.
I would do very bad things so,
I was pretty much forced into baseball.
Jimmy was a naughty kid who loved mischief.
Who was your best friend during elementary school?
The bathhouse's XXX-kun
What kind of person was he?
He used to peep at the baths a lot.
The women's bath?
The women's bath.
When I went to his house we would always
peep from above for a long time.
We wanted to ask more about Jimmy's thoughts on his best friend.
How do you regard XXX-kun?
Well, he taught me how to masturbate so...
He's my lewd benefactor.
She didn't ask you that.
You're talking nonsense.
The interview is gonna continue like this...
Was that the awakening of your sexuality during puberty?
I'd say my puberty started since the 5th grade.
I haven't missed a single day since then.
Missed what?
Masturbating.
Since the 5th grade?
I've masturbated without missing a single day since the 5th grade.
I guess today will be the first time.
This must be scary
for the interviewer.
Because she's a girl.
The first time?
That interviewer must have been trembling.
She accepted the job.
She must have been shaking then too...
How many times did you use to do it?
At least 5 times every day.
The most was...
about 13 times I think.
An elementary school student who followed his instincts.
We tried asking a simple question.
Can you tell me your schedule for a day back then?
I woke up at 2:30 AM to deliver newspapers,
finished between 5:00 and 6:00 AM,
I ran home...
and masturbated,
ate breakfast...
and went to school...
I ate my lunch,
and went to the restroom to masturbate,
I went back home,
and masturbated,
Stop that!
went to baseball practice, went back home and...
and masturbated...
And you went to sleep.
then I went to sleep but if I woke up to go to the toilet,
I would masturbate again.
And then it was 2 in the morning again.
Your lunch is here.
Time: 2 hours 47 minutes
Lunch time takes place at 12:50.
Today's menu is egg drop soup and shrimp fried rice.
Middle aged guys shouldn't eat unbalanced meals.
Do you prefer Japanese, Western, or Chinese food?
Western.
Western-style food?
What kind of Western-style food?
Food like...
fried prawn and...
Salisbury steak...
That's just
wrong...
He's slurping
pretty hard.
I can't watch
this anymore.
Time: 3 hours 32 minutes.
It's 1:36 PM.
After eating a meal and recovering lost stamina,
the interview continues with his middle school years.
I'd like to know more about your middle school years.
Sure.
What kind of middle school did you attend?
My middle school was...
Well, I was in the baseball and judo clubs.
Did you have a nickname in middle school?
It was a long nickname but...
"Guts Ishimatsu's face after losing a match"
Because my face looked just like when he lost...
Guts Ishimatsu's face when he lost a match.
Definitely not his
face when he won.
They called me "Guts".
So then they just called you "Guts"!
Who's your favorite artist?
Inoue Yosui
I really love "Yume no Naka e".
The way the song takes hold of one's heart.
Time: 3 hours and 50 minutes
It's been 3 hours and 50 minutes since the start.
Around this time something
unusual happens to Jimmy.
What does the song "Yume no Naka e" mean to you?
What's wrong? Wait a minute!
The interviewer is asking you a question!
He went into a dream.
TL Note: Yume no Naka he = Into a Dream
Is this some kind of hypnotism?
He did go into a dream.
You're kidding!
Jimmy fell asleep...
They're asking you.
He's sleeping?
Jimmy, are you alright?
Ah, you scared me.
Mornin'
You didn't get much sleep yesterday?
No, I did sleep but...
I just ate so I got kinda sleepy and dozed off. Sorry.
Can I go smoke a cigarette real quick?
You can't.
Please hold it in for now.
After just 4 hours, Jimmy is assailed by drowsiness.
And after that...
What made you start smoking?
That's too fast.
You're kidding, right?
Jimmy, that's way too fast.
Jimmy?
It felt really good.
What made you start smoking?
It looks like you've been up for 16 hours.
Jimmy?
Not good.
What made you start smoking?
JIMMY!!
What the hell is this!
Wake up.
What the hell!
This guy is a monster.
Please wake up.
This is too funny.
Jimmy... Jimmy...
Jimmy!
How many times are
you gonna do this?
Ah, a cigarette.
I can't, I can't
Jimmy!!
If they showed us this during New Year's it'd be dangerous.
Please wake up.
Alright, different question.
I'll change the question.
Okay, what did you think of middle school?
What did middle school mean to you Jimmy?
Wake up!
He's still at it.
Seriously, this is against the rules.
The 24 hour long interview won't be completed if this continues.
They should take him outside!
Therefore...
Yeah.
Yeah, take him somewhere cold.
Jimmy!!
Can I go smoke real quick?
You can't.
We're going somewhere else to continue.
Well then, let's go outside.
Jimmy is taken out of the room in order to wake him up.
Of course.
Do you always doze off?
I get sleepy after eating.
Today is gonna be tough if you won't let me sleep.
!@#$%&。
What was that?
Figure it out.
Nobody could understand that.
Jimmy, do you usually go for walks?
Only when I need to buy something.
Surrounded by chilly air, they walk towards their destination.
Which city do you prefer, Tokyo or Osaka?
There's nice things in Tokyo and nice things in Osaka so...
I can't really pick one over the other.
Time: 5 hours 3 minutes
It's weird how you keep slurring words.
The interview will continue in this theater,
starting with the high school years.
First, what sort of high school did you enter?
Well, I got into high school with a baseball recommendation.
How strong was your school?
I'd say we were in the top 4.
The team won a tournament with private schools...
Back then PL Gakuen High even had...
Yoshimura who later played with the Giants.
That time our school won.
That's amazing.
It was a strong high school.
I'm guessing practice was very intense.
Rather than intense, I'd say it was dreadful.
Back then any mistake was quickly met with a punch.
I heard that you were bullied during high school...
Well, it was just teasing from my seniors.
Things like making me stop a train.
The express trains don't usually stop...
and they really wanted to stop one.
So I stood naked shouting "Stop! Stop! Stop!".
So they made you do that.
Thankfully I did that on a straight part of the track.
Spartan Days
Those were days of nothing but baseball, but what about his love life?
You didn't happen to get a girlfriend during high school?
No, I wasn't really able to get a girlfriend.
When did you have your first kiss?
I think it was right when I entered this world (show business)...
with a working girl when I was 18.
You keep talking about this stuff.
What did you think of high school?
Eh!?
What are your thoughts on high school?
The interviewer
started irritating me.
Darkness.
And why is that?
I thought that without baseball I could have lived a happier life.
Time: 6 hours 37 minutes
It's now around 4:40 PM.
We change location and continue with his beginnings as performer.
Let's continue and talk about your apprenticeship at Yoshimoto.
What did you do after graduating from high school?
I graduated from high school and...
I worked as a stagehand at the Nanba Kagetsu theater,
closing the curtains and setting up for rakugo.
That's were I met Sanma-san.
So you met him around that time.
Yeah, I met him back then.
By the way, why did you decide to join Yoshimoto?
I'd say it was because since my school days Yoshimoto was...
they've been in Osaka for a long time so...
Yoshimoto was very entertaining,
as an entertainer you'd want to join them.
Who joined them at the time?
People like Downtown, High Heel and Tommys.
So you met them all at once, at the beginning.
What did you think of Downtown the first time you met them?
I thought they were amazing. They were very funny.
Mr. Okure
Starting as a stagehand,
Jimmy was able to begin
his life as a performer.
Why did you decide to move on from being a stagehand?
Sometimes I would be part of Downtown-san's performances.
Why are you
adding "-san"?
I really liked it.
I wanted to become someone's apprentice.
So I asked Sanma-san and he told me,
Join someone who is kind, that way you'll be able to keep up.
Bonchi Osamu was very kind so I chose to become his apprentice.
19-year-old Jimmy started his apprenticeship with Bonchi Osamu.
How long were you Osamu's apprentice?
2 years.
Can you tell me what you liked and disliked about your teacher?
I disliked that he was a cheapskate.
He was a cheapskate?
Yeah, he was.
If we ate something better than him he would get mad.
One time we went to the cafeteria and he got kitsune udon while I got tempura udon.
He shouted "Why are you eating something better!"
I thought, "What? There's only a 50 yen difference."
"Make sure you order the cucumber roll".
That was his ironclad rule at the sushi shop.
Changing the subject, we ask about the story of his first kiss.
You mentioned earlier that your first kiss was when you were 18, when you were a stagehand?
Yes, when I was a stagehand...
Sanma-san asked me "Are you a virgin?", I said yes.
"Here, I'll give you 20000 yen, go to XXXX.", he said.
"Go and then tell me how it went."
So I went to XXXX and kissed and stuff...
It felt really good, so I said "I'm coming!"
and she said, "It's fine, go ahead."
But what came out was pee so she got really mad.
I told Sanma-san about my failure but he really enjoyed the story.
Is this really TV!?
I thought it was...
Next week!
How did you seduce her?
Jimmy Onishi's 24 hour interview concludes.
The truth behind his mysterious turnover to painter and his return to show business will be revealed.
Anything else you want to say?
No, there's nothing left.