Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Cocorico
Endo Shouzo
Tanaka Naoki
Yamazaki is late today
Yeah, it's not like him
That's a first time
Excuse me
Something's up if he's late
Komurasaki Kouzou (Komu)
Director
'Morning
Yamazaki-san told me
To come here
To call all of you guys
Couldn't he just come here instead?
I mean, he was really in a bad mood
Again...
So he told me to call you in his place
Bad mood again
He's in a bad mood?     - He is
Where is he?
I'll guide you there
What is he planning now?
He's waiting for you
How irritating...
Are we going?
Please
Geez
He called us, it better be something good
You're right
Why is he looking so shocked?
Yamazaki Housei
Good morning
What's wrong?
You see
There are lots of comedians popping up on tv, recently
And none of them seem to feel nervous at all
They're filling space
It makes me wonder if we're
increasing or decreasing our regulars
Are they regulars?
What?
Is there any regular member?
Well, that's up to them I mean, if they say it's ok to...
You shouldn't wait for them to say it's ok
Are you an innovator?!
Try to be an innovator
You all should try to be one
Back then there were
comedians like Kanbi-san or Yassan
They were innovators! And comedians too!
Yes
I see
Comedians nowadays aren't innovative at all
They don't even feel nervous at all
So I've decided I'll become unsparing myself!
I really don't understand why you're angry     - Yeah...
"I'll become innovative",
That's what I'm trying to say to you!
"I'll become stoic",
Now, move!
It's time to show you how one can be
A real comedian between comedians
What is he mad about?
Translation & Subtitles by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
Visit my gaki archive: www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Support my translations by liking my FB page: facebook.com/shionnotsukai (it's free!)
Or by donating on ko-fi: ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
Yamazaki said that today's
Comedians don't bring any innovation at all
But what will
This true comedian he's talking about be?
What is this?
Come on, this song?
I open up the window facing South~♪
note: he's singing "Love Is Calling Me" by japanese singer Judy Ongg
And I gaze at the ocean's hue by myself~♪
It's so beautiful it's frightening me~♪
And I let its mirage touch my bare skin~♪
Huh? Was this part of the lyrics?
note: it wasn't
Wind is blowing from the Aegean~♪
And this woman is missing you~♪
Miyamoto!
(manager)
Yes
Manager
Miyamoto Yuu
Here
Let's see...
How much should I...?
1000 yen here...
Yamazaki suddenly starts paying everyone for some reason
What the-- what's going on?
What the-?      - 1000 yen here
What's the money for?
What's going on?
That's...
Because I didn't make you laugh
What?
Please, accept it
We can't take the money
After all it's all about 'em, right?
What?
It's all about the money, right?
I failed hard, so I'll pay for it
When you fail to make someone laugh, you pay them!
Yamazaki's way of a true comedian
This makes no sense
This is too weird
It's not weird at all, really
What?
Then tell me, was that funny to you?
I'd say that
That wasn't funny at all
That's why you should take this
It wasn't funny, so you all get 1000 yen
Man, I failed...
Huh?
You know, actually...
I've been criticized a lot and felt lost
Then there's Judy Onng
Which in a way is another person who felt lost
That's the connection
Alright?
I'm sorry, though
About what?
I've prepared another one
Enough--- I mean,
We'll see that      - Yes
Komu!
We'll see that, but let's cast this money thing aside
That's right      - Yeah, let's not make this about money
That kinda...
Lets out an unpleasant vibe to this
It makes no sense
You're changing here?!
I don't get it I mean, he's spoiling that to us
Maybe it's 'cause that's something comedians don't show
Yamazaki changes for his next skit right in front of them
Oh, I see
Like, background
Something like an "offstage face"
Well, that's kinda innovative in a way
I was thinking
We too have to think of something new from now on
Is he ignoring us?
He's totally ignoring us
He's gone
He's going? Huh?
Please!
There's a red poppy over the hill~♪
note: he's singing "Hinageshi no Hana" ("red poppy flower") by Agnes-chan
Telling the fortune of that person~♪
And today too~♪
I'm alone~♪
Memories of love~♪
Are overflowing from my chest~♪
Tears of love~♪
Will fall down today too~♪
I don't have many 1000 yen bills...
Wha-?
When you fail to make someone laugh, you pay them!
Yamazaki's way of a true comedian
To be fair I laughed a bit
I laughed a bit at the beginning, take these back
There's no need--    - No, no
I didn't make you laugh
But I laughed a bit first
I completely failed
Me and Endo laughed a bit
We did
Yeah, but you two laughed when you saw me
Yeah I did laugh
But I
I think you should have laughed more
There's still no need for us to receive 2000 yen
That's because I sucked!
How many times do I have to tell you?
I don't really want these 3000 yen from what I saw
It's just crappy money
Should we head back?
Let's go    - Yes    - Wait a moment
Wait a moment
Please just wait
Man, he gave us a 2000 yen bill too
Yeah, I'm giving them back
No way I'm taking these
Paying forciblly someone is lame too    - You're right
I think he's taking it too far with this money thing
Yeah...
Why going through all of this?
Isn't it impressive?
It's Yujiro!
note: don't mind the white text / beeps, it's a communication for a small earthquake
note: he's singing "Yogiri Yo Kon'ya Mo Arigatou" ("tonight too I'm thankful for the night fog") by Yujiro Ishihara
Our mutual concealed feelings of love ♪
Are wrapped up by the night fog ♪
And I'm wondering if ♪
It knows about our bond ♪
But I'm sure they'll clear up ♪
And until that day ♪
Please keep on hiding them ♪
Oh, night fog ♪
The two of us are always ♪
Softly speaking about it ♪
Oh night fog ♪
Tonight too ♪
I'm thankful ♪
For you ♪
I failed so hard
It's gonna affect my kids' future school exams
But I did laugh
I laughed, I swear     - It was funny, yes
When you fail to make someone laugh, you pay them!
Yamazaki's way of a true comedian
No need for that
Please don't---      - It's fine
That's a 3000 yen one
I insist to pay 3000 yen, I thought I could succeed
To think I set up this thing...
It's so strange I couldn't make you laugh
What are you doing?
This...
Well,
I thought it would make a "shiii~ng" sound
It's not making any sound
So, 3000 yen... no, I'll pay for that, I have to
What?      - Come on...
In return
If you laugh blatantly, I'll take them back
Anyway...
Would you consider stop
Singing the whole full chorus?
Yeah...
Right
It's just too long
He's not doing anything
He's not hitting himself
He stopped 'cause it started to hurt
Must be that
He only lasted for the beginning
Komu?
Yes?
Tch
Yamazaki gets angry because noises from outside ruined his skit
That's not the problem
Trust me, it's not that
You chose to do it here yourself     - Exactly
Tch
Can't help it
It's an hallway, people pass by
Different people pass by
No, wait, we're good, really, stop that
We all laughed
Sakari Takami, right?
note: Sakari Takami is a 1976 born japanese sumo fighter
Yeah it's him     - We figured it right
I wasn't satisfied at all by your reaction
It was no good to me
But...
I bet if Hamada-san did it, everyone would laugh
No way I would     - Everyone would laugh
But because I did it, it's
100% certain I couldn't make you laugh
How can I put it?
It's like I got bald
After an hair transplantation surgery
What do you mean bald? Hair transplantation?
Like, getting bald freshly after it
You really suck at inventing metaphors
It would be best if you don't make any
Who cares about that?
I mean, Endo over there is wearing a
Beret, but still...
That's not a beret
It's not a beret, it's a casquette
A casquette !?
Yes
The hell is that?
I don't have any money left
Yamazaki already used all the money he prepared for this meeting
It's fine that way
Don't sweat it, really
Say, Komu...
You had some matchsticks, right?
What?
Each one of these is worth 1000 yen
Come on, enough of that
We're fine without it, really
What's the point of this?
For now this... 2000 yen for Hamada
Don't lose them, ok?
'Cause if you happen to lose them, you won't
Be able to claim the money
Alright, now, wait a sec
Huh?
There's still more...?
Yeah there's much more
Much more?!      - There's still much more?
note: Yamazaki isn't actually saying anything. Just pseudo-english gibberish.
Gollum
A fiendish creature appearing in the movie "The Lord Of The Rings"
Translation & Subtitles by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
I think we're done here
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
www.facebook.com/shionnotsukai
Want to support my translations? Consider donating @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
Is he still talking?