At a certian hot spring, there is an inn where liars gather
Excuse me, the first cut will be shot from outside, and then...
Before filming
Okay
Shut up
So scary
That was scary
Even though he's explaining...
He tells him to shut up...
Shooting started
That was pretty scary
What was scary?
Even though the staff were explaining things,
You said "shut up". You did!
I didn't say that!
You did say that. What happened?
Ah, I'm drunk
That's also a problem
Yeah, I'm wasted. I'm wasted
He's already started!!
Yeah, I've started!
Fully improvised! Liar's Inn
The person on the card nominates someone to lie
The nominated person must maintain the lie given to them until the OK
So, shall we begin?
Here I go
So Hosei-san nominates?
I will start the story
Hey Tanaka,
You got a brand new fortune telling?
Where did you hear that from? You heard about that?
"A brand new fortune telling?" I'm not sure what that means
There's the personality check,
Yes and the compatibility check
There's so many
There's no other ones
But there is that one, the "Talking fortune"
Huh? This sounds like an uninteresting story
We won't know until that we hear it
Yes, yes it's called "talking fortune", I did it for the first time,
While you talk, the other person tries to find out what the future might hold for you
That's just getting life advice!
There's more to it right?
Ah, sorry I messed up the explanation, I'm sorry
Of course there's also the standard fortune telling questions,
Like my age,
My date of birth, my birthplace
Birthplace?
That's a rare question to ask
Yes, the guy who did the thing said there are even "Birthplace Fortunes"
Ah! He changed it!
Um, birthplace fortunes-
Birthplace fortune? That's totally different
What do you mean "The guy who did the thing"?
Objectively, this fortune is objectively-
Could you try it out?
Yeah could you try it out?
How is your...Spring? What does your spring schedule look like?
Tell you my spring schedule? Well I was on break for a week,
And I have some Rakugoka and TV work
I see. This was enough for me to understand.
Just from that? What did you understand?
From the outside, your life looks just fine
Sorry?
That's not really a fortune
No no Tanaka, I really hated that
How about you try DownTown-san?
Hamada-san?
Hamada-san, of course I'm sure you have a fun and peaceful life,
But is there is 1 thing that worries you?
Even if it's a small thing, that's fine
The iPad I ordered hasn't arrived yet
Even though you've ordered them before, it hasn't arrived yet?
Yes, this is enough
You got it?
What did you find out?
Um, uh, it'll arrive
It shall arrive
I'm sorry
A new fortune huh
It's just, out of all these ones I've done
I was looking for something to say, opening each door, but,
It was like I got stuck at the first one
Timed & Typeset by: Kedomas
Translation by: senor_wristband
Next
Tanaka nominates someone to lie
Tanaka-san nominates
Sorry about this, I thought this was bullshit,
Me?
Is it true you have a Kintoun?
TN: Kintoun is a cloud Goku uses to fly in DragonballZ
What? No way
Sorry about this, I did think no way it's possible
C'mon, what kind of question is that? Let's skip this one let's go
Sorry, I apologize
It doesn't exist in the first place
Next one, let's do the next one
I have 2 of them
2?
Surely you don't need 2. Isn't 1 enough?
Yeah, one of them is like uh,
Who gave it to you?
How do you obtain one?
Could we buy one?
Buy? Well, you can't really obtain one legally
Well yeah of course
Yeah it was coincidentally someone I knew, from a used car lot,  an old man
A guy?
He told you "Endo-kun I have a Kintoun"
He didn't say a Kintoun, he said he had a convenient ride...
I'm curious about the price
Well, it did cost quite a lot
As much as a car?
It wasn't that much, he said I could have it for 200,000 yen
Oh really?
That's pretty cheap
That's way better than a car. Damn it must be so fast.
It is
For example, how long does is the round trip between Tokyo and Osaka?
That's quite the distance
With the Shinkansen these days it's, 2 and half hours?
Yeah generally they travel at 500km/h
Well, about and hour and a half I'd say
That's fast
Hmm...that is not much of an improvement
It's still slower than a plane
What about the fuel?
Fuel? Well if you offer it some salt...
It eats it?
It doesn't eat it though, but if you place some salt or something around it then yeah
I'm not sure about that...
It grows, like that
I'm not sure it was salt...
Shut up
Is it really salt?
Salt, yeah it's salt
How do you ride it?
Yeah how do you ride it?
What is it like?
If this was the Kintoun
Well I just get on it like this,
It's like this really
Sometimes I kneel like this...
Ugh...
Awful
That's awful
It is quite awful
I wonder what you're calling awful...
Yeah, what do you mean? My heart is about to break
Matsumoto nominates someone to lie
Hey Yamasaki,
Yes
I heard you have 5 anuses
Who did you hear that from?
I heard that from Aya-san
When we went to eat together with our families, you went to washroom and she apologised;
"He takes so long, I'm sorry"
"He has 5 anuses so he takes a long time"
Wouldn't it be faster instead?
Yeah I thought that too, I wanted to ask but she told me "Please don't mention it to him"
Where?
Well, of course on my butt, around my butt
Around your anus?
There's one in my anus
1 in your anus?
What do you mean 1 in your anus?
The first one is your anus right?
Yes
And then right near by there's another
That is like a fake-anus
It doesn't do anything
Man, you don't need that
It's dead? It's not active?
It's not active,
And the other 3, well can you all tell,
Can you feel your bones?
What bones?
On your butt
Oh the tailbone?
Yes, oh here yes
I have one near the tailbone,
Is that one fake too?
Not fake, it's a real asshole
So that one actually works?
Yes, it totally works
And your ass has lots of bones right?
Basically I can make anuses appear on bones
What do you mean?
You have 5 to work with, it would've been better if they were in different places
Yeah...
I wonder why they're all down there
That's what I'm saying to the God who made Yamasaki
Yeah, I don't know what that God waj jinking...
Huh?
What happens when you clench?
From the main anus, it comes out slowly
And when that happens, it comes slowly out of all of them
The 3 other than the fake...
One is fake right? So it comes out of 4 places
It comes out 4 places, and that makes my pants filthy
And I really hate that...
But you can take them off
Yeah you can take them off
Yeah yeah I take em off...
Oh wait, did she say it was 8 places?
8 places?
She went as far as to reveal that...
Is that true then?
I understand what you mean now by "He takes a long time"
She even revealed that?
Where are those ones?
Those are here here and here,
Directly, like in the middle of this human body,
Right here, there's one here like this
What here? On the neck?
No not there
What happens when you fart?
When I fart it's just...What do you think happens?
Yeah I'm asking you'
We wanna hear this, we really do
When we fart it's just pffft
It's just pffft out of one place right?
This is different for me, since it has to come out of 8 holes,
There's 1 fake so there's 7 holes though
Oh yes yes I apologise
Since it has to come out of 7 holes
For example, the air in a fart like *pfft* is split up for 7 holes
So really it's like,
Did you hear it?
I barely heard it
How do you use the washlet?
Well yeah with the washlet I gotta clean everything right? So just like this, hole by hole, one by one
I end up in this sort of pose at the end, like this,
Oh, that's why it took so long
That's why it took so long
What emotion do you have?
My emotion,
I think if I hear that then that'll be enough
Ok, Ok
Right now, all I have is a feeling of gratitude
I'm grateful
It's not a good thing though right?
That's, that's cause,
If you had to sum it all up;
They're adorable
Each and every one, anuses, they're adorable
They're oh so small... like rose buds, it's like 8 rose buds
I'm just so thankful
You care for them
I care for them, each and every one
And if you had to sum up why,
If I had to sum that up...
Mouu, they're adorable!
Sorry, sorry. Somehow,
I somehow feel sorry
I really didn't know when to press it
That's true, it's difficult to time that
Wasn't that way too long?
No no no, I just thought it wasn't really a simple story
Please go ahead
Oh? Oh dear, excuse me
Hosei picks someone to lie
What's wrong with this guy. You gotta have something.
Do you know it feels to have your 8 anuses exposed? It's upsetting
Hamada-san...
Crocodile Dundee is based on you?
Is that true?
Next - What is Hamada's Crocodile Dundee story?!
Hamada-san
Crocodile Dundee is based on you?
Is that true?
If that's true it's amazing, I don't think it is though
No, that's what I've heard
Crocodile Dundee? Oh yes
He holds the crocodiles
yes yes yes yes yes
It was, back when I was about as fit as Matsumoto-san
Crocodile wasn't really that macho
Well I wasn't macho but I have to catch the crocodile after all
He was Australian right?
Yeah and he was amazing with crocodiles and-
And then he went to America
Yes, yes he did
Is that so?
Crocodiles...
I don't what Crocodile Dundee is like...
I didn't really know he was based on me, I don't know about that
I just thought people called me that cause I caught a lot of crocodiles
You caught a lot? How many have you caught?
Well uh, well I just did it cause someone wanted a bag
A bag? Explain please
A craftsman?
Using crocodile leather?
Yes yes yes yes
They asked me, I don't really know how many,
I would just catch and skin them
Oh you even skinned them?
Who asked you to do that?
A bag shop
Ah, a bag store requested it
Yeah, cause I was known as a wholesaler
Wasn't Crocodile Dundee someone who cared for crocodiles?
He (Crocodile Dundee) was just a bag wholesaler
That guy
Yeah that guy
Wasn't he a great friends with the crocodiles?
For the movie they changed and hid a lot of stuff
I don't know about the movie, but all I did was cleanly skin them and deliver them
I don't know what product-
Where did you send them?
The bag shop that ordered them
The craftsman knows how to cut the skin to make the bag
And I don't know that of course
Whether it was a big crocodile or a small crocodile, I just sent the skins
I just flipped them and sent the skins
What do you do with whats leftover?
Leftover?
Oh you mean the rest of it? It's gross so I throw it away
Damn...
Isn't there some use?
Yeah, you could eat it. Is it alright to throw it?
Is it alright to throw it?
Yeah people might ask about that so I throw them away late at night
Yeah they don't know it's for a bag shop
Where do you do it? Do you bring them home and cut them there?
Yeah people might complain
And I have a small shop that I rent,
At the small shop, I have them all lined up
Wearing a mask, cause it stinks
Yeah, it's raw flesh after all
Yeah it does have bad smells
It smells gross and raw, it takes quite a long time
Is this Crocodile Dundee? I'm not sure
Yeah everyone mistakes it to be like that. It's not like that movie at all!!
The original is a crocodile skinner
That guy was a crocodile skinner!
If they said that then it would be bad for the film
Oh that's why?
They just make it look cool
Yeah they put whatever title they want
What is the Japanese Title?
What is the real crocodile dundee ?
Like I said, he's a crocodile skinner
A crocodile skinner?
Totally different from the original then
I have no idea no what to say. Even if you tell me he's Australian...
Here I go
Go ahead
Endo picks someone to lie
Endo-chan!
Well, as a juinior this is something that shocked me
It's about Matsumoto-san
I heard your pay last month was just 80,000 yen (~$800)
We all thought no way
That is...
It must be some mistake
Honestly, it has been a while
There's more information?
In fact, since this year started it's been 80,000 yen
No way, but you're doing so many shows
It honestly shocked me, I was at the Yoshimoto HQ and went to greet President Okamato for the new years,
And suddenly he smacked me
But I didn't think he would hate you
He said he was thinking of smacking me since last year
But that's different from your pay
Right? I asked "What the hell?! Why'd you smack me"
Oh yeah also my lip was busted
And it was bleeding
And then he said "80,000 for you!"
I said "No no no no"
Why? Why did he do that?
Yeah, why?
We hate this too
Yeah we hate that, just 80,000 yen
Somehow, he said I was being really cocky, since the summer
What does he even mean getting cocky?
I don't really know
Please tell us in detail
When I asked for more detail he said "Nope, you've been acting cocky"
That's something Okamoto, Fujiwara and Osaki said to me
So I also thought "Maybe I am getting cocky"
But, still 80,000 a yen makes no sense
Hamada-san did you hear about this?
Not at all
He also sends me really nasty SMSs
What kind of SMS
Like "You're so gross"
SMS?
Not an email or on LINE
He said "I saw you on TV the other day, your opening was disgusting"
He doesn't need to go that far
Yeah things are bad
He really hates you!
Yes indeed
Isn't there something you think is the reason? Like "Oh maybe that's why!"
Otherwise...
You know, there one thing. I dyed my hair right?
Something that could be it
And I didn't consult him at all about it
That was a pretty long time ago
That was said too. "It's been a pretty long time"
By who?
By Okamoto
I did wonder when he was gonna say something about it
He said "Hamada is a good guy"
"Hamada is great"
"That guy would never dye his hair"
That's not something to get upset about
So if we do something like that it could also happen to us?
Yeah it might be the end of the line
It's amazing you guys still drink
Yeah...
Even though he got mad at you
That's cause,
They're really trying to push Hamada forward at Yoshimoto
I wonder why Matsumoto has to be brought down for Hamada
Yeah, it makes no sense
Your pay went up right?
They're not pushing for me at all
He told me straight up the rest of my money is going to Hamada
Is something like this even possible
He event sent me an SMS
Why SMS??
He even sent me "Hamada will get the rest"
With, with this kind of emoji
That one, yeah he was in a pretty good mood then
There's no way
No really really I did
I didn't think it was like a punishment, I thought you accidentally got someone else's pay slip or something
No no no. He said, he said like
"You're at the same level as Wacky now"
TN: Wacky is a comedian from the duo Penalty
Wacky makes 80,000?
From Penalty?
I thought Wacky would make a bit more than that.
80,000? I don't know of course
Yeah actually
I thought he was trying to say he's giving me a penalty
And when I said that he smacked the shit out of me
Sorry, it was a depressing story
Matsumoto can predict the future?!
Next
Tanaka picks someone to lie
Matsumoto-san, this is something I've heard
What is it?
I heard when you get drunk you unlock an ability to predict the future
It's not true right
Predict the future?
I heard that ability awakens
That's an amazing ability
Oh sorry, isn't everyone like that?
Not at all
No
Even if I drink
Oh then it's just me who has this ability
That's amazing if it's true
On DownTown Now we drink right?
During then, are you predicting the future the whole time
Oh yes, I could tell everything
I could even tell Hamada wants to go home early, I could tell everything
Is that really predicting the future?
Well ask me something about the future
Did you know Trump would win?
Yeah
Really? When?
Back when Trump was a child
Child?
But aren't you younger
You're younger
Didn't it only happen when you drink?
Yeah, you weren't the age to be drinking
It was Otoso
TN: Otoso is spiced sake drunk ceremonially on new years
It even works with Otoso?
It was this tiny thing. It worked from that.
Is there any celeb scandal you know about?
Of course
There's gonna be another Bun Shisho
You didn't press it now?!
For real!
You were too surprised and couldn't press it
Timed & Typeset by: Kedomas
Translation by: senor_wristband