Translation by
www.shibatabread.com
Shibatabread
Edited by
@tofupizza on Twitter
Mrs. ShibataBread
Standing by for GNT recording time
WHAT?!!
Hosei Yamasaki
Cocorico
Shozo Endo
Naoki Tanaka
What did you do?
Downtown
Masatoshi Hamada
What'd you do?
You just gave me a look
Yes, I just looked at you but...
I get yelled at just for that??
I don't know how you can ever work together
You must've woke up on the wrong side of the bed, Hamada-san
Trust me, I won't look your way
He got you good
I'm scared now
By the way, what's with your small bag?
That's new, right?
No, I've had it for awhile
You're serious?
Downtown Manager
Naoya Orita
Good morning
Matsumoto-san has requested that all of you...
Oh, I just assumed he was running late
Me too
What do you want?
Well, he was wondering
how well you know his likes and dislikes
He seemed very preoccupied with this idea
He's that curious?
I don't get it
So what should we do?
Well, he wants you to come to studio
But why?
Why can't we talk about it here?
We can discuss it here, right?
He was very set on having it in the studio
How can I feel good about this?
Am I right?
Downtown Presents:
Gaki No Tsukai Ya Arahende!!
Wow!
What a huge space we've got here!?
They get invited into one of largest studios
He's in here?
Yes
In here?
But why in this studio?
Yeah, why?
Wow!
How big is this studio?!
It's gigantic
It feels huge when there's nothing in here
Where's Matsumoto anyhow?
Matsumoto-san is...
What's that say?
What's this?
What's that sign say?
"Present Something Matsumoto Likes and Win His Heart!"
There used to be a show like this
What?
This will tell us if he likes certain things?
So we put an object here?
His favorite things go there
I see
Should we go for it?
Win him back?
Let's go find stuff he might like
Since we're here, there's no turning back
What can we find around here?
They search for items Matsumoto might like...
30min later
We got some stuff...
We got some random things...
Now what?
What's first?
Let's just pick one
We can pick whatever
He likes these kind of snacks...
Yes he does
Let's start with one of them
Which one first?
Beef Jerky
Beef jerky or...
Dried squid?
Dried Squid
Which would you pick, Hamada-san?
He likes both of these
But he's getting too old to chew on these...
Too old??
Beef Jerky
Dried Squid
I know that makes two of us but...
But you're not that old
C'mon, you can still chew on it
I know but this one seems a bit...
I know he's a big fan of this!!
You sure?
He has always liked gnawing on them
Could you say it any more foul sounding?
Beef Jerky
Dried Squid
Go with this one?
That's it
I'm positive about this
You're 100% sure?
Let's see if we can win him over
Here's beef jerky
Beef jerky!!
I'm 100% sure
So that idiot's been hiding in there
Yes, I can her him inside
There's he is!
That's him
What a moron!
That's him alright
Oh, he's taking it!
He's taking it
I thought he'd go for the dried squid but...
I wish he'd hurry up
He's contemplating
Which is it?
He took it!
But seriously, what the hell's wrong with him?
What's that all about?
I still
have a fond memory
of trying this for the first time...
He remembers liking it the first time he tried it
He remembers that?
That's why he likes it
Seriously, what is this?
How irritating...
So he likes it?
That's why he took it!
So you were right!
Right?
You got it, Yama-chan
I knew he liked Beef Jerky
Is that so?
Does he have a sweet tooth?
Like this Swiss roll?
Swiss Roll
Right, the Swiss roll
I'm stumped...
Does he eat sweets when you guys go out?
He started to recently...
He never used to
Right, he never touched sweets
until recently
So he orders dessert?
Yeah, I catch him munching on dessert all the time
Can you be less graphic?
Did that sound bad?
I didn't mean to...
I'm curious about what would happen with the roll
It's a mystery item
I would like to know his position on this one
Next up is the Swiss Roll
Is Matsumoto a fan?
He started to eat sweets recently
You sure?
Yes...
Even Swiss rolls?
What's with the sound effects?
Please let me smack him once
Seriously, what the hell do you think you're doing?
Take it already!
He must be contemplating
He's thinking about it?
Does he like it or not?
Can't you reach?
See?
You were right!
You got it?
Why the stare down?
Very hard stare down
I wish he'd hurry up
Incredible!
I didn't know...
I had no idea...
Right?
Because of its
robust flavor...
Shut the hell up
he likes it because
I don't get it
What's a robust flavor?
He lost me
Let's yank him outta there and beat him up?
Is that OK?
If Hamada-san if giving us permission, then...
We'll gladly help you
What a combo though
Beef Jerky and Swiss roll
He likes them for sure
We pretty much got things we like
You're right
I don't know if it's a coincidence but...
But who from Osaka wouldn't be into Takoyaki?
Of course, he likes it
Or the pork buns
Hit him with the Takoyaki?
Let's go for it
He's 100% into this
We did something like this before...
That's right!
I'm pretty sure he likes these
Let's put them right here
Right on the line
What?
This thing isn't designed well
Not only that, but something's wrong with his teeth
Where's his other tooth?
What happened?
Can he take it?
He needs to find a way to grab it
If he likes it enough, he'll get it
That's right
He can make it happen
It's still inside the square
He's gonna pull a muscle
That'll hurt
Where there's a will, there's a way
If he wants it bad enough...
If he likes it, he'll get it
He got it!
He loves it
Incredible!
Because Takoyaki always
makes me ecstatic
It doesn't take much...
All it takes is Takoyaki to make him ecstatic
Only Takoyaki...
He's from Osaka after all...
You got a point
Good point
Yama-chan, your turn
Offer him something
Well, well, well...
Endo and Tanaka just went so...
I see...
How about this one?
What's that?
This is more like a "necessity"
It's a hair clipper!
What did you think it was?
I thought it was an electric razor
It looks similar
OK, so you choose the clipper
Matsumoto's good friend, Yamasaki, chooses the hair clipper
I'm sure he likes this
A different movement
What's he doing?
Is he confirming something?
He's looking at it
Oh, he can pick things up
I thought he could only pull things in
He's still looking at us
He's got it in his hand
How's it gonna be?
Which is it?
It's not something
to like or dislike,
right?
It's neither, I guess
It's not a "like" or "dislike"
See, you shouldn't have picked something like that
From now on...
If you're wrong, you will be
slapped in the face
I don't want that
Seriously, what's this all about?
By the way, his voice is way too distorted
His voice isn't clear
It's hard to understand
Endo, you go again
Shall I?
I don't want to be wrong
A face slap?
I don't want to be slapped
Who's slapping us anyhow?
I choose the socks
Just pick what you like
You're right
These are quite useful...
See these toe socks?
You're going for it?
That's your final pick?
Yes
Go for it then
Here we go
Here's a pair of toe socks
He sounds a little different
He's got a different set of teeth, too
His character keeps changing
Take them!!
There! He got them!
Take them already!
Keep it down!
The machine's broken
It's completely out of order
It's sweating bullets too
He doesn't like them...
A slap
from Tanaka
From Tanaka?
So I slap him?
I'm supposed to slap Endo then?
I see, Tanaka gets to slap me
Me?
This sucks
I don't like it either
What're you gonna do?
Shouldn't it be Yamasaki or Hamada-san?
Well, it was an order
Ok, I'm ready
This sucks
You ready?
He's looking!
He witnessed it
He peeked
Yes, he was looking
Was that good?
OK, I'll take it
OK
That was good
He sounds very easy going
He's really pissing me off now
Well, not much I can do now
I'm feeling this one
This comes in handy when your face is sweaty
I choose the wet wipes
I've got a good feeling
Go for it
I'll get him
Good luck!
Here's a set of wet wipes
What the...?
He's looking!
There he is!!
He's out!
Using both hands even!
Pretty good
That's a new move!
He's acting like he's into them
Hurry the hell up!!
Don't try to break the machine!
He breaks easily
You hurt his feelings!
Why didn't he hurry up and grab it?
I mean, he's already sweaty and gross
Because you tore my spirit in half
See that?
It's not about just the things he likes
Slapping him was a bad move?
Sorry about that
I apologize
Endo slaps Hamada
No way
Phew!
I was just thinking, "Please don't make me slap Hamada-san"
This sucks!!
Hamada-san, I don't know if I can...
I need to watch this closely
You don't get to see this too often
This never happens
I'm sorry in advance
Please don't take this personally
Damn, he's been staring the whole time
Right, he's been staring with both eyes
He's not even trying to hide
That's beyond peeking
He might as well come all the way out
Please excuse me
Look at him chuckling
No hard enough
I thought that was good enough
I disagree!
I slapped him fair and square!
Hit him a little harder
What a nightmare
Yeah, pretty hellish
This is the worst
What a bad deal for both of us
Endo, there's not much you can do now
Even Hamada-san can't do anything about this
Just make this one count
What the...
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU LOOKING AT!!??
He's not shy about this
Just get over with
Right, I don't want to have to do this again
Agreed
Try to ignore him
I won't hold back then
Here I go!
Ready?
You OK, Hamada-san?
OK, Hamada-san!!??
Hamada-san!!
Tell me you're OK
You OK?
My ear is ringing
Ringing ear
That was
awesome
"That was awesome"
How dare you hide behind there and laugh hysterically
That shook my head
I'm so sorry
I'm mature enough to keep my composure in front of the camera
Wait, you'd be pissed if there were no cameras?
What would the viewers think if I got seriously pissed off?
Next up, Tanaka chooses an electric toothbrush
Electric brush?
Electric or not,
He'll like it
Who doesn't like brushing his teeth?
Come on!
Get it!
Yes, it's electric
Just scoot it in
Bring it home
Just take that with you
Drag it in
It's electric
Hurry the hell up!!
Don't discourage him!
Hamada-san!!
You knew he'd retract once you hit him!?
We don't have all day here
But he went away because you hit him!
Maybe he just didn't want it
Right, he didn't like it from the get go
I agree!
Well, can we ask him why he left?
Could you tell us why?
Because I was physically violated
Hamada-san...
So it was Hamada-san...
It makes no sense!
Otherwise, he would have taken it
And here come the slap
Hamada slaps Tanaka
Let's make it quick
Go easy on me
Don't worry, I'll go easy
Slap him
using bad aim
Bad aim?
Not good
So not directly on the cheek?
He could get hurt
So hit me over here?
Like towards the back of my head and stuff?
What if I just graze your face?
That's bad aim
It'll hurt either way
So that's how it is
He's looking
He gets shy once we look at him though
Ready?
That's the painful type
What do you want from me?!
That's what I was told to do!
You did that perfectly
Right!
It was a badly aimed face slap
Your turn, Yama-chan
Can I choose pork buns?
No, I don't think so
Why not?!
It's my turn, and I get to choose!
You can't offer him that
Nonsense! This is a game!
Of course, he'll like this
Well, there's no guarantee
He can choose what he wants
Thank you
How's Osaka's favorite pork buns?
Here they are
Pork buns...
He can talk now?!
I did it!!
Of course!
He even said "pork buns"
He'll definitely take it
Looking good
He opened it!
I don't want this
right now...
He can talk now
See?
He doesn't want this right now
From Hamada...
No way...
This is so rigged!
What?
I get slapped too!!
He seems to have changed the rules of the game
He didn't say what I'm supposed to do to you
Hamada will...
kick his front
Wait, this show took a weird turn just now
Agreed
What happened?
It didn't start this way...
Why a kick?
Why should we even participate?
Seriously, why are we putting ourselves through this?
He won't miss this...
Man, I hate how he acts timid
I'm terrified
A frontal kick sounds...
It sounds scary
Seriously...
Ready?
Stomp on his leg
Stomp on leg?
No, no, no, no!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
He's looking!
He did!
That's good
I'm done with this...
I don't want to play anymore...
Let's do the last item
OK
Well...
This is perfect, right?
Ultra-man figurine collection
Let's do this
This is good
As long as he uses his preference to judge this
Look, he's not even hiding anymore
Please, take a good look
Tell us whether you like this or not
We got the full set
I think...
I think we got him with these
Well...
I can see his elbows now
I'm not a fan after this generation...
I understand but...
I'm only know the ones up to this point...
But here are Ace and Seven...
I didn't watch much of the Ace series...
I've got a good feeling...
He'll accept these!
What's up with him now?
OK, that's the breast stroke...
Maybe the Ultra-man Seven???
Well, he grabbed the Seven...
OK, got him, let's go home
He likes it then
We're done
Let's go home
He liked it
Wait a sec...
There's a little more left...
See you next week!!!!
What's he saying?
Same time, same place next week!!!!
What a wast of time
I'm not kidding!!!!