TPF
The first annual Gaki no Tsukai Ya Arahende Chiki Chiki bet your life on this one bite
for 100,000 Yen: Kiki Apple Juice!
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Umm... Last time, when I was not here...
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Yamazaki Hosei
Yes we did do Kiki once
Yes you did one Kiki episode, right?
You got it right when I was not present
July 2010 Kiki ep. 27: Strawberry Jam
Only Hamada got it right
It was definitely fixed
Why the hell would it be?
What are you trying to say?
There was no match fixing or anything like that
You must have got some help from the staff or something...
What do you mean "match fixing"?
Endo, don't say such stupid things
Last time they got a Kiki right (Currently Ep. 28)
Tanaka
Yamazaki
Matsumoto
Endo
March 2002 Ep. 10 Custard
May 2004 Ep. 15 Miso Soup
October 2005 Ep. 18 Yakiniku sauce
February 2007 Ep. 20 Oolong tea
Anyway, today is Kiki episode 28
That's amazing
I haven't done Kiki in ages
Yes, it's been a while for you
Actually, you haven't got it right since Yakiniku Sauce
way back in 2005
Tanaka is even worse
Tanaka hasn't got it right since 2002!
It's been nearly 10 years!
That's right
10 years!
Your tongue's been flipped over for about 10 years basically
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents
Downtown Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Translator:
Typesetter:
Proofreader:
Mickstar(Team Gaki)
Otviss
James (Team Gaki)
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
**We are on Facebook and Twitter.**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
Kiki Apple Juice
Taste one while blindfolded
and pick the correct one out of 15
Get it right and you receive 100,000 Yen, but get it wrong and you receive a severe punishment
Get it right and receive 100,000 Yen
Get it wrong and get punished!!
Okay, go and get me one
First off is Hamada, who got it right last time and has been accused of "match fixing" in the previous Kiki
Correct answer for Hamada
Welch's Apple 100
Calpis
so for Hamada, he gets the 140-year-old company, Welch's Apple 100
The sample you try at the beginning
always seems to trick your senses
This actually has a weak taste
weak?
You know, there are some strong tasting ones
Well they are delicious
When the taste is weak, it's just a bit...
Yeah yeah yeah, I agree
They are delicious
Correct answer
Welch's Apple 100
(Calpis)
I have never drunk apple juice from a bottle so I will try one
Oh, he's never tried one from a bottle...
Posmann apple juice
Now tasting
Apfelsaft
(Lotte Rose)
The first sip is just so important
It's so important
No, this is quite thick
This is wrong; the one before was thinner and this one is thick.
The one I drank was not Posmann apple juice
¤ We throw away all empty bottles
He's so fast in deciding
The one I tasted was NOT Kibounono Shizuku
Now tasting
Kibouno Shizuku
(JA Aoren)
Now tasting
Homemade-style apple
(Tropicana)
With his quick decision making, Hamada easily clears 3 in a row
Now tasting
Fruit Fiesta Apple
(Meiraku)
4 Cleared
Out of 15 total
However...
It must have been different
Man I'm tired
This is always so tiring
Tiring?
It tires me out, this does
But you haven't done that many yet
He's right, you've just started...
No no, when you do it you'll understand, they're all the fucking same!
What's with his attitude?
He's got the most right out of all of us in the past...
I know...
Apple's cheek
Now tasting
(JA Yoichi)
Apple's cheek
Man it's thick
I don't think it was this thick
Can I just
quickly drink this one too?
Huh?
No no, you must get rid of that one first
It's like love
You have to get rid of this one first
before you move onto the next one
You can't be with two people at once
No, it wasn't this thick
The one I dr- ank was...
NOT Apple's Cheek
Please, I beg you, please
Oh man, I don't know
Are there really no clues?
I'm sure there is
OK, this one, if it's a thin juice, I think this one could be...
Now tasting
Welch's Apple 100
(Calpis)
Now tasting
Welch's Apple 100
(Calpis)
Oh man, this one is close as well
Now tasting
Welch's Apple 100
(Calpis)
Now tasting
Welch's Apple 100
(Calpis)
He's gone through 5 now...
It's close
Hang on...
It's so tiring
it's so bloody tiring
It can't be tiring, can it?
I don't think it can be tiring surely, just...
This is really sweet though, right to the last
You're so close to me
Too close, way too close
I'm sure it was thinner though
He's struggling on this one, isn't he?
Oh man, what should I do
Am I going to regret not choosing this one?
The sweetness though was just
A LITTLE BIT DIFFERENT
He's having so much fun over there!
I'm so happy for him
The sweetness is different?
I'm so happy he's enjoying it
The one I tasted was NOT Welch's Apple 100!
I really thought he was going to go for it
I thought he would too
I thought he would go for it
It's coming
The Batsu...
Wait, what the hell, oh shit...
IDIOT PIECE OF SHIT APPLE GORILLA!!
Apple Gorilla?
Wait, from so close??
That's not good!!!
Oh shit oh shit, this is bad!
Is it bad?
Shit shit shit shit
That hurt so much, so fucking much
Oh man, it was that one!!
2nd up is the man who looks to get one right in nearly 10 years: Tanaka
The one chosen for him is Aomori prefecture's Gold Nousen's "Ringouen"
Correct answer for Tanaka
Ringouen
Gold Nousen
Will he make up for his previously poor results?
How is it?
Umm... yeah
It's not got anything strong in particular
It might be a really easy
apple juice to drink... I believe
What kind of apple juice is that!?
Surely they are all "easy to drink"
Have you ever drunk one which was "hard to drink"?
Correct answer
Ringouen
(Gold Nousen)
But Tanaka is really bad, man; he's only got 2 right
Yeah, he's not got one right since 2002
You've participated in every episode, right?
Yes I have
I would like to try this one, the most expensive apple juice at 1800 Yen,
This Ougon apple juice
Now tasting
Ougon apple juice
(S C W)
It's so wrong
It's wrong!
Everything is different!
That's great then, if it's all different
It's all different?
Then go and bin it already
If it's all different
I might get this...
Every time on the first one, he says "it's totally different"
It's wrong!
The one I tasted was NOT Ougon's apple juice!
¤ We throw away all empty bottles
I see, so there is a difference...
So the key is what is different...
yeah, you need to find out what was different
But the colour is different, maybe the ones over here have a stronger taste.
Ringouen
(Gold Nousen)
Correct answer
When the juice comes into my mouth
it comes in at a totally different pace
That's probably because you drink it differently every time...
Surely that's got nothing to do with it...
The speed is completely in your hands
It is actually different though
You mean when you swallow?
Umm... sure
That was totally casual chat
Correct answer
Ringouen
(Gold Nousen)
Now tasting
Shiboribanashi
(Kotobuki)
He's concentrating so hard that he starts talking to his seniors casually; Tanaka claims that he can distinguish the differences clearly
Now tasting
Apfelsaft
(Lotte Rose)
Now tasting
Umakappe juice
(Aomori Farms)
Now tasting
Red and Green Apple 100%
(Minute Maid)
He then clears 4 in a row!
5 Cleared
Out of 15 total
I'm
starting to get into a rhythm now
No you're not
Not in the slightest
Not at all
Even if you were, we'll still edit you out
If that's the case
The one that Hamada-san got stuck on before...
Just call him Hamada
The one that Hamada got stuck on...
Wow wow wow, no no no
You can't do that, no way.
the one that he got wrong
Just say the one he got totally wrong
the one that he got totally wrong
I guess when he's playing, anything goes...
I think it's Welch's because I am looking for a smooth and light one
I will go for the Welch's apple juice
Now tasting
Welch's Apple 100
(Calpis)
It's wrong
It's wrong, it wasn't this kind of taste
Everyone always say it's wrong and then we get it wrong...
However, today's Tanaka was different
Now tasting
Jus de Pomme
(Obuse Winery)
He smells and tastes and goes through each one
Correct answer
Ringouen
Gold Nousen
Now tasting
Grated apple juice
(Junzosen)
And gets 7 in a row clear
12 Cleared
Out of 15 total
Today's Tanaka is different to usual!
3 more left!
Amazing Tanaka!
Surely he's got it
I'm going for Kibouno Shizuku
1 in 3 chance...
Now tasting
Kibouno Shizuku
(JA Aoren)
It might be the first time he's got this far
It might be
The scent is really close
It was close
But the taste...
The taste is close but...
You've got a blocked nose man
Did you hear that noise?
I'm not convinced at all...
It's close but it's wrong
Wrong, it's close but it's wrong
The one I tasted was NOT Kibouno Shizuku
13 cleared
Out of 15 total
YES!
It's one of them!
Now tasting
Apple's cheek
(JA Yoichi)
It's been over 30 minutes since he started...
I know, right?
The question is how much will he remember?
I'm sure it was a bit more refreshing
Tanaka-san, you have to go up front or chuck one of them
I understand
He has to decide on one of these after all
I'm sure it was a bit more refreshing
He keeps repeating that
I get it... I totally understand how he feels
Well it is one of them after all
How many times is he going to say that?
That's all he's got to go on
That's his only clue
Will Tanaka get it right after 10 years?!
After the break
Now tasting
Apple's cheek
(JA Yoichi)
Correct answer
Ringouen
(Gold Nousen)
It's similar
But I'm sure it was more refreshing
How many times are you going to say that?
That's not going to make it into the final edit, you know?
How many years worth of times are you going to say that?
Seriously...
WRONG
This is different, so the one I think is correct
is this one
The one you haven't drunk
I haven't drunk it
You're going to take that one to the front?
but I will take this one to the front
The one I drank WAS RINGOUEN!
CORRECT!!
Amazing
BRAVO BRAVO
Kobayashi Hiromitsu
Nakamura Yoshinobu
Producers' Dancers
Amazing
I haven't seen this dance in ages
Yes!
You're right
It's been so long
Tanaka finally, since 2002 custard,
Wins 100,000 Yen!
Thank you so much!
If that was Yama-chan up there, we would have changed the answer
I really didn't think they would fix it at this stage
It was fixed?
Because he didn't get it right for 10 years...
Next up is Endo, who also hasn't got one right in 3 years
The correct answer for Endo is Dole's Apple 100%
Correct answer for Endo
Dole Apple 100%
Megumilk
Will he follow Tanaka and get it right too?
Drink up, Endo!
Down it, Endo
I see, but that might be a good idea
I might put a bit on my tongue and taste it and stuff but
I wonder how that would turn out
The moment when it passes through your throat
That was a lot at once, like it really was
It didn't all go down though
No it didn't
Just go quickly
Correct answer
Dole Apple 100%
(Megumilk)
Yeah, just down all of them, one after another
Like before
Ougon's apple juice, 1800 yen, I will try this one
Drink each one in 5 seconds
Now tasting
Ougon apple juice
(SCW)
They all go for the most expensive one first huh...
Wow amazing
Your stomach is going to fill up so fast though
Are you serious?
Yes Shozo!
The one I tasted was NOT Ougon's apple juice
Amazing Shozo
Damn it, it would have been so funny if the buzzer went off there
Welch's Apple 100
Do the same as before
Now tasting
Welch's Apple 100
(Calpis)
What's the order strategy here though, Shozo?
You should remember the taste still
You should be able to
He's going to break his stomach
The one I tasted was NOT Welch's apple juice
Go go go
That's amazing, man
He must be in hell when he knows it's wrong
He knows it's wrong and he still has to down it...
That must be hell!
Jus de Pomme 840 Yen
I will try this one
Now tasting
Jus de Pomme
(Obuse winery)
That's a good price
The smell is
If he knows it's wrong at this stage...
The scent is totally wrong
The scent is totally wrong huh, there is no way it could be this one..?
It's totally wrong
The one I tasted was NOT Jus de Pomme
Endo this is just...
It's a new character
Correct answer
Dole Apple 100%
(Megumilk)
Now tasting
Apfelsaft
(Lotte Rose)
Finally Endo has risen
The scent is totally wrong
It's totally different huh?
He's drunk so much
Now tasting
Red and Green apple 100%
(Minute Maid)
He downs them all at a frightening pace
and he adds to his growing list
Now tasting
Grated apple juice
(Junzosen)
Now tasting
Apple's cheek
(JA Yoichi)
He's not going to be able to drink much more...
His stomach should start hurting now...
Now tasting
Kutama apple juice
(Shiny)
However, Endo's drinking pace doesn't slow down at all
Now tasting
Shihorippanashi
(Kotobuki)
and he downs one after another
His face is so scary when he drinks
In a blink of an eye, there were only 4 left
11 Cleared
Out of 15 total
This is a great pace
He's got 11 right so far
There are only 4 left
4 more
Can I just have some water?
Wait what, you're still going to drink?!
He's going for it!
Go for it
Now tasting
Kibounono Shizuku
(JA Aoren)
He even downs the water and now there was no limit for Endo
Now tasting
Umakappe Juice
(Aomori Farmers)
He then gets another one right
He has now got 13 right
and there are only 2 left
13 Cleared
Out of 15 total
Amazing
Amazing, Endo-san
Let's down the water
This is important too
There you go
What a kind senior
I know, I feel bad
It's one or the other
I'm amazed you've managed not to pick the right one up until this point
It's amazing
This is the last one
After all that
Come on, let's go Endo
Okay
Dole Apple 100%
1 litre for 210Yen
Now tasting
Dole Apple 100%
(Megumilk)
Now tasting
Dole Apple 100%
(Megumilk)
Here I go
Now tasting
Dole Apple 100%
(Megumilk)
Now tasting
Dole Apple 100%
(Megumilk)
Did you hear that sound?
Okay
I don't think it's this one
If he has to receive a punishment, that would be so bad...
He will spit it all out
The one I drank was Fruits Fiesta Apple Juice!
What was the point..?
Stand up
You, stop smoking with the waitress!!
No idea what he said
Neither
Not a word...
It was Dole
Your stomach must be SO full
What the hell was I doing?
Just mucking about
Next up is the man who has done a lot of miraculous things in Kiki: Yamazaki
Correct answer for Yamazaki
Kibouno Shizuku
JA Aoren
The one chosen for him is one which is very popular in Aoyama, JA Aoren's Kibouno Shizuku
Wait, this is so sweet, are you serious right now?!
God you're so bloody loud
Wait wait, I'm serious
To be honest, all of us in the studio
after Endo's show
we are just not bothered
They aren't?
I will go for Welch's first for sure
Correct answer
Kibouno Shizuku
(JA Aoren)
Now tasting
Welch's apple 100
(Calpis)
Oh this is totally wrong
The weight is different
The weight? Maybe there isn't as much in this one...
It's totally wrong, 120% wrong
This one, you idiot!
I'll kill you!
The one I tasted was NOT Welch's
Not funny in the slightest
Not funny at all
They're saying you're not funny at all
Now tasting
Ringouen
(Gold Nousen)
He doesn't get affected by the negative atmosphere, and clears 3 in a row
Now tasting
Homemade-style apple
(Tropicana)
Now tasting
Kutama apple
(Shiny)
4 Cleared
Out of 15 total
What is this..?
Unfunny comedian
It's so quiet here...
It really is
I'm going for Grated apple juice
Now tasting
Grated Apple Juice
(Junzosen)
It's wrong
Huh?
What?
Are you serious?
Are you serious, sir?
Finally, did you feel that?
No one is laughing in the slightest
Hold on
Give me a second
Have you possibly chosen it?
Yes possibly, this is a tough one. Please please please...
This is not fun at all, is it?
I just want him to finish already
Me too, I want him to just finish
That's exactly what I wanted to say
I want him to just finish already
I'm going for it
I always look stupid
because I don't go to the front
Man he's mucking around
This is just really bad huh?
Yes, he's totally mucking around
The one I tasted WAS grated apple juice
Obviously not, you were mucking around too much
You apple amateur! You piece of shit comedian!
Piece of shit comedian...
This looks so painful
Please don't...
Hold on a second
That looks so painful
I'm sure he was pissed off too
Yeah...
Thinking like "this guy"...
Last up is Matsumoto
He didn't participate last time so it's been around a year since he last did Kiki...
Correct answer for Matsumoto
Dole Apple 100%
Megumilk
The one chosen for him was the same as Endo: Dole's Apple 100%
I don't think that will help at all...
I've not seen this approach before
Nope, I haven't either
What an idiot
It's not very sour
The amount of sourness
This is what is very important
I see...
I think umm... I would like to go through all of them
Correct answer
Dole Apple 100%
(Megumilk)
I am the last of us after all
Who decided which one to give me, I'm guessing
Hamaya-nen did right?
Hamaya-nen
We all chose it together
Hamaya-nen?
Was that your nickname back in the day?
During your school days? Hamaya-nen?
We chose together
I really like
don't know which one to
pick first
Eh??
Eh?
You can choose any of them
Just choose one that you want to
Okay okay, I got it
Anyway, I will go for Welch's first
Man he pisses me off
Now tasting
Welch's apple 100%
(Calpis)
This is really sticky
I totally get it
Oh man, it's this easy? The sourness in this one is too strong
Compared to the one I drank
The one I tasted was NOT Welch's
¤ We throw away all empty bottles
You know what
It's about the sourness, not about the cloudiness and all that
It's about the sourness
Now tasting
Homemade-style Apple
(Tropicana)
Seriously, can I just go through all of them really quickly?
Yes of course
It's totally wrong, the one I tasted was NOT Tropicana
Impressive
Can I just go through them one after another?
He's getting into it
Now tasting
Dole Apple 100%
(Megumilk)
Now tasting
Dole Apple 100%
(Megumilk)
Now tasting
Dole Apple 100%
(Megumilk)
Now tasting
Dole Apple 100%
(Megumilk)
He stopped...
He just said he was going to go through them one after another
He did say that
Can I just do something?
Oh I see
This is a new technique
He got it really quickly but do you think he can see through the eye mask?
That's true!
It's totally wrong
When I tried this one, my memory from before
came flooding back to me in colour
I see
Can I just keep the eye mask?
Wait, you got to get rid of that
I meant the eye mask
That might be a good idea
The one I tasted was NOT Dole Apple 100%
Just as he came up with that new innovative idea
with the eye mask
Are you serious?
Man, our senior is lame!
Your bald head! Shall I grate it!?
He's so angry
Of course he will be angry
Oh shit, it's scary
Oh God!!
This video was brought to you by tofu panda fansubs
Ouch!
That is going to hurt
You're sweating so much
It was Dole
You didn't "get it" at all
I really thought from here on, I'm going to be working hard
using the eye mask
I really thought I was going to be using this loads so I was just...
shocked...