A Battle Of Nakedness
This.........is who I am.
We saw that shocking scene at the New Years Eve Show
The big applause for actor Harada Ryuuji
Tonight, he will be one of the chief judges,
A different face for the comedy industry!
First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende:
Ryuji 100% Grand Prix!
This is the second Grand Prix,
Ah, yes, in that sense it is
2nd Grand Prix after Sunshine Ikezaki's
Ryuji is here
You mean Ryuji is taking part again?
Indeed
Ryuji, and Akira ...
They've been raking it in since last year
Harada Ryuji and I meet at work a lot
Maybe even more than Hamada?
Amazing
Tanaka-san?
Where is your partner?
Yes, it seems he's not here
I think, perhaps,
That guy...
Can't we force him to take a vacation?
First, the main judges of this competition
These gentlemen, enter!
In the criminal underbelly of Tokyo, one man strives for peace
Officer, good work!
Please, don't forgot about that time with me
Being naked is a marvelous thing
When that convenience store got robbed
Master!
They're doing it
Ryuji Harada
Senpai, what's situation at this scene?
Everyone, I ask you for your cooperation in this matter,
I am...
A man of these credentials
TN: That's a police badge
I am Detective Marugoshi
Hold on a sec,
Something fell there, pick it up!
Blonde hair...
There's one there too!
Why's this here?
Does he need to jump like that?
Can you think of any blonde haired men?
What's that? That part-timer who quit had blonde hair?
Senpai, he's the criminal!
Wait a second!
There's someone there!
Stop! Criminal!
Don't think you can get away
Stop!
Throw away the gun!
I'm not sure what to make of this
Peace Secured!
So that was our two judges - This way please
I wish I had a meal to enjoy this with
Dinner Show
I would go to a restaurant like that
Could you tell us some things to look out for in this contest?
Yes, the gracefulness of the movements,
The originality of the dialogue,
And that sense of "Can I see it or not?", that's an important aspect for comedy. That's something that will be judged
But, what about Ryuuji here,
You've got a lot of work this year?
Often, I,
Hitoshi-san and I,
You call him Hitoshi-san? Not Matsumoto-san?
Only you and my wife call me "Hitoshi"
What an amazing relationship you have
2nd Ryuuji 100% Grand Prix!
Who will be the first challenger?
In the criminal underbelly of Tokyo, one man strives for peace
Officer, good work!
I'm Watanabe Yuta, a second generation actor
Akinobu Shinagaya,
and Nishina Masaki, both turned this job down,
I got this offer at the last minute
As befitting a second generation actor of the lowest calibre
You know, a burglary occurred here
His ass is snow white!
What a turn of events, this white ass
The victim, Tokomitsu Masayuki
Unemployed until 30 years old
That boy used the hell out of his father's connections,
He came in like a cat burgular
The MC of "Goji ni Muchu!"
On TV Tokyo's "Ladies 4"
Ah, very nice
Housewives didn't watch either show!
You could call this a graduation,
Although he was just fired
This is the father of that man
So that was touching your dick the whole time?
Kazuo Tokumitsu
Since then, that man took part in another show
And he got married to a female announcer
In a - Marvelous - Hall - in the City
Using his father's money
In any case, he will keep going till his sneakers melt off
Even now, he still gets New Years Money
Wait a minute... who's that over there?!
On that suspicious man's position - ZOOM IN!
There's no doubt he's the criminal! Stop, criminal!
Don't think you'll be able to get away!
Stop right there!
Throw away the gun!
Stop!
Peace Secured!
Thank you very much!
As expected of an announcer
I'm tearing up
What emotions?
What do you mean?
The rehearsal was so arduous
Was it really?
That director Takahashi ... he was honestly working me to death!
We're well aware how difficult it is working under Takahashi
Don't cry!
Does your father know about this?
I haven't said anything about this
If I messed this up,
My dad might stop getting commercial offers,
So I had that pressure as well
Stop crying!!
Surely his musuko's musoko won't put him out of work?
TN: Matsumoto is making a pun here; Musuko = Son and also Musuko = Mistake
Chief Judge?
It was brilliant
The tears that came out,
It was the results of your hard work
If you're gonna cry that much, why do this in the first place?
2nd Ryuuji 100% Grand Prix!
The next contestant is this guy!
In the criminal underbelly of Tokyo, there is one man who strives for peace
He should have been the 2nd one
Detective! Good Work!
He's got a nice body now
Last time, I only got laughs because I was unfunny,
I really bombed, so this time,
I came here to get my revenge
Was it here that the robbery occurred?
I looked into it myself
The victim, Endo Shozo, 45, Comedian
Recently he's been dieting,
He's dropped all excess intake from his diet,
And lost his funny looking body type
And his position in the comedy world is falling rapidly too
I get that
And, his partner Tanaka,
Last year he appeared in 5 dramas,
And in the fall he will be ZIP's new MC
I see
The gap between these two partners is amazing
Acting skills
Culture
Favourability Rating
While Endo's only talent is hooking up with cheap women
The talent his partner has,
He envies all those attributes
Now that I think about it, his self analysis is spot on
However, that Endo has recently been trying to become more like this person,
Former NHK Current Affairs reporter, Ikegami Akira-san
You're gonna get told off
Endo has apparently been invited quite a lot onto that person's show,
However, maybe because he doesn't understand that show's topics,
He was talking nonsense, but with a face like he knew,
He only asked questions that were way off the mark
He even pretended to take notes! To make himself look smarter!
What? Something ran over there!
What's with that acting
Stop! Criminal!
Don't think you're gonna get away
This is the tricky part
Wait! Stop!
There's a bit near the bottom
I can see it!
Peace Secured!!
So Tanaka-san?
I saw a little *Laughing Bag thing sticking out the bottom
TN: A Laughing Bag is a small drawstring bag with a speaker inside.
No no I covered that
It's all good
I was amazed by how you were able to keep it covered with that trick,
When you spun around. I thought that was brilliant.
You practiced a lot?
Yes I did
And beside me Tokomitsu-san was getting destroyed by Takahashi
Seriously, like he was getting destroyed!
So you're saying, you rehearsed in the same hall
That is hilarious
How was this compared to last time?
I felt that I got my revenge!
He took that criticism into account
Wait really?
Honestly I thought it was too long
Again?
After this, an unexpected Handsome Actor!
"If Ninjas still existed, what jobs would they do to earn money?"
But you know, they do exist still
Ninjas are here right now
Where are they?
They're Ninjas so of course they're hidden
If they're hiding then we wouldn't know they exist!
If I tell you where they're hiding in here, I guarantee they'll Shuriken me
100%
It will be a really nasty Shuriken-ing!
Well since I've never seen before, I apologise,
You're saying you've seen them before right?
Yes, that's why I'm saying this
I mean of course Ninjas exist. *Ningyo have always-
TN: Ningyo = Japanese Doll
Ningyo?
Ningyo also exist!
There's Ningyos and Ninjas!
Of course they'll stay hidden in this complicated modern world, they want to fight after all
They wanna stay hidden? But you said if you point them they'll shuriken you, so they're here aren't they?
The Ninjas can hear me, they're Ninjas after all
They can hear you?
They can
So they're here somewhere?
They are indeed
There's one beside that wall like this
There's one by that wall,
But actually he's not there, actually it's that wall
So by saying that...
It's dangerous I told you
Everyone but you thinks they don't exist, so I was just shocked
After this shoot wraps up, since I've been spilling the beans about Ninjas, I guarantee you,
They'll leave me a voicemail
You guys are really good friends then
It's fine then if it's just a voicemail
They won't Shuriken you
"Hello? You told me you won't say anything"
Then there's a beep
But they've already recorded it!
"You said you wouldn't say- BEEP"
Why?
There's 2 messages
Maybe it didn't record properly the first time
So he thinks it didn't record the first time, and for the second recording,
He records it with a "Let me tell you again" vibe
Well you guys are great friends so you'll be fine
You need to start seeing like I do
How badly do you want to avoid seeing Ninjas?
You're gonna hate it when there's a Makibishi in front of your door!
TN: Makibishi = Sharp spiky trap
Well I can just go over it like this
But after that is really terrible, like,
They're so visible!
You can't see them, you can't see them but you can hear them "pitter patter"
But that's not good either! You shouldn't be able to hear them
But I shouldn't have told you this
Cause of that you're gonna see your partner die from a Shuriken
It's a bad image
It'll be stuck in my head in my portrait
Why would you-
They'll take a picture of it being stabbed in?
There's gotta be a better picture
"Come see his face"
They're not gonna put you in the coffin like that
When they cremate me the Shuriken will be left behind
My bones and the Shuriken
What will they feel when they see that?
The Grand Prix so far,
Tokumitsu & Endo have gone so far .. and behind the scenes...
Time for the second half ... First off is this man;
Criminal
Detective, good work!
They were looking for "a handsome man to do some dirty work", for real
"There's no way a useless naked detective like that can exist" you say?
Alright, I'll show you the proof
These are my credentials
There's no doubt I'm a policeman
So this is it isn't it? The home invasion crime scene
I came here to investigate
The victim, Nakamura Masaya 30 years old
An actor
Thinking of the actor Hayami Mokomichi,
He joined the show "PON!"'s cooking segment,
as a useless assistant
That's how he graduated from "PON!", or should I say fired.
He wanted to be reborn, in his hometown he had a "poverty-character"
His specialty was a "Basketball-character"
His hobby was a "Pachinko-character"
Even though struggled to rebrand himself
TV Tokyo didn't really like him
What are you gonna do with that?
That looks hard
He currently has 0 regular shows,
If you type "Nakamura Masaya" into Yahoo,
It says I've disappeared!
Apparently his life is hell right now
Actually amazing!
Someone ran there!
Is he the criminal? Stop criminal!
Don't think you can get away from me
Throw the gun. Throw the gun!
Peace Secured
Thank you very much.
How does it feel, after all this time?
There were so many props
Indeed
There was one unfortunate thing.
When you flipped that disk over,
I wish your ex-wife was on the other side
I'll prepare that for next time
I gave up everything for this
I was moved by that, a bit
Do you think I can go on without him?
Do your best please!
Ryuji, what did you think?
That "Ball on Balll" was great
He's not Shirai! (Japanese Gold Medalist)
Ryuuji 100% Grand Prix - This man is the last one up
In the criminal underbelly of Tokyo, one man strived for peace
Detective, good work!
His knee is distracting
I'm detective Marugoshi, here to revive this project
This it huh? The break in crime scene
I came here to investigate
His ass is so flabby
Your ass looks like Chinese Steamed Buns
It's full of soup isn't it?
That was my big break
I debuted as a child actor
In the past, I appeared in a lot of CMs,
For over 10 companies
My highest income, somehow,
30 million yen, in 4th grade
However, after I left show "Appare-san Madai-sensei",
I lost my income,
In addition, I was a high school dropout,
What are you doing?!
I lived a simple life after this transition
Naturally,
Certainly,
You forgot your line?
Hmm? Hold on!
Is that the criminal?!
Stop! Criminal!
Don't think you can get away from me!
This is standard move
Throw the gun, throw it!
Peace Secured. Thank you!
This guy is an old lady!
TN: I'm not sure I got this line
Yamasaki-san, what did you think?
It was good, but he did forget his line
I didn't forget it, I just thought it was unnecessary
You skipped it?
You're gonna get scolded by Takahashi later
You didn't move much
That's true
You were like the annoying guy in the neighbourhood
I was a little distracted by his knee, it hampered my focus a bit
Is that Kitsune? (Fried Tofu)
It's not fried tofu
What about the Steamed Buns on your ass?
They look like Steamed Buns
Soup will come out if you split them
Ryuuji 100% Grand Prix - Who will snatch victory?
The winner is.............Nakamura-kun!
Indeed 100%
So can I be known as "Masaya 100%" now?
Ask the master
As long as you don't surpass me
Don't shake things up
What did you think Ryuuji?
If you ever bring shame to the master,
I'll pull out his eyeballs
Tokumitsu-kun worked really hard
Those tears
I'd rather not talk about it
He was crying back stage
Takahashi was really hard on him
I'm middle-aged!
I've never been yelled at that much
We rehearsed really hard the past 2 weeks
It's not about winning
Yes indeed, that feeling is important