Traduit et sous-titré par hotarubi
Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende !! Presents
"I wanted to try this! Number 9!"
"Absolutely Tasty: Pasta !"
Right, Matsumoto san ?
Yes !
It is already the 9th Absolutely Tasty !
DOWNTOWN
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Already the 9th episode!
Each one presents 2 recipes which will be evaluated on 10 points.
Planning
Present delicious pasta recipes that will be evaluated on 10 points.
COCORICO
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
But this time, you'll only present the ingredients,
Yamasaki Hosei
because we have a chief cook.
This cook wants to *Beeep!* so much!
ALBERTO Restaurant
Cook Tsukagoshi Takayuki
GAKI NO TSUKAI
YA ARAHENDE !!
Tanaka's Pasta
Tanaka goes on first! What will he prepare?
Narrator
Yamada Shin'ichi
Here's my first recipe.
Ingredients
Nukadoko*
Chinese
Cabbage
Radish
Eggplant
Cucumber
What's this?
Nukazuke pasta !
Hey, it could actually taste good, Tanaka!
I think this can give new Japanese pasta
I put al dente pasta in the nukadoko yesterday.
Aren't these the vegetables you had to put in?
No, I didn't put them in.
You didn't ?!
You just need to put the pasta and the vegetables together, there's nothing special.
What happened to the pasta?
Tanaka
Nukazuke Pasta
Check this out.
Original.
This is really original.
We really need to try this out.
You call THIS pasta?!
Mix the assortiments with the pasta which has been put in the nukadoko.
The smell is really strange!
I know, but I'm sure this is gonna be delicious when everything will be clear!
I really want to try it and see what it tastes like.
Okay, so here is my second recipe.
What's this?
Ingredients
Fukujinzuke "Soup"
Potatoes
Onion
Carrot
Pork
Fukujinzuke Pasta!
Weeew! I don't want it!
Everything's macerated with you.
Tanaka Naoki presents: Maceration.
*Missed line*
I really love fukujinzuke! But did you know you need to throw the liquid before eating it?
Tanaka
Fukujinzuke Pasta
I know, but I could not do that!
That's why I had the idea to soak the pasta in!
I'm kinda afraid of this
The other ingredients are the one you need for curry rice
Mix the curry rice's ingredients with the pasta which soaked in the fukujinzuke liquid.
Oh, the idea is to do the same as with the curry rice.
Exactly. At the end, you mix everything up and you eat.
Tanaka
Nukazuke Pasta
Tanaka's first recipe! What will the nukadoko pasta taste like..?
OPEN!
Bland taste!
Yeah, seems like it is tasteless
It's like some flat diet!
Well, let's it!
There's no particular smell.
You're right.
It's really salty !
A pronounced salty taste.
Too salty, this is too salty !
Now, you know that tsukemono are ALWAYS salty...
It has to be served with rice.
Alright.
I don't like this.
Don't say that!
It's very different from what I have imagined!
If your wife prepares this for you, you'll  overturn the table!
You'll get mad.
You had a really bad day, you arrive home, you eat this, you'll overturn the table!
Your kids will be crying.
The dog will be barking.
You overturn the table.
I give a 2 or 3.
Even if he did not make this thing, since Tanaka always looks dirty...
Okay, so I'll give a 2 !
You have 2 because you're dirty.
I'm not dirty !
Not a 3.
Tanaka
Nukazuke Pasta
Influenced by Tanaka's dirt, his recipe got 2 points.
Tanaka
Fukujinzuke Pasta
Let's see the pasta which has been soaked in the fukujinzuke's liquid.
OPEN !
What the hell is this colour !!
Interesting !
It looks like some spaghetti with ketchup !
That's true! You can add some ketchup if you want...
Fukujinzuke...
Depending on your taste...
Fukujinzuke
Curry's powder
Fukujinzuke AGAIN ?
or curry's powder.
We'll see what it gives after we taste it.
Yes, let's taste it first.
Those who want can add some if they like.
Let's taste this pasta without adding anything.
It's really good !
It's good, isn't it?
It's a bit sweet isn't it?
Really good!
Not bad!
I can feel a good mark!
Well done, Tanaka! This is spectacular!
I feel it good!
What do you thing about it, Hamada?
It's delicious if you add curry !
It's not bad, but no need to shout like that...
I give a 3.
Hey, hey, no, is this a joke !?
This dish deserves more than a 3 !
Then, I give a 3 too.
If I had a wife, I would get mad if she prepares me this 2 days one after the other!
C'mon, this is disgusting !
Tanaka
Fukujinzuke Pasta
The taste is not bad, but because of Hamada, his pasta only got 3 points.
Endo's Pasta
It is Endo's turn. What ingredients is he going to use?
Here's what I'll need !
Ingredients
Gohan desu yo !*
Ajitsuke Zasai*
Ajitsuke Menma*
Ika Shiokara*
Momoya products...
I call it Momoya Pasta
It will be delicious !
These things are already delicious!
Back in the time when there wasn't a lot to eat, I used to eat those Momoya products.
Endô
Momoya Pasta
They are all really delicious.
You're going to use everything ?!
I'll mix up everything with the pasta.
We'll see what it gives.
Mix the pasta with these Momoya products.
It will be delicious, I'm certain of it!
Seriously, those Momoya products really saved me.
Stop talking! Present us your second recip !
You're trying to seduce someone?
Here's my second recipe.
Ingredients
Dry Calabash
Fungus
Shiitake
Eggs
Cumcumbre
Denbu*
Algae
(dry)
What's this? It looks like makizushi
Yes, I'll try to create makizushi with pasta
Generally, we use rice to make makizushi. But I've heard that some people make it with soba
Endô
Makizushi Pasta
I'll use pasta.
You'll replace rice with pasta
Pasta will replace the rice in the makizushi. They need to be fried before served.
And finally, we fry them.
Fry them?
Yes, we fry them a little bit before eating them.
Endô
Momoya Pasta
Endo's "Momoya Pasta" are finally ready!
Here's the result.
Not bad, not bad!
Not bad, not bad !
It smells good !
This looks delicious !
Not bad at all !
It looks delicious.
The form appearance is perfect.
Yes!
I beg you, be delicious !
But it's...
really good!
But a little bit salty.
I find them salty too!
You're right.
I want to eat this with rice.
Anyway it's really good.
Even the pasta is good!
They're good!
Alright. You just need to reduce the chili sauce, and it will be perfect.
How much you'll give?
I'll personally give...
... 7!
Thank you so much !
You're generous!
It deserves it.
a 5 is enough already!
I'll give a 6, it's my day.
You're really severe today, Hamada-san!
If you give me a portion, I'm not sure I'll be able to eat it all.
But to be honest, the taste if perfect, it's a 100%.
Thanks !
It's delicious, but...
This is Momoya's recipe...
Yes, that's true...
This is not an Endo's creation.
You did nothing !
Nothing !
I'm sure Cocorico would have been better without Endo!
Tanaka alone ?!!
Everybody says that.
Seriously?
It's true that's it's Momoya's creation but...
a 6 is not bad at all.
a 6 is good. Try to assemble all this pasta.
We could open a restaurant !
Endô
Momoya Pasta
The taste was welcomed, but the whole thing only got 6 points.
Endô
Makizushi Pasta
His second recipe is a mix between Japan and Italy, Makizushi's Pasta!
Here's the result.
You could have added some more flags...
Why are there only 2 countries?
Since it's pasta and sushi, it represents Italy and Japan.
It's an Italian-Japanese alliance.
Bon appetit !
Endo, this thing has NOTHING to do with Pasta !
No link at all!
Seems like regular makizushi.
You don't feel the rice's texture, do you? You feel the pasta.
How much do you give, Endo?
Me ?
After what you told me, I feel like I'm obliged to give a bad mark.
I'll say 8 at least.
You're too high of yourself.
You're just excited because your family comes to visit you on New Year's Eve.
I've been often told: "Don't get mad !"
* They're speaking with Osaka's dialect.
I've been told: "Stop it fool!"
That's really not it, I'm sorry!
So what, you'll give me a 2?
I give 1, you're okay?
I'm okay with it. I give 1 too.
1 ??!
You didn't thing about the pasta's feelings.
What do you mean?
Yama-chan is saying something interesting!
What do you want to say?
What do you mean by "feelings" ?
This is rambling !
What's this face expression ?
From the angle we see it from, it's really funny. But seen from TV, I'm sure it is not.
It's much more funny from our side!
So, how much shall we give? 2 or 1?
1 !
Ok!
Endô
Makizushi Pasta
Since he didn't thing about pasta's feelings, the recipe gets one lonely point.
Yamasaki's Pasta
The next one is Yamasaki. Will his pasta be appreciated by everyone?
You both were disappointing.
Exactly.
We're sorry !
Show them!
Here!
You definatly love them!
Ingredients
Umai Bô*
(Tastes: Tonkatsu salsa, corn's soup, salad)
I really love Umai Bô. I'll use the one with corn taste,
salad taste and tonkatsu taste salsa.
I'll create 3 different types of pasta.
Without mixing them together.
Umai Bô are crushed into small pieces then mixed up with the pasta.
Until now, spaghettis were a dish for adults.
Really?
Children love it too...
Yamasaki
Umai Bô Pasta
(3 kinds)
No, it's not true.
Kids really love spaghettis...
Spaghettis are an adult dish.
I see...
It is not fit for children. So I imagined a dish for them.
Perfectly fit for children.
And it doesn't cost more than 10 yen! (0.08€)
You don't prepare spaghettis for you children, then?
I do, and they eat it.
But they sometimes think "Oh, this is for adults"
And they cry-
Heeh?! What !
Idiot!
Epic fail.
Sorry.
Are you my friends or my enemies?
Oh! This looks good!
Ingredients
Candied chestnuts
Fresh cream
I want to eat is "as is".
Look, it looks like spaghettis.
Yamasaki
Mont Blanc Cake Pasta
You're right, looks like pasta.
Chestnuts' cream
will be made with pasta, genoese too.
This is disgusting...
Mont Blanc Cake is made with pasta, candied chestnuts and fresh cream.
Spaghettis became a dessert !
Oww! This is too much!
This is disgusting.
It is a good idea.
You'll unleash the god's wrath upon you.
What do you mean?
Don't say that !
Yamasaki
Umai Bô Pasta
(3 tastes)
His first pasta, specifically for children, are ready.
Let's go!
Interesting.
Looks like urchin's eggs!
Good point.
This one is canned tuna
You're right
And this?
What do you mean?
Don't ask us that!
Who told you we're tasting everything?
We'll only eat the nearest pasta.
We aren't trying the 3 sorts.
...
Eww..
This is not that bad..
It's sticky...
It's sticky with a special sensation in the mouth,
but the taste is excellent.
Liar !
I'm only talking about the taste !
Are you serious ?
The problem is to know what we're going to take into consideration: the bad sensation or the taste.
I'm telling you both are bad.
The taste isn't that good...
We did take the 2 points into consideration.
We have to make the final decision.
I give a squeletton head.
Non, wait, this is not possible!
You're lucky we know you for long.
If you were a new little boy,
I would have called you in my office.
Did I really do something bad !?
I would have said to you: "What did you do!!"
We got it, so it's a 1.
Yamasaki
Umai Bô Pasta
(3 tastes)
Appreciated by it's inventor but not by the others, it got one point.
What does his second dish look like?
Yamasaki
Mont Blanc Cake Pasta
Please give points for the design.
It's very important when it comes to cakes.
Let's go.
It's pasta isn't it?
Yes !
The design is really not bad.
Looks like real Mont Blanc.
Exactly.
Ouaah! Look at the genoese!
It's pasta too !
Incredible.
I really don't want to eat that !
Don't say that!
I'd prefer this part.
Bon appetit !
Hang on a sec !
What?
You have to mix it up before eating.
What !?
Otherwise you won't taste the fresh cream. So mix it up!
Are you serious?
Mix up with the fresh cream.
I'm a little bit scared.
It looks like carbonara pasta!
That's true !
It was way better looking before.
What's this?
It's the worst.
It's sweet !
Too sweet.
That's really not it, Yamasaki.
Maybe it's not that good...
I think it's the time to give...
No squeletton head, please.
It's time...
It gives a really bad impression.
A squeletton head !
Here we are.
Wait !
We decided it's going to be a skeleton head
This is not what everyone thinks !
It deserves a skeleton head, really.
And you, Tanaka chan?
a skeleton head is good with me.
Yamasaki
Mont Blanc Cake Pasta
Even with a good design, the sweet taste didn't please anybody. It's a skeleton head!
Hamada's Pasta
Hamada's turn. What is he going to present.. ?
The theme is "party".
Here's my first recipe.
Ingredients
Wheat flour (poor)
Potato
starch
What's that?
Pasta that could be served on a buffet.
That's all ?
I'll mix this with the pasta, and I'll cook it on a stove.
Like senbei?
Exactly !
We eat that during party.
Hamada
Yaki Pasta
I don't know what it'll look like.
You'll know very soon.
The pasta is mixed with wheat flour and potaton starch then cooked on a stove.
We mix the ingredients together
We'll cook that?
It looks like okonomiyaki, doesn't it?
Look at the cooking.
While he's preparing it, I'll show you this.
What's all this?
Ouaah! Unbelievable!
Ingredients
Chicken
Foie Gras
Ham salad
Consommé
It's a luxury dish.
Is it...
It's foie gras
with ham salad,
consommé,
and roast chicken.
We take all those ingredients and we put them inside the chicken.
Hamada
Celeb Party Pasta
So that was it !
And I put it in the oven.
And when we cut it...
The chicken is stuffed, then put in the oven.
Exactly, then when we open it...
I'm kind of scary..
It's a dish for stars.
The other one is for buffet.
Hamada
Yaki Pasta
The first dish is the pasta on the stove.
Eat it up !
You can choose between tentsuyu, yukukoshô and tartare sauce.
It's.. hmm..
Depending on the taste...
Tentsuyu - Yuzukoshô - Tartare sauce
... a dish for the poor !
I'll try it with tentsuyu.
Bon appetit !
I put yukukoshô.
I'll try tentsuyu.
I put tentsuyu too.
It's delicious with tentsuyu.
It's good !
It's really good !
It's a snack.
The texture is particular somehow. I'll try with yuzokosho
Not bad with the yuzukosho
Delicious with the yuzukosho
Excellent !
Really good.
I think what's good is what we put on it
not the pasta in itself.
You ate tons of it !
It deserves a 8 though.
It's too much!
You give an 8?
What do you think about it?
It's really good.
Wouldn't you eat this at an italian restaurant?
I would!
Wouldn't you?
How much would you give?
The idea is not bad!
Should we say the mark aloud?
One, two, three
6 !
9 !
6 ?
It's a 6 for me too. We were 3 saying it.
Since we were three saying it, it's hence a 6.
a 6?
Hamada
Yaki Pasta
The crusty pasta get 6 points.
Hamada
Celeb Party Pasta
Next to the dish using the luxury ingredients.
Wow, this kicks ass !!
True!
After all what we put into it..
Yes, there was a lot.
Incredible.
It seems like...
A dead chicken after eating too much spaghettis.
Matsumoto san, don't say that !
Don't say that !
We can actually feel the chicken's smell
I'll serve you chicken too.
It's evident.
Go on!
Looks like leftovers.
Yamasaki just said it is leftovers.
Don't be idiot!
Look at this !
Leftovers.
Is this the celebrity pasta?
I worked really hard in my life
to not put myself in a situation like this one.
This is impossible...
No thanks, I don't want it!
This tasta comes from...
the bottom of a lane.
What sort of taste is this?!
It comes from the bottom on a lane in a big city.
What's this thing ?!
This is disgusting !
Not good at all !
He's right, it's disgusting !
DISGUSTING !
It deserves a skullhead !
but why ?
A whole skeleton !
Not only the head, a whole skeleton !
Hamada
Celeb Party Pasta
Not good in style nor in tast, this dish gets the first full skeleton !
Matsumoto's Pasta
At least, Matsumoto's turn. Will he make something better than the others ?
So, how do you feel? Bad, don't you?
Exactly !
Don't exagerate.
My theme today will be "Freshness."
Well, my theme has always been "freshness"
Look
Ingredients
Little watermelon
A watermelon ?
A little watermelon.
What do you think about it? I'm sure that you, members and staff of Gaki
you think it's a weapon
Oh, true, we used it once
in Yamasaki vs Moriman
Remember that it's something you eat
It was a weapon !
It's food !
It's a bit risky to use a watermelon.
I wanted to make you taste that freshness.
It sucks.
The capellinis and watermelon pieces are mixed up.
It's like visiting your grandma on summer holiday.
And your second dish?
Don't forget that the theme is "freshness" so that's all.
Ingredient
Toothpaste
This is too much !
What's this dish ?!
This is way too much !
Matsumoto
Morning Tooth Pasta
It's not even an ingredient !
We'll first prepare some delicious peperoncino spaghettis.
Then we'll add a little bit of toothpasta
to have a cool peperoncino.
Mix the peperoncino spaghettis and the toothpasta.
Trust me !
I always try what nobody has ever tried.
And we'll not have the disgusting bottom lane taste.
This will erase it.
I don't doubt that !
Matsumoto
Watermelon freshness pasta
The first Fresh Matsumoto dish is ready !
Each one of us have a watermelon
This is how it is inside.
It looks good.
If you want you can add
some condensed milk
Depending on the taste...
Condensed milk
Rock salt
or rock salt
Like this...
Why are you trying it?
This pasta looks like noodles.
So it looks fresh
It's true, it's noodles !
If I used bigger pasta, it would have looked bad.
Is this really spaghetti?
I see...
DISGUSTING !
UNEATABLE !
Disgusting !
Unbelievable.
I feel like a beetle.
You better not put condensed milk on it !
We better stop now.
This should be banned.
Ouaah! This is disgusting !
Disgusting !
Tanaka !
We're on TV !
It's really bad isn't it?
This is uneatable !
It's really horrible.
Don't say it's disgusting.
It's uneatable, it deserves a skullhead doesn't it
Yes, a skullhead !
I hate this thing more than I hate Hamada's dish.
I understand.
Tanaka, I'm telling you we're on tv.
I think we're allowed to give 2 skeletons.
Yes, that wouldn't be too much.
This is not true...
Matsumoto
Watermelon freshness Pasta
His dish didn't get the desired effect. Result: 2 skeletons !
Matsumoto
Morning Tooth Pasta
At least, the peperoncino spaghettis with toothpasta
No, you don't need it at all.
Hang on a sec !
We're putting too much of it !
That's too much isn't it?
Not at all. Look, there's a lot of pasta.
If you want you can add mouthwash.
We don't want it !
Like if it was tequila.
It smells bad !!
What a smell. Incredible.
It smells like toilets.
Look, there's no more!
You served by yourself, that's why
It disappeared !
You're the one who decided for each plate, idiot !
Since you're the last one, you got a lot of toothpasta
I don't want to be the last one !
Record it !
They ate everything !
Nobody ate yet.
Good!
I don't want to eat it...
We really feel the freshness, the smell is incredible.
It looks refreshing.
Excuse me, but...
It's disgusting !
Taste this!
Sorry but I can't...
It smells like if shit happened.
Hamada-san, don't say that !
It's true!
It's like some sort of flavouring.
It smells...
like the deodorant for toilets
It's gonna be delicious~ !
Enormous.
Bon appetit !
I hear a small voice
deep inside me saying
The aftertaste is not bad at all
It could even be a batsu game !
It IS a batsu game!
Seriously, you have to taste it first.
We're preparing ourselves for it.
Ready?
It's not good at all.
Ouaah! The aftertaste is horrible !
What are you doing ?
We're adding the mouthwash.
It will get the smell out.
The smell comes from the peperoncino and toothpasta mixture.
I just added some mouthwash.
Now, it smells like kitchen scraps.
This is incredible.
It could be a weapon.
a weapon of mass destruction.
Incredible
I really want people to try this at home.
If we ate that everyday...
This thing is incredible.
We would become monsters!
Traduit et sous-titré par hotarubi
And that's not even sure !