A certain library in Tokyo
It's crispy
Super crispy
You two should do all of it, got it?
That's how it should be
The person who draws the skull card will undergo the punishment as displayed
Double forehead flick
Ready, set...
Good, good, good, this is how it should be
Making noise will bother the others, so they can't raise their voice no matter what
So we'll go in pairs
So Yama-chan and you
Ready, set...
This must be painful
It should be a forehead flick
Not a punch
I'm sorry, so sorry
Please follow the rules
Sorry, sorry, it should be a forehead flick
I misunderstood it   -Yeah, these things happen
Are you literate?
Are you even literate?
Be quiet
Subbed by Appieopie, more episodes at
www.laughseejapan.com/user/18797
I hate this game
It hurts
Are you okay?
He's insane
Yoga mat ass beating
I hate this
Miki can choose the card first
Let me get the safe card for every round, please
Ready, set...
Good job, bro, well done
Like a baseball swing
You ready?
Duck you head, dude!
I told you to duck you head, dude!
It's about your ass, not your head
Butt's up!
Ready, set...
Be quiet, be quiet
Nothing we can do about it
I can't take this anymore...
You're the first one who drew the card   -Exactly
Let me take the last card this time   -Sure
Eh? What the heck is this?
*Shin frozen orange
Shin frozen orange
Frozen orange?
So it must be stiff
Ready, set...
Wait a second...what the heck is happening?
Seriously? For real?
Scary, scary
For real, we did nothing
Really?
We have no idea   -This just happened
The audience may think this is fake   -Exactly
So your shin
Which part hurts the most?
Maybe over here?
Wait a second...
Too high
It's stiff
Don't be afraid, it will be fine
3, 2, 1
This thing is so hard
You're in trouble today
What's wrong with you today?
Is this for real?  -Yes, it is
It's real, we didn't do anything
Nothing we can do about this
He's incredibly lucky in another sense though
So Kosei 3 times, and next Asei 3 times, deal?
*Today's protagonist
Eh? What's this?
Today's protagonist
Hey, wait a second...
Oh, you want to be the dealer?
It couldn't be him again   -Yeah
Let's open
Ready, set
What the heck is that?
This is just normal
It won't always be him
Scary, scary, scary   -This must be nasty
Will it bump on his head?   -I can't trust the staffs
This is so scary
What's happening?
Wow, here comes so many muscular men
So scary
Wow, so scary
It's so small
The mat is so small   -Yeah, it's too small
The mat is too small
This is lame but nasty
This is just so scary
He was so high
And he screamed like "kyaaa"
He screamed like a young girl
It was so high, I was terrified
So he's the protagonist
It's not my fault
Crotch balloon explosion
I definitely don't want to do this one
Let the young men do this   -Agreed
Do this Asei
We are the one who use it the most
You guys are no longer using it, right?
That's why we need to treasure it
Oh, this way?
He's speaking a lot
Sorry, sorry, you're right
Does he understand the concept of this theme?
He's an idiot, right?   -Who's drawing the card?
I hope it's these two lads again
Let's open it
Ready, set...
I get it, so this is how it's going this time
I get it, so you can't be the dealer
I'm so happy, thank god
Let's keep up the pace
Be more exciting, make it more interesting
Then put it inside, right? Ok, ok
Oh, I see
Remember to be quiet
Don't raise your voice, be quiet
Well done, that was spectacular
That was spectacular
So it's no good to be the dealer
How many more rounds?
Asei, you're next
We already filmed enough scenes, right?
Boiling Go game
I can't even understand this
Why, dude?
You think one of it is the skull card?
So scary! This is miracle!
This is the worst
Scary, scary, scary
What the heck is this?
What is this?
Boiling Go game
The person who drew the skull card, please come in front and lie down
Oh, the Go game   -Here it comes
Asei, don't move and stay still
You're the Go board   -Endure it
It's steaming hot
It's so hot
This is something serious, so remember to be quiet
So hot!
Wait a second...
-No please, wait a second...
-I told you to stay still   -Show his nipples
Wait a second, this is no joke
Endure it, dude   -No, seriously, I can't endure this
Don't move, dude
Endure it, endure it
What about putting it on his nipple?
Right here
Ouuuuch!!
What's wrong with you?
Thank you very much
They didn't even get to play the game
My nipple is burning
Asei, do you want to be the dealer, or do you want another person to do it?
Don't do it yourself, let Matsumoto-san do it for you
Me?
I see what you're doing
So that's how it is this time
Hamada Kick
Wait, what if I'm the one who drew the skull card?
I don't get this
The dealer has been punished for 2 consecutive times
What will be the fate of Matsumoto!?
Oh, he switched those two
Ah, he switched it again
Okay, let's open it
Ready, set...
Scary, scary, scary   -Scary, scary, scary
Scary, this is so scary   -Incredible
Eh? How come?   -This is incredible
He switched my card at the last second   -Yes, he did
So you can't switch any cards this time
No, no, this is none of my business
No, no, no way
After all this time?
I told you it's not me, just go in front
Come on, no way...
Why is he wearing this costume every time?
What the heck is this? What the heck is happening?
Ouch, ouch!!
That was so strong
That was a fabulous kick
I completely underestimated him
That boy must be doing martial arts
It hurts so bad
I completely let my guard down
I thought it's an easy one
Seriously, it's incredible today
Yeah, better not touch any of these cards
Me?
Come on, it couldn't be me this time
Rotten fish box
The dealer has miraclely drew the skull card for 3 consecutive times
What will happen this time...
Okay, let's go with this
Ready, set...
No, no, no   -Don't do what Yama-chan did just now
Why am I being blamed
This one stinks
Tanaka hate these kinds of things
He definitely dislikes this
Oh, so cover his head?
It stinks!
Take a deep breath and calm down
Calm down, dude
It stinks
It stinks!
He said it, he clearly said it
He clearly said it stinks   -Spray him, spray him
Well, yeah...this is necessary
Because he stinks, he really stinks
This is how you guys treat him?
He clearly said it stinks
Tanaka-san, would you mind being the dealer?
So only me and Hamada is left   -Oh, me too?
Not yet, sir
Hamada thought he got punished already
Hamada-san thought he received Batsu already
You guys heard that just now?
You guys heard that?
Shall we stop filming for a while?
Not necessary
What happened to you?
I've been helping the last few punishments, so I thought I got punished as well
No way, that's unbelievable
That's ridiculous
He gave someone a dropkick, and yet thought he is the one who got dropkicked
What kind of memory technique is that?
That's serious persecutory delusion
In conclusion, Hamada-san and I are not yet punished
Not yet?   -Yes, not yet
Let's continue
Untouchable deep kiss
I hate this one
Let's open, ready, set...
The fourth time today
Four times?
Go in front
Shall you do the Boiling Go as well?
That's too awkward
-Why should I be kissed while playing Go?
-Here he comes, here he comes
It's always this guy
I saw him before, I definitely saw him before
I saw this old man before
But it doesn't hurt   -Go, go, go for it
Pluck up your courage and go for it
Until he is satisfied, until he is satisfied...
This is so deep   -Amazing
Will that thing break apart?
That would be terrible   -Game over if that happens
What the heck is this?
Feels like being forced   -That's a deep kiss
But well, this does no damage   -Exactly
Only mentally, that's all
Here it comes
Nice shot nasal hair plucking
2 cards?   -Yes, 2 cards
Give me a break...   -So 2 people
This is much more risky
I really hate this one
Let's open it
Ready, set...
Tanaka and Asei
Go in front
Come on, I really hate this one
Oh, I see, so I'll swing and hit the gold ball
Ouch, it's so hot   -Oh, it's hot?
It's so hot   -This is tough
Endo is pissing me off
Is it hardened?
Yeah, pretty much
Take a full string at the ball connected with two noses!!
Endo-san...
Both of them came off right?
Both of them right?
Is this mine?   -There's so many nose hair on it
The amount of Asei's nose hair is horrible
Wow, Tanaka's is horrible too
So embarrassing
This is so embarrassing, please don't film it
Wait, please don't film this, so embarrassing
This is so embarrassing
This is really embarrassing
This one is both painful and embarrassing
I think this is enough for today   -Same here
Yeah, this should be enough
Tanaka has been punished quite a lot of times too
A first time collaboration
What does that even mean?
No idea how we'll be punished
A first time collaboration
Looks good?
-We never did this one before
-We just have to accept whatever comes
Let's open, ready, set...
It's Cocorico
Tanaka is being punished a lot today
He starts to scratch his head, he's probably feeling itchy
What? What? What is this?
Tanaka is feeling itchy
His nose again?
Tanaka's nose will be destroyed
Yeah, it's always about his nose
Now it seems that the rotten fish box was actually the easiest one
So scary, scary, scary
Oh, so the cake will be raised and cut by the knife here
So you two need to move forward, as much as you can
Okay, move forward
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
He don't even have any nose hair
Pull it, pull it!
Move forward, move!
This is it, they reached their limit
They are miserable
You're sweating like a pig
Last, last one
Squid ink bazooka
It should be him   -Why me, dude?
Just let it be you   -No way, no
This rule is ridiculous   -Considering the order...
Just do this properly, and accept the result
Leave it to luck
Can you open the cards one by one?
Oh, so in a row?
Just let Kosei do it, right?   -I did it 4 times already
So...
Let's start with Kosei-san
Choose your card   -Can I open it?
No, no, no way, this is too hilarious
-There's nothing we can do about this   -I can't even say let Hamada do it now
Being the first one to choose, and showing no shame
Without any sense of expectation
Without any sense of nervousness
You should be punished because of this too
Today is just incredible
The dealer always get punished
Fire the squid ink bazooka towards Hosei!!
Today's cards are incredible   -Absolutely incredible
Stand over there Yama-chan   -Yes
This looks amazing
The staffs are not even letting him to wear goggles
He's asking for it
No worries
They said "no worries"
They said it's fine without goggles
Because it's squid ink
No problem, you'll be fine
Ready?
3, 2, 1
This is amazing   -Like a piece of art
Yeah, it looks like an artwork
Look, look, look behind you
Look behind, look behind you
He's laughing, he's clearly laughing
He's laughing out loud
Super trendy
Laughing out loud