The 6th time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arehende!
So loud!
Let's Play World Tabletop Games!
No I said it softly
We're just normally playing tabletop games right!
*In the last episode they pranked Hamada
Yes, this time it's exactly as you say
No no no, this is weird
"exactly as you say"?
I'm sick of this already
The first is a German game "Hamsterrolle"
It's a balancing game
Oh, this is...
This hamster wheel looking thing
Normally it's suspended like this
I've given everyone the same color blocks
In order
we place the blocks
Whoever runs out of blocks first wins
That's the rule
Simple
As we place more blocks, it will become unbalanced
And the blocks will fall out
In that case
The person who caused it has to take the fallen blocks
They become your blocks
It increases your pieces
That's right
Also, another thing
For example, if you put a red piece here
The next person
can't place the same color in the same spot
In that case, if you want to put a red piece
You have to put it in the zone after the next zone
Well, just say something when it happens
Like, "you can't do that"
Okay, I'll say something
This game will be played by these 4, starting from Housei
For the first piece, we skip the first empty zone
Oh, I see
So it's fine to put it here
I see, you can place it like that
Sideways is fine too
But this is still fine
We can place another one here
But you can't place a piece on top of another piece
You have to place pieces in front of the last piece
Then that means
If you place it length wise, you block the zone
Then we can only place a piece here now
Exactly
You just suddenly set us up
You made a great play
That was my strategy
You knew that?
Yes
Seriously?
You can place it in the next zone or the one after
So here
That did quite a bit, see
In this case we can go back right?
You can't
We can't go back
The next block has to be further than the last
Further
As long as it's a different color
You can place in the same zone
So I can place this then
Yes, that's fine
Yamasaki's zone is okay too right?
On the side is fine right?
Well you can't go backwards anyways
You have to move forward
Ah! I see
Tanaka I can't go here?
No that should be fine right?
On top is fine right?
You can go on top
This is surprisingly complex isn't it?
I can't remember all the rules
What's this?
The person who caused it to fall
It becomes their piece
This one?
Yes, yes
This isn't one of the ones we placed
It's not
It looks like something you'd find in a shrine
So this is mine now
You have to place that somewhere now
Can I place it like this too?
It's fine as long as it fits right?
If it fits it's fine
Does it fit?
It fits, it fits
You're pushing really hard
It doesn't fit
That one fell out
That's bad!
Wait wait
That's Housei's now
Eh, my turn's over?
The fallen piece is yours
That was amazing, just now Tanaka
made the scariest face since his debut
Since I debuted?
It's unusual for Tanaka to make that kind of face
Since his debut, #1 scariest face
I made that kind of face? Really?
It was kind of amazing
Then, my self will...
This one, this round one
I can't place in front here, it has to be above
But this one's round so I can't place here
I can only place here then
My self placed one here so
I know, so can I place on top of it?
On top of my self's piece is fine
Tanaka which is it?
It's as my self says
I tried using Nakajima Miyuki's "my self"
So if you place the round piece
I want to do this again
This time is practice
I have a question!
What do we do if it goes past the table?
I'll put it back.
Such a practical answer
The key to the game is controlling the tilt of the wheel
As well as having a delicate touch when placing blocks
Both of these skills will control the game
Oh, amazing!
Plus it didn't move at all
Everyone's remaining pieces have decreased
The game approaches it's final stage
Ah, but this is
perfectly balanced...
That's true, it's a bit scary
That's risky
Seriously!?
Nice nice nice
Seriously?
Only 2 more pieces Matsumoto
This is impossible
You could put one there
It'll fall over if he does
He's gonna try there?
No way!
This is like
my invention you know
No wait a second
That technique
This technique is amazing
No everyone's been doing that
Wow he did it?
It's moving
Now that it's like this it's more interesting
I finally see what makes this game interesting
Now is a pretty tense part
The balance is so delicate
There's nothing confusing about this
Yeah really
Ah it keeps moving
His farsightedness is making it worse
Seriously it's so hard to see
I think this impossible
If you fail, at least scream or something
Make the ending interesting
I really can't see
Eh, didn't he just place it?
This is
doable?
Well
maybe with a light one
This one then
I have a small one but
This looks doable
You're gonna put it on top of the purple?
I have to put it on top of the purple
The purple is in the 7th zone
No I think the next zone is fine
Baldy!
He's calling you
Don't care
Not bald
Can't be me
Another move and they'll fall
Why am I clapping, I'm next
But if you place it Matsumoto, it's your win
Of course
Really?
This is my last piece
But it's over there, he has to place there
He might be able to place it
But you have to consider the weight
This is probably the heaviest one
You left the heaviest for last
Is he gonna lose out?
This is so scary
My astigmatism is flaring up
This game is impossible
for our age group
One time I was watching TV
"Single Mother Ootsuka Ai" it said on top
Ootsuka Ai got really fat, is what I thought
She has this many children? I looked closer
"Single Mother Big Family" is what it said
You misread Big Family as Ootsuka Ai
Come on man...
No really my astigmatism, I can't tell things apart
If he places it he wins?
This is pretty hard, it's the 7th round
This sucks
This sucks, it wasn't even funny
He got four of them
Wait a second, this can't be real
What do I do with these?
Leave the wheel as is, and Matsumoto takes the fallen pieces
The wheel stays as it is?
Just like this
Hamada is about to finish isn't he?
If I place this OK then it's over
It's Hamada's win
I'll go here
I think so too, there's nowhere else
What the hell is up with this
It's moving so much
Why is it moving so much
Well it is round
No you gotta do it more gently
He did it!
Hamada's Win!
Thank you
How do we decide the rankings?
Well you're first
These two are tied for second
Which makes you fourth
No I have the shrine relic
It's not a shrine relic
It's kinda scary, it's all black
Next up is the French Game, Doctor Eureka
This one's really simple
Inside these test tubes are some balls
These are like, strong chemicals
Now some cards will be played
For example if this card was played
We have to copy the card
That's right
But because they're strong chemicals
You have to do it like this
You can't touch them
The balls right?
You mix them like this to copy the picture
This is tough
Whoever finishes first wins
This one's pretty tough
It's basically a puzzle
Nice nice
This is an elimination game, who will be left last?
The first one, is this
How should I do this...
Copy the picture
Ah this is annoying
This green one needs to be on the bottom
I think this is impossible now
I think I made it impossible for myself
Is this definitely possible?
Yes it's definitely possible
Ah! If you drop it you
lose instantly
Done!
Hamada wins
Oh he did it
Done!
Wasn't there someone who dropped them?
Hamada
No I didn't
It was Hamada
I didn't drop them
It definitely was around here
Right I heard it happen there
I'm the one who dropped them...
Couldn't you have said that earlier?
It was you?
I was the only who dropped them
Plus I didn't finish
You lost first
Ah, I forgot to mention something
Once you finish, you have to say "Eureka!"
He didn't say it
No he just told us that
That's no good
You didn't say Eureka or anything
By the way what does it mean?
Doctor Eureka is
our boss
Professor Eureka?
What the hell is that
Round 2
Let's raise our hands and shout Eureka
Sorry I didn't explain properly
Okay 4 people left!
And go
Eh? This, what do I do?
Oh this one's done
Eureka
Well this looks like Eureka to me
We can just decide last place with this
Since he couldn't do it
And there's 4 of them in here!
We're competing against this!?
It might be different next time
If she was watching the TV, your daughter would cry
That's enough papa
This is hard to watch papa
'Next is the German mental card game "Neu"
Written on these cards are numbers
50, 10, there's a bunch of them
Everyone gets 3 cards
Then one by one
The played card's numbers
are added together
Whoever's card adds up to 102 or more loses
The numbers are 1 to 10, 50, -1, -10, 101, ten types in total
For example
Like 3, and 6, we approach 102
Whoever's card adds up to 102 or more loses
You might have noticed this card as well
Now it increases right
When this is played, it goes up to 101
Eh?
What I don't get it
No Tanaka, this is 12 right
It's 9
Oh 9
9 plus 101 equals 110
Not in this case, no matter when you play it
When this is played,
all the previous numbers are ignored, and it becomes 101
This card ignores everything and sets it to 101
The only ways for the next player to avoid 102 are
Playing a -1 or -10 card, or
The can also play one of the 4 Pass cards
It's 3 cards,
it'll end fast then
But when you play a card, you have to draw another from the deck
No matter what you always have 3 cards
Oh the entire time?
Who's first?
I'll go first
Why don't we have Tanaka go first?
Okay 2
We're going in that order?
Don't we always go around like this?
Always?
Well it's fine
47 huh?
It really went up
It's getting close to 102
You had a card like that...
It's a turn so now it's Matsumoto's turn again
Pass the turn and reverse the order
You lose!
You just lost
That doesn't count
That's the end!
It was a joke!
It's a comedian's joke!
What, a comedian can't make jokes!?
You can't make jokes on this show!
It's a joke!
You're so loud
Despite that, it wasn't a smooth joke
Wait a minute, this is kinda, upsetting
Gaki no Tsukai is
a show you can make jokes on, is what I heard
That's how it was pitched by the producer Suga
That's how he pitched it in Osaka
That was 30 years ago
Card Game Neu
The loser drops out
Who will win?
Then,
Matsumoto first
May I
Pass?
What's the point?
Who are you passing to?
What's the point in passing?
It's the first turn
You should save this for later
Let my just say
I only have Pass cards
Oh all 3?
All 3 were these confusing cards
Alright 7, 9
9, then, 59
I can play this
That's fine right?
Right, you can play 101 at any time
Right
Yes yes, since it's 101
It's 101 right now?
It's 101 now
100, I see
It's become 100
It's only 1 away, I can only do this
Endo aren't you in danger?
I can only do this
Eh?
What are you doing?
I didn't have anything
I mean, 10 would've been fine too!
You chose the slightly smaller one
Endo is the first to drop out
After this is an unfortunate game
What why?
If I don't have a pass card, I can't pass?
Housei drops out
Even worse is Tanaka...
Huh?
Why do you only have 2 cards?
You didn't draw at one point
You definitely didn't draw at one point
It doesn't make sense otherwise
I'll just take the loss
Well yeah
Tanaka makes a huge foul, drops out
Therefore the final round is a Downtown battle
A rare match to see
It's the final game
Let's try to avoid another lame ending
This will determine the winner
Can I go first?
Oh it went up
78?
You didn't draw!
He's really watching you
There's a really strict judge
If there's only 2 players, pass to the other player
This one
88 right?
98...
Ooh, 89
Well,
Draw!
Is this on purpose?
I can't imagine this to be anything else
97, here it is
There it is
Draw!
This is like already
It's over!
In this situation I can play this right?
Yes you can, you can play a double
What is this?
The next player has to play 2 cards
A huge card has been played
There's no 0.5 card
You can only play the cards already in your hand
That was a huge card
That was huge
Oh he has something
Incredible!
okay okay
Draw
Doesn't he have to play 2?
Can he draw another first?
He can't draw another
Can't he draw then play?
Without drawing he has to play another
Translation - Tekno Typesetting - mattee53
I want to draw, I want to draw another
You can't continue with those two cards right?
Well honestly, it's over
Maybe you had a chance if you drew
If I drew another...
So lame...
It didn't even matter