Are their hearts connected? No Smartphone Meetup
The Rule; They think of a location to head to based on a theme
The game doesn't end until everyone meets up
The first theme; A typical bridge intersection
Starting at NTV in Kojimachi,
I'm getting on
The 5 head off to the places they thought of in a taxi
It's gotta be this one! Everyone will head there
Look how clearly you can see it
Namiki-Bashi
As expected nobody meet up, and Tanaka held everyone up
Tanaka is still driving
CMON!
DAMN IT!
Ikejiri-Ohashi, Ohashi, Ikejiri-Ohashi!
Ikejiri-Ohashi?!
For real?
The next hint; A restaurant with a lot of autograph plaques
Have you ever written one?
The only place I can remember is the Sex Museum in Atami
Once again, nobody met up
It's been 1.5 hours since the start; Nobody has met up yet, the worst outcome!
They wanna meet up soon! Time for the 3rd theme
What in tarnation?
No clue no clue
Tennis Court
"A huge tennis court" it says!
There's one that came to mind,
But the location, it's the Kinuta court
Tanaka was thinking of a tennis court in Setagaya
A tennis court they often use as a studio,
But to head towards Setagaya would take some time
And Hosei, in Nishiazabu?
Tennis courts are usually hidden from view!
There's one I thought that's really far away!
Kinuta!
The one I remembered right away,
The one you just remembered?
Near TMC, Kinuta court which we use as a studio...
The one I thought of right away, is the tennis court near TMC (Kinuta)
There's no way they'd go there
They'll ask "are you an idiot?"
This is difficult
But I came up with 2 locations, pretty quickly I'd say
In Hatagaya, by the aqueduct. The tennis court next to the Denny's
That one's been there for so long hasn't it?
I used to live near there, in Hatagaya. I passed by it every day
That one, and the Kinuta studio one
Everyone said the same thing; The tennis court in Setagaya
If everyone went with that option, they'd all meet up!
It's the Hatagaya one right?
Right?
I think Yamasaki will come
We used to pick up girls and go to the Denny's together
let's try and meet up with Yamasaki at least
This is hard to do alone
Aiminig for Hosei, Matsumoto chose a tennis court with a lot of memories
But will Hosei share in those memories?
Hold on please,
Towards [@!!#@#], ple@$3
Alright
He understood, he understood me
I stuttered so much but he understood me
Meanwhile in Akasaka, Endo considers his options
Isn't that Makku Akasaka-san?
Oh yeah
That's Makku Akasaka-san
Cocorico!
Passing through coincidentally
Makku Akasaka
Excuse us, we're shooting right now
What brings you here?
My agency is here
Ah, is that so?
You look low-energy,
SMILE!
Thank you very much
I kind of forgot, where was it again, what was it?
What location did Endo just forget?!
Matsumoto heads towards a tennis court in Shibuya
Do you think Hamada-san would go to Kinuta?
He might be, I thought of that place too
If I went there, I think if anyone would come it'd be Hamada
Everyone won't come, so it'll just be me and Hamada
And I really hate the idea of getting on the highway in the same taxi as Hamada for the next theme
That was something I considered to be honest
It's annoying isn't it?
Hamada heads off to his objective
What's the point of putting a vending machine there?
Ah, it's a studio?
And then,
It's for bands and stuff
GAN!
Hamada recieves heavenly punishment for disrespecting the vending machine
It's cause I was talking, you guys should've warned me too
So just where is Hamada going?
Jingu,
Head there please
Hamada relies on his memories, and heads towards Jingu-Gaen tennis court
I think I've seen a tennis court there...
Hmm, yeah nobody would go to Kinuta
So I've thought of another one,
Where?
[@#!@#!]
Kitagawa, alright let's go
DownTown can't meetup, but there's a chance 4 people might meet up
Will anyone be able to meet? Tonight we find out!
Timed and Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband
Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
No Smartphone Meetup!
Finale tonight!
Are their hearts connected? No Smartphone Meetup!
The theme; A large tennis court
Tanaka uses the highway to get to his destination quickly
This is the 4th time right?
This is the most confident I've been for any theme so far
The huge tennis court
There's no way I'll be by myself at this one
Tanaka heads towards his tennis court with absolute confidence
And Matsumoto arrives at the Shibuya tennis court
And then...
Is that taxi someone elses?
Will this be the first meet up today?!
This tennis court right? It's pretty big
Is that someone else?
C'mon...
It's just my manager
I thought it was one of them for sure
Well whatever, can we go in here?
This place here, I think this is pretty big for downtown
1, 2, 3, 5 - There's 6 courts here
Right?
And Tanaka as well arrives at his tennis court
Yeah, yes look there. Is someone there already?
Tanaka arrived at the tennis court beside the Shibuya Park exit
Even though the other members usually drive, this tennis court is visible from the road
I think they'll come for sure
Seriously, I'm so confident
Meanwhile, Hamada arrived at his destination
If they don't come here, then where the hell will they?
We even played baseball on the grounds there
They might have seen it while walking by it
If they think like that, Endo at least does play baseball
He might remember "Oh yeah, Jingu-Gaien had that tennis court"
Is he not coming?
I thought this would be a good one
HAMADA-SAN! WE DID IT!
HE'S HERE!
Hold on, I just said "Endo isn't here"!
Thank you!
I even said I thought you wouldn't be here
Thank goodness!
It's gotta be here right?
Yeah, they have the grounds there,
Then, did the others meet anyone?
Possibly
Only Hosei is still in transit
There's no way he won't come here
You see? There's 6 of them!
There's no other place with 6 courts here in the city
Seriously, someone will definitely come
What other answer is there but here, sorry to be so persistent
Which tennis court is Hosei heading to?
Then the other guys are still driving right?
Right
Ah! There!
Wow! Yama-chan you're amazing!
You really got it!
You came!
This place is really wide, I was at the other end looking for the entrance
I see I see
Thank goodness!!
This is fantastic
I can't think of anywhere but here
Tanaka-san, it's time up!
You're lying! For real?
You're kidding me!
Eh?!
Time up
Noooo no no no no no
The 5 call to report their locations
There's 3 of us here already!
3 of you?!
EH?!
Excuse me
All the capable members have met up
Gaki's capable members have assembled
Where did you meet?
Meiji Jingu Gaien tennis club
Where the hell is that?!
How many courts are there?
How many you say?
There's like 50
50?!
There's no way that's true!
Tanaka where are you?
I'm at that place, the tennis court near Shibuya park's highway exit
How many courts are there?
There's 3 here
3!
What the hell is that? You can find a court like that anywhere!
Matsumoto-san, where are you?
I thought at least Yamasaki would come here, I have a lot of memories with Yamasaki here
The aqueduct,
There's those tennis courts next to the Denny's right?!
There's goddamn 6 of them!
Just 6!
That was there?
AHHH YOU LIAR! You know they're there! The 6 courts
I can't remember the tennis courts at all
No no no no there's 6 of them! I saw just now, everyone is having SO much fun!
That's not relevant
You guys should reflect on this
No you reflect!
Yama-chan you don't remember those tennis courts?
What a troublemaker!
I don't remember at all. I have no memories with him
2 hours from the start, and 3 people met up right away. Just Tanaka and Matsumoto left
Next, the 4th theme
Nobody came here...
"Long flight of stairs"?
There are some I can think of, like for the trains
Yeah train stations. Like the Ginza line maybe.
What the heck is this?
There's one that came to mind immediately
Is it close by?
It's close by yes
It's close by. That place right? I think that place for sure.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
If you think about it, it's that one
You're right
Where did you 2 think of?
Yama-chan tell him
In Akasaka, Hie Shrine right? Yeah Hie Shrine.
Certainly! That place, yes.
It's a good one right?
That place is good I think
The 3 head towards their destination, Hie Shrine in Akasaka
It's gotta be that place
[!@!#!!@]
Cause Yoshimoto's headquarters were there too right?
So everyone has been in that neighbourhood for sure
I honestly can't think of anywhere else
I'm not considering my options, just that place
"A long flight of stairs" huh?
That place, Hiea Shrine? In Akasaka
I've never been there, but I have this feeling that place has long stairs
Let's go to [@!#!@#!], in [!@#!@#!]
The stairs at [!@#!#@]
I can't think of anywhere else
Should we bet on that place?
I wanna meet them
Will Tanaka's wish reach the other members?
Everyone wants to meet up with this theme!
Matsumoto heads towards his destination, Shinjiku south exit
Lumine huh?
TN: Lumine is a theatre owned by Yoshimoto.
I wanna be on stage there
Watch, you'll see me up there
I'll perform at Lumine for sure one day!
Meanwhile Hamada, Hosei, and Endo arrive at Hie Shrine.
Look how obvious it is
This is the only answer
Right in the middle of the city
If Tanaka doesn't come here, it's gonna be so unfunny when he's left by himself right?
That's true
Tanaka is slowing us down on purpose
He's not that type of guy
That's how he got the job on Zip!
Wow, so when you're not here they talk so much shit about you!
I feel bad
I can't think of anywhere else
Will the 5 be able meet up at Hie Shrine?!
Tanaka is right out
The timing doesn't make sense
Yeah he's taken too long
Then just where did he go?
I actually am curious
EHHH???
He's here! He's here!
Tanaka is last after all
Seriously?
What the hell...
This is it! Of course! It's here!
I will say though, my tennis court was definitely the right one
No it wasn't
And you went there a lot before!
When I lived in Hatagaya, you went to the Denny's so often!
We picked up so many girls, and took so many girls there!
And then we would all go back to my place.
And then we F[@@!$] a lot!
Let's leave it at that
I said everything
Just where are Tanaka's long stairs?
Where is Tanaka? They confirm his location
Where are you?
Me?
Yeah
I'm at the big stairs next to Fuji TV, the long ones
Odaiba...
Listen man, listen!
You can't go to Odaiba! They yelled at me for that!
We said Odaiba is out!
Seriously, we've said it so many times
Tanaka broke the rules they made and went to Odaiba
See! Look
Aren't they long?
Certainly, they are long. They fit the theme card.
They're even longer up close
That's inside FujiTV
Yes
It's private land
Odaiba...
We can't go there on an NTV show you idiot!
Seriously, c'mon seriously get it together
These stairs are really long!
Us 4 have already met up...
Eh?! Matsumoto-san you met up?
OF COURSE IDIOT!
Akasaka's Hie Shrine
There it is! Hie Shrine!
Hie Shrine! Oh damn they have stairs there?!
Of course!
Of course they do!
They're hella long!
We're gonna shave you with hair clippers
Please don't shave my head. Please don't shave my head.
We're in Akasaka, Tanaka
Please think about me too please
The hell we will!
It came up didn't it, Hie Shrine
You didn't think there were stairs?
I didn't think there were stairs. Why did I think of this place?
2.5 hours since the start, only Tanaka is left
They want to clinch it this time, time for 5th theme
Denny's
The one in Aoyama is famous right? The Aoyama Denny's
Ahhh! that place right?
It's a big one
Or there's the one on Kyuyamate, the Denny's in front of the Jojoen
Ah, by Shinsen intersection
They say Mori Shinichi goes there all the time
He orders 2 different plates,
He eats half of one and switches with his manager
He wants to try different things
What amazing information!
Can we go with my idea?
Why?
The Kyuyamate - "Why"?
Let's take a vote
Let's go with a vote
This is a tough one
Who says the Aoyama Denny's?
EHHH Really?
If you guys are wrong I'm shaving your heads!
Or I'll pull your eyelids off with pliers
Which one? Which one?
Neither
It's the first time we've had 4 people today, but maybe I'll split up
You go by yourself? Let's go already
I'm not convinced at all
It's gotta be the Aoyama Denny's
No no no no no no
So what will Tanaka do?
I got it! There's 2 of them though
There are 2 options
Damn this is hard!
Incidentally, could you tell us?
Aoyama, there's a Denny's in Aoyama right?
That one, or the Shinsen intersection one
That one -UWAH! This is hard!
Aoyama, or Shinsen?
[@!#!@#$%!]
[!@!@#@] Denny's
Are you good with that?
I'm good. Let's go
Tanaka chose from the same 2 options as the other 4
I gotta meet up this time
His 3rd time on the highway today
I've been on the highway so much today
We've been on the highway so many times...
I don't like feeling like a burden
Here right? Aoyama Denny's
Ah, here?
The 4 head to the Denny's in South Aoyama
One man is not convinced
If Kyuyamatei is the right answer, how will you bastards atone?
We're not your allies?
I was very insistent!
You filmed that right?
I think he'll come. Right Hosei-san?
Yeah, anytime now.
It'll take some time leaving from Odaiba
Tanaka gets off the highway, moments from his destination
text I want to end it with this one
But I can tell! There's no way he's coming.
Thank you!
So cold
If it comes down to that, you bastards...
It's fine if he got it wrong, I just wanna end this quickly
Yes, indeed
I'll bury you at Aoyama Cemetery
C'mon Tanaka
I said it right?!
What?!
Eh? YES!
TANAKA!!!!
TANAKAA!!!!!
YOU GOT IT DIDN'T YOU?!
Yay!
What the hell were you doing?
I feel great! It's gotta be here right?
Thank goodness!!
It's gotta be here
Why did you think of this place?
I was conflicted,
Between where?
Shinsen
AHHHHH
Yes
I tried to take us to Shinsen
Oh really?
But I knew you'd come here after all
No no no
Hold on hold on
He was so pissed off
He threatened us
He wanted to split up
He said if you didn't come, he'd bury us at Aoyama Cemetery
Timed and Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband