THIS IS PART 2 OF A TWO-PARTS EPISODE. PART ONE WAS NOT SUBBED BY SHION NO TSUKAI! IT HAS BEEN SUBBED BY DCSUBS, YOU CAN CAN FIND IT SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
Previous episode
I wrote these letters for me by myself
It's Hosei's 47th birthday
Hosei wrote fake thank-you letters to surprise himself
Hosei wrote fake thank-you letters the other members will read
You put my 100 yen lighter inside your pocket and gave me 10,000 yen
You told me you liked when I said "ho-ho-hoi"...
And you asked me: "ivory or Downtown, pick one"
Your words resonated in me so much I quit searching for ivory
Tonight, Matsumoto will read his (fake) letter for Hosei
Secret
A surprise guest will read their own letter
We'll also have a surprise guest with us
That's my precious memory...
I said it...
TRANSLATION BY SHION | TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS | MORE EPISODES: SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM | SOCIAL MEDIA: TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI & FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI | WANT TO SHOW SUPPORT? YOU CAN DONATE ON KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI OR PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
The Drunkards' Bar
Quit it, guys
Really, give me a break, I just can't
Master
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Mama
Tsukitei Hosei
Really, let's stop this
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
I can't anymore
Cocorico
Tanaka Naoki
Let's call it a day
He's right, that's enough
This one will be our last one
Oh, come on!
- It's really gonna be our last one
I can't, guys...
How far are you planning to go?
Everyone read their own letter one after another,
but I don't have a fixed timing to read my own, so...
Oh man...
- That's something...
I mean, that's my plan
- I get it
It'd be bad if I don't have anything to read, right?
Come on guys, what's this? A prank?
Oh boy...
This is too much
Is this really happening?
Is this Gaki no Tsukai? It barely fits in!
What's with this episode?
But we're already here, so...
- Yeah, he's right
There's a lot we don't know
- Right
Here's Matsumoto's letter for his beloved junior
From Matsumoto to Hosei: a letter of gratitude
Dear Yamazaki,
To be honest, I never thought I'd be writing you a letter
in my entire life, let alone a letter of gratitude
If there's something I should be grateful to you for,
it's from the time Downtown had success in Tokyo
And I was at the peak of my popularity,
being featured in over 10 regular shows
But no one ever asked for my opinion,
I was nothing more than a yes-man
But only you, between all of them,
you told me, "are you an idiot, Matsumoto?"
You got near me with your usual friendly smile
and told me lots of funny stories everyday
When I looked at you, always behaving like that,
I thought "It would be nice to have a little brother like him"
I always thought of you as my little brother
One more thing,
I'm not sure if this is a thank you or an apology,
But five years ago, when we were walking down Roppongi...
We got attacked by 5-6 gangsters, do you remember?
I was trembling with fear, my legs were shaking
But you suddenly jumped towards them
And you shielded me, saying "run away, Matsumoto!"
Sorry for running away, that day...
But then you came to my house
You told me "it's alright", with your face all swollen
And then you showed me again that friendly smile of yours
From that day on, I decided I needed to protect you,
and not the other way round, so I started working out
And now I'm friends with all the musclehead comedians
If you didn't show me your courage, that day
I don't think I'd be a muscle-comedian to this day
Thanks so much, Yamazaki
What the...
You chose to become a rakugoka, a wonderful job
You study so much and work really hard,
I'm sure you'll become a master in no time
And when that happens,
let me, your biggest fan, hear a rakugo story
And when I'll eventually stop being a comedian,
please stay with me as my brother
To my little brother, Tsukitei Hosei
Signed: Matsumoto Hitoshi, from Downtown
I see...
- I didn't know about that
That's news to me
I didn't know it
You really remember a lot of stuff, don't you
Your memories are really good
I have lots of things I've forgotten myself
You do?
Yeah
I may have forgotten about them, but you guys...
Just how many things do you remember?
It makes me think I should try to remember more
So I can reconfirm them all
Oh boy...
Were you...
Are you crying?
Did you come up with this together?
You decided this thing together?
It's one of those surprise shows, huh?
You all knew that, right?
Well, not exactly...
How can I put it...
- You did, didn't you?
Well, the shop is...
We're about to close here,
I don't think anyone else will be coming
Yeah, I guess so
Hey, are you still open?
Manabe Kaori
What now?
Here I am!
- Don't say it as if I knew it!
Staged dramatic episode:
Hosei's Fake Birthday Letters - Conclusion
Yeah, I guess so
Hey, are you still open?
What now?
Manabe Kaori
Here I am!   - Don't say it as if I knew it!
Sit down, please
- Can I?
How are you? Is everything alright?
Are you that familiar with him, Manabe?
Kinda
Don't worry about that
Try this oolong high
Alright, one oolong high
Sure
What the hell is happening, today?
Here
- Thanks
Come on, staff!
I didn't expect this guest, to be honest
I agree
- Can I drink it? Cheers, guys!
I'm gonna scold the staff, later
Cheers!
- Alright, alright, cheers I guess
Manabe's image doesn't really line up with Hosei's
But I'm glad she's here
I mean, this bar was getting pretty melancholic
I agree   - Oh, is that so?
Now she can liven up the mood a bit, I guess
Ah, I'm glad
Yeah, I agree
It's more lively now
- I'm glad, guys
After all today's... you know, Hosei?
It's your birthday, right?
That's right
It's his birthday
- Wow, she actually knows that
I really wanted to come here today
And since you're having this set up for today, I wanted to...
I wanted to let Hosei know about some things...
Oh my!
You meant that?!
Yeah, that's...
You came here for this?!
That's right
You tricked me again...
I thought it was a good moment, can I?
Did you write a letter?
- I did, actually
So, can I read it?
I mean, she's here already, just listen to her
Oh my...
- Can I?
Alright, but please, read it cheerfully!
Alright, in a positive way!
- Yeah
The atmosphere got really tense in here, enough of that
I see
Alright
So read it cheerfully ok? Go!
- Sure
Dear Hosei,
We happen to meet frequently when we're working,
And I bet you think all we do is just say hi to each other
But it's not the same for me
To be honest, before I entered the showbiz,
I used to be your biggest groupie
My youth was painted in your colors, Hosei
As soon as I finished school,
I rushed my way towards the TV stations to see you
And I always checked every show
you could have popped up in
I especially liked "Kurobuta Tengoku" from Tokyo TV
Black Pig Paradise
And of course, I still have lots of Hosei-themed goods
in my parents' house
Tee-hee! How embarrassing!
Before entering college, I was scouted
by someone from the showbiz in Shibuya's Yoshinoya
And the first thing I thought was "I get to enter Hosei's world!"
And the first time I met Hosei in real life,
I was so nervous all I could do was watching you from a distance
That time you glanced over at me only once,
and that's my most treasured memory
Tee-hee! I actually said it!
From that moment on, we even shared some TV shows together,
But my girly heart was so nervous,
I couldn't talk to you at all
Oh, sorry, this was supposed to be a gratitude letter,
but it ended up being a sort of love letter
I'm sorry, tee-hee
There are lots of reasons for why I'm grateful to you,
but if I have to say one in particular
That would be the third time I met you while we were working
That day, you were kind of different...
I remember seeing you in a corner, looking cool,
typing a draft on your PC by yourself
When I looked at you like that...
I thought "that's right, maybe Hosei can get to know me
if it's through a PC!" and so I started my own blog
I always waited for the day Hosei would notice me,
and I kept updating my blog on a daily basis
And then, one day, the media started
referring to me as "the Blog Queen",
And I was able to get lots of job offers from that
That blog I've created just to be seen by you
changed my entire life forever...
Maybe it makes sense only inside my head,
but I'm really grateful for what you've done
You chose to become a rakugoka, a wonderful job
I don't think you know this, but actually...
Rakugo? Again?
- Yeah...
Truth be told, I snuck up several times to see you perform
your rakugo skits, and sometimes I waited for you outside...
Hosei, thank you for making me experience such youth
Signed: Manabe Kaori
I see...
- Come on...
I didn't know that's the story behind her blog
There's a lot we can't know, if we don't ask
That's right
I had no idea, really
I didn't realize
You really saved me, I owe you so much
You've been so good at hiding it
You were my groupie?
That's right
Since I was part of TEAM-0?
Yes, that's right
Since TEAM-0?!
- Since TEAM-0
But really, mama...
Let's call it a day, shall we?
Yeah, I'm running out of tears here
- Can I have this?
Thank you so much
More?!
Shimoda Kageki
Seriously...
- You were here, huh
Hi there, Shimoda
It's been a while
- Indeed
Please, have a seat
So what do you...
- You too?
What do you want to drink?
- Let's see...
Sweet potato shochu, mixed with hot water
Sweet potato shochu...
Sweet potato shochu, huh?
- With hot water, please
He's a pro at writing, isn't he?
That's right, he's a professional
Cheers
- Nice atmosphere
Here's to you
Cheers, cheers
This is a surprise
Really?
- What brings you here?
Can I read you something?
No way...
Whatever, please...
I have no idea about his relation with Yama-chan
I didn't know they knew each other
- That's news to me
To my dear Hosei-chan,
Hosei-chan, it's been almost 3 years since we last met,
how have you been doing since?
Today I'm here to tell you how grateful I am to you,
But I want to start by recalling our memories together
Me and Hosei-chan first met around 20 years ago
We had this episode in which
I appeared inside your fantasy
And we slapped each other,
and in the end, we kissed. That was it
That time, we parted our ways without getting any closer,
But we had a miraculous second encounter
at the hair salon we both went to
And then, Hosei-chan, you suddenly told me...
"I happen to know a clothing store which I think
is perfect for your tastes, wanna go there with me?"
And so we went shopping together
It was a shop in Nippori full of fancy stuff,
some of those clothes were a bit showy
And there, you bought me fishnet stockings,
which were perfect for my tastes
From that day on everything else happened so naturally,
and in the end, we started living together
The life I shared with you was really exciting
You were particularly picky on my fashion sense,
you told me "no-sleeves is too flashy, don't wear it!"
You gave me lots of advice,
such as wearing more than 10 colors together
And after 17 years of living together...
A period marking the end of our life together finally came
You became a rakugoka, and moved away to Osaka
The day before you left our house,
We went to the hot springs together
And then we talked all night about silly stories at the Bamiyan
Like that time we went to pick up girls in Odaiba
We recalled so many things, and we cried together, until dawn
Hosei-chan, you're the one who brought the most joy
in my life, the life of an old 74 years old man
And I'm truly grateful for that
And now you chose to become a rakugoka, a wonderful job
I still dream of the day we can live together again
Signed: Shimoda Kageki
That's incredible...
I had no idea this happened...
What you just told us couldn't have happened
Yeah...
- You know,
If it was anyone else besides Yamazaki, am I right?
That's right
He's the one behind my hair, and my job
And even my activity as a writer for illustrated books
Man, he had such an impact on your life
Oh boy...
You didn't say anything, did you?
That was the most unexpected one
I mean...
- Yeah, I think so to
They lived together, huh
I feel like I've been completely uncovered, today
That was really evil of you
Such a bunch of bad guys
We can't have other episodes like this one
I agree on that
No one's gonna gain anything from it
Alright, we're done!
The fuck are we doing?!
So irritating!
- What's the meaning of this?!
I had no idea what's going on anymore myself...
Happy birthday, Hosei
From: Downtown, Cocorico, Shimoda Kageki, Manabe Kaori
I had no idea what to feel about it
Short Talk
How were your rooms arranged when you first moved to Tokyo?
When I first came to Tokyo, huh?
I don't really remember...
- I'm done with mine
Mine was like this
It was a single room made of 6 tatami mats, in an apartment
Where was it?
It was in Kugayama, monthly rent around 66,000 yen
Ah, Kugayama?
Here's mine, it wasn't far from Tanaka's apartment
In Tokyo, yeah
We lived pretty close
1 room (8 tatami)
- Bathtub
- TV
- Front door
- Kitchen
in Kugayama
I lived together with my cousin
My cousin lived there in Tokyo for a while,
I moved here as a freeloader at first
And two months later, Tanaka came to Kugayama
and we started to work together
I see
Tanaka didn't have a bathtub, so...
That's right
He used a coin shower, usually
- But...
You had a bathtub, right, Endo?
Yeah, I had one
Sometimes Tanaka...
Like, when the coin shower place was closed, during nighttime
He dropped by to take a bath
That's right
Coin showers are 100 yen for 4 minutes
And I had no money back then
Endo always told me to feel free to use his own bathtub
But he made me pay the same price, 100 yen every 4 minutes for it
For real?
- And I was like, whatever, I'll go to the shower
No way
That's evil, Endo
- Back to the coin showers, I guess
There are still traces left of his evil
- That's when it started
It was like this
I see...
- So...
It was when I was 20, 27 years ago
27 years ago, huh
I used to live with Noriyasu, my former partner (TEAM-0)
With him? I don't know much about that period
- Really?!
We shared a single room in Higashi Jujo
- Higashi Jujo...
Even so, the rent was around 80,000 yen
It was the peak of the bubble, you know
Its price was really high
- Really...
It's this room's fault we stopped getting along
I can understand that
It's the worst, you were always together
- That's right
During summer, Noriyasu slept during the day
While I worked part-time
I used to leave home after setting the heater up
Man, you're evil
- You suck!
Really?
- What the hell, dude
I guess it was fate you couldn't stay together
Right...
- It really sucked
I remember one time me and Hamada had this show
And stayed in Okinawa in the same room for a week
We were still around 20
Being one entire week with him made me so angry...
He grinds his teeth so hard when he sleeps
I swear, I couldn't sleep because of his bruxism
I could only sleep when he woke up
And he even said "How long are ya gonna sleep?!"
it was so goddamn infuriating!
I remember that
I couldn't wake up properly in the morning, because of him
I couldn't even have breakfast!
Yeah, sometimes I went alone
- Cause he slept through, huh
Yeah, I was asleep
- When I got back, he was still sleeping
And you went "are ya still sleepin'?!"
Inside my head I was so furious
You know what I mean?
- I know
Man, this guy sucks...
I remember I clearly thought he sucked
- That was around 30 years ago, right?
Coming up:
Downtown's rooms reveal
Here's mine
The fuck is wrong with you? What's this way of drawing?
- What are you...?
What's that?
- What do you mean?
I mean...
- Is that a map?
Is that a treasure map?
It's an office
- What's that?
Come on, it's easy to follow
- This is my office
Ah, is that an office?
That's not it, this is...
- You lived in an office?
We can see his style even when he draws stuff like this
The hell is this?
- This is not the entrance, this is a hallway
A hallway?
Is that it?
- I had a bedroom here...
Then, kitchen, toilet and bathtub...
- What the...
It's so hard to tell
There was also a living room, on the left corner
It was shaped like an L
- Oh, I see
Do you remember how much the rent was?
- I think it was...
200,000 yen or something like that
- Yeah, makes sense
My apartment too was around 200,000 yen
- Yeah
- Must be that
It was like this, a big L
Did you have any friends at the time?
Or like, some juniors you knew?
Weren't you married?
- Yeah, I had my wife
I see, so you had your family
- He lived with her
That's right; what about you?
I don't think I remember clearly,
I was in an apartment too
I had an entrance, a bedroom and...
man, the proportions are all weird
It's all weird
Why is the living room so small?
- What's this? What's this part?
Sorry, these two are bedrooms
This is the bathroom
With the bathtub and all?
- That's it
And what's this?
- It's the hallway
You suck at drawing, you know?
And I hosted several parties in this room here
I mean yeah, he was single back then...
One time we had a great party,
but Yamazaki disappeared in the bathroom
I went there and asked him if he was ok,
and I saw him washing his dick
Why are you washing your dick here?!
TRANSLATION BY SHION
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI