The 1st time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arehende!
When will Hamada notice, verification test!
This is about Hamada...
recently his senility has been, amazing
Japanese people
He probably thinks that includes as far as Taiwan
Even further maybe, Asia
Possibly the entire Northern Hemisphere
Today we will be doing something we've done several times
Tanaka's expertise
World tabletop games
World tabletop games right
But that's not actually the real theme
We'll be doing things to see if Hamada will notice
We won't go as far as messing around but
We'll have some tricks we'll do
We'll see when will Hamada notice
If he never notices then it'll be
rough
If he never notices, we'll have to keep going the entire time
I think if that happens
We should fire him
Fire Hamada?
He can join
London Boots instead
An agent contract?
He'd be at the same level as Ryou
I mean he won't make it on YouTube alone
These recent events are slowly...
Sorry sorry I shouldn't continue
One at a time, each of us will
Endo, Me, Yamasaki, then Tanaka, are you ready?
I'm ready
We'll start with Endo
I'll be going first
I will, for the entire recording
I will not say a single thing
He should notice that
Everyone will be talking a lot
Since it's a tabletop game
Not talking there is kinda...
Plus, only 1 person out of 5 not talking is strange
If your family did that it'd definitely hurt your feelings
That's true
Here at Yoshimoto we're a family
I feel like I should say that
Now the preparations are complete
It's time to standby for the prank
Okay, I'll go fetch him
Everyone acts normally
Waiting for the clueless Hamada to come
And then suddenly
Don't need it
Please
Say "you always say that" or something
I look like the bad guy
The first up is Endo
Now will Hamada ever notice?
Will he notice!?
Starting in 4, 3, 2
The 6th time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arehende!
So loud!
Let's play Tabletop Games from around the world!
We're doing this a 6th time?
This is the 6th time
Who wanted to do this?
He really loves this, seriously
I heard his thing was half standing on the way here
That'd make me a huge pervert
Just stop already man
Just play by yourself
But if he was alone,
it'd be limp
First is the same as always
They check out all the games
How much earlier did you come in?
I was around an hour early
Very meticulous
I had a confirmation
You we're lectured about all this
Yes, from the easy ones to the hard ones
Like let's do it like this
You've got it all inside you
Some of these were here last time and some are new
Like I remember seeing this
Right there are new games
There are some card games
And I've included some games that make you move a little
What are we playing?
Out of these, the one I thought of first
Is this German game
I think we should start with it
Germany
The Candy Witch (Knusperhexe)
Oh really?
Let's start with this one
Alright then, take a seat at the table
He really likes this huh
We'll it's true that
We all enjoy this
That's right
This is the best one right?
You can play it at home for a few weeks
Yes that's right
I think we need something like this
First is this
"The Candy Witch" a German game
I will begin explaining
There are four kinds of candies
Then just like this
We create a roof
The set-up is a little hard
This is just setting up?
Yes
Now if you'd like, we can all go around
Carefully placing cards in the middle
And make a roof
We're making a roof?
Right, first
This is unrelated to the game?
It's unrelated
What the hell?
This kind of a game...
You could've just set this up ahead of time
But then you wouldn't have seen this state of the roof
The thrilling part will come after this
It's gotten quite stable
Oh you're right
I see I see
We can fill in the middle part?
Yes, it's okay to fill in the middle
This is kind of amazing, a very strange idea
In order, we take a card
If it's chocolate then chocolate becomes one of your cards
In the second round, when it's your turn again
If you draw another chocolate
Rather if you draw the same card
You have to put it back
Put it back?
Both of them?
Just one
At the end whoever has the most cards wins
You want most unique candies
And if you cause the roof to collapse, you lose
That's obvious
At that time...
I suppose you're right
It's pretty obvious
That's why we were all doing this
At that time, whoever has the most cards wins
Say something!
Huh, what, what?
Congratulations!
What's going on?
This is scaring me
What? x9
Incredible!
As expected, Hamada!
Seriously this is scaring me
You're actually scaring me
Incredible!
Today there was actually a secret theme
"When will Hamada notice?"
How conscious is Hamada of the other members?
was the secret theme
Since the opening, Endo has not said a word
Really, Hamada
I didn't notice here, at the start
I didn't notice over here either
But once I came over here
I thought He's not saying anything
I'm so glad
For me it was slowly getting funnier
He wasn't saying a single thing
When is this guy gonna say something
I'm really glad
We're going to reset
Right let's clean up
I want to actually play
What the hell, seriously
Right, this is a fun game
To resume the game, they clean up the area
Can we go over the rules again?
I didn't really get them earlier
Currently, Hamada still has no suspicion
Were you actually filming?
Yes
We're filming?
A new trick awaits
This is fun though, really
Tanaka can you go over it again
Honestly I didn't get it before
Endo wasn't really listening I think
I thought if Hamada didn't notice
I'd say something to Endo directly
Early on it was nerve-wracking
It really was for me
What order are we going in?
We'll go around like this, starting with Housei
I'm first, okay
Can I take cards from the bottom?
Yes you can them from anywhere
If it collapses, that's bad right?
Collapsing is bad
Okay I got a candy
If it collapses you lose
A cupcake
Woah! You were really rough there
He really went for it
Chocolate
Huh? We got all 4 types
That's right
But we can get the same ones too?
That's correct
This was just a coincidence
It's fine, if you get the same ones, you just put it back
Perfectly getting all 4 types together
Isn't that a miracle?
We just grabbed the ones Tanaka put down
Oh really?
What the hell are you talking about?
No I'm just trying to include everyone and have fun
Sorry that was rude
In the first and second rounds
He doesn't notice the trick, the game advances
And we arrive at the third round
The target age is quite low
From 5 to 99 it says
From 5 to 99?
100 would be fine too!
They should include 100 year olds too
Include 100, seriously, they can play
These two are the exact same
You're afraid of it collapsing, right?
Does it collapse so easily?
Well it's stacked pretty densely
It's starting to get difficult now
It's probably still fine
It's the third round now
What should I do...
True, in the third round it gets a bit...
Aah, which one do I pick?
What? Just take any of them
It's still fine
I don't know...
What do you mean you don't know?
You can definitely grab one
Look these ones around here are fine
Just slide them off
Hm? Which one?
Like this one
This one's fine too
No I'm a little scared
Because it's on the corner
Aren't you like, really tall?
Congratulations!
What the hell, come on!
Say it sooner!
Oh it's this!
He didn't notice at all!
You were pretty slow!
I wasn't slow at all
How did you notice?
When I stood up, and was talking
I thought "Huh?"
You've seen him so many times so
I was like "Huh?"
Sorry! Sorry!
This is really
Cut it out already!
Let's play seriously!
This was really interesting
Play seriously
I'll play seriously, really
You're absolutely huge!
Right, that's why you should've noticed sooner
No I wouldn't know so early
Well he still noticed it in the end
Enough with these streamers already
The second reset of the day
How many centimeters are these things?
These are pretty tall
11 cm
11 cm would make you 183-184 cm
Let's play the game!
Right, this is a really fun game
However, the tricks on Hamada are not over yet
Oh sorry
There's a lot of these
The staff withdraw a little too carefully
Hamada appears extra vigilant
They're getting it all
It's fine if you leave some
That's true, now that you say it, it's really...
Alright we're going to resume filming
Starting on Tanaka, 3 2 1
Alright, once again, let's resume the game
It's Matsumoto's turn
You should be a little careful
How durable is this thing
Ohh, nice
He's definitely getting a duplicate
These edge ones are a bit scary
You put back the duplicates
This is a duplicate so
you put it back
I already have the walking stick so I can't take that one
Walking stick?
It's candy
It's "The Candy Witch"
You're completely off
Maybe I shouldn't talk after all
Endo and Tanaka grab their cards
Next up is Hosei
I'll grab...
I'm safe
You already had that one
He has to put that back
Put it back
I should remember that one
Only one, only one
So naggy
This is fine
Now I'll take the one I saw Matsumoto put back
And this is safe right
The tempo has risen a bit now
Yep, I'm safe
Hm, what to do...
Maybe the middle
Okay, safe
Man I don't remember any of them
Ooh, okay okay
Soon we'll be able to see inside
This is dangerous
Woah, that's a risky move
This is probably fine
Cupcake, okay
Now we can see inside the house
Which one should I take...
Ahh, this is no good
But it's still anyone's game
We all have around the same
Right, but I've never gotten a chocolate
Yeah you have no chocolate
Ah chocolate. I kind of want to take that one
I'm first though
It's a cane, so there's no point for you
Right, I'd have to return it
Man this is kind of...
It looks like it's about to break
One piece decides the game
Next is Hosei
Which one...
This one
Breasts!
Enough!
Thank you very much!
Enough already!
You we're slow again!
What the hell is this!
We all said we'd play
I wouldn't think he'd be next
You were a little slow Hamada
They were really poking out!
Why would I look at Yamasaki's chest?
When will Hamada notice, verification test!
Up until now, Endo, Matsumoto, Hosei's trick
Hamada has masterfully cleared them all
Sorry sorry
Let's play already, play the game
We'll play
This is the third reset today
As expected of Hamada
This... This is kind of...
The clean up is suspicious
Isn't the clean up kinda suspicious?
Really?
While they're cleaning...
They leave the set during cleaning
Otherwise it doesn't make sense
Suddenly Yamasaki's chest becomes huge
Now we change to another game
Eh, we're stopping?
This is good, it's good
Better than the last one
Thank you
This is good right
"Bounce Off!"
Okay okay okay okay
All the past American ones have been surprise types
We resume with a new game
"Bounce Off!" an American game
America Bounce Off!
It's a 2v2 Team Battle
You draw a card with these marks
You want to line up 3 balls of the same color
Each team tries to throw their balls onto the board
Throw?
Whoever makes the pattern first wins
When you're throwing, you need to bounce it
Wait how do we throw it?
Ah, like that? Ah nice
Right, just like that
Housei and Matsumoto Team
Hamada and Endo Team
They need to aim the balls into their place
This one's really hard
The four balls can be anywhere?
Yes, anywhere is fine
Then we'll go first
What why?
Shouldn't we do rock-paper-scissors?
He said it so casually
No no no no
Between us, it's a versus game
You're trying to notice things right?
I'm pretty on-edge right now
Seriously
Now we start the game
This is hard
Now it's the other team's turn
I see
Ahh, this is difficult
No way!
The game heats up
Seriously?
Then nothing happens for a while
I'm going to try and aim over there
And so the yellow team wins
This is fun, I like this one
Another round?
Let's change the teams then
Tanaka, do you want to play?
Yes
Why don't you swap with Endo
Okay sure
Let's do Rocky-Paper
Rocky-Paper?
No, it's not that
Oh to swap
To decide who's with who
You didn't mean me and Tanaka
That too, that too
We'll do that too
Okay, I see
Now we change up the teams
Carefully aim the balls into their place
This is the pattern
This is a hard one
It got really hard
It really is
Now decide who goes first
I mean either is fine
Rocky-Paper Sho-, er oops
It's not that, it's not that
This is just his old age showing
Sorry about that
They start the second game
Both teams reach the match point
You're both one away
This is hard
If you did it it'd be amazing
Concentrate
It'd be super cool
I'm going
Did you fart?
No I didn't
He just farted!
No there's nothing
I didn't even fart, what's wrong
No I heard this rumbling noise
It wasn't me
My stomach was growling
Oh my bad
Please apologize
Oh I'm sorry
Tanaka concentrate
Tanaka's bad side is showing
That was a huge blunder Tanaka
Now I just need to land it there
Hamada you can do this
You pretty much know where to bounce it
If Downtown can land this they win
Downtown Team Wins
It was really right there
That was great
And that's it
Alright! We're OK! That's a wrap
Already!?
Translation - Tekno Timing - mattee53
Typesetting - Teknova QA - Shion
Man I hate this
It's exhausting
I've been so exhausted
The correct answer was "There's nothing else!?"
Ah, it was that...
Nobody had any tricks
I see, it was just three
"There's nothing else!?" Of course it was
"Tanaka's not doing anything!"
Of course, it was that
Ah, I'm sorry!