Translated by eChie
Remastered by Shappuri Agemasu Subs
Good morning.
Good morning Hamada-san.
It shouldn't be so hard to tell.
It's me.
You don't usually wear such an outfit, do you?
Because you're a performer.
That's very clever, Yama chan.
Thank you.
"Because you're a performer."
It doesn't matter at all.
I have a favour to ask...
What is it?
Matsumoto has something he really wants to do.
Again?
He told me that the other day.
Yes.
What does he want to do?
What is it?
He wants to set a world record in the high jump.
Huh?
Why?
I don't know, since he was crying...
Was he crying?
The current world record is 2m 45cm
2m 45cm? That's high.
It means he wants to set 2m 50cm, right?
But there's nothing we can do about it.
Wrong. That is why I'm dressed like this. Come on!
Don't make me explain everything. What does this outfit make me?
Kuroko (Stage assistant dressing in black).
He really wants to high-jump. What can we do?
Assistance, right?
Assistance?
Let's help him to high-jump, shall we?
Will he be satisfied?
Will he be satisfied, high-jumping with our assistance?
He will. He really wants to high jump.
Are you sure?
Will you help?
Yes. Yes, we will.
Will he be able to exceed the world record of 2m 45cm set by Sotomayor from Cuba In 1993?
Wow, this is high.
Here he comes.
Good morning.
He's ready.
You may be thinking that
Matsumoto is being selfish again.
When you have been
in this field for a long time,
a time like this
does come.
Yeah, a time you feel like high jumping.
But my base strength is not enough and I have not been training for it.
So it seems to be impossible
Yes.
So I hate to say this but
just a little is OK so
I need your power
All right. Let's do it.
Shall we?
So high huh?
Yes it is.
Is it that high?
I count on you guys.
Yes, we understand.
Let's just make it happen in one time
Yes
Hey wait...how...
How...
Leg...leg...
OK.
OK..OK.
Ready?
Yes
Hey hey hey. wait.
Timing was bad.
Not good at all.
Sorry.
You go there.
Yes, only timing.
Now, timing..
So it's just about timing then.
It's the timing, yes
Let's get off to the excellent start.
Ready?
Yes!
Three!
Matsumoto san!
Our fault?
Well, we tried our best!
What should we do?
We should go.
What should we say though?
We should apologize anyway, in this situation.
We should lift him up higher. Huh?
But he's heavier than I thought.
Yes.
Right?
Matsumoto is doing his knitting
Matsumoto
I think the angle was wrong.
I don't care that I couldn't.
The important thing is, everyone is going in the same direction. Right?
I'm not mad because I can't high jump.
If you're not going to try hard, just quit it!!
No, it's not that.
No, stop it.
Don't waste it.
You did a good job. Nice color.
Leave it to us.
It's angle.
Please come, we will be perfectly ready.
We'll be waiting.
Changing the mood, here's the 2nd challenge!
We should do a talk too.
Well
just let's do it, OK?
Let's hurry
Ready?
Yes.
Put it on there.
No no no..
What?
Sorry.
I thought it was angle.
Wasn't it strange?
No.
Let's try again. It's gonna be OK.
Sorry, but next time will be OK.
Sorry
It'll be no problem at all.
Let him lay down.
It's OK.
So heavy!
Ouch!
Use your hands.
Take it off it hurts!
Lift him up!
Lift.
Matsumoto san!
Our image was once we lift him up, he will...
He would be pulled up high.
Then we could've thrown him over.
Go to Matsumoto's dressing room again to apologize
Matsumoto is playing imaginary drums
I want to high jump!
Don't make me wear strange accessories.
Too long.
I waited for way too long.
We are trying hard though.
Matsumoto tries the 3rd challenge!
It's so high.
It is so high.
Let us begin!
We need one more. This side and that side.
Is it OK like this? This side is sticking out.
This is going to be good.
Right?
It was long.
He was watching us while laying down.
Go to Matsumoto's dressing room again to apologize
You shouldn't laugh when he's mad
We're sorry, we'll try not to
Since you guys laugh; it makes him more mad.
Yes.
Matsumoto is filling out an embarkation card
I am NOT an old man,
who needs to stay for such a looong time
in bed.
What the hell. What do you think?
When people watch it in the studio,
I want them to think I could do it!
There are people who actually high jump close to that height.
As for me,
It's not that I can't. But looking at the bar....
REALLY MAKES ME WANT TO HIGH JUMP!! 💢
We're sorry.
That's true.
Still a long way to the bar.
We should seriously think about how to lift him up higher.
We understood, Matsumoto san.
We'll do it next time.
We should go up.
Yes, we think so too.
Let's use ladders
Yes.
We can go really close to the bar.
Hoping this will be the last, the 4th challenge!
It'll be OK.
Let's do it.
Come here! Come here!
Sit there.
Parallel to the bar.
Ouch.
Ouch!
Ouch! Ouch!
Heave ho!
Matsumoto Hitoshi 2m 50cm
The World Record has been broken!?
You did it!
You did it!!
He did it.
Yeah.
What's the matter?
Go to Matsumoto's dressing room to check him out
Matsumoto is trying to remove chewing gum off his shoe
Was it good?
Do you really think viewers would go like "Wow, Matsumoto did a great job!"
Do you?
Nope
You don't!?
No way.
Well, rather than "Macchan is great..."
I'm not satisfied with the staff's applause
We'll do it again after next month.