They said "you guys buy them"
They said "buy them"
So Japan bought them
Shut up you two!
In this episode, they will point out things they see and spout some trivia
There's gotta be something about bowling
Incidentally they would give turkeys as presents to those that got 3 strikes
So that caught on with young people
The heavenly voice verifies their trivia
And on this drive,
the end won't come until they've accumulated 100 trivia
Starting at Shiodome, in front of NTV, they got off to a good start,
The roller bags these days can spin in multiple directions ... it's convenient
No shit!
The quality of the trivia started to drop
Tanaka rescued them from this pinch!
Something about Condors,
There it is, the animal trivia
This is gonna be good
Crows can manipulate around 40 words
What do you mean "manipulate"?
Even inside the Family Restaurant they took a break in, he continued with the animal trivia
Trivia Count
2 hours since the start, they've come up with 45 trivia
However, sometimes they can't come up with anything
Yamsaki is forcefully supressing his sexual desires right now
He almost jumped at an old lady's ass at the bank
Wrong! Wrong!
Will they be able to get 100 trivia?!
Timed and Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband
Trivia Drive, 2 hours since the start. They head out on National Route 1 once again
Drive A GO GO!
TN: "Drive A GO GO!" is a show Hosei appears on
Why?
Why did he say that?
Trivia Count so far:  45
They are still far away from their goal of 100
I can't remember where I heard this,
They say men in their 40s think of sex once every 4 minutes
It really pissed me off
As a representative of men in their 40s, allow me to say,
That's totally incorrect
Definitely incorrect right?
That's impossible, every 4 minutes
There's no way it's every 4 minutes
There's a McDonald's there
Oh, what is it?
You know the McShake?
When it first came to Japan, it was really mediocre, and unpopular
So they changed something and it exploded in popularity
They changed the straw,
Ahh I see
They made the straw fatter, and the size they changed it to,
They made the size similiar to the average female nipple size
They made the suction required similiar to that required to drink milk from a mother's breast,
And it took off after that
The McShake became popular after they changed the straw
Oh wow
As expected
Alright more on McDonald's
When they first came to Japan, I think DownTown-san would've been in highschool
Do you know how much 1 hamburger used to cost?
Around 500 yen?
It was 1 dollar,
360 yen
I see!
That's cool right?
The price of a McDonald's burger in Japan was 80 yen
Wow really? That was...
Asshole!
No way!
Pull over and let us out
Let us out asshole!
So 1 dollar used to be fixed to 360 yen right?
Do you know why they decided on 360 yen?
Americans didn't understand anything about Japanese culture,
So when they were considering how many yen a dollar should be,
They said, let's base it on the circle
TN: The character 円 for "Yen" can also mean Circle ("En")
360 degrees
Ehh?!
Between 1949-1971 based on a fixed exchange rate 360 Yen = 1 USD
Let us off!
Get out of the car asshole!
Let's change drivers
You better cut it out
Eh? What's going on with me today...
You really gotta knock it off
There's a poster of an Elephant on that convenience store
Stop forcing animal topics like that!
You're really forcing this
An elephant's nose and upper lip stretch out as one piece
They're the same part, the upper lip and the nose
Tanaka's stories are so disturbing!
An elephant's upper lip and nose are attached
Like the bald vultures
We're halfway done
Aoyama Clothing
It reminds you of Miura Tomokazu right?
Yes indeed
So we can go from Miura Tomokazu -> to Momoe-chan
So everyone thinks Momeo-chan's last concert was at Budokan, where she left the mic and said "See ya", right?
In fact the actual last show was 2 days later on the Show "Yoru no Hit Studio"
That was the last one
Eh? Really?
Hit Studio was the very last one
Ah, is that so?
Momoe-chan's last concert was on Yoru no Hit Studio
Ah that felt nice
Cause everyone thinks the Budokan was the end right?
A train just passed by
Trivia Count: 50
Oh yeah, we're heading towards Yokohama
Ah, oh yeah,
You see that roadsign, I'm not sure if it applies to that too, but,
You know those male female symbols for washrooms?
They originated in Japan
I think it started with the 1970 Osaka Expo
Ahhh the World Expo?
It was easier for foreigners to understand symbols instead of writing
At the Osaka Expo? Wow!
Yes yes
Washroom male female signs originated in Japan
Wow!
I didn't know that!
Ah, you see the Yokohama Landmark Tower?
That's the tallest building in the world
Actually, at 296 metres it's the tallest building in Japan
Ah, tallest in Japan?
Won't the Skytree surpass it?
It will be the world's tallest Broadcast Tower, at 634 metres
Endo you're so smart!
That's amazing? Wow, the tallest Broadcast Tower?
Yokohama Landmark Tower:  tallest building in Japan (296m)
Tokyo Skytree:  Tallest Broadcast Tower in the world (634m)
Endo's counter was great just now
I was like *pow* *pow*
There's Yokohama Stadium
It's Yokohama Stadium
Yokohama Stadium huh?
Do you know why Baseball has 9 innings?
I don't know either
In the past, after the game both teams would come together and have dinner
And the guy that would cook for both teams,
He would finish cooking lots of tasty things usually by the 9th inning
And the cook got pissed, he said "When are you gonna eat?!"
"My food is gonna get cold!"
So that's where the 9 innings started
Wow, that's why?
Baseball has 9 innings because a cook complained
Oh it's true!
I didn't know that
How does this guy know that?
Trivia Count:  57 + 1
2.5 hours since the start,
They begin to exhaust their collection of trivia
So in order to think of more themes, they head to Yokohama Chinatown!
What kind of trivia will the be able to come up with?!
Well, it is useful to be on the street
Yeah
This is a "Chinatown" right?
Yeah a Chinatown
But there's nothing here!
Gold medal!
Ah, a gold medal
Gold medals are made of silver aren't they?
Entirely silver?
Gold medals are made of silver?
Gold medals are made of silver
Yup
Ehh that's amazing!
They're made to look gold
You know the word "Aho" (idiot) from Sangokushi?
TN: Sangokushi is a manga adaptation of The Romance Of The Three Kingdoms
"Ato" was the name of Shu Han's child (character in the manga)
And that kid was really reckless, so in Japan "Ato" became "Aho"
It became "Aho"?
The etymology of "Aho" comes from the name "Ato"
Wow!
What the hell man? Stick to animals!
Yeah!
I'm so disappointed
Cause I saw that thing
Tanaka actually really likes Sangokushi
He does like it
Anything, anything could work...
Umm, this pig here...
We think pigs are fat right?
We have that image right?
They're mostly muscle
No way!
So when we call fat people pigs...
It's very rude to pigs
Cause it's muscle?
They have the same body fat percentage as models
Pigs are mostly muscle
Really?
Wow!
I wanna say something about Chahan or something
Yeah
Ah, shark fin..
Sharks are cartilaginous fish,
So the only fossils they leave behind are their teeth
Since sharks are cartilaginous,
only their teeth remain as fossils
Yeah so ... That "aho" fact was unnecessary
Just animal facts
Yeah!
That "Aho" was unnecessary!
I just like Sangokushi
Hello!
I can't come up with anything
Peking Duck, is actually just the skin
Yeah of course
You knew that already of course
It was too shallow a fact
A bit too shallow
There it is!
Panda!
There's a lot of Pandas here
We have this image they only eat bamboo, but their omnivores so they eat things like bugs too
They eat insects
Pandas are omnivores and eat also insects
They're omnivores huh?
Yeah, they eat insects too
There was a photo of Agnes-chan there,
Agnes-chan can actually speak Japanese really well
Well yeah, she just has an accent
Ah, Shozo might know about this
Ahh yeah!
Matsumoto-san speak about that please, that Dragon
The "Touch the reverse scale"?
Dragons have a single scale under their chin that's in the reverse direction
So if you flick that, the dragon gets really angry!
The phrase "Touch the reverse scale"
Dragons
have a single scale under their chin that goes against the grain
That's where the phrase came from?
That's where it came from
As they say
Wow!
Manholes are round so they don't fall down
If it was rectangular it would fall down if it wasn't aligned
But circles are always aligned and it never falls
I see!
Ah that one felt great!
Manholes are circular to prevent falling
That one felt great
With the help of Tanaka and Matsumoto, the 5 continue to accumulate trivia
They get back in the car, and set off on National Route 1 once again
Trivia Count: 69
We're almost done
Finally, 69
Well in the worst case, we stick to animals and Tanaka does the rest
That's true
I'm sure we'll finish in no time!
Tanaka definitely knows 30 animal facts
Nissan...
Carlos Ghon...
You know Carlos Ghon, even though he looks like that, is NOT a sea turtle
He doesn't make an animal call after laying eggs
He's definitely a sea turtle
Shall I say something about sea turtles then?
We have this image that turtles tuck their heads and limbs into their shell right?
Sea turtles don't do that
A lot of people don't know this,
They put their limbs to the sides right?
They put them to the side, yes
Land turtles chose to defend themselves by entering their shell,
Sea turtles chose to escape quickly by swimming
Ah I see, they gotta defend themselves after all
Sea turtles don't enter their shell
Ah, that reminds me of something
Sharks often attack humans right?
So the mo-
They don't often do that though
They often attack,
I have heard about such incidents
Only a few times though
And often, surfers-
It's not often, though
Sharks really go after surfers,
Do you know why?
I think I've heard about this
Oh I don't know
Turtles are shark's favourite food
And if you look at a surfer on a board from below, they look like turtles
And that's why they get attacked
I see
Surfers when paddling
look like turtles to sharks
That's true
We're finally in the 70s
First time he got it
It's not my first time!
A gorilla, look there
Gorillas ....
They can be gay sometimes
Gorillas can be gay
Wow, Gorillas are like that?
Tanaka you're incredible!
Wow, finally
Trivia Count: 78
Wow, we're only 6km from Totsuka
Oh crap. What about Totsuka Yacht School?
Totsuka Yacht School...
Trucks, there's Isuzu trucks there,
The three lamps they have on top, they indicate the speed
Ah yeah, that's right
20 - 40 - 60 km/h
Yes, that one is indicating 40 km/h
Ah, is that why?
The 3 lamps on trucks indicate speed
Like that one right?
Yeah, the middle light is out
Woah, that's what that means
So Takeda Tetsuya looked at those lights and said "I ain't gonna die!" - He knew he'd be fine
TN: Reference to the film "101st Proposal" in which Takeda Tetsuya jumps in front of a truck and survives
"I'll be fine if that hits me"
After this
They get to 100?!
"It's only going 40 km/h"
Trivia Count: 90
It's gonna be rather difficult to finish this off
Just 10 left
It's gotten really difficult
There aren't as many billboards and stuff
KYOLEOPIN
TN: KYOLEOPIN is a health drink
Imada got smacked by Hamada cause of that
The KYOLEOPIN incident
What happened?
Imada was told "Go buy some KYOLEOPIN"
And he didn't know what that was
"KYOLEOPIN?"
"KYOLEOPIN!"
He didn't know how it was spelled either
He didn't think it was a Katakana word
So he asked for KYOLEOPIN, and he got something that might be it. He thought "Well this'll do"
But Hamada said "THIS AIN'T KYOLEOPIN!"
And then slapped the shit out of him
That was more or less the first time they met
I think that's pretty good trivia
Can I use the fact that I'm feeling sleepy?
Yes, please
When you want to sleep, there's the sheep counting right? "Sheep 1, sheep 2"
The reason it's sheep - In English, 羊 means "Sheep"
And 寝る is "Sleep" - So because the words are similiar, it makes you sleep
So Japanese people are weird then
They are
The reason behind counting sheep is
because sheep sounds like sleep
There we go!
There are some people that I think can't tell the difference between sheep and goats,
The most obvious thing is the goats live in high places,
And sheep live in pretty flat lands
You can tell by looking though
Sheep
Goat
Some people can't I guess
Yes,
Water Bugs (Tagame) and those other ones are also hard to distinguish,
Water Bug
Diving Beetles? (Gengoro)
Diving Beetles
Diving Beetles and Water Bugs are hard to tell apart,
So there's a way to tell,
There was a clear difference between them, but I have clearly forgotten
Clearly forgotten
Kengoro is my dad's name
My dad and the father of Hiromi from B-21 were in the same class at school
Eh?!
That's my trivia
Hamada's dad was in the same class as B-21 Hiromi's dad
And they both went to Tosoya?
My dad went to Tosoya, his dad went to Daiiku
Ah Daiiku
That's amazing
My older sister, and Tsutsumi Shinichi (actor),
Were in the same grade at the same high school
Just leave that for the last 6
Tsutsumi's friend said they liked me,
And they came over to my house,
And I've recently they're now a story teller in Kansai
So hard to follow!
Trivia Count:  95
There's nothing at all out here!
Yeah...
Damn this is getting worse
We're in the last 10
Ah, there it is, an ambulance
Ambulance!
119 (Japanese emergency number)
Do you know about the 110 number? (Calls the police)
What about it?
In the past, they used rotary phones right?
1 and 0 are the farthest numbers on the dial,
So it takes time to dial 1, 1
They picked the farthest numbers?
Yes, so you can take the time to think calmly
Like "Do I really need the police"?
Yes, something like that
They picked 110 because 0 is far from the 1 so you can take that time to think calmly
I
Just 4 more...
I think that's not good though, it should be faster to dial
Yeah, so you don't have to think
Hold on, I really,
Trivia Count: 96
REALLY don't want to keep driving
Yeah, we've traveled really far
Just 4 more!
Can I use the topic of phones?
In the past, when Japan first got phones
The phone numbers weren't multiple digits long
And the most famous example,
"Castella is #1, Phone is #2, 3:00PM Snacks from Bunmeido"
TN: Bunmeido is a snack company
That was Bunmeido's number, if you asked to be connected to #2 in Shinjiku,
It would connect to them
Shinjiku's #2 was Bunmeido's number
3 more left
Finally, the last 3
Anything is-Ah a Tanuki just ran by!
A Tanuki?
Liar!
From the mountains, see!
Stop lying!
It's the lost continent of Mu, see there
The Mu Continent?
On the billboard there
There might be something about the Mu Continent
Game? Okay I got something
Do you remember when that game "Seaman" was popular?
Oh yeah, I remember
Seaman
Do you know what happens at the very end?
I don't, tell us please
He turns into a frog
No way, a frog? What kind?
Really?!
He turns into a frog with a human face
Seaman turns into Frogman
He ends up as a frog?
He ends up as a frog
Just 2 more!
Well the last one, it would nice to end on a high note
Yeah, a high note
If you say something like that, we'll never finish!
Trivia Count:  98
Shizuoka...
There's a lot to say about Shizuoka
I'm gonna end up in Shizuoka
It's gonna be a pain to get back
Yes, it will
Harajuku Park 3...
The guy on the bike that passed us had a Seahorse on his jacket
Don't lie!
No really! He did! The camera could confirm it
It was a blue jacket
We gotta confirm that first
But we're in a jam, he might've gone ahead
Alright, say your Seahorse trivia
The thing about Seahorses,
The one who gets pregnant is not the female, but the male
The female deposits her eggs into the male,
And the offspring grow inside the male's body
It's the male's role to reproduce!
Male seahorses are the one that get pregnant
I want to confirm that jacked though
Yeah, we gotta confirm that somehow
I'm very certain it was a seahorse
Tanaka has the worst eyesight too...
That's true, the one with the worst eyesight...
Alright!
After this:  The final trivia?!
Last one!
Trivia Count: 99
Should be a good trivia for the last one
Yeah
Something as good as the Turkey one
It sucks now there's traffic
Yeah that's true
Whale! It's a whale!
Yeah, it's a whale!
There is! For real, a whale!
There's a dolphin too
Ah, this is a good one
Which one should I pick? What should I do!
Pick a good one, for the ending
Hurry! Before the signal changes!
Generally, dolphins and whales are the same species,
Under 4m is a Dolphin, and over that is a whale!
It's kind of underwhelming
No, that's not it, that's not it
He even said "generally"
That's not it right?
Whales...Ah that's not it!
Umm, no that's not it
Calm down Tanaka, calm down
This is one of those situations
Whales, you guys know this,
Their nose, their nose is on their back right?
They shoot water out of there-
That's their nose?!
I didn't know that
THAT is amazing!
That's their nose?
"You know their nose?" you say...
That's their nose?!
That's their nose
Wow!
Whale holes are their noses
We did it!
What kind of ending is this?!
I didn't know that was their nose
"You know they have their noses there" - You're amazing man!
You're too advanced!
4 hours 41 minutes after leaving NTV,
4 hours 41 minutes after starting
100 Trivia Accumulated!
They finally got 100 trivia!
He was so many steps ahead,
"You know their nose right?"
He was touching his back, I was so confused
That was impressive enough on it's own!
Why did you start with the thing about Dolphins and Whales?
Timed and Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband