First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai! Battle: let's cook somethin'
good with the ingredients inside the refrigerators!
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Endo Shozo
Tsukitei Hosei
So, what are we doing today?
Today we, who can't really cook... I mean we all actually cook
Yeah but we're not experts
Yeah, that's it
But it's not like you never cook, right?
Well, I mean... I actually cook a lot but...
Pick one, dude!
He feels like the cooking type
Do you cook at home?
Not that much but like... if you tell me "chop suey" I kind of understand it
Are you the one who cooks at home?
I'm not!
Rules are simple: you just have to cook up something good with what you have in the fridge
Each fridge has its own main content: beef, pork, chicken, fish ,and seafood, but you won't know which has which until you open each of them!
Hosei
Endo
Tanaka
Hamada
Matsumoto
They have drawn each number tile by lottery
Which type of dish will they be able to improvise with what they'll find in their own fridge?
Translation by Shion
Typeset by AleksP94
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
facebook.com/shionnotsukai
patreon.com/shionnotsukai
Our first challenger is Tanaka, who once learned Chinese cooking on a Gaki episode
Alright Tanaka, first off open up fridge number 4 and check its ingredients out
I'm opening it
His main is...
Woah! It's fish! I'm so glad it wasn't me!
I'm so glad
So Tanaka, the first thing you have to do is to think about what to make with them
Yeah, let's see...
Well, if I was him...
Ah, I got you, they're already good this way
What the hell, man!
But I mean... right?
The hell are you sayin'?
Alright... I made up my mind!
Alright, please tell us what have you decided
I'm gonna make a uh...
Using fish and uh... vegetables...
A sort of Chinese-cooking!
What the hell!
How?!
Are you dumb?!
It doesn't feel right, Tanaka
Your fridge is the least fit for it!
Note: bowl of rice with different toppings on top
Ok, I wanna make an original Chinese-styled donburi
So, with rice?
Yes
Let's start cooking!!
Alright
Does a Chinese-styled donburi actually exist?
I think so, yeah
But look, I mean it already looks good, after all it's the typical men's cooking, the problem is gonna be its taste, though...
Yeah, that's right
So that's how you cut it
You should at least know that
Are you for real, Endo?
How have you been cutting it?
I mean, that's obvious
Well, to be honest I never actually cut an onion in my life...
You're over 40 and you've never cut an onion in your life!?
Yeah, I never cut an onion before, I swear
Man, that's unbelievable
For now it's all pretty watchable, nothing feels strange
Agreed
Is it ok for him to fry those?
I mean, that's just potato starch​
Yeah that... that's alright
Is it?
He's gonna stir-fry them for sure, later
Those sounds alone are amazing
Yeah
It makes him feel professional
Oh, so he's putting them there
Maybe the fact he used potato starch​ could make up a nice coating for the dish
But I must say...
- It seems pretty tasty, right?   - Yeah
I have no idea what he's doing
Ah, he's pouring water on them
I think that this dish's base... has no flavor
It won't have any flavor
Note: Tanaka is pouring more potato starch​
That's a lot... are you kidding me?
Its taste...?
I mean, he poured so much water the flavor must be so dim
Yeah, of course
What is he pouring in now?
Soy sauce
That's saké
It would have been good if he did that before the potato starch
Why doing it after pouring it in?
What's that?
You can't mix em up!
He's pouring so much in, is it gonna be fine?
And so, how are the results for Tanaka's original seafood Chinese-donburi going to be?
Here goes my original Chinese-donburi
Here it is
Doesn't really make me wanna eat it...
It's a bit stagnant
If not it would have been good
But I must say
In terms of smell, it's pretty Chinese-ish
It smells good
Let's just eat it
Really, smells nice
Tastes like raw fish!
Tastes like raw fish?
Yeah, that flavor comes right at you
Also, this thing is incredibly sour
Eh? Is it sour? Mine doesn't have a flavor to begin with
Are you for real?
All I can taste is the sweetness of the onion
That's true
We have a rating system with 10 points at max, how should we rate this?
How much?
I was hoping for a 6
No way, no way
Don't talk nonsense
All I could taste was that onion's sweetness, so I'd say 1 point
My opinion
That's me
1 point?
From my point of view
He did it while having "Chinese cooking" on his mind and sort of had success in that
So I think it should at least be a... like, 2 or 3 or so
That's so gentle of you
I may be gentle, but this thing I just ate was way more gentle than me
Alright, how about 2 points then?
2 points? Man, 2 points...
Our next challenger is Hosei
And Hosei's main dish is...?
This is chicken meat
You can see I got some chicken wings here
I also have some leg meat
Note: thick starchy sauce made of kuzu powder, usually for udon
I think I'm gonna make a chicken with herbs covered in ankake
Ankake? He's just gonna use it to cover everything up!
Is it a donburi or what?
No, it's not it
Which is it then?
It's a single dish
Let's start cooking
I think this kind of dish fits Hosei's character pretty well
I don't think he's a guy who cooks that much...
Also, he said herbs
Didn't he?
He just washed his hands and he grabbed the meat again
What was his purpose?
He just wanted to show us he's doing something
To show us he's clean
I can totally see that
It feels like he's trying to remember what Tanaka did
Yeah, I feel like he's copying me
I didn't think his level would be this low
Is he gonna roll em up like that?
He placed it down
That ball hasn't been seasoned, I bet it has zero taste
Is he gonna pour em in eggs and fry em?
Are you kidding me? He needs bread flour
This...
Isn't safe to place in oil, right?
What is he...?
Well yeah, you need breacrumbs to do that
So, he covered it in eggs and in flour again
That poor chicken meat with no flavor
What's the point of those eggs?
He then covered the chicken wings and legs in wheat flour and beaten eggs and fried them
Woah woah, that's gonna lower its temperature so much!
How much are you expecting from the temperature of that oil?
While the chicken cooks, he makes the kuzu sauce
That's a lot
That's way too much!
Consommé and broth?
What's that?
Kuzu sauce, right?
This is gonna kill us all
What is he doing? Is not even moving
For real, what is he aiming at?
What the-?
No idea
That's bad
Is that water?
Really?
Is he planning to pour that on it?
This can't be good
He's 100% gonna pour it over the chicken
Come on, that's the stuff you use to glue back broken sliding doors
He hasn't cooked it yet, not that it changes anything
Some salt and pepper in...
Salt and pepper
He sprikled em inside it
He actually did it
What now?
It's salt, he said it
Isn't that too much?
That's too much
I mean, the chicken is tasteless
Ah so he did this... I see
Oh, he mixed them all up
I guess that's a sort of a sweet-and-sour pork, a sweet-and-sour chicken
Hosei goes for a taste test
Enough of this, we had enough
We don't want that
Why have you made such thing?
Curry powder
Are you kidding me?
He's tampering it
By sprinkling that
This guy is dangerous
This is a pretty damn crazy guy
And so, how are the results for Hosei's herbs and kuzu sauce chicken going to be?
Can you
Please start by opening your lid?
This is my deep-fried chicken with stir-fried vegetables
But you
You said "herbs", right?
Where are those herbs?
Well, there's curry, which is a spice of course
And I may wanted to use curry from the very beginning..?
He never made that promise before
First time hearing this
Yeah, that's not it
For now, let's taste Hosei's dish
What the hell is this lump of stuff?
This is so bland
Yeah
I don't even like how you try to cover everything up with curry
I think this is a zero
Yeah, that's it
Are you for real?
Yeah, it's no-vote
Are you kidding me?
Our next challenger is Endo
His main ingredients are shrimps, octopus, clams and other sea food
What will he try to make with them?
L-like an omelet rice...
Which on the inside has pa-- paella-styled seafood
That's what I want to present to you guys
I didn't understand
Isn't it just an already existing dish?
Yeah, the paella
But the paella is cooked with rice
He said "-styled", so it may not be the exact same thing
Can he make a paella? Oh, he's going for the rice
We know for sure he has to do the rice omelet first
Ah, like that?
All I have is seafood, so I'm tossing everything inside
Also the clams... can I take the clams?
Are those clams?
That's wrong, dude
So barbaric!
That's not how you do it
Are you kidding me?
He's an animal
Oh, he only took its innards
That's impressive
You put it like that, right?
Yeah, with the shell, they open up as you cook
He's a monkey, a monkey!
I can't break those
For real?!
This guy's incredible
You have to put em in with the shell for paella, yes?
Yes
But I really wanted to put em in
Give it up man
I'm borrowing this
For a while
He's spilling out salt
What should I do?
Isn't that worse than me?
If I don't take em out we can't eat em
If you heat em up they'll open, but...
It seems he doesn't know that
Sorry, I'm adding those
What's that?
And so, how are the results for Endo's paella-styled rice omelet going to be?
This is what I just made
Here, to describe it simply we can say it's an Ome-paella
You don't pour anything on it?
No well, if you want you can add soy sauce, simple sauce
Or ketchup
What the hell are you sayin'?!
I thought you wouldn't say it for once!
Who would pour it on that?
What? No way!
Are you ready?
I don't really want to eat it, I don't like its smell
It's not a paella, it's just "styled" after it
About its taste...
Not a strong first impression
Yeah, there's like no flavor at all around the rice
Yeah
It lacks flavor
But I mean, all you guys
Are talking while eating, so...
Doesn't it mean it doesn't taste that bad?
You know, if we have to compare this to what Yamazaki made before
I can eat this without a problem
So, talking about points...
I think it's between Yamazaki's and Tanaka's, so it's a 1
So, we have a zero, one and two, everything starts from now
Our next challenger is Matsumoto
Which will his main ingredients be?
Woah, it's beef
This is... huh?
There's a load of meat
Cow
What will you make?
A beef-burger katsu-don
"Beef-burger katsu-don"...?
Sounds pretty damn hard
I have a feeling I can make it
Alright, gotcha
Hamburger katsu-don...
Let's start cooking, then
This is minced meat, yeah? I'm gonna make some balls
Like this
Then I'm going to fiddle with it
At this point I guess I could also add some onion in it, but...
Is that the right way to do it? I don't know
It's fine
Oh, ok
But man, really
The other guys were the worst
I never thought I'd be in the same show with people who don't know when to use potato starch
It's so shameful
I'm gonna cut the onion in big chunks
So you can feel it as you chew
Pretty big
Isn't that too much?
Is it gonna be ok?
I really don't know that myself
His face changed a bit, is he feeling a bit panicked?
Well, I don't know how this will turn out
But this is fine
Next up is the soup
First some broth
note: oyakodon is a bowl of rice, chicken and eggs
If I remember correctly for an Oyako-don you use water, soy sauce, japanese broth and mirin or such
You're pouring so much, you sure it's ok?
Yeah, yeah, don't worry about it
This is no good
He says it's fine
I'll also pour water
I don't have enough soy sauce
Eh? You really sure that's not too much?
This can't be good for the body!
Alright, in the meanwhile I'll fry this
Should we trust him?
While it fries I wanna make the soup
Let's pour some mirin
I see, so that's how he's doing it
What is he doing?
That's a egg-soup, isn't it?
But he didn't say that before
And so, how are the results for Matsumoto's beef-burger katsu-don going to be?
Let me say this: I never made this before
So it's your first time?
I just made it thinking about how it will turn out
And that's how it looks like
Looks yummy
It looks really tasty
It's my minced-beef katsu-don
I can't deny it smells delicious
Yeah, it surely smells good
Ok guys, eat up
Alright
Let's eat
It smells good, no complaints on that
It smells nice
This is frickin' delicious!!
It tastes a bit too strong
Yeah, it's kind of spicy
Alright but this is good, isn't it?!
But it's spicy
It's the soy sauce
Yeah that's it
Curry?
Soy sauce
But
Yeah?
The meat is pretty good too
Can I get a refill?
This was really good, I swear
It has a strong flavor but it's good
The soup was a bit too strong
So Endo, how many point do you think it's worth?
Around 3!
Endo, you're not funny
My head started to hurt
Who cares, come on! Be realistic
Isn't a 3 or a 4 good enough?
Yeah, 3 to me
3 should be fine
Our last challenger is Hamada
And of course his main ingredients are...
Well, of course is that
He's left with a good one
No one went for a noodle-based dish, should I do it?
You sure?
Yeah but what? Pasta?
There's this here and it can do it too but maybe this
Ah! Pasta!
You sure you're ok with that?
The pasta-based dish Hamada chose to do is...?
All-sort-of
Ingredients pas---
Carbonara
Isn't that a normal carbonara?
I mean, there's also milk here, I can totally pour it inside my carbonara
Counting on you
Alright
It's passing through
The knife is passing through
Is he cutting it?
He's not cutting it at all, it just feels as if he's doing it
His face alone is amazing
Only his face is praiseworthy
Which style is this?!
This feels so wrong
I never saw that way of cutting onions before
I heard everything's better with some garlic
And here he goes again, what the hell?
He's just passing it over it
He's stabbing it
Maybe he can't just see
Oh, that's possible
Is that how it is?
This could work if what you're cutting are small bones
With a pike or such
But that's not a pike, doesn't make sense
He should have peeled em off first
I should cut em together
In a bundle
I can't make em stay still
What's the point of this?
Here he goes
It's pike-cooking
That's his own style
The hell?
Next up, he cuts up the enoki mushroom
Maybe I don't need this bit
Huh?!
What is he doing?
I think he may be actually good with a pike
He's going for it
It's not really full of ingredients
It's definitely not so much
And feels tasteless
This is sad
Let's keep on cooking this
It's becoming all black!
This isn't good for the body!
Let's do this, shall we?
Here goes
What are you...?
He's pouring milk on it
I don't wanna eat that...
Is he gonna...?
Stop!
Please don't do it
He can't just do that
Yeah...
How is Hamada's special all-sort-of-ingredients carbonara going to be?
That was... one hell of a ride
Also you said "lots of veggies" when you started...
Where did that promise go to?
There are veggies here
You see? Onions...
Shimeji mushrooms, bell peppers...
Why did you cut the enoki mushrooms?
You should have put it entirely
You're all fussing around, just eat this
I think my tastebuds will die
He cut em in such small parts...
There's also a refreshing tomato here
They're stuck
It's all becoming stiff
It's not stiff at all
Enough of this
Let's skip this
It feels off
He only goes to good restaurants
That's why
Let's eat
Eat the spaghetti and the tomato, you'll feel refreshed
'Cause it's rich
Let's eat
Alright
The milk made it thick
This is horrible
What the hell is this?
This is not edible
What's this? What's this taste?
Is it carpet-flavored?
Tanaka tell him which is the most basic thing in a carbonara
Translation by: Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
It's eggs and cheese
You have to blend em together and make a cream
I put em in
Typesetting by: Aleksp94
No, you didn't
That's what makes it like this
find more at: shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
It's dangerous
So, its score?
I think this hits rock bottom
like my page: facebook.com/shionnotsukai
Eh?! Worse than Yama-chan?!
This is a skull mark
support my content on: ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai or patreon.com/shionnotsukai
Shit, it was the egg in the end...
I should have put it in
You admit it?
Come on
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TWITTER.COM/FGRNDNOISES
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT FAN-TRANSLATION MADE BY A FAN FOR OTHER FANS. ALL COPYRIGHT ARE RESERVED TO THEIR RESPECTIVE OWNERS.
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
SPECIAL THANKS TO ALEKSP94 FOR TYPESETTING THIS EPISODE!!