First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai
Risk it all on one bite and fight for a 100'000 yen prize
Kiki mentsuyu (noodle soup base)
He said 100'000 yen, but I think 20 millions would be better
Please do it, I'd love to
I'm going for it
Ok, if you get it, we'll give you 20 millions
Are you kidding me?!
You gotta promise that!
Rules are pretty simple
You just have to find the mentsuyu you tasted among the 10 types
Get it right and you'll earn 100'000 yen: who's going to win?
Translation & editing:
Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
mattee53
IRL friend who lives
in a forest
Typeset:
Quality Check:
more content @ shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Our first challenger is Hosei
Please be nice to me!
They chose the industry leader
"Tsuyu no moto", by Ninben
Its dense and delicate bonito taste
Makes for an excellent product
You can also add wasabi
He ate a lot
How is it?
Amazing, I love this salty taste
I mean, it's mostly soy sauce...
"Salty taste"?
There's more if you wanna go for another slurp
Give me those
Let me borrow your chopsticks
Give him those goddamn chopsticks
He's 51 years old, you know...
Let me say this first
You haven't been nice at all
Which one of us?
All of you!!
How come?
I was clearly suggesting you to pick this one
But I can tell it wasn't this
Why don't you think it's that?
He's right
Let me try this first
Why that...?
Yeah, he could be wrong
It could be
Please say the product's name
Its name is...
Akomeya... toukyuu...
Are you sure?
It says "soy milk"
He's right, "Akomeya Tokyu"
It's "Tokyo", actually
What's going on?
He got it wrong too
It's "Akomeya Tokyo"
And he came here just to correct me
See? It's different
Its smell?
Yeah, it's not close at all, you haven't been nice
But you can't know for sure
You could be wrong
It's completely different
What I ate wasn't soy milk mentsuyu ♪
Correct!!
No one is gonna laugh at it...
Can I go for "Ago-dashi"?
Oh, a different one
It became popular, lately
It smells so different
I'm glad I ate that
He's eating a lot
What I ate wasn't ago-dashi tsuyu ♪
Correct!!
You're laughing a lot, aren't you?
It's 'cause the staff isn't laughing at all
[muffled "x isn't what I ate"]
Aside from his comedy, his sense of taste is in good shape
And before he realized it, he completed 3 in a row!
I think the one I ate was somehow strong
I think it means it has a high salt content
Can I try this one?
Go for it, permanent boy
How did he call that? Design permanent?
I don't know how to call that
That's new
How about trying it with soumen?
You're right
Oh crap...
Really?
Did you really pick one from the center?
That's dirty, man
I don't think so
But man, it tastes the same
I can't just throw this away
But you said it wasn't "ago-dashi", didn't you?
Yes but I meant it was not that  ago-dashi
But I'm sure is this  ago-dashi
Alright, here goes nothing
Should I go for this one...?
What do you mean?
I'm asking you if I win by bringing this here
I swear today so far you have 0 laugh points
That's why
That's why I can't lose this game
At least, huh?
I feel you
WATCH ME GOOOOOO!!
Alright let's do this, I'm tired of staying behind that table
The one I drank...
"Drank"...?
Was Ago-dashi by Mitsukan!
Incorrect!!
Are you kidding me?
He's a mess today...
Your tongue is rotting away!
You expired comedian!
It was this, Ninben's tsuyu-no-moto
It was that
It's less intense than that one
Woah... it's this one!
Please don't say that
The next contestant is Tanaka
This one...
They have chosen
"Koi-dashi Hontsuyu", by Kikkoman
Its strong flavor goes well as mentsuyu
And it's also excellent for seasoning
Woah, wait a minute
Is it good?
Yeah, it's good
This is bonito
I know
Alright, I'm ready
Let me take this first
Oh! He looked!
You've seen it!!
I didn't see anything
This will cost you a penalty
I din't see it
You've just seen it?
You've clearly seen it
You saw it!
Tanaka, you've seen it, didn't you?
I did
Why?
Why did you look at it?
Wait
Wait, what should we do now?
If he gets it right, he'll get no prize money
Wait a minute, what's my motivation then?!
Let's make it 10'000 yen
It's not a good thing to lie
I thought Yoshimoto employees learned that last summer
Why haven't you learned that?
Yeah, you haven't studied enough!
Now you know for sure it's not a soy-milk based one
It's not this, I know
Of course you know
He said "I didn't" when he clearly saw it...
Yeah...
With such a straight face too
He seemed so honest about it
It really felt like it
I don't know which is it, but by the circumstances I can narrow it down to 2
But I really don't know which is it
That's because you saw it
I mean...
He looked at it from a 6cm distance!
The moment Tanaka stole a glance
That's not it, it was just a moment
But you know by now how it looks
Let me reenact how it went
Not convincing
But it's still something
It was way closer
Today's episode is crazy
Wrong
Are you talking about its taste?
Or maybe about its looks?
I'm sure this one's not it
Alright, the one I ate was not Iwate's local "Old shop tsuyu"
Correct!!
It's from Sasacho brewery, isn't it?
Why did he took the eyemask away so early?
Real strong tsuyu from Kikoman, here I go
I think we all ate this one at least once in our life
Hmm?
Compared to the other I just had, this is way closer
How about its looks?
It's close
He just confessed
Oh boy...
Wait a moment...
I think it's this one
The one I just ate
It's really this one, I'm going for it
Ok
Is it really true that even if I get this right
I won't get even one cent?
Well yes, can't be helped
Ok, let me just get this right first, we'll discuss it later
The one I ate was Kikoman's "real strong tsuyu"!
Correct!!
He looked at it, after all
He's not really happy about it, look at him
What is he thinking about?
They didn't give him anything
They just danced for him
He didn't seem so happy about it
Thank you so much, it was fun playing
I had fun
You could have actually got it right
I was so positive I could make it today
Our third challenger is Hamada
You gotta keep in mind Hamada is dumb
For him, they chose Mujirushi's Mentsuyu
It's made of a mix of frigate tuna and bonito
An excellent tsuyu with a refined taste
He's not saying anything
What a mouthful
Such a graceful way to eat
How is it?
I guess it's kind of thick
I think
It's like the broth you use for tenzaru soba
No one asked you
I'm pretty sure it had bonito in it
This one has shiitake mushrooms, it's not it
Could be this ago-dashi here, I don't know
It's a regular bonito broth
Uhhh, bonito broth
Wait
It doesn't seem thick enough, though...
If you told me it's this one, I'd agree
Huh?
He's stuck
- This is uncommon
Yeah, he's in trouble already
See, I ate a lot of these before
And now I narrowed them down to bonito-flavored ones only
And there are only these two left, so
I'm gonna taste real quick this other one too
You can't
For how long have we been doing this?
- 42 times
It's our 42nd round, man
Why bringing up bonito broth now?
Of course it's going to come out
I mean, it's mentsuyu, it's not unusual it's bonito-flavored
Am I allowed to smell it?
- No
You can't
He's eating a lot
This one's really close
Isn't it good?
We can't say anything
I'm not sure about its saltiness
Alright, I'm sticking to my first guess
Shouldn't I?
He's gonna mess up his neck
I guess our viewers just want me to hurry up
The one I ate...
Is Yamaki's mentsuyu
Incorrect!!
That was quick!
Way too quick
You got it wrong
Here he comes
Not only your face is hideous, your taste buds too!
He's saying pretty awful things
He hit really hard
Some fragments flew away
My ass hurts already...
Which was it?
You were close
You think so?
- In a way, yeah
That's right
In a way
It was Mujirushi's mentsuyu
You sure?
He has no confidence whatsoever
Alright, I'm ready
Get ready, Endo
The one they chose for Endo
Is Sasacho Brewery's tsuyu, from Iwate prefecture
Its matured broth and soy sauce make it shine
A high class mentsuyu
This is thick
Its smell?
Do you usually eat mentsuyu?
Yeah
I eat it a lot when it's summer
Usually for lunch
I really don't think of it as something you eat at night
It's more something you enjoy with your family
What does your wife think?
She likes it too---
Hurry up already!!
I think I'm going to find it by chance
I want to try the shiitake one
Just to see how different it is
He wants more screentime
He doesn't get much of it
He just wants to appear more
Nope, not this one
That's his biggest flaw
The one I ate is not Yamae's shiitake flavored tsuyu
Correct!!
That was an easy one
I was pretty sure about it
Now you're clear
I think I'm going to try the soy milk one, just in case...
He can't just do that, come on
I think it's essential he has the will to venture
But it's just as Yamazaki said
He already knows that's not it
The one I ate is not Akomeya Tokyo's----
Correct!!
Can he say that?
You surprised me with that
Ok, here I go
So, the ones you haven't chose yet are these 5
But the one I ate was bonito flavored, pretty simple
I don't think it had konbu kelp nor it was ago, it had bonito
This one is also the most expensive
It must be the Isetan one, or the Mitsukoshi
Or the Kinokuniya, I'm going with this
Here comes my prejudice kickin' in, at last...
Mmh? Prejudice?
- At last...?
"Prejudice kicked in"...?
I swear the saltiness of the noodles is really close
The noodles have nothing to do with it
How should I say it? The chemical reaction from when I put 'em in...
I don't think there's any chemical reaction involved
You're just putting it in your mouth
I just have to keep on looking for the right bonito broth...
Wrong!
The one I ate isn't Sasacho brewery's tsuyu
Incorrect!!
Why didn't you go for it?
No way, dude
You were so close
Dontcha dare doin' another food report with Tsubokura again!
That was the worst one
What a waste
We all failed so far, so you have to get it right, Matsumoto
Why do I have to
Be put under pressure all the times?
I know it's something I should say aloud, but...
Can we fake my victory?
What?!
Just pick that soy milk tsuyu for me
Maybe we should
- Or that other one
The last challenger is Matsumoto
Just pick that white one on the table's edge
They picked this one to outsmart him
It's the soy milk tsuyu Matsumoto requested before
This is our only soy milk flavored tsuyu
It's easy to figure this one out, but will he?
I must say, it's not as clear to me as I thought it would be
This is one of the those with ago? Possibly?
It's considerably watery
Mh? You sure you stored this properly?!
Oi, you bastards!!
You're so noisy
It's sweet
The first thing that came to my mind is the ago broth
Because I haven't really ate it before
So I think the possibilities it's ago broth are high
It's not this one right? Or did you actually choose it?
Shoul I just go for it?
You can at least reply to me, you know
I just asked if I should go for it, answer me
It's 'cause this is our last round, you know
I think I should start from here to get it right, right?
Can this really be chosen as the last one?
Completely wrong
Completely wrong, I can do this
Totally wrong, what I ate was not Kikoman's strong tsuyu broth
Correct!!
Alright, I was really sure about that one
It must be the ago broth, after all
Sorry, when I said "ago" I looked at you, Tanaka
"ago" (type of broth) in japanese also means "chin"
No offense taken
Matsumoto is leaving the ago broth ones for last
And proceeds without risks
Why does it have to take this long to ring?
Alright, it's time to try this one, isn't it?
I just have to
I'm trying this
I didn't think this...
Oh no
My memories are gradually fading away
Holy crap
This is pretty close
Did you actually do it?
That's not it, right?
You can talk, you know
This is weird
Wait a second
I never had ago broth before
So I have no idea
Maybe this is not it
But if I get past this one, I finally enter the ago broth zone
Right?
This feels like bullying, really
No way
It's not like that, I swear
rectangle
Other episodes on shionnotsukai you may have missed:
ABSOLUTELY TASTY TAPIOCA
LIMITS - OMURICE
LET'S PLAY NOSTALGIC ARCADE GAMES
LIMITS - HIYASHI-CHUUKA
BANANAMAN SHITARA'S SHICHI-HENGE
BANANAMAN HIMURA'S SHICHI-HENGE
BURNING HOT TENNIS LESSON
REFRIGERATOR BATTLE
SHOJI MURAKAMI'S MICHAEL JACSKON CLASSROOM
and many many more
(how to make bubble tea even more useless)
(subs by TofuPanda)
(time slip from when the world was a nice place to live in)
(Yamazaki being racist)
(Man showing his d*ck to young ladies)
(Missed tip-tap master)
(Endo becomes gay... again)
(Do not try this at home)
(The king of pop would be so proud)
I'm going
The one I ate wasn't Akomeya Tokyo's soy milk mentsuyu, please!
Incorrect!
You friggin' did it!!
He did
So you really did this for me
Thank you!!
You're really good friends after all!
You're really the best guys, I swear!
At least get it right!
"Can we fake my victory?"
Wait a minute guys, I'm in a state of shock
Quit the proteins
And start drinking mentsuyu!
You thought it was ago tsuyu
Yeah I was sure about it
If only you would have talked to me some more!
You really bullied me here, giving me that cold attitude and everything
No way
I'm dead serious
Final thoughts?
You're really good guys, friends are the best!
So friggin' loud
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TWITTER.COM/FGRNDNOISES
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
SPECIAL THANKS TO MATTEE53 FOR TYPESETTING THIS EPISODE!!
(QC a cura di un uomo che ha già visto sto episodio in anteprima, quindi perché lo stai rivedendo? eh? perché? scherzo tvb)
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT FAN-TRANSLATION MADE BY A FAN FOR OTHER FANS. ALL COPYRIGHT ARE RESERVED TO THEIR RESPECTIVE OWNERS.