TPF
Gaki Dressing Room
In the Gaki no Tsukai dressing room...
Two particular members are missing...
Cocorico
Tanaka Naoki
Endo Shozo
Yamazaki Hosei
Huh?
Matsumoto and Hamada aren't here..
That's true
Have you seen them?
No we haven't seen them either
Gooood morning
Good morning
Good morning!
Good morning, indeed
It's the rainy season
The rainy seasons are here again this year
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
However
We always seem to expect a lot of rain
But in some years weirdly,
we get years where we barely get any rain, so I've heard
Oh, really?
I've heard that too
So...
LET'S GO
Hamada isn't here today
No, he isn't
Hamada's trying to gather everyone..
Hamada-san is?
License
Kazuhiro Fujiwara
Takafumi Inomoto
So...
...to keep it short...
He wants to win fights only with 'Nanyanen'
I'm not quite sure what you mean...
Only words?
For example, during the times of late night music programs
late night music programs...
I see
you don't feel like losing
Using only "Nanyanen"
He wants to overwhelm his opponents using only that line
When he told this to me
He seemed very adamant about it
I'm not sure about that
Is there a purpose to all this?
Is he here today?
Yes, he is
He has descended upon us
descended?
Yes, he has
I guess we should head there then
Yes
Please
"I haven't taken in any carbs"
is what he said
I don't think that's related to what he's doing
Overwhelm the competition using a single phrase
Testing his greatest asset to fight them
Using only the single phrase "Nanyanen" to combat his opponents
testing the true potential of his abilities
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents:
Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Translator:
Typesetter & Proofreader:
Tako
Otviss
**We also have Facebook and Twitter.**
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
__________________________________________________________________
If you ever see this video being distributed online but not by us, keep in mind that on Youtube
individuals may make money off of sharing fansubs like this that are not their own. Please go back and
support the original creators. Fansubbing is voluntary and is not meant to generate profit. You can
download episodes on our website instead. Thanks for watching!
He might be a bit nervous
In this challenge, there are only two outcomes so
There's a lot on the line
Go in with a warm smile
and say "Good Morning" to him
Yes
Alright, let's go
Good morning
Good morning!
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Good morning!
So you heard?
Yes
We did hear about it but...
to be honest, we don't quite understand
Well, it's not that there's difficulty understanding
but it's really just what it is
"Nanyanen" for me...
Back in our more prime years
losing was never an option
In our most prime years
that is
So...
What's wrong Hamada-san?
He's charged
He's very charged right now
The challenge only allows
for the saying "nanyanen"
He must be very charged
When Hamada is wearing chino pants he's usually this charged
What?
...and he's wearing chinos
He does seem very pent-up
So I think...
his opponents are probably
ready for him at the studio
So we already have the opponents ready?
Yes, they're in the studio on stand-by
Some are also around the same age as him
Wow, amazing!
This has to be a pretty big group
This studio's big, too
This is exciting
Oh, there are the opponents in the same age as Hamada
50 people are in the studio as his opponents
50 People varying from ages 20~80 are on standby as opponents
Rules
Basically,
We have people of varying types
Men and women?
Yes both genders
All sorts of people
Hamada must go against the group in a verbal battle using only "nandeyanen"
Varying in occupations, ages and backgrounds
and Hamada using only "Nandeyanen" to defeat all of them
Only "Nandeyanen"
Alright let's go!
We have to watch closely
So many people
There is
They're all looking at us
Just staring
Such intense stares
I'll take anyone
All age groups are represented
Even elders
This guy looks like he can put up a fight but...
Nanyanen?
Huh?
Supermarket Worker (Age 37)
Nanyanen?
Huh? Nanyanen?
Nani?
Nanya?
Nanyanen?
ALL RIGHT
HAMADA WINS
Okay
What happened?
I'm not sure what just occurred
He fainted
He's down
How did he go down?
Well he's already out
The power
had a "flash down"
Just consuming him
His head just went blank
That took a little too long...
For my first, I thought I'd do better
So that's what it's like
So yeah
I'd like to go faster next time
It just seemed so quick already though
But he was young
I guess the young ones can fight
Being 37 and all
I can probably go faster with the older ones...
That's true
I think I can do better
I've seen this baldy before
Who?
Nanyanen?
What do you want?
Apartment Landlord (Age 79)
Huh?
What's so funny?
Punk
Nanyanen?
What the hell do you mean nanyanen?
What do you want from me?
Nanyanen?
What's so nanyanen?
Kid
Little brat
Hey
Huh?
Nanyanen?
I'll beat you little punk
Huh?
NANYANEEEN
ALL RIGHT
HAMADA WINS
I'll beat you little punk
NANYANEEEN
Wow
That was pretty brutal
Very powerful
I should've ended that a little sooner
Was it that dangerous?
It seemed very brutal
It was pretty strong
His tongue was out
That's a bad sign
Dangerous
He was looking for a beating
He did
He was really
trying to get him to break the rules
but he had just enough restraint
To stick with his one phrase
That was some solid defense by Hamada
Very restrained
So it takes some time?
Should I go faster?
Well I don't think time is too big of an issue
If possible
We also have to consider
not taking up too much air time
So we should try going faster?
Perhaps
I guess I can see which ones I can take out quickly
He might be
silent
There's a nervous tension
He's got the height
He's got the height on him
That's an advantage
He's pretty tall
Also pretty young
Nanyanen?
Restaurant Worker (Age 35)
What's this about?
Saying nothing but nanyanen?
Huh?
Nanyanen!
Eh?
What's the problem?
Nanyanen?
What is it?
DONE
HAMADA WINS
That was very quick
I didn't expect it to be so fast
Who?
Not even a chance
He's out of his level
Can you tell just by his looks?
That wasn't even fair
He seemed very nervous
I guess you can tell
Totally different league...
Oh, okay
Nanyanen?
Pastry Worker (Age 30)
30 is pretty young, I think
Nanyanen?
What is the matter?
What is it?
Nanyanen?
What is your problem, sir?
Whats the..
Nanyanen?
Nanya?
What
What's the..
Nanyanen?
OKAY
HAMADA WINS
So quick!
That might've been a new record
His head is tilted
That was crazy
Well
He was a bit of an amateur
This wasn't that fair either
It almost felt bad kind of watching him
Since there are all sorts of people
Right
Special One-Shot Nanyanen Move
The Special One-Shot Move of "Nanyanen"
The pressure rises
as Hamada continues to defeat his opponents one by one
Hamada continues to defeat his opponents one by one despite the arising pressure
Dental Hygienist (Age 40)
Even against dental hygienists
Auto Repairman (Age 60)
and against calloused auto repairmen
Six victories unchallenged
Now taking 6 wins unharmed and unchallenged
If you want me to take anyone on here
You can just tell me
Really?
Taking anyone here...
If I keep choosing my opponents
People might call me out for only choosing
the opponents that are "easy" to me
I don't mind you guys choosing at all
Just look around
Okay...
Seems like there are a lot of dads
Very stern looking people
Scary
Truly
That is certain
Tatsuya Tokudaiji
Occupation:
Imported Good Shop Manager
Relationship Status:
Single Independent
Just looks really scary
It's no problem
Are you sure?
I can definitely win this
Yeah
His expression is pretty intimidating
Him, right?
Yes
Nanyanen?
Imported Goods Shop Manager (Age 64)
Nanyanen
He's strong
Nanyanen?
Nanyanen!
Nanyanen?!
Nanyanen...
Yup
HAMADA WINS
It's..over?
It's over?
Yeah
Was there a deciding blow?
He couldn't stand
His knees with his feet were..
So that can lose you the fight also
He was surprisingly weaker than we thought
Nanyanen?
Nanyanen...
Yup
An anxious challenger slips down mid-fight
In the heat of the match, the challenger slips down
The referee calls a win for Hamada
With the referee's call, Hamada is declared winner
That was a quick match
I didn't know technical wins were possible
Look at that person
Who?
The person on the very right
Tamai-san
Daishiro Tamai
Occupation:
Part-time Post Office
Relationship Status:
Married
You guys are the same age group
The same age group
Nanyanen?
What
Part-Time Post Office (Age 47)
Who are you?
HAMADA WINS
Wow
Within seconds
It feels like he wasn't able to finish what he was saying...
He didn't really get to finish..
That was just him
His mouthpiece was coming out
Amazing
Everyone kinda looks different now
Was that okay?
Yeah, it's fine
Huh?
He just keeps winning
I'm sure
We have some familiar faces here
Yoshinobu Nakamura
Occupation:
Producer
Family:
Wife & one daughter
Same age group!
Even the same age!
He is the same age!
Who're you talking about?
The man over there
Now?
Well..
It would be interesting to watch, I think
I can do this
Thank you
Nanyanen?
What is the matter?
Television Program Producer (Age 49)
Nanyanen?
May I help you?
He's scared
Nanyanen?
May I help you?
Nanya?
So close
He might fall over
Nanya?
How may I help you?
Nanyanen?
Nanyanen?!
He's definitely freaking out
NANYANEN
Nanyanen?
He could fall over any minute
He's also shaking
May I help you?
Nanya?
NANYANEN
May I help you?
How may...
I help you?
NANYANEN
OKAY
HAMADA WINS
Now?
Yep, it's over
He's gone
Gone?
Hold on, you guys
Saying stuff like "He's shaking"
Don't say that
That might not be the most well-mannered thing to say
I know it's your first time experiencing this...
but just remember
Don't try to add commentary on the situation of the opponent
I'm sure you guys were aware of this
You could tell just by watching
Yeah
Let me take a break
That was pretty tiring
You said something too, right?
Yeah, I did
I need Matsumoto
to explain this better for you guys
That was...
Yes
We apologize
...Unacceptable
They're just trying to enjoy it
You can't do that
It's not all about
you guys enjoying the fights
That's not the purpose of all this
I knew he was shaking
And when I hear that from behind
I'm very sorry for that
This is our first time
We didn't completely understand the situation
DON'T TALK ABOUT THE SITUATION!!
I truly apologize
That's the last thing you want to do
I'm sorry
Please, give us one more chance
Alright then let's go
Thank you so much
This is a big deal
Up Next
New Star Appears!
He's using his talent to fight right now
Something about the way he's sitting
Sitting next to the lady, the man over there
Just something about him
Should we go?
Is that okay?
So just him?
I'm not really sure why he's sitting like that
So the guy just a little tilted
Could they just be a couple?
These two?
Just the way they're sitting seems a little off
I wonder why they're sitting at a place like this
Maybe to...
...catch his attention maybe
It's happening
Nanyanen?
Middle School Faculty (Age 51)
Huh?
What the hell do you want?!
Nanyanen?
Huh?
Let's go, man
Nanyanen?
Huh?
WHAT IS IT
NANYANEN
What the hell-
Nanya-
HAMADA WINS
Wow. That was very intense.
Is she coming for revenge?
Piano Instructor (Age 51)
Nanyanen?
Huh?
OK
HAMADA WINS
Wait. That's it?
All she said was "huh"
So they were a couple
Definitely
That was a lot
They were most likely very experienced
Those elderly people there...
They might not be in your same age group but...
The man in the white hair
He could be a real veteran in the game
He could be one of the oldest people here
Takei Tokuji
Occupation:
Retired
Family:
Independent
Probably the oldest
I see, people like this
He could be very strong
It's possible that he's actually very strong
True
who?
He seems strong
This could be a tough match
He's got his hand out
He seems to be ready
There seems to be an aura around him
Just something about him
Yeah
Nanyanen?
Unemployed (Age 82)
Alright
HAMADA WINS
Was that..
Who won?
I'm not sure who won
It was a little hard to follow
That must have been hard to understand
His eyes are still..
Alright
Okay
He hasn't fallen over
Alright
I don't think he fell over
He's just..
He hasn't fallen over
He's still awake
Huh?
You're really excited, Hamada-san
When there are matches like these
It's scary
That was really scary
It gets difficult sometimes
It's probably just a mulligan
Unemployed (Age 82)
Just a mulligan
Nanyanen?
Whakkan I help you widh?
Nyngh...
Nanyanen?
Alright
HAMADA WINS
He's down
Is he really down this time?
Well..
This guy's a little different...
His fighting style...
...Could just be different yes
Very different style
Maybe he's out from a different discipline
There were probably people from different events
There's also another guy in the same age group as me
Really?
Well if you really want to do this
then...
Try it out, Tanaka-san
Are you sure?
I..I'm not sure
We've never tried this
I have never done this in my life either
The man over there looks as ready as he can be
Yeah
76 years old so
Sato Masaichi
Occupation:
Plasterer
Family:
Wife, two daughters
& two grandchildren
He's older than your father, Tanaka
Yes, that's true
Alright
Plasterer (Age 76)
Nanyanen?
What!?
Okay
PLASTERER SATO WINS
He lost?
He flinched
He did jump back
You're so weak!
That was only one exchange
A very quick fight
Okay, sorry
Oh, he's back
How was it?
Do you remember losing?
You lost your memory?
Yes, I did
You really flinched
Nanyanen?
What!?
Flinch
A sucker punch from Plasterer Sato warps
Tanaka into a knockout
Plasterer Sato sucker punches Tanaka back
into a knockout
I'm sorry about that
Why is he still up when I already took him out
He's got a
high sense of freedom
He might not go down
Until you completely beat him
That's tough
Why did you say "that's tough"
when you're so close to the opponent?
Well..you know...
There are some parts I haven't taken care of yet...
Let's try it
I thought I'd beaten him by now
That's true
Yeah
Nanya?
That's tough
Why did you say "that's tough"
when you're so close to the opponent?
Well..you know...
There are some parts I haven't taken care of yet...
Wow
Let's try it
I thought I'd beaten him by now
He's really putting up a fight
Yeah
Unemployed (Age 82)
Nanyanen?
What is it?
So strong
How could he be this strong?
He's been taking quite the hits
Nanyanen?
How can I help you
He's an old master, an old master
An old master can truly put up a fight
What do you want?
UNEMPLOYED TAKEI WINS
Hamada-san!?
What!?
Oh no!
Hamada-san!?
EH!?
What happened!?
What about Hamada-san!?
Eh!?
This is too much
Amazing!
What just happened!?
It's scary because these things can happen
Really
Events like these CAN happen
Even he can't really tell if he's won or lost
This must mean that he knows what true power is
He didn't even intend to win
I didn't mean to hehehe
I didn't mean to?
I didn't mean to...
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
Overwhelmingly defeating his opponents one by one
Paving his own way to victory
However
His ambition to beat all 50 people was struck down
By the 82 year-old, Unemployed Takei
Hamada learns that there were no limits to the competition he faced