For the first time ever on Gaki No Tsukai
The wonderful Cafe "Garu" Tour!!
I have no idea what this is
Endo Shouzo
Hamada Masatoshi
Tsukitei Housei
Fujiwara Kazuhiro
Inomoto Takafumi
Tanaka Naoki
Honestly I have no idea what this is
You don't understand it huh?
No idea
We'll we still have to explain it
I want to come out on Yorutamori
Tl: Yorutamori is a talk show program
I can't understand why but
And can I just say one thing?
The one with the most basic outfit is
Hamada
Isn't it really basic!?
What the hell!
Seriously!
You look really basic!
Well then Matsumoto
What do you think of these shoes?
Ah Tanaka's shoes?
What's wrong with my shoes!?
It's cut lemons!!
They sell those?
Yes, Yes they do!
Of course they do!
Did they just come out with these at Yoshimoto Goods?
I'm sorry but
You said you don't understand the rules
This isn't the time for free talk!!
This feel's like it's gonna be awful!
Rule's
You will recieve a Garu card with word's such as "to feel hot"
"to feel pain". Once in the cafe you must act it out
Arent there words like "to feel hot" "to feel pain"
Everyone will get one of these card's and act it out in a cafe
Act it out?
That's right
When you mean "act" you mean completely?
Like over reacting
We'll trust you to do what you'd like
Shouldn't Tanaka be aware of Kouki Mitani?
The mail came!!
Kiki Green Tea
"Today's drama wasn't that good!"
Wasn't good!?
It wasn't good!? You put a lot into it!
Coincidentally, for this episode
When you enter the Cafe
The maid will enter and then
Once the maid delivers the coffee and bow's you start
Rules
We'll determine who did it the best
And decide who was the worst
Well, who's deciding it?
Everyone is
Finally, After a discussion the worst and best will be chosen
Rules
Everyone decides?
You'll decide between everyone who's the worst
Why the hell can't it be decided by one person?
Well
Who would decide?
Me!
"Me!"?
Presented by DCSubs
Gaki No Tsukai #1255 -The Wonderful "Garu" Tour
www.gaki-no-tsukai.com
www.reddit.com/r/GakiNoTsukai
Acting according to the topic
The wonderful "Garu" Tour!
Acting out a "Garu" at the Cafe
The Wonderful Cafe "Garu" Tour!
The Wonderful Cafe "Garu" Tour
Narrator
This cafe is the stage they will act on
Each person pull's out 1 "Garu" card each
Before that however, they must pick out their "Garu" card
Starting from Tanaka!
Yes!
Would you show us your card!
"To feel scared"
"To feel scared"!
Feel Scared
That's not that bad
Look Hamada
For this super ham actor this...
Feel Embarassed
To feel embarassed!
This one is bad huh!
Now Hamada
Pride...
To feel prideful
To feel prideful!
Ah! Prideful!
What the hell!!
That's pretty bad huh!
Seem's that way
Now you Matsumoto!
To feel sleepy
Feel Sleepy
Now Housei!
To feel hot!
Feel Hot
Unexpectedly It's gonna be hard to bring out that distinction
Now that the 5 have all picked out their cards
In Nervousness and Uneasiness
They push forward into the Cafe
So where are we sitting
Tanaka
Hamada
Housei
Matsumoto
Endo
Embarrassed
Prideful
Hot
Sleepy
Scared
There's hot towels and camera's where we have to sit
Sit wherever
Well I don't really mind where
Yea it doesn't matter
Then you sit there Tanaka
Got it
It feel's like
It's not gonna be easy
The atmosphere and all
Maid
Hip Shaking Old Lady
Don't drop those sprinkles
There's like confetti in her hair
"Garu" Start!
I want this!
It's ice coffee right?
There isn't enough cream
"Cream" you said?
It's fresh
"Fresh"....
Hamada
Aren't you putting in a little too much?
"Too much"?
Isn't it a little too much?
It's fine with this much
Please don't look this way!!
What's the temperature?
What temperature?
Like 19 degrees?
It's so hot!!
Huh?
Are you sure you should be doing that?
It's so shallow!!
Is it normally this shallow?
Look at this!
I found something amazing!
Look the syrup is really shallow!
Please stop it!
If the employee's hear you....
Hamada.. The syrup...
Please stop!
He's already sleeping!!
What did they put in this
Please stop it!
It's so shallow!!
Have you ever seen it so shallow?
I've never seen it this shallow!
Housei!
Cmon, Let's stop
Cmon Housei
This shallow!
Endo! Look at it!
It's so shallow!
Hamada!
Please don't show me!
If the employee's hear you
They'll be really upset!
I said he's already sleeping!!
It's so hot!
It's crazy hot
"Garu" Complete
Good work!
What did you think?
This guy was weird!
No No No!
Matsumoto huh
Matsumoto
To feel sleepy
Weren't you just sleeping?
That wasn't "to feel sleepy"
It's "to feel"
Before that
The one that was the worst
is this one!
What the hell!
I had no idea what you were doing!
Hamada
Prideful
I was saying that I found this
I've never seen
Shallow?
Syrup this shallow before!!
You and you were fine!
But you!
You were awful too!!
It's "to feel sleepy"!!
I was frequently waking up!
But was your card "to feel like waking up"?
Your wrong!
Even though it's the first Cafe have you decided?
Who was the worst?
You ask us!
Was Tanaka the worst one?
Were voting on the worst huh?
The one who did their "Garu" the worst!
Raise your hand
Well, He wasn't the worst
0 Votes
Your safe
Those who thought Matsumoto was the worst raise your hand
3 Votes
3 votes huh!?
That's terrible you shouldn't put me on the bottom of the list!
Well, Let's continue
Who think's Housei was the worst?
0 Votes
Not the worst huh?
Well then who thought Hamada was the worst?
Of course!
2 votes?
Of course
I tried to do it!
So who thought Endo was the worst?
0 Votes
That's suspicious
If you were part of it who would you pick?
Me?
Who was the worst?
Endo then!
Your lying!
Seriously why!?
He was the worst?
Why'd you say that?
Well compared to everyone else
Your's was the easiest challenge
I thought that was the biggest point
Everyone was challenging each other!
This is the first time I've seen this!
Were being absurdly stretched by Inomoto!!
Are you serious Inomoto!?
What about you Fujiwara
Me?
Hamada
You agree huh
I couldn't understand
It was this!
what you were prideful about
I know that but
Why were you prideful
about the Syrup's Shallowness?
There was no pride from Hamada huh
Well, Yea.
Hamada isn't the syrup
Well everyone shall we go to the second building?
Here after they go to the next stage
The second Cafe
Picking out new "Garu" card's
Sure enough, The five's pick's are
This one!
Let's start from Tanaka
Please show us!
"To feel cold"
Feel Cold
There was this "Garu" card huh?
Alright Endo!
"To want"
To want
This is perfect for Endo
Alright Hamada!
"Wanting to know"
"Want to know"
This is pretty different from before huh
It's like a Changeup in baseball
Now you Matsumoto
"To smell stink"
TL Note: Basically everything he smell's is awful
Well compared to last time...
Finally, Housei!
"To feel pain"
"To feel pain"!?
To feel pain
That's not too bad
The 5 have brand new "Garu" card's!
After some reflection and thought
They go into the second Cafe!
Endo
To Want
To feel pain
To smell stink
To feel cold
To want to know
Tanaka
Hamada
Housei
Matsumoto
That's definetely not Ice Coffee!
We didn't get a chance to order
"Garu" Start!
I drank this earlier though
Thank you~
If you don't need it Hamada,
Can I have it?
Well, I'm not gonna drink it but...
How long
has this store been here huh?
When was this place built?
It sting's~
Tanaka your not
drinking this right?
Give me this one too!
It sting's!
Is it just me or is it cold!
What's wrong?
When I took a drink of it I got really cold!
Ahh It stings!
In one drink!
What do you mean?
I took a sip and I felt really cold!
Explain it to me!
It stink's!
It stink's!!!
Ow ow ow!
It hurt's!
You! It hurt's!!
What's wrong!?
Please put on the heating!
Why are you cold!?
You smell!
You smell!!
Hamada stinks!
What do you mean stink!?
Uwa! You stink!
My partner stink's!!
Uwah! Endo you stink too!
Please let me!
What!?
C'mon please!
Why do you want this so bad?
Why!?
Can I please borrow your jacket!?
Does this smell?
Why!?
Why, Why!?
Does this smell?
Wait, Why!? Why!?
I don't understand this!
It stinks!
This
CCD camera stink's!
My stomach hurt's!
What is this?
Wait a second! Wait a second!
Does this CCD stink too!?
Excuse me!
Can I have this!
What's this light!?
Why
Did you turn on the heater!?
is this thing blinking!?
Why
I'M BEING SERIOUS IT HURT'S!!
WHAT'S WRONG?
YAMACHAN!
EEEEEH!?
What did you eat!?
OW!
OI! Wait a second what's going on!
Tanaka
Matsumoto
Housei
Hamada
Endo
"Garu" complete
Good Work!
Everyone was up on this one
This one was totally different than the first one!
How did you think about yourself this time Hamada?
Hamada
This time I did really good!
You really wanted to know thing's huh?
I really did want to learn!
I wanted to know about the camera
and I wanted to know about everything!
Well, When you were over there with Yamazaki what was that about?
Why does your stomach hurt?
What's wrong?
What did you eat?
Oh you were asking him that?
At that time I felt a sharp pain!
Rather than "to feel pain"
It just hurt!
Seriously? It hurt?
This time I thought it's was Housei who was "Wrong"
No, No wait!
Well actually
Everyone was really moving around!
Originally the pain was very small
And so I looked around!
Hamada really want's to know!
Tanaka looks pretty cold!
Endo really wanted things
Matsumoto
didn't really stand out
At last,
Matsumoto
I separated myself from the others
I was the only one alone on this stage!
I see!
For the time being should we just decide this by majority again?
Like the first cafe
Alright let's do it
Put your hand up if you thought Endo was the worst
2 votes
Alright then
Who thought that Housei was the worst?
I did sorry!
Your lying!
2 votes
Once again 2 votes
Well, the cameraman didn't really give you much attention as everything was going on
Even though you say that, I was alone till the end
I was alone on this stage
Matsumoto
Hamada
To smell
To want to know
0 Votes
And finally, Hamada and Matsumoto got 0 votes
Raise your hand if you thought Tanaka was the worst
1 vote
Well you weren't the worst
Tanaka
To feel cold
1 Vote
Coincidentally what would you two vote?
I see, Well...
Personally
Endo
Wait a second Inomoto
Matsumoto said it before but
Supposing there was a pattern change that I did but
If there was a pattern change it was you!
Are you being serious?
I'm being serious
I think
you went too far with it
Like you were taking other's things
What do you mean?
You were going as far
as to take other's things
I was really wondering what stunk
It was because
Endo's acting normally stinks!
I thought this smell and that smell was different!
It really was the difference between our acting
Alright, Let's go to the 3rd cafe!
While Endo is calm and composed
They go to the third and final cafe!
Well, You guy's know this is the last one
We leveled up the "Garu" cards!
The "Garu" topic has been leveled up!
Special Rule
So it's gotten harder
Finally, The leveled up "Garu" card's are!?
Starting from Tanaka!
"To want to be Antonio Inoki"
He can do what he want's right?
Want to be Antonio Inoki
Perform it however you want to
We're not bothered by the quality of it
Now Endo!
"To want to randomly notice your surrounding's"
So to notice thing's about the Cafe?
To want to randomly notice your surrounding's
This one's a little...
I want to see his tearful face from this
No, You won't see it!
Alright Hamada!
"To want to use Nori Tsukomi"
Tl: Nori Tsukomi is when the Tsukomi play's along with the Boke before pointing out the joke
To want to use Nori Tsukomi
THIS!?
It's gonna be difficult!
Matsumoto!
This is bad
"To want to be Mori Shinichi"
This one is perfect for Endo!
This one would of been good for me!
Now you Yamachan
"To want to praise the other member's"
I have to praise the other's cards?
Want to praise other member's
Yeah this one is pretty bad
And now the tour with the leveled up "Garu" card's!
Finally, The last Cafe!
So this place has this kind of feel to it
Matsumoto
"To want to
be Antonio Inoki"
use Nori Tsukomi"
"To want to
be Mori Shinichi"
"To want to notice
the surrounding's"
"To want to
praise the other's"
Hamada
Tanaka
Endo
Housei
This is definetely not Ice Coffee!
What's with this "bring your own" program
Garu Start
Aren't you putting
too much?
Isn't it too much?
That's really good!
Good evening
We entered there right?
Delicious!
Tanaka that's really good!
What floor is this!?
This is delicious huh!
This is underground right?
We entered from the first floor and went downstairs right?
That's good!
But it's a little different huh!
So we entered through here!
Amazing right!
This is so good!
Now I feel really good!
I drank Ice Coffe and
now I feel really good!!!
That's so good!
The best!!
It's good right?
GOOD!
HOUSEI!
Over there!
If you go to the back
It looks like it becomes a room!
Your right!
This is great~
♪ WINTER'S~
"Winter's ~" is good!
This is great~
This is impossible!
Did you create this loft?
This is impossible
I cant do anything beyond a doubt
No ones setting me up
♪ WINTER'S~
He's said that too much!!
Is it delicious?
Goood!
♪ WINTER'S~
Enough already!
Garu Complete!
This was impossible for me!
Everyone was amazing huh!
I brought it all out!
Hamada was horrible!
How was I?
Want to praise
other members
All that praise
Well to be honest you were in the way
But there was nothing else you could do
My partner
was pitiful!
What exactly did you do?
Hamada
You were all doing as you pleased
Everyone was just focused on themselves
You guy's wouldn't look this way once for me!
With him going all "Winter's~"
And you all like
I couldn't do anything!!
Because this is the last one we will vote
I think
we should discuss about
who was the worst out of all 3...
This one isn't related!
It's for everone of them!
I dont think we can figure it out between us
Can't License...
We have no other choice but to trust License
Please tell us the winner as well!
You want us both to decide?
Give out a name on "3"!
Both at the same time!
First the winner...
If you say it at the same time there will be no complaints
Alright then we will decide the winner
3,2...
The winner of the "Garu" tour is!?
Alright then we will decide the winner
3,2..
Matsumoto
"Garu" tour winner
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Thank you!
I completely
understand!!
Completely understand?
Your feeling's
I completely understand them!
Thanks!
The reason Matsumoto is the winner is because
He properly did
all of the "Garu"'s!!
I was great huh!
Now let's
do the worst person
Yes, The worst
Do it on 3
Well,
Because I won can I decide as well?
Ah, I see!
By the way have you decided?
Yes I have
So have I
Alright, got it!
Should all 3 of us say it at the same time?
Yea
On 3?
On 3
1,2...
Finally, The worst person is!?
So we're gonna all say it at once right?
Yes
Endo
The worst "Garu"
Cocorico Endo Shozo
What about Hamada!
Well Hamada got "Nori Tsukomi"
He never got a chance to use it
For me, Endo and Hamada were real close
It was at then end that I decided it
When I looked at it for the third time
I really thought you were pitiful!
"Garu" right
"To feel Pitiful"
Seriously it seemed like you were pitiful!
I really thought I was pitiful huh!?
Why!?
Endo get's the working overtime "Garu" medal!
Punishment
"To smell stink"
Doesn't it stink?
"To feel pain"
It hurts!
"To feel sleepy"
He's sleeping now
I almost fell!
He taking a really raw personality!
"To feel hot"
Excuse me!
Can you put on the AC!?
"To feel cold"
Sorry, I meant do you have a blanket?
"To want to know"
Is this Brazilian?
"To want to be
Mori Shinchi"
Ah It's out!
He's really good at this!
Delicious~
As expected from him!
Delicious!
I'm really sorry!
Presented by DCSubs
Gaki No Tsukai #1255 -The Wonderful "Garu" Tour