At NTV
First time on Gaki No Tsukai CHIKI CHIKI
Trivia Drive GO GO
In front of NTV
Indeed that's what this is
Today's project is very simple,
The 5 of us are gonna go for a drive,
And we'll see buildings, billboards, people and whatnot,
And come up with some trivia related to that
I see
Show off our trivia knowledge
The drive won't end until we say 100 things!
Wow, a 100?
I think Yamasaki-san and I should be good at this
I'm a natural
We'll spout trivia at the same pace as our advance
Really?
I'm not sure about these guys though
Yeah these two, honestly-
"These two"?! What about you?!
He knows about animals
Yeah I know a little bit
Ah, animals?
I know sports
Oh yeah!
That's true
Sorry Hamada-san
Let us look you up and down
What the hell?!
In a condescending way
Ah I see
Our route will be National Route 1
National Route 1?
Incidentally, this National Route 1,
It's not called that because it was the first route ever made,
It's cause it's the mope- most impopant route-
Enough already!
Alright that's one!
What are you on about
Timed and Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband
This episode, they will spout trivia as they drive
Following National Route 1,
An outside voice will judge the validity of their trivia
The drive doesn't end until they've come up with 100 bits of trivia!!
Here we go
Hurry up!
The endless drive starts with Endo at the wheel
We've started right?
I've already said the National Route 1 trivia,
So by now,
You guys must be overflowing with trivia
You can't wait to spit it all out right?
Basically we see something and say it right?
Well yes
Alright then,
This is something that surprised me when I went to the Netherlands some years ago,
Their 1st and 2nd floors are different from Japan's
Instead, they start with the 0th floor
So what we call the 2nd floor is their 1st floor
So if Japanese people visit Netherlands, they'll probably panic!
That last part was unnecessary
Why?!
Isn't that what this is about?
What do you mean-
See!
In the Netherlands, buildings start at floor 0
This is what this is about
This is a really great start isn't it?
What did you see that reminded you of the Netherlands?
These buildings, they have a first floor don't they?
The trivia must be related to something they saw!
You should say that then, "Looking at these buildings"
Yeah
The concept of 0 right?
The concept of 0 is a good one
Alright then, going off the concept of 0
Computers can display images and whatnot right?
In implementation, they are just arrangements of 1s and 0s
Hold on, I don't get it
For example, the character あ is "01"
And い could be "001"
They're just arrangements of 0s and 1s
They're just arrangements
I wish someone else said that though
Someone a bit more...
I didn't want to hear from a "000" person
000?
Computers use binary to represent information
Oh wow
Amazing
Can I go next? Going off of Matsumoto's foriegn travel, which would've been on an airplane
You'll never board an airplane from the right side, it's always the left
Oh yeah, now that you say it...
Yeah, and the reason why is,
You may know of America's Boeing and Europe's Airbus
Boeing makes airplanes now,
But they started off making boats
And on a boat the anchor is on the right, and you board from the left
And that legacy continued to their airplanes,
So that's why airfields became Airports,
And also the uh, things like, um, uhh
Like the pilots and so on
Umm
The cabin attendants,
Now I'm not so convinced
But the most important takeaway, is why we get on airplanes from the left
That's the lesson I want you all to take away from this
Oh that was close!
I thought it was good, but the delivery could've been better
That's true
I felt concerned for my junior there
I apologise
Ah Tokyo Tower!
Oh?
Yes, to our left
Can I use Tokyo Tower?
Yes go ahead
Tokyo Tower is made of steel right?
The girders that it's made of
It's made from tanks right?
You're stealing my trivia?
The US made a ton of tanks, and after the war
He took it from you!\
Why?
And there was a crap ton of scrap metal from those tanks
And then, those tanks,
Recover it!
They said "you guys buy them"
They said "buy them"
So Japan bought them,
Shut up you two!
What is this back and forth stealing
Cause I already know this!
Really?
Yama-chan you can't let him steal it from you
Nobody was impressed so this trivia didn't count
Wasn't I the one who told you this fact?
Oh yeah
Let's avoid this sort of thing
The smooth going trivia drive finally reaches National Route 1
Trivia Count:  3
There was that trivia about numbers just now,
You know Pi, the 3.14 number?
It continues forever right?
Yeah
They say within those infinite digits,
You can find every possible sequence of numbers
For example, my phone number
Or our numbers, every number sequence in this world is in Pi
Woah!
Well obviously, cause it's infinite
Everything is in there ?!
Yes
Well cause it's infinite, of course, cause it's infinite
C'mon, just act impressed
Pi contains all possible number sequences
Yeah just let us be impressed
Yeah
Do you know how they decided on the
blue yellow red traffic signals?
The most important one is of course red, meaning stop
Right, cause it's dangerous
So even with roadside trees or billboards ahead of it
It's the most visible
It's the rightmost signal
They gotta distance if from the green light
In order to be visible even with roadside trees blocking the view, the red light is furthest to the right
We got it!
Yeah we got it
Hamada-san!
You can use something you see if you want
Ah, that,
Did you know there's always an Origin Bento nearby a 7/11?
Ah is that so? I didn't know that
There's an Origin Bento there
Where? Oh there!
Origin Bento has stores nearby 7/11s,
Cause 7/11 has good information on where to open stores, that's how they choose locations
So in order to save money on research,
They thought "If we open near them we'll get customers!"
Ah it'll be popular!
That's what I've heard
Origin Bento places its stores near 7/11s
That felt great!
Wow, I didn't know that was a thing
Is there any schoolgirl trivia?
Schoolgirls...
Schoolgirls go to Shibuya 109 often right?
TN: A department store
The pro-golfer Katayama Shingo,
He's known to wear that hat,
Katayama Shingo
Yeah he does
He bought that at Shibuya 109
No way...
Ah is that so?
Really?
No no Tanaka
That's-
Tanaka it's true
Who cares about that? Where he bought it...
Katayama Shingo bought his hat at Shibuya 109
Oh I got it!
Oh we can say stuff like that?
I see
I'm feeling good
A good pace now
Yeah
There was a marathon being run just now right?
The reason marathons are 42.195km is,
A soldier ran for 42.195km,
Marathon triva
Marathons are 40km long because of the fable of Pheidippides
Ah I'm wrong?
I guess so
Something similiar to that, you remember CDs?
They're 72 minutes long
The reason being,
When they were making CDs, they were thinking how many minutes it should hold,
They decided it must hold the 9th Symphony
Ah, it's the length of the 9th Symphony?
It's the length of the 9th Symphony, 72 minutes
There's an am/pm there
Oh yeah there is
Could you wait for my "ping-pong" chyme?
In fact...
CDs can hold 74 minutes of music because of the 9th symphony
And I'm wrong too?!
You got it wrong!
That was wrong? It felt nice to hear though
This is embarrassing
I thought it was so interesting
We haven't driven that far yet, but we've got a lot
Trivia Count 9
Yeah, we're making good pace
Could you tell us the am/pm trivia?
Ah am/pm?
I did a commercial for them
Yes, you did
Of course that one doesn't count!
Yeah...
We're at Gotanda
Gotanda?
There's a lot of billboards here
Behind the behind of that building,
Hide from Penalty has a brewery back there
TN: Might have got this one wrong
It's a pub isn't it?
Why would it be a brewery?
Hide's Shop
It's not even trivia, let alone correct
Yeah honestly
And it's not even behind there
Is that thing about National Route 1 true?
I thought it was the first road made
They call it Route 1,
Cause it's the most important route,
The first road that comes to mind
They say during the war, the used this road as a runway
Apparently they landed planes here
Verifying
Ah, verifying?
Verifying...
The outside voice will announce after confirming
If we don't get a 100 quickly, we'll end up leaving the city
Oh yeah
It'll make it harder for us
Yeah
And it'll take time to get back
That's true
In fact we've passed Kannama already
That was quick
There's gotta be something here
Hmm, it seems like there isn't!
It's too soon to say that!
Sake... There's a Sake shop there
Sake...
There's gotta be something about alcohol
Whisky...
Whisky has no purine content
Whisky does not contain purines
What are purines anyways?
No clue
You just wanted to say that
I don't know what I don't know
I just know quite well that whisky doesn't have them
That's all
The trivia about highway runways,
Is incorrect
There is no proof that National Route 1 was used as a runway
Ah, it's wrong...
I was wrong?
Magome...
Something about the station?
There must be something
Magome Station...
There's gotta be...
How about this - The CEO of BOOK-OFF is the older sister of Shimuzu-san from Anonenone
Ah that's why he was in the commercials?
Yes yes
A heavy user
It makes you wonder "How does he even know that?"
The CEO of BOOK-OFF is the older sister of Shimizu-san from Anonenone
That's true, like the 7/11 thing
Yeah, probably,
He knows a lot of CEOs
Why would I?!
He knows about businesses
Why would I?
There's a lot here
That roller bag was popular before
Everyone used to have one
In the past, roller bags could only roll along one axis right?
The bag could only go back or forth
It's confusing how you said bag and back there...
But roller bags these days can go in many directions ... It's convenient
No shit!
They start to run out of trivia...
50 minutes since the start
They start to run out of trivia
In this pinch, one man will save the day by opening his mouth
I just saw a Condor Taxi pass by,
Oh yeah
So a trivia about Condors
There it is, the animal trivia
This is his strength
Condors...
This feels kind of forced though
There really was a Condor Taxi!
Condor have no feathers on their head and neck
And the reason why they're bald there,
They eat raw dead animals right?
To eat meat,
They stick their head in and dig in
When they do that, the blood
The blood gets on their head
It sticks to their face
It sticks to their face,
I see
If  they had feathers, the blood would stick and give them diseases
So that's why they're bald there, so the sun can hit their skin
And they can keep clean. That's why there's no feathers there.
I see
Condors have bald heads for sanitary reasons
That's amazing!
That's amazing
It's a very gruesome story though
Still 1/4 huh?
A crow flew past just now-
No it didn't!
A crow-
There was no crow
The Condor Taxi was a lie for sure
There was a taxi, to our right!
Crows can manipulate around 40 words
What do you mean "manipulate"?
They can remember 40 words
You're the one speaking in broken Japanese!
With your 40 words
In their language?
They can communicate with their caws
With each other?
With each other
Wow really?
Crows have around 40 words in their vocabulary
There's gotta be something about bowling
Ah bowling?
Bowling,
What do they call it when you get 3 strikes in a row?
Turkey
Do you know why?
Turkey is that bird right?
Yeah
In America when bowling first started,
It was rather difficult to get multiple strikes,
So some representative decided to create a present
Coincidentally, really coincidentally, they decided to give out a turkey if you got 3 strikes in a row
So that caught on with young people,
When people would get 2 strikes in a row, they would say "If you get another strike, that's a Turkey!"
Ahhh, I see
That felt good
The origin of "Turkey"
If you got 3 stirkes in a row,
you would be awarded a turkey as a present
Feels great
Golf has that "Eagle" thing too right?
It does
Hmm, I think Endo would know this too, why Golf has 18 holes,
Oh yeah, 18 holes
The UK is a cold country right?
So they would drink a flask of Scotch as they played
And they would drink each time they cleared a hole, warming their bodies as they played,
And right around the 18th hole their bodies would feel warmed up
Ah, they finished drinking?
Yes yes
Golf's 18 holes;
The bottle of scotch would finish by the 18th hole
It would've been so funny if you got the buzzer there
Endo, you knew that too right?
Yes
Ah, we're about to enter Kanagawa soon
Ahhh Kanagawa
There'll be less stores to point out too
Yeah you're right
They enter Kanagawa Prefecture
1 hour from the start,
The Trivia Drive leaves the city and enters Kanagawa
And then,
I need a pee
Yeah a pee...
I've been drinking a lot of water
Yeah, that makes sense
We've been driving the whole time of course,
We've gotta pee of course, drink things of course,
We're not robots after all
They should play the "pin pon" noise there!
Yeah!
Yeah honestly
There's a GUST there
Let's go to GUST
I might eat something
The 5 take a break at GUST
With Cocoroico in the lead, they've accumulated 33 trivia so far!
Although this is a break, since they want to finish soon, this is also an opportunity to accumulate trivia
The 5 order whatever they want
1 Iced Coffee
Would you like to use the drink bar?
Is it more beneficial to go and get it?
If you'd like to yes
You...
All you care about is benefits
C'mon!
The drink bar is out there
Alright, understood
Should we go ?
Go get them
I will
I want, a hot tea
Hot tea?
I want a hot drink after my meal
So you don't want one now!
GUST huh?
I'll go get the drinks too
Really?
I need to take a piss though
You two get along please
They can't just leave us alone like that
Yeah...
Our plan to leave DownTown alone with each other was a success
Nice!
We succeeded didn't we?
Well done Big Bro
Alone for the first time in a while
What the hell have you been filming all this time?
3 minutes later
You took your time on purpose right?
No no no no
They only had hot drinks
So we put ice in it
Seriously?
The reason I wanted ice coffee,
Was to cool down my body,
But originally in South America, in those hot countries, they started drinking coffee because it cools down the body
Ehhh
Coffee has a cooling effect on the body
There it is
Going off that,
You'd think they drink Oolong tea in China right?
But recently they've been drinking more Coffee
Oh really?
In fact this might have resulted in the cultivation of coffee beans surpassing the cultivation of tea leaves
Eh?
No no, even if you make that face...
Waiting for the pin pon sound
- I have no idea though!
He ran away
Here it is
Ah, excuse me
This is that thing,
It's a birthday!
Yeah
Speaking of birthdays,
Nagashima Shigeo (baseball player), Antonio Inoki, and Shimura Ken share the same birthday
They were all born February 20th
That's cool though
That's amazing
Did we pass by a Bikkuri Donkey?
We probably did
Incidentally, houses that look like Bikkuri Donkey stores,
Amagasaki had a lot of them
After this
Once again, DownTown are...
Chicken,
These days young girls have bigger breasts
They say it's because of eating chicken
Why?
They say the food they feed Chickens
Contains things that increase breast size
That's correct?!
Chicken is an effective food source for increasing breast size
Even outside of the lactation period,
Humans have enlarged breasts, which is unique among mammals
For animals, it's important to be able to reproduce right?
Other mammals walk on all fours,
So the rear end of the female is within their eyesight
So they can see the female's buttocks,
and it serves as a sexual signal, that makes them want to reproduce
But since humans are bipedal, in order to have "buttocks" in our view,
Human females have enlarged breasts to simulate them
That's amazing
Isn't that amazing?
Human females have enlarged breasts to substitute for buttocks
That reminds me, Yamasaki-san is forcefully suppressing his libido right now,
So while in line at the bank, he almost jumped at an old lady's ass
Buzzer! Buzzer sound!
I didn't know that, that's new trivia to me
Tanaka it's a good time for coffee right?
Ah, after the meal
Let's go then Tanaka
Let's go
Is this funny?
Idiots
What was the issue Endo had? Gallstones?
Incidentally, if you eat too much of this [REDACTED], you'll end up with that issue as well
Food Product
Pin Pon!
No no no, that's not right
It's not?
It's just someone coming inside!
They say men think of sex every 4 minutes
Next Week - Trivia Drive Finale
To think of more trivia, they head to Yokohama Chinatown
****** can now speak Japanese properly
And the drive continues into the night
I DON'T wanna go there
Will they be able to accumulate 100 trivia?
Timed and Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband