Let's take our first step!
On this year's "Let's Take Our First Step"
We got to see a 24-hours long show full of courage and love
The challenge of our 5 old dudes will begin!!
And now, 5 old dudes will face a similar challenge!
Eat from all the 32 shops in the 23 wards of Tokyo!
Eat from all the 32 shops in the 23 wards of Tokyo
Gyoza's King Sarae Marathon
They'll have to eat in a relay-style
6 gyoza from every shop in Tokyo's wards
They'll eat one dish at every Gyoza's King in Tokyo in a relay style
Their objective is to complete a meal in all the 32 shops!
Let's call here our first runner
Special Reporters
License
Fujiwara Kazuhiro
Inomoto Takafumi
- Yes
The first runner will be Yamazaki Hosei, please come here
Look at him running
He's running
1st runner
Yamazaki Hosei
Hosei, that car censored your best part
I wonder why
That caught me off guard
TYPESETTED AND QC'D BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATED BY SHION
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI | TWITTER.COM/FGRNDNOISES
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI | PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
THIS EPISODE IS PART ONE OF A TWO-PARTS EPISODE
IF YOU'RE WATCHING THIS AS IT'S BEEN UPLOADED,
PART 2 ISN'T ONLINE YET AND IS GOING TO BE ONLINE
SOON. IF YOU'RE WATCHING THIS IN, I DON'T KNOW, LIKE,
2 YEARS FROM NOW (SEPTEMBER 2020) THEN YOU CAN
FIND PART 2 ON SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
ALSO I HOPE 2022 IS BETTER THAN 2020 'CAUSE IT SUCKS
Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
One person's quota is to clear 6 shops (36 gyoza) from a total of 32 shops.
They'll aim to clear the challenge within the shops' business hour (23:30)
The marathon starts from Minato Ward, the objective is to eat one dish from every shop
The quota is 6 shops each
Will they be able to complete it before the shops close?
You're the first one, are you ok?
Yeah, I'm good
Are you sure?
I'm not worried at all, quite the opposite...
When the staff told me I could eat as much as I want I got pumped
Oh, is that so?
I'm gonna eat so much today
You sound so confident about it
- You're gonna eat a lot?
Definitely
That's amazing
- He's going for it, folks
I'm ready
Total of 32 shops
1st shop
In front of Shinbashi station, Minato Ward
The old dudes marathon will start at our first shop, in front of Shinbashi's station
Here's our first dish
Here it is
And we're starting
This is it
This is what I'm talking about
Bon appetit
He's so focused
- And the marathon has now started
This is only our first shop
Delicious
Glad to hear that
Are you enjoying it?
It's so good
I bet it is
He's keeping up a nice pace, isn't he?
- I agree
Yamazaki easily eats 3 gyoza in a row,
and he's ready to finish them
That's a pro move, soaking them beforehand
I just realized this
Yeah?
I see
I've become able to calculate the exact amount I can eat
Now that you're done?
What do you think of this as a starting point?
Don't you think he's done really well?
- It's a really good start
By the way, you've just eaten 5 of those,
how's your stomach?
I'm hungry to be honest
Oh my, I think...
Hosei can probably do 10 shops by himself
I definitely can, this is nothing
Well, it's a marathon after all
- And so, as we're speaking...
Yes
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza:
He finished them all
- That's right
Thanks
(28 minutes since start)
32 total shops:
shop no. 2
Togoshi-ginza shop (Shinagawa Ward)
You ready, Hosei?
Yamazaki had a perfect start
It's time for their second shop at Togoshi-ginza
He's usually not much of an eater
But nevertheless
He completed his second meal in a blink of an eye
And now Hosei...
He completed his second meal
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza:
- Nice done
Congratulations
Alright
I wanna eat
I wanna eat some more gyoza, let's go
Travel distance: 7,1km
Travel time: 23 min.
from Togoshi-Ginza
to Kamata east exit
Minato
Shibuya
Setagaya
Meguro
Shinagawa
Ota
Next up, Hosei, is the shop on Kamata's east exit
You're killing it
I have so much space left, I wanna eat more
Right now?
Yeah
It's gonna take us some time to move to our next location
Is this time going to affect Yamazaki's determination?!
(1 hour and 2 min. since start)
32 total shops:
shop no. 3
Kamata station's east exit (Ota Ward)
They've finally arrived to the third shop in Kamata
But how is Yamazaki's stomach going to be?
Let's go
Let's do this
Come on
Let's get in, Hosei
Ok
Let's just do this
You said you were still hungry on our second shop...
- That's right
I bet you're gonna destroy these
Huh?
The pace has suddenly slowed down
- How are you doing?
Are you ok?
It looks like...
You've lost your motivation, what happened?
Why--
Why do you suddenly look dead inside?
To be honest, I'm starting to feel really full right now
Yes?
Maybe it's because it took so long
to get there, but he's feeling full
Still, his fast pace has crumbled down
I know you've lost your pace, but give your best here
Just few more
And now
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza:
He just finished his third meal
Travel distance: 8,1km
Travel time: 18 min.
from Kamata's east exit
to Ookayama
Minato
Shibuya
Setagaya
Meguro
Shinagawa
Ota
You completely changed during the time span
between the 2nd and 3rd shop
Can you see how hard this is pressing on my belly?
Oh, I can see it
- Are those leggings?
Yeah, they're so tight now
It became adherent?
I think
They're gonna affect me a lot
I definitely underestimated this
Is that so?
Yeah
It was so sudden, wasn't it?
(1 hour and 26 min. since start)
32 total shops:
shop no. 4
Ookayama shop (Ota Ward)
Yamazaki is so full he's not feeling at ease anymore
But it's still time for their fourth shop
As expected, his expression can't hide his distress
His chopsticks barely move
And there's something glittering on the tip of his nose
Say, Hosei...
This isn't easy
- I can tell you're in danger...
'Cause there's sweat on your nose's tip
It's pretty bad
Oi
Yes?
Remember I told you I got hospitalized 2 years ago?
I do
You had stomach problems, am I right?
Yes, my large intestine
Large intestine, right
From that time on...
I've been taking so much medicine
Even now?
But don't broadcast this, alright?
It's been how long? 2 years?
Don't broadcast this intestine talk, ok?
If you eat this one here...
- You have like... 10 left
You just have to do two more shops
You have to do 12 more
- Only 12 left, yes
Only 12, Hosei
He did it!
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza:
- Meal finished
All done!
Oh shit
Would you like some water?
No, I'm fine
You sure?
I'm...
Look here
Looks like you're about to burst
I can't keep it in
Travel distance: 3,8km
Travel time: 7 min.
from Ookayama
to Gakugei University
I think he's pregnant
'Morning
2nd runner
Tanaka
7th shop
arrives to Sangenjaya's shop
At the same time, our next runner Tanaka arrives at Sangenjaya
How are you feeling?
My stomach?
I'm ready
Are you?
I'm feeling really good today
And...
You had breakfast?
I didn't, of course I came here empty
And my condition is just perfect!
Glad to hear that
(1 hour and 55 min. since start)
32 total shops:
shop no.5
Gakugei University's shop (Meguro Ward)
Let's go, Hosei
Yamazaki arrives at the fifth shop at Gakugei University
He tries his best to munch some more gyoza
But then he thinks about something...
Are you feeling it?
It's getting harsh, isn't it?
- I can tell
If you overcome this...
Pass me the phone, please
He suddenly makes a call
And he's calling...
He's really full
He's about to explode
You can see the curve from this side
Hello?
Yes, hello?
Tanaka?
It's me
'Morning, listen...
Sangenjaya shop
Gakugei University shop
Tanaka Naoki
Yamazaki Hosei
Call
I wanted to ask you...
Yes?
If you could come to Komazawa University
Mh?
It's where I'm going now
Is he trying to blame the staff for this?
- Definitely
No way, wait--- didn't we agree to do 6 shops each?
Sangenjaya shop
Gakugei University shop
Tanaka Naoki
Yamazaki Hosei
Call
Just come
I'll explain everything once you're there
Once I'm there?
Yeah, sorry about this
Komazawa University?
Just go there
Sangenjaya shop
Gakugei University shop
Tanaka Naoki
Yamazaki Hosei
Call
I can't talk to you unless we meet
Alright, I got it
Thanks
He couldn't eat, right? He's giving up
And he's trying to blame the staff for it
That sucks
It sucks so much
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza:
Alright, he did it
- And he's done!
Nice
Let's move on
It took some time, but Yamazaki somehow cleared 5 shops
But the limits of this old dude's weak
stomach are turning sweat into tears
His steps towards the next shop are as heavy as lead
His stomach is swelling like a balloon
Can he rely on his friends to help him?
Here we are
Yamazaki finally arrives at the sixth shop
32 total shops:
shop no.6
Komazawa University front shop (Setagaya Ward)
(2 hours 11 min. since start)
He enters the shop at Komazawa University to wait for Tanaka
Welcome
- 'Morning
He's here already
- Here we are
I think you have to talk now
2nd runner
Tanaka Naoki
Yeah
Just so you know
Yes?
I'm still pressing the 10 mins. button
What?
So please keep it short
What? Really?
Welcome!
- Yes
Just a quick chat, ok?
Please, eat some more
I really can't Tanaka, I'm dead serious
Please, I beg you
I can't, I can't, I'm done for
But I promise, Tanaka, next time
I'll do it for you next time
- He's passing the baton
I promise
You're not doing it
I'll do it
I swear
Haven't you been lying like this for your whole life?
That's not true
I can see through your act
Seriously, Tanaka
You get it, right? Seriously
I'm dead serious here
I've been watching how you live
I swear I'll help you next time
I'll take my part
Are we doing this?
Fine, let's do this
From now on
I'm taking this sash
And continuing this marathon
Let's go then, start!
Our second runner receives the sash
And this is Tanaka's first shop
So, how is it?
They're really delicious
Are they?
They're really good
Not to ruin anything, but we already saw that face on Hosei
So nostalgic
- I agree
But I swear, these are really good
Well, yes
Your face is gonna become like this
Look at him, look at his face
Really? Is that true?
- Yes
- Yeah
Good luck
Such a weak support
- Barely heard him
I think I can do this
You think so?
Mh-mh
Only one left
Yes
- Only one
That was quick
Only one
I'm gonna eat it
He's done
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza:
I can do this, it's fine
Can you?
If I keep this pace
I thought I would have started later
But I think I did my part
Are you excited?
Yeah, I am
To go to other shops?
I am, really
Why are --
I'm serious
Why are you sympathizing with him?
Travel distance: 2,0km
Travel time: 8min.
from Komazawa University
to Sangenjaya
I can do this
Are you sure?
I'm pumped
We're counting on you here
I'm gonna do this
We can tell by your voice you're ready
I know, right?
I really think I can do this
But the fact Hamada is right after me...
It's pretty terrifying, you know
Yeah, I know
And you can't see him
Yeah, I mean
Oh boy
I'm gonna do my best here
(2 hours 42min since start)
32 total shops:
shop no. 7
Sangenjaya's shop (Setagaya Ward)
As Tanaka feels Hamada's pressure,
he heads to the shop he started from
That was quick!
Let's go!
Ready and... start!
Let's go
Gotta hurry up, there's not much time left
How is it here?
It's just as delicious
Tanaka quickly eats one gyoza after another
He's looking promising
That's a nice pace
It took me an instant
It really took you an instant, yes
- Really quick
What should we do? Can I get the check?
I think it's ok
Sure, go get it
While he's eating
- Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm comin' in a flash
Alright then
Really? Alright, I'm gonna pay then
Yeah
Don't mind if you do
I'm going
Here I go
Counting on you
Last one from Sangenjaya
Yes
He did it
Thanks for the meal
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza:
What do you think?
Very good  - So quick!
Let's go
Hurry up!
Tanaka rushes towards the next shop!
That was fast, huh?
Yeah, last one was really quick
I knew it
From when we arrived and got back to the car now...
4 minutes... or 5, that's how long it took
The fastest yet
The fastest?
Yes, the fastest
The fastest today?
It's today's record
Neat, I did it
At least for now no one else has made it this fast
- Alright, I'm glad
You're #1 in the world
- World record
I've been aiming at it
(3 hours 7min since start)
32 total shops:
shop no. 8
Kyodo's shop (Setagaya Ward)
We're here
Here we are
Tanaka quickly enters Kyodo's shop
His fast-paced technique shines again
The gyoza disappear in his mouth one after another
Last one here
Yes
Good pace
Here goes nothing
New record?
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza:
Meal finished!
It was delicious!
(3 hours 24min since start)
32 total shops:
shop no.9
Shimokitazawa's shop (Setagaya Ward)
Tanaka is doing well
And now it's time for their 9th shop at Shimokitazawa
So good
It's perfectly cooked
Must be nice
He's still enjoying their taste
So good
He's a professional
He's taking one shop after another
And he's not wasting time around
[indistinguishable gyoza sounds]
Here I go
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza:
He's done
- Nice
Shimokitazawa is done
Thank you
Travel distance: 4,2km
Travel time: 20min.
From Shimokitazawa
to Shibuya Hachiko Exit
Toshima
Bunkyo
Shinjuku
Chiyoda
Minato
Chuou
Nakano
Suginami
Shibuya
Setagaya
Alright, let's move on
Let's go
- Shibuya's shop
Shibuya, huh
How are you feeling?
Are your leggings still ok?
Hosei told us that
Halfway through it, they got tight
Nothing, no problem at all
He told us that if they feel tight
Then you can't eat anymore
- I heard that
They're not tight at all
Are you really ok?
On the opposite, I think I'm raising the speed
Nice
Yeah
But this car ride is going to bring
a sudden change inside Tanaka
Alright, Tanaka
Yes?
We're finally at our 10th shop
Oh, number 10
Yes
We're at Shibuya's Hachiko exit
(4 hours 7min since start)
32 total shops:
shop no.10
Shibuya Hachiko Exit's shop (Shibuya Ward)
Finally they arrive at shop no.10
It's Shibuya Hachiko's exit shop
Oof...
"Oof"?
Here they come
The fifth dish is placed before a sighing Tanaka
Thanks
He wanted to easily clear this shop too, but...
Ok, tenth shop
At Shibuya Hachiko, let's go
Start!
Alright!
Foohhh...
You've been breathing a lot
- Right
He just went "foohh" now
- Yes
I'm fine, I'm completely fine
How is it?
- So?
Mh, it's good
Is it? Glad to hear that
How's your stomach?
I'm completely---
I'm full
Full?! Excuse me?!
Can you repeat it?
- Sorry
I'm feeling full
Are you for real?!
I can do it
I'm starting now
That was bound to happen
- Well, yes
Of course you'd get full
Alright, I'm ready to face it
Let's move on then
I'm not drawing back
Well said
I'm dead serious
Yes
From now on it's all about willpower
True...
I know
Tanaka's stomach is already full of gyoza
But he's getting his willpower back
You shouldn't drink that much
- You're gonna swell, man
- You'll explode
Don't drink that much
Alright
If you give your best here
It'll be easier for the runner after you
- That's right
My leggings are getting really tight...
I swear
Wha-
I told you so
I swear, I wonder why
Are they tight?
They feel really tight
It's incredible, they're so tight
Really, it feels like...
They just shrunk---
You spat something out
- Something fell down
It feels like they're down two sizes
Sorry
I'm going
Alright, let's finish this
Here I go
And it's in
Let's see how it's going to affect him...
Last one!
- One last gyoza
Hang in there, Tanaka
I'm really about to
To...?
To reach my limit, really
Hang in there
And he's done
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza:
Let's pay up and move
Ok
Oh boy, I can feel it now
Back there in Shibuya...
I ate the first gyoza and thought "oh crap"
Third runner
13th shop
Hamada
arrives at Nakano's shop
At the same time
Hamada, our next runner
Doesn't look like anyone's coming, huh...
(4 hours and 55 min since start)
32 total shops:
shop no.11
Shin Okubo's shop (Shinjuku Ward)
Here we are
And Tanaka has arrived to the 11th shop at Shin Okubo
Come on, let's go
In order to pass his sash to Hamada...
Tanaka keeps on eating gyoza with a dreadful look
Is he getting close to his limits?
I think this is probably the best cup of water I've ever had
Like, in your whole life?
In all my life, yeah
If you eat this one...
You're done
Come on
Alright
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza:
- Excellent
You cleared Shin Okubo's shop
- You did it!
Let's go
Can you wait a sec?
Tanaka?
Is Hamada...
Is Hamada already inside that shop?
He is
Hamada is currently inside Nakano's shop
And now, Tanaka...
Wait a second...
What's wrong?
I can't do this
I hate this phone call...
Tanaka is finally at his limit and calls Hamada
Shin Okubo
Nakano
Call
Tanaka Naoki
Hamada Masatoshi
What do you want?
"What do you want?" already...
Oi
He's already pissed off...
Hello?
Don't keep him waiting
He's angry
Hello?
Answer
What do you want?
He's pissed!
Weren't you expecting it?
He's furious
He's so angry he's gonna kill me
Of course he is
Hamada is seriously pissed off
You gotta do it
The hell is wrong with you?
Hello?
Sorry for this, it's Tanaka
Sorry but, Hamada...
Well...
Shin Okubo
Nakano
Call
Tanaka Naoki
Hamada Masatoshi
I think I've reached my limit
Oh?
And I'm... I'm currently at Shin Okubo's shop
Shin Okubo, ok
So...
You're currently at Nakano's shop, am I right?
Yeah
Can we meet at shop no.12 at Takadanobaba?
Takadanobaba you say?
Right now I'm--- yes, that's it
I'm at my limit, I can't fit one more gyoza in my mouth
Not a single one
I just can't get 'em inside me
What are you talking about?
Listen to me
I beg you, I'm really sorry about this
But please--- leave Nakano's shop
And move to the previous one
It's at Takadanobaba, can you go there?
No way dude
I'm really sorry about this
But please--- Takadanobaba's shop---
Take a ride to Takadanobaba pleeease
DEAL WITH IT YOURSELF!!
He got so mad I didn't know what to say
For now let's--- let's just head to Takadanobaba
Let's go then
Then I'll think again
That's the best choice
Right, I'll think about it again in there
Yes
This is tough, huh
Can I say something?
Please
I'm suffering so much
I'm dying
It's really unbearable
The hell is this? It came so suddenly
Was it sudden?
Yeah...
Gyoza really fill you up for good, huh?
They do, actually
- Right...
(5 hours 32min since start)
32 total shops:
shop no.12
Takadanobaba's shop (Shinjuku Ward)
Fearsome Hamada, fearsome gyoza
Tanaka arrives at Takadanobaba's shop
He forcibly eats one gyoza against
his screaming stomach's will
Can I ask for a take-out?
Sure, I'll get you a box
Sorry
I can't anymore...
What are you gonna do with it?
Here's a box for you
Can I?
Thank you
Sorry, it's a take-out
But what are you gonna do with it?
I swear, I can't...
A take-out is all I can do
Are they for Hamada?
You gonna give 'em to him?
M-mh...
I'm really sorry
Tanaka unexpectedly chooses a take-out and
heads to Nakano's shop where Hamada is waiting
(6 hours 2min since start)
32 total shops
shop no.13
Nakano (Nakano Ward)
An exhausted Tanaka heads to the 13th shop, Nakano
To deliver his gyoza to Hamada
Welcome!
'Morning
You're so goddamn late, man
Good morning
Sorry for being late
I'm sorry, hear me out
Third runner
Hamada Masatoshi
I'm leaving now, you take care of it
Come on, touch
I'm going home
W-w--wait, wait a second
What?
Hear me out
Please listen to me
What was that?
I have no room left for a single gyoza anymore
You're the third runner, aren't you?
That's not it, what is this?
I got these from Takadanobaba's shop
Gyoza take-out from Takadanobaba's shop
Did you... is that a take-out?
I'm sorry about that
He's the worst
He ate one of them
But I did my part, I ate them all
So it's Yamazaki's fault?
That's right
In other words, this is Yamazaki's part
I want you to understand this
Well, if it's Yamazaki's part let's have him eat it at the end
I see
Makes sense
I see, it's his part... let's save this for last
I know, right?
Let's do this
Here's your sash
What the hell...
I'm giving it to you
It finally happened
I have a bad feeling already
He's finally passing it
Sorry
It's  time for our third runner
It's yours
How do I put this on?
Here
The sash has been passed
Here I am
We're counting on you
Alright
Can I eat?
Sure
We're starting
Counting on you!
Deli~cious!
King's gyoza are so good!
And it's a downhill from now on
If you think your stomach can do it, why don't you
do a bit more than the scheduled 6 shops?
What?
Can I?
Of course you can
Of course
Are you kidding me?
It could really help the second half
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza:
Really good
He's done
Nakano's shop has been done
If you think you can eat these as well, please do it
Ok
Hamada completes his first meal too easily
He's now wearing the sash of hope
I think it was around the 4th shop
Maybe the 5th, that's when it hit me
Also, I really hope it's clear enough to Hamada
that those leftovers are actually Yamazaki's
(6 hours 35min since start)
32 total shops:
shop no.14
Fujimidai station's shop (Nerima Ward)
A joyful Hamada enters the 14th shop at Fujimidai's station
Let's go
So good!
I can eat hundreds
Good
Despite his old-dude poor appetite,
he easily clears another meal
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza:
Alright, he's done here
They're really good
Fujimidai's station shop is done
They're delicious!
He's so lively!
That was really quick just now
No big deal
Still feeling hungry?
Yep
Can you do this?
I can
So much confidence, wow
I'm doing this
I'm feeling great
We can tell
(7 hours 12min since start)
32 total shops
shop no.15
Nishidai station's shop (Itabashi Ward)
A still hungry Hamada enters shop no.15 at Nishidai's station
This is Hamada's third shop
Yes
Let's do this: start!
Mh, very good
He's so fast
Even after his third dish, Hamada is still fine
He might be an old dude, but his pace is fast
and gyoza are disappearing one after another
He's really the man you can trust in the crucial moment
He's done after less than 3 minutes
Were the other two as fast with the first three dishes?
Yeah, they were all pretty quick at the beginning
Curse of the 4th dish?
That's right
I can do it
I can keep up all the way to shop no.22
Until shop no.22 at Suidobashi? That's Endo's territory
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza:
currently
objective
How much do you think you can eat? It's 10 dishes, you know
How many gyoza?
60 gyoza
Next week...
Hamada's stomach finally reached its limit...
I smell trouble
Endo will help his senpai in a pinch and raise the pace
And then, the sash arrives to Matsumoto
Why is this happening? You should have eaten more
I'm thinking about going home...
You want me to #%@&!§ now?
No no no no, that's not it
What will they see at the goal !?
Whaaat?!
And now...
It's time to announce the release of Matsumoto's movie!
Matsumoto's movie: about to be released!
GAKI NO TSUKAI NEWS  - MOVIE: SYMBOL (2009)
(I LOVE THIS MOVIE, PLEASE WATCH IT)
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Director
Is there anyone?
Where am I?
I wanna go home...
Symbol
9/12 (sat.) - nationwide roadshow
TYPESET & QUALITY CHECK BY KEDOMAS || TRANSLATION BY
SHION || MORE EPISODES: SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
LIKE MY FB PAGE: FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI | FOLLOW ME ON
TWITTER @SHIONNOTSUKAI | WANT TO SUPPORT MY CONTENT?
YOU CAN DONATE FEW BUCKS ON KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
OR ON PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
THIS IS PART ONE OF A TWO-PART EPISODE | PART TWO IS EITHER GOING TO BE UPLO
ADED WITHIN THE NEXT 10 DAYS IF YOU'RE CURRENTLY LIVING IN SEPTEMBER 2020 |
OR IT'S ALREADY ONLINE IF YOU'RE FROM THE FUTURE, LIKE, 2050 OR SOMETHING | IF
YOU'RE A TIME TRAVELER CURRENTLY STUCK IN THE PAST I'M SORRY BUT I CAN'T HEL
P YOU | | |  THIS IS A NO-PROFIT FANMADE TRANSLATION MADE BY FANS FOR OTHER F
ANS | NO COPYRIGHT INFRINGMENT INTENDED, NO ADFLY, NO MONEY INVOLVED EXCE
PT DONATIONS WHICH ARE NOT EVEN REMOTELY MANDATORY I'M LITERALLY DOING T
HIS JUST BECAUSE I LIKE DOING THIS | THANKS FOR WATCHING <3