Are their hearts connected? Meet up without smartphones
The rule; go to a place based on the hint. The challenge ends if they all meet up
Last time, the first hint was: A store you can line up outside
Nobody was able to meet up
I thought you guys would understand this
You guys are clueless
The second hint, was a hotel
Everyone but Tanaka relied on their memories
Thank god
Only Matsumoto & Hosei were able to meet
Hamada is scary isn't he
Will they be able to meet up?
1, 2, Dogenzaka
There's no answer but Nikotama
There's someone, there's someone, there, there!
subbed by senor_wristband
1 hour and 34 minutes since the start,
Time for the 3rd hint
Here I go
That's difficult
UNIQLO
You know, I just thought of one,
I actually have no idea,
On 3,
1, 2, Dogenzaka
Shinjiku
I think either one
The [Shibuya] 109 place right?
I think either one,
I think the one in Bic Camera, they call it BICQLO or something,
On Shinjiku-dori in front of Kinokuniya [Department Store]
We were just there
We were there, now we have to go back?
That is a big one though
But I thought of either Shibuya or Shinjiku first
Shibuya right? There's one in Ginza too
But Ginza is out right?
The Shinjiku one is a BICQLO though
It's the collab with Bic Camera
Oh yeah Tanaka would say something weird about that
So that means, Shinjiku?
No, Shibuya
Right, Shibuya
I just, spaced out. You're right.
That's the BICQLO right
The two head towards the UNIQLO in Shibuya
Yamasaki is usually close by, like the billboard from last time
I don't really wanna say this, cause I could go on forever,
To put it simply, this is a problem of IQ
That's true, their IQ is too low
It's a question of their IQ
But maybe we just don't know, there might be a huge UNIQLO somewhere
That's what made me think Ginza
Really?
The one's in Ginza show up on TV a lot
But Cocorico and Hamada in Ginza...
I think Hamada is probably banned from Ginza
That's not true of course
I have no idea
For example, there was that huge UNIQLO in Ginza that was on TV
But will those guys think of that one?
Where else is there?
Is there one in Shibuya?
There's one in Shibuya
There is right
I don't think Shinjuku. Maybe Shibuya...
Let's go to #!$!@@$#!
Which UNIQLO is Hamada heading to?
They're gonna administer justice on me,
If I go to the wrong place
There's 2 things that Hamada doesn't use, that normal people would use,
The first, is the word "delicious"
He will never exclaim "Tasty!"
His taste is garbage
"Delicious!" He will never say that
Normal people would say that for sure, but not him
And the other thing,
"Nostalgic!"
I've never heard him say that
NO right?
I've never heard him use the phrase "So nostalgic"
Never heard it before
His blood isn't liquid
Hamada-san's?
It's in powder form
He's never seen blood before
Yeah he hasn't. That's why his is powdered
I want to meet nice people
Because then I can be justified
Cause those two are together
They think they decide the right answer
But still, Hamada is like the pus of this show
C'mon, that's not true at all
All the problems stem from him right?
It's all messed up, everything about him
His fortune
His fortune?
Nah nah that's not...
Tanaka has still not chosen a location
UNIQLO... where else can I find one besides Nikotama?
The answer he came up with?
In !$!@#$,
Was there one?
Let's go to !@$!@
Is that alright?
What UNIQLO did Tanaka choose?
Keshigomu (staff), is there a store you can think of?
Keshigomu = Eraser
I would say the one in Ginza
There's a big one in Ginza
I don't know the big UNIQLO in Ginza...
A big UNIQLO in Ginza?
There's ones in Shibuya and stuff,
I don't know the location though
Let's go to $%@!$
Matsumoto's car hurries towards Shibuya
Will there be anyone else that will be able to meet?!
If they hand me a phone again I'm gonna flip
There gonna tell us some different place they're at
It makes you start to hate them
It makes you go "Why? Just why?"
"Woah, we don't know each other at all"
"Are we speaking the same language?"
The 2 reach Shibuya Dogenzaka
I can't see any other staff
The UNIQLO itself,
Hmm? Matsumoto-san
Look
Isn't that someone there?
Isn't that someone there?!
It's Keshigomu!
It's him right?
Is that Keshigomu? Oh there's someone there!
yes yes yes who is it who who
OOOHHH TANAKA!!!
See!
Right?
This is the answer
Thank god!
Cause it's huge right?
Oh thank god
Thank god!
This is the only answer
Either here or Shinjiku
But the one in Shinjiku is a BIQLO,
And we thought "Tanaka would have some problem with that" so we came here instead
Ah I see
It's just Hamada, we gotta aim for him
You're right
That's true, he's the weird one
He's the problem
My bad, I thought Tanaka was the problem,
But the whole time in the Taxi we were talking about Hamada
The whole ride
The fact that he didn't come to Hotel Yoko really hurt
Ahh, there
Why Westin?
My parents stayed in that place
Westin?
There's no way we would know that
There's no way
"Oh yeah Tanaka's parents stayed there!!!" - did you think we'd say that?
Did you think that?
And then Endo and Hamada show up
"Of course right?! Tanaka's parents stayed here after all!!"
"See you next week!"
would that happen?
But Endo shocked me at the first hint,
We were talking about the line up place right?
We even mentioned Hirunandesu
So he would have rememberd the pancake store
Right? The pancake place
Actually I wouldn't think of a pancake place either,
But Hirunandesu was men-
Your fly is totally open
Your fly is so open
He is that age after all
And I don't think you closed it properly right now either
Are you trying to make us laugh?
Just where are Hamada and Endo?
First, Endo
I went to the UNIQLO in Shinjiku
Like we said,
That's not it
That's a BICQLO
It does say BICQLO, but it says UNIQLO properly next to it
There it is
I'm never gonna forgive you
I will never forigive you, no matter what happens
Over here, Me, Yamasaki and Tanaka all three have met!
We've met up
Tanaka is there?
We're at the Dogenzaka UNIQLO
Dogenzaka UNIQLO?
It's the most obvious one!
It totally stands out
Hamada
What are you doing?
What do you mean "What are you doing"
UNIQLO ... You're at one in Japan right?
Yes, I'm at a UNIQLO
In Ginza
There it is
He said it, Ginza
There's one in Ginza?
Of course, it has 12 floors!
It's the biggest one in the city
Nah, you gotta think of the flow,
You guys are just using the power of numbers to decide what's right
Is quantity what decides?
I think that's wrong
The point of this episode is to get the most people
Even if you say that,
It's a "meet up" episode
That's the point of this challenge
Whatever, enough. We'll talk later, alright, alright
They hung up?
Even Tanaka is there
Enough of this crap
2 hours and 2 minutes since starting
Time for the 4th hint
C'mon!
A location to interview people on the street
There, we already know it's there
I actually got this
I do too
You get it right?
What's with that stupid face of yours?
I'm definitley thinking of the same place as Yamasaki
The same
What's with that expression?
Okay yeah, say the answer together,
1, 2, Shinbashi!
Shinbashi!
Center Gai!
It's Shinbashi, no question!
It's gotta be SL Plaza WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN WATCHING?!?!
There's probably interviews there now!
But isn't Center Gai the centre of Shibuya?
They interview people there all the time
Those are interviews on niche topics
It shouldn't be about just fashion or topics like that,
But like, what you see on Japanese news shows
So it's definitely that place right?
It's SL Plaza!
This whole time I was like what is that "GACHA GACHA"
YOU'RE THE ONE MAKING THIS CHAIN HIT THE THING!!!
STEP FORWARD A STEP!!
Makes my blood boil
This was the noise?
For the entire phone call this stupid GACHA GACHA
That was you?!
I thought it was some noise from the phone
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
It's infuriating, infuriating right?
Thank god we met him, imagine if we didn't
Yeah thank god. I guess me and Yamasaki think the same huh?
Matsumoto-san we got this, we'll finish with this one
Ginza! Hamada's there, that's his location
That's close by,
If he's a decent person, he'll come to Shinbashi
They head to SL Plaza in Shinbashi
Will they all meet up?
And Endo?
There's only 2 answers,
SL Plaza, or Shibuya?
In front of Hachiko, you often see them there with the mic
He considers SL Plaza, and Hachiko's statue in Shibuya
Which will he pick?
Meanwhile, Hamada,
I know this one
This is that place, !@%!%^
It's gotta be that one, there's no question
Let's go. That's the only place.
They're full of confidence this time, but will they meet Matsumoto's group?
I do have confidence in this choice,
If they tell me I'm wrong, this will have become a political issue
They have the numbers on their side
From now on, Tanaka films Matsumoto's group
If this was "Journey to the West", Tanaka would be the priestess
What do you mean?
He meets each of us 1 by 1
So he's the priestess?
And I'm Son Goku of course
He's the priestess, and you're Son Goku
Who am I then?
You're Sagojo right?
So then, Hamada-san...
Hamada is Chohakai yeah?
And Endo?
What would Endo be?
He's Gautama Buddha
Amazing
Endo is amazing
That's amazing
But you know, I'm just saying, but we basically just watch NHK, right?
And on NHK news, they usually film at SL Plaza, whatever it is,
Oh really?
It's just an association in my head
"SL Plaza - Shinbashi"
Then the sound of the train going by
So it's gotta be, SM....
It's an SM club usually
The course right?
You wonder what SM course they'll choose
What are you saying?
SM...
That was dangerous, I almost spit it out
... the course ...
He stuttered!
He got confused between SL and SM
No no that's not true
Then he tried to cover it with the SM club
Damn I almost spit this out
He was talking about SL at first
He stuttered the L into an M
No I just thought I'd end my story there, I changed the topic
Matsumoto's group head towards SL Plaza in Shinbashi
Will Hamada and Endo be able to meet them?
Tanaka, what's the first Olympic sport you can think of?
An Olympic sport?
I got it
Shall we say it together?
Oh yeah let's do that
100 metre dash
Gymnastics
It's gotta be the 100 meter dash
This is gotta be that one
That's the association with the Olympics
It's the first one that comes to mind
The headline
But the people in the 100m dash, they do some gymnastics first
Is that how you think it works?
First they compete in gymnastics
They prepare by doing gymnastics?
That's not an Olympic sport then
There's Judo and Wrestling and what not,
They all prepare with gymnastics
All of them?
We're close right?
Shinbashi is on Hamada's way, he's in Ginza
They arrive at SL Plaza
Will the challenge end here?
Anyone here?
There isn't
Nobody huh?
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, OH!
There is there there there there!
You're right!
Who? Who's that?
Who, who is it?
Over there
Of course, right?
I'm glad
This is it right?
You were in Ginza, closest to here
There a lot of interviews in Ginza,
But it's gotta be here
Wait, where's Endo?
Not here
But, where was he coming from?
Shinjiku
Let's wait a little longer
He's probably almost done, I think he just hasn't reached yet
They haven't given us the phones yet
Yeah there's no call to be made
There's a chance he's on his way
Will Endo appear at SL Plaza?
He could be in Shibuya, at Center Gai,
It's like-
Good work today!
This is it right?
Thank god!
I really thought you wouldn't come!
I thought this was the only place
But you guys were already at Shibuya,
I was thinking that too
But I bet on this place
This was pretty tiring
It really was
But man you guys suck!
The BIQLO
The pancakes
The Hyatt!
The Grand Hyatt
only IDIOTS here
But of course Yamasaki and I, the viewers already knew-
You guys are just using your numbers to decide the answer
You've stayed at Yoko so many times!
I have, but the hint was "A Hotel"
Yoko has nothing do with that, it's irrelevant
That giant hotel in the middle of the city
Did you really think we'd all go "yayyy!!" and meet up there?
Yes, that's why I was there
Tanaka consults with the members;
A story that happened while shooting a drama
I wanted to hear your thoughts on this,
I was going to be in a drama,
You want to work there instead right?
At the studio-
You totally want to work there
No, that's not it,
Take me with you dude
Yeah it's risky for you now
Take me with you
There's always Busjack 2
There's no news about that at all
They could make a series
Not a peep. Even though it's been such a popular topic online.
They should just make it
We all said we'll appear in it
Right? DownTown in a movie together,
Yeah, yeah we'll do it
We said we'll do it, they should start making 2
It's such an ocassion to see these two on screen together
All of us, we can all do it
Exactly, exactly,
Busjack is one thing,
There's always gifts right?
Yeah, on dramas there are
They always give them out right?
So on that drama I was on, I was with Yoshimoto's team
I was talking to them about bringing in gifts,
I was wondering what sort of gifts I could give out, and what time to do it
So on that day I told them to bring in the gifts,
I was waiting for someone to say "Tanaka-san brought these in for you guys"
But nobody said that,
But at 10-11pm, after the last cut of the last scene, exactly after the work ended,
Someone said; "Tanaka-san brought some cherries in for you guys"
I get what you mean
At 10, 11pm, after the shooting wraps up,
who would want to eat cherries?
They wanna go home
There were these paper cups with 5-6 cherries lined up on a table,
So the staff would grab the cherries on their way out
Who? Like who would appreciate this?
-Is what I'm thinking
Like is this alright?
It's bad timing
Is this a claim against Yoshimoto?
This is a claim against Yoshimoto
So Yoshimoto's drama team did all that,
But sometimes you get these gifts that are like, the hell is this?
Yeah, there are
They do make you go "The hell is this?"
That drama staff that brought in the gifts,
They had no idea what it was, so they said
"Tanaka-san brought some jelly looking snacks for you guys"
They just didn't know
So stuff like that happens,
They try to be a little fancy
Cliche gifts are just fine, right?
Like last time,
Like that tofu
A normal gift is fine
For "Ashita Ga Aru Sa", they had that Coca-Cola the sponsors provided
"Ashita Ga Aru Sa" is an NTV drama that all Gaki members except Yamasaki appeared on
There was like a mountain of drinks
Sorry, can we stop this
Hosei-san's face has become gloomy
If we keep talking about this,
Re:Japan
TN: Re:Japan is the musical group for the drama ... that Hosei wasn't in
His face becomes like that when we talk about that
What is "Ashita Ga Aru Sa?"
We were in it remember?
It was a long time ago
I've never heard of it, I don't know what that is
I don't know a thing about it, I don't know it!
We were on Kouhaku too
TN: Kouhaku is a New Year's Eve music special that competes with No Laughing Batsu
Nope, doesn't ring a bell
On Kouhaku Uta Gassen
We were on Kohaku
I was watching Gaki on New Year's Eve
You don't remember that happened?
I even show up in Gaki No Tsukaiiiiii
What an annoying way to talk