The Unholy Axis Presents:
Typesetting
Sacro
Translating
Clippy
QA
John Dread
Gaki no Tsukai presents the 3rd
Chiki Chiki  Never Been There Before, Let's Ask Their Best 3
Never Been There Before, Let's Ask Their Best 3!!
Matsumoto Hitoshi    Hamada Masatoshi
Tsukitei Hosei        Endo Shozo        Tanaka Naoki
We used to do Best 5, but
Today's Plan
The 5 guys go to a town they've never been to
and they will ask the locals for info to determine that town's Best 3
Yes, that's right
It reduced by 2
Yes, they reduced it by 2 because Hamada made some complaints
Like, "There's too many" or "Let us go home already"
Really?
You made complaints?
I didn't say a damn thing
1 metropolitan area, 6 prefectures, all train stations
1 metropolitan area, 6 prefectures
All of their train stations are in here
Right
Before, we got Chiba and Chiba
T/N: Chiba is a prefecture in Japan just to the east of Tokyo. It's also where Narita Airport is located.
Kanto is the eastern region of Japan that includes Tokyo, Kanagawa, Saitama, and other prefectures.
Rules
They will pick a lottery with all train stations in Kanto written on them.
If even 1 of them have visited that place before, it is disqualified.
Yes, we did have Chiba and Chiba
Matsumoto, you pick this time
Oh right, Chiba and Chiba
That's right, we've already had Chiba and Chiba
Yep, so far it's been Chiba only
What was picked last time?
T/N: Shinanomachi is a station within Shinjuku, Tokyo.
Shinanomachi
I have a feeling that the pick before that was very different...
Yokohama!
And the town is...!
This is pretty good
Iwahara...
T/N: Iwahara is a station in the Kanagawa prefecture.
Iwahara
I don't think I've heard of it
Iwahara?
I've never heard of it
I've never heard of this either!
Find it, Hosei
I have to find it on here?!
Iwahara!
Finding it on here would be amazing
Iwahara?
[Staff] It's on the Izuhakone Railway Line
T/N: The Izuhakone Railway is a private company that serves in the Kanagawa and Shizuoka prefectures.
Izuhakone Railway Line??
What... No way
It's over here
Found it!
Iwahara... Uwahhh...
This is...
Iwahara
Where is this?
There it is!
That is one hell of a pick
Yes, it is
Huh? What?
[Staff] It's an unmanned station
T/N: Unmanned train stations are stations without any railway staff to ensure payment, safety, etc. Only really small towns would have an unmanned station.
What?! Unmanned station?!
An unmanned station...
We don't know if there will be anything at all
2 weeks later
Alright everyone
We are in Kanagawa prefecture, in Minamiashigara City
Tokyo
Yamanashi
Kanagawa
Fukuoka
Minamiashigahara
Izuhakone Railway Line
Iwahara
And we've made it to Iwahara Station
Wow... Iwahara is very nice
There ain't nothing nice about it
"There ain't nothing nice about it"?!
Well, no...
There's no way there's "nothing nice about it"
Yes, I agree
We're only starting
Yes
It's so far
Starting from rank #3, they start asking for info
Without delay, they start from #3 on the rankings by asking for information
Look, there's a student
Oh hello
Hello!
That one...
Let's start with the one with the forehead
Excuse me!
Hello!
May we ask you something?
Yes?
Oh my! Very proper
His forehead
Are you okay?
Hi
Did you get hurt in a competition?
Looks like you were hit with a chisel or something
Oh
I practice judo
Oh, judo
Resident for 18 years: Kimura
Third Place Recommendation is...?
Born and raised in Iwahara, Kimura's recommendation
Rank #3 is...?
And now, your recommendation
What would you...
Kimura-kun, what makes you think, "It's gotta be this!"?
When you think of Iwahara...
There's nothing...
No, there's no way
No, there has to be something
He's hurt
There's blood...
He's hurt...
There HAS to be something...
There's gotta be something
You definitely can't say that to people
You can't
There's people who will hit you for it
In your opinion, #3
Ignore #1 and #2 for now
There really isn't anything...
No, you can't say that
If you say that, people are going to...
There's gotta be something!
This is your hometown
C'mon, there's something
Is that what you...
Is it because #1 and #2
can't be mentioned at all so you can't say...
Or is there really nothing at all?
There's really nothing
Is there really nothing?
There's really nothing at all?
There's nothing?!
Then I don't want to do this!
I don't want to do this anymore!
Continuing on, the next person they ask is...
Ogura Family
This family that lives in the neighborhood
Alright alright
We're going around, asking for the Best 3
And we're looking for #3
They all went out of business
Oh really
Unfortunately
Oh no, they went out of business...
It's very unfortunate
They ALL went out of business?
Yes, all of them
All of them going out of business is impressive in its own way
"Grill Toshio"
This is different
She says, "Grill Toshio"
"Grill Toshio"?
That sounds nice
Sounds delicious
What the hell is "Grill Toshio"?
"Grill Toshio"?
It's next to where Family Mart used to be
T/N: Family Mart is a Japanese convenience store chain.
Is what she says
Wait, next to Family Mart...
That's...
Family Mart?
But it actually exists, right?
Does it still exist?
It's there, right?
Uh huh, it's there
Grill... Toshio
Toshio
Grill Toshio, got it
Grill Toshio
Hm, what's good there?
Are you okay?
What should we eat there?
You're just clenching your teeth
This entire time, he's just been messing with the back of your head
You've been clenching your teeth, but are you okay?
And also...
There's an old man in the small window up there
Hello
He likes it
He must really like that
Hello mister
You like hiding over there
We're looking for the Best 3 in this town...
Does anything come to mind for you?
He sure likes it
I just moved here so I don't really know
What?
You just moved?
They said "Grill Toshio"
They said it's good
But...
Just stop talking to the old man upstairs
Mister, if you could come down here...
Enough of that!
Enough of that
There's a place with good barbecued meat!
Oh, there it is!!
Oh there
See, now he's saying something
He's jamming his face through the railings!
Are you okay?!
If he were a lion, that could've been bad
They part ways with the old man in the window
They head towards rank #3, Grill Toshio
Have you guys been to a place called Grill Toshio?
Yes, I have
Is it good?
Yes!
What's good there?
What's good there...
Your recommendation
Pork cutlet!
Soba
T/N: Soba is Japanese buckwheat noodles.
But you guys definitely went for soba, didn't you?
Well, just for today
Today is soba
Oh it's here
It's suddenly there
Is this the place?
It was this close by
It's kind of got a marine aesthetic
It's a western style restaurant
T/N: They mean "western" in the sense of it having influence from western countries.
"Grill Toshio"
Go ask them if it's okay to film
Yeah, that's right
Okay, I'll go ask
Think it's okay?
Lunch bento?
Oh, lunch
Filming Negotiations
That's until 2pm, and then...
Immediately, Endo goes in for the filming negotiation
We're part of a TV program and we'd like to film...
He has such a sense of duty
Pardon me
We're good
Oh, it's okay?
Great!
Go ahead
So... This is #3, right?
There's other customers here too, so...
#3!
#3?
There's other customers in here too, just to let you know
#3
Grill Toshio
I wonder what Toshio is like
Pardon us
The owner Toshio, yeah
Everyone scoot to the back
Please excuse us
Toshio-san?
Yes?
Oh, you are Toshio-san!
Are you Toshio-san?
Yes, I am Toshio
Thank you very much
Thank you, Toshio-san
Katsu Pilaf
T/N: Katsu is fried pork cutlet. It's a sort of Japanese comfort food.
Cheese Hamburg Steak Pilaf
Tonkatsu Hamburg
Steak Set
Oh, this looks good
This is what you came up with, right, Toshio-san?
Yes, that's right
It came from a staff meal
T/N: Staff meal as in the food that all the restaurant employees would eat before or after their shift.
Oh, from a staff meal!
So that's why you have dishes like katsu
It was really good, so we thought about putting it on the menu
How long have you been doing this?
This restaurant, about 46 or 47 years
Established for 47 years, a western restaurant loved by the locals
Grill Toshio
A comforting western restaurant, continued to be loved by the locals
Choosing a dish
First, they choose a dish they want to order
But Hosei...
But then, Hosei...
How about the lunch set?
Their lunch hours are over
It's only until 2
Oh, it's okay
Toshio-san
Toshio-san is so kind
You must be pretty hungry
Amazing
From that way you're ordering
Can you eat a full meal alone?
Sure I can
The portions seem pretty big
That's right
Yes, the portions are big
Then we'll get one lunch set
One lunch set
And uh...
Katsu Pilaf and the Katsu Curry
And Katsu Curry, got it, thank you
Thank you
That lady is his daughter, right?
Is it?
It definitely has to
Looks like it
Are you Toshio-san's daughter?
Yes I am
See?
Is your name Toshiko?
T/N: Many girl's names end with -ko, which means child. Such as Sachiko, Tomoko, Chieko, etc.
Haha, no it is not
It is not
Oh, it's not
Further more
Further more, behind them is...
Here?
This is his son
Wait, of here?
Yes
Toshio-san's son
Oh, is that right
Really?
Toshiya-san?
T/N: Toshiya is a fairly common boy's name.
Why do you keep starting everyone's name with "Toshi"?
Don't just assume everyone's some variation of "Toshi"
Toshiya-san, what do you do for a living?
You're not Toshiya, right?
I'm Hiroshi
Hiroshi
Hiroshi-san
Waited for 10min
Waited for 10 minutes
Even though the lunch hours are over
We asked them to make one, so it might take a long time
Oh I see
Because lunch is already over
You should just eat some of the bento in the green room, what the hell is wrong with you?
I did
Even though I already ate a bento, I'm still hungry
We haven't even done anything
And just then
Thank you for waiting, here's the lunch bento
Yes, please put it in the middle
Wow
This is for you, Hosei, we have our own dishes coming
We have our own coming
But really, look at this...
T/N: Roughly around $6.75 USD.
This is only 750yen!
Lunch Bento 750yen
Are you serious?
So cheap!
It even comes with miso soup!
This is so cheap!
This is very cheap
This is very nice
And then
This is the Katsu Pilaf
If you could just place it here
Wow, this looks good too
Oh this is very nice!
Wow
They all come with miso soup
And now the Katsu Curry
This looks so good!
I'll put it right here
This is the Katsu Curry?
This is the normal portion?
Yes, this is the regular size
Katsu Pilaf
The recommended Katsu Pilaf and Katsu Curry
are large servings filled with Toshio's love
Katsu Curry
Is it good?
The katsu is so good
You can't go wrong with curry
You're right
Very delicious
Ding
What? She's right there!
The katsu is very delicious
Is it delicious?
Thank you very much, I'm very glad you like it
Thank you
Stuffing their faces with exquisite katsu
The four chow down on the exquisite katsu
Waiting for Hosei
Within no time, it's finished and now they wait for Hosei
We're just waiting for Hosei now
I'm actually good now
I'm done
I'm good
Since the old days, he mashes up his food with his chopsticks
He does have this habit
All the time, when he does this
I can't even go, "Then I'll eat it for you"
Huh? Really?
No way! I can't eat it if you squish it disgustingly
Yes, that's a bit much
We even said, "You gonna eat all that?" and he doesn't
He's like a dog that digs a hole to store his bones
Who are you doing this for?
Go over to the park and find a place that can act as a doggy bag
How embarrassing
T/N: Taking leftovers home in a to-go container is not a common practice in Japan. Many restaurants do not carry any takeout containers.
If you want to take home leftovers, we have takeout containers for you for free.
Please ask an employee.
Hosei ended up not finishing his meal so he takes his leftovers to-go
To-go
They packed it up for me
Thank you for the meal
#3 Western cuisine restaurant "Grill Toshio"
And with that, #3 in Iwahara is
a humble western cuisine restaurant run by Toshio, who will be 70 years old this year, and his daughter
Confirmed
"Grill Toshio" has been confirmed
To the station again
To get information about #2, the five go back to the train station
They're curious about the old man, however...
It's closed
It's okay, he'll definitely come out
Could you hold my jacket?
But the old man only just moved here
Will he come out?
He won't know, he only just moved here
T/N: The clapping that Matsumoto is doing is part of the ritual for when you pray at a Shinto shrine. The clapping shows respect for being able to meet with the Gods/spirits.
There he goes again...
He won't come out, right? If he did, that'd be amazing
No no no, it won't work...
He came out before
Before, yes
He's praying, like he's asking for good fortune
If he comes out from this, then this was pre-planned
He's sleeping
Yeah, this isn't...
Ahh, looks like he's not going to reveal himself
Oh my
Oh look! Matsumoto-san!
Look, there's some movement
Oh!
Hello, mister!
Thank you
Are you kidding me?
Really??
No way!
Hello, good day!
Seriously?
We got some food!
Oh really?
It was delicious!
Come have a drink
Wait, is it okay for us to come into your home?!
He says it's okay
What rank is this!
This is a special thing, not a ranking
What??
For Iwahara
This will become second in Iwahara's best
Can all of us come up?
Come on in!
Shall we go?
Let's go up there
Let's go
Recommendation Extra!
To Mr. Nagatsuka's Home!!
And so, we will take a visit to Mr. Nagatsuka's home
Hello
Excuse us
Come in
Oh yes, thank you
Matsumoto-san and him, just the two of them
Come on, let's go then
Pardon us
Sorry there's not much space
Not at all, you just moved in recently, right?
Wanna drink shochu?
T/N: Shochu is a Japanese liquor which is usually made from either barley, sweet potato, or rice. Very similar to Korean soju.
Well, we're currently filming on-site...
One glass won't hurt, right?
Oh uh... Sure...
Then maybe...
Hello
What are we having?
Shochu okay?
We're going with shochu...
Oh then I'll just have 1 drink. Might as well
What the hell are you doing?
The nice man is offering to make me a cocktail
A cocktail?
Huh?!
We have to go find first and second place
Couldn't this place be  first place in a sense?
Dairy Product
Black Tea
Shochu
Special Cocktail
Taking his kind offer, Matsumoto will drink Mr. Nagatsuka's special cocktail
Is it strong?
Maybe I should've added water
It's actually not that good
It's not good?
Wait, it doesn't taste good?
But it's drinkable
The cocktail that he made you?
So far
Is that even a cocktail?
Iwahara
At the train station,
Interviewing for
Second Place
For Iwahara's Best 3 recommendations,
the members go to the train station to ask around about second place
We're looking around Iwahara for...
5 months old
5 months old?!
Iwahara Residential Moms Group
Second Place recommendation is?
They speak to a group of moms who seek to raise their children in Iwahara
Third place is "Grill Toshio"
We've found third place
We'd like to know what would be second and first
Second place
Second place is that bar over there
No, that was...
That's not even a bar
That's not really a bar
A bar? Was it?
Anything is fine
Yuuhi no Taki
T/N: "Yuuhi no Taki" is the name of the waterfall that translates to "Waterfall of the Sunset".
Oh no way
That sounds good
Yuuhi no Taki?
There is a waterfall
A waterfall?
So you hike up there?
Do you climb up a mountain path?
Yes, that's right
Then this should be... Endo's responsibility
No no no, the last time--
Filmed: October 15th, 2017
Outskirts of Iwai Station Recommended Best 5
We'll all go there out of obligation
And then once you get ahead, you can walk the rest alone
We won't go to the end
Why aren't we deciding with Rock Paper Scissors?
It's decided that it's me?
I mean, for now...
Even if you say that, in Rock Paper Scissors...
I didn't even lose and I had to endure that [cocktail]
Ashigara Pass
Yuuhi no Taki
Daiyuuzan
Iwahara
Transport to Yuuhi no Taki commence!
T/N: Mount Kintoki is also known as Mount Ashigara.
And now, they head to Yuuhi no Taki that is on Mount Kintoki by car
Oh wow, there's cherry blossoms
Very nice
It's full bloom in Tokyo, right?
Yes, I think so
Yes, full bloom
Finding first place will be hard
God told me of a barbecue place, you know
Did you guys get barbecue yet?
Oh not yet, but we'll go, what's it called?
Yanagi
Yanagi?
There's Yanagi
Is it-is it close?
It's really famous, so...
So he's God, that man?
What is he the god of?
He's uh... Kind of a...
The source of all happiness, it seems
The source of all happiness??
You know, he had those two dogs, right? They did something bad
They used to be human, but they were transformed into dogs
It's so beautiful, see the cherry blossoms?
Cherry blossoms, yes
I don't really find cherry blossoms to be that pretty
Huh? Why?
Are they pretty?
Yes, cherry blossoms are beautiful
In regards to cherry blossoms everyone is always saying...
"Cherry blossom this, cherry blossom that" too much, I think
So you're saying the focus on cherry blossoms is too much?
Yes, that's right
But that's normal for cherry blossoms, isn't it?
But this is probably
related to the climate too, right?
The feeling that it's getting warmer
Feels like the start
If you say it just about the flower...
That's right, Endo gets it
Right?
"Where do you want to go for an international trip?"
Everyone always says "Hawaii"
Yeah, that's probably number 1
People always take distance...
And money into consideration
If everything was free, then
the answer would definitely NOT be Hawaii!
That always pisses me off
"Which..."
"Which city would you like to live in?"
You gotta think about the rent!!
If all the rent were the same, then the answer would absolutely be the Tokyo metropolitan area!
Those kinds of surveys are such shit!!
Was he always like this?
Which side are you annoyed with?
Has he always been like this?
Come on, what is happening?
How did you come to feel this way?
You guys know more than anyone else
I haven't known him nearly as long as you have, Hamada-san
Well, I've always thought that he has this side to him, but...
Was he like this since elementary school?
What happened all of a sudden?
You're in rage
I finally see the sign
But
Oh you're right
There it is, Yuuhi no Taki
Yuuhi no Taki...
These cherry blossoms are pretty, huh?
He said the cherry blossoms are pretty
Cherry blossoms...
The cherry blossoms...
You didn't listen to a damn thing I said
Didn't listen to your senpai's once in a lifetime boke!
T/N: In case you're not a weeb, "senpai" means upperclassman or senior. Basically, someone you respect due to age, rank, etc. "Boke" is a part of Japanese comedy, based on making airheaded jokes.
You've got to be kidding me
Didn't even get that riled up about it
Ashigara Pass
Yuuhi no Taki
Daiyuuzan
Iwahara
Arrival at nearby parking lot
After a 20 minute drive,
they arrive at a nearby parking lot
But even here, you can hear the sound of water pretty well
They head towards Yuuhi no Taki by foot
Head towards "Yuuhi no Taki" by foot
What kind of games do you play with your kids?
Look, we can see where our current location is
Oh okay. That's big
So... The waterfall is...
Our current location and "Yuuhi no Taki"...
Is this it?
Just as I thought
Waterfall, waterfall, waterfall... Waterfall of the Sunset~
Well I mean, this is kinda nice
Yes, the atmosphere
Very nice!
There's something over there
So I guess you go up there
Ah, yes, most likely
Should be nearby
This is really nice
It's so beautiful
What exactly have you been calling beautiful?
Like the water
The water?
If you're talking about water, then tap water is beautiful too!
You got told
Why do I have to get yelled at?
Advancing into the forest
When they advance further into the forest...
I'm sure it'll be fine
There it is!
Oh, you're right, look
You're right!
Should we go?
It's so close!
So nice!
So close
That was very nearby
We will arrive at Yuuhi no Taki shortly
Yes, Yuuhi no Taki
Yes it is
Yuuhi no Taki
Yay!
He's so far ahead of us
He's so excited
Ahead of us
Did he always love waterfalls?
Why did he suddenly get so excited?
Matsumoto-san...
Amazing!
This is very amazing
Ain't it amazing?
Wow, this is impressive!
Amazing
This is nice
Wow, this is so nice
Very nice
Impressive, impressive
This is nice
Yes, very nice
Was it okay with all of us?
T/N: Matsumoto is doing the ritual for praying to God, which is the same thing he did when he was summoning the old man at the window.
He's not going to come out
Yeah, but...
If he came out from there that'd be terrifying!
Yuuhi no Taki
The fall distance of the waterfall is 23 meters, just upstream from Sakawa River, Yuuhi no Taki is...
T/N: For those who use freedom units, 23 meters is roughly 75.5 feet.
Fall Distance
Approx. 23 meters
The Legend of Kintaro
Where that legendary Kintaro had his first bath as a baby. It is an extraordinary power spot.
T/N: The Legend of Kintaro is a famous Japanese folktale about a boy with super strength who grew up in the mountains. Some say that he is based on a real man, a samurai by the name of Sakata Kintoki. Kintaro is referenced in many different media like anime, kabuki, art, etc.
The Legend of Kintaro
Extraordinary
Power Spot
T/N:  Power spots are places with great spiritual energy. Many Japanese people visit these places of spiritual significance to rejuvenate themselves in hopes of gaining greater powers. They usually are places that are important to Shinto/Buddhist religions or are historical spots.
This is it right? The water has negative ions
T/N: Negative ions appear naturally in many places, including where water collides. Although there isn't scientific proof of the effects of negative ions, it seems to have some perceived positive effects like reducing stress or preventing the growth of harmful bacteria. Take this with a grain of salt.
Oh, I see
This is
The splashing of the water causes negative ions
Amazing
Indeed, this is amazing
The water is really rushing
There's no pollen here, right?
Ah right, there wouldn't be any here
What the hell is he doing?
He's hogging it all to himself
I wonder why
I want to be struck by the water
T/N: You've probably seen in other Japanese shows or movies, but standing under a waterfall is a training from Buddhist and Shinto origins to focus and test yourself.
About how many meters is this?
Struck??
Well, you could...
Wanna go get struck?
It's just a thought
I WANT to be struck
It starts and ends with just a desire
No really, I'm serious
No one's stopping you
No, I'm really saying this for real
Although we don't know if it's okay to get in or not
Ah yes, that's true
That's a good point
I see
We got the okay to film it, but...
Whether it's okay to get in or not is...
Getting in the water and being filmed
could cause a lot of problems, so...
That might be asking for too much
Are you okay?
Let's go
You're trying to rush us to leave
It took us so long to get here and we're leaving already?
Let's stay here a little longer, since we came all this way
A little more...
If we stay here any longer
they're going to get permission and force him in
They're going to ask for permission?
So before we get permission...
Asking for permission from the Board of Tourism
Given this situation, they ask for permission from the Board of Tourism
It's okay, you don't need to make a call
There's no rush in calling them
Are you an idiot?!
Wait wait wait, wait a minute
Are you serious?
Well, it came from your mouth, Hosei-san...
No, I just wanted to express my desire
I didn't say anything about actually doing it...
Are we not allowed to say, "I want to"?
Am I not allowed to unless I carry out my words?
And then...
They don't endorse it, but
"You will bear full responsibilities" is what they said...
So... We can?
No, we can't, right?
He said we can
If you can take responsibility...
Let's do it
In any case, the result is we got the okay
Result is, we got the okay
Yes, we can
You're kidding me?!
Can this really happen!?
I ONLY SAID, "I WANT TO..."
I DIDN'T SAY "I WILL..."
I DIDN'T SAY THAT
And so
Off to Yuuhi no Taki!!
Will my body be okay?
Off to Yuuhi no Taki!
It's March...
Yes it is
I'm going in
Yuuhi no Taki
Everyone come over here
Air Temperature 15° Celsius
T/N: For those who use freedom units, 15° Celsius is 59° Fahrenheit.
Ahh, this is cold!
Hosei, go to the right, the right!
Watch out!
Go down there through the right side!
Take your time, it's freezing!
COLD!
This!
This is so cold!
Ease into it
Oh well, there he goes
SO COLD, SO COLD!!
You'll get used to it!
COLD!
WAIT A MINUTE
COLD!!
That will definitely be freezing cold
I said it's cold
Oh my, it's so cold
Oh wow, it's right in front of him!
Note: We obtained special permission to film.
If you choose to get into a waterfall,
it is your own responsibility.
Right there
Second place
Yuuhi no Taki
This is going to bring you good luck
Wow, this is really...
You're doing good, just a little more
Slowly, don't rush it
Go slowly, slowly
Slowly!
AHHHHHHHHHHH!!
T/N: It might sound like he's saying something, but it's unintelligible chanting/yelling.
THAT WAS TOO FAST!
TOO FAST!
A little more, a little more
*More unintelligible yelling*
Too fast!
Hosei-san, just a little more!
10 seconds!
Get right in the middle of it!
We didn't get the shot!
You can totally see his bald spot
So cold...
Cold...
We know it was cold, but...
Did it hurt?
What is the #1 best thing in Iwahara?
It hurts
Did it?
It... It's freezing
Freezing...
Next week, nearby Iwahara Station Recommended Best 3 Part 2
Next week, nearby Iwahara Station Recommended Best 3, Part 2!
I offer you my love~
♫
Their goal is a row of cherry blossom trees
Hey, what the hell is this?
However!
We've been tricked
We were completely duped
What will happen next?
*More unintelligible chanting*
Too fast!