Gaki no Tsukai Dressing Room
The usual Gaki no Tsukai backstage
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Do you have any clue what this thing here could be?
It kinda feels like herpes, I really don't know
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Tsukitei Housei
Cocorico
Endo Shouzo
General Director ::::::::
World Famous Heipo::
Oh I know, I also got them when I've was lickin-
What the heck!
Don't attempt such dirty jokes against your will!
It pisses me off
I know right?
What was that for?
Excuse me
Excuse me!
'Morning
Good mornin'
License
Fujiwara Kazuhiro   Inomoto Takafumi
And we're in
'Morning
It was about time
I knew you two would pop out
More importantly,
What's the reason for the shirt they made you wear?
We've been told to wear them from Tanaka
He did?
note: On the shirt "OUR TANAKA"
Yes
It's on the back too
Pretty powerful
It's TOO MUCH for me
To be honest we really don't know
But he said "I can now see what was dim before"
I have already enough of this
I feel you
He also said "Anyway, just come"
Hey!!
Where do you think you are stopping?
Oh I'm sorry...
YOU'RE ON MY WAY!
All the rage towards the world came back inside this human
They worshipped the man carrying all this madness like this...
OUR
TANAKA
On their way to the studio where Tanaka is waiting
It appears that his madness has awakened once more...
Wha-?
Good morning !!
Oh, there he is
What's going o-   - Good Morning!
This is filthy
I'm sorry!
Something fishy it's going on
What's that? I think I may or may not seen it before
Exactly
You know
There has always been something that made me feel uneasy
I swear
What's that?
You know, on our "No Laughing" series...
I've always been thai-kicked
Without any sort of explanation, unreasonably
Well, if you say "unreasonably" keep in mind that we go through some pretty unreasonable stuff too
That's because the program itself is unreasonable
Hey, Tanaka! Look here!
You're getting a thai-kick, scum!
At the end of the year, on our "No Laughing" serie, as a custom
I had enough!
All the unreasonable thai-kicks kept on happening
IT HURTS I CAN'T STAND THIS ANYMORE!
This is the reason for Tanaka's madness
So basically
Total of times it happened during No-Laughing series till now: 8 times
What I had been thinking all the time
Is that it would be way better to thai-kick someone
Rather than being thai-kicked myself
Tanaka's realization:ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooi
It's better to perform a thai-kick rather than receiving it
Not anything I wasn't expecting him to say
Yeah, I can understand him
Yeah but the way he speaks...
It's too much  - There's no hatred in his tone
So, ya know...
He didn't hear a thing we said
Today
What I'm gonna do
Is to call here on this studio all the people who recently made me angry
For what they did or said on TV
What?
What's the deal? - Yes
You mean tv stars?
Exactly
So basically
I'll ask them lotsa questions
And I'm gonna thai-kick the hell outta them
As soon as they make me angry
I think there's gonna be more than a problem with this
Tanaka's realization:ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooii
Questions to the guests ➡ thai kick if they make him mad
I want to make them taste
Whether or not
A rage-induced thai-kick is unreasonable
Eh?
I don't think it's a good thing
What do those people think they're coming to do here today?
They're coming believing it's an episode of "we've asked 100 people"
"We've asked 100 people"?
I mean, "100 things"
Quiz: 100 Thingsoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooii
It's a show were, in the form of a quiz-show, the guests arei
asked about their private life / way of thinking & behaving
So they think they're gonna be interviewed
I'll call out the guests
Making them think it's "100 things"
Yeah but, isn't it kinda awful?
It's worth it
Ok but...
Have you ever met em all before?
Like, just 2-3 of them
Everything just became more awful!
Let's just stop
I told you today I'm gonna go for it
No way
Tonight, Tanaka will strike the unreasonability of thai-kicks
In the arse of comedians who don't know anything about !!
IDOL
ACTOR
MUSICIAN
TV STAR
TRANS
MANZAI
ARTISTS
Translation, subtitles & encoding by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
More clips? Subscribe to this channel: Shionの使い
Find all my other subtitled clips on this channel or on my wordpress:
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Support my translations by clicking like my Facebook page:
facebook.com/shionnotsukai
Rules:ooooooooooooooooooooooooOOOOOOOOOOOOOoOooooooi
Tanaka will ask questions to the comediansoooooooooooooooooo
If he gets angry, he'll push the voice-button and strike a thai-kick
I think it's also pretty harsh for us to just stay here and watch
We didn't do anything to begin with
Right
Besides---   - Our first guest's entering!   - What, for real?
My heart is kinda racing
I wonder who's coming
I'm coming in!
Good morning
Oh
Oh, it's Shinoyama-kun
'Morning
G'Mornin'～ !!
Good morning
G'Mornin'!
Uhh, well, Tanaka is...
Somehow today Tanaka's acting a bit strange...
So sorry for that
Stand right here, here!
Why don't we have him talk to you first?
Endo knows him, right?
Do you know each other?
Nope !!
Err... nice to meet you
'Sup
Get here
Right here, yes   - This is somehow incredible
TV STARPPP
SHINOYAMA
AKINOBUPP.
His father is Shinoyama Kishin, his mother Minami Saori
He's currently working on NHK as a reporter etc. for "asaichi"
Akinobu Shinoyama
Both his father and mother are famous characters
And he's the thouroughbred of the entertainment industry
Something that infuriates Tanaka!
This is bad, this--
So, ya said your parents are famous, huh?
Who's ya pops?
"Pops", he said
Well I think...
My dad's huhhh...
I think that's a pretty rude way to refer to him
He's a photographer, he's also a writer
Right, I read that
Who's ya mama, huh? Huh?!
Who's ya mama?
She...
She... used to be a singer bac-
A singer ya say?
Yes a singer, Minami Saori...
So today you recorded huh?
※On this day, Shinoyama shot the live broadcast for NHK'S "Asaichi"
It was a live broadcast, huh? I've watched that
Yes, it was for my morning news program     - Oh, is that so?
And I had to shot my relay as a repor-
Ya totally sucked at being funny
What does it have to do with him?   - He's not a comedian, you know
Tell me now
Yes?
What club were ya in at school?
My club?
Yeah, tell me what club activity ya were doin'
He's asking a lot...    - Yeah
My club...
I've always been doing
Both soccer and the drama club
Which kind of drama?
More than acting on a play
I took part in several musicals in english back th--
Are ya sayin' ya can speak english?
To be honest I can't speak it at all
Try sayin' something in english that ya like
Something in english that I like?
Just tell me somethin'
English words I like...
I guess in the end
Th-that's got to be "LOVE" or something...
What's going on?
Shinoyama: Thai-kick
Wait that's---
Stand there!
Excuse me but...
Weren't we supposed to do the "100 thin-
So predictable, "LOVE" or something
W-wait
Oh, so that's how you're gonna do it?
Hold him, License
Why a thai-kick...?
Huh? Tanaka-san... what's going on?
A thai-kick
W-wait...
This is scary
Are you for real?
UGH
I bet that hurt
It definitely hurts
Are you ok?     - We're sorry for that
What was that for?
I bet he's angry        - Yeah, it was painful
He... he's not listening to us
Now ya free to go, c'mon
A-are we done already?
Yup we're done here dude
C'mon you can go now
But... haven't you said you've watched my morning program, before?
I did
By the moment I was done with it
I rushed to come here from Katsuura, in Chiba
I see
※It takes roughly 3 hours from Katsuura to this stage
So you got here in hurry to do the 100 things show
Yeah I've been told we were going to do that
Yeah yeah, we're done with it, it's over
CRUSHED
SHINOYAMA AKINOBU
That kick... was for real?
Yeah it was
Tanaka, let's just stop this
It's no good if you do that for real   - Yeah dude
Don't worry it's ok
On top of that
there's no connection between Katsuura and Thailand
I think the next one is about to come too
Really?
Yeah
I'll have you look at it
Well I think that may be a problem
- Yeah, I'm really bad at this...
He even said "nice to meet you"
Sorry for the wait
The guest will be entering now
Alright, there it is!
Who will it be?
I'd say it would be better to stop this
Yeah, like, just being here watching is--
Good morning!
Mornin' !
Morn---
G'Mornin', mornin'
A girl is...
Maybe it's a bit harsh if it's a girl, Tanaka
IDOLPPP.
KIKUCHI
AMIPP.P_
She debuted as the 16th member of "Idoling!!!"
Now she's an indispensable being in variety shows
Ami Kikuchi
The fact that she's the idol who appears the most on variety shows
Made Tanaka snap!
Get over here
You're being rud-
Here
What is this?
Nothing nothing nothing, don't worry
Huh? Oh I see
Questions... was it?
May ya tell me ya name?
Ami Kikuchi
Ami Kikuchi, huh?    - Yes
I'm 22
Where ya from, huh?
From Hokkaido
Hokkaido?
And since when ya came here to Tokyo?
Since I was a first grader
Highschool, huh... and what are ya doin' now?
Eh? My Job? I'm an idol
Is there, like, a place ya like to go buy clothes ya often go to?
Yes...
Of course there is
It's Shibuya's 109
109?
Yes
Ya like 109?
Sorry but what is this?
It's ok it's ok    - Just play along
What's with him?
Oi! Ya know,
I've heard 'bout that
About what?
Looks like Hamada-san it's pretty into ya, aight?
Oh, yes
Come on!      - Really?
Yeah that's right I--
S'dat real?!
Yeah, it's true, I swear
How about ya do the opposite thing
Yes..?
And tryna say what's good 'bout Hamada-san instead?
Something appealing?
This pace...
Maybe the fact that he has this image
Moreover, what the hell is this, so irritating!
Of him being seen as a scary guy
He's actually not that at all, he's really nice
Like when we were all together at the lobby...
Wait, have we started already?
Yeah we started
Eh? Wha-- why, this feels somewhat wrong
Who cares 'bout dat?
JUST TELL ME!!
Like when everybody got up at the lobby
He said to everyone "come on, don't worry, stay down"
And whaddya think ya aimin' to be from now on?
How do ya want to be in the entertainment industry from now on?
From now on...
I guess someone like Katsumata-san...
note: I guess she's refering to Shizuoka-born comedian Katsumata Kunizaku
Wha-wha-what's going o---
Kikuchi: Thai-kick
Wh-wh-what's happ-
What's this? It's unsettling
I could have not imagined ya would pick him outta everyone!
What? But why?
You're kidding, right?
This will be painful to watch
You're kidding, right? Right?
It's not just you doing this    - Don't worry
I'm scared...
GYAAAAAAAAAAH
That was surely painful
It totally went "BAMMM"
It made a clap noise!
That's no good
That hurt like hell, what was that for?
I know I was told today we were recording, but...
You can clearly see that bit of regret in his face
You're reconsidering this, aren't you?
You can tell by his face    -  It's getting clearer
Don't say such bullshit...
CRUSHED
KIKUCHI AMI
Tanaka you... you sure you're not reconsidering this?
Ooh no way, I'm not
You su-
It won't happen
No way I'm going to regret this
You're face is becoming a bit twitchy though
You're right
But when this is over you're going to apologize, right?
No no, I won't do that
Even the fact he's doing this with no context for them...
The guest will be entering now
C'mon c'mon c'mon!
Here we are again, starting from the guest's puzzled look
...Good morning
G'mornin' !
Here comes another big one    - This time it kinda...
In a way I think this couldn't be helped
Come here, come here
CHOREOGRAPHERPPP.
PKABA-CHAN
She's the coreographer for songs such as SMAP's "sekai ni hitotsu dake no hana"
Her eccentric look makes her stand out even in the world of transexuals
Kaba-chan
Her eccentric look makes her stand out even in the crossdessers panorama
How is Tanaka going to pick a quarrel?
I want to kick her too    - What's with this style?
Why are you dressed like this?
I want to do it too, Tanaka
What is she holding?
Are ya already makin' fun of me? What's ya name?
Kaba-chan--
Your REAL name?
Eiji Kabashima
Ya age?
I'm 43
She's 43!?
She's 2 years older than us       - 43!
What are ya holdin' in ya left hand?
I would have asked it too
What's inside it?
It's a ladies set
What do ya usually do everyday?
I have a tea with Midori-chan...
Who?!
Who's she
Who's this Midori-chan?
My transvestite friend Midori-chan
My transvestite friend Midori-chan?     - Yes
Oh I see, Midori-chan the trans....
Ya always hang out with Midori-chan?
Yeah
So ya two are basically dating, right?
No no no!
We're both women so that can't be happening
It's nothing like that
Kaba-chan: Thai-kick
Why?
You made me snap!
W-wait
Why? Why?
It's better if you stay still
- Yeah, don't move or it could be dangerous
Huh? Why? Why is this--
Be careful
What are you gonna do?
IT HURTS!
Ouch ouch ouch     - That may have hurt
I think it hurted a bit
Kaba-chan?
Are you hurt?
You can think of it as a sort of vaccination
That way the pain will be duller, right? It's fine it's fine
It was painful...
I bet it was      - What is this?
We're done here, Kaba-chan
Wha-?
We're done with this
Say Kaba-chan...
Do you still have them..?
Facebook: /shionnotsukai  |
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
----------------------
Translation, subtitles & encoding by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
More clips? Subscribe to this channel: Shionの使い
You do?    - I'm guessing so
Yeah I do ♥
I don't like her getting close to me so happily
But
Since I caught Rubella
At the end in January
It seems like my @#%&£ was gone ♥
Should I kick your butt one more time?
After this...PPP.....................................'.
That "HIT MAKER" will appear !!PP.P_
The guest will be entering now
Here comes
Enough of this, Tanaka-kun...
Right?   - We're continuing this
Find all my other subtitled clips on this channel or on my wordpress:
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Are you ok?
Are you for real?
You sure you ok?
G'mornin' !!
It's Jinbo-san
G'mornin' !!    - 'Morning
Good morning
Support my translations by clicking like my Facebook page:
facebook.com/shionnotsukai
Mornin'
I don't know how this will go...
Get ya ass over here
How are you refering to him?   - He's a big senpai, you know
Good morning
ACTORPPPP
JINBOPPPP.
SATOSHIPP.
He's a big actor who starred in several movies and dramas,
His most famous one being "Aibou". This is his first encounter with Tanaka
Satoshi Jinbo
How will Tanaka, who has never meet him before,
Debut in front of this actor he doesn't personally know?
Startin' now I'm gonna make ya a bonch
. . . .
Of questions
"A bonch of questions", he says
Ok
So answer me, ok?
You're close    - That's too close
Let's keep the distance, Tanaka
Ya name is?
Satoshi Jinbo
The way he asks his questions is weird
How old are ya?
I'm 50 years old
He's way older than him
What's ya hobby?
My hobby?     - Yeah
My hobby is golf
How much can ya spin ya golf club?
By now I uhhh
I get around 100 meters or such
Is there a club ya particularly like?
A club I like?
Oh you mean a golf club I'm good with?
Is there?
He has never done it, why is he asking?
I like the Sand Wedge
And whaddya like about SANDWICH?
. . . .
It's not "sandwich", it's "sand wedge"
Not "sandwich"
You're embarrassing
The hell are ya laughin' at?
Huh? Why you ask?
I said, why are ya laughin'?
Well 'cause you said something funny
How about ya try to tell me ya favorite golf-related term?
Do questions like this one exist?
We talkin' 'bout golf terms, tell me ya favorite one, c'mon
"Body" (swing)    - I can see he choose that
And why do ya choose "body"?
Givin' there are a lotsa golf terms why d'ya choose to tell me "body"?
'Cause if I manage to get a body I'm happy
Aren't there other good ones?!
Yeah, like "Eagle"
And why didn't ya say "eagle"?
'Cause I can't really get an eagle
YA PISSING ME OFF !!
What the hell!
Jinbo: Thai-kick
What the hell is this?!
Really, the hell?!
License!!
Please, get over here
The hell, dude
I bet he has no idea what's going on
Do I have to stick out my butt?
Your butt, yeah
THAT HURT!!
That must have hurt, we're sorry for this, Jinbo-san
- I bet that hurts, we're sorry
Man, for real...
Yeah really, this one...
- It looked painful!
Feels like something came out from it
I know what you mean, really
It's just a momentary feeling, it shouldn't last for long
Why was I kicked?
You made him mad 'cause he's doin--
I mean, that's the first time we met
Well technically yeah...
Yup, that's right
We're done here!
Thank you for coming, we're sorry
- Thank you, we're done
But... wasn't I supposed to answer some questions?
There are no questions       - We're done with this
We have to go on now
He looks angr--
Huh!?
License!!     - S-sorry
Thank you!
He looked a bit angry      - Ok  - We're done with this
Tanaka...   - You did something bad
Jinbo-san looked a bit angry
I think Jinbo-san was actually a bit mad
Yeah the way he spoke...
May I?
May I move from this one to the next guy?
CRUSHED
JINBO SATOSHI
MEOTOPPPP.....
MANZAIPPPP...
DUOPPPP.PPPP
KATSUMIPPPP.
& SAYURIPP.....
The meoto (married couple) manzai duo symbolizing Oosaka
Katsumi is a senpai 11 years older than Tanaka, Sayuri 2 years older
The married couple manzai duo, Katsumi & Sayuri
Needless to say, they're both big senpais to Tanaka
How will he attack them?
The atmosphere feels terribly wrong
He's not really acting as the usual Tanaka
He always greets us so happily
Is that so? Why don't you just do that instead?
What's ya name?
You know them
They're senpais, it feels wrong if you talk to them like this
I'm Katsumi!
And I'm Sayuri!
Poyoyo～n !!
The hell was that!?
Wait!    - Calm down!
DA HELL WAS THAT, HUH!?
I've pulled my flowers and went "Poyoy-
DON'T YA DO IT AGAIN !!
Ugh
They will
I mean, they always do it
Right      - Always
I heard ya guys
Are running a shop, aight?
Yeah that's right
What's that?
"Boyoyon Sweets Garden"
It's in Dotonbori    - Yes
note: Dotonbori is a famous street in Osaka
What is this...
It's real, you know
What's ya recommendation from the menù?
You know, that one
S-sweets...
Sayuri: Thai-kick
What do you mean?
What's happening?
Not Katsumi-san?
He's spared
Just Sayuri!
Must be because of her answer     - Yeah
Don't let her go, License!
You're kidding, right? Are you kidding me?
We're sorry, just endure this
Katsumi too has no idea what to think while watching this
Hey be careful, don't--
AAAAAAAAAAAH!!
That was painful
It hurts!
That hurt so bad
It hurts !!
We're sorry for this
Now go!
Oh, looks like it's over
Go!      - Huh?
He usually acts normal, right?
Yeah he's...
He's really polite     - He is, yes
One time
There was this pretty girl on make-up in Osaka who said was a fan
And I went to ask her phone number for him
He just laughed!
Was it me? Ya talkin' to me?
Ya sayin' I told ya to take her number?
CRUSHED
SAYURI
Let's stop this
You heard the "BAM"?
You went through this for many times by now    - Right
I plan on keeping this till the end, one by one
The guest will be entering now
C'mon c'mon c'mon!
I'm enterin--
What is this?     - Well...
It's...      - Mornin'!
'Sup
Cm'here, cm'here
What's this supposed to be?
It's Hyadain...
It's a first time for me too
Right, that's actually the second time we met
Sorry it's just that's different from what I was been told
It figures
Would ya please cm'here?
Sorry, he's nothing like that...
I thought so
Sorry     - Alright!
He's a bit more reserved than this, right?
SINGER /
SONG WRITERPPPP
HYADAINP
Graduated from Kyoto's University's, faculty of Integrated Human Studies
He's an hit maker who composed and wrote music for SMAP, Momoclo etc.
Hyadain
An hit-maker who produced music for a lot of artists
How's Tanaka going to move against him?
What's ya name?
Oh, I'm Hyadain
Age?
I'm 32
Hyadain?    - Hyadain
What's that?
It's a name
My name
What's that?
It's my n--     - Just tell me what's that
A name
Why "Hyadain"?
That...       - He won't say it
I absolutely...
Why is that?
Just search for it online
Let's pretend it didn't pop out, just tell me!
Tell me why it's "Hyadain"
I can say that, you know
C'mon then
But it's not like it's going to be funny or anything
Just tell me anyway
I'll just say it and you pretend it to be funny
The hell are ya talkin' 'bout?
Woah woah let's calm down
Whaddya want?
We're sorry for that
I mean, what's going on?
What is--       - You're too close
How much is ya rent?
Who cares about that?
I mean, it's his rent
My rent?
He may not be renting it
Ya selling lots?
Which is it?
That's no good
So?
From this distance I can see you have lots of freckles
What do ya want?
There there
- You're too close      - Come on
Enough of this!
- Come on, Tanaka!
Why do ya choose the room ya have?
Who cares?
Tell me why you choose it
Let's just stop fussing over this
Dude your teeth are really dirty
Hyadain: Thai-kick
Eh? What do you--
Does it mean that...?
I don't get it!
Are you for re-
IT HURTS !!
What was that for?
It happened so out of the blue
Is it cause I told him his teeth are dirty?
I think he's probably regretting kicking you
Isn't that true?
No I'm not
The hell are ya sayin'
You're actually regretting this, right?
- Huh?
What wouldya gain from me saying "yeah"?
CRUSHED
HYADAIN
Unprecedented unreasonable thai-kicks
How many unreasonable thai-kicks have we went through until now?
All the resounding screams and jeers
note: narrator voice same as the text
And then...
The source of Tanaka's anger will finally show itself
Anyway
"Thai Kick"
We have to call him, if I don't manage to thai-kick him
I can't feel fine at all!
Hyadain: Thai-kick
Tanaka accidentally pushed the voice button he's holding
Oh     - What happened?
He must be agitated
That's nothing good too
This whole thing was completely useless
After this That man will appear!!
The guest will be entering now
Alright
Woah
There he is
Are you for real?
He's really here
It's really him
Is this ok?
Yeah yeah, welcome
Yeah, I was waiting for ya
FORMERPPPPPPPPPPP
MUAY-THAIPPPPPPPP.
RANK 1CHAMPION PP.
ON RAJADUMNERN.....
He's in charge of thai-kicks in the No-Laughing serie
He's the source of Tanaka's anger along the others
He's the source of Tanaka's anger
Who made him face countless hardships
Now he'll finally meet and confront this man!
I wanted to meet ya
What's ya name?
Uh...
My passport is
Hackam Naronpat
My sport is
▲★@■%&●
My nickname
$◆ヱ=￥Ω√
Is
Which is it again?
Hearing is a bit...
Yeah a bit uhm...
Where do ya come from?
Sushi?
note: he mishears "shusshin" (place where you come from) for "sushi"
Eat?
Fish...
I guess he doesnt' understand
"Sushi", right?
Of course he doesn't it's hard    - Yeah, he's from Thailand after all
Alright alright alright
Are ya married or such?
I am
Is there any place ya wife was charmed by?
Play?
Playing what?
He has answered for real, "play"
He could have said "which places does your wife like"
Are ya going out together to play?
Mountain
River
Temple
Cherry tree
I pick her mountain...
I can't take it anymore!!
Tanaka: Thai-kick
It said "Tanaka"
Something's wrong! That's not how it was supposed to go!
As expected, the real deal strikes harder!
It must have hurt
Oh, amazing! How was it?
It was unavoidable at this point
He stored too much grudge from them
Yeah you're right
It friggin' hurts like hell
AFTER THE.
RECORDING
I'm really sorry
- It's ok
Really, forgive me
- Don't worry it's fine!
I'm really sorry for that
- There's no need to apologize
After the recording, he explained the contents of his project
And went to politely ask forgiveness to everyone
Translation, subtitles & encoding by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
More clips? Subscribe to this channel: Shion (ガキの使い用)
Find all my other subtitled clips on this channel or on my wordpress:
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Support my translations by clicking like my Facebook page:
facebook.com/shionnotsukai