Green Room
This was a long drive
DOWNTOWN
HAMADA MASATOSHI
I couldn't find this place
- I'm with you, my GPS didn't find it either
I was expecting a more posh place
YAMASAKI HOSEI
I drove by a bunch of industrial warehouses
COCORICO
ENDO SHOZO
TANAKA NAOKI
First Annual Gaki No Tsukai Ya Arahende!!
Chiki Chiki "Mom, My @#$% Hurts!!"
No need for your mom to be involved really
DOWNTOWN
MATSUMOTO HITOSHI
As I promised last week
I brought the medicine
An Experiment To See How Much
the Medicine Will Hurt Everyone
I just want you guys to know
that I wasn't making it up
My balls were itching the other day
So I headed to the pharmacy
and picked up this medicine
And when I applied just a drop of this
Holy Jesus!!
It knocked the wind outta me!
Seriously
I felt this high pitched
Peeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
That's hilarious
I'm not kiddin'
I was like this
Ahhhhggghhhh!!!!
Then I'm all
Ummmmmmmmmmmmmmm
Peeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee!!!
It really does kill
- This is no joke
My guess is that Nostradamus
knew this was coming
This is a real medicine
you can buy over-the-counter
I haven't added anything funny to it
Let me see it
Yeah, it's for ringworm
Who should start then...
Tanaka
* Not harmful to your body
You put a lot
Hot!
You serious?
- Serious?
Serious?
- Yeah
You're bullshitting
It's really hot!
It's hot?
- It really does makes you that way
You just become immobile
What's the matter?
- It's hot!
It's hot?
- Yes
Does it hurt?
- No, it's hot, really hot
It's just hot!
This is what you can expect
Once it gets in your skin,
it burns and becomes really hot!
Anybody wanting to step up
to this challenge is welcome
How about over there, professional
Lighting-Man
Coolest mustache in the
Lighting Department
LIGHTING
Mr. MIURA
I bet he had no idea this
would happen to him
How about Motoichi then
WRITER
MOTOICHI
Keep thinking you're looking
nice with your sports jacket
Come over here
Whatever you do,
keep it away from your face
Good luck
Isn't this too much?
- No
Serious?
No two should react the same, right?
Ouch
@%$^&*#$%^@@$%^*!!!!
Where're you going?
Nice face!
What's with his face?
You OK?
He's not kidding around
You just can't make any kind
of movement like this
This stuff is insane
Let me try it
After seeing all that,
I gotta try it
No idea how this guy's gonna react
Wait for it
What?
What is...
It's getting warm
It's getting..
Serious
This hurts!!
How long does this last!?
When is this OVER!!??
Ouch Ouch Ouch Ouch
You're sweating hard
- Look at the sweat!!!
Not good
Not good at all
Anybody watching this show...
Where can I wash this off?!
I have to get this off!
Some viewers are probably skeptical
about what's happening here
But this is for REAL!
Ouch Ouch Ouch Ouch Ouch Ouch!!!!
I'm sweating again!
That HURT....
I will never doubt you again
Alright, next up
Heipo, you're up
DIRECTOR
Saito Toshihide (HEIPO)
Let's have two of you
Yamasaki and Heipo
At the same time?
- Yea, like a tag team
* Not harmful to your body
Are you guys ready?
Go for it
I put too much on
Way too much
One common reaction is that
nobody can sit up with it
You're so floored
I'm OK with it
- You're kidding??
It feels rather soothing
We're all different, I guess
Why don't we go all at once?
Like ten of us
It mean all you guys in the back, too
Go ahead and rub it on
All of you guys should have
different reactions to this
Awesome Kodak moment!
What is this, a new religious ritual??
Ouch-Ouch-ism
Well, that should do it
Or, shall I go
Now??
After that orgy we just witnessed,
It's definitely a tough act to follow
I don't wanna kill the buzz
His pain threshold is not that great
He's rather a baby when it comes to the pain
This medicine got the most outta you
THE PAIN OF THE DAY