j-addicts.blogspot.com
Facebook: J-addicts
Good afternoon...
Laura will interview the recruits of the Earth Defense Force
Laura's interview
TN: Laura is a Talent and Model
Good afternoon...
You just came in...
I don't really like this
Seriously it's good...
Fujiwara-san is playing with us...
She enters with a laughter...
She's laughing
She makes you wanna laugh
That girl... instigates laughter...
Laura please be composed...
Please be composed
What you have to say...
I have to instill...
Have to be quiet... quiet
I have to be quiet...
Laura is really bubbly
This is really HARSH
Really, please stop this
Really... please stop this!!
We haven't even gotten into the real scene yet
I'm hurting... hurting
I'm a reporter for the Earth Defense Force Magazine...
And the reporter for the magazine publishing company
I'm here today to interview the new recruits...
Laura will interview the 5 members
I'll ask "here and there" questions to each one
Here and there??
Please listen carefully...
Hamada-san...
Why do you hit people in the head??
Is it fun to hit them?
It's part of my job/work... um...
The role is "Tsukkomi" to "Heighten"...
Well that's the reason
Why are you the only one with breasts?
It's true, you see that
I completely forgot about that
I would be curious too
I never thought of it
On this episode it's like a female recruit.
Alright, I understand...
I'll ask you the next question...
Hamada-san, do you still kiss your wife on your way out?
Please answer the question
I haven't done the kiss on my way out
What, really?
Yes
What does still mean?
Mean in the past you had?
That's right!
Like a routine
Oh... well...
Maybe when we were newlyweds...
How creepy
Maybe when my wife and I were newlyweds
I've been only asking Hamada-san questions...
Yeah
I'll ask Tanaka-san some questions...
That's good... please!
Tanaka-san, do you wash your hair?
What kind of question is that?
It's question that a reporter would ask...
That's what she thinks
Getting beaten up...
I'm hurting
Yes, of course
I wash my hair everyday
I understand
You know what... I'm 23 year old now
My classmate from high school got married
Recently, you know she had a baby
I've been really wanting to meet her husband
I'm gonna meet them soon
What type...
What is the husband like...?
What's the husband like...?
How is he like...?
What kind of husband...
I wouldn't call this an interview
What the...?
I don't care about the husband...
She's just playing with us!
Yeah... I'm playing you all
Playing??
Playing... Like you are "Jerking" us off...
Yeah... I'm "Jerking" you off
When you "Repeated" the sentence... I couldn't hold back!!
They came flying
When you repeated that part... We couldn't resist
You're right!
There's no other way to express it
Hamada-san, how much savings do you have?
I really don't know the exact amount...
um...
I don't really know... I have someone manage it
Is that so... By whom?
Excuse me...
Who manages it?
Like my wifey
Your wifey!
Yes
I bumped into your WIFEY the other time...
His "WIFEY"... yeah WIFEY!
Please support Gaki no Tsukai next year too.