At a certain hot spring, there is an inn where liars gather
Why are you so angry
No no, it's not that I'm mad
I forgot how this thing started
If we started right away or not
Ah I see
Fully Improvised Liar's Inn
The person on the card nominates someone to tell a lie
The nominated person must maintain the lie given to them
Here I go
Yeah go on
Hosei nominates someone to tell a lie
I think it was during the student years, so this is a decades old story,
Matsumoto-san, you went to a vocational school for Onmiyoji right?
TN: Onmiyoji are people that study Onmyodo; "a system of natural science, astronomy, almanac, divination and magic"
Yeah, I did. In fact I still go.
To the Onmiyoji?
I don't really know anything about it
Can anyone go to the classes?
Ah, this is something that's kind of bad to say, I had a rewards points card,
And if you got enough points, you could get into that sort of thing
Eh, you can get that?
I think Hamada can get it too
Really?
It's in the top ten. There's a special catalog for long time customers
Oh yeah there's lots of stuff
You can stay in a hotel somewhere,
Stuff like that
Special prizes
Special prizes and so on. But on the back, is the real thing,
I didn't know about that at all
"You may be able to enter Onmiyoji!"
"May be"?
That's on purpose, like "You might". You can go actually of course,
But on purpose, to catch your attention. Like "You might!".
So it's been, 2, 3, ... 20 years? 20 years I've been doing this Onmiyoji thing
How many points does it cost?
That one, it costs 58,000
It costs 58,000 points
That's quite a lot
Most people, most people spend it on Matsuzaka Beef
If they had that many points? It is quite a lot
Excuse me but,
At this age, marbled beef is very heavy
When you're younger though, you can eat 200-300 grams easily
Enough of that. Are you knowledgeable about it now?
Of course I am, I've been doing it for 20 years
What do you do?
What is Onmiyoji?
Ghost expulsion, and also ghost capture- chewing
Chewing?!
You eat ghosts?
Sometimes I have to chew them, the small ones
It puts people off though so I didn't wanna talk about this
I didn't know about this
I don't wanna say too much
Please tell us (x2)
How do you capture them?
There's different types of ghosts too
So, if I had to explain it, like a Japanese version of Ghostbusters,
That's easy to explain
They use like machines and stuff
You know that start shaped thing? What do you call it, the star thing
I summon them there
By like placing a Banana or something
Banana?
When I wake up in the morning I catch quite a lot
It's like you're capturing insects isn't it?
You use a Banana?
What do you do then?
It depends, on my mood, if I'm hungry I'll chew them
So you are eating them?
You just eat them like that?
You feel the electric shock though,
Electric shock?
Cause there's a thing (barrier) there
You're the one who put it there
Ah, right, I have to break the seal, and then eat them
How do you break it, like this?
Like "I'm gon-na break the seal"
I don't have my notes right now though
You look at your notes?
Even though it's been 20 years?
You can't memorise it! I'll show it to you then, it's super thick
You basically just eat them? Are there big ones too?
There are big ones
What do you do for those ones?
How large are they?
The biggest one
Hmm, I guess about this big
That's not big
You guys don't understand the category!
You don't know! This is huge, the normal ones are this small
Ah, normally they're this size?
Ghosts are like that? I thought they were bigger
You've never seen a ghost before in your lives and yet you're deciding what's big and small
Saying things like "that's small!" pisses me off
I'm done! I'm not talking anymore!
I'm done talking!
Please don't say that. We just don't know anything, I'm sorry
Is it just ghosts around you or do people call you over?
They do they do
There's a lot in the political world
I'm only telling you guys,
What kind of ghosts?
Only I can see them, you guys can't right?
There was one climbing up and down the Diet building
That's fine
Do you charge high fees for places like that?
I do say "It's not about the money"
But even if I don't take their money, they send me impressive gifts at the end of the year
Like Matsusaka Beef
Matsusaka Beef?
It should be on the Point Card
You don't like Matsusaka Beef?
No, no, I did the Onmiyoji because I don't like Matsusaka Beef,
But in the end, I still received it
In the end-
If we can't see them it doesn't matter
You eat them though right?
I do I do
I didn't know that
One of them even ran away after I ate it
That's scary
That's super scary
One leg, it ran away on one leg
Scary!
Endo nominates someone to tell a lie
Endo-kun
He came to Gaki the other day,
Ryuchell, you know him right
Yes, Ryuchell
Hosei-san, I've heard he's rather a close relative of yours
Oh, how?
Yeah, are you relatives?
Would you call us relatives?
He's my father's sister's son
That's a relative
Oh, that's a relative
You're pretty closely related
You guys must meet if you're that closely related
I've never met him before, but I do care for him
Eh? But when he came the other day it didn't seem like that at all
He did say that. I am a comedian,
And Ryuchell, is a fashion...person.
So Comedians and Fashion cannot mix
That's not true. You see it on variety shows all the time
It's impossible after all
Is it hard to work together?
It sure is...Cause sometimes I can tell he's looking at me, cause we're relatives
So you only met recently
Did he contact you before he came to Gaki?
Actually he did
On LINE, he said "Next time,"
He calls me Hosei-chan you see,
"Hosei-chan, I'm coming to Gaki, let's work together"
He said like "Please bully a little"
"Please bully a little" he said
Who bullies who?
Ryuchell,
He's bullied by who?
Me
Like "please pick on me" you mean? But that didn't happen
I didn't do it of course, but he did say "Please bully me" in an Osaka dialect
What?
In Osaka-
So hard to follow
Is my story hard to follow?
It's hard to follow, it's super hard to follow
Why that face...
Who picked the name Ryuchell
Ryuchell...was decided by my mother's side
It's his real name?
It's his real name
That's his real name?
Ryuchell isn't his real name,
Ryuchie~.... Ryuichi
Ryuichi?
Yes, Ryuichi
It's Ryuichi?
Ryuichi is his real name
So Ryuchell isn't his real name at all then. It's Ryuichi?
He said it was Ryuchell before
He did
I messed up his real name, but I asked him for the truth and he said it's Ryuichi
He does a lot of secret work! He does it all the time
The beauty parlor and everything is done secretly
What the hell is that?
Like in real life him in and Peko aren't dating
Oh sorry, Peko-chan and him are good friends
Oh I see
It was dangerous at one point
It was dangerous at one point, but my dad got involved, and I got involved, and we worked things out
What happened?
Oh you don't know?
When was it again? Right back when Rachell...
Rachell?
Horrible. This guy sucks.
This guy really sucks
Timed & Typeset by: Kedomas
Translated by: senor_wristband
Fully Improvised! Liar's Inn. They must maintain the lie no matter what!!
Here I go
Go ahead
Hamada nominates someone to tell a lie
Hamada-san
Dahama-san
Tanaka, earlier I saw you really fighting with your manager
What happened? I've never seen you be that angry before
Well, to sum it up, I couldn't take it anymore
Like I exploded
Tanaka exploded...
What happened?
It's his mocking
Him mocking me
Tanaka maybe you're overthinking it. A manager, making fun of their talent?
First, he said he really hates me
My manager
He said that?
That does kinda suck
It does, but he said it to me very clearly
Did you ask why?
I did. He said "You're not funny"
That's... I hate that too actually
That's not good
He said he hates having to manage an unfunny comedian
Why does he think you're unfunny?
My performance
He didn't say anything about Endo?
It seems he doesn't really like Endo
No way, me too?
Well yeah, unfortunately it does make sense
If he hates Tanaka, it makes sense he wouldn't really like Endo
I never really got that impression
It is unfortunate, but yeah he hates me
And, yes, he hates Endo too
Like joint responsibility kind of
He said he hates me, which I don't like,
and even after this is over, I just hate it
Cause even after this he's gonna say it again
"You weren't funny again today huh?"
That's really not alright
If someone says that to you...
Your mind just starts to snap. Every set, every shooting, no matter the occasion
So he said it to you before we started today?
He did he did
He said like "You're gonna be funny today, right?"
So you just snapped
I snapped like "Cut it out already, every single day you do this"
That's what I saw
That's what you saw, me telling him to cut it out
So when you got the job on ZIP, it would be normal for a manager to say "Congrats, do your best!"
He didn't say that
"What the hell are you gonna be able to do on ZIP" is what he said
Seriously?
And that just made me snap
That would make you snap
What was the first thing you yelled at him?
"Stop calling me like boring and unfunny"
"Stop saying that to me, it's driving me crazy!" is what I said to him
And right after I said that he beat me up...
And you don't remember
He beat you so hard you forgot, that's the worst
He called you unfunny and then beat you
Matsumoto nominates someone
Matsumoto-san again, you will pick someone...
I heard Nukumizu-san smacked Yamasaki in the toilet
Eh?!
That guy is really mild mannered
In the NTV Kojimachi toilet, here
Yes yes yes.
Right now, and I don't agree, but everyone says my hair is getting thinner right
Ah your hair?
Yeah, my hair is getting thinner
I don't think it is though
I get it thinned by the hairdresser. They take a lot off using the crescent moon scissors
So I do tell people that when they ask me, not just Nukumizu-san,
At other studios when people say "Oh your hair is getting thinner"
I say "I'm just getting it thinned by the hairdresser"
So maybe that was aired
And Nukumizu-san saw that it seems
He asked like "You're getting it thinned?"
That's fine though
Why did he get mad
You met him in the washroom?
Why does he care if you're getting it thinned
"You're getting it thinned you say?" Is what he said
And I said like "Oh, did I say that?"
He replied "Yes you did"
"Hey asshole!"
All of a sudden?
All of a sudden
Why though? What's there to get mad about?
Maybe he was angry from the start
And it's not like you said anything to Nukumizu-san
Yes exactly. In the start I had no idea what he was talking about
"By saying you're getting it thinned...Isn't your hair super thin?" he said
Sorry I don't understand, I really don't understand
Can I eat a mandarin please
No way, you're telling a story right now
Yeah sorry I don't understand
I can't eat a mandarin in the middle of my story
What happened?
Nukumizu-san?
I can't understand at all. What?
Nukumizu-san, even though we've never met he really took care of me
Nukumizu-san took care of you?
So he got angry after that? I heard you got smacked
Yes, it starts from here
After that, so many times (nanpatsu)
Nanptsu sounds like Sanpatsu (haircut), so confusing
Enough already
Enough already! Such a goddamn uninteresting story
Endo nominates someone to tell a lie
Endo-san
This is something that shocked all my juniors,
Hamada-san, you've used a meridian channel before?
When you press it
Oh yeah I know that one
It makes you explode right?
Ahhh yeah yes
But doesn't using it kill you?
Yeah I wanted to know how you stopped it
Oh yeah it's not a big deal, I just put some pressure on it
Oh, so it does make you swell?
Who made you explode?
Was there a meridian channel master nearby?
Yes yes
I don't know exactly, but he went like "Hey Hey"
Where did this happen?
A foreigner?
Hey Hey?
Like "here & here & here"
Where did this happen? Were you eating, were you backstage?
It was on my way home. Right as I parked the car in the parking lot,
Wow so they totally ambushed you
I think I was being targeted
You never saw them before?
Not at all
So it was like Fist of the North Star?
I don't know if it was like that, but he did have a Mohican haircut
That's totally Zako from Fist of the North Star
Wow, he really exists
"What is this guy? What's his deal?" and slowly my face started swelling
I went "Oh crap"!
Well it's a good thing you were in your neighborhood, you could go home right away
Yes yes exactly. I was just swelling up like this
I got home and said "Go get me some ice!"
Oh right, you iced it down
So basically you just thought to put ice on it?
Yeah I didn't know what to do, I just thought ice is good for swelling
And I gradually pushed it down
And nothing happened after that?
Like swelling up out of nowhere, or seeing some swelling when you wake up?
Oh no, but actually like Endo just said, when I use the bath it does puff up a bit
I thought it would be bad to get a fever, so I just rushed out
And I got the ice again
Oh, you didn't mention that
I would never have known without asking
Tanaka nominates someone to tell a lie
Tanaka-san
Tanachi
Well we were talking about Meridian Channels. And well I don't know if this is true,
Endo,
I heard you got bit by a zombie,
and miraculously recovered to a human
Well whether or not I recovered is up to your judgment I guess,
Have I recovered?
I can't really tell, I thought that story was a lie
Then I think I have recovered. If I'm being serious
I do try to recover, but I can't really tell myself.
Isn't this turning out the same as Hamada's story?
Oh yes, not at all, no no not at all
So it's true then, you got bit by a zombie?
Zombies exist?
Yes they exist, I got bit after all
Where was this?
Right as I parked the car in the parking lot
Parking lot?
Just like how I parked my car...
Well it was a different location of course
In a parking lot, he came out from behind the back of an Alphard
It just rushed me like *PAPAPAPA*, seriously just rushed me
They move that fast?
Yeah super fast
Why though?
Yeah like, like this he came at me, and bit me like,
Here, this area, he bit me like this
Ow ow ow! I did that of course
It was pretty late at night, like 11:30, around then. He had his knife stabbed and his eye dangling
Enough of that, what happened when it bit you?
I went "OW!" and I thought for now I should,
I should go home, and I told my wife "Let's try cooling it down"
With what?
Ice, from the refrigerator
What the hell are you saying?
What were you even talking about at the end
Hamada nominates someone to tell a lie
Dahama-san
Oh me?
Matsumoto-san, is it true, you've been asking the agency for some advice
Oh, you know about it
Oh, is it about that thing?
What thing?
He said something about turning his right hand into a drill
Eh? What do you mean?
This is,
"Is it alright? Will the agency mind?" is what he's been asking I've heard
Why do you wanna do it? The drill?
I was drinking with Takasu-sensei coincidentally,
And he said something like "Don't turn it into a drill"
But why did he say that?
What's the point?
I was super conflicted but we decided on changing just 2 things
That was fast, but why?
Why a drill?
Why a drill? Alright listen I'm a southpaw,
When I write I use my left hand, basically I do everything with my left hand
So thinking about how little I use my right hand,
And when I talked about this to Takasu-sensei, he said like
"Matsumoto-san, are you using righty?"
And it just shocked me
He said that?
It just convinced me, I thought let's do it
I've already got the mold made
But, what's the point of the drill?
Yeah, instead of a hand
Even this, this is a fake hand
It's like a false tooth?
It's like a false tooth
It can work like a drill?!
No no, it's a temporary hand
They cut it off once,
And when they attached it, it was rotating like this,
I asked, "Sensei, isn't this rotation weird?"
He said "Sorry!" it's a matter of millimeters after all,
They got rid of the hand they cut off, so I have a temporary hand right now and it's kind of hard to move
But I can't tell at all...
You were fine up until now
It's something that I have to be aware of
When do you rotate it?
Oh, like when I have a bad morning
What do you mean?
I can massage myself like this when I have a bad morning
Isn't that dangerous?
I don't do it that hard, it's my own drill after all!
But isn't it dangerous when just wake up?
Yeah I could take some skin off, that's not good
I just go "whir whir, whir whir" like this
If you're gonna bother doing that, you may as well wake up normally
It's not just for that, I can use it for cooking, and there's lots of attachments
It's not just a drill?
Yeah, there's also a thread spool one
A thread spool?
Something to spool up the thread
And also, a thing for whipping stuff
Do you use that though?
But you don't cook that often though
Yeah the doctor laughed like "Now you can cook Matsumoto!" "GAHAHA"
That was the master at the bar laughing
Oh right, the master
The master was listening on us the whole time
And this is an inappropriate thing to say, but I can use it for that sort of thing too
Oh?
Yeah, the drill, if I put something on the tip of it
I can use just the drill too though, like using the tip to *chin chin chin chin*
You know, I was forced to lie,
And when I get a little dirty, you guys egg me on,
No no no, you could've ended the story earlier
Timed & Typeset by: Kedomas
Translated by: senor_wristband