1st Time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arrahende
"I'm the One Who Understands you Best!"
"Anyways, I Think You'll Like this Item!" Azuma Mikihisa Edition!!
I really hate this title.
Nobody talks like that.
A special series on Gaki, where the members buy gifts for guests based on their interests!!
Today's guest is actor Azuma Mikihisa.
Actor
Single
45 Years Old
The five member's will present a top, hat and an accessory which they think will suit our guest.
Can they find something to suit the currently single, 45 year old Azuma Mikihisa?
Today, I'm going full attack.
And...?
I'm taking this chance.
Up until now the guests have been hard for me to pick for.
I'm also pretty confident this time.
Why is everyone so confident this time?
We know him quite well from Downtown DX.
On there we have a corner about casual clothes.
So we should have a general idea.
I see.
What about you two?
We've also watched Downtown DX before.
So, without further ado, let's bring out today's guest, Azuma Mikihisa.
Azuma Mikihisa
So it's this kind of thing.
You're quite...
Is this how you usually dress?
I like to dress quite simply.
Not always like this.
So casually...
So your casual clothes are more simple?
Yes, I don't wear suits all that often.
Before the show started, the Gaki members went shopping.
Yūrakuchō
Hoping to find a top to suit Mikihisa, Hamada heads to Yūrakuchō.
Why do I have to worry about what Mikihisa would like?
This looks pretty good, I wonder what it feels like to wear.
This'll suit you.
You could see Azuma Mikihisa wearing this, right?
He's probably already bought this.
Shibuya
Across town, Hōsei is...
Today it's gotta be... a jacket, right?
This is...
...who do you think this is?
Who?
Like, who among the Gaki members?
Staff
Endō-san.
Yes, this is so Endō.
This would be perfect for Endō.
Staff
Erm, but we're looking for Azuma-san.
Ah Azuma-san.
Omotesandō
Endō has come to Omotesandō in search of a hat for Mikihisa.
The image I have of Mikihisa is...
Teamer = Gangs of youth often wearing American casual clothes.
...dark skin, white teeth and a former Teamer.
I think most former Teamers
would like stuff with skulls on.
Do you have anything with a skull on top?
A skull is maybe a bit much.
This is the most similar we have...
If you did this with a skull print, it'd be perfect.
Ueno
Searching for an accessory, Matsumoto has come to Ueno.
I think...
...I'd rather buy something for myself, it's cold out here.
Let's have a look in here.
Thinking about it...
...maybe something like this.
Maybe this'd be good.
What sort of situation would you use this in?
I can't think of a time when I'd need something like this, can you?
Tanaka has come to a western shop in Ueno in search of a top.
Ah this is cool.
Thank you.
Would you mind putting this on?
Ah that looks great.
It looks even cooler when you see it on someone.
As I thought, this is good.
I think he's going to love this.
As always, the guest will take home their favourite items. The worst will have to pay out of their own pocket.
To start off, Tanaka will present his top to Mikihisa.
Shall we get going?
Let's do it.
Let's see your attack Tanaka.
If you don't attack, you're not gonna win.
It's alright as long as you don't embarrass yourself.
Since I'm first, that won't happen.
Please.
What is this?
This is truly special.
8,800 Yen (£51/$81)
Price conversions are approximate for time of airing.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
You're just messing around.
A waistcoat!?
Wait.. not a waistcoat, a vest.
Mikihisa-san
definitely has this image of wearing a vest, don't you think?
Does he?
An image of a vest and shirt.
He definitely does.
When have you seen that?
I've seen it plenty...
This is truly awful Tanaka.
This isn't even something to laugh at.
Shishido Joe is an old Japanese actor known for his role in the Western: Quick Draw Joe (1961).
Is he Shishido Joe?
No! I have this great image of him wearing this vest along with an open shirt...
That's true, maybe...
The vest with an open shirt, right?
Mikihisa, do you think you could try it on for us?
This'll look great.
Even if the shirt is a little smart...
This is...
See!
It looks terrible.
He looks like a comedian.
He looks like the manager at a steakhouse.
Timed, Typeset & Translated by Inepped
"I think you'll like this item"
Endō is the next to present his top.
It's black but...
...I think a long t-shirt will really suit Mikihisa-san.
3,456 Yen (£21/$24)
A long t-shirt?
It's a long t-shirt but...
...if I'm right...
...Azuma Mikihisa-san...
...was a Shibuya Teamer.
Yes I was.
This is for Azuma Mikihisa?
It's a skull of roses.
Ah, those are roses.
White roses, red roses...
Right right, it's nostalgic right?
I don't remember this.
That sort of
rebellious feel.
Teamers were over 25 years ago.
Next up is Hamada, what sort of image of Mikihisa does he have?
When you think of Azuma Mikihisa...
...you picture him wearing a jacket.
Rather than just a regular jacket
I thought something like this would be good from time to time.
I think that's from Omotesandō.
I picture him wearing one with buttons rather than a zip.
Ah, that's probably true.
It's a pain if there's loads of 'em though.
You're just buying for yourself.
14,580 Yen (£90/$100)
That's just for Hamada-san!
That's definitely a Hamada-san jacket.
This'd probably suit you more.
The material is so soft and fluffy!
Put it on properly!!
The button's stuck.
Do it right man.
But, you know...
But...
How is it?
You can also pop the collar, which I like.
This is good!
It is right?
You've even buttoned it up wrong!!
Get it right already!!
Next up is Hōsei, what sort of top has he found?
Mikihisa-san
I think this'll get you excited.
I don't think the others were particularly exciting.
I see what you mean.
Camouflage?
15,984 Yen (£92/$48)
This isn't it.
Cut it out with the camouflage.
I guess camouflage comes in various colours.
Yeah, normally you see the green camouflage.
It's tiny!
It's a little small.
The size is totally wrong!
This looks great!
Look Mikihisa-san is laughing.
This is just awful.
The size is...
He's turned into a scientist!
The sleeves are like a lab coat's.
Last to present is Matsumoto. How will it go?
Well you're up Matsumoto-san.
Matsumoto-san was quite confident...
When I was walking around...
...I was thinking, 'What would he like?'
I saw this and thought, 'Ah, this is it!'
You guys weren't thinking enough about him.
I feel so sorry for him!
Please choose something more colourful next time.
It's vivid.
What's with that? Vivid?
This is high quality.
They make stuff in this colour?
It looks great in this colour.
30,240 Yen (£174/$280)
A blue P-Coat.
A P-Coat in a deep blue.
This is a great choice right?
I'm not so sure.
This might not work for everyone...
...you've gotta fit the style.
This'll definitely work.
Have a look at the monitor, it looks great on you.
What do you think?
It's not that it doesn't suit him, but casually...
I see where you're coming from.
I don't know if he'd wear it all the time...
Maybe you can wear it when you're over 60.
It'll be perfect for then.
So, which top will Mikihisa choose as his favourite?
Matsumoto
Hōsei
Hamada
Endō
Tanaka
Tanaka is once again...
It's definitely last.
You think mine's last?
I don't know. Are you sure?
You're way behind the curve.
It will definitely suit you Mikihisa-san. Truly.
You'll have to be holding a stone hatchet wearing that.
In first place is...?
First is...
The size and feel are excellent.
When I was on the escalator, I saw it and knew it was the one!
It couldn't be anything but this!
So in second is?
In second...
Second is mine right?
Thank you.
Well, it's easy to wear.
And in third is Endō's skull t-shirt.
Which of these tops will come in last!?
So we're down to the final two.
Which will be the worst?
Yeah, please be honest.
In fourth place is...?
It's this.
Of course it is. I wasn't even worried.
Seriously...
Seriously Tanaka, look at it!
It's weird.
Really?
This is just...
...impossible.
You were surprised right?
Yeah.
Even if I were naked, cold and dying, I wouldn't wear that.
Tanaka has to pay out 8,800 Yen (£51/$81)!!
Next, finding a hat to suit Mikihisa. First up is Endō.
This colour?
Yes.
Please show it.
12,960 Yen (£74/$120)
He's trying his best.
No, no, no.
The feather gives it a slightly wilder feel.
This is perfect for a former Teamer.
Stop it with that.
It was 25 years ago.
See! It looks great!
The size is a little...
The size is totally off.
I look like I'm ready to fire the starting pistol.
You could tell by his face that he'd never wear this.
Next up to present his hat is Hamada.
Shozo's and mine aren't too different.
The style is pretty similar but a different colour.
This feels like Mikihisa's style.
Another completely different colour.
20,520 Yen (£118/$190)
This is kinda...
Kaneko Nobuo was a Japanese actor, often playing a hardened Yakuza.
It's Kaneko Nobuo.
Why Kaneko Nobuo?
I think this red colour will work well.
Hmm, I guess so.
Blue...
I mean it's mostly that same hat just in a brownish colour.
That's true, it's pretty similar.
Well... maybe. But it looks better in red.
Try it on already!!
Hurry up.
He hit him earlier as well.
Put on the hat.
It'll look different compared to the white.
The size looks the same.
Just the same.
It doesn't look as small.
I had a feeling most of these would be similar.
Third up is Matsumoto, what sort of image is he thinking of?
You guys have played quite safe.
Not anymore.
You've all shown his calm side.
But there's a wild side lurking within.
You might not use it all the time, but you'll definitely use it.
Please put it on.
Wild.
It's a little on the different side
5,292 Yen (£30/$49)
and you might not always wear it but
I think this colour palette suits you perfectly.
You definitely don't hate that colour right?
Hmm, I do like it.
Try it on.
It really suits you!
Wold you shut up already!!
Let the guest say something.
It looks great!
Could you imagine him showing up on set
saying "Good morning" wearing that?
I definitely couldn't.
He said it pretty clearly.
Next is Tanaka, can he get revenge for earlier.
So far everyone's gone for the same style.
Matsumoto
Hamada
Endō
That's true. I think that style fits him pretty well.
Please.
What's that.
He's just bought swim shorts instead.
What sort of bag is that? Is there a celebration cake in there?
He's laughing.
He's got no choice but to laugh.
What am I looking at?
Why?
Are you kidding?!
3,132 Yen (£18/$29)
Stop messing around!!
I'm not messing around.
You are just messing around!
I'm really not.
Look at all of ours, they're all pretty similar just in differing colours.
Matsumoto
Hamada
Endō
These are not messing around.
Then, look at yours!
Yes, but...
Everyone's told you to stop messing around.
I'm not.
I'm really being serious.
This feels like a new form of bungee.
Wait a minute, I'm really trying hard here!
Mikihisa, can you put it on?
Yes, please try it on.
You think this'll suit me?
Yes!
With the fake fur knitted on...
I can see the knitted look.
Yeah, with that image in mind...
I tried to go that extra step.
Why are 'you' trying to go the extra step.
Just try a little bit.
I...
There he goes messing around again.
What do you think?
Don't you think it really suits you?
Try lifting it up a little.
Ah, it covers the ears?
Yes yes.
Try lifting up the front a bit.
See, lifting the front... and you can also lift this back bit.
Don't you think it really suits you Mikihisa-san?
Last up to present his hat to Mikihisa is Hōsei.
Hōsei-san, you went with this.
7,776 Yen (£45/$72)
Wait a sec... What's the imagery?
Isn't it great. It's a kind of modern look.
We haven't seen anything like this yet.
That's right.
Surprisingly...
It actually looks quite stylish.
Doesn't it look a little too big?
No, it's not big at all.
Is it supposed to have this height to it?
Yes, yes.
His face kind of betrays how he feels.
'Is this alright?'
It looks like he might pull out a dove at any moment.
Which of these will be Mikihisa's favourite!?
I'm pretty confident in mine.
In first is...
...this.
Really?
Of course it is.
Sorry, but can you explain why.
It was a close fight, but I like the colours on this one.
In second place
Matsumoto's leopard print hat.
And in third is Endō's white hat.
I don't have anything like this.
So, which of these will come in last place!?
Again, the same last two.
So, in fourth is...?
Well that's a given.
That was a quick decision.
What are your thoughts on this?
I can't think of a time when I'd wear this.
Tanaka, do you need a change of manager?
Are things not going well? Are they giving you duff info.
Things are being done properly.
Are they telling you like... you need to mess around on this one.
No, they've told me properly and I tried hard.
Tanaka has to pay out 3,132 Yen (£18/$29)!!
Next up is an accessory. Hamada is first up.
This is also something I thought you might not have.
Ah, Beams.
This is only for certain times of year.
Ah, so it's seasonal.
9,180 Yen (£53/$85)
You put this over your head rather than around the neck.
Ah, it's a scarf.
Will that suit him?
It's pretty different.
No no no.
It's got a jagged pattern.
Put it on!!
This is all planned.
They had a meeting before this.
It fell flat.
Every time he takes forever.
See, it sits right on the neck.
It's much simpler.
It's much easier than wrapping a scarf around.
It's convenient.
Next is Endō, what will his accessory be?
Is it a coat?
A bag.
A bag with a cool design.
12,960 Yen (£74/$120)
That's an impressive amount of skulls.
There's loads of skulls.
You sure love skulls.
Third up is Hōsei, can he challenge with his accessory?
Well...
...this is certainly something.
It's a thong.
A thong?
1,327 Yen (£8/$12)
This is impossible.
He's taking you for a fool.
When would I wear this?
For a date.
With a lady?
If I were a woman, I'd be so pleased to see you in this.
Will Matsumoto's selected item suit Mikihisa?
I was thinking 'What would he enjoy?' when I picked this out.
What? This looks bad.
He can't help but laugh.
Nah, it's fine.
It's just that it's such a unique item.
What's wrong?
9,504 Yen (£55/$88)
You're joking right?
What even is that?
What is that?
It suits him perfectly.
I never imagined wearing something like this.
They look great.
Look at his face though.
As I thought, they suit you so well.
This is the first time I've worn fingerless gloves.
Perfect when reading a script.
Rather aren't your fingers gonna get cold.
You can quickly flip to the previous scene.
Like this.
They seem pointless.
You don't have anything like this right?
I don't.
He 'still' won't.
Finally, with two losses already, Tanaka.
Please, I'm really hoping for a win with this.
Just look at that face!
You won't have anything like this.
What is it?
A poncho?
It's a rain poncho.
9,612 Yen (£55/$89)
Can you ever imagine Mikihisa-san wearing that?
A rain poncho, it's the first I've heard of it.
Right!
That's exactly why it's great!
You've never worn anything like it before.
I'm not really sure what this is for.
For rain or snow!
Instead of an umbrella!
Nah, you'd just carry an umbrella.
Yeah, I'd just use an umbrella.
And you'd just hop in a car.
I mean, if you were camping and it suddenly rained...
Yeah yeah yeah!
But I bet he doesn't really go camping.
Probably not.
He doesn't have that image.
Maybe a festival or something.
You see him going to a festival in the rain?
A festival?
Would festival goers really wear a poncho like that?
So, which of these will be Mikihisa's favourite item!?
First is obviously... this.
Thank you.
As long as it's the right season, this can be used anywhere.
And in second is... Hōsei's thong.
See!!
In third is... Endō's bag.
To be honest, I didn't think it'd lose to those two.
So, which will be the worst accessory between these!?
The worst is...?
The worst is... this.
Of course it is!
I thought so too.
You must be joking!
Really?!
Of course it is.
I'm still not sure what these are.
Matsumoto has to pay out 9,504 Yen (£55/$88)!!
So, Matsumoto-san, how do you feel?
Shall we continue this series?
I've realised after this episode...
...that I'd like to replace Tanaka with a new regular.
You just mess around.
Take a peek in their dressing room next time.