Are the scary stories from
around the world really scary?
Welcome to the 2016
World Ghost Story Summit
are the scary stories from around the world really scary!?
Usually when you talk about
scary stories in tv shows like this
Something weird has to happen     - Right
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Endo Shozo
Tsukitei Hosei
It's like a rule
But this time nothing will happen if we joke around
We won't joke around
We'll just listen to our guests
That's it
That's right
It's not going to be a fun corner
foreigner stars will tell us horror stories from their own country
we're going to see if they're scary if japanese people listen to them
note: narrator voice = almost the same as below
Such a dynamic punchline!!
This time, 5 foreigner stars will join us
World Ghost Stories Summit 2016: curtain-raise
Tonight, the 2016 World Ghost Stories Summit will be held
I'd like to call here our first guest from Switzerland
Please!
Our representative from Switzerland is miss Christine Haruka
Haruka Christine
Switzerland                   representative
Please
Switzerland
Switzerland, the land of historical fine arts and Alps
How is the scary story from this country going be?
When you're ready, miss Haruka
What I'm about to tell you
Is a story about a church
on a certain Swiss town
There was a big, big
clock tower in this church
And beneath it
Lied the remains
Of the XIV century mayor of the town
Said to be killed by a deadly poison
The mayor under the tower
Time passed, and in the XX century
A group of scientists
Unearthed the mayor's corpse
In order to perform an autopsy
The examination went on for roughly one week
But when they were about to bury his bones back
For some reason
The skull was nowhere to be found
In the end, they decided
To deposit the corpse as it was, without the skull
Then, few weeks later,
Near the clock tower
Two siblings were playing soccer together
At one point, the ball started rolling away
Until it reached a grassy spot
Right under the clock tower
And in that grassy spot...
There was a man on all fours
In desperate search for something
When the big brother hurried up to get the ball back
The figure of that man...
Already disappeared
The brother, who found it eerie,
Hurried up and picked the ball up
And quickly run back to his sister
But then, she noticed something
And shouted as if in pure agony:
"NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!!"
The brother, surprised,
Looked down to the soccer ball he was holding
And then...
He realized...
The ball have turned...
...Into an old-looking skull
Is this... famous in Switzerland?
Yes, it's one of the most famous
To be honest, by the moment the soccer ball came in
I thought myself, "that must be the skull"
It kinda leaked out
I thought
It may change to a different path from there
Me too, I was like "it just can't be that!"
But it was      - Just as we pictured it
Yeah, just like that
Translation & Subtitles by Shion
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
www.facebook.com/shionnotsukai
Want to support my translations?
Consider donating @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
@fgrndnoises
Translation & Subtitles by Shion
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
www.facebook.com/shionnotsukai
Want to support my translations?
Consider donating @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
@fgrndnoises
Our next entry for the 2016 World Ghost Story Summit
Is a scary story from Congo
Our representative for the Democratic Republic of Congo is Mr. Muwete Muluaka
Muwete Muluaka
Democratic Republic of Congo representative
Congo, the heart of Africa's wonderful landscapes
Democratic Republic of Congo
What kind of scary stories are told in this country?
In a certain village in Congo
There was a young man called Pier Thunkai
note: I don't know its actual transcription. It's "pieerutuukai" in katakana.
Pier Thunkai
One day, this young man
Wasn't home all day
And while he was away
All of his property were stolen
And so he started asking the villagers
"Who stole all the things I had?"
While going around from house to house
None of the villagers listened to him, though
But unluckily for him
At that moment, Pier Thunkai
Accidentally slipped
And fell down from a cliff
note: he mistakenly says "date" instead of "gake" (cliff)
And so, Pier Thunkai went missing
Later on, when it was night
A monster showed up in the village
That monster had a single eye,
A single leg,
And a single hand
Every single part of his body
Was only one of a pair
And so, that monster
Started asking the villagers
"Where are all the things I had?"
He started going from house to house
Killing every villager he met
The villagers shouted "please, don't kill anybody else!"
And they started to chant
a prayer to calm Pier Thunkai's anger
That song was like this:
And it repeats
But that song didn't reach him at all
Pier Thunkai just kept on killing each villager
Until there was none of them left
In Congo, to this day...
We say "if you steal, Pier Thunkai will come for you!"
And it came to be a common phrase
What kind of story is that?
It's Pier Thunkai's story
How are Pier Thunkai and the halved monster related?
It's the same
Pier Thunkai himself became the monster
He did?      - He transformed into the monster
It came out so suddenly
Yeah it was sudden
But almost everyone of us got that,
like Cocorico and Yamazaki-san
Yeah we did       - I got that
Me too halfway
I thought I'd better off stop following it
I mean, I can't even remember
the main character's name
Pier Thunkai, right?        - Yes
So, he fell down a cliff
- Yeah, he fell down
And revived as a monster
He didn't fell down a cliff (gake)      - Huh?!
He fell down a gliff (date)
Of course he meant "cliff"
Come on, get it
Next up is a scary story from Brazil
Marzia
Brazil representative
So, our representative for Brazil is miss Marzia
Pleased to meet you       - Same here
It's a pleasure
Whenever you're ready
The story I'm about to tell you
Is about an experience I really had
in Brazil when I was 14 years old
I was still very young
And I was trying to call
for a ghost, just for fun
In short, I was doing something
like the japanese "kokkuri-san"
note: a divination game similar to the western ouija board
On the table, I've placed
The summoned spirit
Two cards labeled with "no" and "yes"
Then I've light up two candles
And planned to ask the ghost some questions
So it would answer, that's it
And so, I started the ritual
But then suddenly
The wind started to blow
And when I opened my eyes
Before me
There was a blond kid
So I asked him
"Who are you?"
And he said
"I'm Paolo"
"I died in an accident"
"And I don't have any friends,
so why don't you play with me?"
That was the first time I saw
a real ghost right before me
So I got really scared
So I told Paolo
"You're not in this world anymore"
"You shouldn't be here" - I desperately told him
And so he
Quietly pointed his index towards the "no" card
I gradually became even more terrified
And, scared, I told him "go home"
"Please, just go back home!"
And yet
He just kept on pointing the "no" card
So i took the cards and the candles
On the table and took them away
And cleaned everything up
And while shutting both my eyes and ears
"Go away! Go Away! Vá embora! Vá embora!"
I just kept on shouting this
And after some time
He disappeared into thin air
But...
On the table, there was a single tarot card left
When I looked at that tarot card...
I realized its meaning...
...was "friendship"
Paolo...
So, you actually experienced this?
I was around 14 years old      - 14 years old...
I've always been kind of sensitive to ghost sighting
They're always sticking close to me
And always pop out, like, a lot of them
So there's a chance it could stick close to us?
It could happen, yes
Will it be Paolo?
If you call him, he may come but---
Even tigers could come
A tiger?
It actually happened I was once possessed by a tiger
It's not something to laugh about!
I'm not trying to sound funny
This too was from that time,
I was like 15 years old
And what happened?
A tiger
It bit me
It bit you?      - It did
It bit you?      - Yes, on the neck
It's scary, huhh
What is it?
But it would be scary even if it wasn't a ghost
No way!
I mean, even if a non-ghost tiger would bite you...
Next up for the World Scary Stories Summit
It's a story from our italian dandy
Girolamo Panzetta
Italy                   representative
So, our representative for Italy is mr. Girolamo Panzetta
Girolamo Panzetta
Please, take a seat
When you're ready, Girolamo
Please
My story is... of course, happened in Italy
It was... from when I was around 20 years old
I wanted to make a new product
A perfume
So, the city of perfumes is in France
On the southern side of it
In Provence
It's a place called Grasse
In that place there are a lot of small factories
And you can sort of create your own perfume there
But the town I was in was Naples
So I had to go from Naples to Genova
By train
And from Genova
I had to take a car and travel along the coast
And then I had to get inside a mountain road
Just when I entered this mountain road
There was a small station, and before it
There was a little girl
She was hitch-hiking, doing the autostop
She was wearing a white dress,
her shoes were white too
The white girl
She had a big bag, like a Chanel bag
And her skin was pale white too
I asked her where she was headed to
And it was exactly the same
town I was headed to, Grasse
As soon as she got inside my car
I noticed that her smell was really similar
To the perfume I wanted to create myself
I thought "that must be fate"
So, we got in the car and
went running through the mountain road
But the girl kept on saying
"take it easy, go slower"
You know there are lots of cabins here
We were going straight
but then she was like
"Stop!"
So I stepped on the brake
I was surprised
When I turned towards her
She was gone
I was confused, but when I looked ahead
Right before the cabin I noticed there were the remains
Of an incident
There were victims
She told me to stop and so I did
I wasn't involved in that incident
So, I had goosebumps
And when I looked over
The place lit by the lights
Which was on the roadside
I noticed there were lots of flowers
And beside them
There were pictures of those
who died in such incident
And one of them
Was the girl who was with me
That was my story
There are similar japanese stories      - Yeah
It was kinda japanese-styled     - It was, yes
Its style was similar
Was this your experience?
It was      - A real experience? Woah...
The most amazing thing about this story
Is the fact it involved the smell
It was stylish
I know, right?
It's kinda... italian
I mean, the whole episode
I mean, it was about a perfume
With that on mind, he may be lying, you know
It's not--- I mean, I always
get that when I tell this
Even his horror stories are fashionable
Yeah, sort of
You know, that girl had a name
Which was it?
It was Paolo
This was a lie, sorry
See?
He did it right in front of us
It was a joke, uh...
He really loves to say such hard-to-get jokes
"Hard to get"...
I don't know when he's joking!
- I got it thanks to Hamada
Coming next
A scary story from Nigeria, Africa
Our representative from Nigeria is mr Bobby Ologun
Bobby Ologun
Nigeria representative
Please
Nigeria
What will be the scary story from Nigeria,
A place where believe
in black magic to this day?
This is...
A story I heard from my mama
It's a cursed tale
Of a village
Still existing to this day
In this village, from old times
The cursed village
There was a food's name
You couldn't say out loud
Because by saying its name
They said
A 2-headed 6-legged huge monster
Called [some nigerian name]
Would surely shows itself
It's a gigantic boar
A boar?
The legend says
That if it shows up,
someone from the village
Will die from a mysterious
death within 7 days
The village still can't say
The name of this food to this day
But then, one day...
A certain group of magicians
Tried to solve this mystery
And so they came to the village
To put an end to the curse
In order to solve this mystery
They danced... exorcism dance
all over the village
They started to dance
Err...
This...
While saying that forbidden name
But each time they said it
The 2-headed, 6-legged
[monster name] appeared
Each time he shouted
A mysterious death will occur
One day passed
And then people died
After two days
Again, 10 other people died
When six days passed
The 200 magicians
Were reduced to 7
And so, the people from the village
Became frightened
And expelled the
remaining 7 magicians
From then on
If someone...
...Would end up
entering this village
They would surely be
caught by the villagers
And they would
beat them repeatedly
Before they would
say that food's name
The name of that food
note: "inya" is based off what I could hear. Not sure about its actual name.
...Was "inya"
[yoruba language]
The end
What the heck?
Sorry but...
I'm not sure I got it
Its second half was horrible
I have no idea what it was about
I listened to it though
He sounded more like an old lady
from Okinawa on the second half
I didn't understand anything!
Why?
In this village
There's a food
name you can't say
Yeah, that part is clear
By the moment you say it
The [monster name] will
emerge from the ground!
That's the first time we heard "ground"!
But it's obvious!
It's not!!
It's how it goes for this story
- It wasn't obvious
Which food is it?
It's inya
What?
Inya
What is it?
Inya!
What's that?
Inya
- Inya?    - Inya..?
What is it?
It's inya!!
Yeah but what?
- We got that, what is it?
What is it like?   - What kind of food is it?
What kind of food is it?
- It's inya!!
But what is an "inya"?
- Explain us!
It's food
- Is it a fruit?
Is it a fruit?
Is it something like a potato?
It's like a mochi made from sweet potatoes
So you knew it!
Just say it if you know it!
Just say that
Why didn't you say that?
Is it good?
Everyone in my country eats it
And how do you eat it?
With tomatoes
You stuff em all inside a roasted capybara
And then you gulp it down
That's an impressive food!
That's incredible!
- It is
Capybara!?
That's not normal at all!
That's not ok!
It's the worst!
- It's not!
Italy
Nigeria
Swiss
Democratic Republic of Congo
Brazil
Pier Thunkai
The White Girl
The Cursed Village
The Mayor Under the Tower
The Summoned Spirit
With all the 5 of them, our scary stories meeting is over
So guys, with this we're done
Are we?     - Yes
- I see...
What now?
Encore
Tell the same scary story in your native language
Are we having our usual encore in native language?
Encore
Tell the same scary story in your native language
Let's do it, yes
Let's choose one of them
Why don't we
Ask Bobby?
Shall we ask him?
For real?
Yeah, for the time being
For the time being
Come out already
We'll now listen to his scary story in Yoruba language !!
Nigeria Representative
Bobby Ologun
Yoruba Language
"The CuRSEd village"
Our representative from Nigeria, Bobby Ologun
Will now tell us the Cursed Village story in Yoruba!
The cursed village
In Yoruba
note: I'm going to translate only the japanese bits of it
..."norowareta" (cursed)
Huh?
Is it in japanese now?
He totally ignored us
...Tamashii (soul)
He said "tamashii"
- He clearly said it
translation & subs by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
Support my work: like my FB page: facebook.com/shionnotsukai
The end
Or make a donation on my ko-fi page: ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
It felt so different to me
ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
There were some japanese words in it
That's mainly because
I couldn't translate what I said in japanese in yoruba
ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
But it's your native language!
I speak in yoruba just with my mom
ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
Kids nowadays don't speak it at all
But...
- Has your mother ever been in Japan?
She's here now
So you're taking in yoruba now!
You are speaking it!
- How irritating!
His mom...
Never heard of such a well timed thing before
I mean, she's here now
What the heck!
Why is she here now?
She...
She came to see her nephews
For more Gaki no Tsukai episodes & clips visit
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com