First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende
Ikinari Steak 100,000 yen
Yamanote Line, 37 store,
Completion Challenge!
You did not speak clearly at all
You bit your tongue
You sprained your ankle,
It didn't feel like I tripped
It's been 6.5 months since we did this
We're doing this at our age?
6.5 half years
By the way, has anyone been to Ikinari Steak before?
I've, one time,
Nope
Never
No
I have
You haven't?
TN: Ikinari = Suddenly
So it's actually suddenly steak?
A store where you can eat great steaks,
A national chain brand, Ikinari Steak!
At every store, the 5 will work together to finish 200g of steak
Starting at Ginza Yonchome, they aim to finish all 37 stores along the Yamanote line
It's 200g per store for all 5
So 40 per person
So 37 stores
So 13kg per person
It's not that high
That's not true
What exactly did you calculate?
What did you write down?
The staff are going "No no no no"
They're all highly educated people
We're all morons here
If they finish all 37 stores, they win 100,000 yen
But if anyone gives up, the challenge ends
Whoever gives up has to pay for all food eaten thus far
Ikinari Steak Food Marathon - First, they choose their steak at Ginza Yonchome
This is the menu at Ginza Yonchome,
You will draw balls here to decide your item
I see
We'll get to eat a bunch of stuff
Hamada-san first,
What, me? What about Yama-chan?
Leader!
Why am I "Leader"?
What did you get?
Middle rib?
Compared to top rib, it is fattier and has better marbling. A tender and complex steak.
I see, I see
Nice to have this for the first one
It is possible to get this again though
We put the ball back in?
It would be better if it was cleared
It doesn't clear if you eat it
Oh really?
We'd be done by the fifth store otherwise
The least educated member?
He failed his boating license you know
I got the license
He thinks we're on a boat
Typeset by GakiDave
Translation by senor_wristband
Is there like, a steak sauce?
There is
We can use that if we want right?
And, if you want, you can order from the side menu
Screw that
Why?
Why would we?
They have like black oolong tea,
That would be good
They have salad too
TN: "Sara-to" means easily; "Sarado" means salad
You can shove it down "sara-to"
Salad and "sara-to", I can't believe you...
"Sara, sara, sara, sara", I just hate that
Sorry, so we have to split it right?
It's up to you guys
There's unwanted items too
There are unwanted items?
I can only eat if it's well done...
Ah, the doneness,
Oi, Busjack, the hell are you saying
That's one hell of a nickname
That's his nickname?
Well done?!
They arrive at the first store, in Ginza Yonchome
There's not many people
The time, right
Usually lots of salarymen
So everyone, here
We'll order first
This is the rib steak
Middle rib?
This is where they cut the meat
It's gonna be like this here?
It's the first store I guess
There may be some variation in the weight
224 grams
224 grams?
That's ok!
I recommend cooking it rare
I'd like it well done, please.
We'll get it done medium-rare.
Understood
Everyone, the table,
The steak cut in front of their eyes, grilled using charcoal
I'm starting to feel hungry
I'm feeling it, the hunger is being invited
You, eat the fat only
I can't eat the fat, seriously
I can't eat the fat either
I can't
What's with you guys? Now, here?
"I can't eat this, I can't eat that"
You haven't eaten a single bite yet
Oh, here it comes!
It's sizzling
I can totally finish this
1 person could eat this too though
Oh really?
Like, suddenly,
Shit I said "Suddenly"
After telling us not to
First, they all taste the steak,
You're cutting on the skillet?
Yes, yes,
I see
I could eat this in one bite
Here I go
This amount is good, I can finish this no problem
I want more
The steak is finished in a blink,
Just the corn and onion is left
Maybe Endo should be responsible for the corn
My favourite food ever is grilled corn, actually
I thought it was soybean flour
Oh yeah, grilled corn is second then
This won't be aired
Woah, I can finish this
Is it no problem?
Finished!
Marvelous
Truly marvelous
Still hungry, they head to the next shop
They choose the steaks before leaving
Sirloin!
Ah, sirloin steak!
We're getting the sirlon steak.
How shall we cook it?
Alright Endo, you decide
Well Done
We're heading to the second store
It's hot, isn't it?
It isn't!
Sorry
You've been saying this the whole time
It's so hot!
Right after the start, Matsumoto starts complaining about the heat
Is the heating alright?
No heating?
The heater is definitely on
It's annoying, right?
Complaining "It's hot!" by himself
And next,
Why do the curtains need to be closed?
If people see your faces from outside,
they might take pictures, and such
Who cares
Not being able to see outside is depressing
We're all thinking it; "What a pain in the ass"
"This guy is annoying after all"
They arrive at Ginza 6-chome
"Suddenly" we are here
So exciting!
He pushed this pull door first though
He definitley pushed it first
So "Sudden"
From Australia, Naruo specialty beef Sirloin Steak
This time the steak will be served well done, because of Endo's insistence
It's so cooked
Hoisei-san, what's that?
Wasabi!
What to do with the corn?
There is a corn lover here
Endo's well done is really pissing me off
After eating it
Finished!
Let's go to the next store
The next store they arrive at, Yurakucho store
This kind of store is nice
Here they enjoy a rare US Angus sirloin
What do you think Endo?
Tashty
The tenderness stands out
He put wasabi on his soy sauce
The corn is so plump and delicious
I messed up, making Endo eat the corn by himself
Do you want some?
Nope, it's a rule now
Something like this, would really fill us up
That's good information, you can have ingen with that
You can swap the corn for another topping
Hurry up and eat!
Why so angry, all of a sudden?
He hits the wall in sync with his laugh
What happened?
He's finished!
Isn't this easier than Gyoza?
Still feeling hungry, they arrive at the 4th store
I want some rice
That make sense, some white rice
Should we order white rice?
Not yet
What I really want is some red wine
I think I'll have a little bit
Ikininari Steak 4th store in Toranomon, where Matsumoto has been before
The red wine is here
Matsumoto's red wine
He has to finish it right?
Yes
You never said that before
Sorry, a bit late
Tell me that at the first meeting
You should've told me when I first met you
You want a little, right?
I'm driving home
No you aren't!
You dirty Kansai comedian!
The rules allow the 5 to share it
But since nobody wants any, he has to drink it himself
Where should I place this?
Here
In front of Endo
In front of ... Endo?
Yoshida-san, I'm Endo.
"In front of ... Endo?"
This time, Ingen replaces the Corn. The sirloin steak is done medium.
Fantastic
This is way better
Just gulping it down
It's super delicious
All finished.
Matsumoto you have some wine left
Wait listen
I was never told anything
Enough of that joke now, just take a sip someone
I can't move!
Is it always this much?
This is the standard amount?
Yes, that's a large serving!
It's a large, right?
That's the large one?
Yes, yes it is
Yoshida-san, you certainly are unique!
Right?
Definitely unique.
A little out there
I've been here before actually
Eh-?
Eh-!
In front of Endo
In the end, Matsumoto finished it himself
Man, I'm drunk
Where we going?
Shimbashi Kabiyaguchi
Is it a long drive?
It's basically 10 minutes away
That's amazing,
This Ikinari! Steak network
Ikinari! Steak network
Even cows use it
At the 5th store in Shinbashi, they get their Rib Roast steak done medium
Sorry for the wait
It looks amazing
This rib roast is aged for 20 days to bring out the flavour
That looks amazing!
Yeah
This is so different, it's suddenly ...
Don't say sudden!
Piece of shit
What else would I say
I got it cut
It's way different from the others
Tender and delicious
I think I'm gonna stop getting well done now
Nobody likes well done
I want medium even if it means I'll die
Finished!
He's going like "ahhh"
It sounded like a huge one got out
Something huge came out
It did
It means "I'm finished"
Like an old man waking up
A groan from Hamada
Are you ok?
Now that everyon'es eaten 200g, the amount consumed has passed 1kg
They decide steaks for the 6th store in Shimbashi
Tenderloin
Nice!
Is Ingen alright?
Ingen, hmm
Potato
It seems now that we're trying out different variations,
Medium
The end is near right?
What does Broccoli have in it? Vitamins? Was it Iron?
Vitamin C...
Broccoli is rich in Vitamin C
And Iron!
So annoying, right?
Broccoli is defintely rich in Iron!
They say Broccoli has 5 times more iron than nails
The first tenderloin steak today, they will enjoy it rare at Shimbashi store
With less fat, the flavour comes from the lean meat
The potatoes are chosen for the side
Oooo yeea
Amazing!
The fattyness is so different
You're right
First time today, Filet
How is it?
It would be a shame if it was firm
Rare is the best after all
You like rare now
I wish we could undo the well done back then
The potato is tasty too
Is it good?
We didn't really need to try the potato though...
The ingen instead?
For this episode
For now, by yourself,
We shall see the overture soon (TN: Not sure about this one)
Isn't the pace increasing?
Finished, congratulations!
Choosing steaks for the 7th store
But,
Middle rib.
Middle rib?
The one from the first store
The very first one
Tanaka says he wants some red wine
Red wine at his point...
Please, it's a bit...
Shall we order it?
No no, it's OK
We'll decide when we get there
Order it, order it now, now do it do it
My stomach is,
totally fine still
That's true
If 10 is the max, what number are you?
Matsumoto-san, how much for you?
For me it's pretty much,
Pretty much zero I guess
Like you haven't started
Like I haven't started
Hosei-san?
I'm For Realz 6
For Realz 6?
After 5 more stores, I might just die
Ikinari Steak Marathon; Store #7 is here in Minato Ward, Akasaka-Dori store
You had the wine?
The forcefully ordered wine reaches Tanaka
I can feel it already?
Already? You only licked it
Honestly though, why don't we all take sips from this?
The fragrance is amazing
This is too staged
Is that so? I see
This time, it;s the middle rib steak again
But still,
It doesn't look unappealing at all
The red wine will go with it
That's true
Tanaka is a red wine kinda guy too
Need to think about the balance
You sure love corn
You can grill your lips on the grill if you want to
I think this tenderloin is good
Tenderloin is best?
The filet or the sirloin
I like this taste
If you'd like, just take a sip, just a sip
Corn and red wine go together, right?
I've never heard of that before
You've got a weird vibe, all by yourself with that wine
It's all your fault though
I just wanted to share the red wine
I just don't want you guys to miss out, on this fine drink
Finished!
Fantastic
8th store now
3 hours since the start, they've eaten 280g each
Do they still find it easy?
They answer that question with their body language
You're rubbing your stomach
It's my habit
Did you always have that habit?
It doesn't matter if you're full
It just matters that you keep eating
So it's alright to say you feel full
That's true right?
There's no need to lie and pretend otherwise
This guy said he was at 0!
We can all eat together,
we just need one person to eat at each store
Do you think it's okay to encourage gorging on all this meat?
An old man eating meat by himself won't get laid
So 5 old men eating meat won't get laid either
NEXT WEEK! The marathon continues
Many events occurr!
Store person!
They reach the limits of the stomach
There's a time limit to consider too
From where I'm standing, that just looks like a cow
Hosei-san, are you ok?