"Are their hearts connected?" No Smartphones Meetup!
The theme; "An Oasis in the City"
Using the taxi, they head to a location they think fits the theme
Maybe we'll meet at Ueno Zoo
Very nice, this really is an oasis in the city
I told you right? They're idiots!
Nobody met up with the first hint
Next, "A large pedestrian bridge"
Hey!! Who is it?
With this prompt, Matsumoto and Endo met up!
And meanwhile...
Is that Yama-chan? He's not stopping at all!
Is that guy for real?
A near miss!
There's 4 bridges here!
How many do you think we have?!
These are there current locations. How will this end?
subbed by senor_wristband
If you'd like to support my subs,
I've setup these accounts :)
patreon.com/senor_wristband
ko-fi.com/buresurettosan
I don't care about your appointment
C'mon, don't waste time on purpose
1 hour and 30 minutes since the start. Since they're all within 2km of each other, there's a good chance they'll meet!
What theme will make them meet up?
Nadai Fujisoba location (chain store)
No clue
This one is really hard
There ... was there one here?
I don't really go to Fujisoba that often...
I've got no clue!!
This is so hard
The first one that came to mind ...
... Is that one there
It totally stands out
It really does
But, it can't be here of course
They would expect you to leave Ueno?
Yes, yes yes
With that, he leaves Ueno
He relies on his memories of Fujisoba
Hey, do you know if that one is a Fujisoba?
That place near Bancho,
What street was it...
NTV Road?
Yeah, on NTV Road,
And everyone should know NTV Road,
Exactly,
They come there to record every week
Can we head to Bancho?
He decides on the store that might in Chiyoda, in front of the NTV studio
However, there is one concern...
Was that a Fujisoba?
It might have been a Fujisoba .. I'm not sure
That's my one worry
What should we do?
There's none in Ueno right?
If you ask me just to name a store,
There's one in Ebisu, I think
That would be a good choice
If you consider Hamada, and Yamasaki ...
They bet that the others will head for the store closest to them
So they head to Ebisu, where Hamada and Yamasaki are
Meanwhile
There's one there isn't there?
Right there
Let's bet on that one
We're in Shibuya,
So then we've got to head there
The Fujisoba over there
Let's walk there
Matsumoto had the right idea,
However, there's one problem...
Near Ebisu station, there's 3 Fujisoba locations!
Their fate depends on the store they choose
And here in Tengenji, just 1 km from Ebisu
Those two, and Yamasaki are in Shibuya right?
He has the same idea
Where did he choose?
I only go there sometimes, but there's one in [!$%!@$]
Since Matsumoto and Endo are together, I bet one of them will suggest it
There's one near [$!@$!] right?
That's it then ain't it?!
The nearby 4 aim for each other,
Will these 4 be able to meet?
Wait! Sorry, but I still think,
We can't understand the thoughts of those idiots who didn't come to this massive intersection (in a previous challenge)
Like high school students taking a middle school exam ...
Let's just tolerate them once more
Let's just tolerate them once more. But if it gets too much...
We really need to tell them off
Tell them they need to stop messing about
If they're doing this as a joke, that's not good
And if they're not joking, that itself is a huge problem
Either case is bad
Meanwhile, the troublemaker Tanaka ...
That store...
Whether or not it is a Fujisoba...
I'm not sure
Just wait a second
Wait, I'm getting nervous
In that area there's Fujisoba, Yudetaro, Komoro Soba. Lots of chain soba stores like that.
If it turns out to not be a Fujisoba ... That's a big problem!
Well there's nothing else we can do. We just have to head there and see.
Meanwhile, Hosei in Ebisu...
Alright, come on. Somebody come here.
And then, appearing before him ...
Oh there's one
I didn't even notice it
There's one there too right? Sorry, that's the one I was thinking of
He goes out of his way to head to Ebisu station's south entrance, in Daikanyama.
There it is!
This one here
A Fujisoba
Will his choice of Daikanyama lead to a victory? Or defeat?
Meanwhile,
I want at least 3 of us here
Yes, that would be nice
Finally, Matsumoto and Endo arrive at Ebisu
It's gotta be here. Come on, please come!
Get off here?
Which Fujisoba did they both get off at?
I think we all found this one difficult. I bet nobody will meet.
Ah, there!
Alright alright alright
No way! No way!!!
Amazing!
I'm amazed
We took your location in to consideration. This one stands out the most
I did that too. Hamada-san is in Tengenji, I'm in Ebisu, and you two were in Shibuya
And then we went to find a nearby store,
You picked the obvious one
Exactly
This feels so good
Meanwhile, Hamada arrives
Before leaving, he was confident,
"Since Matsumoto and Endo are together, I bet one of them will suggest it"
That choice is revealed now!
Hamada-san, we can see it
Really?
I can see it, but there's nobody there ...
You're joking right?
Seriously?
They're not here?
That confidence ... Just where is this place?
"Since Matsumoto and Endo are together, I bet one of them will suggest it"
Right? There's one near Yoshimoto right?
That's it then ain't it?!
Because of that, he ignored Ebisu, and headed to Shinjiku
Then which Fujisoba did they go to?
Speaking of "which Fujisoba?" ... This man is still unsure if he's got the right place
The troublemaker, Tanaka
Right right right, there's one there right?
Down the hill?
Yes, either at the bottom of the hill, or somewhere along here
20 or 30 metres, to the right
Please let it be it
He's put it all on the line, oh let it at least be a Fujisoba!
Here?
Yes! Here!
It's a Yudetaro Soba ...
Yudeta-
Yes! Here!
I've gone and done it...
That's a Yudetaro isn't it?
Tanaka-san, you can't think of another place right?
I can't
So then let's at least get out of the car
Let's get off-
I don't wanna
He failed to follow the hint card, the very basis of this meet up challenge!
Oh man I've done it now
I've really done it now
It says it very clearly doesn't it? That's a Yudetaro alright
Oh man, I'm scared. Oh no!
I really don't like this, this is not good
And finally Time's Up!
I don't wanna...
Hello?
You know,
We've been waiting for a really long time
That's true. It is a bit congested now.
I just want to say,
Endo, Yamasaki and I have met up
Hosei-san is with them...
It's the Fujisoba at the intersection of Ebisu station
At the south entrance of Ebisu station
The Fujisoba in Ebsisu?
Hamada, where are you?
I am, in Shinjiku/
Shinjiku?
Right at the intersection of Meiji-dori ,
Where in Shinjiku?
It's near the (Yoshimoto) headquarters,
In that neighbourhood?
I see, I see
Then where is Tanaka?
I thought about where you guys would go, so I went towards the studio in Kojimachi-
Kojimachi?
He's even laughing out loud
What were you thinking?
I, I got the store wrong a bit, actually,
What do you mean?
You got the store wrong?
What did you mistake it for?
I went to a Yudetaro Soba...
Yudetaro? Oh yeah! There is one, near the studio in Bancho
This guy is a troublemaker
I genuinely almost smashed the phone
Yudetaro?
I see, we should have changed the card to Yudetaro then
You idiot
I am really sorry abut this...
See you
I'm sorry about that
Tanaka is amazing huh?
The Yudetaro in Kojimachi he said
2 hours and 20 minutes since the start,
With those 3 together, only Hamada and Tanaka are left
So, what's the next theme?
Concert Hall
A concert hall? Can we say the first one we thought of?
Budokan
Shibuya Public Hall
Where?
Budokan...
I think...
It's Shibuya Hall! Shibuya Hall!
I was thinking Yokohama Arena...
Yokohoma huh?
Let's not
Where did that come from?
Let's stop taking risks like that
For this one, there's gotta be just one choice right?
When you think of a concert ... It's gotta be the Budokan!
Am I wrong?
Hamada heads to Nippon Budokan
Matsumoto & Friends head to Shibuya Public Hall
With this, Tanaka has 2 correct choices to pick from
I've got a lot. A lot.
Shibuya Public Hall,
Hibiya Yaon (Open Air Concert Hall)
Nakano Sun Plaza,
But, let's go to [@!$!@]
Let's get inside, we'll think more afterwards. Let's end this.
Will they all meet up? Or remain scattered?
Matsumoto's group heads towards Shibuya Public Hall
It's close though, Shibuya Hall
They used to film "The Top 10" here right?
You know, I think Hamada,
I feel like he'll go to Budokan
Really? I guess Budokan does stand out
What other choices are there?
There's Nakano Sun Plaza,
If we don't meet up here, I'm definitely gonna miss my salon appointment...
Meanwhile, Hamada...
If it's just me going to Budokan, and Tanaka meets up with them, that would be the worst
I'm thinking maybe Tokyo Dome might be it...
But we have finally gotten back to the centre
Indeed, indeed
Just remember one of them said he's at a Yudetaro in Kojimachi
The theme; A Concert Hall
There are two correct answers for Tanaka to choose from,
Shibuya Public Hall? Or Nippon Budokan?
I am wondering about some places,
What places?
Maybe Yoyogi ... Yoyogi National Gymnasium,
Also, Shibuya Orchard Hall
It does seem like a classic answer
Yes, certainly
Also, I guess after all,
Shibuya Public Hall. 3 of them are in Ebisu,
You wanna aim for them?
Yes, let's meet them
Other than those ... A concert hall huh?
Well, considering the closest one to Kojimachi,
Budokan is the closest
I forgot about Budokan
It's famous for Rock concerts
Yeah true, I wasn't able to come up with Budokan
With this, Budokan became the right answer,
And Hamada, who is unaware of this ...
It could be that they go to Yoyogi,
And Tanaka and I meet up at Budokan
An awakening...
Right?
Meanwhile, Matsumoto & Friends arrive at Shibuya Public Hall
It has now been 3 hours since the start
Budokan is totally wrong
Yeah Budokan is out
It's been 40 minutes already
I think Yokohama Arena was a bad idea too
No, you're right, I don't know why I said that. Forgive me.
That is the worse idea,
Why did you say Yokohama?
Sorry, I could only think of that one...
But there's so many other places! Like Budokan, or Shibuya Hall-
Now that you say it, you're right
Sorry, can we move on now?
Wow, you're trying to avoid that conversation
You're apologising so much
I'm kind of hungry too, can we move on?
So annoying
Shall we grab lunch?
Hell no!
Just get lost already
Meanwhile,
They're not here. They would be standing somewhere obvious like that if they were.
A bad atmosphere at the deserted Budokan
Enough already!
That's enough
Meanwhile, Tanaka who still has a chance to meet up heads towards Shibuya
He had to choose from 3 concert halls,
There's also NHK Hall, isn't there?
Is NHK Hall different from Shibuya Public Hall?
They're close by, but different places
I'm a bit confused...
Out of nowhere, a 4th choice!
His 4th choice is just 400m from the others,
Will it be Shibuya Hall where Matsumoto's group is?
Where exactly did Tanaka get off?
I'm counting on this one, seriously
The fact he went to Yudetaro is so shocking...
He needs to face some punishment
I really want him to face some punishment
Shall we boil him?
(TN: Boil = Yude)
Here?
They're there! They're there!
See! They're there!
No way!
Sorry for the wait,
But this is great!
Thank you
We thought you wouldn't come here, so we were talking shit about you this whole time
Of course I came! When you think of a concert hall, it's gotta be Shibuya Public Hall
Right, they've got the theatre in there too
Yes, exactly. Also considering the distance.
Incidentally, where else did you think of?
Shibuya Orchard Hall
So close!
Your sketchy personality is showing!
Time's Up here
They report their locations on a group call
Over here, we've got 4 people
You're lying right?
We are waiting in front of Shibuya Public Hall
Where the hell did you get Shibuya Public Hall from?
It's the first place you should associate with a concert
No way, you associate concerts with Budokan!
There it is
No, listen. This is where all of the great artists had their live concerts
That's true for Shibuya Public Hall too
All they did there was "The Top Ten"!
I mean they did do that here,
Who cares about that
Piss off! I don't care about your salon appointment
Listen, there's 4 of us here
Alright
"The Top Ten"!
That's what they did there
It was just Machiaki!
(Machiaki = Masaaki Sasaki, who was in that show)
"Let's finish this!" -  What's the theme this time?
The last one right?
Aquarium
Let's say the first one we thought of
Ready, ste-
Wait!
There's too many to choose from
You know too many!
There are 5 aquariums within Tokyo,
Which will they choose?
It's gotta be that one,
Shinagawa!!
Sunshine!!
What did you say?
Sunshine...
It can't be Ikebukoru!
It's gotta be Shinagawa
I see
Thinking about the size
There's 2 of them in Shinagawa...
There's also Shinagawaw Prince Hotel Aquarium
The more popular one...
Which one?
I think Shinagawa Prince...
Ah, the Aqua Park?
That one is a mutiplex, so maybe he went a movie with his wife there
With his wife?
With his wife, or a different wife
Meanwhile, at Nippon Budokan
What did he come up with?
Maybe I'll go home...
There it is, Aqua Park!
Matsumoto's group arrives at Aqua Park Shinagawa
and Hamada?
You're joking...
What? No way!
He's not here!
There was no sign of Hamada there
Man it's gone dark now...
Then where is he heading to?
That tall bean pole (Tanaka) probably felt like this...
Every time...
If we have to do 1 more theme, I feel like we'll do 2 more themes,
He could be in Ikebukuro
He could have gone there
It's possible he went to an aquarium we could never come up with
Hamada finally arrives
Enough
I think today...It's not happening
Will they be able to meet up?!
If he went to Kasai or something, the next one will be impossible!
Just simply im-
Thank god!
Finally, congratulations!
Don't you tell me "congratulations", idiot!
You went to Yudetaro!
Yudetaro-
I don't want Yudetaro man to tell me congrats
But man, that is amazing you did that
I will never forget that
Please, it's so embarassing
Will you make it to your appointment?
I think so, If I go there