On the night before the struggle..
Subs by FlondrapicaSubs (flondrapicasubs.tumblr.com)
the snowfall in an district of Kanto
From here on out, the challenge will be cruel
For the first time, this is Gaki No Tsukai Ya Arrahende
We have to be positive without any reason
No Negativity allowed in the middle of Winter Tour!!
Yeaaah!
So, this is the second time..
Well of course I knew, something was going on today
As soon as I saw these Boxes for changing I was really pissed off!
As soon as I saw the boxes I was soo pissed!
- I totally get that
On an extremly hot day the year before
The members of Gaku No Tsukai who are prone to making negative comments
had to put on winter clothes
and go on a sightseeing tour where they had to hide their real feelings
However..
Couldn't they have parked the car somewhere closer?
- Look, there it is!
The road is freakin' packed
Because you idiots chose such a stupid time do this recording!
In the end, their negativity came out rapidly!!
On this day, they will pretend that they are in midsummer
The crazy temperature we have today is 6.4°C
Nice kick!  Nice punch!
Your negativity came really out there
Only your positivity today please!
And that idiot is taking a day off!
- Ah, that's right!
Hosei Tsuketei is missing due to a case of influenza
- Even though you had a box for him
He doesn't feel too well so he took the day off
If it's hot, you can't say that it's hot
but if it's cold you can't speak at all
One can just be silent
Yeah, but..
Ouch!
These two are in a really bad mood, so could you please stop?
We also say that to &$%§$
During the tour many
negativity traps will be layed
Absolutely no negativity allowed
The most negative person will be punished at the end
The rules:
Because it will be tiresome to be positive all the time
I brought a whistle with me
Only if I blow this whistle, the negativity ban will be lifted
So we can just complain normally then?
- Then, let's go
- It's pretty cold, right?
Please, wait a moment
Come on..
First, you need to change
From here on, the negativity ban starts!
But even now it's already really fucking cold
The ban just started so you already instantly collected one point there
- Wow, I don't like this game at all
With that being said, they will change into outfits that one would were in the midst of summer
You have to be kidding me...
This reminds me of New Year's ..
I really don't want to take my hat off
- We will count that as negativity as well!
After three minutes..
Ah, this is really good!
but it's colder than in the summer, right?
Wow, this is awesome! Are you for real?
While surpressing their inner feelings they behave positively but..
Aaa, this is bad, this is bad..
- Everybody, how are you doing with your change of clothes?
I'm still freakin' changing!!
I can't come out right now!
- What the hell? I'm still changiing!!
This is really harsh..
This is so harsh!
I don't want to say it again but we have already started!
The negativity flows out of their mouths, now Downtown already has a small lead!
Can we start?
Let's do this! Open the Boxes!
Oh yeaah!
Oh yeaah
Awesome!
Those are Mouton Boots, right?
Huh, what do you mean?
The clothes are not distributed fairly
Trap
That's strange!
- Look at your ears!
Well,, everyone has something different
Well, I have the thinnest clothes of all
Trap
Only a tank top
and it's also very short
Trap
The clothing doesn't fit
I would have liked to wear them
- This is not warm at all
And my shorts.. Why this size?
The warmest part of my body right now is around here
Your microphone?
Except for this part, I'm feeling cold everywhere
Fully enjoying  attractions and marine sports
Tokyo Dome City
Odaiba Seaside Park
Even while on the move there is no negativity allowed
Will we be actually able to do this?
I don't want to catch a cold! I really don't
He said it
- If I catch a cold, what then?
I can't have a cold right now
- That's negativity as well
This baldy is still here, so it's fine!
Minuspoint for Hamada
Makes fun of unassuming staff
You just badmouthed him!
and he isn't even bald even one bit
- He's so bald!!
That's really positive, Matsumoto
- He's not bald at all
Where exactly is he bald?
At last, the bus drives of!
And in order to improve their mood..
Since we are just normally on the move right now, we will do a positive Shirotori!
Shiritori: A Japanese word game where the players have to
come up with a new word starting with the last kana of the previous one
He's presenting it very poorly
Let's do with a "warm" theme
Let's do it!
Endo is also complaining a little bit now and then
- What do you mean?
Let's do it, Let's do it!
Let's start with "ri" from Shiritori
It itches..
That's also negative!
- What the hell!
He's like, if it's cold then it is okay to have an itch
He thought he was safe!
To complain about an itch is negative too
- Come on, what the hell
And when will you freaking come up with something?
It takes so long!
To completely bite into an apple
What's that?
Look look
Hey, I'm a tsukkomi!
He's so cruel, are you even paying attention to him?
That was cruel..
"To completely bite into an apple"
Okay Matsumoto, say something starting with "ri"
Ri .. Ri .. Uhh
Risa Stegmayer!
Because there is nothing negative you can say about Risa Stegmayer!
- There really is nothing negative
- Risa Stegmeyer!
So Hamada, something that starts with "ya"
Yahoooo~~~
Well, that was positive, wasn't it?
That was good!
That was unlike him!
Thank you very much
That has a good meaning, right?
Well Endo, say something with "ho"
Positive things, right?
Hop! Step! Jump!
Everything he said ended in a "p", though!
30 minutes after the tour start
Shut up!
Negativity ban is lifted
You just heard that, right?
Yeah, but it was after we blew the whistle
But you heard that, right? That was directed at the whistle
You don't have to say that every single time, you bastard
You heard that, right?
We can say anything we want right now
You idiot! You freakin' moron!!
Did you just hear that?
Can't you just fine him for that?
I was just cushed at so harshly
Some bad things about Gaki No Tsukai are showing today
Some harsh thing we are doing..
We couldn't do that on TV Asahi [a tv station]
But I haven't appeared on there even once
The bus arrives at the first part of the tour
Well our first station will be the attractions of Tokyo Dome City
They say it's especially fun there
Okay, what is it?
Hamada is looking like he's dead right now
I'm not dead! I was just looking at where we are going
I didn't want to interrupt
Negativity ban tour station #1
Tokyo Dome City Attractions
We will let them have fun with the different attractions!
(Staff) We will do some preparations
Please wait a little bit
Trap:
The staff member and License are leaving their seats
This is really harsh
Negativity is still being judged
This will be so bad
There are so many shadowy spots
I will catch a cold
We'll definitely catch a cold
They don't have any water here at all
Trap
No drink were prepared
When I'm so dehyrated, whatever you might tell me..
If you tell me that, it's definitely a loss
"Ah Matsumoto-San, we don't have any water"
There are a bunch of cameras rolling right now
Negativity ranking
45 minutes have passed and Downtown already has a big lead.
Is the winner already settled?
Temperature: 4°C
We have some cool attractions so please hurry
This is impossible, right?
Isn't this awful?
As soon as they go outside, the negativity rapidly increases
Hamada! Hamada
What the hell are you doing?
This is so spacious, I like it
Hamada dashes to a sunny spot the moment he sees it. This of course counts as negativity
The weather is good, right?
Yeah, this weather is awesome
Wonderful, wonderful
With some sprinkled positive remarks, they approach the attractions
Everybody, please take a look
First off, this is our first attraction:
Super Biking Sorabune
We will let them enjoy this trill where the swing even reaches a height of 15 meters
Well, everybody, let's go!
Well, shouldn't the senpai go first?
That is like a rule
Strong punching
A negativity point for Hamada
Cocorico said they want to ride it at any cost
Are you for real?
- Ah sorry, my body height is not sufficient
It says you have to be at at least 110 cm tall.
You're not taller than 110 cm?
- I'm 109 cm
That's humour, just humour
Come on, let's go
To make it simple, rather than just saying something random:
This ride is really scary!
Right?
But this scariness is good, right?
Please, just go everybody
Negative point for Hamada:
Strong punching
Freakin go ride it!
He has just been so negative all the time
He just hit me!
Just surrender!!
I just want you to have some fun
FUCKING RIDE IT
While Downtown is grumbling about, they are  somehow approaching the riding platform
Everybody, please
I really don't want to
It's really unpleasant and it's so fucking cold
Downtown is really no good for this kind of thing
But some middle school students just rode this..
Well, let's just stop the camera
and just call Okamoto [creative director at Downtown's agency]
To see if it's okay to ride?
If Hamada rides I will ride too but
if Hamada is acting up so much, I just want to match him
So if Hamada rides..
Us being a duo, I really want to treasure that
I won't ride this!
With that, in the end only Cocorido rides the swing
Are you all set?
Then let's go!
Do it for 20 minutes!
The attraction starts!
Trap
Facing strong wind, it becomes even colder
They don't even put up their hands..
They are putting so much force into their shoulder
They are not waving back at us at all..
Cocorico's negative point
Not waving their hands at all
They are not waving back at us at all..
Welcome back! How was it?
It was cold, really awesome!
You should have looked more happy riding it
- You didn't wave back at us!
If Matsumoto and me would have been on there,
we would have done it like this
- I want to see that
I reached out to Okamoto, he said we couldn't do it
23 times
15 times
Negativity ranking
38 times
41 times
With this stop, Hamada remains at the top
1 hour since starting
Betting on a price, the two duos face of in a shooting game
Sure enough the result was..
Finish!
With 3050 points over 2830 points, Downtown wins!
Downtown triumphs!!
Watercannon fooooooou!
With this positivity appeal, Downtown attempts to come back
Hamada, how was the water cannon game?
- Yeah, it was fun
You just were silent and concentrated, right?
Well, the water cannon game itself was fun
And when I looked to to my side, there was my partner
and I thought: Man, this is such a splendid thing we're doing right now
And now a short break for their tired bodies
Well, these chairs..
The chairs are made out of cold aluminium
Trap
So cold!
You were splendid at the water cannons
so here is your reward
Trap
Their price is an extra portion of ice cream scoops
Congratulations!
Trap:
Only the winners receive a special scoop of blissful flavour
Strong wind
Ou, this is awesome
It's so freakin cold!
It's really so freakin' cold
I won't eat this
I hate chocolate chip icecream
My toes are about to tear off because it's so cold
They're about to tear off, it's so freakin' cold
Do you have a coat or something?
Oh, we have some
To anger Matsumoto, another trap awaits
Why can't you open it? NAKAMURA!
Trap:
The buttons and the zipper are shut
FUCKING HURRY UP
Enjoying attractions and marine sports
Tokye Dome City
Odaiba Seaside Park
Even when they allow me to put this on, it's still impossible to do
Before one knows it, the five put on some jackets. The next halt is...
This is our second attraction, the Sky Flower
No way, no way..
This is absolutely impossible
The Skyflower
We will let them enjoy a superb and unbroken view of the city
Let's have Cocorico take a little look
Take a peek so see what it is like
Meaning, you will ride after that, right?
- Yeah Yeah, exactly
We are already talking to Okamoto on the phone
Take off your coat Tanaka, take it off already!
- For the time being, let's just go
Now now now just wait a second, please wait
Please, let's ride with everyone at least one time
For some reason, this turbulent situation remains unstable
Endo's negativity point:
Attempting escape
Hamada's and Tanaka's negativity point:
Also escaping
A little bit too abrupt end to this tour
Come on, this skyflower thing is impossible for me to do
- But there's nobody left but you
- You're calling this sky flower, but there aren't any flowers here
Come on it's so cold, I can't handle this talk right now
and this holiday season is also unappealing
Talk with the 5 Member
Suddenly on New Year's..
Well Endo.. in Guam
Well in Guam I unexpectedly met Hamada
Well, I went there with my parents and my girlfriend
We stayed at this hotel which was located inside a golf course
And at 7 in the morning when hardly anyone was there
my girlfriend and I went out to get some breakfast
we saw some kind of staff and we thought something was going on
I thought I was wrong but as I was putting I saw Hamada sitting and smoking a cigarette
He was just like "Good morning"
I didn't know anything about it at all
- You'd be surprised, right?
- I was so surprised!
"I went to the golf course with my girlfriend, just the two of us!"
"While I'm doing Cocorico"
I remember something similar
I first met Endo when he came to a recording for Gaki No Tsukai
That time, he also brought his girlfriend with him
This is true, right?
There was a woman beside him all the time
So I couldn't get it off my mind asked him: "Who is that?"
"That's my girlfriend"
We then talked for a bit.
He told me he had liked Downtown for a very long time  and always wanted to see us in person and then he said:
"I just tried to pick up some girls"
You're the worst!
For real?
At our location?
You wouldn't even come up with that, right?
I was really troubled at the time so..
I don't think anyone of my juniors was troubled like that
For me, I also didn't have a good impression of them, when I met the two for the first time
Well Tanaka..
It was Tokyo Station, right?
So we two went to pick him up from the station, right?
A taxi was hard to find so I said to Yamazaki: "Sorry, we have to go pick him up"
So I told him this bean pole is my junior Tanaka
So me and Yamazaka where in the back and Tanaka sat next to the driver
and then for the whole journey
he didn't utter even one word
I thought he was on sleeping pills or something
You didn't say one word, right?
I was really nervous and stiff so
so we drove from Tokyo Station to Shibuya
And while we were driving through Aoyama..
Yamazaki said to Matsumoto: "Who is this clay doll-looking guy?"
That you had to ask while we were in Aoyama..
He had seen the taxi driver more often than Tanaka at that time
Thanks for watching!
Feel free to like my facebook page:
www.facebook.com/FlondrapicaSubs