TPF
First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai! Limits series:
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Yamazaki Hosei
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
How far is omurice still omurice? Let's bet on its limits!
Here we are
We already did 6 rounds before
Yeah we did
Limits series
Round 1:
Ice Coffee
"Limits Series" explores how far you can change words when making an order
Round 2:
Hiyashi Chuuka
In the past, they tried it with "Ice Coffee", "Hiyashi-Chuuka"
Third round:
Mild Seven
Round 4:
Cutlet Curry
And several other words
Round 5:
Char Siu Men
Round 6:
Napolitan
Last time, Matsumoto ordered a "Napolitan" by saying "Tamori-san"
Here's the result
An egg & veggies sandwich
is that what you ordered?
Excuse me, I'd like to order a...
Tamori-san
Ma'am
Is my Tamori-san on its way?
There's a Napolitan coming up...
Huh!?
We are making a Napolitan, you hear me?
You got that?
Yes
My spaghetti Tamori-san
What the hell?
Are you kidding me?
Do you like omurice?!
So noisy...
You startled me
Do you like it?
Omurice
Yeah I guess so
Is that so? Today we're doing it
That's what we'll do
But I changed the rules a bit
Really?
We have some phrases in the box, you just take one
Order your omurice with the phrase you took
from inside the box: if you win, you'll get a prize
Rules
And we go with that, but the prize money...
Producer Suga sets the prize money for each phrase
It's up to Suga
Producer
Suga Kenji
I see, it depends on how hard it is
Exactly
If you think that you just
Can't do it with that price
Someone else can do it for you
Oh, I see
We can negotiate
That's right
Negotiations are ok
And now
Matsumoto will reveal this round's phrases
Here's our first one
Difficulty lv.1: Oomori raisu
(Large rice serving)
Oomori raisu
"Oomori raisu"
This one is going to work
You think so?
No doubts about it
I think so too
It clearly says "rice" too
Right
But how much is this worth, Suga-san?
I think 3000 yen at best
3000 yen?!
Yeah but isn't it good
To get 3000 yen out of this?
Next one
"Omoronai ssu"
Difficulty lv2: "Omoranai ssu"
(You're not funny)
Say it, dude
This one, you see...
"Omoronaissu", mhh
It depends on how you say it
"Omoronaissu"
"Omoronaissu"... yeah
I think this one is around 4000 yen
4000 yen, I see
Seems fair
Stingy prices, huh?
Stingy indeed
So it's real, the bubble did burst
It surely feels that way
Next one
"Komura aisu"
Difficulty lv3: Komura Ice
This is the "food vs food" one
The one when they say "alright, got it"
But you don't know which one they'll bring
Yeah, those
This happened before
Next one
"Homuresu"
Difficulty lv4: Homeless
It's homu-raisu...
"Homeless"
This one's harsh
Is this harsh?
Next
Difficulty lv5: Homo Sapiens
"Homo Sapiens"
From this point
It gets really difficult
It is hard, we can see that
Next
Difficulty lv.6: "Tabenaissu"
(I'm not eatin')
"Tabenaissu"
Not eating?
This is dangerous
It's risky
You'd get skipped
They could say "ok, ok"
Yeah, they'll skip your order
But it depends
Alright, next one
Difficulty lv. 7
Can you please make me
a modified chicken rice?
"Can you please make me a modified chicken rice?"
I think this is going to work
This one's good
You think so?
I think they'll get it to you
Yeah but how are they "modifying" it?
That's the issue
There's only one way
Don't you think it's gonna be it?
But they could just add ketchup
Oh, that too...
Or make it larger
This could go well or not, it's a gamble
Next one
Difficulty lv.8: 〇〇rice
"〇〇 raisu"
What?
This is a bet too
It's an ad-lib for the waiter
You just say it and see if an omuraisu will come
Ah, I see
It's like a quiz, I see
Yeah, a kind of quiz
A playful one
This is not good at all...
Next
Difficulty lv.9: Ann Lewis
"Ann Lewis"
I think it's better than this one
It's doable
I think it'll come
I can see that
Here's our last one
This one is amazing
Final lv.: Samurai
"Samurai"
Samurai...?
Is it really Samurai?
I mean, for omuraisu?
Yes, Samurai, just one kanji
I mean, if it was "SamuraiSU" I could see that...
Right?
That's unacceptable
We're going with just one kanji
This is more suitable
We're sticking to this
Suitable? It's just "samurai"
What is he talking about
And you're not one to talk, you said "Ouyang Ice Coffee" to order an ice coffee before
That one was horrible
It was
Challenging the limits of "ice coffee"
Oh,
I'll take one Ouyang Fifi
Ouyang Ice Coffee
Ice--
Ice coffee, right?
You clearly said it
I think in some cafès they now have Ouyang Ice Coffee on their menu
As if they do!
Such an orthodox boke-tsukkomi exchange
They'll now decide the first
phrase for the challenge
They're going to take
The first phrase from the box
Which one will it be?
Which is it?
Woah, I got a big one
Let me reveal it
"Homo Sapiens"
First phrase: "Homo Sapiens"
This is a tough one
How about this one, Suga?
"Homo sapiens"? Well, we started from 3000 yen
Yes
I think it's worth 30.000 yen
"Homo sapiens": 30.000 yen
Nice, isn't it?
We'll start from 30'000, it surely fits it
This word does
I agree
I mean, look at how many extra letters we got...
It's pretty bad
You're right
I don't have much confidence with this...
You think?
Yeah, I don't really want to do it either
Me too
That's a bad one
Then we're counting on you, Hamada
Me?!
Should I do it?
Are you going to?
Yeah, why not?
Well, everyone else is sayin' "I can't, I can't"
That's right
So I feel like I have to
That's so manly of you
Yeah, right?
Sometimes he's assaulted by **** old ladies
I swear, it's true
He's a rice bowl topped with unknown objects
Tofu Panda Fansubs Presents:
Down Town's Gaki no tsukai ya arahende!!
Translator:
Typesetter:
Shion
Otviss
**We also have facebook and twitter.**
______________________________________________________
To see progress of each episode we're working on, please visit Tofupandas.tumblr.com/subs. There you can find both streaming and download links for subbed episodes!  Be sure to also visit shion's site at shionnotsukai.wordpress.com!
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
So, Hamada-san
Yes?
First, they disguise so they won't be recognized
And now, they all move to their first shop
Let's be honest
You're the first one
So you have to get it right
We don't know if things are going to get worst later
You think you could do it?
What?
Getting this right
I think I can, if it's me, I did that
What?
Why the past tense?
Will they be able to get omuraisu
by saying "homo sapiens" instead!?
Will they get their omuraisu by saying Homo Sapiens?
Hamada's challenge begins!
Excuse me
Can we order?
Sure
I think omuraisu is not what I'm getting
For some reason, Matsumoto says "omuraisu"
Laughing Yamazaki
Is there hayashi-rice in the menu?
There is
Then I'll take it
Do you serve drinks as well?
We do
Then I'll have an ice tea
I'll have an ice coffee
I'll get that too
You're not gonna eat?
We're good
You're good with only drinks?
Alright, I'll have...
This is something
Homo... Homo Sapiens
What?
Let's see
Homo Sapiens
Excuse me, can you please cancel my ice
coffee and make it an ice au lait?
Alright, I'll have Homo Sapiens
You're not drinking anything?
An ice au lait and...
Homo Sapiens
Omuraisu
Sorry
Impossible
Well, this was a complete failure
It was impossible
Can't be helped
He also said "omuraisu" before, this idiot
What was that about?
I just couldn't help it
By the time I saw it on the menu
I thought "oh, they do have it" and I just said it
Should have stayed quiet
That surprised me
Really, I was surprised too
I thought "what is he sayin'?"
No way that could have worked
How can "homo sapiens" do it, huh?
I still think I could have pull it out
Then please
Can we please watch again
Matsumoto's failure before my order?
I think...
OMURAISU
is not what I'm getting
That was really bad
Unforgivable
Really really bad
Unbelievable
I couldn't believe it
I'm gonna do it
Round number two
Don't forget about paying Suga back
What the hell?
I'll be waiting for thy sum
"For thy sum"
Ok, next one
Ann Lewis
Next phrase: Ann Lewis
Here it is
What should we do?
This one...
This one is really...
I think we can do it
First, let's ask Suga its value
60.000 yen
Ann Lewis: 60.000 yen
For real?
Really?!
Of course
It's level 9 after all
It's normal
Homo Sapiens was way harder than this
No way, man
Are you kidding me?
It's 'cause you're stupid
Who wants to try it? I guess everyone, right?
I want to
I want to try that
You 3, play rock-paper-scissor to decide who's going
Uh? "You 3"?
Yeah
It's fine like this
After that huge failure you just did
I didn't fail at all
I didn't do anything like that
Alright, let's see that again
How many times?
I think...
OMURAISU
Is not what I'm getting
That was absurd
You three, go for it
Ready and, rock-paper-scissors
I did it!
He got Ann Lewis...
Will Yamazaki get an omuraisu
By saying Ann Lewis instead?!
Next challenger is Yamazaki
Will he get an omuraisu by saying Ann Lewis?
Can we...?
Sure, I'm coming
Whenever you want
I'll have an ice coffee
Sure
I'll have udon, please
Udon, got it
I'll have a cola
Cola, sure
Cream anmitsu
Yes
I'll have Ann Lewis
Man I'm thirsty
Me too
Tell me when you decided it
Oh, I have
Ann Lewis
Here goes
An ice coffee...?
Can I have a cheesecake too?
Ann Lewis
I think I'll have Ann Lewis
Orange juice, ok
This is the worst
It sucks
But we discovered something
If you say "Ann Lewis", you'll get orange juice
We now know that
This is...
That's way harder, man...
Shocking
Can't help it
Alright, your turn to draw, Yamazaki
Please give it all you got, you three
We will
Yeah, I mean
Of course we will
Suga-san is supporting us so much
Is that a big one?
Here it is
I see
Third phrase: homeless
"Homeless"
Perfect timing for this
You're right
Perfectly timed
I just thought about this, but...
I think the "MU" in omuraisu is the most important bit
I see
I see, huh
Ok, who's going for it?
I'm going
Really?
You haven't asked its price yet
You haven't yet
It's 200 yen
What!!
So loud
Let's make this 20.000 yen
Homeless: 20.000 yen
Not bad at all, you can do it
Will they be able to order omuraisu
by saying "homeless" instead?!
Can they order "omuraisu" by saying "homeless"?
Here's Tanaka's challenge!
Let's see...
I'll have ochazuke and nori
Ochazuke, alright
I'll take an ice coffee
Let's see... homeless
Sorry, what was that again?
Sorry but I heard "homeless"
Omuraisu
Omuraisu? Ok
He gave up
You just said it, dude
Yeah, so clearly
He said "omuraisu"
Dude, you just said "omuraisu"
He said it, yeah
It was only your second attempt
Right, too quick
But I---
When she got closer to you...
You panicked, right?
Right when she got closer
I couldn't do it
That was so bad
The hell is going on, today?
We're screwed
Did I really say "omuraisu"?
The first time you clearly
said "homeless"
And the second time you clearly
said "omuraisu"
That's exactly how it went, no more
and no less than that
I'll be counting on you
Listen
We changed our plan
By now there's no point
In doing the first ones
We have to think about
What our audience wants to see
So I thought about what we should do
And I think #7 and #10 are good
"Can you please make me a modified chicken rice?"
And "Samurai", me and Endo
Are gonna do them
Don't you think it's good?
I think it's good
How much was it? 3 million?
Say that to him, Endo
What the hell?
You said that, right?
You said that before, dude
What are you talking about?
We'll do it for 3 million
By the way, Suga-chan, how much is the chicken rice thing?
This one?
It never appeared before
So I'm gonna say...
They're 70.000 yen and 1 million
70.000 Yen
"Can you please make me a modified chicken rice?"
100.000 Yen
Samurai
This is huge
Here it comes!
Here it is!
But it depends on the shop we're going to
Yeah, right
You don't know if it works, it depends
Let me say it again
If you say "can you modify it?"
And they're like "how about omuraisu?"
That's no good
If you say "yes", it doesn't count
I see, I can't say "yes"
So I just have to act as if I'm thinking about it, right?
No
If you say anything implying "yes", it doesn't count
So I just have to keep quiet
"Can you please make me a modified chicken rice?"
Will it work for an omuraisu?
Endo is going to say "Can you please make me a modified chicken rice?"
Will it work for a omuraisu order?
Sorry to keep you waiting
I'll have a cake
I'm sorry, we don't have them today
Oh, you don't
Then I'll have an ice tea
Ice tea, ok
I'll have the same
Can I have a cola, please?
I'll take an ice coffee
Sorry, listen... can you please
make me a modified chicken rice?
To chicken rice?
Yeah, I'd like to have it kinda modified, you know
You want me to add something to it?
You just have to
modify a bit a chicken rice
Got it
Wanna order anything else?
Oh, we're good
Ok, got it, I'll be back soon
He said it according to rules
Really?
That waitress took that nicely
But we don't know what's gonna come
Excuse me...
I'm sorry to disturb you
But we don't have chicken rice
We can make you a Mexican pilaf or a sansai pilaf...
Chicken rice...
No Mexican pilaf, then?
I had chicken rice
yesterday, so... is there anything like it?
Mexican pilaf is similar to it
How about you just modify a Mexican pilaf?
Is there anything you want me to add to it?
Just modify it a bit, that's it
2 minutes later
How about a Mexican pilaf and fried chicken
set? Is that good?
I'm sorry, sir
Let's see...
We can make it a single serving
No
That's not really it...
What are you saying?
You're just babbling about...
You know, I want it to look like this
Come again?
Yeah, look like what?
Dude, she's busy you know
Excuse me
It's fine
Can you like, wrap it up or stuff?
You mean omuraisu?
I really don't know much about that...
Man, he's so sly
I'll leave it up to you
Is it really ok?
You're practically already out, dude
You're so out
"Wrap it up" was not good
But I didn't say "egg" or anything
That doesn't mean anything
You really tried, I recognize that
Or better, that waitress really tried
Yeah, she sure did
Let's give her 70.000 yen
What dish is she going to bring them!?
Sorry to have kept you waiting
Here, I asked the chef
To do a chicken rice and make an omuraisu out of it
Surprisingly, the omuraisu appears
Oh, thank you
That's what I wanted to eat
Excuse me
This means nothing
They don't have it in the menu
But it doesn't mean anything
How should we judge this one?
This is outside the menu
I think that hint you gave doesn't help you
You mean "wrap it up"?
What should we do?
If only you didn't say that phrase,
"wrap it up"...
That sentence is against the rule
It got you your omuraisu
Try eat that, try
What do you think about it?
Here I go
It tastes like modified chicken rice
Suga-san, here's what happened
First off,
This restaurant had no chicken rice on the menu
I see
I told them if they could modify a chicken rice
And at first we got stuck on that
Then I told them to "wrap it up", I used those words
This is no good
I know
Me too I thought I've lost, then it appeared
And they brought me this
Out-of-menu chicken rice
With an omuraisu thing on top of it
What do you think?
You failed
And we're done
Four consecutive outs...
All four of us, yeah
This is impressive
And that means we reached our finale
Samurai
It's time for Samurai
I'm gonna do it truthfully
Really, I swear
I won't do anything shady, I'm gonna make
that omuraisu appear by saying that
It's "samurai", you know
I'll say just that
If it doesn't come, this ep would suck
You gotta do it for Gaki
You have to say "samurai" and nothing else
What do you mean?
What do you mean what?!
That's how the game works
Right
You can't say "samuraisu" or such
If you add a "su", you're out
Yeah I mean
That's a huge rule violation
It's worth a fine
I could get fired for that and I wouldn't complain
Ordering "omuraisu" by saying "samurai":
Is it possible?
No one succeeded yet in this Limits series episode
Can you order an omuraisu by saying samurai?
Matsumoto is going to try
I'm going to the toilet
Matsumoto plans on ordering it
as he's coming back from the toilet
I'm ready to take orders
I'm taking a soda, ma'am
Alright, what else?
Two sodas
I'm taking a coffee
Hot coffee is ok?
Cola
There's another one at the toilet
Oh, excuse me
I'll have a samurai
What was that?
Samuraisu
Omuraisu? You're ok with that?
Yep
Is it really ok?
Yeah
No man, you didn't say that
You said "samuraisu"
You said it
You said it with such resolution
You're playing dirty
I just got that right, didn't I?
You didn't
Everyone had a face like "what?"
I was like "huh?"
Samuraisu
You said "rice" so clearly
I bet he didn't want to say that
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
But he clearly said it, that's what happened
Samuraisu?
He said samuraisu
We told you couldn't add "su", didn't we?
Yeah, no "su" allowed, right
And why did you say it?
Of course you end up sayin' it
Did I say that?
Stop denying it
We released a book to celebrate of TV show Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende's fifteenth year, which talks about its story.
Its title is "kiseki". It also features a special interview with Hitoshi Matsumoto and Masatoshi Hamada.
You can buy it now on any bookstore and featured shop!