TPF
Here comes a loud voice
The first ever Gaki No Tsukai Ya Arahende Chiki Chiki!
Huh? That's not really...
I've always wanted to try this!
Absolutely Tasty Okonomiyaki!
Here we go!
Can you do that one more time?
He totally didn't put any effort into it!
They're gonna think you're on the verge of death!
It's been 5 years since the last one!
We haven't done it.
5 years!?
r
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tsukitei Housei
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
"I've always wanted to try this!"
Ah, Really?
Really
We have quite the great theme today
It's Okonomiyaki!
Block
Using ingredients that they think are absolutely delicious
They must make Okonomiyaki and be judged on a scale of 1-10
Yep!
I wanted to complain about something earlier regarding Okonomiyaki
Okay
Alright
It's "Okonomiyaki" but they wouldn't let us do what we wanted
TL Note: The Okonomi means "preference"
Your "okonomi"
Even though we can't do what we really want, we have to cook
I get it now
So because of that, you know, like, it's
Say it
Please go ahead
It's impossible!!
Impossible!
It's totally off!
I just thought I'd let out
some of the anger I had towards this food
It's something you all want to do right?
You can do a lot of Okonomiyaki.
Of course I've been thinking about it!
So we're gonna pick a winner at the end?
Yep!
Yeah!
Is that so?
I think there's a punishment as well.
A punishment?
Punishment?
No way...
A punishment for this?
Punishment...
A Skinhead.
Skinhead!?
The one with the lowest score
Skinhead
Can I rethink my menu over?
That's a pretty heavy punishment!
You're right.
Block
Absolutely Tasty Okonomiyaki
Planning a delicious menu
Devising fresh and original recipes,
The Absolutely Tasty Okonomiyaki Challenge!
Absolutely Tasty Okonomiyaki
Hamada Masatoshi's attempt
The top batter is Hamada Masatoshi!
Open!
Yellow
Basic
Ingredients
Boiled Vegetables  Pork Ribs  Curry Powder
I see!
Huh?
It's curry.
Curry!?
That's a good idea!
It's not good huh?
I think it's smart!
What do you think of him playing it safe like this?
I'm not "playing it safe"
He's really playing it safe, right?
Is that so?
Then we have this
The vegetables
Looks like a lot of fun!
Housei really loves it huh?
He got really interested in it
If this tastes bad then he's out of the running!
I agree...
This is...
I have 2 dishes!
One of the two at the very least...
Wait...
I want to say "Look! It's delicious huh!?"
Yeah well...
So the next one
you challenged yourself, right?
I'm not sure if I challenged myself...
Really?
Please try to
In private he's
always challenging himself, though
When would I ever challenge myself in private
He always says "no, I can do better" in private
Brush on the oil
Oh yeah, I need to do that!
He forgot the oil until right before it's done
He's shaken up
The oil, huh?
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents:
Down Town's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Translators:
Typesetter:
Proofreader:
DCSubs
&
Callanse
Derek
Otviss
**We also have Facebook and Twitter.**
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
____________________________________________________________________
If you ever see this video being distributed online but not by us, keep in mind that on Youtube
individuals may make money off of sharing fansubs like this that are not their own. Please go back and
support the original creators. Fansubbing is voluntary and is not meant to generate profit. You can
download episodes on our website instead. Thanks for watching!
The man who's gonna help us cook today
Oh
The owner of Mojihei Okonomiyaki, Mr. Nakano!
Supporting Cook
Mojihei Okonomiyaki's Jun Nakano
Thanks for helping us today
Should I put this in now?
Go ahead
The batter is from Mojihei so
Is that so?
Yeah.
Yes
Info Box
Grilling on the stove
Cooking Step 2
We're all gonna use it
It's good stuff
So really anything we make should be good
Right
There's a disgusting amount of carrots in this
"A disgusting amount"
It's ok
Following this, He puts the bacon on the grill to cook
Cook it however you like it.
Alright, I'll cook it.
He couldn't even lay it on the grill!!
What was with that?
Did you see that?
Did you see it?
I saw it!
What was that!?
I sure saw it!
Right here!
You saw it!?
He's so bad at it
So bad
You're wrong!
If this was darts, it would have hit the pool cue resin
The pork stuck to my finger, that's all
It doesn't stick, so
This is scary
Some funny stuff is happening
Info Box
Once one side is
cooked, flip it over
Cooking Step 3
Put the pork rib meat on top
and flip it over when the bottom is cooked
So the perfect dish is 10 points, right?
Usually, yes
Yes
I think
Just for this recipe taking away 4 points
is about right
Since he played it safe
A perfect score would still be a 6
I'm not "playing it safe"
Just using straight up curry
That's right
What the hell...
His personality is coming out
Huh?
He's not yelling at us
He always likes to play it safe
Really?
When we first started comedy
"We're going with Yoshimoto"  is what he told me
Is that the safe route?
I said Schouchiku was
the best for us
If we went with Shouchiku we wouldn't even exist
Flip it over to check if cooked,
then leave it to finish
So now I'll use this
Ah! Here we go!
Finally, here we go
Ah, right on top
Oh, he's using it like that
Like instead of sauce
Info Box
Pour the curry on top of the cooked okonomiyaki
Cooking Step 4
Exactly
Wait wait wait
So it's a curry sauce?
Of COURSE it's gonna be delicious
He isn't being adventurous at all
Not even a tiny bit adventurous
Hamada's First Dish
Curry Okonomiyaki
Hamada's first item
Curry Okonomiyaki! How does it taste?
But really
I am looking forward to it
Looking forward to it?
Of course he is!
I am
Not at...
Really?
This'll be exactly what we think it is
It's like
Mori Shinichi  singing "Ofukurosan"!
But isn't this kinda fun?
It is, right?
We get to eat the standard okonomiyaki
So do we eat it just like this?
Eat it how you like
If the curry isn't enough...
Itadakimasu
He said "eat it how you like"
That was awful
Isn't it scary?
He said the one word he's not supposed to say
If there's not enough curry, just put more sauce on it
This is it
I mean,
it's good, but
really
it's good
Can I say something quick?
It's really really good!
Sorry to say
It's really really good
It's good, right?
Of course it is, BUT
It tastes good, but
I f we're talking about how challenging it was to create...
Right?
We have to think of that
That's what counts
Honestly I could eat 2!!
However...
Exactly
That's why it's hard
It's delicious
That's right
If it tastes good it tastes good
Alright, so
Ahhhh
How many points was my okonomiyaki?
You see,
In a way it's a 10
You're right
It could even become a product
Right
A good product
A delicious one
It's a 10 out of 10
But since he didn't challenge himself how many points should it be
What do you think
5 points for me
What about Tanaka?
I'm thinking 3 points is right
You just said it was really really good!
It's good, but
It's only good because
the curry is delicious
Because the curry is good
That's it
These 3 points
are only there because of the curry.
Right
That's why
Tanaka is absolutely right
That's the reason
I was drawn in by the curry
The curry
I know that now
Because of the curry...
I know I was pulled in by the curry
Curry Okonomiyaki
Since he didn't challenge himself,
he lost some points, ending with a 4/10
The next item is
This!
Yellow
Basic
Ingredients
Salt Grilled Sanma   Grated Daikon
Huh?
He's challenging himself with this one
I can't imagine how it'll be
This is adventurous
You guys all like sanma, right?
It's delicious
I love it
Me too, so I really wanna eat this
Is it ok just like that?
The bones and everything?
I see, for calcium
Info Box
Make the sanma into a minced paste
Cooking Step 1
It's good for you
The whole thing?
Even the head
I'm using the whole thing
So even the internal organs
Yea, the black stuff and everything
Everything?
Absolutely everything
That's kinda...
It's salt grilled, right?
That's right
I'll spoon all of this out
At least
It's an adventurous recipe
Right?
That's true
Now there's just this okonomiyaki batter
Info Box
Mix the Minced Paste and Batter Together
Cooking Step 2
It's already coming together
The whole fish
is mixing in well
It really is
What is this gonna taste like?
Put the oil on the pan already!!
I'm doing it right now, ok?
Oil the pan, already!
I'm doing it right now
He can't learn
You can't say it right before I'm about to
you said it a little too early
No no no
No no no no
You have to do it before that
I see, I see
It'll be fine if I do it now
He really just did it again
Yes he did
He did
See, look
Looks good, right?
Info Box
Spread It on the Grill
Cooking Step 3
He's not using any other ingredients
I'm kinda looking forward to this one
Yea
What'll it taste like
Right?
Exactly
Info Box
After Cooking Both Sides, Add Soy Sauce for Flavor
Cooking Step 4
After both sides are cooked,
add soy sauce for flavor, and it's almost done
Huh? And then...
This is that smell
That smell?
Uh, kamaboko?
Info Box
Load It Up with Grated Daikon
Cooking Step 5
You're putting that on while it's grilling, huh
Shouldn't you do that over here?
This is warmed up too, so
It'll get too hot
This
Huh?
This is warmed up too
Is it okay to do it like that?
I have to do it here to get you guys excited
"Excited"?
How's it look?
So he's not doing this part on the grill
Info Box
Squeeze Some Citrus on Top
Cooking Step 6
I don't get his rules
Hamada's Second Dish
Sanma and Grated Daikon Okonomiyaki
Okonomiyaki using an entire sanma
How will it taste?
It actually looks like
fish cake when it's like this
Oh yea, it does
Oh, I see
It has the kamaboko, right?
That's why
Itadakimasu
Here we go
What the f### is this
This isn't right
What IS this
It's crunchy, and
the texture of the bones and stuff is the worst
It tastes awful
You really wanted to mess with us, huh
What is this
I feel bad after eating this
Unpleasant
It's unpleasant
I hate this
Hate it?
I hate it too
Honestly
I never wanna eat this again
Me neither
It's cat food
Cat food
Cats will love this
1 point
Me too
What's wrong with you?
No no, it's a 1
I'd give it a 1
What gives it the 1 point?
Because it was warm
It was warm?
Yes
That's because it's okonomiyaki, though!
What's wrong with you!
Because he cooked it
Everyone's is warm
It's warm so 1 point
I gave it 1 point because
in middle school we were good friends
Sanma and Grated Daikon Okonomiyaki
The taste and texture was bad
so the rating is 1 point
Absolutely Tasty Okonomiyaki!
Shouzou Endou's Attempt
The next presentation is Endou's first dish
Here it is
Yellow
Basic
Ingredients
Mapo Tofu
It's Mapo Tofu
Looks good
It does
Really, I'm trusting you
So I'll just put this right in
Just putting it straight in
Already
It's extremely simple
Info Box
Mix the Mapo Tofu and Batter together
Cooking Step 1
Straight away,
mix the mapo tofu and batter and cook
It's really simple, just like this
Very very simple
For me it's just, I love mapo tofu
Really?
Have you always loved it?
You really didn't know?
No idea
In Osaka
I know a really great place to get it
Osaka, huh
Let's go together, Hou-san
I'm good
He doesn't know one in Tokyo
What about Tokyo?
You should know one in Tokyo then
Tokyo...      Nope
Info Box
Cook Both Sides, and Flip
Cooking Step 2
Now, after cooking both sides
flip it over, and it's done!
It's really soft since it's tofu
But... This might be pretty good
Endou's First Dish
Mapo Tofu Okonomiyaki
Endou's first dish, Mapo Tofu Okonomiyaki
How will it taste?
Let's eat
Itadakimasu
The tofu is surprisingly unchanged
Here we go
How is it?
It's alright
It's not bad but, it lacks flavor
There's not enough oomph
It's just alright
Unfortunately
It's too bad
I see
It's really unfortunate
Something's missing
So how many points does it get?
Can I say it?
Please
6 Points
Oh, Thank you
I also give it a 6
Thank you
Is it really even a 6?
I personally wanted a little bit more from it, so
5 Points
5 points, huh
Hamada-san?
5 Points
Oh, really?
That was a pleasant surprise
Very pleasant
I thought he'd give me a 2 or 3
After all he's the only one who ate all of it
You even ate all of it for me
After saying it was just a 5
Mapo Tofu Okonomiyaki
After Hamada ate every last bite
The highest score so far, 5 points!
Now my second dish
It's Protein Okonomiyaki
Wait, I don't wanna eat this
It doesn't look the least bit appetizing
Yellow
Basic
Ingredients
Protein Chicken Tenderloin Broccoli
I don't want this!
The first impression is...
If this turns out good
It'll be revolutionary
True
In the fitness industry
this could be it
Then you two can eat it all
No no no
You don't look like you'd hate that
If it was good
Yea, he looks like he'd like it
The fact that you could get so much protein would be great
Exactly!
Really?
That's why I'm using it
It doesn't look like it'll have flavor or texture
Right
It'll have texture
Yea, it's lacking something
Ok, first of all
Without flour, just using this
Without using flour
Correct
He can't just use flour
Right
That wouldn't be good would it?
No, it wouldn't
Instead of using flour, protein will be the base
Seriously?
There we go
This is kinda gross
4 cups of it
What is this...
Put in 4 cups
Matsumoto-san probably already knows, but
Chicken Tenderloin
Chicken tenderloin, you definitely have to eat chicken
Eat lots of chicken tenderloin
Eat chicken tenderloin
Broccoli is good, too
It makes you feel full after as well
Endou, just
Go to Matsumoto's house and make it there
I agree
Right?
Yes
What is this?
This is soy milk
Soy milk is good for you too
Soy milk?
I see I see
It's important
It is important
And then,
He's not the least bit interested
Now the egg
Next is egg
You got a strange assistant, there
A strange assistant
Actually, the egg white alone might be good for this
The truth is yes
You're very well versed, that's actually true
Now we're a protein show
A protein show
Info Box
Mix the Ingredients Together
Protein Chicken Tenderloin Broccoli Soy Milk Egg
Cooking Step 1
Whenever you try to lose weight, you never really feel full, so
If this turns it good, it'll be a great innovation
They don't care at all
What are you eating over there?
Gum
You a big leaguer, or something?
Okay, here I go
This is the nail in the coffin for them, Endou
Right
Like Kinni-kun and Kasuga
Nakayama
Kinni-kun
Toshiaki Kasuga
That's right
That's a narrow target, huh
It really is
Info Box
After Cooking One Side, Flip it Over
Cooking Step 2
The perfect diet Okonomiyaki
But will it be delicious?
Doesn't it look pretty good?
It does
It looks, and smells, like garbage
Come on now
Look how well-cooked!
It looks nice and crispy
Smells awful!!
It smells
It doesn't smell bad at all!
This awful smell...
It smells really bad
You know in your heart it smells awful
It doesn't at all
It does you liar!
Does it?
It smells awful
If I were to describe to smell to the viewers
Burnt skin is the fragrance
Endou's
Second Dish
Protein Okonomiyaki
Finally, after brushing on some protein mixed with water
it's ready to eat!
Alright
Alright, this is a taste
Here's a taste of it
Itadakimasu
It's hard
It's true
Is it the chicken?
It's stiff as a board
What is this?
I thought this part would be softer but it's the hardest part
It's really hard
What is this?
Uwah. It's tough...
It's so dry
What the hell is this?
Gross
It's rough
This is just stupid
It's not even food
It's no good
We can all just give this a 1, right?
Well
Yes
It really gets all in between your gums
I can't get it off of my gums
This was a mistake
This is a crazy result
That it's so dry
There's not enough oil
Oh yea, maybe it's the oil
It's really hard to swallow
Now I see
It's trying to become my gums
In general it's just...
As soon as I took a bite it started trying
Screaming "UWAAAAAH" as it turned into gums
Is that so?
It really sticks
This was no good
Protein Okonomiyaki
With its pointless adventurousness,
It get's the lowest score, a single skull!
The Absolutely Tasty Okonomiyaki Challenge!
Hamada Masatoshi
Endou Shouzou
Curry
Sanma
Protein
Mapo Tofu
Here's the scores up to this point
Up next is Tanaka's dishes!
As for me...
I'll be using this.
Yellow
Basic
Ingredients
Salmon
Shimeji and Enoki Mushrooms
These
You didn't cook the sanma!
Hold your horses
It's salmon
I'll cook it with foil
Aluminum Foil-Cooked Okonomiyaki
It's gonna be good
That's what it is?
You said yaki twice
First I'll put it all in raw and wrap it up
and then steam it
Steamed Okonomiyaki, you see
Sealing in the flavor
withing the foil
Steamed Okonomiyaki
Is that gonna be good?
So you're not grilling it
Right, no grilling
I'm steaming it
Isn't it innovative?
You are coming out of the gate with something new
Right
Steaming it
Info Box
Spread the Batter on the Aluminum Foil
Cooking Step 1
The concept has kinda changed now
A little bit
So that's how, huh
He's an idea man
Idea man
That's our Tanaka
Info Box
Lay the Ingredients on Top, and Wrap the Foil
Cooking Step 2
Put the salmon and mushrooms on top,
and add flavor with soy sauce and butter
Then wrap it all in the foil
This quickly becomes like this
Keeping it all in
That's right, folding the sides
This is interesting
It is, right?
Is this still okonomiyaki?
It's still okonomiyaki
Info Box
Place It on the Grill, and Steam-Cook
Cooking Step 3
And now,
right on top
And you don't need any oil, right?
You don't need any oil, so
Now we wait 20 minutes
That's so long!!
I'm not waiting!!
Just 20 minutes
I don't wanna wait
It's a 30 minute TV show
Wait, I know
While it's cooking,
I'll prepare the next dish
And now, the second dish
is this right here
Perfect for the season
Yellow
Basic
Ingredients
Chilled
Chinese Noodles
Chilled noodles
The perfect summer dish, Chilled Noodles
Yes
Some people might think I'm playing it safe with this, but
Of course
I'll specially prepare this with the chilled noodles in mind
So I'm not just playing it safe
I think this is a good idea, Tanaka
It's good, right?
Right?
Really challenging yourself
I am
I'll mix this
Mixing it all, huh
Mixing it all together
Info Box
Mix the Chilled Noodles and Batter Together
Cooking Step 1
This isn't Okonomiyaki, Tanaka
No no no no no
It's of course not finished yet
Just keep watching
OK, now
The oil already
Yes sir
Whoever forgets to put the oil on next
will be fined 500,000 yen, got it?
Seriously, though
Alright, now I'll pour this on the grill
Info Box
Spread on the Grill and Cook
Cooking Step 2
I hope it's not acidic
That will be the decider
Alright, it's good like this
Because tomatoes add acidity, so
So I'm cooking this one right now
but when it's done,
Since it's chilled noodles
I'd like to cool it in a fridge
Now
How long is that gonna take?
2 Hours
2 hours?!
Are you stupid?
Info Box
Cool in the Fridge for 2 Hours
Cooking Step 3
Of course he'd call you stupid
Look,
You're taking up too much time
I actually came early
Oh good
I came and made one already
Good thing you did
I cooked and chilled one already, so
Right, here it is
It's already...
Is it cold?
Yeah it is
Ah, It's cold!
Tanaka's First Dish
Chilled Chinese Noodle Okonomiyaki
Perfect for the summer season,
Chilled Chinese Noodle Okonomiyaki! How will it taste?
It's already completely chilled
Actually, Tanaka
I'm all for it, now
Oh really?
Me too
Shouldn't it be pretty good?
Right?
Since it's cold, it doesn't have a smell either
To start,
Try it just as it is
Yea
Really?
Some sauce
That's where it'll go wrong
is already inside, so
Please eat it as it is!
Chilled Okonomiyaki
See...
Since eating it hot is...
It's too tough
the standard
This is no good
No good
Stupid Bad
Absolutely no taste
This is awful
It's just unpleasant
No taste
Seriously? Is it that bad?
There's no taste
I'm telling you, it's bad
Isn't it probably because it's cold?
That's the problem
Right?
This is one step away from Raw Garbage
If my mom gave me this for lunch during summer vacation
I'd smash her glasses, I think
Chilled Chinese Noodle Okonomiyaki
Chilling it caused it to backfire,
and with no flavor, it received 2 points!
After this!
Tanaka's Foil-Cooked Okonomiyaki!
Tanaka's own dish
How will it turn out?
Tanaka's Second Dish
Foil-Cooked Okonomiyaki
Tanaka's own dish, foil-cooked okonomiyaki
How will it turn out?
It's steamed okonomiyaki
Steamed, huh
Hmmm
Thank you
The warm area
"Not grilled, but steamed"
Here it is!
So it's not grilled at all
Take a look at this
So it's not crispy, either
Correct
Look!
It actually cooked
It smells really good
It is a nice smell
You're right
I got way too much salmon
I got most of it
Can we already it eat?
As you like
Green onions
He said As you like even after last time!!
Of course he would
I had to
Of course
Try adding some ponzu
We're using ponzu?
Yes
Add some ponzu
Right now?
Right away?
Well
We should try it without, right?
Alright, try it as it is first
I already used it
He's beaten up
I already used it, too
It's fine
Just try it as it is
I found a bone
It should be packed with flavor
Itadakimasu
Disgusting...
First time someone used the bucket
The first bucket of the day
Isn't it still uncooked?
It feels like
I'm eating straight up flour
It's coarse
Seriously?
I'll try adding some of this
As you like
Excuse me
It's getting worse
and worse for him
Green On Screen Box
"As you like" Said Twice
That'll be 1,000,000 Yen, two 500,000 fines
Didn't Put the Oil On
And you forgot the oil earlier so 1,500,000 Yen
Fine
¥1,000,000
¥500,000
¥1,500,000
You better have it by next week
Skull, skull
This gets a skull
Next week as a skinhead you're gonna
have to bring 1,500,000 Yen  with you
Yea
There's no way I can
Seriously
No way, huh?
There's no way
NEXT WEEK
Next week!
The Absolutely Tasty Okonomiyaki Challenge, Part 2!
Next Week Absolutely Tasty Okonomiyaki! Final Part
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
Housei will introduce his pickled ingredients
So good!
What happened!
However, Tanaka thinks...
Isn't there a bit too much *****
And then, Matsumoto comes up with a new dish!
Will this be edible?
We'll find out if it's edible
Don't miss it!
If my mom called me for lunch during summer vacation
and gave me this
I think I'd smash her glasses