This year was tough too, huh?
TN: They're talking about the No Laughing Special
Yes, it was
It was, yes
It was exactly 1 week ago right?
Exactly 1 week ago
That ruins my health usually
At least it's over
I'm the youngest one, right?
Yes on Gaki no Tsukai
I'm 43 years old
I'm the youngest at 43,
But the next day, the pain on my ass, the body fatigue I have
I'm always thinking actually,
Tanaka's ass hurts the most
I have a strong impression of Tanaka's ass hurting
Our asses hurt too
They hurt
They hurt but I bet Tanaka's really hurts
It's probably the Thai kick
Exactly thats it. I get the Thai kick every year
That has stayed with me the whole time-
You need to tell the staff to cut it out
te-tell them ..
Tell them?
You don't tell them that's why you get kicked
I can tell them?
I told them, that's why I don't get kicked
You didn't tell them anything!
Tell them to stop it
I can't just tell them to stop
I wrote them a statement, to cut it out
You can't do that!
You wrote them a letter?
"Please stop the Thai kicks for me"
"Enough Thai kicks. Please stop"
Then I'll write one too!
He didn't write anything, just conveyed his feelings
"Stop the Thai kicks"
BUT THIS TIME I got kicked cause of this asshole!
Yeah I couldn't believe that
He really said, my name?
And without honorifics!
oh yeah
You really did that to your Senpai
That was cause I was still thinking about a previous segment
There was a segment like that before that happened
First time in a while I got kicked
I think there's something here I need to apologise for
This "Thai Kick" batsu game,
Ignoring actual Thai boxers,
I invented this Thai Kick for variety shows
Matsumoto-san introduced it
I should have spoken up more back then,
"This could be dangerous"
"Cut it out"
I should have said so
But it got laughs,
But now it's like a staple batsu game
Like an obvious thing to do
It's like an an axle
But a Thai kick is something you do to apples
That's something you use to defeat an opponent
Exactly
It's something a pro does to another pro
It's not something a pro does to us
Exactly
So this is all your fault
This is something I want everyone to understand
Also, we don't need that youthful vigor
Like, on that tag game
The slipper guy
Those young guys have too much strength
I know what you mean
Yeah
I wish they used like 40 year olds
40 year old middle aged men will catch us?
We don't need that youthful vigor
Speaking of, "that" guest came on that segment
"That" person
That miraculous guest
That guy was amazing, he really didn't wanna get caught
He was seriously running away
There's no need for him to run away so desperately
In the end the Oni couldn't keep up
Couldn't catch that guy
We had to catch him ourselves
That person is like that
Is that a good way to be?
That guy is ... that guy is
I'll say it - he is painful
Painful
He isn't aware of that painfulness
We can't really say that to him
We have to deal with it
There's no helping it then
It was amazing though
It was amazing, really amazing
It's been 9 years right?
No Laughing Batsu -  Airs December 31st, from 18:30 to 24:30
Yes, it's been a new year special for 9 years
Yes 9 years
We're doing too much ...
NTV is messed up in the head after all
Speaking of that,
The No Laughing and Yamasaki vs. Moriman,
we had two ongoing series
That was a lot back then
It was a lot
Yamasaki's screen time was really something
Honestly I thought the same thing back then
We don't need that youthful vigor
If you ask me why,
"don't need that youtful vigor"
They do simulations, right? (for the punishments)
Exactly
To make sure there are no injuries
Yeah to prevent injuries
Exactly, exactly
But all the people doing the simulation are young guys
Right?
They're 20 - 23 years old,
but the one actually recieving the punishment is a 40+ old man
But these young guys can deal with it,
I get what you mean,
But there aren't many old comedians that can do the simulations.
Basically only Lytton Commision
They're even older than us
What's wrong with that?
Older than you?
Lytton are older than us
Should we make them do it?
Lytton-san should do the simulations
They can wear "Matsumoto" and "Hamada" T-shirts
You think that will work?
I think that will work
Will that work for us juniors?
The simulation won't work
Ah is that so
Yes certainly
Oh yeah
Today, you might have noticed
An American
Something's different
Yeah
What is this?
They're covering us for an American TV show
Is this real?
It's not like that "African Channel TV" right?
Exactly exactly
No, no, no, it's real
They're not gonna write "Act stupid!" on a cue card right?
subbed by /u/senor_wristband
What brings them here?
There's an American TV show,
"The Greatest Shows On Earth"
TN: This show was renamed to "Planet Primetime"
From all the famous Japanese variety shows,
Gaki no Tsukai was chosen to be covered by them
That's crazy
Seriously?
Covering us today, "The Greatest Shows on Earth", a show that will air next year in America
TN: I think Gaki appears on the first episode of Planet Primetime.
A show that features TV from around the globe,
examining the different cultures and audiences
And the first episode, representing Japan,
is Gaki no Tsukai
Amazing
Isn't that amazing?
We did it!
"We did it!" ?
That's amazing isn't it?
I think Shoten would be better though
TN: Shoten is an ogiri show, airing since 1966
Shoten would also be a good choice, of course
Of course, of course
They've been airing longer too
Why this show, I want to ask
Yes, let's ask
Let's ask them to come in
Allow me to introduce them,
This is the host of "The Greatest Shows on Earth",
Karla Cavali-san
Welcome, Karla-san
Nice to meet you
Is this real? This all feels like a prank so far
This is serious
Really?
Have you seen this show before?
TN: She is speaking English
What did you see from this show?
What did you think was funny?
The Omonmari
Is your brother a pervert?
I guess you don't need to understand the dialogue for that
You can watch it and understand from the movements
I see
Have you seen anything else?
The tataite kabutte
That thing
That's a really old one though
That's world famous right?
We haven't recieved any money from that though
It's world famous?
Yeah yeah
It's been adapted by different countries
Silent Library? That's amazing
Really? That's wild
So after seeing that,
Karla-san wanted to cover this show
No, no,
We wanna ask why this kind of comedy isn't popular
Are any one of us popular in America?
The show as a whole is popular
C'mon do it
Housei-san's gag?
She wants to see your gag from the New Year specials
The thing from the new year specials?
You can do it right away right?
Right before breakfast
This is a huge chance!
I can spread my wings!
She's requesting after all
You can do it casually
You don't know what gag would be good huh?
Oh the New Year's Party
The thing from the New Year's Party
Oh that thing? That hilarious one?
Who said it's funny?
That's not really your gag though
It doesn't matter though
You guys, stand up
First you guys stand up
Stand up
Say "Hai Hai Hai Hai"
Set up the comedy for me
Face this way?
Should we spread apart?
Just do it like normal
This is a huge chance
A huge chance. You might get tons of laughs.
You're gonna get huge laughs
I got it, you're gonna get huge laughs
I'm telling you, you're gonna get huge laughs
I'm really glad about this
I'm gonna do it!!!
Hurry up man she's waiting for you
Ready?
She really likes this
She's laughing so hard
Turn your face towards America's cameras!
He's adding variations to it
This is not very Japanese
Enough already
What did you think of that?
That's great
I will say though,
LITERALLY anyone can do that
I see
That was good though
That was good
Karla-san, is there anything else you'd like to see?
There's no way man
Wants to take part?
What are we gonna do?
Cause I've been the champion before
Oh yeah
Champion, champion
Certainly
Ah I see
Cause I'm the champion
I mean you are the champion
I'm going to play seriously
Wouldn't it be better to have the mat here
You have to teach her how to play
Do you know what to do?
Janken?
Oh yeah she might not know janken
She has a basic grasp on this
You gotta teach her rock paper scissors
Do you understand?
You're supposed to be teaching her!
You gotta teach her
Do you understand?
There's also the timing
Tataite - Kabutte - Jan-ken-pon
Remember the song
And this .. like this
Try and sing it
Do it slowly first
Are you taking the piss?
Only Endo needs to sing it
But what the hell is "Habachaba?"
Let's start this
If I win I'm gonna need to hit you
I might hit hard
Avoid the face
Just the head
This is kinda scary, I'm nervous
Yeah, this is like
At times like this Endo really hurts people like @!@#$
He really said that name, @!@#$
An American Show Came to Gaki No Tsukai!
Tataite Kabutte Jankenpon - 1 Round Battle!
Here I go,
We're beginning
Let's begin
Ready, steady,
Of course, of course
Hold on a second
I lost!
This is like some Kyoto teahouse
You're having so much fun
Having a ball of a time
This not the end,
There's more Karla-san still wants to see
We didn't need a translation for that
Chinko Machine
Yeah I understood the "Machine"
A producer?
Which producer?
Oh her producer?
Yeah I thought it was gonna be Suga-chan
Will be it able to hit Robin properly?
Yeah
It's not desgined for his size
Eh? Isn't this impossible?
Robin is freaking huge
It seems fine
Does Robin know this Chinko Machine existed?
He knows!
This is amazing
Is this gonna be OK/
It's gonna be 3-2-1-Go
It's really scary huh?
Robin you can do it
Get ready Robin, here we go
That really hurt him
It hurt Robin
He went "Ow"
That's the end
I see
From America's "The Greatest Shows on Earth",
Karla-san!
Thank you!
Thank you very much
So that was real after all
This will be broadcasted by them
We should have copyrighted the Chinko Machine
They might copy it
They'll copy it
Right?
We would be able to get royalties for it, if we trademark it
Chinko Machine?
What the hell is a Chinko Machine anyways?
It'll be as popular as Karaoke abroad
Chinko Machine, Karakoe,
Chinko Machine
At amusement parks and such
They can have them there
This year's batsu game, what do you think after reflecting on it?
For me it's, after all,
Before the No-Laughing started, I injured my abs once again
A week before it started, I was told to be very careful
Sorry could you explain that again?
Why did your abs hurt?
Nobody understands why you kept saying that
Why did they hurt?
Right, right, right,
I'll tell you why, but before that,
If this happened to you, you'd definitely skip work
That's how much I endured, acting like it was nothing
No, no, no, no
Tell us what happened first
It was an iron pole I said
This is the first time hearing that
For the people watching TV
No I've said this at other places, it was an iron pole
What happened with the iron pole?
I was doing flips at a park
Alone at the park ... doing flips?
You were doing flips and hit a pole?
When you're doing flips, you have to keep the bar close to you right?
I understood that
So I did one flip like that
But when I did another flip,
I was too far from the bar
So then when I reached the top of the bar, I fell down and hit my abs on it
And that stopped me
And that's what happened
So you got bruised?
A bruise ... well well
It was a straight up fracture
No way
There's no way you got a fracture
You've never done that before
You didn't go to the doctor?
I didn't go to the doctor
Then how the hell do you know it's a fracture?
I've done so many flips before,
I am my own specialist doctor
I could just tell
No way
You've never broken your ribs before
I didn't make a sound or anything
This guy can't even sneeze quietly
You went to the doctor then?
It was just a bad bruise, right?
It's totally broken
It split apart like *PAN*
It broke?
He didn't go to the doctor!
It really broke
He never got an assessment done
If it was broken it would stab your organs
If there was even a tiny little fracture-
He didn't have a fracture
It really split apart,
And the meat got stuck in between them
It got stuck, that hurt as well
It pierced your organs?
Between your bones?
What the hell are you saying?
You wouldn't know you got organs stuck
between your bones unless you went to the doctor
Exactly
I saw in the mirror I had a divot
You could see that?
That's a serious injury then
Yeah that's crazy you could see it from the outside
It was really terrible
And I debated taking time off,
But I decided not to
It was really terrible, but I pushed through
My sense of service
It was a collection of willpower
And you didn't say "Ahh that hurts" even once
That's my sense of service
Yama-chan when your shoulder was hurting,
It did hurt still
You didn't go "Ahh" ocassionally?
No, no, that's my sense of service
So it didn't hurt?
No, no, it was my sense of service
Sense of service?
Yup
My sense of service
To who? To what?
Please tell us
A sense of service?
I'm speaking to people who don't understand that right now
No we understand what it is
You had a sense of service to that job?
Well it hurt right?
But if I said anything you guys might worry
And that will dampen the comedy
I didn't want any sympathy so I endured it
So when Yama-chan was going "It hurts it hurts"
What did you think?
"This guy is seriously so useless"
He kept telling us it hurts
"40 year old shoulder" he says
It's supposed to be "50 year old shoulder"
Why the hell did you decrease it by 10 years?
In what world does a 47-48 year old have "40 year old shoulder"
That's 50 year old shoulder
I'm still in my 40s
That's why I said 40 year old shoulder, I'm still not 50
You're 47 years old though
I'm still in my 40s!
You are 47, Housei-san
And my hemorrhoids were killing me too
So it was a double whammy
You said your hips hurt too
Oh yeah, that's a triple then
It was a huge pain in the ass
No Laughing is definitely the most physically taxing job we have all year
That's for sure
So you know we try to stay careful,
But staying careful we still get caught up in those kinds of events
What the fuck Endo? I'll kick your ass
M-
Me?
Why, me?
He's the one said the least to you
Said the least to you, just nodding in agreement
The one who sympathised
Yeah
You've been pissing me off since the day you debuted