First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai
Special talent demonstration meeting - let's raise our views!
That's exactly what this will be about
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Everything's ok as long as our views will increase
As long as every minute our audience will grow
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Yamazaki Hosei
License
Fujiwara Kazuhiro
Inomoto Takafumi
Is anything really gonna be ok?
It's about our special skills
- I see
I mean things we usually don't do on tv, as long as our views will increase
This is something new
As you can see, our regulars are on this side
And we have guests here
Hosshan
Fujimoto Toshifumi
Haranishi Takayuki
You sure you guys have special skills?
- Of course we do
Ameagari Kesshitai
Miyasako Hiroyuki
Hotohara Toru
Look how villainous his face has become
- Who? Fujimon?
That's the face of a man who's thinking of money
- I'm not
I bet they'll show us a pair nude
Tonight, our members will compete with
special skills they never showed on tv before
Their objective is to show their skills succesfully
in order to make ratings per minute skyrocket!
Simpler-than-usual subs & translation by Shion
Like my page:  fb.com/shionnotsukai
More j-comedy @ shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
▀
Subbing takes time & effort.
if you want to show your support,
please consider donating few dollars:
- on ko-fi @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
- or patreon @ patreon.com/shionnotsukai
Tonight, each one of them will show us their
special skills they've never shown on tv before
Their objective is to show their skills succesfully
in order to make ratings per minute skyrocket!
Here we go
- Alright
Here's the first one
Who will it be? The first round is important
"Blowpipe while riding a ball"
If they actually do this, people at home will watch it
That's right
They would stop zapping
- Of course they would
Whose skill is this?
Here!
Really?
- Never heard of that
I don't even think he has the lung capacity to shoot a dart...
I do
He's also the first one, so...
- That's right
If he fails doing it, everyone would go watch Wowow instead
Alright, head to the challenge room
Alright, let me do it
I want to see this
- Over there?
Endo did you know this?
No I didn't
You don't?
- I don't
We're aiming at top rates, so it's best if everyone could enjoy this
So that even people not good at japanese...
- I see
Can watch this and enjoy our show
CHALLENGE ROOM - WARM UP
Everyone's expectation is on our first challenger Tanaka
Will he be able to do it properly
and make the viewers stick to their tv?
Looks like Tanaka is ready now
I want to see this
Let's call him, Tanaka!
Yes, here I am
No way
I'm ready for it
- Is he for real?
I'll hop up on this
And I'll walk for around 5 meters on it
- No way he can do that
- Yes
Then, as you can see
There's a balloon there
It's 8 meters away from here
This is impossible...
- And while I'm still on it
I'll blow a dart and pop it
Incredible
That balloon is so small
Even his dart is really small
Let us know when you're ready, you think you can do it now?
I'm ready
It'd be great if he can
Here's Tanaka's attempt to raise our ratings per minute!
Just that
- It's in front of him
RATINGS RAISE: START
Can he really do it?
Yeah I mean, what's this? It's hard to imagine
It sounds freaky enough
Are you kidding me?
Looking good
He's on it
- This will raise them for good
He's really on it
Keep on going, man!
That's the type of thing people want to see
Show us his face, that's the funniest part
This isn't...
A face you see everyday
This is gonna be a hit
Almost there!
Now he must pop the balloon
He completed the 5 meters, so now he must shoot the balloon
How...?
He has to face the other way
He's changing direction for real!
This is amazing!
- So good, it's incredible
- He's so stable
- Looking good, keep on going!
If he actually does it, it'd be so cool
He's aiming at it
- It's not stable, is he gonna be ok?
Is it ok?
- It's not really stable
Incredible!
He did it!
- That was incredible!
Alright
Can you see our studio from here?
I can
- You can
You got a full standing ovation
You think I got the ratings up with this?
- I think you did
I raised em up good, isn't it true?!
Amazing
Wait a second, what was that?
- That was impressive
My partner is amazing
- What now?
Are we expecting even better skills?
- That's the plan
Endo just said something we all missed
That made me think "I have such an amazing partner"...
I bet you did
- It's been 20 years since our debut
And that seriously made me think "I'm glad I paired up with him"
He's back
That was incredible
Your face was kind of pale
Yeah I know
But the face he made while
riding the ball was hilarious
Alright, let's keep this pace
Here's our next special skill
"Blast wave plastic bottle knock down"
I don't know what that means
I know, right?
Who's this?
That's me
Fujimon?
Yes
What does it even mean?
When I was a student, I used to do athletics
So I have an impressive lung capacity
So much that I can easily knock down a 500 ml water bottle
By only using my breath
So you can do this because of the track team?
Yeah but my lungs...
Doesn't that mean everyone from the track club could do it?
Probably, but still I'm a monster when it comes to lung capacity
I mean, he's right after Tanaka's great success...
I'll build a nice flow to this
I'm gonna keep it high
Ok then, head to the challenge room!
We're counting on you
About this...
This didn't seem much to me
But the more I think about it...
It's impossible
Matsumoto, try it out for a second
- It's impossible...
It's so round--- is he gonna use this?
With this, right?
- It's so round, air would flow sideways
It didn't even budge!
- It's impossible!
Try it, Miyasako
I told you
Of course
This is absolutely impossible!
CHALLENGE ROOM - WARM UP
Will it go well?
An under-pressure Fujimoto
will try his best to raise the ratings
Can he do it?
Looks like he's ready, so let's call him out: Fujimon!
Yes
Those are huge!
Are you going to knock down 3 of them?
- All of them, yes
You should show them to us so we know there are no tricks
Like, try to lift em
- Ok
They're full of water
- Yes, as you can see
See? They're full of it
It's true
Incredible
Ready, Fujimon?
Yes, I'm ok
Here goes Fujimon's views-raise attempt!
VIEWS-RAISE: START
Is he for real?
From that angle?
This already seems good
No way they're gonna fall...
Alright!
How was it?
Incredible
Amazing
He's getting dizzy
That was good
First head back here, then you talk
Yes, I'm not in the best shape right now
Come back here first
- Yes
The pressure is getting harsher and harsher...
I'm sure our views are skyrocketing like crazy
Yeah I can feel it
Oh, he's back
How was it?
It was amazing
Incredible
That was great
Thanks
Are you dizzy?
Yeah it really made me dizzy
Of course it does
Did the views raise?
I really think they did
It'd be so cool if we could do them all
Let's work hard and raise em up good
Here's our next special skill
I'm starting to enjoy this
"Free kick water bottle knock down"
Who's this?
It's me
Oh, is it Inomoto?
Yes
Free kicks?
I'll set some water bottles 10 meters away from me
- From 10 meters?
And I'll hit it in one shot
Ten meters?!
I'll hit them clean
- Really? Can you do it?
Alright, head to the challenge room
Countin' on you
It sounds incredible
It does
CHALLENGE ROOM - WARM UP
Can I kick one of them now?
Inomoto, our talented contestant who even
made it to national competitions during highschool
Will he be able to kick away this piling up pressure?
Looks like he's ready
Here we go
Inomoto?
- Yes
He was right
Is this for real?
This looks so hard
Are you for real, Inomoto?
- This is impossible
You weren't joking around, weren't you?
Here I go
- Already?!
Are you for real?
You sure you're ready?
I'm ready
Let's start then
- He's so confident
Here's Inomoto attempt to increase our views!
I'm excited
Is he for real?
This is exciting
VIEWS-RAISE: START
In one shot, he said
[repeating from before]
He's gonna fail
That was not even close
Come on...
It went way over it
What are we gonna do with this?
I played soccer too back then, can I say a word about this?
That guy sucks at soccer!
\ Wait a moment, please /
I swear I can do it!
But you didn't do it
I brought a VTR with me, just in case
How about we take a look at it together?
The VTR is even greater than this
Just take a look at it, please!
Of course he's gonna make it
He's sweating so much!
He sure have practiced this
See?
Oh, they're in succession
He did knock it down
He's going for them all?
Really?
- So bold
He seems relaxed
Two in a row is pretty impressive---
Eh?!
Are you kidding me?
- Three?!
No way
Be honest: how many attempts did it take?
I don't know the exact number
But it took me 1 hour and half
Man that's a long time!
- 1 hour and half?
What do you think, Fujiwara?
I mean, it's amazing
Can't argue with that
He wasn't as nervous as the previous ones too...
But he set up that "just kidding" thing
- Yeah, he failed
I bet some are thinking "that was too carefree", right?
I'm outraged, I feel like he's messing around with us
We should tell him like "don't lie to us"!
I won't forgive him for this
By the time he failed it was already surreal
Shut up, Miyasako!
Our fourth skill is "100% full score singing at karaoke"
Who's this?
Here!
What the hell!
- It's impossible
Isn't this like they used to do a lot on tv?
We'll have a full score without having the actual singer doing it
I, Endo Shozo, will do it in one shot
Are you kidding me?
No way, it's impossible
Which song, by the way?
Wada Akiko's masterpiece "ano kane wo narasu no wa anata"
"you're the one who rang the bell"
You know
If you fail this, Akiko will be involved too
You may hurt her pride
- You're right
So
You'll be officially scolded by her
"Officially"?
- That's right
Head to the challenge room
Here I go
- Go
I hope he can make it
I never saw him doing it
Is Endo really that good at singing it?
I can confirm that he once scored 100 points singing it
Really?
- You saw him?
But he also scored around 90 or so with it, so getting it at his first attempt...
It's not accurate
When I scored 100 with Uchuu Senkan Yamato's OP
Space Battleship Yamato
I was like "goodbye, oh Earth"
Like, emotionless
Too much modulation won't get you points
CHALLENGE ROOM - WARM UP
As the general enthusiasm dampens, Endo is ready for his attempt
Will he be able to ring the full-score bell?
Looks like he's ready
Endo!
He's into it
- He's so focused
Endo
- Yes?
Your face has become... weird
That's an "I'm gonna lose" face
That's the face you're giving us?
What are you looking at?
Are you okay?
I'm ok, I have confidence
Let's go then, here's Endo's attempt to raise our views!
Really?
VIEWS-RAISE: START
The beginning is important
♪ YOU'RE THE ONE WHO RANG THE BELL
I'm so glad I could meet you
He looks ready
You have the same scent as hope
Even if I'd trip and get hurt
And even if I'd cry
Is that his best?
He's putting his all in this
You'd still have that refreshing scent of hope
But it's different from
the original song
The town is now asleep
And you're the one who rang the bell
He just made a mistake
He got that wrong!
While everyone is lonely
He sang that as if
it was the last part
You're the one who rang the bell
There are some mistakes
Here goes
Yes, yes, that one
was good
Wasn't that just now a big mistake?
Why all these mistakes?
Man...
How was it?
- How much did he score?
Come on
Wait for it...
Here it is
Yes yes
- How much is it?
"WELL, NOTHING UNLISTENABLE"
89 points?
Are you kidding me?
He didn't even score 90
I'm really...
Sorry for this
That much?
Well, he did what he did
He's not coming back here
You knew it dude
Is he for real?
He's laughing
The hell are ya laughin' at?!
I'm not laughing at all
You're definitely laughing
Just come back here
Was it 90 points?
Oh no, 89
- 89, yes
He didn't reach 90 points
That's an average score
I think everyone over 40 can score that
Over 40?
No way
CHALLENGE OVER
Why couldn't I score at least 90 points...?
As the pressure becomes more intense, they reveal the fifth secret skill
Who's this?
"Perfect nunchaku"
I don't get this, who is it?
Who's this person now...
It's me
Can you do it?
The first birthday present I ever got from my dad was a toy nunchaku
- I see
So I'm extremely confident in my nunchaku skills
Basically
If I'm holding a nunchaku, I can knock down everything you throw at me
- That's impossible     - That's bullshit
I mean, I like Bruce Lee a lot
- Yeah but...
Have you ever tried doing that with a nunchaku?
You know our viewers are expecting a lot from this
Yeah but have you done it before?
Have you ever done it before? Huh?
Huh?-- Ouch
The pressure is rising
Can Miyazako sweep this atmosphere away with his nunchaku?
Alright, everything's set
Let's call him, Miyazako!
How is it going?
From now on I will
knock down lots of balls---
I mean, round things
You sure you're ok?
I'll have the staff throw lots of balls at me
round things
They'll gradually become smaller
That last one...
- For real?
It's an BB bullet
note: airsoft bullet
The very last one will be a BBB---
huh---
- Dude!
- What's going on?
- Are you alright?!
He became one with that atmosphere
No one in this room even laughed at what just happened
I don't think they care
We don't need em to laugh
- That's right
Whenever you're ready...
Is that tracksuit ok for this?
Let us know
Are your privates safe...?
Looks good
Man, he sucks!
When you lose a nunchaku, you gotta hide under a wagon
Here we go
Yes
Here's Miyazako attempt to raise our views-per-minute
Can he actually do it?
The last ones are though
VIEWS-RAISE: START
He only has one single hit
Also, how are they thrown at him?
(1) VOLLEYBALL
It has to be one shot one hit
A volleyball?
Well, that one was ok
(2) SOFT-BALL
Man, this one is small
This may be hard
Isn't it too soon?
Yeah, it suddenly became hard
Please hit it
Alright
Well done!     - Ok, ok!
- Nice!
There's still more
(3) TENNIS BALL
He can do this too
Are you sure?
It's pretty small
It's small but I think he can do it
Alright!
Ok!
I can feel our views raising
(4) PING PONG BALL
They're raising, they're raising!
This one's hard
This can turn midair
Alright!
He's killing it
Our views are skyrocketing!
(5) BOUNCY BALL
It's a bouncy ball
This one is tiny
This is significantly smaller
Alright!!
What?!
Didn't he just missed it?
He just missed it, didn't he?
I grazed it, didn't I?
I don't think so
Which was it...?
He didn't hit it
I think I touched it
Let me just do it again so you'll stop complaining
Is he actually pissed off?
What the hell?
- Is he mad?
It totally went "pew"
Could it be a sound issue?
I assure you I heard the ball going "pew" here
BOUNCY BALL - TRYING AGAIN!
'Cause I hit it
But it didn't
come forward
See?
Where did it go?
It went straight down there
But we couldn't see it
That's your fucking problem
✜
Did he hit it?
- Why should it be my fault?!
It did make a sound (when it got hit)
(6) RED BEAN
(AZUKI)
Next one is a red bean
A red bean?
We won't even see it
- We just have to hear it
You're right
It's too small
Alright!
Huh?
- You got it?
You got it?
I got it, this time I really got it
. . .
So you were lying before!!
The super ball!
Were you lying about the super ball?
But you heard I hit it, so it's fine
This is my last one, the BB bullet
(7) BB BULLET
How can we possibly see it?
Ready
Alright!
Oh, this---?
You didn't hit it!
He didn't hit it
It went through
So clearly
But it just went "pew"
It didn't go "pew"
- Come on, enough of that
Just get back here
This guy is a
troublemaker
Get back here
- Just come back
Come back
Let me be clear on this: I'm not coming back!
I think that's the worst one by far...
- Yeah, I agree
'Cause he had some pride about it
Come on, get back here
What are you exulting for?
- You got that wrong...
It didn't go that well
What the hell, man
Man, I didn't think I could actually make it through
But you didn't made it!
No one told me just a "pew" sound wasn't enough...
I grazed em all, it was perfect
But it was "knock down", you had to knock em down
But you saw it, I mean--- the super ball fell down, yes?
Yeah it did, behind you
- It fell, right?
Behind you
And it made a "pew" sound too
Our views-per-minute are slowly dying, let's quit it
He's right
Here's our next special skill
What is it...?
"Drawn sword fresh cut"
It sound dangerous
- So cool
Who's this?
Drawn sword, yes
I mean, we know you used to do kendo back then
But a real sword is completely different
But really
A single false step and there goes one leg
You'd be like "AH!"
What a great shout!
Next week...
PART 2 COMING SOON @
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Views-per-minute raising: 2nd half!
The passionate battle of comedians risking their lives for views...
...will come to an end!
Who's coming? Matsumoto? Or Miyasako? Which one?
Don't miss it!
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
WEBSITE
FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
LIKE IT
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
DONATIONS
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
PART 2 COMING SOON...