@ShibataBread
@TofuPizza
The King of Bikkuri Face Grand Prix!!
The King of Bikkuri Face
Grand Prix
Downtown
Hitoshi Matsumoto
Masatoshi Hamada
On today's show...
as he just announced,
Yea?
We will decide who will be the Bikkuri Face King.
See the drawing of us back there?
Isn't that something?
You know who drew this?
It's by Mr. Umezu himself.
That's right.
Illustration by Kazuo Umezu
Mr. Kazuo Umezu.
Right.
I'm sure he wasn't expecting
such a weak reaction from you guys.
No need to point that out.
Let's get to the show then.
Here's how you will judge each contestant.
So I'll judge five elements of each act.
As shown in this pentagon graph.
First is "How Much You Shit Yourself"
It's a facial expression contest,
but I still want to see your whole body react.
Like, "Did he just throw his back out?"
That much?
Yes, I'd like that.
I see.
And this should be obvious but,
"How Well You Hide The Show"
That's the toughest to judge.
We've had contestants in the past
who exposed the show.
And that's no good
And we have...
"E-Eye Pop...
"Eye Pop & Dislocated Jaw..."
Sort of like Dolce & Gabbana...
Hell no.
Please explain.
It's part of the facial expression.
Like, "Shit, his eyes are about to pop out!"
or "His jaw just dislocated!"
And this needs no explanation...
N.B.T.
What the hell is that?
What does N.B.T. stand for?
Nice Bikkuri Timing...
You had to read it, too, asshole.
"Shitting Pants Percentage"
Bikkuri Minutes
"Prank Not Exposed"
"Eye Pop & Dislocated Jaw"
5 Judging Elements
Bikkuri Minutes
Challenge Ending Signal
Judged on length of Bikkuri Face
Loud scream by each challenger
The last judging element is
"Bikkuri Minutes."
The act is over once the challenger lets out a big scream.
Let's start the show.
Here's our firs challenger...
C'mon out!
Challenger
Hiroaki Ogi
(OGIYAHAGI)
You're Ogi?
He's the lead-off challenger.
Yes, I made it.
Good job.
This is my first time leading the show...
Not only that,
You're the first with leopard-printed frames.
They aren't quite leopard...
Oh, they're not?
A skilled player
a bespectacled master, ready for the challenge!
Ogiyahagi
Ogi
Target
19-Year Veteran Comic
Kazuya Kojima
Setup
Dinner
His target is Mr. Kojima,
a seasoned comic
Does Ogi have a strategy?
Well, Kojima's very slow and...
Just not a smart person.
You'll see, he's not very observant.
I see.
So, I feel like...
He might win this.
I can get away with a lot.
He's going for it.
I see.
I'm just gonna go for the gold.
The king of Bikkuri Face
Start
Ogi looks ready after doing some stretches.
It must be nerve-wracking.
As his target arrives, Ogi makes his move.
I concur.
Excuse me.
Dungaree.
- Huh?
Got your Dungarees on?
What do you mean, Dungaree?
Talking about your shirt.
- Oh, right.
You reserved this table just for us?
Everything else was booked.
What are you getting?
Meat?
Oh, I want fried rice.
That was quick.
Braised Pork Belly looks good too.
Shark Fin Soup is 1,800 yen.
1,800 yen?!!
Very natural.
Very good.
Nice flow.
I guess that's normal.
That was good.
That's what I'm talking about.
How about Mapo Tofu?
I called it Poma.
Poma?!
Yes, Poma...
Good one.
He has zero idea...
Not a clue.
As Ogi predicted, Kojima is utterly clueless.
Ogi cruises along without getting caught.
Good so far.
So how are
your gigs going?
Just had an amazing show.
Which was?
The show is called "Music Lovers."
"Music Lovers"? Refresh my memory.
What do you do?
I was one of the supporters
Oh, you get to cheer'em on.
I didn't do much more than clap my hands.
They were so cool though.
What made them so cool?
Their looks...
Now you've done it.
I see. You used a prop.
Right, more than just a facial expression.
When our eyes met,
I waved at'em.
You were directed to do so, right?
Directed...?
Not really.
Why're you pissed?
I don't think that's a Bikkuri face.
Well, he rarely makes that face.
I was surrounded by all these girls,
and became one of them.
As for me, I react more with experienced comics,
I'm more like "OH!!"
Like Takeshi and Sanma...
Or if it's Downtown, you'd be like, "Oh!!"
Yes, of course.
Like who?
Well, let's say I met Downtown...
I don't know about this one...
You wouldn't be like, "Ah?!"
Yeah, like that, too.
What about with Unnan?
What sort of emotion is that?
How does he not know?!
It changed a bit.
What about with Sanma?
And with Downtown?
Now, he's just messing around.
What the hell?!
What about with Ame-Agari?
-So they got the biggest reaction.
50 minutes have passed.
Ogi doesn't show any sign of slowing down.
Excuse us.
May I get another drink?
- Coming right up, sir.
Oolong tea for me.
Oolong tea?!
Why're you yelling?
Nothing wrong with tea.
Give me some tips on food reporting.
Amazing that he doesn't know
Right.
I have food show gig coming up.
Say things like, "Great texture!"
WTF?! That ain't no Bikkuri face!!
He has shown a variety of reactions,
but to be the champion,
he must end with a bang.
Of course.
Ogi makes his move for the last big finish.
I almost forgot
You know that television show?
The name escapes me...
It's called "Gaman TV".
Like an endurance test?
Yea, and it usually involves pain.
So I'll be using that paint brush over there
They'll tickle me everywhere with the brush.
And I'll have to endure it.
They judge who tolerates it the best?
Yeah, so I was thinking you can help me...
B-But why?
Give it to me then.
Kojima unknowingly becomes part of Ogi's act.
What kind of Bikkuri face will Ogi make?
Ready?
What the hell?!
You're gonna lose.
What're you doing?
I don't know...
I don't think you're trying.
- Maybe, I should stand up.
Seriously...
Okay, go ahead.
Go for my neck.
Shut the hell up.
Do it again, again, again, and again!!
Do more!
Do it now. Do it now!!
Hurry up!
Cut it ou, pervert!!
Tough to score this one.
Oh, is over.
The King of Bikkuri Face
Over
Keep it down.
You cut it out.
Listen, Ogi.
You were just playing games at the end.
Kojima's seriously slow.
I'd say he had no idea.
I get that but...
Let's see his scores.
Here they are.
He's perfect on not exposing the show.
Kojima still hasn't figured it out.
I agree.
Even after this airs, he will have no idea.
But the "Eye Pop & ...
Dislocated Jaw" could've been better.
This one's pretty high...
Well, his timing was...
What's this stand for again?
"Nice Bikkuri Timing."
N.B.T.
Got it.
Let's see how the others do.
Looking forward to it.
Let's see who's up next!!
Challenger
Takayuki Kinoshita
Crack!
What?!
How dare you...
You just had to break the last step!
Jeez...
Kinoshita, with his chameleon-like ability,
is ready for the challenge!
Kinoshita
Target
Keiko Kinoshita
Setup
Dinner
His target is his sister Keiko who resides in Osaka.
And who else?
To make his sister feel more comfortable,
their mother Sadako will be Kinoshita's partner in crime.
Let's act the same as any other family gathering!!
Okay
Let's do this!
The King of Bikkuri Face
Start
Mother and son wait for Keiko's arrival.
But something is wrong with Kinoshita...
Aren't you hungry?
I don't feel like eating...
Are you nervous?
Yea, it's a strange feeling...
I can sort of understand...
(Chuckles) Hilarious!!
His mom enjoys the fact that her son is really nervous.
And then...
Oh!! There she is!!
This is a surprisingly gorgeous room...
- You made it just in time...
She said "surprisingly"...
Right off the bat.
You just arrived in Tokyo?
Yea, literally just arrived.
Where's your manager?
- He's not here.
It's just us three tonight
Is that so?!
Just after Keiko's arrival,
Kinoshita finds an opportunity to strike.
What's that?
It's for Valentines's day...
It's for the two of you...
Long face time.
They're for you and your manager.
Too long.
- Thanks, I'll take them now.
There they are!
I respect your old-school Bikkuri reaction.
So he's doing it right now?
Yes, it's game on.
Traditional style.
Thank you very much.
Could you take a picture of us, please?
Yes, ma'am.
I see. A family photo.
Thank you.
Take one from here.
Okay.
I don't know...
If this should count.
Thank you.
Here it is.
Thank you very much.
They look delicious.
Sister
Thanks again.
Keiko has traveled to Tokyo
for a reason.
To showcase her skills as a fortune teller,
we've created a fake show for the two siblings.
Thinking the show is scheduled to tape tomorrow,
she has traveled to Tokyo from Osaka.
I have the script for tomorrow's show.
You'll be reading my fortune in the studio.
And then the unexpected happens...
I usually use one of these to do a reading.
Yaki Imo!
Roasted Sweet Potatoes!
That scared the heck outta me.
Just a mobile sweet potato truck.
In a room like this, I thought it was
some sort of a spirit or ghost.
Why don't you read my fortune?
- O-Okay...
We need to rehearse for the show.
Give me some bad news!
I would say this year, you'll have to...
have to watch yourself in July...
I should work on my reaction to the reading...
- Good idea.
Be careful this month, too.
This is an awesome move.
...so that will be my reaction.
"I should work on my reaction to the reading..."
His excise must have done the trick.
His sister lets the Bikkuri face go.
Of course.
Having succeeded so far,
Kinoshita dares to take the mission further.
How was your vacation in Korea?
...But why?
...because I put down a mattress
between two beds...
And because I couldn't speak the language, I was...
Bikkuri at the Wall
WTF?
Ongoing
Stretch it.
Stretching it.
Taking his chances.
Stretching it thin.
He's still at it.
Do you see a bug?
Still going.
What is it?
That was close.
That was way too close.
I have trouble seeing these days...
This room is kind of creepy...
Oh!
Do you see that thing?
Watch it!
Close call!
They're going for the traditional look.
That's their intent?
It's been two hours since they got together.
Kinoshita, with his mom's help, prepares fir the big finish.
Damn, took him two hours?
Amazing.
Still got stiff shoulders?
Yea, they're very stiff.
I can massage them for you.
- Thanks.
What a dirty trick...
By hiding his face from his sister,
he can accrue more minutes...
He did this the last time around, too.
But his sister's watching...
His the plan falls short as he unexpectedly
attracts her attention.
It looks like his plan isn't going to work, but...
How are your shoulders?
Yea, mine are bad, too.
He's definitely got your shoulders, Mom.
Go for it, don't hold back.
Is that so.
Go for it. Don't be shy. Use your full weight.
Like mother, like son.
Don't say that.
I'm not a fat - pig like him! No way.
Don't put us in the same category.
What's going on here?
Totem Pole!!
I know, right?
It' crazy...
I wasn't expecting this...
You're so thin...
but you're tense.
And with this...
I feel like...
What do you call that?
What the hell?!
Even though I'm very comfortable...
Explain that expression.
What's going on?
Is that Bikkuri face?
His mom needs to cut it out, too.
I have had enough!!
I don't get you...
The King of Bikkuri Face
Over
What was that all about?
You just had a nice dinner with your family...
Your sister was like, "What's going on?" a few times.
It got sketchy when you started staring at the bug.
Could you present his scores, Matsumoto?
High score on "Bikkuri Minutes."
But other than that...
I felt like your Mom helped you out a lot...
When my fortune said I needed to be careful this month,
My Mom was seriously like, "Oh shit!"
A very normal maternal reaction.
Let's move on.
Next challenger, c'mon out!!
Challenger
Shozo Endo
Naoki Tanaka
(Cocorico)
Thanks for having us.
They did the challenge together again.
Yes!
So you've decided to only participate as a duo?
Yes, we got permission.
Yes.
You had to get it approved?
Did you have to say,
"Pwease?"
One part unique talent and one part "pwease"...
It's Cocorico, here they come!
Cocorico
Target
Overseas Business Worker
Kiyoshi Hiraiwa
Dai Wen Chi
Setup
Metting to Discuss Overseas Business
Cocorico's targets are overseas business coordinators
who have been summoned for a meeting
to discuss Cocorico's future in other Asian markets.
Please watch our superb collaboration.
Yes.
We'll do our best
to focus on our one-two punches.
The King of  Bikkuri face
Start
Endo waits alone for his targets to arrive
What's up?
Oh, hi there.
- Hi there.
- Good evening.
Pleasure to meet you.
Endo notices there's something up with his target.
Are you a little drunk?
As the tipsy target settles in,
Tanaka shows up.
Man, it's cold.
What do you mean you're cold?!
Where's your freaking manners?!
Tanaka
Is that a Bikkuri face?
I'm very sorry that I'm late...
I don't think that should count.
Here's Dai-san's business card.
- Oh, that's hers?
- I see.
How do you read your first name?
- Um...
My first name is pronounced Wen-Chi.
It roughly means "beautiful cloud" in Chinese.
I like it.
I see, beautiful cloud.
- What a coll name.
Beautiful name.
How do you think Japanese comedy
would do in Shanghai?,
It goes without saying, but the language will be the challenge.
Ni hao.
- Ni hao.
Suddenly, Tanaka starts speaking in Chinese.
I remember you studied Chinese for a while.
How old are you?
I'll be 26 this year,
and how about you?
Endo
I'll be 41 this year.
Ongoing
Too long, too long.
Too long.
He's still at it!
Way too long.
They didn't notice though.
What's your occupation?
What did you ask him?
- I asked him about his occupation.
They seem clueless.
Get outta the frame, Tanaka!
I'm still going strong.
That's a long one.
W-what do I do?
What's my occupation?
Endo
I don't think that counts.
You're a comedian.
What about...
when you first came to Japan,
did you have a boyfriend back home?
Yes, I had a boyfriend before I left China.
But we broke up once I moved here.
Tanaka
I started dating another man
but we're no longer together,
Does that count?
Oh, it's Tanaka's turn.
But we're no longer together.
And that's where i'm at right now.
So you're single.
Were you dating a Japanese guy?
No, he was also an exchange student.
He was also from China then?
Why are you Bikkuri at Endo?
From Shanghai?
No, further north.
From Peking?
Yes, from Peking.
Anything wrong?
She must be like, "what a weirdo".
What a nice story.
I think she knows what's up.
Isn't it?
No, seriously.
Yea, she knows.
It's been an hour.
After successfully displaying numerous Bikkuri faces,
they aim for the big finish.
Your show "Golden Legend" is very popular in Taiwan right now.
Tanaka
The show "London Hearts"
is also playing in Taiwan.
If Atsushi showed up with his
band "Jealkb" in Taiwan,
and he stepped out in public with no disguise,
He would totally get recognized.
100% sure you've been exposed.
No, they didn't know.
Tanaka
Hiraiwa
But this ain't normal.
Seriously, no idea.
That's what I heard.
They didn't know.
This isn't right.
Excuse me.
Can I ask what this is?
We're submerging prawns in the
Shaoxing Wine to get them drunk.
- Let's check it out.
splash
Honestly, this is...
This is a high "Shit your pants" percentage
Scary...
Aren't you guys scared?
That was uncalled for.
They serve this in Shanghai too.
- Oh, is that right?!
May I have the check please?
It's interesting...
WHAT??!!
That's a huge bill!!
The poor server had to hear that?!
The King of Bikkuri Face
Over
Please, let me get that.
You don't think they found out?
I believe we barely made it through.
I bet she didn't feel
it was appropriate to call you out,
let alone in her second language.
I'm afraid you have a point.
So here's their score.
Let's see it.
Here it is.
I'm pretty certain that
the show was exposed.
They must've been very suspicious of you two.
I have to agree.
I see.
When we told them the truth later,
that male coordinator,
started crying.
Tears and everything.
He's a passionate guy and he had been thinking
"I have to do a better job..."
And that Bikkuri'ed (surprised) us the most.
Next week.
Well will continue the King of Bikkure Face Challenge.
Newcomer, Tsukaji, is in big trouble!
I'm getting lots of TV gigs though...
Do it!
The "Surprise" attack of Gekidan Hitori.
Don't miss it.
To those whom we've inconvenienced
What's this?
I'm really sorry.
But you have been setup.
You've been taped the whole time.
Is that why you paid for this?
W-Well, I suppose...
Well, I'm going to do better...
Why are you crying?
Really, why're you crying?
I appreciate your passion...
You made us realize,
how much you care about your work,
Thank you.
But I don't know how to react to your tears.
Looking forward to working with you.
Thank you.
Excuse us.
Good job, guys.
What a surprise.
What?
Can we see tour Bikkuri face please?
Thank you very much.
What the hell?!