TPF
Today, a certain man's special segment
Everyone, could I have your attention for a moment?
Somehow...
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Cocorico
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hosei
This weather is pretty heavy, isn't it.
You can feel it, yeah.
So, this time...
Endo has, in the past,
done a bit where he dressed up as Mori Shinichi, and performed as him in some situations.
"I'd Like to See Mori Shinichi Do This"
Endo responds to requests to see
Mori Shinichi in a variety of situations
I vaguely remember something like that.
Just a very faint memory.
It hasn't been that long since he did it, though.
No, it hasn't, but I was feeling like it had been at least 8 years ago.
Well, you see, regarding that segment
Endo himself actually really liked it.
Why?
Why exactly?
Probably, um...
I mean if he liked it, that's fine, it's his preference.
Yes, he really enjoyed it.
He really did like it.
I mean it, he actually did.
So for this time...you're familiar with the program 'Uchi Kuru!?', right?
(Uchi Kuru!?) is a program on Fuji TV that began in April 1999. It's a show where they and other guests visit a celebrity's home and/or hometown to try local specialties and showcase the guest.
He said he wanted to do Uchi Kuru
Endo said he wanted to do it?
Uchi Kuru!?
"You're Coming to My House!?"
A program where the hosts visit a featured guest's favourite shops
and ask them about their memories and personal stories
Yes, he said that he wanted to
do Uchi Kuru as Mori Shinichi.
Yeah.
Sounds annoying...
So...
How many people do you reckon are actually going to watch this?
He's very excited about it.
Mori Shinichi himself doesn't make appearances
on variety shows very much.
And for that very reason,
Endo wants to come do Uchi Kuru as Mori Shinichi.
This is Gaki no Tsukai though, so I mean...
This isn't actually Uchi Kuru and he isn't actually Mori Shinichi
It's like wearing another person's dirty underwear, isn't it
Mori Shinichi's Favourite Eats and Personal Stories
Brought to you entirely by Endo's imagination
And now, handing off to our guest of the day,
Mori Shinichi's favourite foods, memories, and personal stories
will all be brought to you according to Endo's imagination!
So let's introduce our guest!
Mori Shinichi, in person - Here he is!
Good afternoon, everyone.
I'm Mori Shinichi.
Today's Guest
Mori Shinichi?
So, just now,
I think Tanaka has already explained a bit...
Huh?
I think Tanaka has already explained a bit about this.
I've received a lot of requests to see what it
would be like if Mori Shinichi were to appear on Uchi Kuru!?
I've really been hearing it from all over.
So today we're going to see what that might be like.
Sorry to interrupt, but
How long of a delay is Gaki running on today?
(Staff)
It's scheduled for a 30-minute delay.
30 minutes, huh?
Would've been nice to push it back further, though
We won't be going home until the middle of the night.
I don't know about that...
So this is just like a segment of Uchi Kuru, or more accurately Uchi Iku ("going to your home").
Can you give us the title call of the day?
Uchi Iku ("We're Going to My Place")
Goin' Goin'
Uchi Iku!?
Shall we get started?
Let's go, let's go.
Let's get a real early start on this one.
Let's head out to our destination.
The one you personally selected, yeah?
(Staff)
Alright, that's finished!
Excellent work.
(Manager)
Your vehicle will be over here.
I guess this is because he's supposed to be Mori Shinichi.
He's got an amazing entourage with him.
What are they talking about?
We're not getting that level of of treatment!!
Who is that, anyway?
That's supposed to be his manager, I guess.
We haven't even started moving yet, so where the hell are they going?
Good working with you all.
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents:
Down Town's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Translator:
Typesetter:
Proofreader:
Lian-Jie
Otviss
Christian
**We also have Facebook and Twitter.**
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
If you're unhappy about anything regarding the episode, please send us feedback at: Tofupandahost@gmail.com
*Komazawa is a neighbourhood in the Setagaya Ward of Tokyo City
A Trip with Mori Shinichi: Trying out local cuisine in Komazawa
The four go with Mori Shinichi to try out some of his favourite eateries. Let's see our first stop of the day!
And right here, is a restaurant
that Mori-san comes to quite regularly.
So Mori-kun, uh, Mori-san, uh
It's hard to know what to call him
I can't quite get the hang of it...
What could they be chatting about?
Is there a point to coming here so early just to meet us like this?
It's amazing, really.
Oh, hello!
I kind of, uh,
got here a bit ahead of time.
Of course you got here first, you left before we did.
Multinational Cuisine George
2nd Floor 1-3-1 Komazawa, Setagaya Ward
Mori Shinichi's first selection is right near Komazawa University Station
"George", a restaurant specialising in multinational cuisine.
So Mori-san, do you live somewhere around here?
Ah, well you see,
I'd really rather not say...
¤ Endo will answer questions and give personal stories based on what he imagines Mori Shinichi would say
This is Uchi Kuru, right?
You'd expect some info like that right?
You would, wouldn't you?
In any case, I come here about
three times a week.
That's quite a lot.
Three is, yeah, a few.
So when you come here,
Where do they usually seat you?
Well when the weather is nice,
I sit out there on the terrace.
How about private rooms, you don't use those?
For private rooms...
if I can get a reservation I'll use them.
If it's you, you certainly should be able to get one!
So there's times where you can't get a reservation?
Yes, there are.
That expression you made
That was the same face you made when you retired!
Ehh...
I'm fine with it, really.
You just looked really sad for a moment there.
Using the entire body
Pasta with Lobster
And here we have Mori's first selection,
this prepared pasta with lobster
How did you hear about this restaurant?
Well, you see...
A close friend of mine...
Who are you talking about?
Yeah, who?
He's just a friend I have,
H-His name's Inoue.
So he's just an ordinary guy?
Okay, sure, but-
And he's the one who introduced you to this place?
Yes, it was Inoue who told me about it.
What sort of work does Inoue do exactly?
Well Inoue, he...
Over in Sakura-shin, he runs a Teppan-yaki place.
So wouldn't it have been better if
we went to his place for lunch instead?
Ow, ow, ouch...
And Inoue would've gotten something out of it too.
Yeah, for his Teppan-yaki place.
There's water right there.
It's right in front of your face!
Could I get a cloth?
Let me have that, thank you.
Well let's ask for some too, then.
What, you mean a cloth?
He's got loads of assistants here.
I wish he'd introduce some of them to us.
The make-up assistants are seriously up there in years.
Are there really 3 make-up assistants?
So first of all, the lobster
Let's eat.
When I heard about this, I figured people would watch it on TV and some Mori Shinichi fans might come out.
You'd hope so.
I think we have an opportunity here.
To ask him about stories from before he
made his debut as a singer...
I imagine you must have had a hard
time in the industry until you hit it big?
Well, I was born in
Yamanashi, you see.
Huh?
So he actually is giving some real info here.
Mori Facts - Profile
*'Group Employment', or 集団就職, was a system of finding work
wherein unemployed graduates (usually of Junior High Schools)
would come to urban areas for employment of varying quality.
It seems to have been more prevalent in the decades just after WWII.
Via group employment,
Born in Yamashi Prefecture, then lived in Kagoshima Prefecture
After Junior High, he came to Osaka via group employment*
I came to Tokyo
How old were you at the time?
Around 20 years old
Right around there.
That's pretty late.
You were 20?
20 is definitely late, man.
He should've been in his teens back then.
Somewhere in the middle, yeah.
Apparently he started working after Junior High.
That's not what he said at all.
Ah, well...anyway.
Anyway?
You have to support your family.
And you weren't married back then, were you?
I just mean the family from before I got married-
the family that raised me, you know.
So who, for example?
Do you have any siblings?
Oh, as for that,
I do have some, yes.
Please tell us!
Actually tell us about them!
Sisters? Brothers?
I had an older sister as well.
Yes, an older sister.
Mori Facts - Profile
Together with a younger brother and older sister, the Moriuchi (Mori's real name) family had 3 kids.
So, in the beginning-
How about a dog?
Did you ever own a dog or anything like that?
A dog, right...
It's not like I said
"Let's get a dog" or anything, but,
there certainly was one.
What the hell are you saying?
You have no idea, do you?
What was its name, then?
It was called Pera...Bera
Pera...Bera
Pera...Pera.
Pera?
It was called Pera?
There was Pera and there was Bera, you see.
So you had two dogs?
He had two?
Ah, I see, two dogs.
Who debuted around the same time as you?
At that time...
There was Ikuzoh, Yoshi Ikuzoh.
That's definitely not right.
Yeah that can't be right.
His debut was a bit later, I think.
Well actually, most of them are already dead.
If they were really dead, you'd remember them a little better than that!
Yeah, you tend to remember dead people.
Anyway, so-
As for the types of work you've done, I've heard
Mori Facts - Profile
Including sushi restaurants, dining halls, transportation, and ironworks,
Mori Shinichi has had experience in close to 20 different fields of work
you've had close to 20 different types of part-time jobs. Is that true?
That's true, I have.
I was a roadie once,
and I've also worked at cafés.
Cafés?
Let's see, what else...
Being a ticket man at the aquarium and stuff like that.
You mean you were a ticket collector?
Are you okay?
This is terrible, man.
What sort of circumstances brought you to an aquarium?
Hmm...
What's the matter?
It's just,
today's been pretty exhausting.
Exhausting?
Are you alright?
It's just my face...
Your face?
Ah, I bet his face is tired.
So that's what's exhausting.
I see, I see
What job made you quit the fastest?
My job at the aquarium.
How long were you there before you quit?
It might've been my first morning, actually.
Really?
That very same morning?
A surprise visit from one of Mori's friends
After the break, an old friend of Mori's comes by for a surprise visit!
So I've already heard this, but
You've even had a job at a furniture store in the past.
And while you worked there,
you learned some unique skills.
That's what I've heard.
Unique skills?
Like for a piece of furniture-
Being able to carry a heavy cabinet with your shoulders
Ohkawa Eisaku  had a trick like that
Yeah, that's Ohkawa's thing
Well,
Eisaku actually saw me doing it first
So he copied you!
I see, so you started it
We've actually prepared a cabinet
just for the occasion
Looks pretty heavy.
He's going to carry this by himself?
I mean, if he can pull it off,
it'll be be quite something.
He's amazing.
What's the trick to doing something like this?
It's his back, I'm guessing.
Right, of course.
Ah, this takes me back.
So is that how you used to do it?
You were measuring it by sun*
*(a unit of measurement that equals roughly to 3cm)
Yes, in suns*
You measured it in suns*
Back in my day we would measure these by sun, you see.
That's how you're doing it right now!
You take this...
He did this for over 20 years...
I have to be careful
Those people over there are looking really concerned.
They're making a face like
"Don't make him do something like this!"
Excuse me, but uh-
Yes of course, go ahead.
I'm not sure where to grab it.
It's comin' out, man.
This is gonna be the scariest part.
That's dangerous!
Mori-san?
What the hell is wrong with this guy?
Did they really write that this is a skill I have?
Hmm, yes, we heard this was a unique skill of yours.
The thing is I just did it once way back when...
Well if you push yourself too hard you'll just get hurt.
Ah, he got it up there.
Just like we expected, you did it just fine.
And you'd carry it like that, I guess.
Experience from his old part-time job
Why did he kick it?
What reason could he possibly have to kick it?
What's the matter?
Maybe they didn't tell him about this in the meeting.
We're very sorry for all that.
Once more from back then
A Big Surprise From His Youth
And now, to relive moments from his youth, a surprise guest is here!
Apparently, the longest part-time job you ever held
was as a waiter at a cabaret in Shinjuku.
At the time, at that cabaret...
There was a co-worker who
really supported you, wasn't there?
That same person has come to see you today
It's a co-worker you came to know very well - Honda-san!
Wow, it's Honda-san!
Long time no see!
Old Friend from Work
Honda Kiyozumi
How've you been, Mori?
It's certainly been a while.
And you haven't changed a bit.
I guess these things really do happen.
You don't really change much?
Yeah, I suppose so, but-
You lost a bit of weight, didn't you?
I just got old, that's all.
He he he
Well of course, I've aged a bit myself.
Did you just know each other at work?
Or did you go out to drink some nights, or anything like that?
Back then it was all about Mahjong~
We enjoyed it a lot.
And you'd go 'Honda Reach'*!
*(Reach is a Mahjong term)
Ah yes, I remember that one.
Eeeh...
What is this 'Honda Reach' crap?
So Honda-san, what was his work like at the cabaret?
Well, you see, the place was a cabaret,
so naturally, we had quite a few scary customers come in.
But, at times like that
Mori would, with his personality and character, respond really well to those types of situations.
So there were times where you had to deal with that sort of thing?
I would say something like "please stop that..."
One time though, he was like "let's take this outside,"
but when he came back,
he was shaking the guy's hand and had a smile on his face.
Do you remember that?
...there was that, yeah.
If you don't remember, that's fine too.
I don't remember it too well.
Of course, it was quite some time ago,
and usually third parties remember it better anyway.
After this time in his life he would go on to
pursue the life of a singer.
So we'll be hearing about that
at our next stop on the trip.
Thanks so much.
(Staff)
Alright, that's it!
We got it!
Alright, well until next time...
Mori-san?
He's super pissed.
I think he probably lost it at that
thing with the cabinet.
He was really angry after that.
A Trip with Mori Shinichi: Trying out local cuisine in Komazawa
Thanks for being with us Honda-san!
Now we once again head back towards Komazawa Park~!
Now, right here,
we would like to make one of Mori-san's old dreams a reality!
Surprise Segment
Mori Shinichi's dream comes true!
What do you say?
Yes, of course.
As for what will make his dream come true - Let's see it!
Well, well...
Here it is, here it is!
Wow, that's impressive.
It's arrived just for you
And it is,
The sidecar of a
Harley Davidson motorcycle
Ah, wow!
Say something, for fuck's sake.
That's irritating, is that how he acts when he's happy?
The ultra-classic sidecar of a Harley Davidson
Mori-san's thoughts on this bike are...
I grew up in a very rural area, you see,
out in the sticks and stuff,
There'd be bikes for plowing the fields and things
Sort of like tractors.
Right, like tractors.
And basically that's all I'd ever seen
I thought, so there are bikes out there with leather on them
And from there, I just sort of fell for them.
Do you have a license to drive one of these?
Well,
I went and got one, just for that reason.
Even though it was your dream, and you even got a license,
you didn't actually buy one?
It was a bit dangerous as well, you know.
You do like bikes, though.
Driver
The driver's going "uh-huh, uh-huh"
"Uh-huh, uh-huh"
You can't just jump in
with that crap.
I am happy about this, though.
Yeah, you're going to fulfill your dream today.
Can I get in?
Go on, go ahead.
So this time, he'll-
He's going for the side.
Why the hell did he get a license then?
It was his dream to ride in the sidecar, I guess.
Are you sure you don't want to drive?
I'm pretty sure he can hear you.
Hey!
MORI!
Let's be going then.
You'll be riding in the sidecar then.
I see, I see, have a nice trip!
I'm going!
I wish he'd just ride that fucking thing all the way home.
His Sought-After Harley Davidson
Mori Shinichi's dream came true.
A Trip with Mori Shinichi: Trying out local cuisine in Komazawa
Our next stop on our trip with Mori-san is~
Meshi-Dokoro Den
6-14-2 Fukusawa, Setagaya Ward
A restaurant known only to those in the know, Meshi-Dokoro 'Den'
We'll be having the Soba Gozen, with this season's tempura and a side of sashimi.
Soba Gozen
I'd be curious to hear about the concepts behind this meal.
Like the proper way to eat it,
what's the etiquette?
Well this, you see...
You totally just opened it to check what was inside.
Anyway, Mori-san,
I've been told that the catalyst for your debut was when you won a singing contest on TV.
Mori Facts - Profile
Took first place on a TV singing contest, 'Rhythm Singing Match'
His talent was picked up on and was signed to a large agency
Yes, that's true.
That's right
Which record company
were you contracted with?
It was with Victor・JVC...
Tanaka, is that...
I don't have that
info on here.
(Staff)
That's correct.
You were surprised to hear that just now, weren't you?
You were completely taken aback.
Mori Shinichi's Passionate Singing
After the break, we hear Mori Shinichi's passionate singing!
The Hamada Bamyu Bamyu Project
We've finished putting together the music.
Musician and Producer Tanaka Yasutaka
Masuda, I'm already over 50 for god's sake!
Art Director Sebastian Masuda
Release coming in the next few days!!
The manager you had at the start of your career
was there for both good times and bad, wasn't he?
Yes...
Actually,
Here today, we've invited your
first manager, Nomura-san, to come see you.
Hey, Mori!
It's been so long since I last saw you...
Mori's First Manager
Nomura Shinji
This is just so moving...
It is, isn't it.
I mean, it's someone he's known for a long time.
Isn't he crying?
Ah, he's not even tearing up.
He'd cry at this, you'd think.
But, I guess he isn't going to.
So Nomura-san, how many
years were you with Mori as his manager?
Well, Mori-san was...
Wait, Mori-san was what?
We're talking about Nomura-san.
It's been such a long time since you've seen each other, I'm sure-
But,
this time,
with memories of your struggles together as a team,
Nomura-san has brought a letter
he wrote just for you.
Would it be alright if
he read it aloud for us right now?
Mori-san's face is a bit...
To Moriー
In my time as a manager,
the three years I spent working with you are irreplaceable.
When you came to stay at my house,
3 years after your debut and hadn't made it yetーI remember that.
At the time, when we were coming back from an audition
in Uchisai-cho for NHK, we only had ￥80 between us.
The train fare back to where we lived in Kamata was ￥40 per-person.
We were starving, and there were two choices in front of us:
Eat the cheap tanuki udon at NHK's cafeteria, or take the train home.
We really stressed over it, but in the end, we went with the udon, didn't we.
On our way back home, you said just a few words to me.
"Don't worry Nomura-san, I'll definitely become a big star.
And when I do, I'll treat you to shrimp tempura udon."
It looks like you were telling the truth back then.
(His face) is just getting worse and worse.
I look forward to the day we'll
share that udon together.
-Nomura
Thanks so much, Nomura-san.
So the shrimp tempura udon, have you...?
I haven't gotten it for him yet.
That was a very Osakan way to say that.
"I haven't gotten it for him yet."
Well it's important to you both.
I see, well,
here today,
Mori-san has something
very important to tell us about.
Uh...
I have, for this very day-
There's a poster for it up there in the back as well, but,
I'm putting out a CD.
"For this very day?"
It's planned to go on sale
starting this Autumn...
It's called "O-Fukuro Botaru" (Mother Firefly)
Ah, so this is actually a promo for the CD?
I asked if I might be allowed to sing it for you here...
Really?
The song, you mean?
Yes, is that alright?
Let's get started then.
As Mori Shinichi:
"O-Fukuro Botaru"
O-Fukuro Botaru (Mother Firefly)
Lyrics: Kageyama Hiroshi | Composition: Aoyama Haruki
When the sea calls out,
a man's heart burns
He turns to drink to mask the fear
Seeing dreams of fortune, he seeks a ship
"The reckless and foolish son"
Leaving nothing but harsh words
Holding a vigil at the shore,
the mother prays for her son's safe return
At the cape of Erimo,
*"The Cape at Erimo" (Erimo no Misaki) is a hit Mori Shinichi song from the 1970s.
The reference here is that this story of a mother and son is also set there.
that wavering light isー
The Mother Firefly
At the cape of Erimo,
that wavering light isー
The Mother Firefly～
Thank you.
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
Thank you all so much.
Alright, that's it! That's a wrap!
Thank you for coming.
Thanks so much for coming.
That's it, we got it.
Really, thank you.
Oh, thanks.
Why does he always leave so damn quickly?