TPF
Ice Coffee
Breaking down "ice coffee" to similar words such as ice mohhii
The group tested the limits to see how far they can keep the order without saying the actual name
"I'll have Ouyanfuifui"*
*Ouyang Fei Fei - A Taiwanese singer
"Ouyanfuifui"
Ouyan Ice coffee
Ice Coffee?
You said it didn't you?
Cold Noodles
Previously, using "miyashi chuuka" or "suzuki chouka"
The group embarked on ordering cold noodles (hiyashi chuuka) using phonetically similar words
Umm suzuki kyouka
Umm suzuki kyouka*
*Japanese Actress
Sui?...
Suzuki Kyouka
You mean suigyouza? (boiled dumplings)
Yes, suigyouza
Suigyouza!?(boiled dumplings)
A new
limit is reached!
And this time, the group approaches a new limit!
Gaki no Tsukai's third...
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Endo, take over
Let's go
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Everyone!
What does that mean?
I'm just trying!
Cocorico
Tanaka Naoki
Alright!
Go ahead
The third gek...
Tofu Panda Fansubs Presents:
Down Town's Gaki no tsukai ya arahende!!
Translator:
Typesetter:
Typechecker:
Tako
James
Otviss
**We also have facebook and twitter.**
______________________________________________________
To see progress of each episode we're working on, please visit Tofupandas.tumblr.com/subs. There you can find both streaming and download links for subbed episodes! Thanks!
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
So mild seven!
The limit of Mild Seven
Yamazaki Hosei
Yes, Mild Sevens
We will be challenging ourselves with ordering Mild Sevens
With ten alternative titles
I see
Have been prepared for us
The transformation of "mild seven"
The first one is
this
"Seven Mild"
A simple switch
An achievable goal
Next
"Tobacco Seven"
How will this play out?
This could be interesting in how it plays out
This could bring you Seven Star (another brand of cigarettes)
Ah Seven Star
Alright next
"Ultra Seven"
This could be a bit of an extreme
"Idol Kibun" (Idol feeling)
Right
This could be a hurdle
It's starting to change
So next
"Maguro Gyosen" (tuna fishing boat)
No one would buy a fishing boat there
"Mild Seven" and "Maguro Gyosen"
Could be possible
And next
"Maiko-san"
Maiko-san
The pronunciation could be key here
Yes
So next is
"my sweet memory"
That's completely different
But when it comes to pronunciation, you could be wrong
Ah
And the last one here
"Maetake Kyosen"*
*Early comedy variety show from 1969-1970
That's a bit old
They're a little above our generation
I'm sure some will understand this
We'll have these three now
How far is "Mild Seven"
Still Mild Seven?
Let's start!
Mild Seven Limit
Research Results
Seven Mild
Excuse me
Yes
One Seven Mild
Mild Seven!?
So this
Ok
Seven Mild
Tobacco Seven
Uh, Excuse me
Uhh tobacco seven
tobacco seven
One
What's tobacco seven?
Tobacco seven
Did you mean Seven Star?
There
Oh wow
This?
Tobacco Seven
I believe this is it
She's just pushing that one
The box says Seven Star
Seven Star of Tobacco
When asked for "Tobacco Seven"
Seven Star is brought out
Tobacco Seven
Ultra Seven
Excuse me
What? What Seven? Mild...
Ultra Seven!?
Is this fine?
We don't have any cigarettes called Ultra Seven
Please
There are no cigarettes called Ultra Seven!
Then... Seven Mild
Alright then, Mild Seven
Scared of the clerk, Tanaka changes the name
Seven Mild? Just one
Alright
Just one
Don't change the name, Tanaka!
Ultra Seven
It was super scary
You have to push past it!
Idol Kibun (Idol Feeling)
Uhm
One Idol Kibun
Huh?
That's how you're feeling
Idol Kibun
Again with Idol Kibun
Idol King?
Idol Kibun
Not Idol King
A Cigarette?
Yes, the cigarette AiRUDO Kibun
Not Mild Seven?
Ah, yes thank you
Idol Kibun (Idol Feeling)
Maguro Gyosen
(Tuna Fishing Boat)
Excuse me
Yes?
Can I please have a Maguro Gyosen
Mild Seven!
Wow!
Maguro Gyosen please
That was instant!
This definitely works!
This is Maguro Gyosen right!
Yes, thank you very much
Mild Seven is given as if he ordered it normally
Alright thank you
Thanks
Maguro Gyosen (Tuna Fishing Boat)
Maiko-san
Uhhh Maiko-san
Euh?
What's a Maiko-san?
Uhh
Huh?
He could've said that better
What's a Maiko-san?
Then, I'll have Maiko-san
Marlboro-san?
Maiko-san
Aiko-san what're you saying?
What is it!
Maiko-san
The lady thinks its Aiko-san
Mild...
What, you want mild?
Three Milds?
You want this right?
Right?
Maiko-san turned into
Mild Sanko (Three Milds)
So three Mild Sevens then
This woman's got a lot of power
Three Mild Sevens then
Three Mild Sevens
Mairudo San, right? (Three Milds)
Which country are you from?
Maiko-san
Hm?
My sweet memory
Memory?
Menthol?
Mai Sen Memori
This is shaky
We have Mild Seven Light if that's what you mean
It was scary
I don't think we know what you're talking about
I've never heard of memories
Tobacco?
Extra?
My sweememroy
The three employees panic
I've never heard of them
Trying to stretch this out
Tanaka begins to get ignored
My sweet memory, one please
What is memory?
Then..
You're not talking about menthol right?
I'm sorry
Maetake Kyosen
Excuse me
One maetake kyosen
He said it so clearly
Maetake kyosen?
Maetake kyosen.
Eh?
What is this maetake kyosen?
It's maetake kyosen
It feels a little light
When some people order Mild Seven
They like to call it maitake
So when people want Mild Seven they ask for maitake?
They call Mild Seven Light "maitake"
Some call it maitake?
A good amount of people call it that
Oh, really!
But maetake kyosen is...
Maetake Kyosen
Well out of ten...
Six of them went through
Were somewhat safe
These are the results but now...
Both of us, as Downtown will go
So we'll finish with this!
Maikeru Tomioka (Michael Tomioka)
This might be a bit of a long shot
This is fine
The only similarity is "Mi"
It also ends with "tomioka" too, so
We also have "ru"
So, Matsumoto-san
Yes, yes
So we're going to a café
Completely disguised to test
Downtown heads to a café
This is a good way to test this
It's relatively common to ask for cigarettes at a café
So we ask for Michael Tomioka
And see if we can get Mild Sevens
Yeah
So let's see if it works
Let's go
Will the duo really
be able to buy Mild Seven?
Will the duo be able to buy Mild Seven?
The results will be on
later in the show!!
Mild Seven Limit
Research Results
Can I have the ice milk tea
One ice milk tea
Alright
Uhhhm ouyan ice coffee
Ice coffee. Right.
Yes
Clear for now!
It's not clear yet!
Will ordering Michael Tomioka
be able to get them Mild Seven!?
Looks like ice coffee came first
Do you have any tobacco?
Yes ,what would you like?
Yes, what would you like?
Michael Tomioka!
In terms of mild
Which Mild?
The Tomioka
Eh!
The Tomioka ones
Do you have Michael Tomioka?
...there are none of them
I'm not sure but in terms of Milds we have
The regular ones. is that fine?
The regular ones. Is that fine?
Here it comes
That's OK
That's OK!
We have a lot of milds so I wasn't sure
Yes, those are the Tomiokas
That's what they're called
Alright
When you said the Tomiokas..
How could anyone judge like this?
But it still came!
Michael Tomioka
It's exactly what I wanted
With enough convincing
Oh, here it is!
Ours is definitely good!
Oh, yeah?
Lady continues to not recognize Downtown
Throughout the end
I promise you
Thank you
Ouyan fuifui
Saying silly things again
I don't know what you're saying
I realized one thing
When you do these challenges
You make a favorable impression towards the employees
In a way
That's because you're trying to be nice
Well I'm not so...