Before recording an episode, someone is missing from the dressing room.
ShinobiSubs
Translated from French by MissPlasticFlower. French Translation from Silver
Additional lines by ShinobiSubs
We're waiting on Hamada!!
He's late.
He's probably practising golf. Like an idiot...
He's really stupid.
He's not stupid...
If you can't keep time, you're not even civilised, you're retarded.
But he's really busy at the moment. He's involved in a drama series.
He is a bit busy I guess
That has nothing to do with it. Gaki is Gaki. He has to respect the meeting time.
That is true...
Hey... well...
Can I show you something?
What's that? It's been a while since I've since one!
It's a video tape but...
But there is actually something on it I want to show you...
What are you saying?!
It sounds scary
-It's not like that
It's going to be something I don't want to see
You're mistaken, I've been thinking about moving house recently
The other day, I had some spare time, so I checked out this place.
I thought the wife would want to see it so I took a camera...
I  went to view the house, but when I got home and checked the video...
So can we...
Stop, that's scary!
No, no, but really...
I really want you to see it
It is really something unbelievable
This is scary!
You know, I was REALLY surprised!
But just what is this mysterious footage on Tanaka's tape?!
FunnyJapan/ShinobiSubs  Reddit /r/FunnyJapan
Facebook/ShinobiSubs  Twitter @ShinobiSubs
Tanaka has brought a video tape with him, but what has he captured!?
I was really shocked.
You were actually surprised?
I was EXTREMELY surprised!
That's why you have to see it
I'm kinda interested...
It's only lasts 2~3 minutes, please watch
What happened is incredible
Do you mind if I film this?
-(Agent) Not at all.
I would like to show this to my wife later
-I understand feel free
-Sorry for the trouble
Please come in a take a look
So this is the house?
Yes, this is it.
It's really plush
Woah, you're aiming high.
It's all white.
It's really beautiful inside.
A hundred pairs of shoes?!
Yes!
He mentioned there was room for 100 pairs of shoes, remarkable
It really wasn't bad at all.
Everything is white.
Wouldn't your children get it dirty?
Hmmm... I am concerned about that.
The toilet is just beside the entrance.
I think having the toilet there is kinda...
Really? It's practical I thought
That's what I think. It must be in the house.
Yes, exactly.
It's a European style.
It's amazing. Very spacious.
Perfect for a family of 4
20 jou! (About 60 metres)
I was really pleased at this point
The TV was included?
Yes, it comes furnished
Does it have parking?
It has
I was really delighted, the TV is included.
It probably relates to the rent
It really wasn't that expensive, plus the TV was 42 inches
It's a really nice place
There are a lot of windows, so the room gets plenty of light
From this part on please pay close attention
It's very spacious!
It has a very foreign style to it
Wait a sec...?
This is the part, I'll pause it
There was something!
It was at this point.
It was only you and the estate agent right?
There was only two of us.
I looked around the whole place, it was modern, and I really liked it
I was filming the place but...
I happened to capture something unbelievable
Please watch again
-In the kitchen?
Watch again
It's really big.
I was really impressed
It's just coming up now, please watch carefully
There was something !
Can you pause it, I want to see...
I'll pause it on the scene
Stop when you see it, got it?
I loved the house, it was beautiful.
There!
It's a member of Downtown...
Is it really?
It's our member...
It's a Downtown member?
It's him right? It's him for sure
It looks like him, but it's hard to tell
But if you look at that face...
With a head that big...
The balance is out of proportion right
Did you say hello?
You didn't say hello?
To this guy
No, I... Also think the same...
I didn't notice him at the time!
It was only once I went home and watched the recording that I thought WTF?!
I'm sure your wife was surprised.
She was shocked
It's usually okay to see him on TV but this...
Actually, I feel pretty uneasy
I was really surprised, I had no idea at the time
No Tanaka, it's rather... How should I put it
I really don't understand
I didn't see, and meanwhile...
Well you weren't looking for him right?
I just don't understand what happened
Can I just mention something?
Well...
Actually, I also have something I would like to show...
-What is it?
The other day, I was taking a break
So I went to play golf with some friends
A friend had just brought a camera
He just wanted to film in general, nothing special
After the golf, we went to eat
And he was always trying to film
That evening, he called me and asked me to come see him
I was wondering what had happened, and well...
There was something in his recording...
I brought it with me
Tanaka isn't the only one... Endo also has "something" in his video!
Can I?
If it's not long, go for it.
It's not long then?
It's not long, it was just meant to be a normal private video
This place, the food is delicious
Yes, those are my friends.
It's a restaurant I often go to.
He didn't have to film, but as it was his new camera...
But it's good to film things. It's preserves memories.
When you forget and find it, this kind of movie is always funny
You played very well for your first time.
You think so? I didn't realise it was so tiring!
It's just a regular private video.
It's a burger restaurant
It's got that amateur shot feel to it with the movement
Haven't you filmed enough today?
It's cool, anyway can I ask something
Both of you are dressed alike!
Like a dance routine!
Look, about this...
Even the same colour!
I dressed after showering and then I realized.
It's quite embarrassing
You have to dress the same as us next time!
I don't have anything stylish like that!
It's such a normal video...
I'll have the hamburger please
(Waitress) Okay
This also please
-Sure thing
Well, I'll have the same.
It's a little inconsiderate to film like that
But well, it's difficult to ask to stop.
I've caught a cold.
Are you ok?
I didn't notice it earlier playing golf
It's probably because I was concentrating
It's only afterwards that I was suddenly reminded of my cold.
You should eat meat to help get better
Please pay close attention to this part
Wait, wait, that part
Stop the video!
I'm not sure what I... Did everybody...?
Let's take another look
The waitress drops a fork and then... Watch again
She dropped the fork just there!
Here! Look!
Can we watch it again but slower?
I'll just re-wind a little
What is the meaning of this
-I'm sure I saw something for certain
This is... Where is it coming up soon...
Stop there!!
It's him...
He's looking right at the camera
Did you...
-Not at all
I didn't notice at all
It's quite a shock...
This is just as much of a shock as the Lehman shock (2008 financial crisis)
What is the meaning of this? What's going on
I don't really know myself...
Did you say hello?
No I didn't...
There's no mistake that is a Downtown member right?
It's him. It is definitely him.
It certainly appears to be so...
But even so with this...
That member doesn't appear to be in a good mood though...
That's true... It's a little scary
Really, what is he thinking....
It's definitely this jerk for sure though ahhhh!!!!
This is weird
Can I show you guys something?
You must be joking...
Housei-san has a tape also?
I was going to a shoot in Osaka...
I live in Tokyo...
I was driving with the manager recording...
It must have been the day before yesterday...
Please take a look
Coming up next, even more bizarre footage?!
Just what is the unbelievable thing Yamasaki saw while driving?!
It's pretty intense
This has an awkward feel to it already
I wasn't expecting anyone to see it
It's a personal recording right?
This is on the freeway
It really is!
What were you doing?!
-It was meant to be private you know so...
It's private but you still do this kind of....
I think I just...
There was something just then
I saw something...
It was on the freeway but we saw something
Can you see it?
-You can clearly
Lets watch again to be sure
This is it, here, here.
-STOP!
This is strange
This is our guy right...
There is no mistake
He's outside though?
-Outside on the freeway!
It's impossible!
He's looking this way
Why do I have to be okay with having him as a partner
Really, it's bizarre
Well look, the meaning of this, let's stop for a second
The data is piling up that he's trying to send a message...
But what is it?
His spirit...
His spirit seeking revenge?
Can it really be...
We know that guy is...
A super sadist, maybe he wants to watch you guys suffer?
It's not the curse of words, it's the curse of Hamada
TN; 言魂kotodama, is 'The spirit of words' that influence the world
The wordplay 浜魂Hamadama being the spirit influence is the gag
It must be the power of Hamada's spirit at work here
The curse of Hamada...
-He shouldn't be cursing or resentful toward us!
Can I say something if it is the curse of Hamada...
What...
What now...
I have something that my prove it...
What is this mysterious footage Fujiwara has that proves the curse of Hamada?!
Recently I was out practising some vocals
I was with the director at a karaoke box
It was being taped to send for auditions and such
Then later, the director suddenly called me
'Something great happened' he said to me
Can I show you?
Is it okay to...
I don't really have any idea of how it will look so...
It's coming up, please listen carefully
I have heard this laugh before...
There is definite laughing
I could hear the laughing
I heard it but...
-Wait, hold on...
There is no other person laughing there
Did you notice it when you were there?
I didn't hear it at all
If I had, you would see my reaction
Can we watch it again?
The laugh is so out of place
There is no mistake
That's enough, that's enough...
You could quite clearly hear the laugh was going on
I have experienced the same thing coming from the next dressing room
I don't even know what he's laughing at
But... What if
That was... How to put it...
I'm sure it was
Crosstalk it's called
Like interference with the karaoke equipment?
Exactly! The more convenient to use equipment has come the more complex it also is
I can understand that...
I'm not going to stick up for my partner but...
I just don't think he is like that
I know what you mean...
Sorry, can I say something?
It isn't great but....
What kind of scene is it?
Just what has been happening to Inomoto?!
Recently I've been snoring...
It's pretty bad and loud
So I set up a camera to record me sleeping
Please keep that in consideration
It isn't a very good picture captured but...
This is a pretty spooky scene
Is the snoring really that bad?
I've been told it is but wanted to see for myself, that's why...
The tape is quite long, you can fast forward it if you want
This is just normal sleeping
I don't think anyone starts snoring that quickly
The snoring should be coming up
But I still haven't hear the snoring it's pretty quiet
Ah I see... Like that...
This part here, here!!
You saw it right?
I was a lot!
I saw a lot! Why...
There was a ghost!
That happens now and again
That's a good thing?
-That's fine, it's after that
Right after that you need to check
It's really scary
Let's watch it once again
It's definitely a ghost!
-That's fine
There!!
The other member!
It definitely was that right?
Lets watch closely
That's how it begins but...
Here! This is a ghost for sure
That ghost is fine, it comes round every night
Look!
The curse of Hamada
The member with the shining nostrils...
He must be in heat, that's why he is shining
It must be breeding season then?
When this happened you didn't hear any voices?
I didn't notice a thing
Does he want to become a ghost?
Why would he? I don't understand
Hamada-san?
Hello?
Hamada?
It's me
Matsumoto
What do you mean you didn't have the number saved? It's me Matsumoto
He didn't have the number saved....
It's Matsumoto, I told you to save my number the other day
Up next, the truth revealed?!
To find out the truth about what's going on, Matsumoto calls Hamada...
No really, yeah... Yeah
It's fine
Seriously?! Oh I see
Oh yeah?
No way!!
-What are they talking about?
Serious?
The 60 minute course?
No fucking way, you really did?!
That's how it was then
I see!! I see!!
That's nice but...
Recently...
Tanaka... Tanaka had a private...
Oh?
Do you know what happened to Yamasaki recently?
Yes, yes...
I see
-What's going on?
Ok, ok, yeah that's fine don't worry about it
Just...
That's fine don't worry
Eh? Hello? Don't forget tomorrows Downtown DX
Okay, yep, see you then
-See you then?
I thought Hamada was going to come here
-I don't get what happened on the phone...
What did he say?
He said he didn't know
Didn't know?!
He didn't know?! Are you sure you got what he said?
He didn't have a clue!
FunnyJapan/ShinobiSubs  Reddit /r/FunnyJapan
Facebook/ShinobiSubs  Twitter @ShinobiSubs