Translation: TeaVilla, Solari, N3gra, Mickstar813 ~ Typesetting: HouseiGIFs
Quiz About
Matsumoto Hitoshi
We want to know more about Matsumoto Hitoshi.
Narrator:
Ohta Shinichiro
After all this time...?
100 questions about Matsumoto Hitoshi.
Surely we don't need to...
As this time, we are doing
100 questions about Matsumoto Hitoshi
and he is the main character on this show.
Right.
Whoever has the least correct answers,
a severe punishment awaits...
Whoever comes bottom
will receive a severe punishment!
Geez...
Surely we don't need to have that...
Question 1.
Ehh, a punishment?
What's Matsumoto real big on right now?
* "My Boom" - Slang for a current obsession
Ehh, wait a minute, first question's that!?
Q1: What's Matsumoto real big on right now?
--------------------------------------------------------------
I haven't a clue about that!
This is how it's going to be!?
No Reaction Pie Hell! (Subbed by DTFS)
Matsumoto’s Sports Challenge #4 - Baseball (Subbed by DTR Subs)
Special edition, Matsumoto Hitoshi finally does "100 Questions."
No Laughing Airport (Subbed by GakiFiles)
Downtown have been together for 30 years this year
Matsumoto’s Sports Challenge #7 - Swimming (Subbed by DTR Subs)
and Gaki no Tsukai has been airing for nearly 23 years now.
So, how much do the 4 know about Matsumoto?
Zombie Matsumoto's Perfect Timing - GnT #1003 (2010.05.02)
Turning Turning Face Ichihenge - GnT #359 (1997.03.02)
They will know learn the truth about Matsumoto.
Q1: What's Matsumoto real big on right now?
--------------------------------------------------------------
I think it's...
I really have no idea...
Oh right...
Reveal answers.
That's not something to be "big on."
--------------------------------------------------------------
-----------------------------------------------------------------------
Housei: Muscles    Hamada: Mobile Games
Endo: Muscle Training    Tanaka: Muscle Training
Well, it might not be a "big on thing..."
He really knows his stuff about iPhones.
Does he?
Yeah, he does mess around with it a lot...
Yeah, he does.
I get it, games...
Time for the answer.
He's always playing on it
I think seriously...
Matsumoto is in a different location and cannot hear what the 4 are saying
I'm counting on you...
What are you real big on right now?
Big on??
Just answer seriously.
This is tough for a first question.
Big on...?
Come on, Matsumoto-san.
Please say "muscle training."
Come on, answer seriously.
I wonder...
Well I guess,
muscle training.
A: Muscle Training
-----------------------
Alright!
You wrote "muscles."
No, of course I get the point.
Fantastic!
He's big on that? He's big on muscle training?
Yep, that's right
He was a bit embarrassed to say that though, wasn't he...
Yeah he was, it's probably because he does it so much.
I think it's (bleeped)...
Damn, he sleeps loads!
I know...
(bleeped)
He's answering so seriously...
He really is.
What...!?
What does Matsumoto have a complex about?
Q2: What does Matsumoto have a complex about?
------------------------------------------------------------------------
Eh, what?
A complex?
I haven't got a clue.
Ah, I've got it!
Eh, a complex?
I have no idea...
Like "what he's self conscious" about?
Reveal answers.
Ah, yeah, yeah.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------
-----------------------------------------------
Housei: Protuding Jaw    Hamada: Chin Jutting Out
Endo: Chin    Tanaka: Thin Legs
Like when they draw those
mangas of him, he always has that.
Yeah, they do exaggerate it.
That's true, his chin is always exaggerated.
Tanaka, what's yours?
Thin legs.
Thin legs...
You really do look at him, huh?
Well, yeah, that's what I thought.
I kind of get it.
You really are observant, Tanaka...
Yeah, it's just my image.
Time for the answer
I get you.
Matsumoto, what do you have a complex about?
I have loads, I really do but, what is it...
Tell us the most obvious one.
Yeah.
Right.
My educational background?
Well, I mean yeah that's probably it.
You're kidding!
A: Educational Background
-------------------
Surely it's your chin.
So that's how he's going to answer, huh...
Surely, your chin first...
He thought his educational background was...
What's with that?
His educational background?
He's never said that before...
What is Matsumoto's favourite type of pasta?
Q5: What is Matsumoto's favourite type of pasta?
----------------------------------------------------------------------------
I have no idea.
I have no idea, Yama-chan has such a huge advantage here.
Right, Housei-san.
You go out and eat with him a lot, right?
God, this is annoying...
I have no idea in the slightest.
A pasta he loves?
I think Hamada-san, you might also
know what pasta he might like the most...
No, I'm not sure about that.
I do.
Because, we used to eat and stuff together.
I get you...
We haven't done anything together for decades...
Well, I guess.
Like we've not eaten together at all.
Like, you wouldn't eat pasta either now...
Well, I guess...
These kinds of things, I have no idea.
Reveal answers.
That's right.
------------------------------------------------------------
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Housei: Squid Ink    Hamada: Carbonara
Endo: Meat Sauce    Tanaka: Aglio, Olio e Peperoncino
There was a time he would only eat this.
* Squid Ink Pasta
Really?
Time for the answer.
Matsumoto, what's your favourite type of pasta?
What would you do if it was some fancy-ass pasta...?
Yeah, like something we've never eaten or something.
Yeah, something we've never heard of.
This is really embarassing but probably meat sauce...
A: Meat Sauce
-------------------------------------
Alright!!
Huh?
I've never seen him eat that!
What's up with that?
Squid ink is a bit off...
Meat Sauce!?
Aren't you a bit embarrassed?
Saying like, "Oh, definitely squid ink."
You were so confident you were right...
Matsumoto, if you could only bring 1 item
to a deserted island, what would it be?
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------
Q8: Matsumoto, if you could only bring
1 item to a deserted island, what would it be?
What...?
What do we do?
I don't know how he'll approach this question.
We do talk about this kind of thing
when we drink together as well...
Yeah, right?
We do...
Yama-chan has an advantage...
Yeah, he does...
He probably does tell you these kinds of things...
There are things he says like, "Probably this..."
I see.
What was it again though...?
It goes through one ear
and leaves through the other...
You don't listen to him at all then...
Yeah, it seems like that.
Reveal answers.
----------------------------------------------------
----------------------------------------
Housei: Dumbbell    Hamada: Pillow
Endo: Book    Tanaka: Milk
I don't know...
I don't know either...
A pillow...?
I thought maybe he was one of those people
who can't sleep unless he has his own pillow...
That's it.
Time for the answer.
Geez...
It's a tough one, huh?
You know...
This is...
Is it OK if I
answer this question brutally honestly?
What the hell?
Like honestly honest...
What is he on about?
I wouldn't take anything...
That's...
The question is, "What would you take...?"
I mean, it's not the time to be thinking that...
No, no...
He's way too serious, what's up with this guy?
A: He would take nothing
------------------------------------------------------
What the hell?
He's so serious!
He's way too serious.
The question is "What would you take?"
He could have said something.
So, our answers are pointless to start with.
The question was "What would you take?"
Right.
He's taking everything into
consideration when answering...
Yeah, that's true.
He's really serious.
That's true.
Question 10.
At what time has Matsumoto been going to sleep recently?
------------------------------------------------------------------------
Q10. At what time has Matsumoto been going to sleep recently?
As if I would know...
No idea...
I have no idea...
Yama-chan has such a huge advantage.
He really does, he's with him
like the whole day sometimes.
He has such a huge advantage.
You guys must talk about it loads.
Back in the day, he would sleep real late.
Yeah, yeah.
But now, he's got a kid and all...
Yeah.
But I think around this time probably...
Reveal answers.
-------------------------------------------
--------------------------------------
Housei: 11pm    Hamada: 2am
Endo: 1am    Tanaka: 2am
It should be about this, right?
It should be.
Yeah, about this.
Yeah, I think 1 am.
No way, he has
dinner at like 7pm now.
Eh!?
But even so, there's no way it can be 11pm...
I honestly think he gets sleepy around this time.
Time for the answer.
Yeah.
Seriously?
About 2am right...?
This is like...
The time I sleep is the same.
Back in the day, I used to stay up a lot and stuff.
Now, usually...
1am.
2am.
about 2am, I think
OK!
Alright!
I think 2am would be right.
A: 2am
----------------------------
Yep!
Right, got it!
That's way too early.
Do you think?
11pm...
Yeah, that's a bit too early.
I'm usually fast sleep about this time.
I sleep at like 10pm.
At 10pm??
Yeah, 8 hours no matter what,
I have to sch-eep...
Sorry?
What did he say?
So close to saying it correctly...
At what time does Matsumoto wake up?
Oh come on...
Well he sleeps at 2am right?
-----------------------------------------------------------------
Q11: At what time does Matsumoto wake up?
Sleeps at 2am...
But you've got to think about
the fact he has a kid.
Yeah, but even so,
she's not at kindergarden yet...
I want to get this one right.
I get you.
It's got to be around this.
Reveal answers.
It has to be.
It's got to be, right?
Either one of these two.
9 or 10 o'clock.
Time for the answer.
Umm, this actually...
changes from time to time
I see.
But recently...
9am!
10am!
10am I guess.
A: 10am
-----------------------------
Alright!
He sleeps so much!
Get in!
He does, 8 full hours.
True.
Who's Matsumoto's favourite young comedian(s)?
Eh, hold on, this is really difficult...
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------
Q14: Which young comedian(s) does Matsumoto think is funny of late?
Wow yeah, this is real tough, huh?
Yama-chan, hasn't he told you
these kinds of things recently?
Yeah, he has...
Even if I know, I don't know if he still does...
I know right?
He did tell me this,
he told me recently in fact...
Ah, really?
Damn, you have a huge advantage.
Oh man, who did he say it was?
I can't remember at all...
Oh damn, what should I do?
I have no idea...
Who was it??
Screw it, I will put this down.
Reveal answers.
------------------------------------------------------------
Housei: Peace duo    Hamada: Sugi-chan
Endo: 2700 duo    Tanaka: Jaru Jaru duo
Do you think?
Peace is...
Nobukobu and Peace, he said..
I guess the point is
what he means by "funny."
He said like, "They're good, right?"
I see...
Oh, like that?
Matsumoto, who's your favourite young comedian(s)?
This is a such a tough one...
Well...
Wow, he's going to answer so quickly?
Like jokes wise...
It has to be Jaru Jaru.
Oh shit, it was them!
That's who he said, he said them!
I got it!
He likes Jaru Jaru's jokes?
When it comes to "stand up,"
I'm not so sure...
He did say it,
he said it last week...
Ah, really?
A: Jaru Jaru
You got it.
-------
Yeah!
So jokes wise, Jaru Jaru.
I got it.
It was at the Osaka's "All That's"...
A yearly MBS special
featuring many comedians
from rookies to veterans.
All That's Competition
Umm...
Right, right.
At the end of the year?
Yeah, he was coincidentally watching it lately...
------
I see.
Hosei-san, you had a huge advantage.
So you knew this...
I did...
What's wrong with you...?
Oh damn, I'm so bad...
That one just now was a bit, yeah...
You should get more of these correct.
I was so wrong...
Sugi-Chan
Sugi-Chan.
Hamada-san thought it was him...
Like totally...
You were totally wrong.
Hamada-san just likes him...
What's Matsumoto's favourite breast cup size?
Q16: What's Matsumoto's favourite breast cup size?
----------------------------------------------------------------------------
I don't imagine him to be like,
"It has to be this size"...
That's true.
We have had these kind of conversations...
Probably about this...
Yeah...
We have talked about this a fair bit.
Reveal answers.
-----------------------------------
-------------------------------
Housei: C    Hamada: C
Endo: D    Tanaka: B
Yama-chan thinks C...
You know, I wanted to write D.
Q16: What's Matsumoto's favourite breast cup size?
----------------------------------------------------------------------------
I don't think he's that bothered about...
I see.
Yeah.
Time for the answer.
Ah, geez, well...
I don't feel like anything
even if they had like F size...
Yeah, we know that much...
Well, I think it's got to be...
D.
I think.
It's D?
--------------------------
A: D Cup
So he does like it...
Yeah, that's pretty big!
Yeah, he likes pretty big ones...
Who does Matsumoto respect the most?
---------------------------------------------------------------------
Q17: Who does Matsumoto respect the most?
Hosei-san, you must know this...
Ah, this is so tough!
I've definitely heard this loads of times.
Really?
Ah, thank goodness!
Ah, I got it!!
Eh, seriously, Ho-san?
Reveal answers.
---------------------------------------------------------------
--------------------------------------------------------------------
Housei: Van Gogh    Hamada: Older brother
Endo: Pablo Picasso    Tanaka: Albert Einstein
Ahh, Gogh?
Yeah, he went to see his work
and did a program on it...
That's true.
Time for the answer.
Err, well...
It's tough to say just one person...
Well yeah obviously, but let's just
hurry up and answer the question...
Think about it seriously...
Ino Tadataka.
* First person to make an accurate map of Japan
A: Ino Tadataka
----------------------------
Person to make the first map of Japan?
Right, right.
Why...?
Why Ino Tadataka?
Let's ask him why...
Yeah, please do.
Please tell us, why do you
respect Ino Tadataka the most?
Well I don't understand anyone
who doesn't respect Ino Tadataka the most...
No, that kind of reply won't do.
I mean if you didn't
That kind of reply will not do...
we wouldn't have car sat navs...
I mean, his stoicism.
No, no, no...
The way he worked so hard...
The courage is amazing...
Isn't it Van Gogh...?
That's amazing, you were wrong.
What is Matsumoto's favourite movie?
Q20: What is Matsumoto's favourite movie?
---------------------------------------------------------------------------
I really don't know...
I haven't a clue about that...
He probably watches loads...
Yeah, when it comes to movies.
Woah, Ho-san's fast.
I've totally got this one!
Does he talk a lot about this?
Like literally so much his mouth gets sour of it.
Geez, I've absolutely no idea...
You're right, I have a huge advantage.
Yeah, you do.
But I haven't got any right, Endo!
I HAVEN'T GOT ANY RIGHT, HAVE I ENDO!?
Reveal answers.
I don't know...
------------------------------------------------------------------------
----------------------------------------------------------
Housei: Paper Moon    Hamada: I Am 5 Years Old
Endo: Alien 2    Tanaka: The Godfather
I'm pretty sure he said he loved
this film back in middle school...
I Am 5 Years Old?
Q20: What is Matsumoto's favourite movie?
---------------------------------------------------------------------------
We watched this film at school
I Am 5 Years Old? Is there a film like that even?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure...
Is the main character 5 years old?
Yeah he's by himself and does something for ages
A 5 year-old child sets out on an adventure
from Kochi to his father's workplace in Osaka.
I Am 5 Years Old (1970)
----------------------------------------
---------------------------------------------------------------
I remember him saying that was his favourite film loads of times...
Are you sure you're not mistaking it for "My First Outing"?
* Hajimete no Otsukai
Ah, Paper Moon.
I Am 5 Years Old...?
"Paper Moon," this has to be it!
Time for the answer
Matsumoto, what is your favourite movie?
Definitely.
Please say, "I Am 5 Years Old."
Oh man,
I was literally just thinking about this.
Yeah, I've got this!
Yeah, yeah!
I thought, "Damn, I would hate it
if that question came up..."
Well, I'm sure there are loads he loves.
Just give me a second...
Just choose one that just comes to you...
There are loads I love...
Yeah, I think it has to be Paper Moon.
Alright!!
------------------------------------------
A: Paper Moon
You had such an advantage...
He did.
Finally, like I got something right, thank god.
You finally got one.
Yeah, I know.
How much money did Matsumoto bring today?
Q21: How much money did Matsumoto bring today?
----------------------------------------------------------------------------
Geez, no clue...
I haven't got a clue
Does he not have a wallet or something?
Last time, at some program he was like, "I don't
have my wallet," and took money out of his pocket...
Oh, you're right...
He doesn't...? Like nothing to put his card in even?
Yeah.
Reveal answers.
-------------------------------------------------------------
-----------------------------------------------------------
Housei: 50,000 yen    Hamada: 60,000 yen
Endo: 100,000 yen    Tanaka: 100,000 yen
I think 50 or 60 thousand yen...
Yeah, I think 100,000 yen is a bit...
Bit much?
Time for the answer.
I just counted lately coincidentally.
Err, well...
about 180,000 yen...
Damn.
something thousand yen...
Damn, he carries a lot of money around with him
He really does.
Is that OK?
A: 180,000 yen
------------------------
Like 180 thousand...
I feel so pathetic...
being so wrong
He does have a lot of money on him though...
Who does Matsumoto think is most lame among the other 4?
Q24: Who does Matsumoto think is most lame among the other 4?
----------------------------------------------------------------------------
"Lame"?
But I think this has to be...
I don't know...
I'm going to go for this...
Yeah, in actual fact...
Reveal answers.
Eh, seriously!?
---------------------------------------------------------
---------------------------------------------------------------
Housei: Yamasaki    Hamada: Hamada
Endo: Housei-san    Tanaka: Yamasaki-san
Like last week, he said.
Oh man, just say me...
He said last week.
Yamasaki.
Yes!!! I mean I shouldn't be happy about it...
A: Yamasaki Hosei
---------------------------
Come on, you can't be serious...
I wonder if he really thinks that.
But why you?
Let's ask him.
What is it about Yamasaki you find "lame"?
Hmm, well...
What is it?
There's a lot of things.
He got married and as he aged,
just became an ordinary old man...
Well, umm...
He's just got that "so normal" feeling...
I see.
Apparently Hosei-san.
Uwah, scary.
He's so pissed... Look at that face.
Uwah, woah...
What does Matsumoto lack?
After this
I don't want to be "lame."
How many pull-ups can Matsumoto do?
Q27: How many pull-ups can Matsumoto do?
----------------------------------------------------------------------------
I don't know...
Whaa...
I think he can do that, but will he be able to right there...?
Reveal answers.
--------------------------------------
-----------------------------------
Housei: 20    Hamada: 12
Endo: 21    Tanaka: 13
I think he will go 10 and just want to stop there...
Potentially.
I think he will go 20...
Time for the answer.
Matsumoto is in a seperate room so cannot hear them
He looks like he's good at pull ups...
I see...
Oh, like this?
Ready, start...
His head has to go above, right?
Go...
It's tough.
Why can I see the white in his eye...?
I know...
He really is.
He looks so stupid.
He's doing well though.
He's starting to struggle though.
Look at his eyes...
His head isn't rising above the bar.
You better not count that one...
The right answer was 25.
A: 25
--------------------
Amazing, huh?
Sure is impressive.
Can't help that.
Question 30.
What does Matsumoto have a lack of?
Q30: What does Matsumoto have a lack of?
--------------------------------------------------------------------
Doesn't he say something like this...?
I think it's this.
I think.
Reveal answers.
--------------------------------------------------
------------------------------------------------------
Housei: Stature    Hamada: Money
Endo: Knowledge    Tanaka: Nothing
I think even at this stage...
Really...?
I think he might say that.
I see.
Umm...
Probably that...
The ability to, like...
moderate...
Such a serious answer...
That's so deep...
I just can't do it.
A: The ability to moderate
-------------------------------
The ability to moderate...!?
That was so deep
Would you really answer
that seriously here?
Damn, that was so serious.
I mean, come on...
The ability to moderate?
I would never be able to write that down...
You've got to be kidding me.
I see...
Q32: What are
Matsumoto's
good points?
Probably the fact I don't have any bad points.
A: He has
no bad points
------------------------------------------------------------------------------
--------------------------------------------
Housei: Finishes what they start    Hamada: Kindness
Endo: Impulsive    Tanaka: ??
I mean...
I would never get that...
Geez...
Q35:
What's Matsumoto's favourite fruit?
Peach.
A: Peach
You're kidding me!
The 4 didn't know anything about Matsumoto...
----------------------------------------------
------------------------------------------
Housei: Mango    Hamada: Pear
Endo: Orange    Tanaka:Pear
I've never seen him
eat a peach ever...
No way...
Not once...?
Q37: What is
Matsumoto's habit?
One after another, Matsumoto answers the question.
Like shaking my feet like this, both of them...
Apparently I do it in my sleep too.
---------------------------------------------------------------------------
---------------------------------------------------------------
Housei: Touching his nose    Hamada: Picking nose
Endo: ??    Tanaka: Always touching chest
A: Shaking his foot
I had no idea.
I have no image of him doing that.
Q39: A show Matsumoto
must watch every week?
I mean right now, it would be...
Burari Tochu Gesha no Tabi.
* Travel show visiting places near public transport lines (1992 - Present)
A: Burari Tochu
Gesha no Tabi
I guessed it would be a travel show...
Q42: What's the most hurtful thing
a woman said to Matsumoto?
Like, "Oh I'm not interested in comedy...
A: "I've no interest in comedy"
God, when you make this person say normal things, he ain't funny at all!
He's too serious.
Even though he's funny when he makes jokes...
Q45. What is
Matsumoto's favourite street?
Who truly understands Matsumoto out of the 4?
-----------------------------------------------------------------
-----------------------------
Housei, Hamada, Endo: 246 (Aoyama Street)
Tanaka: Old Yamate
A: Old
Yamate Street
And then the person to get the punishment will be...
What color attracts Matsumoto most for women's underwear?
----------------------------------------------------------------------------
Q47: What color attracts Matsumoto most for women's underwear?
I think...
I'm going for this.
-----------------------------------
--------------------------------
Housei, Hamada: White
Endo:, Tanaka: Black
Split, black or white...
Yama-chan, you're confident?
Really?
I am.
He loves it.
Really?
Yeah.
Time for the answer.
Well this has to be definitely...
not black or red.
Damn it, we're out.
Yeah...
But like weirdly...
I like beige.
A: Beige
--------------------------
Excuse me...
Come on man...
It wasn't white...
Beige??
---------------------------------
What part of his daughter
does Matsumoto think is cutest?
After this
I mean, beige, really...?
Beige...?
Gaki no Tsukai News!
We are currently taking orders for the Downtown dolls,
this is your final chance!
Hamda figure deadline to order is tomorrow!
Please check the website for more details.
What does Matsumoto think is cutest about his daughter?
Q48: What does Matsumoto think is cutest about his daughter?
----------------------------------------------------------------------------
I mean...
I haven't a clue.
Reveal answers.
------------------------------------------------------------------
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Housei: Eyes    Hamada: Smile    Endo: Smile
Tanaka: Welcoming him at the door when he comes home
Oh, Tanaka it might be...
I thought so.
It could be if he's going to be specific...
----------------------------------------------------------------------------
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, like the whole "missing him."
Well, let's see
Time for the answer.
What do you think is cutest about your daughter?
Just answer normally.
I know, right?
You ask very difficult questions...
Just answer normally...
I don't think this is OK,
I should probably change this...
It's not good for a kid to do this but she does this...
And I know I should tell her off.
Yes, you should.
But it makes me laugh...
Seriously?
A: When she blows a raspberry
I have never seen it...
I guess even Yama-chan hadn't seen it before...
What did Matsumoto say to propose to his wife?
Next week!
Next week, the 2nd part of 100 questions about Matsumoto.
What an idiot!
Amazing!!
Alright!!
And something unbelievable happens...
And who will be bottom?
I see...
Finally, the conclusion!
Your complex?
My educational background?
You're kidding!