Tonight's Gaki No Tsukai - Kushikatsu Tanaka Part 2!
Rules: Each member will eat 2 skewers from a menu of 34
The aim is to eat from one store in each of Tokyo's 23 wards
There's a prize of 10-man yen (100,000) if they can finish
But the challenge ends if one person gives up
Whoever gives up will have to pay for everything eaten until then
Last time I had this it was so thick
You guys didn't do that on purpose right?
We didn't tell them "Make his Yamaimo extra large"
The Yamaimo and Spring Onion are large menu items, however
Until now, the 5 have cleared 7 stores!
16 stores left
Will they be able to finish?!
subbed by /u/senor_wristband
TN: There are some spoilers in here for previous episodes in the Food Marathon Series
The 8th store, in Koto ward, Monzen-Nakacho
The Kushikatsu please
Starting from here
Pork, Yamaimo, Eggplant, Beef, Clam, Tsukune
And here is Ginko Nuts, Quail, Potato, and Nitamago
Tanaka-san has quite the volume there
Quite a large potato
Certainly is big
Yeah
But if anything, Hamada-san's ...
Hamada-san's Yamaimo ...
It's making him suspicious
Attention
This is really good, the Tsukune and sauce
Cause it's spicy
It's more delicious
You just want to look at it and laugh
He wanted to get a good look
This was getting in the way
He went out of his way to move this
He wanted to see your Yamaimo burden
It's pretty heavy huh
Yamaimo
The other 4 merrily finish their Kushikatsu
Only Hamada and his Yamaimo are left
The Yamaimo is not diminishing ...
The Yamaimo, I also
You're scared of it
I'm pretty scared of getting it
Yamaimo is scary huh
He did it!
Fantastic
Brilliant, so
Next, deciding the 9th menu
So, Hamada-san,
What happened?
Man, this is the worst ...
Spring Onion!
Spring Onion again!
Still it depends on how big it is right?
This store's Spring Onion is the fucking worst!
No that's not true
It's delicious right?
It's so delicious he thinks it's the worst
Hamada's second item is Ginko Nut
Matsumoto and Endo have an easy to eat menu
Spring Onion
Ginko Nut
Shrimp
Hanpen
Eggplant
Pork
Let's see Hosei-san's
The colour of his face changed
Yamaimo
Yamaimo has appeared-
BANANA!
Eating that is gonna be something
A nasty combination has appeared
Yeah
This is harsh
This is dangerous
So Tanaka-san,
Shishito!
You're lucky
Shishito is actually so good
He got a good one
What else?
Oyster!
Again!
For real?
Are you kidding me
I'm so full damn it
Since he can't eat Oyster, Tanaka draws two cards and gets Monaka and Lotus Root
Until now, Tanaka has eaten more skewers than anyone
The Oyster alternate rule has created a difficult situation for him
Next, the 9th store
In Edagawa ward, Nishikasai location
Look at Tanaka-san's
Oh boy
That's what I'm saying; Just eat the Oyster!
The Shishito is pretty big
Damn it
Let's go, let's go
Let's go
Shishito
It's too hot, I told you
It's hot?
Look at that
The size of this Banana is really getting to me...
The Banana's Boss Battle levels are off the charts
Seriously?
Was Banana always like this?
Of course
All I eat is friggin Spring Onion
I mean it's not ALL you eat...
Hamada with the Spring Onion, Hosei with his Banana and Yamaimo
Their eating speed just won't increase
I think at this point, we need a penalty for being slow
That's quite an idea ...
You're done the Onion, Hamada-san?
Such a bad mood
And Hosei finishes his Yamaimo too
Only the BIG SIZE Banana is left
He's not having fun at all...
Yes
He has no joy on his face
Even though he's having a snack
He's tormented
Do you need to make that face
Wouldn't that would make it hard to eat, conversely
I haven't eaten the Banana once yet
He's done!
Brilliant!
Immediately after eating, deciding the 10th menu
So Hosei-san,
Beni Shoga (Pickled Ginger)
He got it
That's lucky
Oh he got it!
I did it!!!!
Ginger! Ginger
That's lucky
C'mon one more, one more.  One more!
There it is!
Yamaimo
Yamaimo again
How much Yamaimo are you gonna eat?
How much Yamaimo are you gonna eat?!
Garlic
Ham Cutlet
Pork
Potato
Tomato
Beni Shoga
Yamaimo
Pork Shiso
Namafu Dengaku
Quail
This time, Hosei is on his 4th Yamaimo skewer
We need a few changes to the rules
Yeah exactly
Maybe, you pick one skewer?
You get to choose one skewer
What kind of face is that?
The other one is from the cards
Ah, so we get to choose then?
Yeah one of them
One of them
What should we do after this one?
We'll go with Fujiwara's theory at the next one
We'll go with that
Let's try that
Coming up with a new rule, they arrive at the 10th store
In Katsushika ward, Shin Koiwa store
That's a good one
Beni Shoga
That's a great one
Beni Shoga is refreshing
This is the one I wanted most
I can go for the Beni Shoga
Beni Shoga is good, it's kind of refreshing
So you're gonna eat the Beni Shoga before the Yamaimo?
What else would I do?
What else would you do?
You could alternate bites
No way, I gotta eat the good one first
The other 4 also seem to be reaching their stomach's limits
But they manage to finish
Oh you finished, Hamada-san, Tanaka-san, Endo-san
It was fast
You're still slow
It's hard to eat?
Damn, how is it?
How is your 4th Yamaimo of the day?
That's gotta be 10 cm at least
The inside of your mouth looks rotten
It's like he's grating yam in there
It's like he's grating yam, in his mouth
He's done!
Fabulous
So next we're going to Adachi ward, the Adachi location,
Should we change the rules?
Can we?
What we said earlier?
Starting now, a new rule takes effect
Everyone will pick one item, and the other will be decided by card like before
Matsumoto-san,
C'mon Yamaimo
He got Spring Onion
He got it!
Spring Onion, finally
Finally
Everyone got it
This is really something
Hosei-san's draw?
Please
Banana!
Great!
Banana is great
Well done!
You've got a curse for Banana and Yamaimo
Clam
Mochi
Beni Shoga
Spring Onion
Namafu Dengaku
Banana
Shishito
Clam
Shrimp
Cheese
Hosei is on his 3rd Banana of the day
I've just been eaten Yamaimo and Banana the whole time
That's the impression we have
Yeah
How are your stomachs?
They're fucking full of course
You're all 10/10?
It's not about the 10/10
I'm tired
Tired?
Yeah that's true
I'm tired from the excitement too
But it's not like we can't eat
Eating a bit, they head to the next store
The repetition causes tiredness, and fullness to build up
With heavy steps, they head into the Ayase Station store, in Adachi ward
Hosei-san, you're starting with the Banana?
Oh really
Conversely?
Building pain resistance
Building resistance
My, my,
Your body
My body is building resistance
Tanaka-san, you're quick
The shrimp is done
Hamada-san is done?
The Mochi is a lot, right?
Yeah Mochi is, yeah
This bastard is really something
It sure is
Yeah
Oh, you're already done
That was fast
Matsumoto-san, maybe this time the Onion will go together?
There's the heat to deal with too
Yeah the heat too
The weight too
Pain in the ass
Yup
Eat the BIG SIZE Spring Onion for the first time, he manages to finish
Deciding again using a new rule
Out of 3 cards, pick 2 you want to eat
Starting from Matsumoto-san?
Yeah OK
Cheese
OKAYYYYY!
If the next one is good too, I'm taking that and this
That's a good one
Pollock Roe
Cheese
Isn't this enough?
This is pretty good
Tsukune
They're all winners
Cheese
Pollock Roe
Tsukune
All winners
What will you choose?
That is...
Remove one then
I guess, Tsukune is...
I'll pass on that
OK, so Matsumoto-san has Pollock Roe and Cheese
Let's move on
Hosei-san,
I'm so lucky
Banana?
First is Banana?
Well, there's still 2 more left
Put Banana aside,
Ah, Onion!
No way!
You're amazing
and Oyster!
And now Oyster!
That's it then,
That's all you can eat!
MIRACLE
Cause you can't have that one
This is a miracle!
You're getting rid of that one
You have to get rid of that one
Yeah this is impossible for me
There's no helping it
Onion...
Onion, and ...
Damn, that is tough
So many Bananas
Somehow, now Hosei is on his way to the 4th Banana of the day
Tomato
Liver Katsu
Cheese
Pollock Roe
Banana
Onion
Mochi
Hanpen
Shrimp
Lotus Root
I'm in danger
(chuckles)
Seriously, like,
A little dangerous
It's Bad
I guess so, after all
No way you're OK with Oyster now?
I'm going to do my best
If I work hard now,
God will reward me for next time
give up
Hosei has given up twice 2 previous episodes
But this time, persevering with words of hope,
he wants his prayer to rescue him
Your face looks insane
But I'm gonna work hard
Seriously, I'm gonna do my best
Just this bit
It makes you mad, right?
If I can past this point, I think there's something waiting for me
What?
God, at the next place, will rew-
Ahh great, you go do that then
The 12th store, in Kita Ward, Oji location
This place is so different
Lemme see
Ahh, a quiet voice is nice
Are you kidding me with this?
Look how different the sizes are!
That one, that's no good
I can't eat this!
Banana
Onion
I'm comparing them, look!
Wiener
Let's not compare using a wiener, it'll get tiring
But I guess I can't say anything
There's also a time limit to consider,
Last time,
Yes, at Ikinari Steak
Hamada-san
That's what got him
Heavy!
Is it quite heavy?
It's so friggin heavy
This is like a club
Cheese
Oh yeah, compared to that onion this goes right in
Ah, the cheese?
Indeed, the cheese
Hamada-san, you're finished one?
Liver Cutlet            Tomato
Tanaka-san too?
This atmosphere, it's like he's being made to reflect on his mistakes,
Onion
Has the taste changed?
Uwahh ... So heavy
That's how big the onion is?
Amazing
How's that Onion, Hosei-san?
If we were sharing a table I'd hate that
this kind of person ahead of me
"Why did you order it then?"
Ah, Matsumoto-san is finished
Everyone except Hosei-san
Still has two left
You guys are so fast
Onion has decreased a lot
Decreased for the first time in a while?
That's great, Hosei-san
OH he went for it
OK, the Onion is finished
Onion, finished
Only Banana left
Kushikatsu Tanaka, store number 12
Only Hosei's Banana is left
He gave up
I thought he was gonna finish it
Amazing
He stopped though
But still,
Yup,
It's the last bites
This is the time to persevere
And he bit it
He bit it
It felt like you were about to swallow the whole thing
He still just bit it
He did it!
Amazing
For the next menu, Fujiwara will draw 10 cards at random
The winner of Janken will then choose two cards
Only good stuff
Please
Yeah seriously
Tsukune
OK, OK,
Ginko Nuts
That's not bad
Not bad, not bad
Good
Monaka
Shrimp!
Not bad
This kind of stuff
Asparagus!
Fujiwara's on a roll
Yeah
Cookies and Cream
Ah! Finally!
Finally!
The first time?
Next one?
Shitake
Not bad at all
Not bad
Lotus Root
Lotus Root?
That's good
Here I go
Please be good
Pork
A good one
Good, isn't it?
Beni Shoga
This is the only one we're unsure of,
Yup
Yup, these cards are not bad
I can go for these
You can definitely finish these
Yup
Yup we can
Tsukune
Ginko Nut
Monaka
Shrimp
Shitake
Asparagus
Cookies and Cream
Lotus Root
Pork
Beni Shoga
They get to play Janken and choose from here
But, that man will not play fair...
First is rock, janken hoi
Hosei changes to Scissors at the last second
This definitely not allowed
Right?
Wait a second please
Why, what's wrong with you?
I'm so full,
Hold on, us 4 will go now
What do you mean?
Just now,
Will be taken as a loss
It's just not right
Here, everyone but Hosei will choose their favourite stuff before him
Tsukne
Asparagus
Shitake
Pork
Monaka
Cookies and Cream
Ginko Nuts
Beni Shoga
Shrimp
Lotus Root
Leftover for Hosei, is the Monaka and the Cookies & Cream
You have 2 sweet ones
Are you kidding me?!
But this is definitely good
Cause it's a sweet
The size is not that large
Yeah exactly
So then they head to the 13th store,
Itabashi Ward, Tobu Nerima location
Excuse me,
Tsukune, Pork, Cookies and Cream, Shitake, Lotus Root, and Asparagus
The Cookie and Cream...
Huge!
The thickness, again...
Oh yeah
You got an exceptional one
So heavy
The Monaka was a failure too
This guy is dangerous
This is dangerous
Should I start with the Cookie and Cream?
Why did you "Uwahh"?
How is that?
It's completely different than what I expected
It's all gooey
It's melted?
And Matsumoto-san too, with that,
Making no progress
Making no progress, yes
There's also the question of which to eat first
It's pretty hot huh
Ohhhh I see
Pork
That's quite something, isn't it Hosei-san?
I can smell the sweetness
It has a sweet smell
It's a nice aroma
Endo is eating it like it's nothing
Yes I still can
You won the Janken after all
He dropped it
This is dangerous
Get out the stopwatch
Should we get the stopwatch?
No way,
Should, should we time this?
The Cookie & Cream got him
Alright, I gotta persevere
If you don't finish that Shitake,
Yup
That's right
Start the timer, after I'm done?
How many minutes?
3 minutes
Let's go with 3 minutes?
OK, 3 minutes
After you finish the Shitake,
3 minutes
He can eat it right now too right?
Yeah this is his chance-time
3 minutes-
He smelled the Monaka and just put it down
We thought Matsumoto-san might end up in trouble
The Shitake is taking a long time here
What the hell is this?
Maybe don't say "What the hell is this?"
"What the hell is this?" while holding Monaka
If, if you get past here,
Yeah
You might get good cards,
Exactly
The future right?
You might have a good future
Here I go,
OK, after he's done eating,
Your 3 minutes begin
First the Monaka
This is quite a lot
Pretty, Hamada-san did you find this one pretty tough?
Yeah this one was tough
Yeah it was a big portion
He is not moving an inch
Hosei-san?
He's like a statue
Maybe switch to the Cookie & Cream?
Yeah you're right
Switch to that one
It's good to change up the flavours
He removed the skewer
He thinks doing this will help him
What, what the hell are you doing?
That-
Don't just push it forward
He just wanted to do that
Just wanted to squish it
Time left,
Time left is,
now 1 minute
Here he goes
Are you gonna eat it?
Just one is good
Just gobble them up quickly
He's not eating it after all
What are you trying to do
What are you squishing them for?
Could we see a miracle occur?
He's setting himself up for a cool move
This preparation...
Yama-chan, Yama-chan it takes time to swallow it too,
Almost out of time
He's going for it
He barely took a bite
You're taking bites at this point?
Time's up!
That's game over
The bill this time,
Hosei-san will have to pay 22,739 yen ($204 USD)
I guess so
Unfortunately, the challenge was not completed
You absolutely can't eat?
Impossible,
In fact, it was impossible at the last store too
Amazing you made it here then
Amazing I made it, honestly