7th time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arrahende
CHIKI CHIKI
"Are their hearts connected?" No Smartphone Meetup!
Of course, this is a "No Smartphones" challenge,
I don't think that explains this though,
In the dressing room, you forgot your phone
Well, it is a "no smartphones" thing we're doing
But forgetting this in the dressing room is a different thing
Why do you have it?
"I shall return it" - I said
Oh is that it
For the 7th time, we test to see if the member's hearts are connected!
The Rule: Using the hint card given to them, if they all end up in the same location, the challenge ends
Everyone, look here please,
The results from previous episodes,
The person who meets up first the most;
Alright!
Yama-chan, and then Matsumoto-san
1st - Yamasaki
2nd - Matsumoto
3rd - Matsumoto
4th - Endo
5th - Tanaka
Our level is totally different
Tanaka is 0
Zero?!
Tanaka, in this series, and the outfit coordination stuff
He really does suck
That's true
These two end up meeting first a lot
That's true! Somehow, these two
The person who met up last
The guy who gets left alone till the end
It's Tanaka right?
Of course
Yup, Tanaka
Cocorico really suck
That's true, Endo sucks too
Hamada is pretty terrible too
Yeah, I guess him too
Hold on, I was last once
You have to consider this, and try harder
Yes, I want to meet quickly
Announcing the first location,
A place with lots of pigeons
It doesn't matter if there are pigeons there right now or not
Just a place that you would associate with pigeons
Let's meet immediately!
Yes!
Pigeons?!
There's nothing that comes to mind
Subbed by senor_wristband
The Hint: A place with a lot of pigeons
They start at NTV in Shiodome
Hamada is usally unsure during these challenges
Woah, this is the first time I've been in this type of cab
It's so spacious
TN: This is the Toyota JPN Taxi
I have two ideas,
Either Yoyogi or Komazawa Park,
Somewhere like that I think
Komazawa Park is pretty far from here
Oh, yeah you're right
Those stairs in Komazawa, you can imagine the flapping right?
I do have that image
You do have that image right? The "WASASA"
Komazawa Park, can we head there?
The only thing is, everyone else might not remember,
I went there for the parking lot thing too
I go to Komazawa a lot I think
I really don't want them to say "Damn, you love that place!"
You do have this image of getting on the expressway and heading straight to Komazawa
Woah, even you're picking on me now
That wasn't my intention!
Everyone thinks that then
Where is Matsumoto heading to?
You know, Hamada ...
Tweet ... That episode where you had to end up on Twitter
In Ueno, Hamada had to dance, and he was sweating like crazy
Weren't there pigeons there? Am I wrong?
I guess Ueno Park ...
Should we go there?
Can we? I think it's Ueno, Ueno Park
That episode last time, that took a lot of time to make
I hate these episodes where you don't know when they're gonna end
Last time we had this problem too,
Can we stop these episodes with undecided endings?
Like seriously
Seriously, make some 20 year olds do that
While these two are making the exact same complaints,
Hosei wants to maintain his ranking in this series
Oh hell yeah, it's this type of taxi
I have two ideas,
Komawa Park, was it called Komawa Park?
Komadai Park?
There's a  Komazawa Park...
Oh, Komozawa Park
Komawaza Park, and,
and, there, Meji Shrine
I bet someone will be at [!@!$!@]
Thank you
If he chose Komazawa Park, he'll meet with Hamada
What will happen?!
Who do you think will be there?
You know Matsumoto-san and I, it's like we've met everyday for over the last 10 years
So it's like the same,
The way you think?
The way we think
My wife told me,
"You and Matsumoto have the same eyes"
"Whenever you squint they look the same"
She said I have the same eyes when I do that
"You really know him"
Endo, who is almost as bad as Tanaka when it comes to being left behind ...
I think, it's gotta be a park
I think everyone else will take that approach
Ueno Park, Komazawa, oh yeah Yoyogi ...
They might go to one of those
I think I've got it this time
I think 3 or 4 of us will be there
If Endo is thinking along the same lines, he has a chance of meeting Matsumoto or Hamada,
And if Hosei goes to Komazawa, 3 people will be together
Meanwhile, the worst player Tanaka chooses his location
I do have one place in mind that I associate with pigeons, however,
What location, by the way?
It's, uh, Hachiko. In Shibuya
I do have this image of pigeons gathering around Hachiko's statue
And in the past, I've recorded an episode trying to catch the pigeons there, with Ryo-san from London Boots
Back when Ryo-san was young, I think,
I remember it was near Hachiko in Shibuya
But it was 20 years ago, so I don't remember exactly
Let's head that way for now
Tanaka relies on a 20 year old memory, and decides on Hachiko
I think Endo would really remember that shoot,
He might think "Oh yeah! In front of Hachiko!"
I think he'll have that reaction
Actually yeah, I'm not changing the destination, but,
In front of Hachiko ... I think I went there before
But I think those were crows
Wait ...
The birds we caught with Ryo ...
Were they crows?
Hmm?
I think Tanaka doesn't understand this
Tanaka...
Cocorico will also graduate from Gaki in half a year,
So they're probably thinking about the memories they made on here, I bet
This is the first I've heard of this
Oh, I guess it was supposed to be a secret,
Cocorico and Hamada will both leave this show
We've arrived, however ...
Incidentally there isn't a single pigeon here. Well, that's ...
Matsumoto is the first to arrive, at Ueno park. He is concerned about the presence of pigeons
Like I said, today is really hot!
There's no pigeons here!
Not a single one. Damn it's hot!
It's so hot today
Next, Hamada arrives at Komazawa Park
The pigeons ...
There's usually pigeons there,
And if you scare them off they all fly away,
The pigeon count could not be verified here either
Is there really not a single one?
There aren't any flying around either
Yeah seriously
On a future day, the staff did confirm the presence of pigeons,
It was exactly like Hamada described
Tanaka reaches Hachiko in Shibuya
See! Look there!
Look! That wall
Look at the wall!
They're on the walls
See? I told you
There's so many! Did you see them?
You saw them right?
Look!
See
This is a pigeon's feather
Right?
This is definitely a pigeon's
I can't imagine that everyone won't come here
Time Up! They confirm their locations with a phone call
Where did Hosei and Endo end up?
Hello. Where?
Endo, where are you? Endo?
I, am at Yoyogi Park
Yoyogi Park? Eh?
Yoyogi Park
Yoyogi Park?
Yoyogi Park huh?
You're at Yoyogi Endo?!
Ah, this is Hosei here. I'm at Meji Shrine
Where?
Meji Shrine!
Ahhh, I'm right next door
Damn, so close
Tanaka, where's Tanaka?
Tanaka here, I'm at Hachiko in Shibuya
There's no pigeons there!
Are you an idiot?
There's only people there!!
Tanaka, those were crows last time
Tanaka?
It's insane! There's an insanse amount of pigeons here
There's an insane amount?
There's an insane amount
Right now?
Right now, for real there's like 10 here
So there are pigeons
Huh, so there are pigeons
Mastsumoto-san, where are you?
You guys gotta think about this,
When you think of pigeons, it's gotta be Ueno Park!
Ueno Park after all!
So there must be a lot of pigeons there
They're standing on my head
There's 6 of them on my head
There's 6 on your head?
6, on your head?
Yeah. It's so annoying!
Where is Hamada-san?
I'm at Komazawa Park
You really love Komazawa Park!
What's so special about Komazawa Park?
Alright, alright then. Let's meet at the next one.
Yes indeed!
Indeed!
Well, I guess Tanaka, and I were alright,
Komazawa Park deserves a Batsu Game
Spread your ashes at Komazawa if you love it so much
The next theme;
Theater
This is another really broad query,
This is actually really tricky
There's a lot of choices
Within reach of the members, there are around 200 theatres
How they interpret "Theater" is vital!
A theatre huh...
I think we've got this one
Really?
Lumine (The Yoshimoto)
There's no answer but Lumine
Gaki no Tsukai -> Yoshimoto Creative Agency -> Lumine. That's it.
Hosei has total confidence in his choice of Lumine
Since we're all comedians,
So they might interpret this to mean Lumine, which makes sense,
And that hall where the young comedians work is a theatre right?
Mugendai Hall
And that's a theatre too right?
But with this "Theatre" prompt, would you really go to Mugendai Hall?
That's what I think
In that sense, Mugendai Hall is a theatre too right?
But Tanaka said he's at Hachiko,
If he's considering the distances, he might go there
But that's not really how this works right?
There's two theatres that just popped up in my mind,
Thinking about the distance, it's Shibuya's Mugendai Hall
Cause Shibuya is right there,
Plus ... Endo was in that Tom & Jerry play,
at Bunkamura Orchard Hall
They did it in Shibuya?
Yes, in Shibuya
Plus, another one I just thought of,
That place,
In Toyosu, the IHI 360 degree theater
That theater, the place with the revolving seats
But, the theater in Toyosu ... It's a really nice theater,
And I want to go there,
But the other 4, they don't know where it is I bet
Probably, I think
They don't know about it
I think,
That place, Teikoku,
Teikoku Theater right?
But you know ...
A place like Teikoku, those guys ...
Would they know it?
Those ... idiots, right?
If you ask me to name a theater,
Somewhere like Teikoku,
Or Honda
There's a good chance they'll all go to Lumine and ask "What is your occupation?"
But that's not a "THEATER"!
He's struggled to think of a location, but just where will he go?
It's gotta be Honda Theatre
In Shimokitazawa?
My dentist's office is close by too
Let's go to Honda
Have you ever gone to Honda Theater to watch a performance?
Ah, I haven't
You haven't?
I haven't
So this is really just about the dentist?
Shut up man
Wait, what was that place in Shimokitazawa?
Honda Theatre
Honda Theatre ...
Well, performing in Honda Theater is certainly a dream for comedians,
Kabukiza is also a theatre?
Hmm, Kabukiza?
Hamada-san goes to watch Kabuki
I wish they'd refuse him, the Kabuki theatre
Officially
I wish they would tell him to leave
I'm still drawn to Endo's Bunkamura Hall
Bunkamura...
Endo will definitely be there
Because ...
They were doing that play until recently
They were doing it until recently,
And he still has Osaka performances left to do
For Tom & Jerry
So "Tom&Jerry" is still in Endo's head
It's the stage for his performance,
It's like, just how many times has Endo been to Bunkamura
Like seriously,
I'll be shocked if he isn't there actually
DownTown have a chance of meeting. Just Endo's location remains.
Endo ... does he go watch performances in theaters?
Well he did do that play,
Wait, where did Endo do Tom & Jerry?
In Shibuya
"Orchard Hall" - Well, that's a theatre too
But I bet Endo really wants to avoid that place,
The things he's been through.
He must have some trauma that makes him avoid that place
Did you go watch Tom & Jerry?
Yes
How was it?
It was a lot of fun
Endo is the cat, so he's supposed to run around chasing the mouse,
He told me "I'm 48 man, this is too physically demanding!"
But he was totally running around on stage,
I thought "What? But you said you couldn't do it!"
I think Endo thinks ... He thinks it was a fun performance to be a part of
A theater ...
There's one place, as soon as I saw that hint I thought of,
[!@!@#!] in [*(@$!1#@!]
Will Endo be able to meet someone?
The most confident, Hosei arrives at Lumine the Yoshimoto
"We've got live comedy" - Amazing right?
That's a comedian there
Morning!
Ah! Keep up the good work!
What do they call you?
Somato
Somato? Oh I see
(It says Somato on his shirt)
You're a solo comedian?
Yes
Oh, this is a chance for you! Do something!
I have a one-shot gag
Yeah do it! One shot gag
Here I go,
Okay! Alright!
I apologise, I got very nervous
Well you would right, all of a sudden
Meanwhile, Hamada arrives at Honda Theater
So is someone here, or coming here?
Wait, I think there's someone there
No way, really? Really?
Wait I think there's someone there
Thank you!
This is the place right?!
It's gotta be here
Thank god!
You know, I didn't think you would be here. Maybe Tanaka or someone else,
It's gotta be here right?
When you say "theater", it's gotta be Honda Theater
Thank goodness!!
You know for us, when we were young,
We were allowed to do a live show here,
Ah, is that so?
Then Tanaka should've come here
I thought he'd be here
If there's nobody here, I'm gonna be taken back, actually,
There's no way
Hmm, they're still not here?
Endo will come here, seriously,
There's no other place I can think of. Endo should be here for sure!
But, time ran out!
No way? For Real?
Where did Matsumoto end up?
Tanaka where are you right now?
I, Tanaka, am at Bunkamura Orchard Hall in Shibuya
Why the hell?! Why would go there?!
You did Tom & Jerry here!
Oh yeah, that's Endo's thing
Yes, yes!
But I thought Endo's trauma would prevent him from going there
Trauma? He has trauma from Tom & Jerry?
I had fun doing that show
Yama-chan where are you?
Everyone, what agency do you work for?
There it is
Well, spritually I'm a free agent
Spritually a free agent?
I'm thinking of signing up for an agent
It's gotta be Lumine!
There it is
Hamada, where are you?
Hamada-san and Endo have met up
Our location is, in Shimokitazawa, Honda Theater
Ahhh you went there?
Oh that place was an option!
Why Honda Theater?
Where are you Matsumoto-san ?
You guys ... What nationality are you?
Nationality?
Japan, I'm Japanese
If you think of a theatre, it's gotta be Kabukiza
In Ginza?!
It's gotta be here, this presence
It's gotta be a "Theater" though
You don't need to have "Theater" in the name,
A place where customers come to be entertained, that's what a theater is!
It's gotta be Lumine
There's no point complaining if you're alone,
THERE'S NO POINT COMPLAINING IF YOU'RE ALONE!
A very angry Hamada-san
Next Week - No Smartsphone Meetup Part 2
The Hint: A Gyoza no Osho location
I got this one, I got this for sure. Let's go
If we consider everyone's thoughts, they'll probably think of that place
Isn't this really hard? There's so many stores in the city
I think it has to be [!@$!@]. I can't really think of any other place.
Who will be the last to meet?
Thank you for watching!
If you'd like to support my fansubbing, please consider donating to my Ko-fi:
https://ko-fi.com/buresurettosan