Tonight's Gaki no Tsukai is the "Eating Marathon Challenge"
"Bikkuri Donkey" finale
If you want to eat it, just go for it, that's what we worked so hard for since we were 18, right?
The rules are, for the 32 items on the main dish and steak menu
The team will draw from a lottery to determine which dish to eat and finish
Starting from the Hachioji restaurant, which is a bit far away from downtown
They will finish the mean at each chain
And work towards the goal of dominating all 21 locations in Tokyo
In addition, the new rule of only 4 people will be eating each time
And the one other person can rest up has been added
And then...
This person   -Eh? Matsumoto-san?
What's going on?   -This seriously pisses me off
Up until the sixth chain, the resting man has been between Matsumoto and Endo
Tonight is another 30 minutes full of hamburgers
Will they be able to dominate all 21 locations in Tokyo?
Subbed by Appieopie, more episodes at
www.laughseejapan.com/user/18797
4 hours after the challenge started
The members are now at their sixth chain in Mizuho
The restaurant is here, look at these stairs
Eh? This is it?   -No, the restaurant is up here
Welcome   -Welcome
The seats are tatami mats for this chain   -Eh?
Seiza while eating hamburger?
*Seiza is the Japanese term for the standard formal traditional way of sitting in Japan.
For his third round of rest, Endo ordered ice oolong tea
Sorry to keep you waiting   -Thank you
This is the 300g grated radish burger
Wow, it looks so good
Grated radish burger (300g) 1,175 yen
The burger is divided into 4 equal parts, and they're working together to finish it
Comparing to the 3 members who ate continuously
Matsumoto has been resting for 3 rounds, and should be able to finish it with ease
How does it taste?   -Really good
It's just the same
You mean it's the same good taste right?   -Yeah
It tastes good as always
Hmm...
Matsumoto-san you seem to be...
You're giving off a "heave-ho feel"   -No problem, I'm fine
I just feel like the fork is a bit heavy
Is that because of the salad you ate previously?
Yeah surprisingly enough, salad actually make you feel full
But I'm fine, I'll digest it before we arrive the next chain
Glad that there's no rice
Yeah, it will be tough if there's rice
Okay, let's draw the dish for the next Higashimurayama chain
I'll choose this one
Pineapple curry burger dish
Oh, I see, the pineapple curry burger dish
Yamazaki is responsible for pineapple   -Yeah, you're right
Who will be the resting man, this is the main point...
Let's see who gets to rest up   -I'm not looking at it
The resting man has been between Matsumoto and Endo so far
Who will be the resting man this time?
Please show it to us   -One, two, three...here it is
Ah, Housei-san   -So it's Housei-san
The tide is turning   -Yeah, the tide is finally turning
And you don't need to eat the pineapple   -Yeah
You can't rest when there's pineapple right?
Based on article 42
What kind of law is that?
When you're responsible for the food...
Side menu   -I want oolong tea
Hot, hot, hot   -Hot oolong tea
Oh yes, oh yes, let's go
So now the tide is turning
Tanaka and I have been eating non-stop   -Yeah, we never get to rest
This is awful
This is seriously awful
We just finished the sixth chain, are you guys feeling full now?
I'm completely fine
Yeah, I'm completely fine
What about you, Hamada-san?
Hamada-san kept looking into the distance
That's why he's so quite   -He's staring out the window all the time
And he don't even want to answer our question
The seventh restaurant is Higashimuryama chain
Cocorico should eat the pineapple...   -We'll eat the pineapple
Yeah, we'll eat the pineapple together
This is delicious
It's curry, so maybe it's a bit easier to swallow   -Yeah, it is
Tastes so good
You're eating so fast
The resting man Housei is enjoying his coffee
What are you doing, dude
I'm having a pleasant time here
It's really good to just take a rest
No way, this is just...
Well, you're about to finish it
You guys are quite fast
Okay, so we finished it
The dish for the next chain is...
The dish for the 8th chain will be egg burger steak
Please, Yama-chan...   -Please let the tide turn here
I want to rest again too though
What is this guy talking about
Tanaka-san
I'm the only one who is continuing...
Well, there is nothing that we can do about this
Yeah, I know, but still...
My countdown has started...
Endo show us the "Hamburger" gag seriously
-The Hamburger gag right?
-Yes, think of yourself as the Hamburger-shisho
Hamburger
You're so annoying
The person beside said I'm annoying in a low voice
So I'm afraid that I won't be able to continue
Isn't that too long?
Is it too long?   -Yes, it's a bit too long
You're saying it like the length of "Ametalk"
Make it shorter, please
Hamburger
You're so annoying
Sorry, but the person beside me is in a really bad mood now, so...
The one just now was too short   -Really?
Yeah, it's too short, it sounds weird
Really? It sounds weird?
Hamburger
Ouch
He even hit me in the face now...
Tanaka should do this for you then
Hamburger...
Seriously?
What is that fade out?   -Are you kidding me?
The members arrive at the 8th restaurant, Kodaira Onuma chain
Is it over here?
Yes, it's over here
All of it?   -Yes, the whole building
I'll eat it first
Sure
The resting man, Tanaka, ordered strawberry soft
This is the 300g egg hamburger steak   -Thank you very much
I'll pour the sauce too
Egg hamburger steak (300g) 1,175 yen
I don't want to eat it, just by looking at it
I'm so freaking full already!!
There's still a long way to go   -He must be joking
Do you know how many more chains are yet to be finished?
Even now, the dish has been divided into 4 equal parts
Hamada-san, please eat it while it's still warm...
I really want to get through this
Treat this as the most important stage
I'm so full...
Okay, then we don't need you to eat the egg
No, I just can't eat anything anymore
What?   -Can't eat anything...
What happened?
Did you become a baby again?
But you don't need to eat the egg, someone else will eat it for you
Yeah, just eat the rest   -No, I can't...
Should we draw the next resting man first?
No, that's not the problem
I'm just suffering
Did Hamada make this sound?
That's because other customers are entering
That's not Hamada's sound...   -Ah, he's digging in
Wow, that's amazing   -Incredible
You ate nothing
You ate nothing   -You're just pretending
That's my trick
When I try to trick people!!
Three of the members have finished their quota
Only Hamada is left
I'll try to eat it bit by bit   -Yes, please
That's a good tactic
Slowly but surely
Oh, he did it
Well done my boy
He did it
This is just impossible!!
If you can eat that bit, you should be able to finish it
Yeah, he seems to be able to finish it
Just eat it bit by bit
Good, he did it   -Nice
He's trying hard
Look at his thumb
He's putting his thumb in his fist
Just two more bites...
Well done   -Good pace
This is exactly what happened to me before
You can feel the wave   -Oh, I see
You can feel the wave inside you
You need to feel it and ride on the low waves
Or else it will go "bang!"
You need to ride on this low wave, or else it will go "bang!"
So you need to feel and catch the low waves
We don't want that "bang!"
He's feeling the wave now   -Yeah, he is
Now!
He did it   -He grasped the chance
He finished the hamburger
Yes, only the egg is left   -So he finished it right?
He's digging in   -He did it!
Egg hamburger steak completed!
So for the next chain...
The dish for the 9th chain will be grated radish and perilla hamburger dish
And the resting man will be...
Better let Hamada, who went way beyond his limit, to rest this round
Go for it   -This is crucial
I have faith in you
The next resting man will be...   -I hope it's you too
Will be this person   -Come on
Tanaka-san again
You drew yourself?
He must feel lonely too
This is the first consecutive draw today
This really hurts mentally
Up till the 8th chain, Hamada who hasn't get to rest at all, along with Housei, are both reaching their limits
Fujiwara therefore prepared something for them
I've brought a rescue item for you guys
What is it?
Since herbal tea is a powerful digestive aid, would you like to have some, Hamada-san?
Hey, why do I need to go so far as to finish the challenge?
This man said something philosophical
Can I have some herbal tea, please?   -Of course
Say something, dude!!
Now at the 9th chain
Will Hamada be able to get through this?
-How do you feel for resting consecutively?
-Well, I feel really easy
I bet you do   -Yes
Aiming to finish it together, the dish is again divided into 4 equal parts
Just eat it slowly but surely
Wow, he's digging in
That's amazing
He finished it in the blink of an eye
That's so cool   -Incredible
That's really cool   -Awesome
He finished it before those strange waves arrive   -Oh, I see
I just have to pour it into my mouth
And with water
Endo met his quota
Housei-san finished it too   -Yes
Herbal tea helped a lot
Matsumoto met his quota
Hamada made an incredible effort, and the 9th chain is completed too
The menu for the 10th chain is cheese packet dish with rice
I'm sure that Hamada will be the one resting this time
Just pick the right one, okay?   -I bet it will be Hamada
Yeah, of course it should be me resting this time
Hamada-san please   -Looking good
Come on! Come on!
One, two, three!
It's Hamada-san
This is amazing   -This prolonged his life
Yeah, you're right   -This really prolonged his life
What about the side dish? You want some Spaghetti with Meat sauce?
And let him perform the dig in again
Hamada finally get to rest during the 10th chain
The dream to complete all 21 chains is coming true
The next one will be the 10th chain, how full is your stomach now?
I'm like 8 over 10 now
About 8 over 10?   -Yes
What if you didn't eat that green salad?
Well, I don't regret eating that green salad at all
It was such a good memory
And we were attracted to each other
But if you didn't meet it...   -Then you won't be 8 over 10
But it is the encounter with it...
that helped me go through all this...
Your voice is so quiet
Well, I'll speak louder when I come up with something more interesting
Even Matsumoto-san have those moments!?
The challenge that started from the Hachiouji chain,
has finally reached Tokyo 23 wards during the 10th chain
Hamada ordered coke for his first round of resting
-This tastes a bit strange
-Yeah, the sauce is completely different
Something is inside   -It's cheese
Looks good
How does it taste?   -Delicious
-Tanaka has been resting for two rounds
-Yeah, so it still tastes good for me
Ahhh...
And this has a different taste too
What's wrong with you?
Seriously...I feel exhausted just to sit here
You can't see the salad?
At this time of day...under this light...I just can't see it
-You don't know where the salad is?
-I don't even know what I'm eating
You're just eating whatever there is?   -Yes
We've reached the 10th chain in 6 and a half hours
We can do this, just a couple more hours
Only 11 more chains to go
Everyone finished it, so let's get Hamada to draw the dish for the next chain
Better draw a hamburger-only dish
Okay, what is it?
Oyako burger...   -Eh?
You must be joking   -It's Oyako burger dish with cheese
It's awful to have Oyako burger at this point of time
Why Oyako burger now...   -Oh no, we're in danger
And the resting man who everyone wants to be is...
Please!
Eh? Tanaka again?
Thank you very much
This is awful   -Why Tanaka...
The challenge has started for 6 and a half hours
Yet, there's still a long way from dominating all 21 chains
Come on, dude, even their CEO won't be able to dominate all 21 chains in one day
Arriving the 11th chain, this is their fourth Oyako dish*
*Oyako literally translates to parent and child, which refers to a dish with one bigger and one smaller burger
Here it is   -You mean this thing as well?
Yes, including this thing, everything
Since when did you start to keep on asking these things?
Seriously, he kept on asking me these things
Such a pleasure to have Oolong tea at this point in time
Tastes good
I bet so
This is Oyako burger dish with cheese
Amazing   -That's a big portion!
Yeah, was it this big before?
Isn't the child surpassing it's parent?
No way, it has always been like this
It's like old people providing care for old people
Let's start eating
Hamburger and rice is divided into 4 equal parts
Aiming to finish everything together
I can't see it
Can I wear my glasses? I really can't see it
Sorry, I'm really sorry for this
But I can't see it   -What's wrong with you?
What are you doing?   -Makes me feel stressed
Maybe it's better to not see it though...
What happened to Big Daddy?
He's sitting without moving a muscle
Like a daddy feeding his 3 children
Thank you daddy
Wow, Housei-san is digging in   -Housei-san is amazing
House meets his quota
Awesome   -He finished it
Endo-san met his quota as well
Only Downtown is left
Are you waiting for your helper?
Yeah, he can't pick up the food
Someone is looking a bit strange
I'll work hard
He's wearing his hat like Julie (Kenji Sawada)
Ah, Matsumoto-san is about to finish
Go for it
Awesome! He finished it
Three of them have met their quota
Endo finished the salad as well
Only Hamada is left
However, time has passed, and he's not eating it at all
Finally, the give up countdown has started
Three minutes, ready, set, start!
But remember he has that "dig in" thing right?   -Yeah
We call it the "Hamada Dig"
Wow, he's digging in
That's amazing   -He finished it
He's just trying to build up tension
To dig in and finish it in the last few seconds
Like "here I go!!"
One minute has passed
He's still not going for it yet
Not yet, it's not time yet
Time has passed, and he doesn't seem like eating it at all
-He's drinking a lot of water though
-2 minutes has passed, 1 more minute left
No problem, I'm sure that he will do it for us
Here he goes, he's getting prepared   -Yeah, he is
The countdown starts now, 30 more seconds
Last 30 seconds   -It's time for him to shine
Cameraman, take a close-up shot please
Make sure my partner looks good on camera!!
Finish!!
No way, no way, this is impossible
For a split second, I thought he is going to do it
Yeah, I thought so too, for a split second
When he murmured like "umm"
Hamada will be paying the bill for everyone
By the way...
Who will the next resting man if we drew the cards?
So Tanaka-san will be drawing the card
One, two, three!
Tanaka?!
You're resting too much, dude
This is ridiculous
What the heck, dude?
He'll probably eat dinner at home as usual man
You're still hungry right?
I can still eat a lot!