First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende:
Bamiyan Marathon - 100,000 Yen Prize
Tokyo 23 Ward Challenge!
A series Hamada-san really hates
He seems to be in a bad mood already
That's not true, why would I hate this
Well last time, it ended because of Hamada-san
In the end it's always his fault
I ended it just in time didn't I?
I knew you guys couldn't eat any more
So I ended there on purpose
No no
If you guys clear all the stores, you can win the prize,
So this time to help us- What was your name again?
It's Fujiwara! You're kidding right?
What was your duo's name again?
LISCENCE! We're starting with that?
I'm amazed you're letting me take part
Established in 1984,
With 333 stores across the country,
Bamiyan, the Chinese Family Restaurant
The rule; From a menu of 59, they choose 2 dishes at random to finish at each store
Starting with Himonya,  they aim to clear 51 stores accross Tokyo's 23 wards
So with 2 dishes per store, after 30 stores,
You'll have eaten every dish here
Yeah that's true
But since this is about clearing all the stores,
The rest is for part 2 next week
That makes no sense!!
So in the first part, we try everything?
Then there's a part 2
That makes no sense. If we eat everything it should end.
All you do is complain
Let's be more optimistic
If they can clear 51 stores, there's a prize of 100,000yen
However, if anyone gives up the challenge ends. The one who gives up has to pay for everything the group ate.
First off, the choose the menu for Store #1 Himonya
Red Mabo Tofu with homemade Chili Oil & Sichuan Pepper
The second dish,
And the second dish,
Oh yeah, I like this, it's a good one I think
"Bamiyan Ramen" - The signature
Eat this one please, since it's their specialty
They use cards to decide who takes a break
Who will be the first person to rest?
Oh, Tanaka-san!
You take a lot of breaks don't you?
You take a looot of breaks
Thank you very much!
Tanaka gets to choose something from the side menu
I'll have....oolong tea.
There it is.
A very Tanaka thing to say.
There it is, Tanaka's Oolong tea
The first store, Himonya
They head straight to their table
I have an improvement I want to suggest,
Why do we gotta wear overalls?
You're making us a lot right? It makes me really want a shit sometimes,
But overalls, and pooping,
It's like oil and water right?
Yeah that's not good. They should give you jerseys
At least the top and bottom are separate
That other thing is good too,
The thing babies wear
A romper?
Would you really want to wear a romper at this age?
I'll wear a diaper with it
And the bib as well
I think our objective has changed
Here's the bamiyan ramen.
This is our Mabo Tofu with homemade chili oil
Sprinkle this on as you'd like
How many people is this for?
This is for 5 people
This is gonna be so easy
The soup, noodles, char siu, and even the toppings are all carefully selected for this most popular dish, Bamiyan Ramen
And notable for it's aroma, red Mabo Tofu with homemade Chili Oil & Sichuan Pepper
It's gonna be more dishes like this
Bon appetit!
How does it taste Matsumoto-san?
It's simply delicious
-Tasty!
Easy to slurp down
This Mabo Tofu is the real thing
I can dig into this
Very fast indeed
Piece of cake
Yeah for the first one, we're usually fine
This is seriously tasty!
I think we can do this
Is it easy? You guys ate that up
We licked it up
Could you decide the menu please?
Are you done Hamada-san?
Listen to him
I thought after eating this,
It's liggable
Licka-miyan
It's not Ba-miyan
It ain't Bamiyan
It's Licka-miyan
"Crunchy and juicy - specialty Oroshi Ponzu Fried Chicken"
Please discuss amongst yourselves
And the second one?
Oh!
4 of them? (Shoronpo)  (also called Xiaolongbao)
Which means, we might have 2 people rest
What do you mean? 2 of us can take a break?
(Crosstalk - Agreeing)
And so, it was decided 2 people will rest
The two people resting, ready steady boom
Endo-san and Hamada-san
You're disappointed?
I did want to eat
Hamada and Endo's choices are fried chicken with potatoes and oolong tea.
After paying, they head to the second store at Shimokitazawa South
I wonder what Bamiyan means
It's definitely a Chinese word
Could we a get a hint
We're all doing a quiz you see
We're having a blast you see
Is there a meaning? Really?
There is, there is a meaning
It's probably Chinese right?
It's not
The store is named after something that exists
Ah, I got it
I got it, since I got it I'll stop now
You get it so much you don't even need to hear the answer right?
Shall I tease it out?
"Alrighty"
TN: Not sure I got this part right
Don't say "alrighty" asshole
You're trying so hard to be an Idol. What the hell is "Alrighty"
So disguting
It's the name of a peach right?
There's some peach they call Bamiyan in China right?
Completely incorrect
You should get a batsu game.
Wait, why should I get a batsu game?!
Mandatory
It's the name of an old city on the Silk Road
TN: Bamiyan, capital of Bamiyan province in Afghanistan
TN: Also the name of a great Afghan restaurant in the GTA
They wanted to "Bring Chinese food to new worlds", and so named it Bamiyan
Their car approaches Shimokitazawa
The railroad crossing is gone
The Suzunari is gone!
It's there
Thank goodness, I have a lot of memories there
Surely you don't have memories at Suzunari
Ah, it's Nitta-san's house
(DownTown's former manager)
Yeah him andOkamoto used to live there
TN: Okamoto is the CEO of Yoshimoto Creative Agency
President Okamoto used to live there.
Oh wow, I didn't know that
President Okamoto
Right?
President Okamoto used to live there
We got it. There right?
We set off fireworks in his house
On Gaki?
On Gaki
Oh yeah we did!
We got away with that kind of stuff back then huh?
I don't know if we got away with that
We set fireworks off inside his house
After a 20 minute drive, they arrive at Shimokitazawa South
At this store they will dig into;
Shoronpo, which overflows with meat juices from the pork inside,
And the crunchy & juicy speciality Oroshi Ponzu fried chicken,
This is Tanaka-san's first dish right?
Mmmm...it's delicious!
Very satisfying
The second store is cleared in a flash!
It's not Bamiyan
It's Licka-miyan
So for the 3rd store,
"Tanmen with Plenty of Vegetables"
Oh, very nice
A rice dish would be nice
And then,
Tofu Bon Bon Chicken Salad
I think this is a good balance
Yes, yes the balance is good
Hosei gets to rest, and decided on Anindofu (Apricot Kernel Tofu dessert)
The head for the 3rd store, in Setagaya's Kamisoshigaya district
Endo, sing us a song for Bamiyan
A song for Bamiyan?
There isn't one that exists right?
I think there's one inside you Endo
I think from time to time you can surprise us
I hope I don't disappoint,
Here I go...
Bamiyan starts with B
Totally delicious-
Isn't this too long?
You're doing it like that?
You're making up a new song?
This guy wants to sing it the whole time we're in the store
Do something they'd use in a commercial
Ah I see like a jingle, Ah I see that's what you mean
So like a CM?
Here it is.
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba.......miyan!
I hate that
I just hate it for some reason
Bamiyan Food Marathon - The aim to clear store #3, Kamisoshigaya
Endo, around this area...
Oh yeah, Hosei-san visted me often around Umegaoka
I was soon after I came to Tokyo, right?
Your girlfriend lived with you too right?
Yes yes, when I came to Tokyo, the very first time
The girl you brought to Gaki?
Oh not her
Earlier than her
At least bring her instead then
You should've told me she was your girlfriend
I thought she was some girl you picked up
It was so awkward
"I'll show her DownTown"
Yeah, "I'll show her DownTown"
And Endo and I hadn't really met before that
That's true, it was basically our first time meeting
And you brought a girl you just picked up
To our "Free Talk" segment
What would you think?
Just "Ohhhh I see"
Cause I don't know if she's gonna become your wife or something
I can't really say anything
I can just go "Ahhh Ok"
Yeah I'll never forget I did that
Yeah that's something you never forget
I'll remember that forever
I can't undo that
And that woman didn't even laugh that much
And Tanaka being Tanaka, the first time he met Matsumoto-san
In the Taxi outside Tokyo Station
He got in and sat next to the driver, and didn't speak a single word
I thought he was an exchange student at first
The taxi driver's exchange student
"Maybe he's learning the streets"
I think I introduced him - "This is my junior Tanaka"
And Tanaka didn't react at all
He didn't react at all
I remember being very nervous, incredibly nervous I remember
Did we get food too?
A Chinese place, around Shibuya if I recall
I don't remember at all
When you say Chinese, it's gotta be Bamiyan, right Endo?
Ba-ba-ba-baaaaaa.....miyan!
The 3rds store, Setagaya's Kamisoshigaya location
At this store; The Tanmen with Plenty of Vegetables,
And notable for its dressing,
the Tofu Bon Bon Chicken Salad
Fujiwara and Tanaka are in charge of distributing the dish
Tanaka's good at this. He muight be really good at this.
It's 300g right?
Wow that's kind of amazing!
Tanaka is amazing!
Ah, well that's still pretty good
Here's the last one.
Tanaka's amazing
The one that's a little too heavy is Hamada's
It felt good though didn't it?
Let's eat.
This is good.
The salad is great too
I'm going along at a good pace
The distribution was good
No problems at all
So you would say it's easy?
Still finding it easy
The menu for the 4th store?
Hoikoro.
(Note: Also known as "twice-cooked pork.")
Another non-rice dish?
That's true
"Miso Ramen with Plenty of Vegetables"
We need a rice dish soon
Hosei gets to rest again.
He decided on Honey Fried Bread with Vanilla Ice Cream
#4, the Suginami Miyamae store
This is the Miso Ramen with Plenty of Vegetables
And the Hoikoro
Tanaka is once again in charge of the distribution
300, around 300g
Oh I didn't see inside
Tanaka is unwavering
Amazing!
Are you for real?!
This one is a bit on the heavy side
It was about 10g over
This is good hoikorou.\
This is our 3rd noodle dish
Noodles? Oh yeah it is
We've eaten 1 bowl of ramen by now
Ah yes, you might well have
Finished! Time for the next menu please
Another noodle dish
Gomoku
It's just noodles
This will be the 4th ramen dish of the day
And the other dish was Meat Shumai
And the one who rests?
The third in a row!
You guys fixed this again
I'm hungry too you know
With an unexpected 3rd rest, Hosei decides on Shine Muscat
With the 4th store, 8/59 of the dishes are cleared
How are your stomachs doing? Next is the 5th store
I think it's just right
It feels just right, like I finished eating dinner
How about you Hamada-san?
I'd say the same, I'm ready to pay the bill
Ready to pay the bill?
There's still,
46 stores left ... desu
TN: Inomoto was slow with the "desu"; omitting it would be rude when addressing a senior
That's no way to talk to us
I'm saying there's still a lot left
Bamiyan Marathon - #5 is Kamishakuji
At this store they'll enjoy;
Gomoku noodles, with lots of toppings and vegetables
And notable for it's juiciness, Meat Shumai
This is tasty.
Way good.
These noodles are firmer than the ones we've had today
They finish quickly, and choose the menu for the 6th store
They want a rice dish now, however...
Grilled Albacore Tuna with Hoisin (?) sauce
What is that?
That's true, a rice dish would be nice
Ajitama Ramen!
More noodles!
Give us Chahan at least once
I won't eat Chahan in the second half
This Albacore Tuna is pretty good I hear
And Fujiwara will be the one to rest
So just Matsumoto-san left
No breaks
I've been eating noodles this whole time
Fujiwara decided on a Taiwanese dessert, Lemon Ogyichi
They head for the 6th store
I'm kind of starting to get pissed off
Too many noodles?
Noodles....noodles...noodles...it's just...
Some of us don't like noodles
You know I never picked noodles out of the box
Actually you drew the Bamiyan Ramen
He did do that
We can just edit that!
"I'm amazing, we can eat ramen now!"
We always decide on editing after our talk
Bamiyan Marthon - The 6th store is the Nerima-kasugacho location
My body feels a little heavy
It feels like I'm forcing this
At this store, the 5th ramen dish of the day
Ajitama Ramen, and,
Grilled Albacore Tuna with Hoisin sauce
The taste has changed a bit?
So little!
That's so little
What are you doing?
It just so happens the distribution turned out like this
But you were spot on before
It's difficult to do it with Ajitama
Let's give Tanaka some noodles
Alright, I'll take some noodles
You have too few noodles, everyone give him a bit
Here you go
Wait a minute, hold on...
This is enough for 2 people!
No no that's a fair amount
The Ajitama is pretty good
Everyone seems to be slurping it up
Except Tanaka-san
Alright, leave this to me
Yes, please
Can we decide who rests first?
If I get to rest, well that'll use up my luck
Let these bastards eat noodles
It's Fujiwara.
Again?
Well this can happen, like with Hosei-san
Fujiwara gets it in a row
We should just take turns resting
Next week...
Bamiyan Marathon Finale
Matsumoto still didn't get to rest
And the challenge;
4 dishes at once!
How will their luck turn out?