[clips from the full episode, subbed & online @shionnotsukai.wordpress.com]
Translation by Shion
Typeset & QC by RIDDELL
[clips from the full episode, subbed & online @shionnotsukai.wordpress.com]
And now, here's a clip from last week's episode, "Let's Play With Nostalgic Arcade Games"
They played old arcade games from when they were young
And today, we present to you some rare footage from it we couldn't add to the full episode
You're good at this, Tanaka?
Yep, I played it so much
Oh, this one
I never did this before
You didn't?
Jump Up - strike the button with your hand - you win if the weight stops right at the assigned colored square
They chose a game Tanaka claims to be good at: Jump Up
Strike the button with your hand; if the weight stops on the assigned color square, you win
You go Tanaka
Should I go first?
Yeah, so we can see how it's done
I guess the hard part is to balance
Yes, 'cause it can stop anywhere
I see
You got the highest one
The highest one is the easiest
Right
You don't need to regulate your power
You just go full strength
Really?
Can't it go above it?
No, it can't
To get the highest one, you just have to deal a strong blow
Are you kidding me?
Right, it's the top
It just has to go up
Alright, I'm going to put all my strength in this
Didn't go well, dude
It went too high
See? It went over
Oh shit, is that what happens when you get the highest?
What's that tone of voice?
They're all your seniors here
I was talking to Endo!
But if he got that high, I think anyone can make it
That's right
I didn't remember this
I wanna try again
Tanaka failed because he didn't remember well, but Hosei and Endo too didn't make it
And then...
The central one looks good enough
I wanna strike a bit harder
Please do
So half-assed...
He's an half-assed scaredy cat
I thought that would be stronger
He's so afraid
You got the lowest one
It's the lowest
You should try to do it like Hamada did just now
That's right
What the hell?!
It was my first time touching it!
It's the same for us
They wanted to complete it and did a second round... but it didn't go well at all
That was such a weak-ass strike
So close!
That was probably the closest one
You got that again
Lowest one again
Oh, nice
Go!
Unbelievable
That was really something
Just go for it, we gotta show what we got
Practice first
It's close to what you did before
Stronger, stronger, practice
More! Harder!
I think that's it
You're snapping so much since you got your point
I'm not angry, idiot
Find your rhythm
And "wham"!
Hopeless
(staff) OK, thank you for today!
Even if their recording session is over, they can't get away from the games
What's that move?
How does this work?
That's so strange
Uh? Hamada-san?
I witnessed something incredible
Matsumoto-san
Endo was playing pinball here
Quit it, dude
And Hamada was there, relaxing and watching him
And he leaned against this but it's not attached firmly to the ground, and he almost fell
Of course it's not!
I couldn't focus at all
Of course they didn't dig a hole in the studio
It's so stupid just to assume that
He's so dumb it's scary
I bet you didn't even remember how to do it
After enjoying the games, they decided to play with the spinning top some more
It's spinning!
See? I can still do it
That's incredible
[humming]
[humming last song from previous episode]
I think I can do this
How about Hamada Shogo's songs?
Those were great
I'm gonna spin it
Watch out!
Where did he throw that?
This guys is no fun at all, I swear
I wish he would change school
There was this rumor of him wanting to change school...
Are you kidding me?!
You can do it Tanaka, right?
Sure
Maybe getting older made me forget how to do it
Here I go
Watch out!!
These guys suck, man!
It's no fun at all playing with them
What the hell was that?
That was dangerous
I'm really sorry
What's wrong with Cocorico?
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TWITTER.COM/FGRNDNOISES
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
SPECIAL THANKS TO RIDDELL FOR TYPESETTING THIS EPISODE!!
FULL EPISODE AVAILABLE @ SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT FAN-TRANSLATION MADE BY A FAN FOR OTHER FANS. ALL COPYRIGHT ARE RESERVED TO THEIR RESPECTIVE OWNERS.