Tonight's Gaki no Tsukai
Itao's Third Self-Made Show Idea
It's Back!
Lip-Syncing
Night
Hit
Studio
Opening Lip-Sync
Naniwa Love Shower / Harumi Miyako & Chiaki Oka
Lyrics by: Takatakashi Composer: Chiaki Oka
If it gets a laugh, I'll make my wife cry.
So what? You got a problem, guy?
Rainy Alleyways, Houzen Temple.
Naniwa showers, the orchestra plays.
(Naniwa is an old name for Osaka)
Today, he calls again. Today, he calls again.
Harudanji, you idiot.
You're right, I am an idiot. I chug liquor, and make women cry.
Of course, all of that is for the craft.
Look at me now! I'm number one in Japan.
In all of Japan! You know what I mean, man?
What's with that sad face?
Alcohol! Alcohol! Go buy Alcohol!
For all the worried viewers, we are back
Assistant
Wife
MC
Itsuji Itao
with the program that caused the boom in lip-sync popularity!
To start,
I performed the
opening lip-sync.
What did you think?
You're really gonna ask me that?
And with that,
We have a
fantastic prize lined up for the winner.
Famous Hits Enthusiastically Lip-Synced
Taking place 2 times before, Itao's Lip-Sync Battle!
r
Famous Hits Enthusiastically Lip-Synced
Gaki no Tsukai Members & Staff
6 Groups of Lip-Syncers Will Compete!!!
This time, the Gaki members and crew make up 6 different lip-syncing groups!
Your arm shouldn't hide your face.
3 Hours Before
Itao's Designated Songs
Intense Lip-Sync and Dance Practice
The choreographers teach the moves to the contestants
Staff
You're moving your jaw a bit too much.
If I don't, it'll look like this.
Isn't that how he sings?
Won't we get yelled at?
Difficult Choreography...
This is it
But, honestly
I really don't even feel like doing this.
Enthusiastic Members...
But there's also some enthusiastic members, too.
Is there no rehearsal while wearing the costume?
Asking For
a Dress Rehearsal
What's it like?
We should do it right
It's gonna be on TV, you know
Winner Receives a Prize!
Gold
Who Will Win the Lip-Syncing Crown!?
The winner of the battle will receive a prize. Let's get started!
Here is the first singer,
At the time, it was #1 on
the Oricon Rankings for 10 weeks straight
Akira Terao's "Ruby Ring"
Ruby Ring / Akira Terao
Lyrics by: Takashi Matsumoto  Composer: Akira Terao
Behind the frosted glass, in a windy town.
An unwelcome heart is in pain.
Like a weightless dead leaf blowing all around.
Ever since losing you......
Staring down at your feet,
You took the ring off that day.
If you planned on giving it back to me,
Just throw it away.
Now two years have gone and passed by.
And when I catch a glimpse of that beige coat you used to wear,
I look and see if I can find the ruby ring on her finger.
Ever since losing you......
Thank you very much, come right over here
You were the first one up
and it was like you were completely possessed by him.
Right
Thank you.
Really.
Was there anything you focused on?
I tried to get the feeling
for the mouth posture
Terao Akira's...
Sometimes he goes like this, see
Ah, that was the point of focus
Yea
Forget that though, why did the MC get to sing for so long?
Well, we were the first ones up, so
We had to come out and
show how it's done
and there's two of us...
How was it?
You're really gonna ask me that?
Alright.
She's probably never heard of him before
Have you heard of Akira Terao?
You're really gonna ask me that?
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents:
Down Town's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Translator:
Typesetter:
Hans
Kenny
Akane
Otviss
**We also have Facebook and Twitter.**
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
____________________________________________________________________
If you ever see this video being distributed online but not by us, keep in mind that on youtube
(and other sites), individuals may make money off of sharing fansubs like this that are not their own, please
go back and support the original creators. Fansubbing is voluntary and is not meant to generate profit.
You can download our episodes on our website instead. Thanks for watching our videos!
!!
Itao-Produced Famous-Song Lip-Sync Battle!
The next singer is...
During the 90's it created a sensational boom.
PUFFY's "Asia's Purity"!
Asia's Purity / PUFFY
Lyrics by: Yousui Inoue  Composer: Tamio Okuda
Beijing, Berlin, Dublin, Liberia.
Wait in a bundle, form a circle
Iran, Afghan, Let me hear it, Balalaika.
Pretty girl, Arirang, Gamelan, Lasagna.
Mouses too, be the key.
Mood eleven access, wanna try now?
Open the door, The time is now
We are what's happening...Asia!
Take every panda and line them all up, every single white one
A pure heart is looking to decorate the world.
It's shining
As long as it's loved.
It's blinking
Access love now!
Come on over
As a female duo,
It was like PUFFY...
So stiff, so stiff
uhh,
was here...
So stiff, so stiff
actually singing
So awkward, so awkward
Right Yumi?
We're also wearing real panties.
Women's panties?
You're damn right
That shows how far you're willing to go
I'm wearing Yumi's panties and
she's wearing my panties
Oh, I see, like
"Let's try wearing each others"
Enough already!!
Thank you, go ahead and take a seat
Alright
Here's the next Lip-Syncer
A Godsister of Show Business
Is Finally Entering the Lip-Syncing World
Akiko Wada's "Old Diary"
Old Diary / Akiko Wada
Lyrics by: Kazumi Yasui  Composer: Kouji Makaino
Was her chest always that big?
Back then, both of us
For some reason, because of society
So he's not doing Mori Shinichi
we sulked in how we lived.
Her voice is young
It's very young
In a small love apartment.
I'm not sure about this...
Back then, both of us
For some reason, because of young lust
We were wasting our lives,
Bringing lover's bodies together.
I liked you, but stuff like "love"
Oh, she moves like that?
Absolutely, absolutely never say.
Akiko-san.
I guess so.
Life in the corner of the city
Doesn't he kinda look like Mori-san?
was perfect the way it was.
His base has turned into Mori-san.
Yea, it has.
Back then, both of us
Sometimes he just makes that face...
didn't believe other people.
It was just us all alone,
and we didn't care about a single thing.
Thank you very much, come on over.
You're breathing quite heavily, but
His face was Mori Shinichi!!
You started to morph into him
No no no,
You're singing face was Mori Shinichi.
It really was.
I tried my best to completely become Akiko Wada today.
I completely put Mori Shinchi aside.
Your Mori-san is better
His Mori-san is better than this.
But with Mori-san,
He doesn't really have many hits
Yes he does!!
He has tons!!
That's just disrespectful.
He does, but there were none on the list.
Well it was perfect, thank you.
Please have a seat.
Now for the next Lip-Syncer.
A Performance of a Song About a Nostalgic Youth!!
Kensaku Morita's "Tearful Farewell"
Tearful Farewell / Kensaku Morita
Lyrics by: Yuu Aku  Composer: Kunihiko Suzuki
Oh, this is perfect for Yoshinobu
This is a good pick for him.
Woah, he's barefoot
Who do you say goodbye to?
It's actually kinda funny
Farewells are all too sad
He's good at the facial expressions.
Wait for a rainy day,
If we tried this it wouldn't be funny, though
I see
and say a tearful farewell.
Don't show the tears that will run down your cheeks.
That's a good face
That's just how he sang.
This guy really watched the video
When you can't hold them back, wash them away with a rain shower.
Loneliness and sorrow,
will come and go eventually.
He sang like that too, huh.
But when that time comes,
His smile is great.
It's refreshing.
say a tearful farewell.
Not bad
It was good because he's an amateur
It was good
That was uh,
a fantastic performance.
It was great
It was just like Morita-san.
He really studied for this.
It felt like he really studied the music video.
How much did you study for this?
A couple of... I watched it a few times.
A couple of few times?
What does that mean?
I knew it well.
You know it well?
From my youth.
Second Half After the Cheer Break
More Contestants Will Perform!!
After the cheer break, the second half will begin!
After this, even more contestants will perform!
Let's start the second half.
The Queen of Heartbreak's
First Million Record Seller!
Miyuki Nakajima's "Light Sleep"
Light Sleep / Miyuki Nakajima
Lyrics / Composer: Miyuki Nakajima
Hold on
This is his entrance?
So he's not using the stairs
This is repulsive.
He must have seen this at a concert.
He may have.
It's like a live concert.
That summer day I promised to remember seems so long ago.
That's a great stare.
That wind is gone even from the returning tides.
This is scary!
Ahh, the candle that we lit together in that room.
He's an idiot
He looks like an old lady!!
In the time of overflowing light
But he's so into it.
He is.
Kind of like a fortuneteller.
Where did it fade away to.
This is how you do it.
Tell me how much you miss it
I feel like I've learned something.
I didn't know you could take this path
Tell me the truth.
You can.
That way of singing...
If you're not a stranger, it's all the more, all the more...
She really makes that face
She makes scary faces.
Wandering in a light sleep,
Oh, it changed.
It's a new face
the town is calling out for love.
Wandering in a light sleep,
He has a lot of faces up his sleeve.
the town is calling out for love.
Amazing.
A little scary.
Is that the finale face?
Really scary.
The ending is scary.
He turned into Hiroko Yakushimaru
So this is how it ends.
Thank you very much!
Come on over here.
It was very enthusiastic singing,
or should I say enthusiastic lip-syncing.
Right, well
you see,
It was the theme for a drama.
Was there a reason you chose
this song specifically?
The theme, umm...
It was the theme for a drama.
Say the reason!!
Why did you choose this song?
Because I liked that drama...
And it's the theme song...
Correct.
She's getting mad.
I understand.
Yes.
She's getting mad.
So it's like
You were in a light sleep
and woke up from it, huh?
And also...
Huh!?
He won't even look over here
Like an awakening...
We are now at our last Lip-Syncer!
An Enthusiastic Performance From
a Lip-Syncing King and His 2 Assistants!!
The Checkers' "Heartbreak for Julia"!
Heartbreak for Julia / The Checkers
Lyrics by: Masao Urino  Composer: Hiroaki Serizawa
"His 2 assistants?"
And "a king."
Ah, I remember this song.
Oh, it's Fumiya-san
and Takamoku-san
They look just like them
A candle's light
Bursts and spreads through a glass piercing.
You dance in his arms.
Is this supposed to be Fumiya-san?
Yea...
Heartbreak
A sad carol in the window display.
He really...
He got really old
It turned into silver snow.
He's not very light on his feet
As I walked through the door
The person who cried and sent me off.....
We lost something important in this city.
Do you remember?
He's pretty stiff.
I wish he'd move a little more.
The dream that we had.
He used to move around a bit more
Let's go back to that street corner,
Julia
He got so old.
He finally used both arms
So slow!
Sometimes too early, sometimes too late
Thank you very much, come on over.
How do you feel? Having finished your lip-sync.
I'm 61 years old now, so
Right
After training...
I've had muscle pain for three days now.
Ah, I see.
Your voice is way too quiet!!
During some of it you sort of looked like Daiki Kameda
It's supposed to be Fumiya-san
Thank you very much, please have a seat.
But still,
Mrs. Nakajima is still aiming for the win.
He always goes for high quality
but he never wins
You could really feel his enthusiasm this time, too.
The Lip-Sync Battle With a Prize
Who Will Win the Lip-Syncing Crown!?
The White Hot Lip-Sync Contest!
And now, who will receive the lip-syncing crown?
The winner is...
The Checkers!
Winner
Takafumi    Kenji     Kazuhiro
Inomoto       Suga     Fujiwara
Congratulations!
Lost it again...
We couldn't compete
You had the highest quality
I thought it might be Miyuki-san, but...
Yours was high quality so it's ok
After This
A Real Performance From the Winners!!
That must be frustrating.
It must be, huh.
r
The ones acquiring the prize are "Heartbreak for Julia"
Cue Card
stiff
He always does this.
He did it last time too.
It's not a license!!
The Checkers' "Heartbreak for Julia"!
Heartbreak for Julia / The Checkers
Lyrics by: Masao Urino  Composer: Hiroaki Serizawa
Can't believe we get to see it again
It's even their real voices.
A candle's light
Bursts and spreads through a glass piercing.
You dance in his arms.
He's so gentle.
Such a soft voice.
Heartbreak
You can do better than this
A sad carol in the window display.
Try harder
It turned into silver snow.
So gentle.
As I walked through the door
It's turning into a love-making song!!
Can they keep it up?
The person who cried and sent me off.....
We lost something important in this city.
His voice isn't coming out
Do you remember?
The dream that we had.
Let's go back to that street corner,
Julia
It won't come out
It's really good
It's great
Great.
Thank you very much.
This time,
it was your real voices
By the end it turned into old men doing karaoke
She's still mad
She's still really mad.
I was so annoyed
that I couldn't really hear the song.
Could you please sing it again?
Good idea
Really?
Good idea!
Alright then,
Ok then, get ready
Get the song ready!!
Since she couldn't hear it...
No lyrics, either (on the cue cards)
Let's hear it one more time
Heartbreak for Julia / The Checkers
Lyrics by: Masao Urino  Composer: Hiroaki Serizawa
* No Lyric Cue Cards
Still smiling, though.
See that?
He was like "Where's the lyrics!?"
A candle's light
Spreads through a glass pi--...
You dance in his arms.
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
That's the song of a winner
Not bad.
How was it, Nakajima Miyumi-san?
At some point, uhh
I couldn't understand the lyrics anymore
Fumiya-san, the lyrics...