TPF
They're not even letting
us make whatever we want
And then we're told what Okonomiyaki is
It's like an old lady doing what she wants
I always wanted to try this!!
Absolutely tasty Okonomiyaki challenge
Trying innovative recipes!
It's the absolutely tasty Okonomiyaki challenge!
First up was Hamada
Hamada's innovation was curry
Oh I get it
It's curry
Wow
This is good!
Are you gonna put it on now?
Well since it's curry sauce
Of course that's gonna be good
How did it taste like?
Can I say something?
This is so freaking delicious
Honestly, I can eat 2 of these!!
Then there was Endo with his diet menu
Endo's innovation was protein
Protein okonomiyaki
This is bad for sure!
Yellow
Main
Ingredients
Chicken breast ・ Protein ・ soymilk
Thoughtfully picked ingredients with low calorie content
Endo why don't
just go to Matsumoto's house and make it there
However, how was the taste?
I didn't think it was going to be this stiff
this is awful!!
It gets all over your gums doesn't it
The concept has changed a little
Tanaka's dish was foil cooked salmon
Then Tanaka with his well thought out foil cooked salmon
Wow it's properly steamed
The scent is amazing
But how was the main taste?
It's all gooey, absolutely disgusting!!
What is this?
First bucket of the day
Tanaka
Endo
Hamada
This is the score so far
but who will be the winner?
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents:
Down Town's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Subbed by: Otviss
Special thanks to: Donators, viewers during livestreams, Xueshi & Spectral-K
**We also have Facebook and Twitter.**
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
____________________________________________________________________
Absolutely tasty Okonomiyaki rules
each person presents two dishes
Full score of 10 points
In worst case there's a skinhead punishment!?
The rules of the Okonomiyaki challenge are simple
each person presents two dishes and full score is 10 points
and there might be a skinhead for the loser!
Absolutely tasty Okonomiyaki
Housei's Attempt
In this second part, we'll start with housei's first dish
Let's seriously make some good food shall we?
Seriously right?
Have a look at this
Pickles?
Kyo! (Kyoto style)
Kyoto style and pickles from all around the country, well all kinds of things
gray
Nationwide pickles
yellow
Main
Ingredients
Kyoto style or all around the country which one is it!!
Which one is it?
That doesn't make sense 'cause it has stuff from Akita and Fukuoka too
Shibazuke (Kyoto)
Nozawana (Nagano)
Takana (Fukuoka)
Iburigakko (Akita)
There's just one from Kyoto
Here I go
I'm going to put all of it in
Cooking Step 1
Bing instructions
Mix the pickles into the batter
Aren't you putting too much in?
It's better for the taste if they soak together
Ooooh okay...
This might have potential
As soon as I heard we were doing this, this idea came to me
Instantly?
THE OIL
He forgot the oil
50.000 yen!!
I've said it so many times and you still don't get it right!!
Another 50.000 yen
Hang on a second here
The colour of the oil is odd though
Aren't you gonna use the meat?
Well, because the...
pickles have a crunch to them
I'll fry it so that the meat doesn't become crunchy too
Seriously this is starting to...
kinda...
This idea might get stolen ya know
Good isn't it?
The lining up pattern, Yeah it's good
I wanted Hamada to do this.
Cooking Step 2
Bing instructions
Put the pork over the batter
His dishes were so messed up it was awful
Do we even need the meat?
He could've just went with the taste of the pickles right?
With a simple approach cause it's not negiyaki is it
Yeah you're right
This looks good
Oh this is good
This is really good!
It certainly is!
This is good
Cooking Step 3
Bing instructions
Cover and cook for
3 minutes on medium heat
There hasn't been any real taste until now
There hasn't been any taste huh?
We had curry didn't we
Just tasteless and flat
The curry had taste though
Tanaka's was really tasteless wasn't it?
Exactly
That's why I'm saying we had curry
Look at the balance to the right, it's -150.000 yen
You're right
Look it says 150.000 yen
There's also a skinhead
Even though it says skinhead
We can see Tanaka's hairline clearly
If he was a skinhead you wouldn't be able to tell would ya!!
What a face he's making
So how did Housei's dish turn out?
What's up with this water?
There's so much water
Did it come from the inside?
Oh I get it, because of the pickles
I think he's done
Yes I'm ready
Looks great
Housei's first dish
Pickles from all around the country Okonomiyaki
How does Housei's confident creation taste?
If we had some sauce
this could be dangerous
First we try it "plain"
That's what I'm scared of the most though
Itadakimasu
Smells nice
Delicious
This is delicious
I guess this is how it tastes huh
Seriously though, it's great
It's delicious
Delicious!!
What is this even?
It's good but
I wouldn't say it with such a loud voice
I really think this is delicious but
Don't you think there's too many pickles in this?
Then you can go change it yourself
How many points?
I think I'd give it
9 points
Wow..
If I were to say it super strictly though then a 2
Housei who is currently at the top gets 9 points!
What can we expect of the second dish?
It can't get better from now on so...
I'll do even better don't worry
Nope, no good
No, this is good!
Housei come on
te
Fruits & Custard
yellow
Main
Ingredients
Don't mess around with us
This might be a little...
This is straight up trash
This is just a normal pancake
Its not a pancake. Do pancakes have cabbage in it?
Cooking Step 1
Bing instructions
Mix the custard and batter together
We already get it's bad before cooking
Bare with me Hamada-san
We need some kind of dessert
So I thought if I mishem... both together
Mishem both together...
As I was mixing my tongue made it hard to swallow
Cooking Step 2
Bing instructions
Put the fruits on top of the batter
After the batter has been poured he puts fruit on top
Again with this...
So we have mango and?
5 kinds of fruit
rec
Mango Strawberry Blueberry Grapefruit Banana
Strawberries, blueberries
and grapefruit...
I'm putting everything a kid likes on here
None of us are kids though
The youngest one here is 45 years old
Nothing but the elderly here
Alright here I go
I don't really wanna hear the fizzing of the vegetables
Oops not vegetables I meant the fruits
What's the matter?
What happened?
Vegetables?
Ask any household, There are just too many of them!!
Ask any household, there are just too many of them!!
But he was just using fruit though
Yeah just fruits
Stop it already
Let's stop with this
with this kind of pulling people back
Here I go again
Looks disgusting
What kind of fry(yaki) is this?
Parlor okonomiyaki*
*Referring to "Fruit Parlors", or parfait-focused dessert bars
Fruit parlor okonomiyaki?
Housei's second dish
Fruit parlor okonomiyaki
Okonomiyaki as a dessert, how will it taste like?
Scary is all I can say about this
My eyes hurt from just smelling this
Your eyes hurt?
I smelled it and my eyes started to hurt
I have no idea what this is
So there's grapefruit and strawberry in here
Ugh
This is dreadful!!
This is.. I'm so sorry
Haha, here it comes
How amazing
Devil's corner right here
This is so awful
The sweet okonomiyaki receives 2 skulls. The worst score
Absolutely tasty Okonomiyaki
Matsumoto's Attempt
Last challenger is Matsumoto, what will his creative menu be?
Last challenger is Matsumoto, what will his first dish be?
So what kind of thing haven't we had so far?
So what kind of things haven't we had so far?
Well, chinese, fruits et cetera, all kinds of things
We've had Japanese style too
It's Japanese!!
We already had that with my pickles
The core of Japanese
I have food with originality that's near to a Japanese's heart
Pickles are close to the heart aren't they?
This is really original, take a look
Mahkeeh zooshi (Maki zushi)
That's how a foreigner would say it right?
Yeah mahkeeh zooshi
Hosomaki!
gray
Hosomaki Sushi
yellow
Main
Ingredients
You haven't had ideas like this have you
Eating okonomiyaki and this together I understand though
Yeah, in between right?
As a side dish
In between right
Being kansai and all right?
Hosomaki also has sushi rice in it
He doesn't forget (the oil) does he?
Kind of like "How's this?"while he was brushing it on
He did it way ahead of time
Beginners might
have it difficult with this
Flipping it over too is a technique by itself
Cooking Step 1
Bing instructions
Put the maki sushi rolls on top of the batter
In this kind of style where
everyone in the family can go
Grandpa's gonna have the cucumber
Grandma's gonna have the dried gourd
That's mine! I'll have the dried gourd!!
There will be smiles on everyone's faces
Cause I'm putting the rice facing upwards
I wonder how it'll turn out when I flip it
Any brainless fool can figure it out right?
Huh?
Won't it turn crispy?
I want you guys to enjoy this crispiness
So this is the technique huh
Will this really be good?
It's completely changed now
It's a completely different thing now
This is so comical
Well...
Well it is something but we're doing Okonomiyaki
Worth noting is that I'm adding the tastyness of the fried rice
It's called the aesthetic of failure
We also have the fact that fried rice has kind of strong negative image to it
I'm scorching my opponent
turning it into a negative surprise
wanting to turn minus into plus
I'll just keep repeating myself won't I
I'd just be repeating myself
Okay then everyone
It hasn't changed a bit from before has it
The "Okonomiyaki" in this is weak as thin ice
We haven't had anything we can flip over like this. I don't think its strange
Isn't this nice?
This is basically just fried rice
The crispiness is definitely doing its thing
Cooking Step 2
Bing instructions
Coat it with soy sauce instead of standard sauce
Finish up with a soy sauce coating
Cause they wanted some moisture
These little guys are sucking it up nicely
You look thirsty there you go
Matsumoto's first dish
Maki Zushi Okonomiyaki
Taken straight from the heart of Japan, how will it taste like?
Is this Okonomiyaki?
Yeah i guess so...
This sure is small
Are we supposed to use these?
What are you doing?
Right?
It's fine like this then
You may turn it upside down of course
eating it like this too if you want
I'm getting a Singapore vibe from this
You're right!
It's just like that hotel
Marina bay sands
Just like in singapore right!?
Alright let's eat
I don't really see the Okonomiyaki in this
Hm?
It's delicious
This isn't bad at all
Yeah it's good
Not bad is it?
Well it's not really that big of a...
Nope it's definitely not bad
I did it, it's good isn't it!?
The sushi rice doesn't disturb the other tastes at all
I thought the cucumber was gonna be hard to eat but it's really good
It's binded nice together but
the heat didn't get through
How many points is this?
This gotta be quite high don't you think?
7 points
Well because...
You gotta be joking
Do you even understand numbers?
The pickle okonomiyaki gotta be the king
No that just happened to be in line
Mine should definitely be ahead of yours
No the pickle Okonomiyaki is just the king of them all
The Okonomiyaki's from before were properly done like they would transform into
new concepts and all
You just put these on top!!
Because these are just exposed like this
If they were inside then..
That's just how you make it
Putting it on top like this is no good?
I just happen to be hearing this for the first time
Just be careful from now on then
I mean that's not really what we mean
It's not quite like that
Well of course it's like that
It didn't say that in the script
You gotta mix it together
How many points are ya holding back?
3 points
Holding back 3 points is freaking strange!
I haven't heard any kind of rule
that says I can't put it on top!
Absolutely tasty Okonomiyaki
rec
Second dish
Matsumoto's Attempt
Can Matsumoto's second dish turn this around?
Until now
We haven't really had anything crunchy have we?
We had something didn't we? The pickles
In small pieces though right?
What we'll be having this time
I guess it's a snappy kind of feeling
Only the good stuff here
I'll make a meal from only the suction cups of the octopus
gray
Suction cups from octopus
yellow
Main
Ingredients
Make a meal from only the suction cups?
I think it's good if we take a look at from what I'll be making this
It's this
It's all thick
What do you think of when I say octopus?
Ink...
You're correct
It's octopus ink
Cooking Step 1
Bing instructions
Put the octopus ink into the batter
Octopus ink
I've never had that before
Exactly!
Is it edible?
Whether it's edible or not I don't know yet
Are you for real?
Wow it's all black
Compared to squid ink it must be stronger
It really really looks like it
You're not gonna mix these in?
No I'm not
So that's how octopus ink looks like...
This is what demons eat
You bet
A few of these...
Cooking Step 2
Bing instructions
Put the suction cups on top of the batter
This is unclear
It's becoming one with the grill
He does like putting it on top doesn't he
Absolutely, as he's putting them on top once again
Again with the stuff on top
Makes you flinch at first sight doesn't it
Why?
Just looking at it being black and all
Exactly
Well, like with all dark food
That looks like raw oil
It's like fusing together with the pan
The heat is gonna
get trapped in the sunction cups like crazy
Cooking Step 3
Bing instructions
Cover and cook for 3 minutes
The pan is fighting back. The sunction cups are fighting back
with each other. None of them can lose
Their will not to lose is just too strong
I wonder how it'll turn out
It's hard to tell if its burnt or not
Yeah looking at it is difficult...
It's kind of dissolved into the pan though
It looks like Sludge
Matsumoto's second dish
Sunction cup Okonomiyaki
With an amazing first impact, how will it taste like?
This isn't food
You'll find out soon
I wonder how this will taste
Let's dig in!
What the fuck is this...
There's no distinct taste either
Yeah the taste is...
It doesn't taste much
I need lots of salt for this
Ah, sorry thank you...
There's no taste?
With a little bit saltiness...
Woah!!
Yummy!!
Huuuhh!?
It came instantly didn't it?
Yaaaaaaaay
He said "Yay"
How many points?
Well about 3 I guess
That's just strange
What kind of calculation is that?
Well everyone...
If the one from the before
The hosomakisushi one is an 8
Then this is certainly a 7 isnt it?
Definitely not a 7
No way
Not a 7
How many points?
4 points
no way no way
An octopus will come tonight ya know
Through the curtain Whoosh! and it's there
It just tastes of octopus and I don't feel the Okonomiyaki in this
Honestly I would give it a 3
Yeah I get ya
That makes Housei the winner
Current top
9 points
Housei's dish
Pickles from all around the country Okonomiyaki
It's confirmed then
Since it's confirmed...
So that's the winner huh?
Exactly. Thank you very much
Let's go back to the hosomaki one for a moment
We havent resolved why the hosomaki
was bad yet
Why was the hosomaki no good again?
'Cause they were just placed on top!!
The winner is Housei with his pickles from all around the country Okonomiyaki
Well with Endo having a kid and all...
My neck is in place now after 3 months
Boys and girls are completely different after all aren't they?
Completely different
Like the way they frenzy is extraordinary
One time I was taking a nap and then
All of sudden he jumps on me and
goes WAAAAAHH!!
How old is he?
3 years old
3 years huh?
It's really amazing
Girls don't really do things like that often
You're right it's rare well because they're weaker but
they listen to what they're told. Completely different from boys
They don't listen to a single word
I wondered what to do
my two daughters were watching a film and
well they were watching it together with my son and
It was about a kappa getting killed*
*Kappa is a turtle-like creature from Japanese folklore
There are films like that?
Where a kappa gets slain?
You were voice acting in that film
"Summer days with Coo"?
Yes yes yes!
In his mind where,
the scene where
he was slain in his father's arms?
Ah yes that happened
So he got killed and made this "Kuweeeeh" sound
So...
My son was watching that scene
and said that the kappa scared him
I went "Let's go change your diaper"
and when he said "no I don't want to"
My wife went Kappa will come The Kappa will come
Then I went like this while staying hidden
Is that really how a Kappa sounds like?
Does a kappa really go Koooh?
Well of course they don't but thats how mine went and
then he said "I'm scared!"
And we ended up doing it so many times
One time maybe half past midnight or something
I always sleep apart so
my wife and my son sleep together and I in a distant room
Then my wife in the middle of the night woke up and was like
Can't you do something about this?
Despite finally being able to sleep but then I'd hear
It's scary It's scary! I'm scared of the Kappa!
and he would wake me up
It happened so many times
Now he's too easily scared my wife said fiercely
Cause you overdid the Kappa thing?
Exactly
Alright then I said, we'll sleep together tonight
So my wife, the kid and me here
In a shape of a river*
*He's refering to the shape of the Kanji as it has 3 vertical lines.
Then my son...
The shape of a river is certainly hard for a Kappa to understand
Figuring out whether you're liquid or not
Sleeping as an actual river right?
Anyway, "It's fine its fine" I said and
and he finally fell asleep
Finally I thought and took a look at my wife and she also had her eyes closed
Finally, I guess I'll go to bed too then I thought
Then my son kind of woke up startled
"It's scary! I'm scared of the Kappa!"
What the hell?
Yeah what the?
As I looked at my wife with all her might she let out a snore like this
This is just you putting up a show now
I'm absolutely serious!
That was a brilliantly crafted story!
It's true!
Is it really?
This is true
Then I woke up my wife and went
You've been snoring this whole time!!
and we both burst out laughing
"Oh so it was my snoring?"
Looking from above now, It's just like a Kappa*
*Kappas are depicted as having a big bald spot
That's the end of that
What do you mean "That's the end of that"?
I wonder how girls are though right?
My daughter went to "Kidzania"once
Kidzania
Txt
Kids can use various tools and get to experience
real vocations just like adults in "Kids-in-Charge City"
and then well there are people like...
Variety comedians
Oh really?
Like those vocational schools yeah
And I got shown a video where
My daughter was doing manzai
Wow that's amazing
With her friend
I wanna see that!
So...
There was a Shochiku area*
*Shochiku is a movie studio
and there these young comedians
would teach out different skits
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
Obviously they didnt know it was my daughter
And then they'd remember and do it?
Yeah and I watched it and it wasn't funny at all
Well of course
%!¤#!"#%
That far?
That wasn't needed though was it
Like "What the fuck"
That's just the way it is
My daughters debut!!