Narrator...............l
Ohta Shin'ichiro
"I want to know more about Fujiwara Hiroshi"
note: On screen: "Quiz: Manager Fujiwara's 500 things"
Here's our Quiz "500 things about Manager Fujiwara"
First question
All of a sudden?
No warnings at all
What is Fujiwara's hobby?
Q1. What is Fujiwara's hobby?
I don't need to know
Matsumoto-san, you do know a lot about him, right?   - Well...
We've been... like, 2 years? I mean, we've been hanging out a lot
But we've never actually talked about that...
Former Downtown Manager
...........Fujiwara Hiroshi
Downtown's former manager, Hiroshi Fujiwara
Narrator..........l
Baba Keisuke
He doesn't just play a role in the direction of Gaki no Tsukai's New Year Specials
He's also our Fujiwara, the one who made us burst in laughter on several famous skits until now
But this time
We'll approach his true nature
Drawing near Fujiwara Hiroshi's True Nature !!
Of a man working hard for Yoshimoto
I don't usually wonder about things I don't want to know
That's the point   - Yeah but...
We're doing way too much
Reveal your answers
KARAOKE
MUSIC
SENDING
PICTURES
WITH HIS
CELLPHONE
DRIVING
SAUNA
I have no idea so I think this makes sense
You went with "music"?
"Music"
I think he's a predictable man
- So, music should work?   - Makes sense
BEING FUJIWARA IN A DIFFERENT PLACE, HE CAN'T LISTEN TO THEM
What is your hobby?
Oh, huh...
Sorry, uhm...
Appreciation of tropical fishes
A. Appreciation of tropical fishes
What the hell
Is that so?
I'm considering quitting my job
Translation, subtitles & encoding by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
Find all my other subtitled clips on my wordpress:
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Support my translations by clicking like on my Facebook page:
facebook.com/shionnotsukai
There are still 499 questions left
I don't really want to know about him
I know, right?
For real
Second question
What is Fujiwara's special skill?
Q2. What is Fujiwara's special skill?
I have no idea about this one either
It's gotta be that
I remember this, he even made a skit about it
Ohhh, I see...
You're right...   - Wait, what?
He has done this
But he did this one too
Yeah, that one too    - Yes
It has to be one of the two    - I think so too
SKIING
SWIMMING
I've heard about this
Yeah it's surprisingly true
It seems like he's pretty good at butterfly
SWIMMING
BINGE
EATING
SKIING
Yeah that's true
But you know, he
He's pretty bad ad skiing without the sticks
BINGE
EATING
SWIM-
MING
SKIING
SWIM-
MING
He did that on the show too, right?   - You're right
Here's the answer
That was a good hint   - It's either one of them
- Right?
What is your special skill?
Yes uhm... well....
Swimming
A. Swimming
Told so
It was that one after all
Makes sense
If Fujiwara is asked "please do your favorite gag"
What would that be?
I really can't think of anything except for this one
Q7. If he's asked to perform his favorite
gag, which gag will he perform?
I don't know
I'm not sure if it's a gag to him
Right, that one
It could be
I think he got it
Reveal your answers
That one, he did that too
It's this
HARD GAY
"OYOYO"
"1,2,3
NABEATSU"
Yeah
It's his only one    - "Gather around my boobs!"
Will he do it?
"KOMANECHI"
"GATHER
AROUND
ppppMY BOOBS"
I don't know if he considers it to be a gag
Please perform your favorite gag
Eh? Wait-
Maybe he doesn't remember
He looks so happy though
"I'm itchy~"
That wasn't funny at all
A. "I'm itchy～"
What was that?
He had this embarrassed grin
That was disgusting
Yeah it was disgusting
What would Fujiwara bring with him on a desert island?
Q14. What would he bring with him on a Desert Island?
What would he bring, huh...
I think I'll just leave my seat and have one of you write for me
I really want to leave too
What are you sayin'?
Reveal your answers
What would he do with tropical fishes?
WATER
COMICS
PILLOW
Dunno, studying I guess
TROPICAL
FISHES
SCHEDULE
BOOK
Oh, makes sense
Here's the answer
Uhm...
I'd bring with me a large quantity of food
A. A large quantity of food
Man this quiz is sucking up my energy
I'm still at zero points
It's all about food    - Bringing food is a bit obvious
I bet he said it thinking it was something hilarious
Yeah I can see that    - He was smiling all the way
Wasn't funny at all though
If Fujiwara pulls some hair from his nose, how many can he pull out?
Q17. How many nose hairs can Fujiwara pull out?
He seems to be the guy who can pull out a lot     - Yeah, he does
He's got power
- Fujiwara-san surely can
Nope
Hm?
I think he...
Oh I see
That many?
Reveal your answers
Yeah
I think he can
I think he'll get kinda weirded out
I can see it
And be like "I'm sorry"    - This can definitely happen
It can happen       - That's a good theory
Maybe his finger won't fit
Please show us how many hairs you can pull out from your nose
Okay~
What's with that "Okay~"?    - Is he an idol?
- He's acting like a young girl
Hamada was right
He's just making clear the fact he can't pull a single one out
Wait a moment please, I'm sorry
I told ya the fingers wouldn't fit
For real
He really can't get it
That's because of his chubby fingers
Wait a moment please, I'm sorry
We have to recognize his effort though
I pulled out just one, I'm sorry
He had more     - That was long
He could have pulled more if he changed his method
Don't be so happy about it, geez
The hair was very thick too
Thick and friggin' long    - Yeah
It was a serious nose hair
That nostril hair was the only lively thing he ever had
In case of a major earthquake, what will Fujiwara bring out with him first?
Q21. If a major earthquake strikes
What will Fujiwara bring with him first?
Must be that
Giving that he's soooooooooooo predictable...
He is
So we have to think as if we were predictable?  - Yeah, just like him
Reveal your answers
Really? That's your answer?
MONEY
WATER
BANKBOOK
Yeah, I'm sure of it
Is him really that calm?
It's a bit shifted from his usual ultra-predictable character
CUSHION
BANKBOOK &
PERSONAL SEAL
He shouldn't be laughing
I know right?
Food supplies I guess
What?!
A. Food
It went that way again
Should have figured it
He has a huge consideration of food, huh?
- Yeah that's true
Right
They say he recently managed to suck up soups or such with his finger
Soups... with his finger?
Well it's just an urban legend after all
That's...
You'd get fat that way
Manager Orita is 2 hours late to an appointed meeting
Fujiwara's subordinate...u..
Current Downtown Manager
Orita Naoya
Which phrase does Fujiwara say a lot when he's angry?
Q39. Manager Orita is 2 hours late!
Which phrase will Fujiwara say when he's angry?
"Phrase"...?
Reveal your answers
I bet we'll fail this one too
"I WONDER
WHY?"
"AS A
PERSON..."
"ARE YOU
TAKING
IT LIGHTLY?"
Does he even get mad to begin with?
It's ju--- well
I can't really picture a guy like him raising his voice in anger
What's this "are you taking it lightly?"
"GET
A GRIP"
"HAVE YOU
LOST YOUR
MOTIVATION?"
Like "are you underestimating your job?"
Oh that way    - Yeah like that
A gentle feel      - Well, me too I wrote
"I wonder why?"
It's definitely something like that
How will you get mad if manager Orita is 2 hours late for the meeting you've planned?
He's laughing a lot
What's so funny about it?
Sorry I was so late
Huh?
Woah
Why?
Woah woah    - Something's about to begin
I apologize for being so late
Da hell do ya mean? What happened?
He's angry
Ya overslept?
Don't sleep, moron. Are you an idiot?
Ya always said ya overly concerned about this, aight?
The hell are ya doin'?
He's really pissed off!
Huh?!
He's scary
Ya always said that
It's so long!
Now go, idiot
I'm really sorry
I'm sorry
He was really pissed off, right?
A. "Haven't you said you care about this?"
Yamazaki: "ARE YOU
TAKING IT LIGHTLY?"
Matsumoto:
"I WONDER WHY?"
Hamada:
"AS A PERSON..."
Endo:
"GET A GRIP"
Tanaka: "HAVE YOU LOST
YOUR MOTIVATION?"
He snapped     - Scary!
He scared me     - He was scary
What the hell     - Wasn't that
I mean wasn't that a bit too... realistic?
I thought so too
It felt like he's used to say that
Yeah, right?
But right after that he said "I'm sorry"
It kinda felt like Oozaki-san (Fujiwara's superior)
It felt like he's saying from his point of view
All the things he's been told by Oozaki-san as they are
He must have studied them
What was Fujiwara's most recent reason for why he had a fight with his wife?
Q65. What was Fujiwara's most recent reason
for why he had a fight with his wife?
What could it be?
Reveal your answers
DINNER WAS
DELAYED
MATSUMOTO
YAMA
ZAKI
HAMADA
ENDO
TANAKA
SOMETHING ABOUT
DINNER
HE LEFT UNTIDY
THE CLOTHES
HE TOOK OFF
THEIR COUPLE
LIFE HAS
WORSENED
SIGNIFICANTLY
SNORING
'Cause it's been a while since they got married
Makes sense
I doubt they fight over such thing at this point
BEING FUJIWARA IN A DIFFERENT PLACE, HE CAN'T LISTEN TO THEM
Which was your most recent reason
For why you had a fight with your wife?
Uhm... I'm sorry
Well
There was like this postcard for welfare pension which expired
And she told me I should go and turn it in myself, but I didn't
And she said to me "why are you so irresponsibl-
We don't need to hear the rest
Turn it off please
Let's get back here
A. He didn't turn in the welfare pension postcard
Welfare pension, huh
I see, I see
I don't really think
He knows he's in a quiz and we're here to answer
I wish he would think something like "there's no way they can guess it"
I mean, who can write in here all his endless babbling?
Q. Which song does Fujiwara often sing at the karaoke?
Karaoke...
As time passes
The true face of manager Fujiwara
Gets clearer and clearer!
I think it may be "Sexual Violet No.1"...
Woah, that's what he'd choose?
Yamazaki
"Season in the sun"
Matsumoto
"Runner"
Hamada
"My lovely Eri"
Endo
"TSUNAMI"
"My lovely Eri"
Tanaka
A. Sexual Violet No. 1
Who could have possibly guessed it!
Q. At what age did Fujiwara have his first kiss?
It wasn't serious, but my first kiss was at 14
A, At 14
He said "it wasn't serious"
What does he mean?
What does it mean?
Must be something similar to a coming out
Q. By fighting which comedian Fujiwara thinks he can win?
Maybe someone like Yama-chan?
Yamazaki Housei
A. Yamazaki Housei
You were right
It was a good option
Q. Which was the thing a woman told him
which made him the happiest?
That's got to be something my wife told me
Probably the time she told me something like "I will follow you"
A. When her wife told him "I will follow you"
What the... what the hell is this?
What are we even doing at this point?
This could become a tv show
No way!
Which is the content
Of Fujiwara's favorite adult video?
Q261. What's Fujiwara's favorite adult video about?
This too is... like
A really weird question to ask
I agree
Hamada please cut the crap and fix that string
What?
Looking at it pisses me off
What are you...?
Look at it, it's curling like crazy
What's wrong with you?
I want him to fix it so bad
What the hell
Just put it back to its original shape
Just... look at mine, I--
If mine made even a single curl I'd definitely hate it
I feel the same
While his is completely one with the curls
You're right
I hate it when people do that
I wonder why
I hate people who do this!
This is unbearable
What the hell, dude!
It's an eyesore
Sorry it was completely unrelated but I had to say it
It makes sense you did
I just couldn't hold any longer
It's good you let us know
We got it, so it's okay
Q261. What's Fujiwara's favorite adult video about?
Reveal your answers
Something
involving
interviews
Group sex
Magic Mirror
N°1
Hamada wrote "Magic Mirror" too
Well, there are tons of them
Come on, you just wrote what you like
That's not it
Something
Sado-masochist
Magic Mirror
N°1
Tanaka did too
Tanaka wrote the same
Ok so YOU just wrote what you like
Right?
What is that about?
Like when she goes to an interview and she's like "please don't, please don't"
Ohhh you mean those!
Oh, those
But then she starts not to dislike it that much
The amateurs ones?
Don't talk that much about it
Here's the answer
It's embarrassing
Like...
Those where there's a neat and clean woman
And she gradually grows wilder and wilder
I have no idea what he's sayin'
Those things turn me on
Sorry
A. A clean & composed woman gradually growing wilder
What the hell? It's not something you can think of
But Yamazaki was close, though
Was I?
You were
Ohhh, I see
But mine is more like, something ordinary
Yeah
I guess so
It's just like the old uchuu-kikaku stuff
note: Uchuu-kikaku is a japanese adult video production company
Really
Manager Orita successfully got a big employment
Which phrase will Fujita use to praise him?
Fujita..?
Who is Fujita now?
There are like only 3 people
Appearing as characters
How can he screw up the main one?
He said "Fujiwara" countless times till now
There aren't many people
And why he's "Fujita" now?
Are we changing him?
A new one appeared
So we're doing him from now on?
He must feel pretty bad for this
More like, who is Fujita?
Yeah, who's this "Manager Fujita"?
I bet he'd be mad if someone called him Fujita
Q305. If manager Orita gets an big employment
How will Fujiwara compliment him?
I really don't know
This will do
This---
"WAY TO GO"
"YOU DID IT"
"LET'S GO TELL
OOZAKI-SAN"
"ISN'T IT
GOOD?"
"WELL DONE!
NOW LET'S
GO TAKE A
BITE!"
MATSUMOTO
YAMA
ZAKI
TANAKA
ENDO
HAMADA
Must be one of those for sure
I wonder who will get it right
Here's the answer
Excuse me
What's the matter?
He should know
You just got... a big job, huh
They told him
That's where it began
You did it!
I'd love to get it myself too, really
You worked hard for it
Next time I'll get it too, for sure
You did well, really, that's great
I'll snatch it from ya!
You did good, really
Keep going this way
This is hilarious
This is...
Alright
You did it!
A. "Well done!"
He was like "now go away!"
"C'mon get the hell outta here!"
It would have been fine without the last part
Ahhh, this is weird
What's the title of the movie Fujiwara wants to be the main character of?
Q337. What's the title of the movie Fujiwara
would like to be its main character?
This one kinda suddenly flashed on my mind
Yeah, same here
Reveal your answers
Rocky or Rambo
Rocky
Ranbo
It's tough
being a man
(otoko wa tsurai yo)
HAMADA
TANAKA
ENDO
YAMA
ZAKI
MATSUMOTO
Rocky, huh?
Stallone everywhere
All Stallone except for me!
You're right
He just popped out
Amazing
He really came to my mind so clearly
BEING FUJIWARA IN A DIFFERENT PLACE, HE CAN'T LISTEN TO THEM
The protagonist of which movie would you like to be?
Well...
Probably "Mission: Impossible" or such
Come on...
A. Mission: Impossible
It was Tom Cruise in the end
Tom Cruise, right?
Whatever
What the hell would he do in Mission: Impossible?
He must have thought "It'd be good"
Yeah
You're right
Like "I'd love that"
"I'd love to do that"
"He's so cool"
Yamazaki you haven't get a single one yet?
Not even once
That's impressive
Yeah...
Who does Fujiwara think is the manliest
Between the five of you?
It's easy to think he'd go for Hamada
Q368. According to Fujiwara, who is the manliest
between the five of them?
Yeah right
Yeah, makes sense
I'm positive that's what he'd say
Reveal your answers
I think I got it
HAMADA-SAN
MATSUMOTO
HAMADA
YAMA
ZAKI
ENDO
TANAKA
There could be a twist
Yeah we never know
I was going with "Hamada" first
Yeah me too
Here's the answer
Yama-chan, try to change your target
Just change it
It's Hamada-san
Matsumoto-san
A. Matsumoto
See? I told you!
How do you-
There you go
That was unexpected
Zaki-san is incredible
Yeah
I can't get one right...
You're way too much behind us
Why is this happening?
No luck on this one too
If Fujiwara is told "TV host", who would come to his mind?
Q394. Who comes to Fujiwara's mind
if someone says "TV host"?
A TV host...
This one has to be...
I wonder if Yoshimoto will censor me for this
Alright
I'm getting it
Reveal your answers
Mino Monta-san
Mino Monta
MATSUMOTO
HAMADA
YAMA
ZAKI
ENDO
TANAKA
Mino Monta-san
Oh, all of us
Everyone
We all wrote the same
Alright!
Everyone the same
But I have a kind of bad feeling about it
'cause Yamazaki is with us
Come on, give me a break
You're right
This just happened to pop in our minds so clearly
Right...
But I think he's gonna say Sekiguchi Hiroshi
Here's the answer
Sekiguchi Hiroshi-san
A. Sekiguchi Hiroshi
Holy crap, you were right
You're kidding me!
Look at this...
Are you for real?!
That's a bit creepy...
He was right, it was Sekiguchi-san...
It means it's no good to write the same as Yama-chan
Must be that
Agreed
...Huh?
Is it my fault?
Well...
It was always your fault since the first time you were here
I mean, on Gaki
Wasn't it since the second time?
Are you trying to justify yourself?
Which food will Fujiwara eat by adding mayonnaise to it?
Q415. Which food will Fujiwara eat
by adding mayonnaise to it?
Reveal your answers
CROQUETTE
FRIED
SHRIMP
OKONO-
MIYAKI
I guess...
SALAD
He doesn't give a feeling of being healthy...
Of course he gives no healthy feeling
Yeah I guess
Salad?!
Mayo? Ehhh...
Uhm...
Potato tempura
A. Potato tempura
Tempura... with potatoes?
Dude...
Did he just say "potato tempura"?!
Never heard of it!
Satsuma-imo
note: a type of fried sweet potato
Everyone calls them satsuma-imo, geez
I know, right?
Yeah that's right
Do you think he's actually confusing them?
If that's so, wouldn't it be weird he'd eat em with mayo?
Guess you're right
I have no idea though
Potato tempur---
Never seen it
Me neither
Nope
Yeah...
I'm having them tonight
We'll see then
Can you take a bite? They're hard...
In how many seconds can Fujiwara wear a bra?
Q447. In how many seconds can Fujiwara
wear a bra?
...On himself, right?
Oh, yes
Yeah should be so
On himself
I bet he's going to hook it from the front and then twist it
Oh, is that so?
Normally anyone would go for that one
No doubt about it
Doing it from behind would be a real burden
You're right
Alright, I've got this
Come on
Woah, that's fast
Yeah I think that's too fast
Reveal your answers
I don't think he's going to be that flustered in every situation
note: 秒 = seconds
But it could be his hands won't reach
It could happen, couldn't it?
Maybe the hooks won't fit
Please try to show us in how many seconds you can wear a bra
Wha- wait...
Your clothes, please
What a body
He's pretty fat
He's got boobs, he needs that bra
Right
Ok now, ready, set, go!
Woah, you were right on that
Just what is this guy?
Oh!
See?
He figured that out...
Why is he so good at it?
Shit, it has passed quite a lot of time
It may be close to what Yama-chan wrote
It could be, who knows
For the first time
This part is taking time
What just happened?!
One second!
What the hell!
A miracle
Incredible
Amazing!
This is really something
Even the fact he knew how to do it
Yeah, he knew it well
Here comes another
Manager Orita was dumped by a girl and is feeling down
Which phrase will Fujiwara use to comfort him?
Comfort him?
Q481. Manager Orita was dumped by a girl and is feeling
down. Which phrase will Fujiwara use to console him?
What the hell
Ok, I have it
Reveal your answer
"JUST DO YOUR
BEST AT WORK"
"IT HAPPENS"
"THERE ARE LOTS
OF OTHER BEAUTIFUL
PEOPLE OUT THERE"
"IT'S NOT LIKE
THERE'S ONLY
ONE WOMAN"
MATSUMOTO
HAMADA
ENDO
YAMA
ZAKI
TANAKA
"DON'T WORRY!
MORE THAN
THAT, FOCUS
ON YOUR JOB"
I may got this right
Let's just see his new mini-sketch
Yes
Here's the answer
I've been dumped...
What?
I was dumped
You were?
Yes
Don'--- I mean, it's okay
It's o--- oka--- I mea--
Isn't it good? I mean, huh...
"Isn't it good?"
There are even better chicks out there
Such an unreliable senpai...
Isn't it better off this way?
It's good, you can find an even better one
Right?
Orita
Do your best
Orita...
It'll be okay
"Do your best" he says
It's alright
He sent him off again
He did it again
When it starts getting long he kicks him away
This one is complicated
He said a lot of things
Yeah...
No no, he said it, this time for sure he said it
It's difficult to judge what he said
A. "There are even better girls out there,
so do your best!
I did it!
He sounded kinda tired
Yeah, worn out
Well
At this point, yeah
After failing all these times
But you know, this might won't be part of the final cut
'cause we're all tired
Even though he came this far!
Exactly
What the heck!
It's like the 480th question!
You should have thought over your answers
But that's... you know I mean... It's his fault, right?
After this
It's finally time for the last question!!
No way, no way
It was you
If Fujiwara would get plastic surgery on his face
What would he change?
Q496, If Fujiwara would undergo a facial plastic surgery
what would he change?
This part of him made me feel uneasy even through the monitor
For real?
Reveal your answers
MOUTH
CREASED
EYELID
MOUTH
It has to be this one
Creased eyelid?
NOSE
EYES
Most likely
His eye, huh...
Here's the answer
If you have to undergo a facial plastic surgery
What would you change?
I'd have my nose lifted up
A. Nose
You got it
He'd be weirdly balanced if he gets such nose
It's like having
an European doorknob
on a Japanese house,
it just feels weird
Oh geez
The last one
Really?
We did it!
I'm exhausted
This really is the last one
I had enough
Here's the 500th question
Finally
Between the lines Fujiwara never actually said
Which is the cliché line he'd like to say for once?
What the hell is that?
Q500. Between the lines Fujiwara never actually said
which is the cliché line he'd like to say for once?
The 500 questions which extended for a long time
Are finally welcoming the last one
And the color of weariness is painted all over their faces
But in the end...
Who will be the victorious one?
I see...
That's what you thought...
Reveal your answers
"I LOVE YA!!"
"I'M SORRY BUT
I HAVE A WIFE"
"DON'T WORRY
ABOUT ME,
JUST KEEP
ON MOVING ON"
"PLEASE,
NOW, GO !!"
"YOU'D JUST
GET BURNED
BY LOVING ME"
TANAKA
ENDO
HAMADA
YAMA
ZAKI
MATSUMOTO
"Don't worry about me, just keep on moving on"
I wonder what happened
I feel like he aspires to be in such scene
Here's the answer
Which will it be?
Who knows
Maybe "I love ya"...
Maybe "I want to make love to you", I'm sorry...
A. "I want to make love to you"
He said "I'm sorry" at the end
He said it so clearly at the end
"I'm sorry"
"I want to make love to you"
With this, our 500 questions quiz has come to an end
Ok
With that being said
We'll now announce the winner
Of the Manager Fujiwara's 500 things QUIZ
ANNOUNCING THE RESULTS
The winner is Hamada Masatoshi!
Winner
Hamada Masatoshi
Congratulations!
You've scored 61 points?!
He surely did
He guessed it right a lot of times
Yeah you're right
The central display was always flashing in red
It was, it was
Yamazaki-san you are really something
Yeah that's impressive
One point is impressive
At this point is even more regrettable the fact you just scored one
That's right
Can't we just pretend I didn't get that one right?
We can't do that, so...
Can't we have my score pixelated on screen and make it look as if I didn't get it right?
Why are you saying such stupid bullshit?
Come on, don't say it's bullshit!
How did you came up which such bullshit?
Don't say such things on TV!
Looks like the winner is Hamada-san
Translation, subtitles & encoding by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
Oh, is that so? Thanks so much
I'm sorry
Yeah, really...
Thanks for having me for such long time
Find all my other subtitled clips on my wordpress:
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
I'm sorry there were so many predictable answers
And thank you for everything
Yes
Please keep on working hard from now on too
I'm sorry
Support my translations by clicking like on my Facebook page:
facebook.com/shionnotsukai
I'm really sorry
SOME AD I WAS TOO LAZY TO REMOVE, HERE'S MORE SPAM:
WWW.SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
WWW.FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
WWW.TWITTER.COM/FGRNDNoises
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT TRANSLATION BY A FAN FOR OTHER FANS
SHOW SUPPORT BY LIKING / FOLLOWING ETC. ETC.