So everybody
Today, we will be playing Jiji-nuki again, which was highly praised
*Jiji-nuki is a tweaked version of Baba-nuki (Old maid)
-Endo should remember this game right
-Yeah, Endo lost twice in a row last time
To be honest, I hate this game
Endo, you're having the same hair color as Megumi
You mean Megumi-san from Hiruobi!...
-Well yeah...
-Yeah it's the same as Megumi-san
You better turn around and face the camera to say it again
For having the same hair color as Megumi? Is it necessary?
Well, my hair color is the same as Megumi-san
No way, not at all
The highly praised Gaki Jiji-nuki
Each card has a different question on it
The rule is the same as Old maid,
you win if you have no more cards left
But if you lose, you'll need to perform
based on the instructions of the last card
So Tanaka will be hosting the game
Bunny-chan come on!!
Here comes the Bunny-chan
Is it the same girl as last time?
Yes
I see, so it's the same
Stop staring at her
Please stop it
This is not how you play Jiji-nuki
*Jiji-nuki literally means "Remove the old man"
Let's start by deciding the dealer
I don't remember this at all
So Endo with be the dealer to start the game
At this stage, please draw a card, which will be the joker
Hamada-san can you pick a card for us?
Then put it over here without looking at it
Get off dude!!
This is making me nervous, I really hate this game...
Endo please show it to the camera only
Okay, we won't look at it
You can't look at it too, Endo
-I won't remember it anyway
-Of course you will
-Let's start
-Can I distribute the cards?
Yes please
What are you laughing at?
Wait, what happened to you?
You're in a cranky mood today
-You're right
-What happened?
-Let's try to be kind here
-You're right
The first theme is
Vulgar imitation
No, no, no way
Some of the characters are not vulgar at all
Mine are all vulgar though...
-Anyone have any pairs?
-Yes, here it is
Well, glad that this character is discarded
Inakawa Junji
-No one else?
-Nope
Who should go first? Speak dude!!
-Why are people being so unfriendly today?
-No that's your fault
-There was an awkward silence
-Yeah it's kind of Tanaka's fault
Tell us who is the first player to start dude
Hey!!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!!!
Hurry up, you idiot
So please draw a card from my hand
Who is it?
Well, this is a difficult character to imitate too
Nagashima Shigeo
This is stressing me out
Let me see, no pairs
I wonder which character is the joker
Yeah
Not even close
I have tons of cards
I'm the same too
Oh, I see
They are paired up?
So it's Kuro-chan
Tanaka looks like he's about to cry
Anyway, these are paired up
Thank you very much
The game starts off with
the cards getting paired one after another
These are paired up too
Glad that this character is discarded,
it's a difficult character to imitate right?
Sanshiro Komiya
This is a difficult one right?
Thank you very much
-Here it is
-This is relieving
Hanzawa Naoki
I didn't know he's here
This is such a high-calorie character
It's like two Tuna-Mayo Onigiri
Endo why don't you just do the imitation
as the camera goes "syuuu" and fades out
-Just leave it to the editor
-Edit it as if I lost the game?
Well it's possible but...
Syuuu
No way, no way, let's play this properly
However, here starts the nightmare of infinite loop
-Tanaka is left with one card for a long time
-Yes I am
It's difficult to pair up that last card right
Which one do you suggest?
Suggest?
I suggest the middle one
The middle one?
No way!!!
What's wrong with this guy?
(Matsumoto could have paired up if he took Housei's advice)
What should I do with this?
It's back again
This card is going round and round
Kitano Takeshi
Some cards never move, and some goes round and round
If it's back again, this means that...
...it's back again
Rola
It's been quite a while though
Please be something I have
It's back
This is the same card "Kitano Takeshi" but from Takana
It's back again
What's going on with that card
So no one was able to pair it up
Let's see if it's coming back...
It's back
We're talking about this card right?
This card is always coming back
Yeah it's always coming back
Come on, who is holding the other one
It's back again
What's happening?
This card is always coming
Wait a second? This means that...
Maybe the cards just shifted by chance
No, no, no way
The card was passed round and it's still here!
Something is strange about this right?
Probably someone is holding on to it
Maybe the cards just shifted at a different timing
Okay, yeah I see
Thank you Matsumoto-san
-I thought this must be the joker
-Me too!
I thought it must be Takeshi-san
Yeah it came back many times, but...
How dare you say it came
(same pronunciation as Kitano)
You should never say that
Yeah, it should be Kitano-san
He said it's "Kitano"
This scene itself is enough for today's show right
It's "Kitano"?
You're annoying man
Anyway, Hamada wins
It's surprising to know he's not the joker
I already started to do simulations
I thought it must be him
However, the infinite loop never ends
Maybe Tanaka is going to finish
It's not finishing yet
Sadly, it's not finishing yet
Then it's probably Endo
Let me pair up this last card
Please let me win!
It's not finishing yet
Please!
Give me a second
Which card is the joker, seriously
-This one
-We all know the remaining cards right?
Yeah I've been doing simulations too
Maybe I'll pick this one
I hate this nervous atmosphere, please let me finish this
It's back again
The card IKKO has turned full circle back to Matsumoto
Who is that?
I thought this person was dead already?
No he's not
It's you again?
This always comes back
Maybe it shifted by chance...
This is taking forever
And after 20 minutes
The person that wins after Hamada is...
Here it comes, here it comes!
Antonio Inoki
So this is how it is
I thought it must be this person at one time
Endo wins too
In addition, Matsumoto also...
I told you!
I told you!!
Matsumoto wins
So IKKO is the joker right?
Wait a second...
No way
So Tanaka will take my card
This means that...
Matsumoto wins
and if it pairs up with my card, I'll be winning too
Please don't
Let's see what happens
You need to do the imitation immediately
-Ok
-Right after you lose
Please don't, please don't!
Paired...with nothing
Yes! Yesssss! All right!
So if Yama-chan can pair it up...
Get prepared for the imitation Tanaka
Wait a moment please...
Yeah you have to be prepared
It must be one of them anyway
Ok, pick one Yama-chan
Let's see
Oh, God. Please!
Can he make it?
Let's see
Oh, God. Please!
Can he make it?
Yes! Yesssss!
Housei wins
Which means that the joker is...
is IKKO-san
How come~~~
This must be a joke~~~
I am so surprised~~~
How come~~~
Please behave yourself
Please behave yourself~~~
It's you!!
He's worried about you
It took a long time
Well yeah
But just as Matsumoto-san said
Endo you should have did it right at the beginning
You should say "let me do all of it please!!"
Yeah you really should have did it
That's just awkward, Hamada-san
Well yeah, because it's Downtown
And he moved from a thin house, to a thicker house
Well yeah, it is a thin and tall house
But there is nothing I can do to help, that's a 35 years mortgage
Let's go for a second round
The theme for the next Jiji-nuki...
Is to create a XXX associated to the title on the cards
What's this?
I have no idea
So each card has some words on it
And the theme for this round
Is to create a nursery rhyme
-This is awful
-That's ridiculous
So the words on the card,
will be the title of the nursery rhyme
The titles are completely random
And use it to create a nursery rhyme
This is tough
But on the contrary, this means none is better than any other
What is paired up?
"Castella cake shop" is paired up
"Castella cake shop" sounds easy man
"Castella cake shop" sounds easy right?
-I got it
-What is it
Taraxacum's adventure
So the plant that flies far away right
I got another one
Seriously?
Dango (sweet rice dumpling) under the sunset
I can't even imagine that
You're so lucky Tanaka
The title for the nursery rhyme is
Bamboo shoots on the hill
The dealer Endo will start the game
Tanaka is already about to win
Yeah because 2 pairs were matched
-You don't have any pairs?
-Yeah, I have tons of cards
I'm probably gonna lose this time
But Yama-chan also didn't pair up anything right
No pairs at all
I already came up with a nursery rhyme for "Castella cake shop"
That is such a good title
You have tons of cards man
I got it
The Jizo statue that farted
Well, this also seems to be a good title
I don't think so
I got it
-Spanking
-That's quite simple
I got it too
The school of Earthworms
This is also a good title right?
Yeah, I thought it's a easy one too
Different from the first round
The cards are paired up in a fast pace
The snacks samba dance
And Housei's good luck continues
I got them all
Amazing
-Tengu’s festival
-I never saw that card
You're done?
Housei wins
Following Housei, Tanaka also...
Thank you so much
Tanaka wins
Just let Endo do it
In addition, Hamada also...
-Really?
-Seriously?
Hamada wins
And this means that...
I'll win if this card matches
Please! Seriously, please!!
Wait a second, wait a second
GIve me a break, this is stressing me out!!
This is too tough
Try to be a creator
This demands a lot of artistic sense!!
This is going to reveal your artistic sense dude!!
Come on!!
Please take the card
It must be one of them
Please, please!
GOD DAMN!!
It didn't match?
That's a chance for you
One more pair and I'm done right
It must be one of the 3 cards
Please! I always think this is something perfect for Endo to do
I really think this suits Endo
I want to listen to Endo's nursery rhyme
I have nothing to do with nursery rhyme
Please! Just let it be Endo! Please!
You guys are annoying!!
Choose one
You should be able match this right
I'll choose it!
Why can't I see through it...
Senpai is being desperate
Ok let's go!
Why can't I see through it!!
Please---!!
Oh yes!!
The Onigiri caught a cold
This means that...
Give me a second...a nursery rhyme...
Matsumoto wins
What's the joker?
So this is paired up
And this is the joker
Bamboo shoots on the hill
Over here, over there
All over the hill
-This is shit
-Wow, wow, that's amazing
There is no space to walk through
-What the heck!!
-Over here, over there
-Too long dude
-All over the hill
I did it
No, you didn't
-I cleared that with ease
-No not at all
That was with none artistic sense
Nice song, nice song!
There's no space to walk through?
Yeah, because the bamboo shoots are all over the hill
That was tough
Let's go for the third round
Spin the roulette to decide the dealer
So it's Housei-san
Choose the joker first...
It's already chosen
Joker is already chosen
Oh yeah, for this time...
Hey dude...
What's going on with you dude?
Umm, the rule changes a bit...for the third round...
And I just forgot about it
Excuse me everyone,
for this time...
-The joker is already chosen?
-Yes
And the theme is...
Batsu game
Just let Hamada do it
Why man? It should be Endo right
You came this far with reaction performances anyway...
Then it should be Tanaka right
He've been performing reactions since he was a kid
Batsu game immediately after you lose
Please guess which card is the joker together this time
You only have 2 cards left
Yeah, but it's still hard to tell
Yama-chan is the dealer right? You can go first
You're really lucky Endo
What's this?
No way, no way!
What's that
It won't be able to control itself!
*The card says "A sweet bite from Tosa (dog)"
What does that mean?
What does that mean!! This is pissing me off
It can't control itself?
This is just absolutely impossible
*The card says "Human-sized flash cotton"
Are the staffs idiots?
What the heck is this
While the members are terrified by the Batsu games...
Please! Please let me win!
I got it!
Thank god!
I seriously hate those electric things
*The card says "50 electric machines"
The terrifying cards are getting less and less
Of course this is out
I thought it's definitely a fake one too
I actually even wanted to do this
*The card says "A sweet bite from Tosa (dog)"
-If it's possible
-Yeah, if it's possible
I think this is out too
What the heck is this?
Do you need to read it that close?
I can't even understand this
*The card says "Cannonball in your mouth"
What the heck is this?
Umm?
-No idea right?
-No idea at all
-Is it dangerous?
-It's way too dangerous
Well, Hamada is the one to do it, so never mind
I'm not doing it
Human-sized flash cotton
I thought this is impossible too
Hamada-san?
Yes, please take it
-He's good at this
-Hamada is going to win
What's going on with this guy!
Hamada wins
What's going on with this guy
I got it too
Billiards headshot
Will definitely be dead for this
I thought that's possible, because the staffs are idiots
Both of the cards are horrible
For real!?
*The card says "Earthworms in the nose"
Can we not do this? Seriously
He's talking about this right?
It's his partner right?
Can we seriously not do this?
I hope they are combi
This is...
*The card says "Earthworms in the nose"
This is going to make you sick
Must be the same card!
Which means if I can get this right...
This one?
This is the one that make you sick right!
Oh yes!!
Earthworms in the nose
Matsumoto wins
Well that's also a good news though
It's good that the card is discarded
I'll win if this card pairs up too
I hope you will win
Nope
No?
Give me a break
So now it's Endo's chance
Yeah
Cocorico is so weak
It looks like it is Cocorico's TV show now
*Golden Legend is an ended TV show hosted by Cocorico
It's like Golden Legend 2
*The card says "Cannonball in your mouth"
It didn't match?
Then it's now Yama-chan's chance
Hopefully Endo got the card
It's quite possible
Yeah so a 50% possibility
Draw the card
This is getting interesting
So if this matches...
Please!
I got it!
Housei wins
This card makes no sense, so I thought it must be joker
Battle between Cocorico
Golden Legend 2
Wait a moment...
Maybe this will be the last round
Are you ready Tanaka-san?
Wait a second...
-I'll go for this
-This is nervous
How come!!
-Really?
-Seriously?
Here comes your chance
Endo know which is joker right?
Yeah, this is terrible
This is just terrible...
What a fight for Cocorico
It's Miracle Type
*Miracle Type is another TV show hosted by Cocorico
You're just saying the title of their shows
Yeah, it's somehow embarrassing
Who will be playing the Batsu game, Endo or Tanaka?
Let's go!
One, two...
Oh yes!
Tanaka wins
So the joker is "Chinese foot massage"
It's quite vulgar, so I thought it won't be joker
This guy looks completely different from what I thought
He's young right
His eyes are going mad
-Hey Endo, stay put
-OUCH OUCH OUCH!!!
This really hurts
These masseurs have no mercy
His eyes are going completely mad
Yeah he's going mad
Hamada's eyes are also going mad
Both of them are going mad
Thank you very much
Good for you
Good for your health