HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S TRAINING SCHOOL!!
Vice Principal!
Yes!
They're still not here?
Vice Principal
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Principal
Hamada Masatoshi
I thought they would be here by now
Is that so?
Good morning!
Broadcasted the other day "Hot Blooded!! Hamada's Training School"
Principal Hamada's teachings with an overflowing emotions of love got a huge reaction!
And so for today as well!!
We're ready!
Good morning!
Good morning!!
There's different members today!
There was a bit of minor changes
Ah, I see...
In regards to the Principal
We've gathered only people who hold the highest respect for him!
If you guy's aren't doing this with a sense of death then you will die!
Exactly!
Look alive today!
Yes!
Please act like your alive today!
Don't die!
Yes!
Even if something happens
In order to not reveal it
You all signed the wavers right!?
Without looking at the document you signed it!!
By the way Fujiwara
Did you watch the last episode?
I got a DVD of the last one
I would have been happier if I didn't see it
What do you mean by that?
All that Terror....
Not with terror....
There's nothing to be afraid about!
It was really scary...
It was an extremely heart-warming episode!
The DVD doesn't show it that well
According to one theory It's being washed away by Kabukicho
Kabukicho is a red-light district in Shinjuku
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S TRAINING SCHOOL!!
Shall we get started everyone!
Yes!
Alright Vice Principal Matsumoto!
What are we doing?
First up!
PRINCIPAL RUGBY!!
To explain Princiapl Rugby...
We'll be using this Principal ball
What are you laughing about?
The principal...
Sorry!
With the Principal ball
What are you laughing at!?
Because it's the principal!
You must tenderly and daringly win with it!
In order to not forget about your love for the principal!
The trial of passing the principal rugy ball between the 8 of them tenderly starts!
Is there anyone experienced in playing rugby?
Yes, I am!
Let's start!
This is good huh?
They're really not looking at the principals face huh
Go for a try!
Alright, Line up!
I said it was rugby!
That wasn't bold at all!
It's no good if you don't look at my face when you throw it!
Haranishi you didn't do rugby did you!?
Yes I did!
Is that so?
I want bigger throws!
Did it startle you too much?
You let go of the principal!
You can't let go of the principal in the last minute!
Here you go principal!
It's burning!
This won't give burns
Let's move on to the next one
HOT!
Shall we do another round of rugby?
It came out principal!
Hot water leaked out!
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S TRAINING SCHOOL!!
When your throwing me make sure your looking at me
Don't you think you should kiss when you throw him?
Wanna try kissing it?
How do I put it...
Your not really conveying your emotions of love
Kiss it then throw it from now on
READY!?
That's good!
He's looking strong!
You like the principal right!?
Good! Give him a kiss!
Good! You like the principal!
You understand the principals love right?
Alright!
That's no good!
Right there!
Yes like a gun!
It really hurts when you fire it right at me!
That was no good huh!
If just two of them do it it'll be easy to understand for everyone
You've got that right
Alright go FUJIWARA!
You want us to still kiss him right?
Do it with a better tempo this time!
Do it with the feeling of "This is our Youth!"
You can have an accident later!!
Alright Lets do this!
This is no good!
There's a drop kick rule in rugby!
Sit down
Put down your head!
Getting hit directly...
Gaki no tsukai #1218
2nd Hamada's Training School
Subbed by DCsubs
For more gaki no tsukai content
reddit.com/r/gakinotsukai
gaki-no-tsukai.com
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S TRAINING SCHOOL!!
So Vice Principal!
Next up
We're gonna be going with your body!!
Body?
"Beach Scuba" body movements
Body movements?
You all enjoy scuba diving right?
On this beach, your going to use your body and go scuba diving
Until the principal accepts it your all gonna have fun scuba diving!
With your body
This is pretty bad huh
You got that right
Someones making a profit off this
For whatever reason I thought this was good in the beginning
They're all taking pictures together
They're all gathering like theres bait
It's by no means done yet huh
I still don't get it
I don't get it
Where are you going!!
Where are you going!?
GET BACK HERE!!
What was that!?
That was all terrible!!
We intended to do this for 40 mins in the plan!
You guys definitely couldn't pull that off!!
Haranishi should do it solo
Do your solo Haranishi!
Man this pisses me off!
How is it?
Haranishi is pretty good huh?
That was good Haranishi!
Yamazaki!!
What was that just now?
Join him Iwao!!
Are they friends?
Acquaintances?
Haranishi!!
What the hell is that?
I really can't understand this one
Who swims like that!?
He's a fish!
That's pretty interesting!
Tanaka!!
Find something original alright!
Believe it's your own world!!
I don't need Tanaka!
I don't need Yamazaki!
I don't need Iwao!
As I thought, This is what it comes down to
He's not a scuba diver!
But a fish!
He's in a fish tank!
I'll get the tea
Barley Tea!!
Haranishi
Thank you!
That was really good!
If you work this hard
you can drink Barley Tea as well!!
If you work this hard you can drink Barley Tea too!!
Yes!
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S TRAINING SCHOOL!!
What now Vice-principal?
For the next one we'll be using this drum can!
From now on the principal will be in this drum can!
With these corn dog sticks
Your going to stab your favourite spot
If you happen to stab the principal in the can you'll be punished!!
If you get it then be careful alright?
As planned, The Principal is going to standby in the drum can!
Just what on earth is going to happen!?
Good luck Principal!
So, We'll go in order!!
Everyone take one alright!
The Principal is looking!
He's not looking! Hurry up and do it!
Hurry up and get with it!
This is bad!
Going from the front is really bad!
I guess that might be true!
Fujimon get's it!
I'm safe!
This is what will happen to you if you manage to stab the principal!
Try stabbing me
Stabbing you?
Someone holding one try stabbing me!
It's fine just try stabbing me
Nothing will happen just try stabbing me!
Just try stabbing me
This is just my hunch from being with him for such a long time but
The principal is a pretty rotten guy!
He's a pretty rotten guy!
Only an idiot!
This is pretty unexpected so you'll sure to be fine!
Principal!
Shall we try this one once more?
Once more?
Your starting to look like The Phantom of the Opera!
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S TRAINING SCHOOL!!
Should we try putting someone in there?
What if you all
Tried getting in there!
All of you get in!
The principal will stab you!
That's a good idea!!
Isn't that really dangerous!?
Let's not do it!
Just wait a second!
Let's just try getting in there for once
All we want to do is try it once for now
Inaba try getting in there
Eh?
First try getting in there
That's....
Hurry up... It's gonna get dark
Good Luck Inaba!
Let's try to keep this up
Fujimon you get in as well!
Scary isn't it!
Vice-Principal we can probably fit more in
Seems like we still can
Fujihara get in
Cmon get in
Yamazaki!
Why!?
It's so scary!
You've got enough room for this right?
Like you can run around inside
No... We can't run away!
This is seriously dangerous!
What is this? Hot water?
No way!
I haven't stabbed you yet!
Oh, You can use this
HOT!
STOP! STOP!!!
OVERCOME THE SUMMER!
STOP!!!
Have you overcome the summer?
YES!
Can you overcome it!?
DO YOU WANNA BE THE PRINCIPAL!?
YES!
YOU WANNA BE THE PRINCIPAL RIGHT!?
Alright... Be the Principal!
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S TRAINING SCHOOL!!
So what's next Vice-Principal!
Next is....
Well, You're gonna keep moving without stopping
It's the Principal's favourite
The principals favourite "Don't Stop! Don't Stop!"
In other words the episode where they had to keep moving without stopping
Will be happening in this episode!
What's wrong?
What's wrong with these 3?
Well for this one...
We have experienced this before...
Honestly...
I've seen hell
That was in a studio
This time we're going to try doing it under a clear sky
We're gonna be doing it in the sand as well
Your going to appeal to yourselves
You'll be useful after you go out to society
Let's go from Endo!!
Just by myself?
Until the Principal's plan says so
If the plan is to do it endlessly then your going to do it endlessly
Alright, Let's do it!
Make sure your all watching!
In order to not make it the same thing over and over
Make sure to throw in some difference
That's good!
You don't wanna bear your past!
Go find something new in the sand!
I feel like you shouldn't be standing in the same spot
A battle with your past!
Your bearing your past!
Find a new Endo!
Try and find a new Endo!
There's still much more to come!
This isn't the withdrawal of Endo after all!
He's running away!
He's like an infinite battery
Show us a new Endo!
Endo Complete!
Yamazaki!
Here Endo!
Drink some barley tea!
Last time Yamazaki took the most damage after it all
While we're looking at Yamazaki
Continue with him Tanaka!
They're doing the same movements
Your being pulled a bit!
So that you both aren't pulled by each other
Keep it up Fujimon!!
Yes!
Ah! That's good!
Something new!
Yamazaki is already...
Yamachan can't move at all...
Haranishi!
Haranishi is already showing us his true worth!
Yamazaki Complete!
FUJIWARA is pretty good huh!
Haranishi's got quite a large vocabulary!
Iwao!
Iwao... Go find something new!
Iwao...
That's different for sure!
Tanaka Done!
Haranishi's vocabulary...
Inomoto!
Move! Move!
Please look at Haranishi's vocabulary!
It's everlasting!
His never ending vocabulary is crazy huh!
Fujimon is getting there but he can still move it
Fujimon is moving a lot more than I thought isnt he?
Fujimon's been going for quite a while too!
Iwao is completely devoted to one side huh!
Fujimons good!
Fujimon's doing really well!
Look at Haranishi's sense of stability
Iwao Done!
He's started to use the sand!
Inamoto done!
Is he going to pull out some drastic moves from here on out?
Fujimon done!
Fujimon's world!
It's Fujimon's world!
A new world!
Fujimon done!
That was really something!
What's with you?
What's with you standing by yourself?
Because I didn't hear my name called
I'm still standing here
Can you do it?
I don't know!
Then let's try it!
Try doing it alone!
Fujiwara go!!
Fujiwara Done!
This has really become something huh!
Hey.. Can you guys overcome summer!?
When I look at you now...
It was the best when you were all doing stuff!
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S TRAINING SCHOOL!!
Subbed by DCSubs
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S TRAINING SCHOOL!!
The principals overflowing love is still not over!
I'm extremely sorry!
No good!
The principals voice resounds on the sand in the middle of summer!