Translation, subtitles & encoding by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
More clips? Subscribe to Shion (ガキの使い用)!
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Emergency Plan
Ok, Everybody
Yes!
Today we'll have an emergency plan
An emergency, is it?
It is an emergency, yes
We don't usually deal with emergencies in this show, uh?
Yeah!
Excuse me one second
Looks like you haven't left gaki after all!
＊This episode aired shortly after the "Yamazaki vs Moriman" show, Matsumoto is making fun of Yamazaki leaving gaki-no-tsukai after his humiliation on that show
I'm not leaving, what the hell are you talking about!
Cocorico Endo has been infected by a mysterious virus and is now resting.
So, the emergency plan
You know, there was the "Yamazaki vs Moriman" show recently
Yama-chan, do you remember there was a little match while you were resting?
Yeah, I remember
Of course you remember
That was the funniest moment of the whole show!
No, no, no, no way! Not true!
That one during my break, right?
Yes
Yeah, I remember
With Dynamite Shikkoku-san
Yes
Dynamite Shikkoku-san, uh...
Yes, yes, Shikkoku, Shikkoku, yes!
That was...
After that on my room a lot of people came
You know, asking some questions about him for the audience
Like "Who really is this guy?"..?
Unironically?
Yeah...
For real?
Dynamite Shikoku is a masked wrestler who appeared in "Yamazaki vs Moriman"
He fought with his rival, Escargot-man
But sadly he ended up being defeated due a muscle strain;
His popular "SHIKKOKU SHIKKOKU" performance had the audience go wild, though
Today we'll draw near Dynamite Shikkoku's true colors!
So, let's just call him here
Here's the superstar born from the raging waves of the Naruto strait, Dynamite Shikkoku! Please come!
＊The Naruto strait is a famous strait between the Awaji island and the Shikoku island, famous for its whirlwinds.
Good morning!
Pro Wrestler
Dynamite Shikoku
Do you usually dress up this way?
Normally yeah, I wear this...
With a suit?
A suit, uh...
He's pretty small, isn't him?
You think so?
But really you know... this...
Being called here to join "gaki no tsuKA" is really...
Uh?!
"Tsuka"? Is "gaki no tsuka-i", you know!
It's a pleasure to be here
The pleasure is ours
You weren't in the middle of a training, right? Is it ok for you to be here with us now?
Well, I already trained for about 40 minutes this morning at five
So short!
40 minutes?!
Yeah and I went back to sleep at 6 o'clock
Then why don't you wake up like at 10:00 and have your session until 10:40?
Yeah but you know, waking up at 5 A.M. it's like a rule for me, like a feeling I have to grant
So, I'm counting on you today
That "wake up" and "rule" made quite a messy sentence
＊Shikoku said "okite" (to wake up) and "okite" (a rule, a law) in the same sentence. Matsumoto remarks this.
Shikoku-san, excuse me but
How old are you?
I don't really talk much about it but
I'm 33 years old
Apparently Dynamite Shikoku is 33 years old
Excuse me, for how long have you been watching our "Gaki no Tsukai" show?
Uhmm...
Well it's a bit embarrassing but...
I've always been watching it since the third time it aired!
For real?
The third time he said...
Yeah yeah
16 years ago!
Yamazaki started appearing after around the second time, right?
Am I right?
Yeah...
I was right huh?
Uh...
He just said he's 33!
Dynamite Shikoku refers to Yamazaki (37 years, older than him) without honorifics.
I started watching it shortly after you came in
You said you are 33 years old
But I'm 37 years old, you know so...
He's older...
Well, it's not a problem! Treat him nicely!
Well, yeah, ok, ok
It's completely fine to me
Excuse me Shikoku-san, but why are we here right now
Yeah, is this zone related to you somehow?
Yes, you see, actually...
There's also a training gym near this area...
Is that so?
It's a place where I enjoy go even by myself
I wanted to show it to you
Oh, I see, that's why!
Come on, let's go
Ok, let's go
Which place related to you are we going to see today first?
We're first going to a set meal restaurant I used to go a lot to
You know,
It's been a while since I've been there
Really?
Is that a place you used to go to when you just started being a wrestler?
Well, it was when I was 18 years old
When I first came here this was the zone I lived in
It brings back so many memories... this mansion is still here
That's impressive!
They don't builds things like that anymore
You know, back on the old days this was a gym
What was it?
A gym?
It disappeared!
Oh? Is this Dynamite-san's...?
There's no trace of it!
Is it your gy-
What a big discovery, no one would have guessed!
Translation, Subtitles & Encoding by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
www.foregroundnoises.wordpress.com
OLD UPLOADS AVAILABLE HERE:
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
(links in description)
It's over there
"Sankou-en" uh
Looks nice!
"Sankou-en"...
Looks really nice
So it was this kind of place uh
That's the set meal restaurant which took care of Dynamite Shikoku-san since his arrival to Tokyo about ten years ago, the "sankou-en" restaurant
Good morning!
Welcome!!
Good morning
Are we eating there?
Is there a table for us?
Of course, please!
My~, Mite-kun, you grew up so splendidly!
They're the Downtown duo
Mite-kun?
Mite-kun.
Mite-kun...
Like, it's been a lot since I last saw you!
Yeah something like... 10 years I guess
I'm so happy to see you again!
Please take a seat
Please!
Hey pops, where's Kyoko-chan (his daughter) today?
＊Not actually Shikoku's dad/mom. He calls them this way in a friendly / confidential way.
She got married!
So she got married uh...
Yes
There used to be their daughter with them in here
But she got married after all!
You were late!
You're right!
Uh, yeah, I wanted to ask a question to the owner
You do know Shikoku's unmasked face, right?
Have you ever seen it?
Actually no...
I was always like this
He was like this
Oh, is that so?
You've always been wearing that mask since your debut?
Mh, yeah, fundamentally
Damn, it's hot in here today
Excuse me a moment
What?
Is it really okay to do so?
We could barely see your face
Shikoku-san?
So bluntly...
Well, he said it was hot in here
Shikoku-san?
Why did you do that?
Dynamite Shikoku almost shows his face
Sorry, it was so hot I couldn't deal with it
I can endure anything else but not when it's hot
That way you'll eventually end up showing your face
Mama, you attached this for me?
Yes!
What is that?
Well, that's... wh-when was it? Five years?
Maybe five years?
Five or maybe six years ago...
Looks like Dynamite Shikoku released an LP 5 or 6 years ago
I was involved with this association...
Uh...
So like, so my popularity could gradually increase
And so they helped me release this LP
The B-side is friggin' long!
Side A is wrote there, title is:
"In such night, again, alone... will you get your sleep, scumbag?"
You used two pronouns with same meanings in the same sentence!
＊"kimi" and "omae" are both "you", "omae" can be a rude way to adress someone (thus I've translated it "scumbag")
[he points out something wrote on the CD cover, can't see due LQ]
What do you usually eat in here?
Well here I usually uh...
Usually, uh?
Can you see the menu over there?
There's a 450 Yen set meal
Amazing!
So cheap!
I'd like you to have a taste of this 450 Yen menu
Isn't it good!
Nice!
The usual!
A large serving of the usual?
A large serving is...
Make it a Mite-serving!
A Mite-serving, okay!
A Mite-serving for everyone!
Ok, Mite-servings
Thanks as always
Dear, a Mite-serving of the 450 Yen set meal
Coming!
Mite-serving...
You know this restaurant
Is the best for my body
So a large serving alone
Is not enough
So a serving larger than the large one is the mite-serving, with the "mite" took from me, "Dynamite"
That's impressive!
Sorry I kept you waiting!
It's so huge!
Is this the mite-serving?
All of this for just 450 Yen?
Amazing, so cheap!
That's really something!
Isn't it good to enjoy a meal this rich on a restaurant for a cheap price?
It's pretty unusual, don't you think so?
Yeah
Yeah, definitely seeing your point
Eh?
Why are you doing this?
Dynamite Shikoku doesn't show any sign of enjoyment.
Don't you like what you're eating?
It's delicious, really
Oh, yes, I wanted to ask you
That thing
What do you think of the current wrestling panorama? Don't hold back, speak to your heart's content!
Well, let's leave this talk to later, shall we?
Since you've all come here today
Dynamite Shikoku doesn't want to talk about wrestling at all.
You have the worst manners!
Let's take it easy for now    Wait, what have I done?
You're ruining the mood!
Let's just
Let's enjoy this atmosphere for now
Right, right, right
Now I...
You know...
Is something from the past, but...
What did you do when you were a kid?
Uhm, when I was little you say...
I want to know about it
Yeah
Well, you know
I was a pretty mischievous kid back then
Figures
Uh, it's like... like, there's someone that.. .what was it again...
Is there like a ex-teacher or someone like that who you hold dearly in your heart?
Uhm yeah, thinking about it probably there's someone
I think it's the homeroom teacher I had in elementary school
Really?
Elementary School...
His name was Mr. Narutogawa
Mr. Narutogawa?
It has a Shikoku-vibe to it
It's a pretty uncommon name, uh?
Definitely from Shikoku
It's been almost 20 years since I last met him
With Mr. Narutogawa, right?
From your elementary school period, so...
Oh, it's been a while!
What? Isn't it Dynamite-kun!
M-mr. Narutagawa!
Yes!
It's been a while!
It's been a long time!
You've grown quite a lot!
Ex-teacher from his elementary school days:
Hideo Narutogawa
Wh-what are you doing in here?
Why are you..?
I just took the first bullet train from Shikoku this morning
Did someone told him to come here?
Y-yeah, probably
We didn't know either! We've been tricked!
Mr. Narutogawa secretly came all the way from Shikoku to meet Dynamite Shikoku
It was a surprise for us!   just like a prank!
It's like the set of a prank show!
So he was the homeroom teacher back when you were in sixth grade?
Exactly!
So he the teacher you were talking about...
Good to see you again and nice to meet you everyone
Nice to meet you
That's the first time you've seen these guys?
Oh, yes, I never met them before
Dynamite Shikoku's Yearbook
Let's all take a look at his Elementary School Yearbook
Can you tell who am I?
You can tell who I am, right?
He's this one
I can recognize his look
This brings back so many memories!
I wonder if it'll be visible in the camera?
Bottom Right: Around 6th grade of elementary school
His look's the same
Right
You can tell who he is at first glance
But, you already...
Wore a mask?
Well yes, of course
It's the same, right?
Yeah it is
Good you kept it
You know, he wore that all the time just like this
You have been doing such things since then?
Yeah I've had this passion since when I was a kid and I decided that "I want to be a wrestler!" so...
Oh, that's why
Damn, this all brings back so many memories, Teacher!
Yes, you're right
Thanks for being here
What kind of...
Mr Narutogawa, what kind of kid was Shikoku-san back then?
Well...
He's not exactly the type of kid a teacher would remember
Teacher please enough joking around!
You shouldn't say something like that!
But it's good you grew up this much!
But he doesn't remember?!
The Mr. Narutogawa of that period
A letter from his ex-teacher Narutogawa-sensei
Let's read a letter of encouragement from his teacher!
To Dynamite-kun
Because you weren't really a kid who stood out during the elementary school period
What
When you became a pro-wrestler I couldn't believe it was actually that Dynamite-kun I knew
But seeing your current great efforts made me think it was a great thing you became a wrestler
Me too, along with all your classmates, will always be secretly supporting you from Shikoku
So be careful about your physical condition and become a champion as soon as possible!
- Hideo Narutogawa
I'm sorry...
Again, Dynamite Shikoku almost ends up showing his face
Shikoku-san...
Shikoku-san, your face...
Everyone please, take care of him
Oh, of course
Thanks
I'm sorry...
Isn't it good?
Well, everybody, sorry for interrupting you! See you and thanks!
That was the Dynamite Shikoku showing tears of emotions from the emotional-reunion
The emotional reunion has ended, and now coming next...
Next one will be
Yes?
A place I've been going weekly since middle school at least 2-3 times
Oh, I see, something like that
I see, I see
Ah, excuse me a second
Mr Misawa!
Hi!
Hey Shikoku-san! Good morning!
It's been a while
Your hair grew quite a lot!
Guess you're right
Maybe tomorrow or the day after tomorrow I'll come here to cut them
I'll be waiting!
Sure
Keep on cleaning Misawa, won't ya?
Yes, yes
What a dick!
You're actually a moron, aren't you?
You speak a bit too much
That's because I'm a wrestler
I have to keep my image
Yeah but that just before...
Weren't you a bit harsh?
Well, you see...
We wrestler are stronger than others
Oh, it's right there!
What was that "wrestler are stronger" thing?
Yakitori Shop "Tori-Hana"
'morning!
Welcome!!
Hey!
Hey boss!
Welcome! I'll be waiting for you, Shikoku-san!
Good morning, excuse us
Take a seat!
Can we?  - Of course!
Ok then
Woah, that's amazing
That's really impressive!
Ah, this
A calendar!
Yeah
There's also a photo of him with the owner!
Oh, right!
We've been friends for a long time
Yeah it sure does look like it
The owner is doing the SHIKKOKU move too!
Hey!
You use to do it too, uh?
Yeah, a lot
Woah, that handprint's pretty huge!
I know right? It's quite large
Eh-! It's huge!
Uh?!
Yours is not that big!
Please, take a seat, Matsumoto
Will you?
Is...
Is this yours?
Of course it's mine
Was it Christmas Eve? I just went and BAM
Shikoku-san, you sure go to Shikoku a lot I see...
Yeah...
Uh? What do you mean?
On the calendar: "Dynamite Shikoku's memo: Red circles mean I'm currently back home in Shikoku!
That's really a lot of times
Maybe too many
I thought you went back to Shikoku pretty rarely
It's full of circles!
Yeah there are a lot
Is that a period in which you go back home for a while?
Yeah, from the day before Christmas Eve until January the 10th
Ohh, I understand
So that's how it works in Shikoku uh...
He must really love Shikoku!
He gets to see a lot his beloved Shikoku throughout a whole year!
That's right
What is this?
That on September the 8th?
Yeah, around the 8th
Oh, that's my birthday!
No way! That's my birthday too!
Really?
You know, I actually knew that
I mean, our birthdays
Looks like Matsumoto and Dynamite Shikoku's birthdays are on the same day
Is that for real!?
Next time we'll go together at Misako's
Oh yeah, so we're also both Virgo!
What a coincidence!
Really!
It's really a coincidence, don't you think so?
Woah!
Looks delicious!
Seems like that before his beloved Nabe, Dynamite Shikoku has something more to show us
Hey!
You kept us waiting, you know?
Hurry up and introduce yourself!
Yes!!
I'm Ibaraki
＊Just like "Shikoku" is the name of an Island, "Ibaraki" is the name of a prefecture
Add "Dynamite" to it, you idiot!
Sorry!
I'm Dynamite Ibaraki
＊There are two Ibarakis: One is a prefecture, one is a city in kansai. Dynamite Ibaraki is from Kansai. (the one with the kanji for "tree")
Which Ibaraki is it?
Are you from Ibaraki or Ibaraki?
Ibaraki.
Which one?
The one with the kanji for "tree"
So, IbaraKI, right?
Yes
The one in Osaka?
Yeah, the one in Osaka
Wait...
I was thinking about showing you guys a bit of my personal goods-like products
Like, there's this one...
A book?
Yeah I've recently managed to get to publish it
You did?
Is it for advertisement?
Well, about advertisement I wouldn't say that...
U-uh, wait, which (camera) is it? Oh, this, well...
I'll send this as a present to 5 lucky viewers
Dynamite Shikoku shamelessly self-promoting with presents
＊Not actually taking applications
I'll sign this in case you win it
Thanks for listening     This book, right?
Yeah, number's right there
You see this one's like... you know,
There's half of my life in it
You know, a sort of autobiography from when I was born
But uhh...
On the back side there's a 4-panel manga I've been drawing
Eh?
I didn't know you were into this
Yeah I've always enjoyed it
How much is that book?
This one is...
2900 Yen
＊Roughly 28 dollars / 25 euros
Expensive!
It's expensive though...
It's pretty expensive!
It's relatively high priced
Wouldn't it be better around 1000 yen or so?
Yeah, it's way too high priced!
So from this point on I thought "what else can I do?"
And so...
You know that "Yes & No" pillows, right?
Oh, those, yeah
They often appear as a sponsor to that program, right?
You know I kind of
Followed its example (of the Yes-no-pillow)
And so they made me this "SHI-KKOKU" pillow with the characters from "Shikoku"
＊Yes/No pillows has "yes" on one side and "no" on the other.
This one has "SHI" (四) and "KOKU" (国)
Yeah but what's it purpose?
I'm glad they made this but it's not like it has a meaning or such
It's just "Shikoku", there's no other meaning to it!
Right
I see...
This one I'll...
3 lucky viewers could get their hands on it as a present
Again, Dynamite Shikoku shamelessly self-promoting with presents
＊Not actually taking applications
Just call the number displayed here
It's the Shikkoku-pose!
Yeah, that's it
Dynamite Shikoku-san keeps on showing us with enthusiasm his most popular goods
I actually like this one
Yeah
How much is this shirt?
This is about 12800 Yen
＊Roughly 126 dollars / 112 euros
Is that really this expensive?
Yes
Boss! Can you bring here the usual thing?
Bring here the saké!
Uh? What's this?
WHAT?!
W-what is that?!
Guys this is like...
W-wait a second!
Like, my special way to have a toast
Wait what?
A bit different from putting the saké on the glass and drink it
Sorry I kept you waiting!
So, bottles after all
Yeah of course it's the same deal
So you actually drink a lot, uh!
No way!
"Naruto Zeyo", it's delicious!
Zeyo, uh!
Come on, let's have a drink
But isn't Zeyo in the Kouchi Prefecture?
＊Hamada remarks that the Naruto Zeyo saké isn't apparently made in Shikoku but in Kouchi.
Woah, woah, woah!
WOAH!!
It goes like this
That's really something!
He's pouring a lot!
Dynamite Shikoku pours saké in a pool for children to enjoy a drink to the fullest
Never seen something like that before
That's amazing!
Oh!
Ah so this is where your pose was born from?
I can see you doing it right now
Is this where it was born from?
That was so sudden
Using a pool for children...
How are you going to drink from it?
Let's have a toast everybody, come on, raise your glasses
After this
Something unexpected happens to Dynamite Shikoku...
Thanks a lot!
Cheers!!
[previous segment]
Isn't his face going to be soaked in alcohol by doing so?
No traces of excitement too
We never got to feel not a single ounce of his liveliness today
Not even once since we met him!
Come to think about it...
It's like he doesn't have it to begin with
That's how he normally is
A boring person
Is it...?
He's the one from last time
Yeah...
He's Escargot-man, isn't him?
Are you kidding?
Yeah, it's him
Escargot-man came by chance to the same shop.
Hey!
Hey.
The hell are you doin' here?
Why you here?
It's Escargot-man...
Are you trying to make a fool out of me?
Huh?!
Hey, Shikoku-san...
Wait, wait, wait! - Let's stop all of this
We're in a shop... - That's a bit too much
His microphone...
There's no need to go this far!
Plus, we're in a shop...
I'll get him right where he is
GOOOOOOONG!
Ouch!
W-wait...
Oh.  - Don't tell me...
Yet again, Dynamite Shikoku falls under a muscle strain.
H-he strained his muscle     - Strained, again
Another strain...
It hurts
Boss! Call the usual!
Quick, first aid!
Yes!
What happened?
Didn't last long!
Are you ok?
What?
Translation, subtitles & encoding by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
More clips? Subscribe to Shion (ガキの使い用)!
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
He... walked towards it
They had it ready all along...
Shikoku-san!
Come on, Shikoku-san!
That was truly bullshit.