Backstage- Pre recording
So you guys tell them what you bring...
Yeah like straps quite often...
Oh really?
Downtown
Cocorico
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Yamasaki Hosei
Tanaka Naoki
Endo Shozo
What the hell are you reminiscing about?
I know...
No, I wasn't like that, was I?
You were...
You really were...
Otomo
What the hell?
Producer
Suga Kenji
Otomo..
Umm, yes?
Tachi?
Who's going to play Tachi?
I'm talking about Tachi Hiroshi!
It's stupid just doing this all by myself
So Tachi...
Tachi from Seibu Keisatsu?
That's right
Naoki...*
*Suga is addressing Tanaka by
his first name to be intimidating
Tachi Hiroshi...
Decide with that!
r
For some reason, Suga producer hands
Tanaka a bouncy ball
Decide who's going to be
Tachi Hiroshi, Naoki, you sort it out and decide...
Got it?!
He's so pissed off!
That was so scary!
What the hell was that?
And why is he ordering you like that?
Otomo, what's going on?
Well umm...
He's a huge fan of Seibu Keisatsu
Director
Ootomo Yuichi
He's a huge fan of Seibu Keisatsu
And as you saw, he's Daimon, right?
Yeah, I got that
Producer
Suga Kenji
Seibu Police
Daimon Keisuke
And he's been saying for a while he wanted to do this...
r
Producer Suga wanted to
do Seibu Police kind of things
But this isn't really the program for it...
So if someone could
play Tachi Hiroshi
Just do it
among the staff...
The talent shouldn't have to...
Exactly
I'm above that...
Oh no~ we can't be the only ones to...
right Ootomo~?
Let's all do it...
Are you gay?
Heipo
Heipo-san?
So decide with the Bouncy ball...
r
They must use the bouncy ball and
decide who will play Tachi Hiroshi
who will play Tachi Hiroshi...
Wait, I don't get what we have to do...
So we have to decide who is going to do it?
One of us...
Ok then...
We'll go around the table
For example, throw the ball against the wall
and then when it bounces back, we
catch it one handed
and whoever can't do it
plays Tachi Hiroshi
okay?
I don't want to man..
No no, that's like the only thing I can think of...
Throw the ball against the wall and catch it
text
They take goes throwing the ball
against the wall and catch it with one hand
r
Whoever is the last one able to
catch the ball plays Tachi Hiroshi
We go one by one around the table and they throw the Bouncy ball against the wall and catch it one handed
Whoever is the last one to do it has to play Tachi Hiroshi
Here I go then
White
Bouncy ball
Gold
Don't catch it and
become Tachi Hiroshi
This is...
Yeah, it's fine
That was fine
He did it so softly
Wow, amazing
That was dangerous
That was close
So close
He threw it so softly...
So I can do it as soft as I want, right?
They're getting nervous
No one has failed...
Because of everyone's sweat, the ball is so slippy...
This is...
He'll be fine, no?
Surely...
That was awful!
Your eyes couldn't keep up at all!
That was so bad!
That really was!
Tsutsun, you're up
That was dangerous
It was...
To be honest, the slower you do it, the harder it is...
Yeah
Because it bounces weirdly
Yeah, if you do it too soft
it goes weird
Oh this is bad!
No good...
Out
Okay, here we go
These guys suck so bad!
That's awful!
The talents are just amazing though...
I guess it's our youth!
Heipo now
Here I go
He was skipping there...
He like hit it
You got to catch it...
Second round
I think he's in trouble...
He is
We told you not to throw it softly!
He got it though
You smug piece of shit...
Right then...
What are you on about?
You're an idiot
If your kids were watching...
He's so bad!
So bad!
Surely you're not feeling pressured here?
Oh, he caught it!
So if Heipo catches this
r
If Heipo catches this, Nakamura
becomes Tachi Hiroshi!
This is the one
Here I go...
So that means Tachi Hiroshi...
is going to be Nakamura-san!
Tachi Hiroshi
Nakamura Producer- Decided
Producer
Nakamura Yoshinobu
Seibu Police
Tatsumi Sotaro detective
(Tachi Hiroshi)
Producer
Suga Kenji
Seibu Police
Daimon Keisuke detective
Watari Tetsuya
Let's play golf sometime...
You always say that and never play
Otomo
Yes?
Have you decided who'll play Akira?
Akira?
Tachi just went to you...
Akira I said, Akira... Tera Akira!
Seibu Police
Matsuda Takeshi
(Tera Akira)
Choose someone
We can't do anything, just the two of us
Naoki
Naoki, you decide using that, who will play him
r
Suga hands Tanaka a deck of cards this time
Tera?
That's right, Tera Akira.
I have to?
Yeah, Naoki decides...
Damn, he's rough
So rough...
What's that about?
He has no delicacy...
And what's with the 'Naoki' thing?
I have no idea...
It's the first time I've ever heard him say that
Yeah
So what shall we do with this deck?
I don't know man...
What should we do...
Just make it simple
You're right
Like we all take a card and flip it over at the same time
and whoever has the lowest number...
Oh yeah, I do like that idea
Oh man, so scary
This is quite scary...
So the lowest number...
Oh, wait!
So, If before I draw
I say "hearts"
And then I flip over the card
and it's hearts then I'm safe
Oh, that's a good idea.
Wait, you'd be safe?
Should I be out?
Because it's a 1/4 chance.
If we do that,
It'd be better if you were out.
If you were safe no one would...
That might be better.
I think so too.
Guess the Card Suit
text
Pick a card and guess the suit,
and then flip it over.
text
If the suit of the card is the suit
called out, the player is out.
text
Continue this until there is only
one person left. Loser becomes Tera.
Flip a card over, and if it is the same suit as the one the player called out, he is out.
The last person to be out will perform Tera Akira.
If you guess it right, you're out.
White
Playing Cards
Gold
Guess the Suit,
Tera Akita
If you're right, out.
If you say hearts and the card is hearts, you're out.
Hearts
Safe!
Are we putting it back in the pile?
Nah, just leave it out.
Ah, okay.
Say it out loud.
Hearts
That was close
Thank God
Spades
Wow, nice
There's a 1/4 chance so...
It's over with just a flip.
Endo's the 4th turn, so...
Clovers
No way, I don't wanna...
Right, right
There's still a chance.
Go ahead, Tanaka.
Diamonds
Yes, okay.
It's lookin' like Endo...
Right?
Say it!!!
Hearts
If you don't call it first, you're automatically out.
Diamonds
Just two people left.
It's gonna be Endo!
Just two left, Endo.
Three-Leaf
Three-leaf?
What the hell is "three-leaf"?
Text
If Heipo Guesses Wrong
Endo Will Perform Tera Akira!
I've never heard of that suit.
So it's all on Heipo now.
It's gonna be Endo.
It's already Endo, though.
Spades!
Which means,
Tera Akira is...
Endo!
Endo To
Perform Tera!
Thank God...
Endo Shozo
Western Division Police
Matsuda Takeshi
(Tera Akira)
Producer
Suga Kenji
Western Division Police
Daimon Keisuke
(Watari Tetsuya)
Producer
Nakamura Yoshinobu
Western Division Police
Detective Tatsumi Soutarou
(Tachi Hiroshi)
So we...
Otomo
Yes.
Who's gonna be Gen-san?
Gen-san?
I'm talking about Kariya Shunsuke!
Western Division Police
Detective Genda Kouji
(Kariya Shunsuke)
Kariya Shunsuke...
Naoki
You pick.
It's up to you.
text
This Time Producer Suga Gives
Tanaka a Recorder
Decide with this...
pick Gen-san.
Alright...
Understood?!
Y...Yes.
He really had trouble closing that door.
How should we do it?
What do you mean, we already know how.
Explain the rules already.
Every one will pick
their own recorder...
And only one of these recorders
doesn't make any noise.
The person who gets that recorder
will be Kariya Shunsuke
Recorder Playing
text
Pick one of the recorders from the
bucket and blow into it
text
If sound comes out, safe! The person who
picks the broken recorder becomes Kariya
Pick a recorder and try playing in order.
The person who picks the silent recorder becomes Kariya Shunsuke.
Should we all pick at the same time?
It's a 1/8 chance, so...
If I'm gonna get picked after all this time,
I would have preferred Tachi Hiroshi.
Let's all pick at the same time.
Box
Recorders
Gold
Whoever picks the
silent recorder is Kariya
Alright.
I'm begging you...
We just have to blow togeth...
Oh right, One by one.
Let's start blowing.
Alright, starting with Yama-chan.
It's you!
See?!
Try playing.
See?
It's Yama-chan!
Yamasaki To
Perform Kariya Shunsuke!
That's so unfortunate.
I almost shed a tear.
Yamasaki Hosei
Western Division Police
Detective Genda Kouji
(Kariya Shunsuke)
Producer
Nakamura Yoshinobu
Western Division Police
Detective Tatsumi Soutarou
(Tachi Hiroshi)
Producer
Suga Kenji
Western Division Police
Detective Daimon Keisuke
(Watari Tetsuya)
Endo Shozo
Western Division Police
Detective Matsuda Takeshi
(Tera Akira)
We should be good now
We're good.
It's enough already.
We're definitely good.
He's so...
Otomo
Yes.
How many times are you
gonna make me tell you?
Tani-san. You know, Tani-san.
Tani-san?
I'm talkin' about Fujioka Juukei.
Western Division Police
Detective Tani Daisaku
(Fujioka Juukei)
Tani-san!
Who's it gonna be?
Naoki
Pick Tani-san, with that.
text
This Time Producer Suga
Gives Tanaka a Towel
Pick Tani-san.
It's Kuroiwa. Just kidding, it's Daimon.
Alright, got it. I'll head right there.
Yup, got it. No problem.
*Daitokai is another popular detective/police drama
But Kuroiwa is from Daitokai*
Understood?!
Decide already.
He has no idea what he's doing.
I thought he loved that show.
That way of playing it off,
"Just kidding..."
His face is probably so red right now.
Bright red!
He said "Just kidding"...!
Such a stupid way to cover it up
So what's this?
This is a towel for each of us.
And with these...
There's only one towel
which has ink on it.
Each person will choose a prepared towel and wipe their face with it,
Ink Towel Face Wipe
text
Each person picks a towel from the
bucket, and everyone wipes their face at the same time.
text
The person that wipes their face
with the ink towel will play Fujioka Juukei.
and the person who chose the ink towel will play Fujioka Juukei.
Ah, I can see it.
Let's pick.
After we choose...
It's ready, right?
I could see the ink towel.
He could see it.
Oh really?
Yea.
You can just take off your glasses
if you're gonna accidentally see it.
Oh yea!
White
Ink Towel
Gold
Face Turns Black
=Fujioka Juukei
Alright, here it is.
I don't wanna do this anymore.
Let's just pick for now.
Let's all wipe at the same time.
3, 2, 1...
We were spared...
But I just saw...why me?!
Which means,
Fujioka Juukei will be played by Heipo!
Heipo To
Perform Fujioka Juukei!
Fantastic.
Heipo
Western Division Police
Detective Tani Daisaku
(Fujioka Juukei)
Endo Shozo
Western Division Police
Detective Matsuda Takeshi
(Tera Akira)
Producer
Suga Kenji
Western Division Police
Detective Daimon Keisuke
(Watari Tetsuya)
Producer
Nakamura Yoshinobu
Western Division Police
Detective Tatsumi Soutarou
(Tachi Hiroshi)
Yamasaki Hosei
Western Division Police
Detective Genda Kouji
(Kariya Shunsuke)
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents:
Down Town's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Translators:
Typesetter:
Mickstar (Team Gaki) & Callanse
Otviss
**We also have Facebook and Twitter.**
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*