Tonight's Gaki No Tsuka: Gabburi Chicken Finale!
Delicious!
Bon appetite!
The rules: They must finish an Oyadori (Hen) and Hinadori (Chick) at each store,
Furthermore, at each store 2 people will finish the 100g Fried Chicken dish assigned to them
They will repeat this for all 20 stores in the Tokyo Metro Area, and aim to finish them all!
If they're victorious, they'll win 100,000 yen
However, if anyone gives up the challenge is over
The person who gave up has to pay for all of the food eaten
Served with Daikon and Ponzu
You're so slow!
He is one of the 2 Lady Boys after all
It's too much
I can't eat that much!
Gaki's Light Eater Duo, Hamada and Hosei have been working hard,
Up until now, they've cleared 5 stores,
15 stores remain,
Will they be able to finish?
Typeset by GakiDave
Translated by senor_wristband
After clearing the 5th store, they select the Fried Chicken eaters
First the SAFE people,
SAFE people,
Please! please!
Hamada!
What do you mean? This is the "OUT" table
You're wrong! He said it was the SAFE one
The first person out,
The wing flats are a pain...
The second OUT,
At the 6th store, Cocorico will eat fried chicken as a duo!
So, the 11th store is next...
6th store, it's the 6th store
Just pretend it is, just film it like it is
This is Tanaka-san's 3rd time
It is! It's my 3rd time
How would you rate your stomach condition?
Honestly?
I think 8...
Are you gonna give up? That's almost giving up!
No no, I'm fine I'm fine
If I was out eating with my family right now I'd say "No thanks"
I guess that makes sense,
I'd give up at an 8 too
If you were eating with your family, you'd give up at an 8?
Yes
Well it makes sense with how I feel,
I'd ask if there's dessert
You'd go until 10?
I wouldn't stop at 8 at all
The 6th store is here, at Ikebukoru Station's East Exit
The bone-in Hinadori, and Oyadori
That's the Oyadori?
Yes, we'll take it from there
First off is Gaburi Chicken's specialty bone-in chicken
The Oyadori is nice and firm, and the flavour spreads in your mouth as you chew,
Meanwhile the Hinadori is very tender and juicy
The Oya & Hina - A popular menu item that let's you enjoy both flavours
Look, I'm eating a huge piece of Oyadori
That piece?
It is huge!
Sunazuri? (Gizzard)
There's more than you'd think
Listen to the sound he made!
In terms of a firm bite,
It does have one right?
If you keep getting this, you'll be in trouble
Tanaka is on his 3rd plate of wings today
There's still meat left, what are you trying do?
Tanaka is acting like a convict...
No, no that's not true, that's not true
We all want to work together don't we?
Please check that out.
Move your hands!
Get your hands out of the way!
He's cheating a little bit
Why are you hovering your hands over it?
It's overflowing with meat! That is overflowing with meat
Here's the last piece.
Last of the gizzards
Hosei-san hasn't spoken a single word
It stuck out to me
Tanaka chews down to the bone and finishes as well
Did you see that?
He tried to get up...he OUCH!....went like this..
He got it wrong again?
He was trying to get up
What happened?
You weren't looking right?
His "wings" weren't big enough
His "wings"! Yes they were too small!
Picking the fried chicken eaters for the 7th store
The first person out,
I can't do it
I said I can't do it! This is my 4th time!
The second person,
Tanaka!
Already, Hosei is feeling the pressure,
His steps towards the 7th store are heavy
You complain a lot, whether that's good or bad...
Cause Tenders are...
Hosei-san cut that out please
I'm a Lady Boy you know...
Help me out!
What topping do you want for your Tenders?
How about Tartar sauce?
Chili tomato.
Daikon with ponzu.
It's the same as before!
I think for TV purposes you should change it
TV purposes ....
And of course my recommendation, whipped chocolate
That's a dessert
Actually, I do want to change the taste, at least
Let's get the Whipped Choco, yeah?
But also, Whip Choco-
Alright, Chocolate then
Why would you say something so pathetic?
Hosei-san, what happened?
Hosei gets Whipped Chocolate for his breat, and Tanaka gets Curry for his wings
Gaburi Chicken Food Marathon: They arrive at the 7th store in Suidobashi
You know it looks like we're gonna fail this time like always, that's no good
Let's betray the viewers
Let's betray them!
Thank you for waiting! This is Oyadori & Hinadori
This one is Oyadori
It's huge...
Take the one your chopsticks touched please!
Stop messing it up man
I was just checking
"Hmm is that too big?" - Cut that out
They're all the same size
The closest one? Is this the closest?
Sorry
So hard
The firm bite is nice right?
It has a nice bite to it, he means "hard" in a good way
It's really tasty, this skin
Even the skin is tasty
The Tenders and the Wings, please
Gabburi Chicken Marathon - Time for the 7th store
Hosei and Tanaka have eaten 860g!
For real?!
The Tenders
It's not what I thought it would be
It's not Chocolate, it's Whipped Cream
When Hosei saw that side dish overflowing with Cream...
He's turned into "Ashita no Joe". What happened?
He's not moving at all
This is just ...
Let's not fall into our old pattern though,
Like, "Hosei, once again..."
And they flashback to the Chocolate
Ah like "They should have stopped him"
Tanaka also got a topping, Curry to change the flavour
The wings here are huge!
I'm always getting this
That's huge!
It's huge! It's like they're getting bigger
But maybe with the Curry,
Yeah, I put some Curry on
It's nice to change the taste
That's the best one I think
This is seriously 100g?
This is actually really heavy
You can tell with the chopsticks?
What would you estimate?
Estimate? This is at least 120 grams
Just, is this really 100g? That's all I wanna know
It's 100g right?
How many did Hosei-san say?
(It's 100)
Hosei-san said 120
It's 100 grams. It's all good.
Even the store person had to tell you
Even after that, Hosei's chopsticks just won't move
Maybe try a bite with the whipped choco,
The taste will change
This works
It's good?
It's a dessert
So the main is the Tenders. It could work together.
Miracle
It's a miracle
He's doing it. The goal is almost there
Sorry Tanaka-san
The Wing check needs to be done
It's fine, totally fine
No way, eat it again
This area is fishy, this area
You gotta suck that off
I guess if I suck on it it'll come out
That's it
See? There was so much left
See
He's even biting it
He's eating so much
While Tanaka was sucking on that...
Sorry, excuse me
His cheque bounced
Don't worry, you can make it up somehow
He lost a lot of money!
This is really...
Really bad
He didn't tell his family about this
You just said changing the flavour helps you eat
Yeah it was amazing when he finished that one piece
He doesn't reply when you call him
And now he's become like this
There's also Tanaka's meat problem,
No it's not really like that-
Just going to the bathroom
There it is
From the 4 he had there's still 3 left
Should we go over to the washroom and just see what happened?
Because, you would expect, since Tanaka-san is finished...
Well he's not really finished
I am I am, I've totally finished
There's meat on there
It's not meat, it's bones I keep telling you
He's lying
I'm telling you it's bone
It's as good as finished, alright?
Hosei-san?  Everything ok?
Everything OK?
Feeling relieved?
Such a nasty expression that is
What situation is this?
Maybe he's playing Tsume Shogi
TN: Tsume Shogi is a game like Chess
I mean there's still 3 out of 4 pieces left
If it was just 1 left...
What state are you in? Just tell us how you feel right now
How I feel?
I can't eat anymore
Do you give up?
If you say that...
You're kidding right? It's only the 7th store
That's how I feel
Just his feelings
It's tenders, and only the 7th store
If I go with my feelings, I can't anymore, but,
I can't really end at the 7th store
And it's been me for the past few times right?
Tsukitei Hosei 51 years old - Makes a miraculous recovery!
Oh, there he goes!
He's doing well isn't he?
He's gotta use that too
Yes, that's important
What a man
Once his face starts shaking...
There it is, he's started doing that
He's eating it up!
He does that a lot in times like these
He's been drinking a lot of water
The water and the chocolate
He's going for it!
Now he always dips in that
Yeah
Such small bites
And finally!
Very heroic!
Hosei brilliantly used the Cream to finish! Time for the 8th Fried Chicken draw.
Alright, this one,
Out! Out! ... Out!
This person, this person has to eat
Hamada-san. Hamada-san!
Matsumoto-san. Well it's not that bad.
This person will be safe.
You're so delighted!
I don't care anymore, I don't care!
The Fried Chicken eaters will be Matsumoto and Fujiwara, both on their second plates
It's already been 4 hours. The enter the 8th store in Hongō
OyaHina OyaHina ... We've already eaten it!
OyaHina OyaHina ... We should've beaten it!
Hmm?
Your impression wasn't good at all
But you knew who I was right?
Takeda Tetsuya-san right?
If you can tell then it was a good impression
I thought you were gonna laugh at that...
I'm sorry for creating this atmosphere
Excuse us, thank you!
This one is Oya,
This one is a pain
He did barely finish the Tenders, but he has to finish the OyaHina too
Yes that's right
It's possible to give up on just the OyaHina
Yes, totally possible
That's huge!
This is your second time right Fujiwara?
Boneless Thigh
Matsumoto is also on his second plate. Neck, with Curry as a topping
Well yeah it has been a while since the first time he got Neck
He finished! So quick
Alright 2 sticks of Grease left
Don't call it Grease!
If it comes back up, that's gonna be...
The grease will just SLAM-
Stop saying Grease man, I thought we were clear on that
Alright he finished!
Amazing!
8th store is cleared! Next, the 9th Fried Chicken draw
The OUT person is,
Tanaka-san is OUT
There's still one left
The second one,
THE LOWEST ONE IS OUT!
The lowest person's card is out!
The 9th store's draw has picked Matsumoto and Tanaka
There's no sense of us working together to get to the goal anymore
This complete Mutual Destruction
When it gets to this point?
Yes
We're absolutely crushing each other
Next - Tanaka and Matsumoto destroy each other!
Gabburi Chicken marathon - After the 8th store, Hosei and Tanaka have eaten 1040g
The 9th store in Asakusabashi will be their next stage. A shocking turn of events await!
Hello excuse me, your fried chicken
You got that first huh?
Both of their servings were served on one plate ...
A merciless mutual destruction awaits!
If they do this...
It's fine if Tanaka and I eat half each, right?
Half each?
No listen,
I'll eat one of the wings, so...
Oh that's what you mean?
And Tanaka eats 3 Neck pieces
I just bring myself to touch the wings
That makes sense
Thinking back to before, that scares me
Wing, alright
So the Neck...
Huge!
You're kidding right?
This is 100g, right?
Surely there's no way!
We ordered by the weight
This is your 9th wing right?
Yeah, this is my 9th wing!
Ah Hosei-san you got Onion, I see
It does change the texture, certainly
On this series, we've never really seen Matsumoto-san like this
It's the first time, isn't it? It's the first time.
Yeah it is the first time actually
What's happened to him?
He's still got one whole wing left
But he finished one
You've really calculated your opponent there
Yeah you're right!
He's calculated what's gonna happen
You...
Really, Tanaka?
This guy...
He just stopped all of a sudden
He thinks he's gonna give up
I'm so pissed off
He's eaten the big ones. Half of them.
There's 11 stores left,
If we get to the next one, it'll be halfway
It's a cigar now
It'll feel the same no matter how you eat!
It's a cigar, straight up
So he's getting into the mood,
Something a bit different,
Like "Alright, I'm in a bar"
He finished his Neck cigar style. Only 1 piece left!
Hold on, he's-
He's crying
I'm sorry!
Ah! He's crying!
Is that a give up?
I can't anymore~!
He gives up!
I'm so sowwy about this
You were doing your best though!
So the 9th store!
The CLEAR was denied,
Hold on, this is agonizing!
You just couldn't get it down
The bill until now is 31,644 yen
I just wanna see, what would happen at the next card draw?
Should we pull out a card? This is who's out
I'd be done either way!
I would end either way!
It was a choice of two paths