Fifth time on Gaki no Tsukai: Let's play tabletop games from around the world!
Here we go again!
This is our fifth episode
Yeah, it is
Why is Tanaka running this show?
Tanaka learned each game's rules beforehand
I heard he got here hours before
Do you want to do this that bad?
Of course I want to
They told me you got here this morning
I just got here few minutes before you guys
I know you've come several times to learn them
And you were like "mhh, I see..."
This is embarrassing...
I bet you even took notes
I heard some games sold pretty well after our show
Yeah, I heard that too
Some of those we've played run out of stock
This time too, they'll get to choose and experience some worldwide famous tabletop games!
Translation & editing by Shion
Typesetting by Mattee53
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
facebook.com/shionnotsukai
patreon.com/shionnotsukai
ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
The first game they're going to play is "Zitternix", from Germany!
Long story short, it's about getting as much sticks as you can
Like Jenga, right?
Yes
We start from this and we throw the dice in turns
As you can see there are three colors: red, blue and yellow
Three of them?
If you get blue, you have to draw the blue stick
Each color is worth some points
I see
Blue is 3 points, red is 2 points, yellow is 1 point
Blue ones are thicker, so if you take them the structure could crumble
So it must not crumble, right?
That's right, if it falls down it's game over
This is so simple it doesn't seem fun in the slightest
It's so simple, isn't it?
I guarantee this is surprisingly fun, simple and fun
Alright, we're moving anticlockwise
I got yellow
Yellow is easy, it's right in the middle
But this will inevitably crumble, I mean, not now
That's right
How do you know when it will? It's tricky
For now it's pretty solid
It's going to get crooked
Blue is bad news
Which one...?
But it's worth 3 points
You're fine however it goes
But it's already kinda crooked...
Yes
You can't do that, you have deal only with the first stick you've touched
Eh?
Just say that before, dude
Of course it's like this, Endo
But once you grab one and try to get it out...
You can sway it around as much as you want
What do you mean?
You can move it around?
Yes, you can shake it
While holding it?
You can do that
You can change that?
Yes, you can adjust it as much as you want
As long as you're going to get the stick you're holding
This is such an important thing to say
Why bringing it up now?
It was really important... which one was mine?
- It was that one
- I guess you're getting one penalty
Take that one for now
I'm sure it was that one
Is this ok?
It's fine, it got even more crooked but it didn't crumble down
I see, so the loop is going to move as well...
Another blue one
It's totally doable
I think this one's ok
Can you let go of the one you're holding?
He made it look so easy, everything is alright
It's another blue
Ok, now it's going to be risky
Right, we won't know when it's gonna be hard
If the loop is going to stay as it is, I can do it
I think it's this one
Huh? Is this situation ok?
Yes, it's still ok
Are you kidding me?
I see, now I see
That was impressive
He got so close
Yeah, it was about to crumble
The dice is being such a jerk
Nothing but blue
Yeah, it's unbelievable
We got it, dice
We know it by now
Maybe if you swing it around...
It's moving a bit
It's ok to move it around, you know
You can control it
You can get it back in shape
It is crumbling
It's really close to crumbling
Doesn't look safe
Isn't it better to take it away in one flick?
So stupid
Such a boring way to lose...
That was so stupid of you
Why didn't you try to put everything back?
Yeah, you could have done it
But--
This is how smaller companies crumble down
So worthless
That's a backstreet workshop way of ending it
But this happened because I was trying to put it back...
It crumbled 'cause I tried to prevent it
Just do it the other way round
Let's have another round now that we know the rules
On their second round...
Now I get it
The five started to understand the mechanics of Zitternix
And they collect more and more sticks
That was close
This one looks bad, this other one too
You're right, they're both hard to get
Incredible
Are you kidding me?!
I don't have much confidence in this...
Alright
It's this one, right? I know for sure it's this one
Or maybe I'm wrong?
Wait a second, is it this one?
That one...
Over there
Is this...? Oh, from here?
Wait a second
Ah, this one!
- That's right
Now I see
It's not touching anything relevant
But it's hard to get
He's still in game, right?
I can't get this...
Dude, if everything falls, it'd be your second time
Just go for it
This hesitation is killing me
Let's see...
Why sticking to that? Wait, he has to
Can't help it, he touched that one
He's really...
Where is it gonna fall?
It got even deeper inside
Now he's 100% done for
Come on, man...
You made it impossible
It's between two red ones
And you're forced to take that one
You're in such a bad situation now
Try to use your pinky
I don't think he...
His fingers...
Like this, huh?
That's not how-- what a waste of time
Their next tabletop game is going to be "Slide Quest", made in France
Four player cooperate to balance four levers
And guide the adventurer towards the goal!
Here it is
Looks fun
This is that french game
Which got your attention, Matsumoto
You have to go past several obstacles over the board
By following the white line
And try to reach the number "4" at the end of the road
So, this is our route?
But near the route there are objects like this stone
Or dynamites like those
That's 'cuz you're placing 'em
That's the point of the game
It figures
That's how it is... if there weren't any, it won't be fun
It's fun because there are obstacles
How can we pass through here?
Yeah I mean-- we can't touch it, right?
You end up touching the dynamite while passing through here, right?
If you hit it it's fine, no big deal
But if you knock it over, it explodes and you're out
So we can't make it fall
What if it falls down the hole?
It won't matter
But it'll explode
It explodes?
'Cause it comes from below
Yeah but uh....
I mean, debris could fly towards us
Are you--- talking about a real situation?
Is it really gonna explode?
Can we fall in the hole with the dynamite?
The dyn---
Can we jump inside with it?
Of course you can't
You'd die
You can't fall inside this hole
How about the other two?
All holes are bad!
Is it really going to explode?
What the hell are you all talking about?!
Let's do this
Endo, you should go right some more
We can't fall inside the hole
Well...
Pretty rough
We're still on track, it's alright
Yamazaki stop lifting that, I'm gonna do the same too
That's right, just like this
We have to let Hamada deal with this
Now it's your turn, Matsumoto
Oh boy, now I have to get past that hole
Endo you too
Can I help here?
You went too far, Yama-chan!
We're so close to the goal
No, you have to follow the route
Towards me, Yama-chan
It's not moving
Here
More towards Matsumot---
Where the hell are ya goin'?
We were doing so well...
Come on...
Yama-chan careful! Go back
Let's put it back where it was
Well done, now it's ok
I'm gonna let go
It's up to you, Matsumoto
Why do you always do that?!
He's right
It wasn't me, it was Endo!
It was you, Yama-chan
Let's go
Don't move there
Tilt it, Shozo
I have to
I'm not moving here
Oh, nice nice
Looking good so far
Yama-chan, don't touch anything!
He's right
I'm scared
Don't shout
That was on me
This game is freaking hard!
It's really hard
Look, there are corpses...
Holy shit, it's getting scary
So scary!
Look how many dead guys are in there!
You were doing great at first
Wanna switch places with me, Yamazaki?
Hamada has to give it all at the beginning
At this point you---- Ah!
Are you kidding me?
You got it wrong, it was Shozo
It wasn't me
You pulled the lever so hard
I did not
It went straight down the hole
That's because he pulled so goddamn hard
I didn't, I swear
It's a game about collaboration and trust, but...
Careful, there's a dynamite
Why did you pull it that way? We were doing the opposite
I didn't!
Of course it's gonna fall!
I think I'm done
We were moving it that way, but those brats over there...
He's freaking me out
And he just called us "brats"
What the fuck is wrong with you two?!
I'm seriously scared
Tanaka switches places with Hamada
But his pressure is just escalating
You have to let Yama-chan do this
I'm fine, I'm not moving anything
What the hell are you doing?
It was the two of you just now
You went hard, didn't you?
Yeah...
I went a bit hard
Why did I suddenly get called to join this?
It wasn't sudden at all
Their next game is "Ubongo", made in Germany
It's a speed puzzle game in which you have to fill the blank spaces on the board with the given pieces
First off we're going to roll the dice and see what we get
For example, now we got this serow
Now, take a look at your own serow-marked piece combo
You have to use those three colored pieces to fill the blank space
All of them?
All of them, yeah
You gotta fill it up nice and clean
They all work?
They do
The first person who completes his given puzzle...
Has to shout "ubongo"
And from when the first person says it
All the other players
Have 10 seconds to complete their own puzzle
I don't think it'll be enough for us...
Hamada's puzzles seem kinda easy to me
We don't know that, let's do it
This is hard
Here comes the dice
We got a mask
The mask? The one at the bottom?
I'm gonna do this
How am I supposed to fill it completely?
Put your mind into it
Even if you say so...
You have to use all three pieces
Sorta ubongo!
"Sorta"...?
There's no such thing
You have one spare space
But it's kinda an ubongo, isn't it?
You have to fill it completely, there's no "kinda ubongo"
Ubongo
He got an ubongo!
Ubongo!
TIME UP
And it's over
Wait a sec, now I'm curious to see how can I get an ubongo here
Please, check it out for yourself
I don't think this one can actually get me an ubongo
I can get a sorta-ubongo though
Same here
He did it in a flash!!
The genius boy appeared!
So quick!
Can you do mine too?
What was that just now? Are you kidding me?
It's an ubongo!
The genius boy appeared among us!
I always have one square left
Please, do it
Genius boy
I'm 100% sure you'll have one square left too
Maybe this one's impossible even for genius boy here
He's really a prodigy
The hell is this?!
Incredible
Impressive
If you flip your puzzle board...
You'll get a 4-pieces harder version
Four? Impossible
But maybe it could even be easier, who knows
It could be, yeah
We're doing this?
Just flip your board
I don't think I can win against genius boy
You won't expect it, but Yamazaki has this side too
That was a shock
Let's do this
It's a snake
Four pieces, huh...
The fact you can flip each piece is driving me nuts...
It gets more difficult with four pieces
This is impossible...
I don't think I can get any ubon---
Ubongo!
Genius boy returns
Are you kidding me?!
Amazing
I could make this my job, you know
Wanna be an ubongo comedian?
Their next game is going to be "Quarto!", made in France
There are 4 types of pieces
You have to place them anywhere in the board to form a row
Make sure to line up 4 of them
But there are lots of combinations
For example, four of the same color are ok
How about the shape?
Even if they're not the same color, same length is ok too
Length too?
Yep, as long as they form a line
There are four combinations
color (white or black)
shape (round or squared)
hole (present or absent)
length (long or short)
For a row in Quarto: color, shape, presence or absence of hole, length
Another important point of this game is that your opponent chooses which piece you're going to play next
If you line up four of them in a combo, you win by shouting "quarto", but...
There's a chance you line up a quarto but you don't realize you did it
It can happen
That you don't feel your quarto?
In that case, if the opponent notices that during his next turn...
He can shout "quarto" himself and snatch the opponent's point
You can steal points
Oh, I see...
First challenge on quarto: Hosei vs Endo
I see
So strange you get to choose what the opponent plays
It is
I see...
There are lots of possible patterns to make points...
I think we're few steps away from scoring a point
Yeah, but how?
Quattro
Hosei wins
He's right!
Endo...
Does this count as a quattro?
It's quarto, actually
Quattro is that pizza, right?
Ahhh, it's the color, isn't it?
I didn't notice it
I did, actually
We should count this as a draw
I was looking so cool and then...
Then "quattro"
It's a pizza
That one from Pizza-la
It's that one from Pizza-la's delivery service
Downtown showdown: an unexpected turn of event!
Time for a Downtown showdown on quarto: get ready for a crazy twist!
Do rock-paper-scissors
Get ready and---
Matsumoto is going first
Was that "get ready" thing necessary?
That was so unnecessary
Dude, I just placed this piece here
Yep
And you're not moving?
Oh, do I have to?
He didn't see anything!!
This guy is insane
Of course you gotta move
Alright
Place a piece already!!
This is so bad
What's going on?
I place his piece and then mine?
Yeah
This guy...
Anywhere is fine, right?
Yes
I see, even far away is good
No, I---
It's Hamada's turn to place a piece
Those guys are absurd
No wait-- I knew that
I came here to have fun!
Are you sure?
That's not normal
I'm just here to have fun
Just place a piece already!!
Gimme a break
This is just a thing we're doing now
It has nothing to do with the game
Just quit it, otherwise I'm gonna call it a forfeited game
I was just thinking about my moves, geez
Can't deny you have to
But it's a fun game
You gotta use your head
I'm thinking about several strategies
This friggin' piece you gotta place...
Yeah, it's tricky
It makes you impatient
But I'm scared to be yelled by him, so I place em without thinking
It's frightening, yeah
That's what makes me place them
Place that friggin' piece...
Can't we just pretend I've won this?
Woah, what should I do?
Close to match point, huh?
We're close
That piece is probably upside down
This one?
- Yes, that one
And now...?
Quattro
He said "quattro"! The pizza thing!
Translation & editing by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)  | Typesetting by Mattee53  | shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
"Quarto"?
- That's a pizza
That's from Pizza-la
Enough with this
like my page: fb.com/shionnotsukai | donations: ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai | patreon.com/shionnotsukai
They barely even played!
This game is a blast, isn't it?
It really is
I think pizza will be sold more than this game after we air this
They're all gonna order "quattro" pizza
SPECIAL THANKS TO MATTEE53 FOR TYPESETTING THIS EPISODE!!
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT FAN-TRANSLATION MADE BY A FAN FOR OTHER FANS. ALL COPYRIGHT ARE RESERVED TO THEIR RESPECTIVE OWNERS.
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TWITTER.COM/FGRNDNOISES
FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM