On tonight's Gaki no Tsukai...
Our famous project: silent library!
Youtuber Hikakin will
receive atrocious punishments!
An unforgiving parade of punishments!
Unavoidable screams
It's going to be this series'
harshest hell of punishment!
The curtain is about to open!
Translation & subs by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
facebook.com/shionnotsukai | shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Support: ko-fi,com/shionnotsukai
A library in Tokyo...
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Endo Shouzo
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Housei
Hamada Masatoshi
The person who will draw the skull card
will receive the punishment wrote on the sign
Beach Sandal on Forehead
Theme: Beach Sandal on Forehead
So simple
It's painful
One, two...
Shh!
Beach Sandal on Forehead
Giving that it may disturb other people who are reading
it's strictly forbidden to raise your voice
Aim at the forehead
You heard that?
Bitter Gourd on Shin
Theme: Bitter Gourd on Shin
Pick one, Hikakin
- Alright
One, two...
Shh!
Bitter Gourd on Shin
This is scary
Are you kidding me?
This is a bad one
That was the hardest part!
You went with the hardest bit
It must hurt like hell
Man, you're on a roll
Throat Spray Cleansing
What? Come on...
Theme: Throat Spray Cleansing
I'm going first
I'm scared of them all
One, two...
Matsumoto
Throat Spray Cleansing
I had a bad feeling about this
I totally saw this coming
What's that?
It's about this long
It goes in his mouth
That was awful
Piping Hot Seal
Theme: Piping Hot Seal
Please, Matsumoto
One, two...
Tanaka
Piping Hot Seal
This is going to leave a mark
No way this is going to be ok
Woah, this isn't good
What? That much?
You kiddin' me?
He's gonna get burn
Look, it's boiling
He's right, it's boiling
Couldn't they made it less hot?
Come on
Let's do this
Oh, this one?
Yeah, that one
Are you for real?
His forehead
What does it say?
What does the seal say?
What does it say?!
- I can't read it
It says "chin" ("ago")
Enough with this...
It's ok, leave it like that
Can't be helped
- He looks so pale
I have no idea why they made it red
Why red?
What's the point?
Beatboxing Old Dude
Beatboxing dude...?
Theme: Beatboxing Old Dude
One, two...
Beatboxing Old Dude
Alright!!
And old dude?
Beatboxing dude
This sucks so much
His beatbox sucks too
It stinks...
It stinks so much
That's a lot... that was your third time
So quick!
Here he goes
- What's going on?
Flip it
Alright, alright
Nitrogen Ball Strike
The hell is that supposed to be?
Theme: Nitrogen Ball Strike
One, two...
Matsumoto
Nitrogen Ball Strike
I have to stop doing unnecessary things
It's your fault!
Yeah I mean, we chose them ourselves first
It's them again...
It's going to be an experiment
This is freaking me out
Yonemura Denjiro's Apprentice
Professor Ichioka Genki
This pattern...
- Scary!
This seems bad
This pattern is nothing good
Liquid Nitrogen
The forehead?
Forehead, right?
Isn't this too much?
Do we have to toss it?
Do I have to stand up? I wanna sit...
I don't want to stand up
Place your hands behind you
Is it ok?
I have stiff shoulders, it hurts
Your hands behind!
Are we going? We're going
This is scary
Wait, what the hell is that?
Is this going to be ok?
No way that's going to be ok!
Are you for real?!
Huh? Seriously?
W-w-wait!
What are you doing?
That was scary
Watch out for that!
It's still rolling
Go grab it
Just go
What exactly is this show?
Go grab it so it won't break
This looks dangerous
Should we really do this?
Now it's like lead
- Is it ok?
If you let the gum ball froze up in the liquid, it easily bursts up
but as time passes, it's reverted back to its solid state
Enough
It won't break anymore
It's back to being hard
Man, that was really scary
I know
It's between you guys
Endless Vinegar Rapid-fire
What's that?
"Endless vinegar rapid-fire"...
Theme: Endless Vinegar Rapid-fire
This sucks
I don't want this
Let's go
One, two...
Endo
Endless Vinegar Rapid-fire
You should get on the table
Ugh, one of those...
Vinegar?
Go back, stay still
This is bad, this--
Your eyes...
- Don't open them
What about them? That's scary
Mouth open
He opened them!
I can't
- He opened his eyes
It hurts
It stinks
Why is everyone afraid of me?
We told you not to open your eyes
It stinks
It hurts
Why did you open them?
'Cause I got scared
You got scared?    - Yeah
And you wanted to see?
He opened them 'cause he was scared...
You wanted to see some vinegar?
Athletics World Championships
The hell is this?
Theme: Athletics World Championships
Two people?!
What is "Athletics World Championships"...?
When using a pair of skull cards
The punished will be for two people together
You go, Shouzo    - Ok
Let's just go the way I pass them to you
He's still intact!
Who cares?
I mean, Hamada-san...
You sure you're ok with this?
This is risky
One, two...
Endo
Athletics World Championships
Shoot, this sounds bad...
I knew it...
Whatwhatwhatwhatwhat?
Ow ow ow
What..?
Ohh... I see
Woah, this hurts like hell
No way
- It hurts!
Damn, this is bad
World Championships...
This is gonna hurt
Huh?
Shou-chan?
Shocchan?
You ok?
What are you doing?
Am I bleeding?
Yeah, feels like it
It's not
- You're fine
It was strong
- My mouth...
Sorry but, this guy...
Come on, it's not my fault!
Super Cooling Bazooka
Sounds like another experiment
- Enough...
Theme: Super Cooling Bazooka
Any volunteers?
No
Is that so?
"Cooling"...
I'm picking this
One, two...
Matsumoto
Super Cooling Bazooka
You just said it before
You said you won't do that again!
My shoulder...
- You said it before, man
Is this going to be ok?
Hey! Hey!
Are you sure I'm going to be ok?!
You sure about that?
What's going on?
Wait a sec---!
What's "cooling" supposed to mean?
Come on...
- That's scary
Coming up: a cold, cold punishment for Matsumoto
[from before]
Please, stand here
Wha- again?
This is really scary
Get over here
Goggles and helmet...
- You don't need those
Goggles and...
G-gogg--
- Stand here and stay still
I need someone to trust
Ok, here is fine
I need someone I could trust
The hell are you sayin'?
I need mutual trust and goggles
Mutual trust and goggles
Hands behind
I told ya my shoulders hurt
I just want mutual trust and goggl-
Oh, shut up
Scary!
- Right before him!
I have no idea what's goin' to happen!
That's terrifying
Seriously I have no idea!!
You shouldn't draw back
This guy has been looking
at me like this from before
He chose me
Just face ahead
I'm gonna die here
Your hands!
This makes it ever scarier
I just want mutual trust and goggles
IT'S COLD
So freaking cold!!
Hamada got involved too
Hamada too
He froze up
It's frozen down here
It's getting worse
Aaaah! So cold!
Are you ok?
What's happening there?
Oh, it's actually frozen
It is, really
He looks fine
Holy crap
It also randomly got Hamada
That was something
It felt... good, for a moment
It did?     - Yes...
When did it?
Just for a sec
I swear I'm never touching those cards again
Well, that's what you said before
I had enough...
"Enough"? You didn't do anything!
No I mean like, it's going on for a while by now
There are still like... 2 or 3 I think
Man that was scary
Saliva Face Mask
This is no good
Theme: Saliva Face Mask
This is really nasty
I don't want this
I'm not touching em
Wait a sec!
You gotta pick one
I'm picking the remaining one
You ok with that?     - Yes...
Then pick one
Guests first
Can I?
- Yes
If so...
I see, the farthest one
- Yeah
Let's get over it
Man I really wanna survive this one...
Me too...
- I want to survive this too
This is really risky
Why is no one picking anything up?
Whatever, I'm taking this
I really hate this one...
One, two...
Saliva Face Mask
Alright!     - Nice
He was the first to pick one!
You're right
Coming up: HIKAKIN is going to be covered in saliva
It was him from the start     - Right
We were so worried too
Saliva Face Mask
Huh?
They brought us butter
Salt free butter
Close your eyes... and your mouth too
I see, so he's getting a lot of butter on his face
I'd hate this one
- Yeah me too, a lot
Hope his ears will be fine
Here he goes
Aw, that's cute
That's totally fine
Yeah he was lucky it picked this
What's goin' on?
Doesn't seem so bad
When it was me, the dog was freakin' huge
This is just cute, that's it
He got chosen by this
This isn't bad
- Shouldn't be that way
It's warm
He's really diggin' it
He cleaned him up
Real good too
Totally
He licked him clean
Good boy
- Licked him clean?
Now he's all clean
He's still going
- That's a good dog
Why the artificial grass, though?
He got inside my nose
Thank you
Wasn't that good?
His tongue in my nose...
He got a lot of skulls
Yeah, 4 times
Thank God...
Next one is the last
The last one...
What's that?
Cockveyor Belt
The hell is this?
What the-?
Theme: Cockveyor Belt
Alright
Here
- Hamada is still intact
Here, here
This one looks shady
Are we flipping them all at once?
How about we
Go in circle from here?
Please, please, please
HOUSEI
It may be Matsumoto,
so you should go first Tanaka
Should I go instead?
Yeah, go Tanaka
TANAKA
It can't be me, it just can't
ENDO
Yeah, that's what I meant!
Holy crap!
That's good, that's good
So it's either one of us or Hikakin...
Alright alright alright
How should we flip those?
The three of you all at once
All together?     - Yes
Should we count?
Man, I can't stand this anymore
Come on, we're almost done
Let's count it
Here goes nothing
One, two...!
Cockveyor Belt
Such a bad luck!
Yeah today was bad
- It was
Ohh, looks good
Such a beautiful finale
What's this about?
How does this work?
This will make them travel to him
I see now
Use the chair as a support
A bit closer
Ok, let's go
Yes
Three, two, one, start!
Well yeah, that hurts
- It does, really
That must hurt
Here comes a big one!
Don't move around
The last one
Here comes, here comes
- This is bad
That's our main dish
No doubt this will hurt     - Yes
What?
The hell?
I think it hurts more than I tought
Its juice came out!
For real
You ok? Is the juice a problem?
- It's fine
I was wondering whose juice was it
What the hell dude
Watermelon, of course
Hamada...
Do you think it's fine this way?
Why?
You never got punished
- I think it's fine
The audience isn't satisfied
I think you have to do at least one of them
I told you it's fine this way
I won't let you escape
Coming up: one last big shriek from Hamada
Just one
You're free to pick one
Which number in order from the top?
There are 12 in total
- You don't have to be so desperate about it
Ehhh? Come on...
Which one do you choose?
The second one
The first one
Was this one, Cockveyor Belt
You managed to escape
the Cockveyor Belt
And here's the one you
wished for, number two
Endless vinegar rapid-fire
Hamada
Endless Vinegar Rapid-fire
This is a good one
You picked a good one!
Mouth open, eyes closed
Ok, let's go
Like this, smooth rapid-fire
Smoothly
- I see, it's nice
Don't open your eyes
Translation & Subtitles by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
I can't breathe!
It stinks!
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Here comes that shout
www.facebook.com/shionnotsukai
I was expecting it
Want to support my translations? Consider donating @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
You did it!
- It means it's morning
That means it's 5 A.M.
It's 5 A.M., huh...
He shouts like this every morning
WWW.SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
WWW.FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
WWW.KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
if you want to support my translations, please like my FB page
You can also donate few dollars on my ko-fi page to show support
this is a no-profit fansub made by a fan for other fans. No copyright infringement intended. All copyrights are reserved to their respective owners
one last blank space I feel like filling up with nothing