The First Annual Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende, Chiki Chiki
The third "Get into character with 100 yen items"
Let's meet at Star Wars~!!
Endo said you're noisy
Please wait a moment...
I kept my voice down already, because I know you guys will complain
Matsumoto-san kept saying "So loud, right? He's so loud"
And all I did is a little nod
That's just the same as saying it   -Exactly, he said it
What's wrong with you?
All I did is a little nod, and still, I got my ass kicked
So we did drag queens and Showa stars before   -Yes, we did
And this time, it's Star Wars   -Yes, Star wars
Get into character with 100 yen items
Chewbacca
Yoda
Stormtrooper
Darth Vader
Jabba the Hut
This time, the following characters are selected from Star Wars, the movie loved around the world
Please enjoy the show with your smartphone in one hand, and compare them with the actual characters
First of all, let's draw and decide each member's character
Ready, set
Oh, it's him!   -This is it!
Hamada's character is Jabba the Hutt
It's Jabba the Hutt   -How the heck am I going to do this?
You're super advantaged!   -Exactly
You can do it with just 200 yen
Excuse me, excuse me
Stop messing with me, dude!
Barely enough indeed   -No way
Right in front of the entrance already!!
The members have a budget of 10,000 yen in total
This time, let's decide the budget that each of them can use
Please, this is crucial
Of course, more is better
Hope you can get 2,000 yen
Wow, 1,000 yen
Housei Chewbacca 1,000 yen
Only 1,000 yen?
Chewbacca with 1,000 yen is gonna be awful
That's gonna be awful
How are you going to make it look hairy with just 1,000 yen?
Yeah, exactly
He's not even hairy in real life
The budget for each member is as above
Stormtrooper
Jabba the Hutt
Chewbacca
Yoda
Darth Vader
No way, Hamada-san don't need 2,000 yen
Why the heck?
Not enough, not enough
You're gonna have 1,800 yen left
Just go home and grab a coarse sweater
A loosely woven one
First of all, they will go shopping at a 100 yen shop
Then, they'll make their character costume
And finally, they will perform a skit on stage together, and show us their character
It's Chewbacca
I want to make something that looks exactly like Chewbacca
Please wear this mask
Oh, are you guys selling this now?
No, we're not selling it
Not selling it?   -It's not for sale
Eh? It's not for sale?
Many people say they really want this
The Gaki no Tsukai mask
Okay
Chewbacca
I'll walk around and see what's useful
First thing first, I need some yarns
The face and the impression as a whole are very important
I found it, I found the yarns
The color of Chewbacca, this one right?
Burnt brown color
This color looks good too
I'll use both of these colors
And make them think "Wow, there's two kinds of color, he has amazing attention to detail"
Can these be those fangs?
Those fangs...
LEGO bricks
Is this going to work?
I'm afraid that I'll swallow it by accident
In order to keep within the 1,000 yen budget, Housei continues to select the items carefully
Chewbacca carries a bag, right?
Oh, I found it, this one!
This one, this one!
This is it, this is it
How mcuh?
Oh, 200 yen!!
It's out of my reach
To be honest, 2,000 yen is quite a lot
Darth Vader
It's all about the face, right?
His mouth looks like this, isn't it?
The tip of this thing
These look good too
This one is better
Look at this
Oh my god, everything looks good
Look at this shape, it's made to cover your mouth
Perfect fitting
He continues to search for items in black color
I'm losing my mind
I saw those inks and thought "oh, that's good"
I can't stop thinking about making myself black
I think I'm quite lucky compared to the other members
Which member do you worry about most?
I'm most worried about my duo partner
It's nearly impossible to look like R2-D2
It's not in human form
I only have 1,000 yen, right?
Yes, only 1,000 yen
Said to be the most protective mask against Corona, the Gaki mask
Let's go
I want to be fussy about the form
It has the most unique form within all characters
So I have to make sure I hide my body well
Searching for items that can hide one's body
This looks good
Shower curtain
Hide my body
(To hide one's body) Cylinder, are they selling it?
Oh, I think I found it
Too small, too small, no way
Definitely impossible
Aren't there any cylinders?
Do you think the other members can do well?
Who do you mean?   -Like Hamada-san
Hamada-san is 0 yen, right!!
He doesn't need to buy anything
Hamada-san, please wear this mask first
Okay, let's go
You don't need it?
What do you mean?
He has a big body, so...
Jabba the Hut
Oh, there are some towels here
These are probably too small
Maybe these felts could work?
But then I'll need to buy a whole lot of it
This looks good!!
Glad that I found this, better buy two of these
Just in case it's not enough
Eh, I didn't know there's such a thing
How are you going to make a big body?
That's a good question
I need something like a base to make my body look big
Using just newspaper is too inefficient
Hula hoop, and it can be assembled
So just assemble it and it'll become a hula hoop
I see, I see
The shop assistant was staring at me just now
This thing could be the base, right?
Just put this inside and cover it with fabric, that should work, right?
Right? This is perfect
What else can this guy do?
Yoda
I need to become Yoda with 1,500 yen
Megaphone
These can be Yoda's ears
Too big
Pardon me?
It's too big
Yes, it's too big, and when I put it here, I hear absolutely nothing
I'll need to say "pardon me" all the time
He bought a torch for the lightsaber
1,500 yen is not enough
Sorry, but I can't see this
What should I do?
I really can't see it
His reading glasses are not with him today
What do you think about the other members?
Tanaka is good at handicraft
He's C-3PO, right?
Their body shapes match too
So I think Tanaka should do well
The main point of C-3PO is that robot look and metallic appearance
So I'll put effort into those aspects of the character
Well, this is it, right? This kind of color
This kind of color is ideal
Of course it should have a gold body
But I want to put focus on making it's eyes look good too
Oh, look, this is already C-3PO
C-3PO's eyes look exactly like this
I want that...
Something like a belly band
This should do the job
This is good
But well, this is a bit...
The texture is too rough...
I have sensitive skin, so...
Excuse me
Maybe I can use this too, huh?
Stormtrooper
It's mainly in white color, white and black
So...
It's actually quite easy
I never paid attention to this character though
He's a super minor character, huh?
I'm the protagonist of this show though
What about this?
The color is not right though
Not quite right
The color need to be whiter
Spending all of the time searching for white items
I see
??? should work
This should do the job
100 yen each?   -Yes
Having 4 of these should be enough, leaving some leeway
So I don't even need to spend 1,500 yen...
I found so many other things that I want
In private
After purchasing the materials, the members will now make their character costume
They're now in their own room, and begin working
Stormtrooper
This one is easier to recognize, right?
This one is better
Yoda
Looking good with reading glasses
The non-slip sheet
I should have bought one more
Are you barely within budget, Endo-san?
Barely within 1,500 yen
Then sorry, you have to stick to these items
Is it possible to borrow it from someone?
Can I borrow just 200 yen? Nope?
Jabba the Hut
Why do I need to do this kind of thing?
Grumbling about the theme
I don't even freaking know about him!
Ouch!
Immediate divine retribution
We don't need anymore evidence for the judge (of Hamada aging)
Darth Vader
Assembling the purchased materials in various ways
And transforming it into the desired shape
Freaking good, right?
You're terrified, right? Seriously
I'm terrified of myself too
Chewbacca
Chewbacca Housei is now making the base
Looking good, very good
It all starts here
Can you imagine the final form?
Yes, I can
The characters are inside my mind
I've been imagining it for many times
I have no hesitation in regard to this
Tanaka with absolute confidence
15 minutes later
Tanaka
Tanaka, hey
Yes!
You're done?
No, not yet
You're done already?
No I'm not done yet, dude!
I didn't say I'm done
You've finished it?
All that's left is to wear it
To wear it?   -So fast
Just to wear it?
As long as the atmosphere is similar...
We need to do a skit together, right?
Yes
Should you tell us about it now?
Basically each member will go on stage one by one, and have a little battle
Will the audience be touched by the story?
That depends on your acting ability
After this, the members will gather as their character
Check out their final costumes!
The members have been making their character with 100 yen items
And now, it's finally the time for them to gather at the studio!
Check out their final costumes!
The Imperial Army, led by Darth Vader, which aims to conquer the entire universe
And the Jedi Knights, who are the guardians of peace and justice
There has been a fierce battle ongoing between the two parties
Princess Leia!
Luke Skywalker
Where did she go?
Damn it!
Stormtrooper
Bath chair
Eye mask
Paper cup
Insole
Ladle & Spatula
Kitchen paper
Diapers
Bath boots
Stormtrooper
Using a bath chair as his head
And wrapping the whole body with kitchen paper
The costume has been done reasonably
Where is Princess Leia?
Stormtrooper, you are no match for him, step back
Rubbish bin
Spatula
Torch
Calculator + Labels
Socks
Rubbish bags
Insulation sheet
Slipper
The Darth Vader reproduced with 2,000 yen
The calculator on his chest has been colorized with stick notes
We can clearly see that he is paying attention to details
Seems like you've gone through a lot of training, Skywalker?
However, you're no different to a baby in front of me!
Luke-sama!
C-3PO
What have you done to Luke-sama!
Wrapping paper
Toy balls
Goggles
Storage bag
Bathtub for kids
Slipper
The insufficiency of wrapping paper, has been compensated by the storage bag
This is the limit of 1,000 yen budget
Ah, but there's nothing I can do
What should I do? Oh gee!
Someone!
Someone, please!
Oh! R2!
Bathtube (large)
Mesh sink strainer
Aluminum sheet
Sport socks
Futon scissors
The unique form is reproduced with bathtub and aluminum sheet
However, it looks terrible from the back
Please help us, R2!
I see! That's a great idea!
Chewbacca! Chewbacca!
Yarn x 2 types
Long Reach Catcher
Whipping machine (part)
Felt fabric
Shoulder bag
Rubbish bag
Slipper
It wasn't possible to buy enough yarn with 1,000 yen, and he doesn't look hairy at all
Only the regions around his face has been done appropriately
Even Chewbacca?!
Ah! What should I do?
Someone, please! Please help us!
Wait a second!
That's it
Just leave it to me!
I knew you would come, Yoda
Clothespin
Butterfly net
Felt fabric
Door mat
Torch&drawing paper
Rain coat
Non-slip sheet
Sandal
The main part is the coat, which is made by connecting multiple rain coats
Furthermore
The facial expressions were carefully drew with a pen
Luke, look carefully
Damn it! This guy is really tough
I've been waiting for this moment
I'm a man who will do anything for money
You Jedi knights are hurting my business
Curtain x 2
Socks
Hula hoop
Sandal
The body is covered with two curtains
Hula hoop is used to make the body look big
He did nothing to his face, and went on the stage shamelessly
Here you come! Jabba the Hutt!
Good! Stormtrooper, go beat Yoda with Jabba the Hutt!
Come on!
I'll defeat you guys and restore peace
Not yet! Not yet!
Luke, look at me!
Luke, remember to look at me
It hurts...
Hooray!
Hooray! Hooray!
We did it! Hooray!
We did it
Hooray! Hooray! We defeated them!
Peace has been restored!
Well...
With this...
We're gonna get the Galaxy Award (for TV shows)
Really? We can?
Finally, we got it
Gaki never won the award yet, right?   -Yeah, finally
This dude is awful, right?   -Yes, agreed
Why?
You did absolutely nothing
No, I did
That didn't cost you anything
Yes, it did
I spent over a thousand yen
Eh?   -Eh?
Tanaka, why did it take you so long with just that?
Well, I've only got 1,000 yen
And if that's all you did
I hope you gave me your 500 yen   -You're right
1,000 yen must be enough
What the heck is this?
He's wearing paper diapers?!
Wow, yeah, he is   -That doesn't matter
Honestly, I think my costume has the highest quality
And furthermore, I didn't even spend all of my 1,500 yen
Oh, you still have some money left?
This is for you guys
And furthermore, I didn't even spend all of my 1,500 yen
Oh, you still have some money left?
Yes, yes
This is for you guys
I had 300 yen left   -Why this?
Why the heck?
Matsumoto had 300 yen left after shopping, and he decided to...
Shall I buy a bouquet of flowers?
For some reason, he decided to buy some roses
No, no, that's not right
You bought us some presents?
You're so kind
Can I take this? Thank you
He even bought us presents!
He finished it with ease
Sorry for hitting you just now
No, no, I didn't expect that, but no worries
I didn't expect to be beaten in this costume at the center of the stage
When you got beaten up, the cameras were shaking
I bet they thought Yoda is so damn weak