TPF
Everyone, have you seen
f
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tsukitei Hosei
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
today's set?
It's for that, right?
What we're doing today.
Yes, that's right.
This time, we're trying something different by telling scary stories.
So that's what we're all doing today.
The season is really wrong though.
It really is.
It's way too early for this.
We're getting ahead of ourselves.
I thought it would be nice to try it.
Here we have A and B,
there are two kinds of cards.
I see.
Both of them
have things that show up a lot in scary stories
They have certain words written on them.
The way you're speaking is scary.
He's getting in the mood.
He's getting into it.
I think I'm getting into it.
We have to set the right mood for this.
That's right.
And so, using two of these words...
Sorry, I can't hear you!
He overdid it so much we couldn't hear him.
You're overdoing it.
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents:
Down Town's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Translator:
Typesetter & Proofreader:
J-Lan
Otviss
**We also have Facebook and Twitter.**
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
______________________________________________________________________
If you ever see this video being distributed online but not by us, keep in mind that on Youtube
individuals may make money off of sharing fansubs like this that are not their own. Please go back and
support the original creators. Fansubbing is voluntary and is not meant to generate profit. You can
download episodes on our website instead. Thanks for watching!
Impromptu! Scary Story Inn
A and B, they will pick one of each card and
weave the words into their improvised scary story!
And so, what kind of scary stories will be told!?
Well then, who's first?
How about you, Tanaka?
Starting from me?
Yeah.
Alright, I'll go first.
First an A card.
A is...
Ah, that's good.
It's perfect.
We have that inn atmosphere.
You got it in the first card, the inn.
Ah, "neighbor".
So the room next door.
That's no problem.
You got really good cards.
You already have the ideal setting.
The "inn" and the "neighbor",
I'll use them for my scary story.
This is...
Inn
Neighbor
Um...
Not something I heard from someone else,
it's something that actually happened to me.
I was with my family,
and we agreed to go to an inn.
I think it's nice
to go to an inn with a hot spring once in a while
and spend some time relaxing.
I heard there was
uh...
a really nice hot spring inn in Izu.
So I went
to the hot spring with my family.
And it was
a wonderful inn.
and the food was really good.
They even served sashimi.
It was actually really good.
Later, when we decided it was time to sleep,
right before we laid down,
Knock knock knock knock!
Scary.
That's scary.
There was knocking on the wall.
We weren't making too much noise, right after I said it was time to sleep...
Knock knock knock!
I just thought, "What the hell?"
So I used the phone, to call the waitress.
The front desk.
"There's a really loud knocking noise coming from the room next door."
"What is it?"
And so, the waitress went
to the room next door to investigate.
But when she came to our room, she said
"There are no guests in the room next door."
"Today there aren't any guests assigned to that room."
"How can that be?"
"We heard really loud knocking
coming from that room."
"Ah..."
"It could be that..."
"That?"
"What is that?"
It just so happened
that in the room next door,
a person had died.
And apparently, the person who died
really didn't want to
go to that inn.
Um...
He was forced to go against his will.
Forced to go?
He really
hated the fact that
he had come to the inn.
That's when, that person who forced him...
He stabbed the person who forced him to death.
After they arrived at the inn?
Yes.
And he...
He could have done it before they went.
And he also, well...
Ended up dying, it was that sort of incident.
And that's what happened...
That's what happened at the inn.
I though, "Yeah, that's pretty scary".
It's still going on?
But then, when I looked at my son...
He was making a "I didn't want to come" face.
Scary Story Ends
A "I didn't want to come" face?
The ending is a "I didn't want to come" face?
That was just awful.
You didn't even use the word Neighbor once during the story.
You used "next door" but not "neighbor".
Wasn't it awful?
No, no...
I really wanted to set the right mood.
You know, for this kind of scary story
I don't think we
should be laughing.
We really shouldn't laugh.
If we're gonna do this, we gotta do it right.
We have to "get in the zone" while telling these, otherwise
Just like in your story, we'll get possessed.
Who's next?
Go, 'Zaki.
This is gonna be scary.
Right.
This is 'Zaki's forte.
Ah, that's pretty good.
"Hair"
Too bad it's something this person is steadily losing.
I'm not losing it.
That's scary.
This is...ah, what's fashionable. Sorry.
Don't you know what "wearing your years" means?
We're too young for that.
Coriander?*
*For the americans: Coriander = Cilantro
Coriander.
That coriander?
This... how many years ago was it?
Hair
Coriander
Well, it wasn't that long ago.
It's something that really happened to me.
I really hate coriander.
Like, when it's in ramen or other food,
I always avoid it or put it aside.
But one time,
everyone kept telling me, "Don't avoid eating it".
But I hate it, I can't stand the smell.
I don't like the smell, so I told them "Sorry, it smells bad", but there were people who really liked it.
Since the five of us were sharing, they kept telling me to stop avoiding it.
I said, "Alright then", and just ate all the coriander.
So later, I took a taxi home.
I'm sorry, this is a bit disgusting but,
I threw up.
Yeah, and then
the taxi driver,
he said,
"I want you to pay for the cleaning..."
"Hmm, alright, I understand."
"I'll pay for the cleaning. I understand."
I told him I'd do it but he said,
"I told you to pay for the cleaning!"
"Yes."
"I know."
"It's because I ate coriander and
I just, uh...
felt a bit car sick and threw up."
"I'm sorry."
"What's wrong with you? I told you to pay for the cleaning! Pay up!"
And after saying that, the driver's...
hair went like...
It started wiggling.
"What's this?!"
"Why? Why is it wiggling like that?"
"Wait a minute!"
"Please stop!", but the hair came towards me.
It came near my neck and...
It wrapped around my neck...
And that's when  I woke up.
And that's when, I woke up.
It was all a dream?
I woke up...
That's just...
Scary Story Ends
Can't we just stop this?
Isn't this too awful?
I just couldn't get my thoughts in order at all.
I knew it.
Yeah well, that happens to everyone.
I could tell.
This is a bit difficult.
The next challenger is Hamada.
The first card was "water well".
The second card was "girl with a skirt".
"Water well" and "girl with a skirt", huh?
Yes, yes.
Water
Well
Girl
with a
skirt
In elementary school, around the 3rd grade,
there was a girl
who wore a red skirt.
In her neighborhood,
she was known as a sweet
and lovely girl.
Suddenly, one day, she disappeared.
She had gone missing.
The people in the neighborhood
and the other parents
handed out flyers and went around looking for her.
They did those things but...
they began thinking it had been a kidnapping.
They looked for months, but they couldn't find her.
It just so happened that,
there was a water well in the neighborhood.
When they looked in the well,
the girl had fallen there.
Scary Story Ends
Did they save her?
He left the ending open.
No, if you think about it...
Did they save her?
Did she survive?
Well, this is a scary story so...
Then why not have her appear as a ghost?
Wasn't it too short?
That was the best I could do, sorry.
When I got the word "water well"
I just thought, "I'll have some fall in it"
Someone has to fall in if there's a well.
I thought it'd be an open ending.
You're next, Endo.
Yes.
Very nice.
"Expressway"
Is it alright to have that?
And B is?
This is...
"Thin cardigan"?
Well, I think these are alright.
It's fine, "expressway" and "thin cardigan".
Well...
Expressway
Thin
Cardigan
Sometimes, when traveling from Tokyo to Osaka,
instead of using the bullet train,
I would travel by car.
One time, while I was on the expressway,
I remembered something, you see, I like cars and I replace them constantly.
So when I
got my car sold...
You got your car sold?
When I sold my car
and got another car, the guy told me
"Try to not look behind you."
The car dealer?
The car dealer.
And uh...
While replying "You got it",
I just took off.
Later...
There was a car behind me that kept flashing its headlights.
I got really scared after remembering,
but the car kept insisting with its headlights.
When I looked
behind me with the rear-view mirror...
When I looked,
it wasn't a car.
It was someone wearing a thin cardigan.
Of course.
It a really slender old woman wearing a thin cardigan.
"Open the trunk!", she said.
Knock knock knock !, "Let me ride in the back!"
And so,
I got so scared that
now I always travel to Osaka in the bullet train.
Scary Story Ends
Right, what did you think?
Everyone, please share your opinion.
That was Tanaka's "knock knock knock knock",
his partner stole it.
Yeah, you're right.
This duo is gonna fight for it.
That "knock knock knock knock".
Matsumoto, want to go next?
Alright, whatever.
Pine
Forest
Face
"Pine forest" and "face".
"Pine forest" (Matsubayashi)
Pine forest?
This one's gonna be hard.
This is...
Pine
Forest
Face
something that happened last week.
I was returning home late
and I was wondering what to do.
"I should go to the convenience store
and go home", so I went to the store.
I looked around the store and
I bought some things.
Since I was already at the store,
I thought it was better to keep walking home.
I was walking by myself in the dead of night.
When suddenly, "Matsubayashi!"
"Aren't you Matsubayashi?"
His name...
He didn't even use an honorific.
"Sorry, I'm..."
"You're Downtown's Matsubayashi, right?"
Who makes that mistake?
"You're with Hama-chan"
"Your partner's name is Hamada, isn't it?"
"Yoshimoto Creative Agency's Downtown"
"You're Downtown's Matsubayashi!"
That one's wrong.
"I'm sorry but, who are you?"
Right.
"What do you mean? I'm always watching you"
"You're always on TV", and then he started listing
Your shows.
all my regular shows.
He was your fan.
"I've watched everything,
I also record it all,
and I would never delete it."
"That's how much I watch you, Matsubayashi."
I couldn't believe it.
"You know,
you've gotten everything right,
but my name is
the only thing that's wrong."
"Why?"
"Do you know why
I keep thinking that
you're Matsubayashi?"
"When you get home, look in the mirror."
When I looked in the mirror,
My face...
My face was covered with something.
It was like...
my face looked like I was a "Matsubayashi".
What are you pressing?
Ah, wrong one.
You gotta be kidding me!
You're kidding, right?
Scary Story Ends
You pressed your teacup!
You shouted, "Ahh!"
You pressed on it like this.
You went, "Ah!"
I was thinking, "Why isn't it going off?"
It wasn't going to.
Yeah, it wouldn't.
The staff must have thought that I wanted to drink tea.
What do you want to do?
There are still cards left.
Of course there are still cards,
since Yamasaki has only
done it once so far!
Hosei, go ahead.
Ah, take this one.
This one.
Music
Room
"Music room"
That's a really good one.
That does work.
A music room.
I just remembered...
I'll do it about that.
That was quick.
Swing
"Swing"
Ah, a swing.
They're near each other.
This happened when I was in fifth grade.
If you asked me why I remember that, I'd say
it's because I had just moved there.
Since I had just moved,
I couldn't remember my homeroom teacher's face.
I wanted to fix that, so
in order to remember my teacher's face,
I waited until everyone went home
and just stayed in the classroom.
That's because, if I stayed there,
the teacher would come and ask me why I was still there.
I thought I could meet the teacher there.
I actually, had feelings for that teacher.
Seriously.
It was a female teacher?
She was female.
She was an older woman though.
I liked the teacher,
but I never told her, I didn't want to confess to her.
Because, it was embarrassing.
It was embarrassing to say you liked an older teacher.
Is this the right tone for a scary story?
I thought this would be a scary story.
Yeah, the tone is wrong.
It was embarrassing, so I wasn't able to tell her.
While I was still wondering what to do, she said, "Hosei, it's time to go home", and I replied, "Okay, I'll go home!"
But I decided to follow her.
So I was following her...
Tap tap tap
You could hear her footsteps.
Hm?
Yeah.
I was wondering why her footsteps made that noise.
That teacher was always barefoot, walking barefoot.
In our school,
they would do that.
Then why does it matter?
Then it's normal, it wouldn't be surprising.
It would be normal.
Everyone would do that...
I thought it was only that teacher.
And her footsteps,
tap tap tap,
I looked from behind some cover and
it was the music room.
There it is.
Yeah, there it is.
tap tap tap, she went into the music room.
"Why is she going into the music room at this hour?"
I looked at her like this.
Like with binoculars?
Like this,
I used my hand-held telescope to look.
Using my hand-held telescope.
Just do it normally.
The teacher,
she got on the piano and started playing.
There wasn't anyone else.
There were no students, but she played the piano.
"I'm scared!"
"I'm scared, I'm scared..."
"I can't move!"
"A swing..."
"I want to ride a swing."
That's just nonsense.
You want to ride a swing?
It doesn't make any sense.
It was just his desire.
Scary Story Ends
What was that?
I didn't get all the walking about.
In the end, you could say that the one
that felt the most like a scary story was mine.
Really?
Alright, then you do the last one, Matsumoto.
The last one.
I was the only one who could tell a scary story.
I bet I could do it
if you gave me cards while talking.
That's amazing.
Then give him one card at a time.
"Whistle"
This was
back when I...
How many cards?
This is the last one so... 6 cards.
Right.
Sure, that's fine.
Is this okay?
Yeah, it's fine, the rules don't matter.
Next
Matsumoto will use six cards to tell a story!?
Then you'll get six cards while speaking.
Matsumoto will use 6 cards to try to tell a story!
To finish, Matsumoto will try to tell a story while successively getting six cards.
Whistle
The first card is "whistle".
I went camping once.
It was back in middle school, I went with another friend.
Right? That time, that friend said
Uh...
What was it? "The guy I invited couldn't go, let's go together, Matsumoto". He wasn't a close friend but,
I thought he would be lonely.
And he just kept going like...
Whistling at me.
Cellphone
"Alright, I'll go", I told him.
So we decided to confirm everything by phone.
Despite being in silent mode,
the phone vibrated like crazy when he called.
Laughter
But the vibration wasn't like regular vibration.
It was very intense, but I still answered.
And then,
I started hearing laughing, like in the show "Dorifu Dai Bakusho"
I didn't say anything but it laughed.
It went like "Mwahaha"
School
You're going too fast.
Once you use it, I get another one.
That's right.
I can keep this up forever but...
I won't even know what I'm talking about.
The next comes as soon as you say it.
Anyway, the camp was really fun.
We were supposed to only stay one night but
we kept saying, "One more night, one more night"
Before we knew it, it had been 2 weeks.
2 weeks?
This was just camping?
That's when
Prison
I finally noticed
We just kept eating the same thing...
There was a jailhouse...
"This isn't a camp..."
"I've been caught."
Prison
This video was brought to you by tofu panda fansubs
"This is a prison..."
Knock knock knock knock knock!
That's my...
Lullaby
That's what we used.
"Help me!"
"Please help me!"
"You're too loud,
Matsubayashi."
This guy again.
♪ I am not... ♪
♪ Matsubayashi ♪
You're so annoying.
So annoying.