Searching for the legendary "Marine Serow",
It is our hunter's 14th day
in the Savanna without encountering it.
The serow is still nowhere to be seen.
Bro.
Yo Bro.
Whaddaya doin'?
Eh?
Ah, hunting.
Aah of course, in such an area.
Yo whaddaya huntin'?
Yes?
Whaddaya huntin'?
A serow.
A serow?
Aa, I don't think
there are any here, you know.
What do you do for work?
Bro?
What kinda work do you do?
Well, it varies.
I can't directly say "this" is my job.
Oh! Now this sounds interesting...
I see..!
Well..
I, what do you think I do?
Elephant, you're an elephant.
Well yea I'm an elephant, but my occupation?
What is my, you know, occupation?
I don't know really...
You don't?
I don't. Sorry.
Oh...
Yeah.
Hmm, you know...
Don't you feel
a little disgusted by me?
No no no.
Like "Aah, some weird guy came around!",
didn't you think that?
No no, not at all.
You can say it, it happens a lot.
It's ok.
It really-
No it's ok.
For real tho...
You know..
Yes?
My friends...
...they say...
that I'm pretty weird and...
This is just between us, but...
I'm a little...
I'm sort of a masochist, you know?
Y'know?
Me?
Oh...
Like.. uh..
I wanna get shot, kinda
By somebody
You know?
Yea...
Could you... would you mind?
Would you mind?
Mind what?
Shooting me.
I'm... hunting a serow, you know.
I understand but, just... just a lil.. you know.
When I get shot.
I might react like "Uwaa, I got shot!"
and get a freaking fluffy feeling.
Like "I got shot woaaah" and like, you know,
feel an excitement I never felt before.
Would you mind?
I'm hunting a serow and... you know, I'm kinda short on ammunition.
Yea, I'm sorry.
Aa, well...
Your wordplay is also ok for me, but...
Could you go more like
"Fuck off you Indian elephant!"?
And I'm not an Indian elephant, so...
I'll probably be like "hyaaaa!!"
Do you feel me?
Ah, kinda.
Aaah let's already do it!
Say "Fuck off you dirty little Indian elephant!"
and when I'm about to run away,
you shoot me from behind like "pam!"
Aaa.. I could get in trouble for this you know!..
Could you not just g away?
The serow won't come else..
Again, there's word play in your sentence.
There is no word play!..
And just add "Fuck off,
you dirt Indian elephant!", please?
But I won't say it.
You play around with the words again.
I don't!
Aaa, so that's how it is.
There's no helping it I guess!
Aaa, he's not shooting, eeh.
Man hurry up!
No it's a waste.
You're embarrassing me.
I beg you, please shoot?
Just... it's ok, please?
Ok?
Hmm, where should I aim at?
Eh?! Where would be good..
Ass! And..
at last my face!
Face?
Shooting the face is, you know,
too problematic.
It's too dangerous!
Ah you may be right.
But I could be like "hyaaaa!" you know.
I really can't shoot the face. Sorry.
Then my ass?
Your behind?
Say "Ah!, fuck off you dirty Indian elephant!"
please?
Understood.
Thank you, I mean it.
"Fuck off, you dirty Indian elephant!"
Ah! What is happening!?
Hmm, maybe I'm not a masochist after all?
It didn't feel good at all.
I can imagine.
Ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!!
It's bad!
I feel dizzy all the sudden!
What should I do?
Don't ask me man.
I'm hella scared!
Don't tell me.
I feel dizzy!
I don't care!
What should I say to my wife?
How would I know?!
She'll say "Dear, what did you do again!?"
You asked me to shoot you
although I was just here hunting for a serow.
I didn't think you'd actually shoot.
But you begged for it
so I thought it can't be helped!
And you were also disturbing my hunt.
What!? I didn't do anything!
Maybe I'm a sadist?!
'the fuck do I know!
I'm going elsewhere now!
Dark! It's getting dark!
This is bad bad bad, ouch ouch ouch.
It hurts super bad.
My body's tingling.
My tongue feels funny.
It's tingling now. It's tin-
I'm scared. My tongue is ting-
What is with you?
It's weird!
It hurts!
Ouch ouch ouch ouch.
My wife will get angry.
She'll know that I did it again!
Again? How many times did you pull that off?
Why is it only now tha-
Why aren't you saying anything?