TPF
Typesetter: Fran
Translator: Tako
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
Pochi
Ryouko-san!
Ah..Pochi...
Good evening
Long time no see...
Is your dad home?
da-
...your father, uh wait
hold o...
Yeah.
Excuse me
It's a pleasure to meet you again
Who is this?
From your home in Osaka...
...taking care of me..
back then..
Ah~
yes yes
I'll tell him!
Good evening. It's a pleasure to meet you again
Uhm, excuse me
Outside, lets talk out here
Okay
You came from Osaka?
Yes
I'm surprised you found us
Yes, well, uhm
I heard..your family
had moved...but wasn't really notified
...kinda surprised me there
Oh, yeah?
Yes
So, what is it?
Well, nothing important but..
Uh...
I didn't know we moved so
I was trying to follow you
You know?
I was glad to find you all and..
So...
right now you're owning..
other dogs now or...?
no no no
Oh, really?
Mhm
So then we can all go...
Well..
This area...isn't like the last place we were at, ya know?
Different from the apartments back there, right?
Around here..
They call it "High-Class residential"
Pretty expensive to live here...
Oh, yes... Without a doubt
Like, the neighbours...
Did you see their home?
Yes, I saw it
Pretty expensive too!
What kind of house is that?
Rin..Re..Revolver..or something like that I think
Just something really exquisite!
Really!
...and over there, Tanaka's got a Doleman
I'm familiar with that style!
Oh, I see
I guess, having high quality homes could also mean high quality dogs
Everyone's got pure breeds around here...
I'm sure
Wait..
I'm...
What?
Huh?
I think I might be misunderstanding...
Did I do something...to upset you?
No no no, nothing like that
Well..
Before..
In Osaka when the manager visited the apartment..
And..
I accidentally ended up barking at him
Because I didn't know who he was back then and...
...maybe that was a wrong move by me..?
Well, that's kind of your job too, so...
I mean...
yes yes
He was a total stranger to me..
But there's still acceptable and unacceptable times to bark, ya know?
And even..
...if you bark ALL the time..
That's also a problem
You gotta know when to bark and when to not
Of course..
I guess making noises in general...
Like
I just get the feeling to need to bark. Right?
I guess, but I wouldn't really understand where you're coming from but...
since I'm not like you..it's something..
I understand
I wouldn't expect you to understand senirorities and all that...
In the workplace and..
You wouldn't really understand, would you?
No, I wouldn't
No
Well..
I don't wanna stop you from doing.. you and..
you probably knew what was going on right?
Yeah, a little bit...
but still..
maybe next time...
Perhaps...
I could..
no no no
(Context: Itao is offering him money)
Just...
Wait..
It's not like that!
I can't take this!
No
No, really...
Please
No please, It's alright
You have to...
I won't take this
I insist
Please
No!
I'm not here for that
Or anything like that...
I will make that clear...
Please, I don't really need it
You sure?
Yes
But maybe..perhaps..
I came all this way so..
You could take me, from now on
Well, good luck...
...with everything
I'm sure it won't really be easy for you but...
Uhm...
No...
I'd like to...
..Here..
..stay here..
If that's possible?
Well...
you know..
..A mutt..
...Mixed breed
Yes, I'm aware
Good
Alright
That's true, there's that factor too
Well, It's almost time Isn't it?
Yeah
Well, today's...
my day off so...
...go get some chinese or something
Really?
You're going out?
We should really go soon..
Yeah
Then I'll just stay at home
I don't really think we can have that
How about...Monday?
Have any plans then?
No, nothing for Monday
I'm free all day
All day?
Yes
Then let's talk again on Monday
If you are available yes, please
Yeah
So Monday, correct?
Will work for you?
Monday?
I mean, it doesn't have to be Monday
No, I am fine with Monday
Monday it is
Around what time should I come?
Afternoon.
Afternoon?
What time...
Well...probably around 4..5...o'clock
So monday, at 4
Same place. I'll be looking forward to it.
Alright
I apologize for showing up like this
I'm truly sorry
See you on Monday!
To be continued...