There are lots of different dishes in the world.
Our unimaginable imaginative
secretive cooking, mysterious cuisine!
Today we will be cooking an enigmatic dish!
Discovering Cuisines from Around the World
Subbed and timed (mostly) by : KIEmax
Typesetting proofed by: Otviss (http://tofupandas.tumblr.com/)
Translations proofed by: Oolong (http://dtr-subs.tumblr.com/)
What are you doing?
Let's go!
Hello!
Well then, let's hurry and introduce you to today's cooking instructor:
From Shimantogawa Cooking School, Mrs. Cathy Tsukamoto!
Here she is!
Shimantogawa Cooking School
Cathy Tsukamoto
You bastards! You bastards! You bastards!
IT'S OVER!
Teacher!
Teacher.
That hurt quite a bit you know?
You're energetic today, aren't you?
Well I can't help it since I have so much extra power
But that's something good, right?
Of course it is!
BABO BABO!*
*This is a phrase Cathy Tsukamoto says while pressing her chest
What is going on?
I'm gonna be late you know, gonna be late you know!
I'd press them, if you would just tell me, I would press them
No I don't want that, you'd sexually harass me immediately!
Really, because you'd touch these nipples at once!
I wouldn't do such a thing!
It's just a joke anyway...
Your clothes are very colorful today, aren't they?
True!
Well then...
Today I thought, you know, should I prepare something easy?
But since this is about the world's unusual cuisines, right teacher...
do you have something like that for us?
Well, does Mesopotamia ring a bell for you lot?
Mesopotamia?
Did you learn about the Mesopotamian civilization?
Ah, of course I know about Mesomotamia, teacher!
What?!
What is with you...
But I went recently. Haven't gone since graduation, but I did go
Oh really?
Your tongue got twisted, right?
Yes, exactly
But I know it, of course!
Mesopotamian civilization, Mesopotamian civilization
when you think of Mesopotamia, you think of pizza right?
That's correct!
Therefore it's pizza for today.
Ah, I see...
Really? Pizza?
Yes it's pizza today it's gonna be great!
Pizza is so delicious, right?
Yea, and people don't cook it at home much, do they?
Is that so?
You tend to rely on delivery, you know
Oh, the one that can deliver any time of day
Well, that's something I don't like
This is something I want to say today:
Like you get the delivery and then quickly dispose it
To me, this is also something that's unbelievable
That's right...
What?
It's nothing...
Now, let's start with the pizza.
Now, first let's start with the dough
Yea, begin stretching the dou...
Let's start...
What the hell is this...
This is it!
Teacher, this is...
...The dough of the pizza prototype, correct?
Exactly!
This is important!
Have you guys ever seen something like this?
No!
Isn't that something you can see a lot on TV?
Maybe it is after all...
Now from here on, you just gotta do it
From here on it is?
You just gotta do it, you just gotta do it
You just gotta do it, little kitty
What on earth are you saying, teacher?
I really don't get it
You're in a good mood today, aren't you?
Something good must've happened, right?
Okay, why don't you try then?
Use the centrifugal force!
Centrifugal force, huh?
Yes, you just use centrifugal force, I've seen it so I know
Okay, if I do it like this...
It becomes like this
That's wrong!
Okay?
You have to rotate it! Rotate it you know?
Listen carefully, you!
You rotate it like this!
Like that.
Vertically?
Not like this?
It's better if you throw it higher! Here, go ahead
Throw it higher, okay?
Okay
WATCH OUT!!!
Wait!
Are you okay?!
What are you doing?
Can't be helped if she feels shocked
Although I do understand how she feels too. But...
it's pointless to keep saying such things
Yea
Let's sprinkle some flour shall we?
Yes, let's!
Okaaay, you just gotta sprinkle it, you just gotta sprinkle it
Today Judy is coming!
What are you saying... Who is this "Judy"?
So who knows the answer to what this all becomes?
Ready made pizza dough, right?
Exactly
Got it... It's down here by your feet!
Now it's become like this
Great, is it not?
Teacher, you can easily make this at home too
Right, teacher?
Now, let's put our favorites on that, shall we?
This is the real thrill about homemade pizza
Exactly!
You put on your favori... That is one amazing hairstyle
You put your favorites on it, THAT'S the thrill about it all, teacher!
EXACTLY!!!
We have loads here
Yes we do!
What should we put in?
You know, I think we should go with the most conventional,
salami and bell pepper.
Salami and bell pepper then, let's put it on top!
Let's go!
What do you want?
Sausages!
Sausage, let's do it!
Sausage, right? Here you go
This too, BAM!
Let's add all sorts of things!
Shouldn't we remove the wrapping...?
Doesn't matter, we can leave it as it is.
Let's add whatever
Cheese too, okay?
Then, lets add myself too!
Thi.. This... Let's cover me up with this
What?
Well...
That's... Tha... That's not cooking, now is it?
What's your problem?
Whatever this is, it's not cooking...
What?
Yea it's not, you see...
If you step on it like that it'll get dirty, no?
It'll become unedible...
What is it with you?
Let go of me, quit it
Don't fight... Hey... Um, stop fighting...
I'll get you for this!
What's wrong with that person?
I have no idea
Discovering Cuisines from Around the World - until next week!
Goodbye