Traslation: Zurui
(Aho = Idiot or Idiotic)
The stars sure are pretty, huh?
Yeah
When you grow up, what will you become?
Probably a housewife...
Really?
If your wife.. I mean... groom was in front of your eyes right now, what would you do?
Huh?
Close your eyes
Guess who!
That voice is...
Ho Ho alien!
What are you doing?!
If you want this woman back, give me your father's automobile blueprints
Don't be stupid!
If you don't give it to me, this woman gets...
Watch ya gonna do? Watch ya gonna do?
I still didn't get to do anything with her!
Shut up!
Stop it!
I said to stop!
What ya gonna do? What ya gonna do?
It can't be helped!
Aho Aho man, help me!!
That last move was pretty awesome huh?
Aho Aho man
- Yeah?
He caught my girlfriend!
Please do something!
- OK!
*Wagashi = Japanese sweets
Aho Aho Wagashi!!
The Aho Aho Wagashi expires today
That has nothing to do with this!
What are you doing? Do something!
OK!
Aho Aho Water!!
Where are you aiming?!
The shock to Aho Aho man's head
does something unexpected
Kentaro-kun
Huh?
I...
I feel like I've been in a long dream
What?
What am I doing in these embarrassing clothes?
What happened Aho Aho man?
From now on, I will be a true hero!
For your sake
I will fight for this earth!
Aho AHo man!
You punk!
Punk... I'm a Ho Ho alien!
Get out of here now!
Damn it!
Wind 7 meters... North by Northwest... OK... got it!
I didn't see the punch!
He was just here!
Ladies don't belong in a fight
Aho Aho man, you're great!
Sorry it took so long!
Thank you Aho Aho man!
- Yes
Thank goodness
He got a shock to his head again
What are you doing?!
Yuko-chan!