Looks nice!
This place has changed completely.
Great.
September 24th 1996
The look of this station in the past was really shabby.
I don't hesitate to guide acquaintances anymore.
At Japan Railways Amagasaki Station
This time, we have come to our hometown Amagasaki.
How long has it been since last time?
I'm not sure.
It must have been so long.
I haven't been in this station for maybe more than 10 years.
Because people say Amagasaki has changed, we came here to confirm it with our won eyes.
I was astonished at this entirely changed station.
Me too.
I see Ama has been rapidly changing to the average.
They're normally making an announcement.
Looks so clean.
They sell goods in Japanese yen now.
Should he apologize?
Another currency "Amar" used to be circulated here.
Was it here?
Shioe.
It's the direction of our houses.
There is an exclusive residential district.
It is on a hill.
Shall we go to town?
Here is Hamachu's house.
Oh, Hamachu.
He was our classmate.
His father was a pro baseball player.
He wasn't a really good player.
And his son used to eat snots during classes.
Look at that mailbox.
Your letter will never be delivered if you post it in that.
Don't say that.
My letters were never be delivered.
I know that's just a fake.
I was cheated many times.
(no sub)
Do you think that wall is high?
We two jumped over the wall once when we ran away.
You don't need to say that.
But it's true. We jumped over that.
Ran and jumped.
We needed to do it to escape.
I can't say what we did before it.
(no sub)
You're joking!
I'm serious.
What are you doing here?
Are you Yumi?
Yeah.
Who?
She is Morioka's sister Yumi.
I can't recognize her because her look has changed.
What does your older brother do?
He is in a living room now.
Do you know your brother was mentioned in our song?
Don't say that!
I hate it!
Don't say anything about it!
Anyway, she is Morioka's sister.
(no sub)
Our elementary school, this is the worst place.
No, it's not worst!
This wasn't a bad place.
(no sub)
It hasn't changed over there.
Yeah.
We used to peel our penises over there.
It made us feel good.
We felt good when we climbed poles.
When I was the third grader, I didn't use to stop climbing there even after a class started.
When I saw Hamada at the first time, we were beside that gate.
When I went back home, you entered through the gate.
You were wearing a pantaloon.
Haven't you gone too far?
And had a perm, so I was surprised at your look.
And I was carrying a bag like this.
Yeah, though every student carried a satchel, only you carried a bag like a sandbag.
So, I though you must be an international student.
From Mongolia.
Your mother stood here every morning.
She volunteered to control us like this.
I saw her every morning here.
What disgusted me was,
when I didn't wash my face, she used to wipe my eyes with a handkerchief smeared by her saliva.
My father was here as well.
He used to stand there.
This place hasn't changed a bit.
The smell of broiled pig innards from Yamazato's shop!
Hiroshi!
Oh, dad, I haven't seen you for a long time.
I've regularly come here.
Where is a skewer?
I used to come here, skewer and eat it without permission.
This brings back memories!
You've been running this shop for a long time.
This food looks bad, however, tastes good.
Shake hands with our baby.
I know this baby will be the food later.
(no sub)
Look at the aluminum door.
There was a wooden door before, but we cut that door.
Others are wooden doors, but only that is the aluminum one.
We cut it with a saw.
A foreigner lived in the next apartment.
We stole his underwear.
We took it from a washing machine outside.
He suddenly opened a window and said "Don't steal my underwater."
"Don't come here again."
And we ran away.
We hid ourselves under the stairway.
After our friend went out, we went up ad entered his apartment.
We'd had a duplicate key made.
When he was attending PE class,
I picked a key from his pocket.
I gave it other friend and asked him
to have a duplicated key made.
(no sub)
Itao wanna overcome his father.
So, they are playing a sumo match.
He wanna win a sumo match.
In traditional Japanese way.
Let's see "Can Itsuji Itao overcome his father?"
Can Itsuji Itao overcome his father?
Itao came back to his hometown.
Can he overcome his father?
We leave judgment to his mother.
East side, father.
Look, his son looks so serious.
West side, Ichiro.
She is calling him Ichiro.
* The kanji of his name Itsuji
can also be pronounced Ichiro.
I don't still understand
why she calls her son Ichiro
though his name is Itsuji
His name is a bit hard for her to pronounce.
I see.
Father forgot to hold salt.
Can he beat him?
A horn of a train is sounding.
He is baring his testicles.
As if he wanna say his son was in it.
I see.
He is expressing it with his own body.
Showing his testicles.
Because we are outside now,
he may be arrested.
It might be good that he'll be arrested.
(no sub)
Look at over there.
About 200m ahead of us.
There was Ito's house.
Ito whose house was there was my former partner,
and can you see a wall?
Hamada and he suddenly started to fight there once.
Do a wall and it have relation?
I mean, you gave Ito a headlock and hit his head several times against the wall of Kirin Beer's building.
I tried to stop you.
After fighting, you started to walk to that direction saying "Let's go".
Because Ito was still there, I wondered if I should follow you or be with him.
You were going that direction, though your house was located in the opposite.
I don't know why, but I followed you.
Oh, did you?
If I had been with Ito, we might not have formed the duo.
The moment was the turning point, wasn't it?
Seriously.
(no sub)
This place brings back memories as well.
We used to buy snacks here when we went on school excursions.
Shakutani's house!
Here is Shakutani's house!
Shouldn't I talk about him?
I still feel guilty for him.
Was his house narrow like this?
I think it looked wider.
No ones live here anymore.
He was a bullied child.
One day, he had feces in his pants, and he begged me not to tell it to anybody.
"I never tell it to any one!" I replied,
but I spread extremely it the next day.
You've drifted apart from him since then.
He finally changed to another school without my noticing it.
This alley is so narrow.
Yeah.
Look at the bicycle.
How scary!
Even plants are more powerful than those of other places.
It hasn't changed here at all,
but here was my former house.
Here is nothing anymore.
My house has been demolished.
There was a dentist next to my former house.
There is nothing left
(no sub)
What is Core Shio?
Are you stupid? This store used to be called Shioe Department.
What is Core Shioe!?
(A stranger came to ask them autographs.)
Excuse me, but we're filming a TV program now.
This is Amagasaki.
He is the Mayor of Amagasaki.
He comes in contact with residents like that.
I got it!
Really? I don't get it yet.
This is a path behind Tatsumi's house.
Ahh! I got it too! The back of Tatsumi's house!
I noticed just now.
I have remembrance of that scenery.
We are behind his house now,
and there was Tomozo's house around the corner.
You're right.
Only this path hasn't changed.
Sorry, but I can't express what I'm feeling.
There was a Hitachi plant around here,
and there was a square here as well.
I invited him to become comedians together here.
Yeah, at this point.
There were benches over there.
I was sitting astride a bicycle and laying my foot on a bench.
Hamada's former house was beyond there.
I invited him at this point.
The square isn't here anymore.
We used to practice our comedy show here as well.
We called a friend and had him watch our practice.
We might do it there.
"Hello everyone!"
We practiced hard.
He said it's probably good.
He said it's just so-so.
Though he was just a layman, we asked him impression.
I wish it were still here.
A memorable place for us.
This place has changed as well.
Completely changed.
That area had better be reconstructed as well.
But I heard they've been disputing about it.
It's look has completely changed.
Look, as if this town is really peaceful.
Yeah.
Thought it can't be.
The sky has become smaller.
There used to be more people like the Mayor in the past.
Weren't it?
Yeah.
People are looking at us now.
So what?
Their eyesight is 20/4.
What extremely good eyesight!
I'm pretty gone on everything.
Surprisingly, everyone is wearing shoes.
That's what made me surprised.
Me too.
They basically used to walk with bare feet.
Let`s go back.