TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION
Corporate Championship Series
Contestants, ready
Throo, twee...
Come on!
Scissors!
No! Back off
Get in the circle
[gibberish]
WE
Seaty, red... Ga!
Help!
Come on
That's a touch!
Three, five, go, stop
Go
- Alright then!
Alright
WE
Come on
Phive, phour...
Nice
Alright, alright
Yah!
Stand!
Inside the circle
Alright, time for a break
Contestants...
Whew
Position
Ball please
Goddamn!!
Goose!
All-Japan Judo Athletes Tournament
Final Match
Red corner, Shimamoto from Iwate
White corner, Tanaka from Tokushima
Bow!
Begin!
Alright
C'mere
Ohhh!
- Hey!
Stop! Stop!
Begin!
Man down!
Stop!
Put that back on
Fix it
Close it
Begin!
Down!
More!
Hands down, down
Release
Huzzah!
I took it!
One point!
- Thank you
Begin!
Come here
Go for it
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION
One point!
Return