Translation: eChie
www.echie7.blogspot.com
Facebook: GakiFiles Subs
Fever
Next please.
Mah-kun, you have to tell doctor. OK?
WHAT'S WITH YOU!?
Wait outside!
NO!
Excuse us, Doctor.
Nice to meet you.
Hey!
Tell him!
Hello.
What's the matter?
Well, Doctor. He's been coughing since last night.
Mah-kun, tell him. He won't understand
unless you tell him!
You're irritating.
What's with you? Tell him!
My throat is hurting.
He's been coughing with a sputum.
Excuse me.
Could your hold up your top?
What are you doing?
Why are you doing it?
Front?
Yes, front.
Mah-kun...
Don't touch me!
What's with you...
Why are you touching your son's nipple?
Your my son!
Shut up.
Don't slap me!
Turn this way...
It doesn't matter!
How is it, Doctor.
Does he have a fever?
Um fever...
Stop it!
I can't tell.
You're too noisy. Stay outside.
I have to be here.
Well, this is a cold.
Is that so? Doctor, I shouldn't allow
him to smoke cigarettes, right?
Not when he has a cold.
This kid smokes even if he's under age.
Shut up.
Mild Seven FX.
Stop it.
What's with you?
Too noisy.
You should refrain from smoking.
See? Doctor is telling you not to.
Also at night, he always takes off his
underwear and is doing something.
He scares me.
He scares me. I don't understand.
Parenting.
Shut up!
It's just his youth. It has nothing to do with cold.
Really?
It's good to hear, huh? Mah-kun.
Shut up!
I'm going to give him a shot.
Are you?
On his butt.
That sounds good, Doctor.
It'll be fine.
Listen to Doctor!
You don't have to be here, right?
I should right, Doctor?
Go outside!
I will when it's done!
You're pulling it down too much!
Mah-kun, you got poop stains,
No way, stupid!
Mah-kun has poop stains.
Here's a red spot.
Let me sanitize.
Mrs, please do not touch.
Oh, Mah-kun.
Mah-kun, it's dried out.
It doesn't matter!
I'll sanitize, don't touch.
Oh, it looks great.
Irritating, really.
No!
Be quiet!
Ouch!
It's done. Massage it well.
That's fine. i'll do it.
No, you can't!
I'll do it!
Stop it! Don't touch me!
Is that so? Oh, I'm sorry.
It has to be done.
That's fine. You've done it.
Let me massage you.
Why?
Doctor, there's an urgent patient!
We're shot of type A blood.
Oh! Mah-kun is type A!
Right?
Mah-kun, you should give a transfusion!
Why me?
Let's go, doctor.
Why me? Stupid...OUCH!
Mah-kun!