facebook.com/shionnotsukai
HIGHSCHOOL
SCARY STORY
Man what a relief
Ya spyin' on us?
That aside ya folks
Ya know, I've been waitin'
for this moment for a week
Waitin' for what?!
Come on, don't gimme that
What are ya talkin' about?
I've waited a whole week to come see this!
Wait a sec
- What
Isn't it stinky in here?
Of course it is
Why would you know that?!
It stinks!
- It stinks!
Is someone takin' a dump?
Man, it smells worse than last week!
Shut up
Hey! Someone's doin' it!
Let's see
He's doin' it!
I thought so
Don't take a shit, dude!
Remember that!
Don't go take a dump at school!
UNBABA!!
note: pun on "unko" and "baba" (both "poop")
One, two, three, four
After the meal it comes the Unbaba ♪
Before bedtime it's always Unbaba ♪
Even when in water, here comes Unbaba ♪
So lame!!
Let's stop this!
Isn't it over yet?!
You don't look like a motivated turd-thrower
When I was born, I was Unbaba ♪
As I turned 20, I was still Unbaba ♪
I might lose a battle but I'm still Unbaba ♪
This is impossible
I can't do this
Give me my full week back
You did good, you did good
You gave your best
Don't worry- he gave his best, am I right?
Yeah...
I'll pick up the poop for you!
Ok ok
Don't feel so down about it
Holy shit
I was about to get caught
You did good
We're done
Let's go
You did your best
Alright, good job!
I might lose a battle but I'm still Unbaba ♪
Bye!