The Future Century
Squadron: The Five Rangai!
So yesterday...
Yeah.
...I met him again.
What? Your manager again?
Yeah...
Well, he called me so...
I keep telling you to break it off, don't I!
I know, I know! But...
Who is it?
Hello, hello, hello, good evening.
Long time, no see.
What's with you coming every Sunday?
So Ryoko!
I have a present just for you.
Hey, hey, hey.
This is my home.
Don't you think you're being a little rude?
So Ryoko.
This ir really cool.
Rolling Stones tickets!
No way!
Really!
Cool.
Third row!
They're calling you.
Third row seats! Right in front of our eyes.
They're calling you!
I'll give this to you. Let's go together.
Ok!
I know, I know! Shut up!
Ok, like this.
Help!
Save me!
Stop!!!!
Falkor!
Dokin!
"R" Lady!
No Panties Shabu-Shabu!
Mori Building!
Our powers combined!
The Five Rangai!
Ok!
Go go!
- Escape!
Hurry out of here!
Go!
Get out of here!
Ok!
- Come on!
Hey. Line up.
Line up over there.
Ow, ow, ow.
Ouch.
Line up.
So when I tell you guys
to do what you want...
...this is the result.
This is it, right?
This is your guys idea of heroes, right?
What the hell are you?
"R" Lady.
Can you fight like this?
With a purse hanging from you shoulder?
Of course I can fight like this.
Hey.
Yes!
Don't wear that suit if you can't  move.
Actually, I thought I
could fight much better!
Can you please pass
that foot behind you?
Sorry!
Hey.
Hey!
Yes?
You're the closest out of all these idiots.
Hey.
Old man.
What the hell are you?
No Panties Shabu-Shabu!
Hey, look here.
Is there such a thing as a "No
Panties Shabu-Shabu" hero?
well...
The system, right?
So the idea is to satisfy the appetite
for food and sex at the same time.
I liked the idea...
...and you said to dress like you want.
So I choose No Panties
Shabu-Shabu with confidence.
I see.
You have no right to complain.
Fine, Ok.
Just what are you?
Sorry?
What is that? Mori Building?
Well...
I wanted to be a big man.
This isn't a hero, this is a monster.
I wanted to be big...
...and I wanted to be influential.
Oh!
I see.
Sit down.
So I'm not angry at all today.
I told you guys to do whatever you want.
Right, right.
- Yes, you did.
Yeah, and so you guys showed me.
But I mean physically...
...are these heroes? I mean
if you line you guys up...
Would people think you are heroes?
They wouldn't, would they?
Looking at yourselves.
What do you think?
Looking at yourself, well
you chose what you liked...
But looking at the guy
next to you, would you say...
Excuse me.
- What is it?
Umm.
Something I really felt...
- Yeah, yeah.
Umm.
I mean, I'm guilty of it, too,
so I can't throw blame around.
- Right, right.
But actually I think there
is something wrong.
- Isn't there!
I feel.
Right, right.
Until last week, I honestly thought,
what is Mr. Skeleton talking about?
Ah, you thought that?
So I didn't use "Mr"
when addressing you.
I truly felt that in my heart.
- Oh, you did?
Well that's how you feel so...
But this is how I feel now.
- You see what I mean?
That's the way you should feel.
You're completely off!
Children can't talk about
No Panties Shabu-Shabu.
But, you see, my target
group is middle-aged men.
That's why I'm after.
Ah, that's what you're after?
I thought, "I'll save middle-aged men".
- I see, I see, Isee.
But children are usually
a hero's main group.
Oh. Ah. Oh
- You have to think like that.
I see, I see.
Wait.
You hadn't notice that?
No, really?
- Is that right?
That was the mistake?
Children are your main audience!
That's why I said he was the closest!
I have a weapon.
- He has a weapon, too!
Right, right.
So that is what you mean?
Of course that's what I mean!
So let's try again next week.
Ok. - Ok.
- Ok.
Next week, please.
From next week The Five Rangai.
That's best.
- So just like that...
Today is impossible.
You're not The Five Rangai.
Just looking at us, it's weird, isn't it?
- It's weird, it is.
You see it, right?
- Yes.
Falkor is ok, right?
I thought we just said it's weird?
- Ah, this is weird, too. - I see.
Excuse me.
If I get rid of the purse am I ok?
- The purse isn't the problem!
You just were asking, right?
Well, no.
Whether you have this or not. No.
We see. We completely understand.
You see now?
When we came in before and yelled
out "Our powers combined, The
Five Rangai!"... It felt a little wrong.
Didn't it?
You see what I mean?
I am telling you!
- Your skin felt weird, right?
That's right! If you understand
that now then fantastic.
Well then...
- Starting today a new...
Yes, Five Rangai.
Right!
Until next week.
Ok! Ok!
Ok!
Thank you!
Please eat this.
No, no.
Thank you.
Thank you! - Thanks!
- Thank you!
Let's try again next week.
Bye bye!
Let's learn from our mistakes.
We will!
Thank you!
Good work. Be careful getting home.
Ok?
Yes, thank you!
Thank you!
Yeah, yeah, thanks.
Is there gonna be another one episode next week?
The Future Century Squadron: The Five Rangai!   To be con't.