Translated and timed by Outlaws0020
Inn
It's right here. Come on in.
- Nice room.
Looks so old.
Take a seat.
Sorry for that, but take a seat.
You must be exhausted.
Take a seat.
So where are you from?
Tokyo.
Tokyo must be filled with garbage and smoke.
I guess it is...
Lots of cars and so on.
That's not what I mean. I'm talking about the people.
How they smell?
I'm talking about you two.
You're no good...
A troublesome couple like you.
But you know, you've got a cute wife.
Do you want a bath or something to eat?
I'm hungry.
Something to eat then.
Something to... eat?
Oh I see.
I don't really like you, so I won't make any dinner.
Not you, just... this woman.
I can make something for you, but not her.
Old granny!
Then I'll make something.
Do you want a bath while waiting?
Cause you're so dirty.
So you want a bath before dinner, right?
Remember to shower yourself before entering the bath.
Shower?
Yea.. cause you're so dirty.
Let's get some tea.
There's nothing for you two, tho.
Such a troublesome couple.
I'll go make it, so just wait, okay?
Coming~