Subtitles: Zurui
(Aho = Idiot or Idiotic)
Come out!!
Where are you? Damn you!
Hey!
Come out!
There you are, damn you!
You aren't the same Kentaro as always...
Where's Yuko?
So you finally got here, Kentaro
What are you doing?
You're being a coward!
We Ho Ho Ho aliens, do not have the
word "coward" in our dictionary
I said where is she?
Tell him wife
Don't make me feel like a fool...I have cute nipples!
Why can't I ever understand her?
Look up there, Kentaro!
Help me, Kentaro-kun!
Yuko-chan!
I can't reach her!
You are reaching her!
Damn!
Since the rope is so tight, we won't try stop you...
Just try and save her!
This is a mess... it can't be helped!
Aho Aho man...
Oh no!
Help me...
How cool!
Good, that was good
Help Yuko!
Help me!
Aho Aho Boomerang!
[Aho Aho Boomerang can fly as fast as a Hayabusa and everything it touchs, it cuts]
You will use this to cut the rope, right?
Hurry!
It didn't work! Look at this!
Help me!
Help her!
Aho Aho Extension Scissors!
You can cut with that, right?
Hurry!
[She now looks like a boy]
What's she going to do with that head?
Aho Aho Wing!
[When you wear the Aho Aho Wing, you
can fly anywhere on Friday night]
Today's not Friday!
Put that down!
I've got no choice!
Hey, you didn't have a rifle there earlier!
Shut up!!
Yuko-chan! I will use this rifle to shoot the rope!
Stay still!
Here goes!
Watch out!
Why...
You...!!
You threw a fart!
He's an idiot, a real idiot...
To be continued