Subs by H
(Aho = Idiot or Idiotic)
When this Ohoho bomb explodes,
it will kill all the humans!
Wait!!
Ah! Kentaro!
This is our secret base, it says "Do not enter",
did you not understand that?
You idiot!
Shut up, you!
I was speaking just now, don't overlap me!
Sorry about that, Kentaro!
Go to the back!
Don't tell her what to do!
But wait! You're my wife so... Stand behind me.
Stupid!
I've placed transmitters on your heads
so I could find this place, you idiot!
Transmitters?
Why you...!
Oh, the switch!
Damn!
I feel so stupid!
You'll see!
The explosion of this Ohoho bomb
will destroy the entire planet!
What!?
What are you going to do, Kentaro?
I woun't allow that to happen!
Take this!
Aho Aho Man! Help!!
Are you idiot?
Aho Aho Man! We have to deactivate
this bomb or it'll be the end for us!
Please do something!
Aho Aho Camouflage!
And so it was easy, although...
What the hell are you doing?
We're still exposed to it!
Aho Aho Doppelganger!
Just kidding.
Just kidding?
Don't joke around!
Oh! You got something, don't you?
I trust you, let's do it!
Aho Aho Brother!
Aho Aho Brother
They are not blood related but know each other since they were kids and so, they refer to each other as brother.
Brother! Brother!
Enough already!
What the hell, why are you so filthy?
Turn around, lemme see it!
That's disgustingly big!
What is the matter with you...?
Stop it.
You showed it enough!
Aho Aho...
Music!
You screwed up right there!
Don't you feel embarrassed?
Aren't you going to do anything else?
Aho Aho Union!
When their feelings combine,
they will make the Aho Aho Union.
What is it? This feeling?
What are you doing?
Now! That was you last chance!
I'll explode this Ohoho bomb
now and everyone will die!
Take a look at this!
One press of this switch and this entire city will be reduced to ash-
Wait! Wait! What are you doing?
Reduced to?
This city will be reduced to ash-
Wa-wait! Wait!
Leave me alone!
It will be reduced to ashes!
What!?
However...
If you agree with one condition, I will leave the button alone
A condition... I'll make it!
Very well! The condition is-
Brother! Brother!
Die, both of you!!
Union!
What is it? This feeling?
To be continued
That's enough already!