Sho-ta!
Honey, I can't believe
it's already been a month.
Seems like yesterday.
Sho-ta! - Hey, keep it together.
(Not now.)
It's so boring down here.
- It's gonna be boring for a long time.
I hadn't done anything for a month.
- It's going to be that way for a long time
Let's play. - No.
Please. - Keep it down.
I want to play. - No.
How about karaoke? - No way.
Here, let's do it.
I can't do it.
Funky guts man!
This flame of my life, Funky guts man!
For all the friends I love!
What are you doing? - I'm
sorry for what he did.
Say "Funky guts man!" - Imada, hold him.
You don't wanna fall behind the times,
do you?
Itao, cut it out. - So very sorry.
- What the hell are you talking about?
It's 49th day anniversary of Sho-ta. - Yes.
Cut that crap. - I just thought
that will raise...
What's wrong with him? - I'm so sorry.
Itao, don't do that again. - I won't. Sorry.
Please go on.
- No more crap, OK?
If you don't need me here just say it.
- I'm terribly sorry, please go on.
Your padding went off.
What's so funny?
So you want to play now?
No. That's enough.
Why? - Just 30 minutes.
Just be still for 30 minutes.
How about this?
That's out of the question! - Why?
It would be fun. - It would be a booming roar. How can I possibly cover it up?!
Hey! Stop it!
Pan!(=Bang!) Pan!
Hey, you panpan(=prostitute)!
How much is it?!
Just tell the damn price!
- What the hell are you doing?!
The price! - What did you call her?! - Just what are you trying to do?!
That's enough! Cut it out!
Put that away. - I'm sorry.
Are you out of mind?
That's way out of line! - I'm sorry.
Obviously he doesn't want me here.
- No. Please.
For my son. - I understand that.
Enough already!
Why can't we play?
No. - Why? - Because I said so!
Why? - Just be still!
Oh, I got a good idea.
How about knocking this down?
Knocking what? - The tombstone.
Would be fun. - No.
This thing is absolutely nonsense!
What do you think you're doing?
- What is nonsense? - Nonsense!
Imada, stop him.
Are you OK? - Stop it!
What is he thinking?! I'm leaving!
- Wait!
Look at me!