GakiFile Subs
www.gakifiles.blogspot.com
TOMIYOSHI-SAN
Honey!
What's wrong?
Hey! What are you doing?
What are you doing
in my vending machine?
What's this?
What are you doing?
What?
This is my vending machine. Why are you in there?
Shut up. Leave me alone, stupid.
In this day and age, even Macaulay Culkin drinks alcohol!
What kind of reasoning is that?
What.
You know what?
- What?
This machine contains
the beer that our best customer buys every morning.
If you are in there, he can't buy it!
Hey master!
Hi. Good morning.
We were talking about you just now. Look at this.
I want to buy some beer.
What are you doing old man?
What, Ham Hand.
Ham Hand!
Ham Hand?
What are you saying?
Who's Ham Hand!
I can't buy beer, get out from there!
Shut up, stupid.
He's rude.
Go and call the police.
Good idea.
You know what pops.
What?
Not pops, old man.
We just called the police.
He wont come!
200% chance that he wont come! Stupid.
We just called him!
You idiot, he wont come. Stupid.
Idiot!
What's the problem?
Look at that.
He's in such a place.
What?
Pops.
You're in such a place!
Shut up, Pro guide.
He's rude.
He was called "Ham Hand".
I'm Ham Hand.
Pops.
- What?
If you stay there, you'll be causing them trouble.
I don't care.
You should. You are causing us trouble.
Our customers can't buy beer.
I want to.
Can I tell you one thing?
What is it?
I have been listening quietly and
all I heard was complaints.
You guys don't understand anything. So don't talk.
What..
Hey you. The owner.
What?
You.
I'll tell you one thing since you don't remember.
When you were a kid,
you saved an animal, right?
Well..
No.
I have never.
I'm the puppy.
I said I have never.
Are you listening?
I have never done that.
You know what? Let me ask you this.
As an adult, why doesn't anyone ask me why I'm in here?
Oh, sorry about that.
Then, let's hear why you are in there.
In this world, there are all different kinds of people.
Every person is different.
Some are good, and some are bad.
Some are warm, and some are cold.
Some are so warm.
Some are so cold.
Think about it. It makes you want
to go into a vending machine.
I got it.
Vending machines have hot and cold drinks.
That's what he is talking about.
It does make sense!
But who asked you that!
It has nothing to do with this.
I'm asking why you are there.
You better cut it out. You are causing trouble.
You know what old man.
What.
You are causing a trouble. You
broke my vending machine.
Please pay for the damage.
Why should I? Are you stupid?
If you don't, you will be arrested.
I wont be arrested for something like that, stupid!
Isn't that right?
Listen pops.
What.
If you damage someone's property,
it is a crime.
You'll be arrested.
Serious?
That's how it is.
Will I be arrested?
If I get arrested, my wife and kids will cry!
I'm afraid my kids will be bullied.
Maybe.
I did a bad thing.
Will I be arrested...
Excuse me.
Please.
Are you willing to overlook this?
Please Jyako Nezumi-san!
Who the hell is it?
I'm the police officer.
Who is that?