Set up
Subtitles: eChie
I see.
You guys are finally performing on stage
- Yes.
And then?
Did you decide your duo name?
Yes.
We had a hard time deciding, but
"Laser Beam"
What!?
What kind of name is that?!
But Master, wel...
That name means...to shatter the audience's hearts
The heart is important, but
Thank you.
You guys
A Duo's name is
a sign
You have to use the name for 50-60 years
no matter what
- Yes.
Rethink it
I'm sorry.
- Sorry.
Master Curry Rice, a call on line 3
Hello. This is Curry Rice
Yes, please hurry up and deliver Hayashi rice for me
I am so hungry
Did you think of anything?
Which name?
"Parachute unit"
What does it mean?
To swoop on the audience's heart
The heart is important, but
Master Curry Rice, another call...
You gonna deliver Chicken Rice?
I'm starving
What did you decide?
I'm sorry
What is your name?
Um.
"Milky way"
What does that mean?
We want to
melt their heart
That's enough