The Future Century
Squadron: The Five Rangai 2001!
Takashi. Takashi, I have...
- Takashi and Yuko are so in love.
We are newly wed. And tonight, in the bed
we are gonna . . . (humming).
Takashi.
- What.
I have to tell you something
I've never told you. - What?
I'm sorry I've never told you
this before. I... I, before I met you...
What? What is this?
- I's ... it's nothing.
Coming.
- Hey!
Long time, huh?
- Yes, long time.
How long is it since last time?
- Well... it's 3, 4... - Who he?
Takashi, he is...
- Who is he?
I got married.
- What?
He's my husband, Takashi.
- So, you are her husband.
- Yes. And you are?
Why haven't you told me?
- Hey! What you doing to Yuko?
You don't know our relationship?
- What?
No! There's no relationship!
In fact I don't even know him.
How come you don't know each other?!
- Hey! What's the matter with you?
This is just how he is.
- She was my sex slave.
- Sex what?
No he's lying!
- What does he mean by "sex slave"?
- Don't listen to what he's saying!
Hey! What are you doing?
- Heeelp!
Stop!
Red Rangai!
Yellow-Green Rangai!
Dark Green Rangai!
Greenish Rangai!
Let me spawn!
Our powers combined!
The Five Rangai!
Guys, run. Now!
Wait. Stop it.
I understand it's been a long time.
But, this is 5 Rangai, right?
You. Step back for a while.
- Let's me spawn!
Let me spawn like that night!
- I'll get back to you later.
What are you?
- Red Rangai!
And you?
- Yellow-Green Rangai!
Why Yellow-Green? And don't you think
your cap is little unmatched?
I took balance into consideration,
I mean, with other guys.
How about you?
- Greenish Rangai!
Why greenish?
You should be Green Rangai if anything.
If I call myself Green Rangai I have to
look perfectly green to anybody.
And people tend to have different
opinions about colors.
I'm just  Greenish so they can't say
I'm not Green.
What happened to you?
- Dark Green Rangai!
Originally I was Green Rangai.
- Is that so?
Can I have a few minutes?
Last night, I was washing my costume.
It's so careless of me.
I throw in this black sweater.
Dark Green Rangai!
I can say I'm Green.
But I don't want lie.
But why  you guys all stick to green.
Our team concept this time  is planning a
greening, a sort of.
To protect environment.
- Then you should get green costume too.
I wanted to give viewers
more impact by starting normally.
I came out as Red and other guys
betray their expectation. - I see.
You guys don't think of anything about
him when you came out with him?
Green is the color for this time, right?
And this was what I definitely wanted
to do when I thought of green.
But everything have its limit.
Especially when you try to help somebody.
This guy is insane.
I can understand your reasons.
Not this!
Ouch!
He's just insane. You should tell him.
You are the leader aren't you?
You are, because you are Red, right?
You should tell him when you gather up.
You should tell him he can't wear this.
- I respect their personalities.
But we can't tolerate everything for the
sake of respecting personalities.
Please not the belly.
- Just because you are a team doesn't
mean you should be so protective.
I could play my role if you guys
just do a decent job.
You have a point, but it's been
a long time. So just fight us, please.
Just bring it!
- Let me spawn!
Greenish Rangai!
- Dark Green Rangai! Ouch!
Get the hell out of here!
I've been saying this so many times
for so many years!
Do the job! Just once!
What are you trying to do?
Not the belly, please.
- Seriously not my belly...
- I don't give a damn! Out!
You're not going to fight?
- Just get out!
Wrong, wrong, wrong. You are the
only one. But I can't fight just with you.
It's your fault! You are the leader!
Hey! - Red Rangai!
- What kind of leader are you?
You piece of shit!
Quit it!
If you are too chicken-hearted
to say things straight just quit!
It's been a long time. I was
looking forward to do these actions.
Now, get out. Go.
Go!
Hey! Are you ok?
Just get out!
Itao, are you ok?
The Future Century Squadron:
The Five Rangai 2001!   The end.