Subtitles: Zurui
Not Yet
Mister
I'm returning this!
Why are you mad?
I don't need this!
What do you mean?
I had to pay for this!
What?
This thing doesn't even work!
Well... I...
Give me a break!
I didn't say that it would work perfectly
That's dirty!
I said "maybe"
Give me back my money!
What?
- Return my money!
I can't return your money, because...
it already went to charity
You liar!
Today, I have something...
Never mind!
Really, today I have something that every one wants!
I saved it specially for you!
I save it!
There's only this one!
I can't believe you
Really, and it's cheap
How much?
$50
Hmm, $50
I'm not lying
$50 and absolutely I won't get bullied, right?
That's correct!
See, today I didn't hesitate to say it would work
$50
You carry a lot of cash huh?
Well, actually
today...
"Miracle Camouflage Paper"
This is $50?
Of course! It will stop the bullying
When you wear this mask, you will blend into the pillar
No one will see you
If they can't see you, they can't bully you!
Even the bully can't punch the pillar
Well, that's true
Keep it, and everything will be fine
Really??
I really don't have any confidence in this...
You don't, right?
This mask should work, BUT just in case...
$80
What?
For what?
$100
What??
Why did the price go up?
What?
What did the price increase?
Well, you know how the currency fluctuates... like the dollar
Hurry, it's rising!
That's suspicious
Hurry up!
$100?
- $100
I'll be safe?
Yes
Hurry
You'll be safe, definitely
Here it is
This is the main item
This is the main item?
"Miracle Mole"
When you wear this
No one will know it's you
That can't work
Trust me
Just that one thing will work?
For example...here
Excuse me do you know Masao?
What are you saying?
I'm Masao!
Wow!
You surprised me!
You hair looked longer!
Stop saying stupid things
Are you stupid?
With this you will be fine
Definitely fine
Ok?
I'm going
Really?
I have make my next stop
Ok?
Bye!
Will it really be ok?
As always, thank you!
Hey, Masao what are you doing?
Masao, Masao!
Masao!
It's Masao!
Please look closely, I'm not Masao
I have a mole!
No, look, look well
I'm wearing this!
I have a mole, please look
I'm not Masao
Masao!
Stop it!
You are Masao!
I have a mole...
So that was Miracle Ace!
He still a lot of secrets!
Please look, I'm not Masao!
To be continued