Translation by Shibatabread
www.shibatabread.com
SALLINGER
Greetings, everyone
Hello
Well, my dream has finally come true with the Sallinger
And now you can enjoy it, too
I'm your instructor,
Harita
Pleased to meet you all
Are you an instructor?
Let me know if you're like,
"Hey, I've done this before!!"
Don't be shy and let me know right away
Anyone?
So, this is new for all of you
You're right
Since all of you are rookies at this,
I understand if you're completely lost
But let me first start by taking your lunch orders
Excuse us
What do you want?
How about some instructions?
Well, I need to take the orders first
OK, beef or chicken?
Do you want Beef or Chicken for lunch?!!
I'll have chicken
I got it, chicken
Me too
I'll do beef then
Beef, got it
Coffee with that?
Do you want a coffee with your lunch?!
I'll have a coffee
I got it
Can I get an iced tea instead?
Let me see...
No, not today
I'll just have regular tea then
Maybe an iced coffee?
OK, that's enough
That's enough order-taking
No time for this nonsense
So here's the Auto Sallinger
And I'm sure you want to try it out
Tell yourself just how much you want
To ride the Sallinger, OK?
Of course, you'll see some fish around
Which one of you is like,
"Yeah, I already have a fish as my buddy!"
Anyone?
No, none of us
Then please tell me!
Tell me that none of your friends are fish!
I need to know!
I'm sure you have questions about this ride
I'd be glad to answer them right now
Any question
Anything to prevent you from danger
I have one
How long until we're good enough to ride this?
Well...
It all depends on how honest you are
As long as you're true to yourself,
You can ride this
Of course, the seaweed will be approaching you
Numerous times
Got that?
Of course, the seaweed will see you from afar!
What'd you want, moron?!
Please get that through your head!
What else?!
I got one
Seeing that everyone else is a guy,
I'm wondering if I can ride this
Listen,
Women riders...
There's been some woman riders in the past
And it's because of women riders,
that this Sallinger exists here today
Please remember that
Here's one more thing
Don't ever think
your parents will be in good health forever
I've heard that one before
It's only natural
that your mother and father will go before you!
And that is the truth!
Don't you ever forget that!!
What're you laughing at?
Will you cut that out, please?
That was uncalled for
Why did you get violent with her?
Don't laugh at it
Don't be laughing
You're laughing, too
The Instructor finds some things amusing, too!!
Just keep your hands to yourself
Are we good now?
Let's get to the real lesson
Can we start?
Before I begin
Remember to keep your cool, OK?
So here's the Auto Sallinger
Therer are many ways to ride this
For instance, for womens riders,
the Air Plasma needs to be in this particular position
See?
And for male riders,
Place one of the Air Plasmas like so
Please remember that rule, OK?
With that having been said...
I didn't realize it can live in such shallow water
What did you say, asshole?
What did you just say?
Well...
So they can live in shallow water?
What do you mean?
I mean the water only comes up to here
Go home, moron!
I'm sorry
But why me?
Let's move on
I'm just going to have you ride it
Please don't get hurt
I don't need to be in trouble
What?
Why're you so quiet all of a sudden?
Well, we're focused on the lesson
Please ask questions, OK?
Instructor,
this just broke off
That scared me
What the hell, you morons?!
We didn't do anything wrong
But you just made a complete ass out of yourself
And you were scared, too
Go home, moron
Go home!
You go home now!
Why am I going home?
I paid for this
Listen
Please watch yourself
He's taking it out on him
So...
Who's first?
Well, let's go over the features then
What do you want to know first?
What's the lever for?
This is the "EXMENT LEVER"
This side is for EXMENT
Here's NON-EXMENT
Remember that, please
OK, so what does that do?
What do you mean?
What do you control with that?
What're you talking about?
What happens when you turn that on?
Of course, it becomes EXMENT
As a novice rider...
Just know that it should always
be in the NON-EXMENT position
Anything else?
What's that ring at the end?
That's called the "PILER"
Please don't touch that
or you'll get electrocuted
Serious?
About 2,000,000 volts of current runs through there
It's near the water?
That's really dangerous
Big chance we'll get electrocuted
And here...
Here's the double-fin
We don't need this one right now!
Who the hell do you think you are
I told you to go home, asshole
What are you talking about?
I'm going then
You got all that?
Anything else?
Anyone?
No, I don't think so
Well then, shall we?
Get down and dirty?!
Let's get going
C'mon, get on it!
You, go
I'm going first?
Hop on it
Let's go
Get it right
Don't forget to say bye
You need to say a proper farewell
I'll catch you guys later
No, that's not it
Let's get down and dirty!?
Alright then
What's your name?
I'm Hamada
OK everyone,
watch as your friend demonstrates
Hop on it, Hamada-san
Like this?
Good luck
Now, give me your Fighting Pose
Fighting Pose?
Pighting Pose?
Go ahead and position these any way you like
That's your move, huh?
Is that good for you?
Then, here's my move
OK, then the loser goes first
Loser goes first
You ready?
Don't touch this until I'm done with it
20,000 volts runs through this ring
I thought it was 2,000,000 volts...
You ready?
You good?
Hang on tight, please
Are you ready?
Here you go
This wasn't your first time, was it?