Timing and quality check: KannibleKlown
Translation: GakiNoSuitGuy
Hilarious! 30 year anniversary special.
We've been waiting for this.
This is "Your First Errand".
Happy new year.
George Tokoro
Moriguchi Hiroko
Amami Yuuki
Football hour:
Gotou Terumoto
Hotta Akane
Fujimoto Miki
Ichikawa Ebizou
Mister Tokoro...
Somehow "My First Errand"
has been on the air for 30 years.
Has it been 30 years?
That's right.
Meaning you've been doing this show since you were 6?
No need for math.
And to commemorate those 30 we've brought some wonderful guests.
Somehow we got Mr. Ebizou.
Father of
Splendid.
Thank you very much.
What I know is that
he keeps writing about the program on his personal blog.
The most famous fan.
I always watch the show.
Mikitty mama.
Yes.
One more is on its way.
That's right.
Pregnant
Thanks for having me.
What an amazing silhouette.
Have a look at this.
Huge.
When are you due?
I'm due at the end of this month.
It's almost popping out already.
The heck?
Is it fine for you to be here?
It's fine.
I have so much free time while anticipating.
Amami, what do you think of "Errand"?
I always watch it and cry.
Todays errands will also make you laugh and cry.
The first errand is by a 4 year old boy.
November last year a magnificent wedding was held in Tokyo.
It's the wedding of a kid who went on his first errand 21 years ago.
How amazing.
It's not going well since it's the first time.
He's laughing today but back then he cried hard.
- Very traditional.
- So true.
Keiichirou is 25 years old.
His first errand was also a first for his parents.
An errand that became an irreplaceable family memory.
Let's show it to begin the 30 year anniversary special.
21 years ago...
On the day of moving out of the company provided housing
Keiichirou went on his first errand.
8 in the morning.
They are ready to move out
from the company housing where his parents married.
They've lived here for 6 years and 3 months.
Giving birth to a son and a daughter and becoming a 4 unit family.
To the 4 year old Keiichirou this home has been the center of his entire life.
Let's bring it all to the new house.
His mother decided on this errand on the day of moving.
She wants to teach Keiichirou the importance of saying your goodbyes.
His two friends from the block who have known each other since they were babies.
Parting with your dear friends for the first time is something his mother also has experienced.
The moving truck has arrived.
Keichan.
It's already 10 so mama...
She will make him go.
Can you go on an errand?
Where should I go?
The picture that I took at the farewell party the other day...
She took a picture that he was asked to print 2 copies from the photo store.
This is the picture his father took at the farewell party.
Yuusuke
Shougo
He will hand it to Shougo and Yuuseke.
After that go greet your doctor Nakamura.
Pediatric doctor Nakamura.
She helped take care of his asthma.
He's told to bring her flowers.
And then there's this.
Vegetables?
Give it to Meichan?
The goat Meichan.
Since we didn't get to say bye the other day.
Since we are moving.
Let's play again.
As a special treat on this day she's cut up fresh vegetables.
He's got 3 people and a goat to say goodbye to. Better hurry!
Kei, if you are slow then the truck will depart.
It's papa.
That would be tough.
So I will give you this watch so you can keep track of time.
Papas watch.
How cool. Really makes you overcome anything.
He still can't tell the time but he understands his fathers.
Because the dial has an arrow that the hand can point to.
Keiichirou, be back by then. He's given a 1 hour limit.
It's all in the same block.
Shougo, Yuuseke, the preschool teacher Nakamura and the goat Mei.
It's an errand to say your goodbyes.
Do your best.
The oath between two men - a father and his son.
I will do my best.
Here we go.
3 minutes away is the photo store inside of the supermarket his mother always shops at.
All of Keiichirous pictures since his birth have been handled by this store.
Please.
Are you really moving away from here?
Those 4 years have added up to 10 complete photo albums.
He's become so big already. Goodbye.
Next up he needs to pick up some flowers.
Cause he's supposed to bring them to his teacher.
He picked the doctors favorite peach blossoms and strawberries.
How smart.
He's always being welcomed even on days off.
He's been taken really good care of.
He's known her since he was 7 months old.
Doctor.
She's in the middle of a medical examination.
He just walked in.
I came by myself.
To say goodbye.
You will give this to me?
I'm moving.
You are moving?
Saginomiya in Nakano ward.
Very specific info.
He is able to say it.
Be kind to your sister Minako.
Yes.
Goodbye.
So dry.
Keiichirou that night you caught pneumonia was cutting it close.
Your asthma will surely get better.
He's checking the arrow on his fathers watch.
That's right. He has to hurry.
The truck is packed already.
He's running again.
He has arrived at Shougos house.
The three of them are always together.
He can't reach it.
Are they not home?
Despite having brought the photos.
Despite wanting to say goodbye, Shou.
Ah, they are inside.
Oh, Keichan.
Yes.
Shou has forgotten about it.
That Kei is leaving today.
I didn't come to play. Here's a photo.
One of them is for Shou.
A picture from the goodbye party.
That's right... Kei is leaving.
As he realizes that Shou falls silent.
Aww~ he must be sad.
They really love each other but Shou is too shy to express it.
Today he has to say goodbye.
I will not always be here.
The bashful Shou won't say a thing.
With wide eyes he's holding back faint tears.
The truck is waiting so he's leaving.
Thank you Kei.
Shou was acting weird.
Despite having brought him a picture.
He didn't even say bye bye.
How sad.
Time to hurry.
Papas watch says...
It's still fine. There are 30 minutes left.
He's properly paying attention.
There she is, Meichan.
Meichan is the baby goat kept by the children's center.
He's been feeding her for 1 year.
Scary, scary, scary.
They couldn't keep animals at the company housing but he was glad to have Meichan.
Thank you.
Broccoli stems. His mother has packed it with Meichan's favorites.
I see.
Will he ever be able to feed her again.
Saginomiya is far from here, Meichan.
He's suddenly becoming melancholic.
Please eat it all.
When you do I have to leave.
Suddenly he remembers his dads watch.
What happened?
The time has passed.
The time passed?
He's running all he can.
Mom, dad and the truck is not there.
They left...
You thought we had left?
Everyone was still there.
It's not like they can just leave Keiichirou behind.
Will you go to Yuusuke's house?
I won't go.
He was scared.
He really believed that they had left him for good.
You are able to go by yourself now.
Go while I clean up.
Go and see Yuusuke.
Are you okay with not seeing him again. He's probably waiting at his house.
The fright from thinking he was abandoned.
He wasn't able to go Yuusuke's house so his regret made him suddenly dejected back at home.
But his mother intends to make him go again.
I forgot to go to
Yuuseke's house.
His father also intends to make him go again.
They'll be sad if you didn't go and just cried.
You're a strong boy, aren't you?
Let's bring it in again with Minako.
His father used to be in the rugby club in Keio University.
An oath between men.
Alright.
Keiichirou is not alone.
The 4 unit family is one team.
I will do my best.
His father gave him his handkerchief.
And told him to wipe his tears and go.
We will be waiting.
Hoping to make Keiichirou
properly say his goodbyes to this town.
The entertaining park, the back streets he ran through
and his beloved friends.
Here's Yuusuke's house.
The stairs he climbed every day.
Yes?
It's Hara.
Kei-chan?
Yes.
He stopped crying.
Did you come by yourself?
Come in.
It's just that...
Photos.
He gave it to him.
Kei-chan? What's going on?
His fathers handkerchief.
The handkerchief to wipe away the tears.
Thank you.
Why are you crying that much?
Because you are crying.
Why are you crying, Kei?
Previously when... came home #!&%...
He was about to leave without saying good bye.
Yuusuke's prized possession.
He's giving his Toy Story figures of Woody, Buzz and Rex.
Those are indeed prized items.
It's fine.
You don't have to give them. I already have lots of toys.
Thank you.
And...
Bye bye.
Having made so many precious memories.
Heading towards a new home.
He's tired for the day.
Cause he has filled his minds photo album with memories.
He did his best.
Goodbye Shou.
Goodbye Yuusuke.
Everyone, everyone, be well.
To fill his heart with goodbyes
opens his eyes and makes him ready to face his next home.
Keiichirou what follows goodbye is hello.
A "hello errand" is waiting for you in a new town.
21 years later.
Amazing.
Saying hello again
to Mami who he met at his company's initiation ceremony.
He grew up like this.
Keiichirou is a new employee at a major food company.
He has just started his salaryman life.
Dad, he has risen from the ranks.
And his relationship to his parents is great.
It's still running smoothly.
It's still running?
It's running.
It's the watch from back then.
I don't use it much but I just can't throw it out.
I see.
This.
To commemorate your first errand.
Is that what he has planned.
Let's get a shot with you and dad.
The watch matches him as he has taken after his beloved cool dad.
The Japanese rugby captain Tanaka's son's first errand.
"I will carry it just like my beloved dad" but it ends up in a sticky situation.
It's falling out.
It's coming out.
So moving that it even exceeds his fathers' expectations.
It has been wonderful right from the start.
It was like a movie.
Yeah, it was so moving.
Mister Ebizou you were also teary-eyed.
Is that right?
This show really throws you off your guard.
You get hit from all directions.
The kid himself but also the people around him
and for the crying mother who clearly knows what's going on.
But she was just moved to see his emotional expression.
It really throws you off your guard.
This is dangerous.
I had to avert my eyes.
No, please look.
And Amami?
My nose immediately started to drip.
Unexpecedly early on.
Yuusuke was also a great kid. Wanting to give his prized possesion.
It's amazing that kids can refuse such an offer.
Kids will say "I don't need it".
Don't they understand what the toys mean to the other kids?
Next up is the poster girl at a sushi restaurant.
Kanbanmusume (literally: poster girl): A pretty girl who attracts customers to come inside a shop.
Shizuoka ● Itou city
In the hot spring district of Itou, Izu Prefecture, where easygoing (Nonki) sushi can be found at Nonki sushi.
It's a high-end sushi restaurant.
The dad is a second generation chef.
Close to the ocean and the mountains so the ingredients are abundant.
Mazuma wasabi from Amagi and the golden eye snapper from Shimoda which is a bit fatty.
Looks delicious.
It's on a road where few cars pass by so this is a stop that people go out of their way to make.
It's a family-run establishment.
The proprietress is the grandmother and the great-grandmother is the great-proprietress.
Great-grandmother.
Grandmother.
Little miss proprietress, please also do it here.
Little miss proprietress.
Please make it sparkle.
This is Yuna. She's in work-mode when she wears an apron.
When we are here and you have an apron on what do you call me?
Master.
Yes.
Today she is hosting at the masters' restaurant.
I look forward to working with you the entire day.
To put the young proprietress on her first errand the master has thought of a trick.
The proprietress-to-be, her mother.
Hello? This is Nonki Sushi.
Taking an order over the phone.
The homepa spread?
Homepa spread for home parties.
Homepa?
Master.
Yes.
Can you make a homepa spread for four right away?
For four? Got it.
He will be busy. Furthermore...
One of them can't eat raw fish so...
No raw fish? I haven't prepared any such ingredients today.
A realistic performance.
Asking for no raw fish to a sushi restaurant.
Hey hey, listen to what the master is saying.
White radish sprouts, avocado and cucumbers.
We don't have cucumbers?
This is the errand. Please listen.
What should we do?
Hey Yuna....
We have to do some shopping
can you go buy some?
Today?
I will go on an errand.
Will you go?
Can you go?
Really?
I can go.
Off I go.
Wait a bit.
She's eager.
Big brother.
Yuna
Actually her brother recently had his errand debut
and she's been asking enthusiastically "When can I go?"
I see.
Going to the supermarket nearby.
She needs to get white radish sprouts, avocado and cucumber for the sushi.
On top of that, spring onions and 20 plates.
The shop is nearby, but that's tough.
This is my first time going by myself.
Yes, it's your first time.
It's your "First Errand".
You can't lose. Do your best.
I will not lose.
Off you go.
Bye bye.
I will not lose.
There's a mic in the good-luck charm that has "I won't lose" written on it.
It's what Yuna always says during crucial moments.
With those words her mother intends to make her do her utmost.
It's neither hot nor cold in the clear autumnal weather as the little miss proprietress is going shopping.
Today I was asked to go on an errand.
It's my first time.
An errand?
Yep.
How admirable.
Since she is the proprietress of Nonki Sushi.
She has arrived at the crossing. The supermarket is on the other side.
Her mother gave her stamp of approval and told us that she knows to follow the traffic laws.
How cool.
Right
Left
It's fine. I will proceed.
How remarkable.
After the verification she swiftly crosses.
How pleasant.
Crossing and going around the corner.
The shop is within sight.
She was asked to get all these things. Will she remember them all?
My first errand.
What will she look for first?
Where are the cucumbers?
She starts looking for cucumbers.
I wonder where the cucumbers are.
Aah, it's behind her.
She's a beginner driver at handling the cart.
Ooh.
I will go and ask then.
How admirable.
She has arrived at the cashier.
Errand. Errand.
Wonder who I should ask.
I came all by myself.
She wants to ask someone but...
I don't know all by myself.
she doesn't know who to ask.
Great. She went back to the vegetable section.
Errand'ing is tiring.
This is different from her expectations.
The cucumbers are right over there.
I must do this errand all by myself.
What did you come to purchase?
I want to purchase cucumbers.
Cucumbers are right over there.
Did you get it?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
How great.
Found it. Cucumbers.
For the no-fish spread she needs to get enough for two.
So one is not enough.
I will take two cucumbers.
That's right. She was asked to get two.
But sure. It's fine to get three too.
You are getting four?
Since it's a sushi restaurant they can easily use it.
That was the cucumber.
And what's next?
Avocado. Avocado.
She remember the avocado.
But she doesn't know where to find it.
Let me politely ask for help.
How remarkable.
She decided to ask for avocados at the cashier.
I will do my best despite being lonely.
She's been feeling lonely so far.
So that's why she was talking so much.
She intends to ask: "Where are the avocados?"
She took the cucumbers.
Do you have a wallet?
I do.
She mistakenly ended up purchasing only the cucumbers.
There's still so much to get.
She paid, got her change but stayed at the cashier.
Bye bye.
She completely forgot all about the avocados.
I will go this way.
This is gonna be boring sushi.
I bought the cucumbers but...
It was no good.
Mama.  I bought the cucumbers.
You only bought cucumbers?
Yeah.
She remembered.
There were no avocados.
They said there were no avocados?
Thank you for the cucumber.
I will go back and shop again.
How remarkable.
4 more things to get.
4 more things to get?
It wasn't just avocados.
I better go again then.
You won't lose.
I won't lose.
Alright.
I'm taking off.
Off you go.
Radish sprouts.
Did she forget the avocados?
Also spring onions, avocados and plates.
Radish sprouts.  Radish sprouts.
Back at the supermarket.
What is left is radish sprouts, avocado, spring onions and plates.
Radish sprouts.
She arrives in high spirits.
Hello.
I'm on an errand.
You are on an errand? How remarkable.
Done with the greetings. Time for shopping.
Where are the spring onions?
She remembered!
Spring onions?
Spring onions.
Found it. I found it.
It's one of the four types on sale.
Now there's only 3 items left.
Let's hope she doesn't immediately go to the cashier.
Radish sprouts.
She remembered.
Oh no, she's heading for the cashier.
Somebody. I don't know how.
Avocados and Thai Curry (kaiware => taikare).
Where are the avocados and radish sprouts.
Great, she corrected herself.
Great she corrected herself.
Store manager, store manager.
Come to checkout Nr. 1.
Store manager!?
Store manager. Store manager.
It's a crucial matter. Here's the store manager.
Hello. What do you need?
Radish sprouts and...
steamed fish paste.
Steamed fish paste?
It surely changed.
Avocado became kamaboko.
If you say it out loud they do sound similar.
Or not...?
It's connected by the "bo".
I see.
Is this the one?
Yep.
Will one be enough?
Two boxes.
Two, right?
Thank you.
Not Thai curry but radish sprouts.
And kamaboko.
Kamaboko?
Let's go together then.
Kamaboko, huh?
Was it not kamaboko?
She senses that it's kinda wrong.
But here they are.
So it was kamaboko.
Kamaboko, huh?
Is that fine?
She put in two kamaboko pastes.
Is there more?
No.
Huh? And the paper plates?
Bye bye.
Seems like her head was full of radish sprouts.
I'm home.
You are back?
What a grand errand.
Welcome home.
You bought the spring onions?
Did you purchase more?
This is it. Radish sprouts.
I bought yet another radish sprout box.
Ah two. Proper.
Amazing. Amazing.
I accidentally purchased kamaboko.
She did notice that it was wrong.
I didn't ask for kamaboko.
Steamed fish paste, huh.
I didn't say steamed fish paste but...
We could put it in the dish.
You better do. Put it in.
And avocado?
Did you ask?
Huh?
I forgot.
Then, Yuna...
Can you go again?
Can you?
Yeah.
She's going again?
You won't lose.
I won't lose.
She's not giving up, the little proprietress.
Avocados.
The third time she repeats "avocados".
That's good.
I'm back again?
That's right. Avocados.
Avocado.
Hurry up and go ask.
That's the flow.
She heads straight to the cashier.
For grandma...
I better get a present.
She's doing unnecessary things again.
Her grandmas favorite food is Mitarashi dango.
She went straight to the checkout.
She went to the cashier.
Welcome. Is dango all you need?
Avocados and paper plates.
How good.
She was able to say it this time.
She doesn't know...
Store manager, please come to checkout Nr. 7.
The store manager again.
The store manager has been put in charge of the small proprietress.
In charge.
What do you need?
Avocados and...
Avocados and you see...
Please remember.
paper plates.
Paper plates and avocados. Let's go together.
Yep.
Apologies for keeping you busy, store manager.
Getting two.
I will pick this and that.
Alright.
And what else?
Paper plates.
Here are the paper plates.
This is great.
Is that alright?
Yep.
Alright. Bye bye.
Bye bye.
She has finally gotten all the items.
Finally.
Phew.
Third time paying today.
Looking for the wallet.
What's wrong?
Huh, it was lost?
Did you lose the money?
That doesn't sound right.
It has been lost.
What about here?
That's right. There's no money.
Can it be?
What should I do.
That's right. What to do?
She's in trouble.
Can I touch you?
It's not okay to not pay.
Is there really no money? What about behind you?
It's a pat down.
Pat down in a supermarket!?
Can you do without the items?
That's not an option.
Around that moment.
She forgot her purse!
Oh no.
She forgot it at the shop.
When she came back the second time...
She left it there?
Hey Yuna, can you go again?
The wallet!
The mother left it there.
The culprit of the wallet mystery is the mother!
The proprietress-to-be taking responsibility runs with all her might.
That's how it's gotta be.
Back again.
She made it.
Yunachan.
I'm sorry. I forgot.
I'm sorry.
Please do it better, proprietress-to-be.
She's so mad. So mad.
With this she can finally pay.
The little proprietress has purchased everything.
I did it.
I bought it all by myself.
You did. Thank you.
You really helped me out.
Sorry for being a forgetful person.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Master, will this do?
With these things I can make it all. Thank you.
Thank you small proprietress.
Both the proprietress and the great-proprietress are relieved.
Using cucumbers, kamaboko and avocados for the raw fishless spread.
And the homepa spreads with fish are also done.
Since you did so well today Yuna I will
make you the food you want to eat the most.
I will make that sushi for you.
How nice. Eating sushi at the counter.
Uni, ikura, toro or eggs?
Horse mackerel.
How plain.
How refined.
The local mackerel around here is famous for its fattiness and flavor.
It's the master's priceless ingredient.
Looks yummy.
This is a connoisseur's way of eating.
How refined.
How is it?
I'm grateful to be the daughter of a sushi chef.
Wonderful.
What a tough errand.
Really made me anxious.
Jeez.
I'm sorry.
In the end even the mother went.
It was really remarkable how verbal she was.
Avocados. Avocados.
I was amazed at how the mother said "You won't lose"
cause it made her kid excited and really turned on a switch in her.
Mr. Ebizou, to your children
when you need to motivate them,
do you have a way to switch them on?
No, I don't.
If you motivate them then it will only work for 25 days.
TN: Before his wife died of breast cancer they spent her last 25 days together with their kids at their home. He has blogged about those last 25 days.
And if you keep doing it it eventually loses its effect.
I do it only for those rare occasions.
Kangen
But it only works for about a week after opening day.
It has to come from within.
Shouldn't overshoot it.
So you want him to also learn how to handle even the days that don't go well.
I tell him that many people came to watch the play
and if he does fail
he will sense it himself.
So on those days he will cry tears of disappointment.
So he's really introspective about that.
So I leave him be.
It takes a lot of courage to self-reflect like that.
Gotou when it comes to a motivation boost.
I treat him with a movie and so on.
As a reward?
I will give him candy to encourge him.
What about Mikitty?
We do the opposite with
The Lion King style.
If my kid falls I say: Get back up!
He's like that.
When he says: "I don't want to go today."
I will never allow it.
What do you say during those times?
By saying you won't go today does it mean you will never ever go again?
Then he says: "Yes, I will go."
And he follows up on it.
That's indeed how mothers are.
They will say: "No good. Go right away."
And when I am by their side and say: "I will give you candy."
My wife says: "Oy!"
That's so true. You really understand it.
Later in this program: The Japanese Rugby team captain Tanaka's son will go on his first errand.
Collagen.
Can he purchase collagen for his papa?
Chicken thighs, please.
Chicken thighs.
Tanaka papa's breath is taken away all day.
The Seto Inland Sea is full of delicious fish.
Akashi sea bream in the harmony of Harima's open seas and oysters from Hiroshima.
The second largest island in the Seto Inland Sea is Shoudo.
Here there is a big fishmonger called Gyoden.
It's almost like a fish market.
Today they have Japanese amberjacks, blue crabs, rockfish and conger eel.
Ah, the octupus is escaping.
It fell out.
Everything here is fresh.
Every morning they bring the desired fish to the market
and when they close the entire selection has been sold.
They have such a passion for fish they take the trouble to get it.
There's no one better than this master.
What a nice smile.
The big brother cherishes his little sister.
Previously he would beg to be fed and clothed and being babied.
But now his mother scolds him: "You are not a baby anymore. You are a big brother."
The big brother should be able to go to the fishmonger by himself.
Rintarou, can you go?
By myself?
Now way I can go.
Didn't he become a big brother?
It's impossible to go by myself.
You said you could go.
I absolutely can't go.
A boy who can't go.
You absolutely can.
Because it's too embarrassing.
The big brother is too shy?
But Rintarou yesterday you...
Since he became 4 he has started feeling really shy.
You can't?
That's right since you are baby, Rintarou.
I'm not a baby.
This spring he happily entered giraffe class in kindergarten.
I'm not a baby anymore.
I'm a big brother who can do things by myself and take care of my baby sister.
You are not a baby?
Yeah.
What should we do about Chinatsu? She's hungry.
Chinatsu is crying from hunger. What should we do?
Alright, I will go.
He's manning up.
It went well.
For his hungry little sister
he's getting white fleshed fish at Gyoden
grilling fish of the season and squid.
Off you go. Do y' bes'.
Do m' best'.
He's going.
Since he's no longer a baby he better do his best.
It's tough being a big brother.
Across the bridge it smells of soft rush reeds
It's a tatami shop.
Gyoden is down this road.
The shop sign is within sight.
He's already there.
No way I can lose.
He's getting fish of the season, squid and white-fleshed fish.
For Chinatsu's first weaning meal, they will feed her white-fleshed fish.
He has arrived at Gyoden.
Good day.
Squid and delicious fish please.
Looking for delicious fish?
It's true that fish of the season are delicious.
What's good today?
Did your mother say grilled or boiled?
Grilled.
She said grilled?
The recommendation changes based on preparation.
A fishmonger that even sells to high-end restaurants.
What grilling fish do you recommend today?
Do you want this one? A pink colored fish.
Cherry anthias.
This one is so cute.
What is it called?
It's a sea bream.
Then you want this one?
Yeah.
And squid, please.
It's a young squid. Meaty and with a sweetness.
Anything else?
And perhaps some tuna.
Bluefin tuna?
His beloved bluefin tuna is rarely available here.
The store boasts mostly local seafood.
He doesn't know about largehead hairtails.
It's really beautiful.
What about this shrimp?
Still can't eat those.
Since Chinatsu is still a baby.
And what about this crab?
Also can't eat crabs.
He was told that they can't feed her crustaceans yet.
He understands all that.
Is it fine with these two?
And white-fleshed fish too.
Yes, for Chinatsu.
Since the sea bream is already a white-fleshed fish he ponders his next choice.
I'm looking for an even whiter fish.
An even whiter fish?
Makes sense to him.
Even with her fish expertise the old lady is struggling.
A white one with no colors.
He's looking for one that is white.
A fish without a color? This one.
Red tonguesole.
Like this?
But there's color on its backside.
This is no good.
He's harsh.
Nitpicky.
Like this?
But there's color on its backside.
This is no good.
It's still a white-fleshed fish, though.
He's nitpicking.
But it becomes white.
You peel the skin off and it's white beneath.
I see.
Do you want me to make it white for you?
Can she do that?
Please wait.
But Rintarou really wants to watch.
He's curious how she can make it white.
Since I'm in giraffe class I want to watch.
A morbid curiousity.
It will become white.
It's his first time seeing it.
Here I go.
Removing the darkened skin.
Heave ho.
And it slips off.
See, it become white. Isn't it good? It's white on both sides now.
How pretty.
But please cut off the blood.
Cut off the blood?
He's making demands.
Will you do the next one Rintarou?
The cute fish.
That's right.
She's filleting the grilling fish.
Poor fish looks in pain.
In pain?
Are you scared?
Not scared.
I see.
I will watch since Rintarou is in giraffe class.
His pride from being in giraffe class has strengthened Rintarou who usually loves being babied.
He's staring at it now.
Should I split it?
He wasn't ready for that.
Shock!
But giving it his all.
Rintarou farted.
You just made a toot?
The best.
It smells.
It smells?
I'm wet for some reason.
Old lady...
Having overcome his embarrassment
he has succeeded with the errand.
It's ready.
Let's see how much it amounts to.
Time to pay.
I...
have this dried fish.
The master has been observing.
Will you taste it?
And wants to give him delicious curry as a reward.
Curry. Do you dislike curry?
I dislike curry.
I'm sorry for this in your busy schedule, master.
It was a nice offer, though.
It's fine with only 2000 yen.
2000 yen.
He bought all this for 2000 yen?
It has been greatly discounted by the master.
Thank you.
Take care. Please come again.
Until next time.
Thank you.
What a splendid shopping trip.
The town of sun rays.
I wonder if it will be sunny tomorrow.
The paprika flowers are in bloom.
His mood has changed.
He crosses the bridge in a sunny mood.
The anxious one is his mother.
She keeps looking at the watch.
Rintarou.
It's his mothers voice.
Where?
Here. Above you.
Did you go?
I went.
It's just a bit further.
She looks delighted.
The paprika flowers are in bloom.
Please have a look at this face.
Please look at his posture.
He opens the doors with all his might.
Welcome back. You went? Amazing.
I went.
Thank you for doing your best.
Chinatsu is delighted.
He did his best for Chinatsu.
Boiling the red tonguesole
grilling the seabream in soy sauce and serving the squid raw.
Father
Let's eat.
Of course the Shoudo island-born father loves his fish.
His first meal was also a white-fleshed fish.
This is also Chinatsu's first taste of white fish.
How nice.
Your brother bought these.
Now able to go on errands
who is the big brother in the giraffe class.
Surely it's Rintarou.
What a magnificent big brother.
Nice errand.
Adults speak within a in-the-know context
but white-fleshed fish isn't conveyed well.
He heard it as simply white fish.
In general, with small children - like with kamaboko earlier -
a lot of them think that kamabo swims in the ocean like that paste.
So he will try to avert his eyes as the sea bream is being cut
and while feeling sorry for its pain he will still look on.
I think that's really nice.
I have a big brother so I've often noticed that
a younger sister usually only sees their strong side.
Even when he was on his way home his attitude changed positively.
So to see the troubles of an older brother
really made me emotional.
Speaking of brothers... Amami.
Yes, it's true that I have both a big and a little brother.
I really thought about how the brother did his best.
We often went to the ocean near Toyama during the summer.
One time it poured down. And I was so cold.
I was so scared that I started crying.
We were both huddled under a bath towel.
and said "you can have it".
How gentle.
My older brother was surely cold too
and this segment made me think of that.
You are crying?
I'm sorry.
I'm moved by your lovely story.
You are not crying during a segment but during our talks in between!?
They sound so gentle.
I'm sorry.
I can't believe that this happened during our talks.
And for our next errand.
A thrifty boy on an adventure to man up for his beloved father.
In Aizu, the town of Kitakata which is homophonic with Northway and is famous for their Kitakata ramen.
With its doughy and voluminous noodles.
With its thick noodles covered in broth. It's the best!
When speaking of Kitakata ramen, the soup can vary from seafood broth to animal broth.
From light flavor to strong flavor.
In this town with a population of just under 50,000.
There are over 100 joints.
And this joint that's been operational for 36 years is run by a father who wants to put their child to an errand.
Who from Sendai has taken over the joint just recently.
This fighter who is wearing the same clothes as the owner is the 3 years and 9 months old Ao.
3 years?
But at home where the owner is simply papa Ao is treated sweetly.
But her mother has raised his older siblings with tough love.
But even she has a sweet spot for Ao.
Since he's the youngest and just about cute
I can't help but treat him with cuteness.
He's always looking at his brothers and sisters and is perfectly capable.
He helps out with various things even cooking. However....
He's still drinking milk from a bottle?
He likes it too much to stop.
Ao has looked up to his father since he became a restaurant owner.
He wants to be cool like his father and work.
Their home is just behind the joint.
Ao, it's time for you to put on your work clothes.
Getting dressed for work.
Cool.
Look at the face. He's ready for work.
Remember when we talked about what type of ramen kids would like?
They discussed it yesterday with the owner
to change the children's ramen
They brainstormed on paper.
They would need some petit noodles.
Currently the freebie is some candy but what if they change it to toys?
- Kamen Rider toy
- Stickers
Would be lovely with toys.
They will adopt Ao's idea.
Gachapon: Capsule-toy from a vending machine.
Papa said that it would be nice with a gachapon.
He is usually told not to get gachapon by himself
but this time it will be his errand.
We want an Anpanman gachapon.
Eh? Not getting a Kamen Rider toy?
But only boys will be happy with a Kamen Rider toy, right?
I see, equal rights.
I'm asking you, okay?
A gachapon errand.
But you need them for your experiment.
First he will bring an apron to his father's work place.
Experiment for three.
The petit noodles is at the noodle maker.
He was asked to get gachapon from the supermarket and Anpanman kamaboko and milk.
He's only 3 years old.
Since they need 3 toys he can do it thrice today.
Remember to loudly proclaim
"Thank you for your hard work, owner".
Yep.
Because his father is the owner when he's working.
Off you go.
I got it.
Today he's on an errand so he enters through the backdoor.
He's always told the he can't just enter the store to play around.
But today, he's wearing his work apron so he's free to enter.
Welcome. Order up!
The loud voice of his father.
The shop is full of customers.
The clanging of utensils.
Thank you for your hard work.
He's nervous.
Here is his fathers' apron.
Ao, thank you.
His father makes sure he knows what to get.
Ao.
You are going shopping, right?
Yep.
Do you know what you are getting?
Gachapon.
As expected his head is full of toys.
3 petit noodles.
It's petit noodles.
These short noodles are ideal for children.
Okay?
I'm asking you.
Will he be fine?
Yes, you can exit through here.
Feels like he's only heading for the toys.
Things already look suspicious.
Did he become homesick?
As if stuck to the ground his feet stopped moving.
What's wrong?
He's not moving a bit in front of the joint.
That's expected from a 3 year old.
The joint is blocking the view to his house.
I wonder if he's still over there.
His father can see him.
He's been looking on for 20 minutes.
Ao, what's wrong?
Aren't you going shopping?
Ao, you are a boy, right?
This is Ao who wants to be a man like his father.
You will go, right?
You can't just keep standing here.
The father, told him once again.
Since you are a boy...
Dad's gonna cry too!
Can you go and do your best?
Um.
Please do your best.
I will be watching from here.
Um.
Do your best. Go on.
He's told to do his best not as an instruction
but as his fathers prayer.
A prayer to make Ao strong and go forth.
It's green. You can go. Raise your hand.
Go. Hurry up and go.
Do your best Ao.
He did it! He crossed the street.
His mother was also worried.
Ao, do your best!
Seems like his fathers and mothers prayers have come true.
Since they are making three meals he needs to get three toys and more.
On this street to the left is
the big supermarket with the toys.
Wait!? He's crossing the street?
Which means he's not getting the gachapon but...
he's heading for the noodle maker.
Look at this face. He's not playing around.
He's making a serious face.
The noodles he needs to get are shorter so that kids can easily eat them.
This place is where they get all of their noodles.
They have started allowing regular customers to purchase items here.
They make the noodles inside.
Good day. Welcome.
Good day.
Did you come by yourself? Are you on an errand?
He's been giving it his all so far but...
What can I do for you?
He doesn't know what to say.
Please tell me.
What is it? Did you forget?
Do your best.
Huh!? What was it again?
Three petit noodles, right?
Please have a seat.
Do you want some water?
Maybe he will remember after a drink.
Do your best.
What have you been told to purchase?
Thick noodles.
Thick noodles?
He realizes immediately that it's not right.
I see.
Thick noodles.
Thick noodles?
Did your mama say thick noodles?
Petit noodles and thick noodles.
It's not easy to differentiate for beginners.
Surely the owner can work with these.
Thank you very much.
He was not able to let out his voice inside
but he knows what to say when leaving.
Thank you.
He has more confidence now that he has the noodles.
Yaay.
His mood is improving.
Yayay.
Maybe his mood is too over the top now.
The gachapon is that way.
My mama said to get gachapon.
Three. You should only get three.
If he gets a Kamen Rider gachapon...
He's usually told he can't but today he's told to get some.
You rarely hear something this delicious.
There's also this.
Kamen Rider.
He wants to get the Kamen Rider but he's holding it in.
Today it's this one.
That's right.
Even girls would be delighted by Anpanman.
But it's only 3.
This is the first one.
One came out.
Two more to go, right?
Can I?
What's wrong?
He's hesitating.
But...
"But?"
Since when I
do it multiple times mama scolds me.
Hit a wall.
But it's different today since you were asked to.
He's afraid that he will be scolded if he does it a second time but he does it again.
Since today is an errand.
Needs three.
It's fine. He was asked to get three so one more to go.
I better not do it.
Even though he was asked to get three he could only do it twice.
He's terrified.
Next up is the milk.
He needs to get milk but he doesn't know where to find it.
The easiest way is to ask the shop attendant.
Welcome.
Are you looking for something?
Yeah.
What are you looking for?
Milk.
He was able to ask.
Remarkable.
The old lady is taking him there.
What type of milk? Big? Small?
Yes, a small one.
The big one.
A big one?
He wants to drink a lot so he's getting the big one.
But it's definitely heavy.
What else do you want to get?
Erm...
He was also asked to get Anpanman kamaboko.
Ah! It's right here.
Oh no, they passed it.
What did you purchase previously?
This is ramen.
Isn't it ramen?
That's what I said.
What do you plan to put in the ramen?
What goes well with ramen?
We have a lot already.
You have a lot of naruto?
Both naruto and imitation crab are types of kamaboko (steamed fish paste).
Since it's a ramen joint.
What about this?
Imitation crab.
I'm not sure about putting this in ramen.
He loves imitation crab.
You want to put it in?
Yeah.
That's original.
You have two types of gachapon.
Is this for playing around?
This is for the children's ramen...
Got it.
It's a freebie for the children's ramen set?
Amazing.
Yep.
I got it?
The old lady is sharp.
A ramen joint?
The name of the store is written.
Oh, the Raiyuu ramen joint.
Why didn't you say so? I always go there to eat.
It's delicious.
She's a regular.
Papa is doing great.
He's making delicious ramen.
He is, isn't he?
He's been observing his fathers ramen making.
The work of the second generation owner. Proud of his cool dad.
Carrying...
A heave and a ho.
It's heavy but
It's heavy but he's carrying it.
Can't hold it.
He can't hold it but he is carrying it.
Feels like I can't carry it.
Feels like he can't carry it?
What should I do.
While he complains he does have spirit.
It's heavy and I'm exhausted.
You're not reckless you are clever.
Break time. Break time.
Ah.
Mama said that I should
put it in the bag.
In here.
I see. He remembered what his mother said.
I want him to hurry home.
I know not to peek but I can't help myself.
Do your best.
The thoughts of a parent who can only pray.
Kamen Rider.
After putting it in the bag both his hands are free to.
Hurry.
He feels lighter now.
I'm exhausted.
I will rest at home. I'm exhausted.
Welcome home.
He will inform his mother first.
How was it?
Come here.
It was heavy, right? Mama will help you out.
You helped. You truly helped out.
He better take it to the owner.
This time he's making a grand entrance.
This face.
Papa, ramen.
Did you buy it?
You bought some?
This is not the Anpanman kamaboko
but it's fine.
He will work it out.
You helped out. Thank you very much.
Since he bought thick noodles he made the soup a bit thicker to match.
With imitation crab that kids love.
Might be cuter this way.
Valuing the opinion of children.
Are you satisfied with this?
Okay okay.
It's an okay if Ao says it's okay.
It's a children's ramen who will excitedly anticipate what type of toy is inside.
What you bought I...
He will take a big gulp today especially since he bought the big one.
He can hardly lift it.
Today will be his last day with the baby bottle.
How cool.
He does look cool.
The hesitant way he was holding the 100 yen coin.
Afraid to put it in.
The fact that he was standing in front of the joint for 20 minutes. Made me teary-eyed.
It made me reflect on my own memories and brought back a lot of things.
When boys are able to clear just a single task
and immediately celebrating it
that's such an endearing part about boys.
Despite his maturing
to celebrate it with milk from the baby bottle.
It was kinda cool. He just can't stop.
Wasn't that just cool?
A contradiction.
Even though he shouldn't do it.
The next errand is with a girl but the premise is a sibling fight.
Fukushima ● Yamato city
The C57 still runs in the northern part of Fukushima.
The house is near where the steam whistle can be heard.
Big sister
Big
brother
4 years 8 months
Karin
Karin is the last child among the three friendly siblings.
2 weeks ago she ripped her big sisters playing cards which resulted in a huge fight.
She knew that she had done bad
So she said that: "Karin will buy new cards with her own savings."
When she is determined to go she will go. I asked her where do you want to go
and she said: "Icchan's cards."
When asked who was bad she said: "Karin".
While her sister was playing Sevens
Karin begged to get to play along
She was told no cause they were in the middle of a game.
She got mad and ripped a card.
No matter how much she apologized her sister did not forgive her.
I feel sorry for her.
This is the reason for the big fight.
They tried to fix it with tape.
She said: "I will never forgive you."
This is the first time she's gotten this mad towards Karin.
She wants to go back to before she ripped the card.
"I see. I could buy new cards with my savings."
That's what Karin thought of.
You only have two 1 yen coins.
She only has 2 yen?
Ka~rin-chan!
Please lend me some money.
So you will repay me?
When you grow up?
She will borrow.
With five 100 yen coins you can buy one pack of cards.
One pack of cards for 500 yen.
The mother looked into it.
Definitely wear your hood.
It has started raining a bit.
If I don't hurry they will sell out.
Make sure to wear your hood.
If you ever feel lonely then hug this charm tightly.
Mama made this to protect you, Karin.
The mom has made preparations
A charm with a microphone inside.
A good luck charm.
Her first time going shopping alone.
Be careful of cars.
What's wrong? Wasn't she the one who wanted to go alone?
She doesn't want to go anymore.
Why are you crying?
What's wrong?
Are you anxious?
She noticed how lonely it will be to go alone.
You want to be forgiven, right?
At that moment...
The whistle is blowing.
Her expression changed.
The power of the C57's whistle.
Which made Karin determined.
Please depart with the steam locomotive. You want to be forgiven, right?
Alright.
I will go.
Off you go.
She will go and purchase cards.
And she's also getting her sisters favorite cake.
Her mother gave her money for that.
On the way back she's also getting soba. Her sister will surely be delighted.
Tough.
Off I go.
Off you go.
Be careful of the cars.
I will.
Off you go.
Off I go.
She's going.
I better go shopping.
She's going on her first errand with this sense of duty.
Her mother truly believes that Karin is carrying such a conviction.
This is a determined expression.
No longer anxious. She's all good now.
An expression full of a sense of duty.
The cards are sold in the shopping center.
She was also told to get spring onion.
This is the main street of the town.
2 days ago it was bustling with people due to the soba festival.
The cake shop is also on this street.
Huh? Seems like she's getting cake first?
Welcome. Good day.
Good day.
Are you by yourself? What about your mama?
At home.
How remarkable.
Two gâteau au chocolat, please.
Gâteau au chocolat?
She's purchasing two?
One is for her sister. So the other is for herself?
Who will eat these gâteau au chocolat?
Is it for you?
Icchan and my big brother.
And your brother?
So she's getting one for her brother too?
How kind.
Please separate the two.
You are giving both? So you need two?
Oh you meant "separate" them? I'm sorry.
One more...
The old man is putting them in separate boxes.
Alright, 500 yen.
Even if she's getting two it's fine. There's still money left for the cards.
Be careful of the cars.
Do you know the way?
Which way is Maruni?
Maruni? It's that way.
Amazing that she could ask.
Next up is the most important thing - the cards.
The rumor has spread like wildfire all over town that Karin is on an errand.
Please do your best.
Karin, where are you going?
Maruni.
Maruni?
Please take care.
Shopping?
Please do your best.
This is amazing.
Off you go.
Loving the support.
Everyone has already heard about the ripped up cards. What a small world.
She has arrived at the shopping center.
I wonder if they have some good cards.
Good day.
Oh Karin, welcome.
The store owner is her father's senior Tacchan.
Icchan, you see...
I've accidentally ripped her cards so I've come to buy new ones.
I see.
Did she get mad?
Please wait.
There was only one pack left.
Tacchan has put it aside for her.
There are only these cards that cost 500 yen.
Is that okay?
Okay then. Follow me.
These cards have some popular characters on them.
Why did you rip Icchan's cards?
We were fighting.
You were fighting?
I bet Icchan became really upset.
Did you apologize?
To make her sister forgive her he wrapped it in luxurious wrapping.
She will surely be delighted.
1, 2, 3, 4.
He's giving her a 100 yen discount.
I received this from mama.
No no. You borrowed it.
She gave you some? How great.
Thank you very much.
See you again.
The spring onions are in the food section.
That's the errand her mother asked her to go on.
Spring onions for the soba she's making.
Pretty amazing she remembers all that.
Found it
She found it right away.
They are only for her father and grandmother.
Karin hasn't adjusted to the taste yet.
Good day.
Did you come to shop all by yourself?
How remarkable.
That will be 213 yen.
Thank you for your hard work. You are remarkable.
When she says hello everyone returns the greeting with a smile.
Tacchan has been watching her the entire time.
How kind.
Please do your best rest of the way.
What a nice town.
How lovely.
She has bought the cards, the cake and the spring onions.
Next up is the homemade soba.
Many things to do.
Everyone is still there.
Every face is familiar.
What did you purchase?
Spring onions.
Where are you heading now?
Soba.
She remembers.
There's also someone on the other side.
The old man from the cake shop was also worried so he's been watching from the outside the entire time.
How nice.
The people of this town are watching over her.
So it will be fine even if she's by herself.
She won't feel lonely.
Here at Kyoudoukan you can find the restaurant Soba Dojo.
It's a place to polish your soba making skills.
Her fathers junior, Tadayoshi, should be here today.
I've come to get soba.
This is Tadayoshi.
I will be making the soba now. Do you want to come and watch?
From scratch? That's quite something.
He will be making it now.
Since she came all the way he will show her how he makes it.
This is buckwheat soba. See it's greenish?
So buckwheat soba is greenish.
I will now turn this into noodles.
The principal occupation of Tadayoshi is pottery.
Here in Yamato they have a soba-making workshop for non-professionals
where you can get certified for soba-making.
Tadayoshi is so good he won the title of master in a tournament.
How amazing.
Do you like soba?
Yeah.
And papa also loves soba, right?
And grandma. And my brother.
Grandmother too?
And your brother?
And Icchan too.
So everyone loves it?
No, my mom hates it.
Shouldn't say that.
It's not that she hates it but she prefers rice.
What else did you buy today beside spring onion?
Cake.
You bought cake? Where did you get it?
Tadayoshi and Icchan.
Huh!?
I bought it for Tadayoshi and Icchan.
Her "brother" was Tadayoshi?
Since you always do your best making soba.
So that's how it is.
Tadayoshi is gleaming.
What else?
Icchan's Minion cards were ripped.
Who ripped them?
Karin, you ripped them?
And as an apology you are giving new ones to Icchan? How remarkable.
It's time to cut.
This is not something an amateur can do.
It's done.
How nice.
Nothing but a pro.
Looks delicious.
Here.
Thank you. You bought this for me.
The gâteau au chocolat she bought for Tadayoshiku.
Since he's not charging, this will be his reward.
Delicious.
Please smile a bit more. It's so delicious. Thanks.
Karin is also gleaming.
She really is gleaming.
Here.
Please take this to your mama.
Yes.
It's enough for all six in the family.
It's 4 o'clock and we will be hearing that thing.
There is it.
A town where the whistle of the steam locomotive echoes.
Even during tough times or when she wants to cry it suddenly changes her mood.
It's no longer raining.
She's walking with power.
Her mother did say: "Once she's set on something then she will do it."
The figure of her mother can be seen in the window.
She's on the verge of tears.
She has spotted Karin coming from the direction of the soba shop.
She's properly carrying the soba for six.
Karin.
Welcome home Karin.
Welcome home.
I'm home.
Come to the entrance.
Did you go to Tadayoshi-kun's place?
She even gave him cake.
You really did your best.
This is for Icchan.
Cake for her sister.
And Icchan's cards are inside this bag.
A new set of cards.
They were in stock?
Yep.
You must go with these and apologize so that she will forgive you.
You did will on your trip. Good job.
It would be nice if her sister forgave her.
You did your best.
Good day.
This is the big sister.
Will she able to properly apologize to her big sister?
Please come here. Hurry up.
Icchan.
I apologize for the other day when I ripped the Minion cards.
Thank you.
She was able to apologize.
Please hurry and open it.
Since they only had these she's curious if she will like them.
They are cute.
What a relief.
Thank you.
Her big sister loves these characters.
And one more thing.
Icchan.
I went to the cake shop.
Her sisters beloved gâteau au chocolat.
Thank you.
Furthermore...
Will you forgive me?
Alright.
How great.
I love you.
She was forgiven.
I almost cried but I bought soba by myself.
Her big sister loves soba.
Everyone is sharing it.
Mmmh.
After the meal they play cards for the first time in two weeks.
Karin, please don't get too hotheaded again.
All around well done.
An errand for an apology.
And she did apologize, right?
Why are you crying?
I'm sorry.
It hit bull's-eye.
Isn't that right.
I was so happy she was able to say it.
I was worried that the 2 yen didn't amount to anything but she did it.
Smashing the piggy bank and only finding 2 yen.
Yeah, what can you do with 2 yen?
Hotta, you also cried a lot.
Yeah a bit.
A siblings fight. Yeah, it's not good.
A siblings fight.
Did it remind you of your big brother?
That's right when we fought...
I could never apologize sincerely.
What an honest child.
- but the whole town felt so warm. What a nice upbringing.
- That's right.
Yeah, it makes you want to be raised in such a town.
But since I live in Tokyo it's just not like that here.
But there it seems like everyone knows each other.
As expected from an "Errand" fan. Great analysis.
It's fine.
Next up is the big adventure of a talkative little girl.
When bringing up the subject of an errand
she became so delighted.
Hikari, can you go?
Yaaay.
Hikari
3 years
4 months
Please have a look.
Her fathers handmade flag for crossing the street.
She will be highly visible since it reflects the sunlight.
I'm crossing.
Thanks.
Hikari
3 years
4 months
3 years and 4 months?
Big brother
Father
Mother
Full of vigor and hates losing.
She smooth talks her, 2-year older, brother to get him to do things.
Everyone says she was born with a gift of chatter.
Saitama ● Chichibu
Talking about errands
there's not a single shop closeby.
Ah, there is a single shop. A mechanic. So her mother is sending her on an errand to get a car fixed.
It has a light scratch.
It's an errand to get a forgotten object inside of the car.
And the forgotten thing is...
A pink photo album that Hikari knows well.
Inside it...
Mother
When her mother was young and on a young people cultural exchange program.
She helped as a midwife.
Full of experience.
The friends from 15 years ago came to their house yesterday and they held a party.
And the friends feigned having forgotten the photo album in the car.
To get to the mechanic she has to follow the long road
and she was asked to get two peach juice bottles from the vending machine.
The dazzling smile of
Hikarichan.
So cute.
Off I go.
Remember to say hello.
Full of vigor and hates losing.
Off she goes.
How come?
What's up?
How did they forget it?
She's mad.
She's complaining.
Good grief.
She said good grief.
But she will go get it.
Recently she's been learning her numbers.
Remarkable.
She can even count past 21?
How amazing.
She can count to 39.
I'm so smart!
Ah, it's within sight. It's within sight.
Where, where?
If I go there the photo album should be there.
I'm so smart.
She has spotted the mint green wall.
Her eyes are as sharp as her mind.
Here I don't have to be too attentive to cars.
She even knows the term for "being attentive to cars".
That's right, there are no crossings here.
It's straight ahead on this one road.
She's so smart.
The weather is nice and not windy.
Oh no.
Huh? What's up?
The wind is blowing.
That's what her mother always exclaims when she's hanging clothes.
Phew.
Good grief.
She has learned to say good grief from her brother.
Huh?
Looks like it will rain.
That's also what her mother often says.
Not a chance that it will rain today.
She has finally arrived at the crossing.
Should I be attentive to cars?
[Baby talk.]
Since there's no crossing around here
the father has talked with the traffic police
who has lent him a safety cone.
The dazzling smile of Hikarichan.
Will she notice it?
Stop.
Beep.
Father, Hikari is doing it properly.
How remarkable.
There are none. I did it.
Her hands are free cause she doesn't have to carry the flag.
It's within sight. I did it.
How great that I made it.
The white car belongs to her household.
The vending machine.
If I go there, will I arrive?
She's getting the peach juice first.
Money?
The silver ones are 100 yen.
And the brown are 10 yen. She knows that well.
The peach juice costs 110 yen.
How high.
The word for expensive and tall is the same.
Not the price but the button.
Her mother asked her to get the juice on the top row so that she has to call the old man for help.
It's impossible.
Yeah, it's impossible.
She can reach the money slot but...
How will she do it?
Though it's so close to me I just can't reach.
The peach juice that's close but far.
I can't reach up there.
Can't reach even if I jump.
Ah, what a shame.
Even though she could go and ask the mechanic.
I can't reach up there.
She's been mumbling to herself for 20 minutes.
It's so high up there. How difficult.
And at that moment.
Good day.
Amazing. She can yell.
She called out with a loud voice.
Good day.
Oh, over there?
It's rare that a small customer stops by.
Did you call me?
I can't reach.
I see, you can't reach.
I will carry you so you can push.
Is that alright?
Which one?
He's letting her do it herself.
One more.
After 20 minutes she finally got one bottle.
And... Mama said to buy two.
Mama told Hikari, "I'll leave it up to you."
She was asked by her mother but...
The old man is wondering if it's only about juice.
Did you only come to buy juice?
Yeah.
How remarkable.
What about the photo album?
Goodbye.
What?
There's nothing else that you need to do?
Yep.
I didn't forget a single thing.
Oh, she remembered. Yeah. That thing.
Ah, I forgot the money.
I forgot it.
When she purchased the second one she put in 200 yen.
She remembered about the change. 90 yen.
She forgot the change.
I forgot this.
It's good that I noticed.
How good.
She has completely forgotten about the thing in the car.
As she's about to head home the phone rings at the mechanic.
It's the mother. It's been an hour since she left home and she's worried.
Hello.
Did Hikari come that way?
Can I talk with her?
Yes.
A phone call from mama. Mama.
Say hello to her.
Hello.
Hikari are you okay?
I got two peach juice out.
You were able to buy the peach juice?
And with that I will come home.
That's not right.
Doctor Nonchan
said that she forgot it.
The photo album. The pink one.
Yep yep.
She remembered.
So that's how it was.
That's right.
See you.
Bye bye.
What did your mother tell you?
Album.
Album?
Where is it?
Inside the car.
Behind.
Behind?
Alright, let's look for it.
Found it.
Yay, I found it.
The pink album.
The thing that she wondered "how her mother's friends forgot".
Found it.
You did well.
Thank you very much.
Remarkable.
How did they forget it?
Good grief.
She's crossing the street properly where her father has put the cones.
Bye bye.
Mama, I found it.
Huh, phone?
Yes yes
I found it.
What a convenient mobile.
Ah, I found it.
I didn't know, mama!
She doesn't feel lonely as long as she talks to her mother.
Bye bye.
She is so cu-t-e.
Mama, I'm tired.
Still on the phone?
Better go back home.
I can see it.
Arrival.
Arriving in just a bit, I wonder.
I did it.
I finally arrived.
I'm home.
Were you able to go?
Yeah.
You have it.
Hikarichan.
You brought it back? You really helped out.
And two juice bottles.
And you also got two juice?
You managed to buy it?
The father did a nice job today behind-the-scenes.
Maybe he's been watching over her from somewhere.
The dazzling smile of
Hikarichan.
Who can go on errands now?
I can.
Say yes.
Yes.
The excellent doer with a dazzling smile.
Cute.
After this the son of the Japanese rugby team captain will go on a grand adventure.
And tears of endurance.
A mother's emotional anguish.
What a bright and energetic child, wasn't she?
Angel... That's right.
She was so smart and lucid.
And that scene that walks along with her and then the drone zooms out.
That must've been so expensive.
You thought about that?
To use a drone...
Of course I was also moved by other things but
all of this was done for Hikari.
I am raising a daughter and when I look at Hikari I notice how much she copies her mothers' speech.
Like "I'm so smart"
and "good grief".
I better be careful too.
Three year olds
they absorb new words
but can't put them together well
which I think is normal.
But seeing how she's speaking sentences amazes me.
I'm close but can't reach it.
How unfortunate.
When my son was three years old
he was obsessed with Super Sentai
and he wanted to play fight but he only understands the overall mood
And he would hold a sword and say
It's you, isn't it?
I totally get that.
It's you, isn't it? Who do you think you are?
Complete nonsensical.
I had no clue what my role was.
Collagen​. Collagen.
A kid was asked on an errand at a shop within sight.
I wonder what collagen is?
It's right there.
Base for collagen soup. The mother intends to make soup pasta.
What are you going to purchase?
Collagen.
He can finally say it.
Eh? He's this small?
Collagen.
The is the 3 year and 3 month old Mao.
Can you say it?
Who said that they wanted to eat it?
Hmm...
Papa.
That's right. Papa said he wanted to eat it.
Can you go purchase it for papa?
- He's not listening. Not at all.
- He's not listening.
The shop's parking lot is in front of their house. He's small but he can run.
Collagen is such a difficult word. Wonder if he will remember it.
What's with that?
This please.
He pointed at something.
What do you want?
This.
What he pointed at is shoulder roast.
- It's collagen.
- Oh you!
How much do you want?
Two.
Apologies to mom but he couldn't say collagen.
The shady looking guy behind the cover is the father having a peek.
He is dressed up like the staff but you do recognize who he is, don't you?
It's the Japanese rugby team captain Tanaka Fumiyaki.
With his mere height of 166 cm and a small build
he's the small giant who smashes against the big boys.
Rated as top 8 in all world cup history.
It's a father who has made history.
And the mother who is watching a match and handling this boy like a rugby ball.
That's the boy who is trying to purchase collagen.
This time he's the one spectating his son and his errand.
Thank you for waiting.
He got shoulder roast which he wasn't asked to get.
How come?
Mama. Mama.
Looks like he hasn't noticed his father.
Heading straight back to his house through the parking lot.
Alright. No cars in sight.
Try (rugby term).
Are you okay?
He is fine but his purchase isn't.
Did you buy it?
Did you buy it? What did you buy?
Sliced shoulder roasts.
We want to make soup pasta.
That's why we want collagen. Wait wait.
He's not listening.
One more time.
Got it. Just hold up.
One more time. I made a mistake.
His mother told him it's wrong and she wants him to do it right.
Father
Mother
Mao
3 years 3 months
Ema
6 years 1 months
The father is away from home about half of the year.
The reliable big sister.
Thanks to her
they conceived an errand for Mao.
This is the second errand.
The mother is making him go to the butcher in front of their house.
If he can do this then the follow-up errand will be to go to a supermarket.
I see.
Well...
Don't you want to see your daddy delighted?
When his father is brought up Mao does what he is told.
The sister gives him some advice.
Collagen. Don't touch that.
It's a camera.
The power company is measuring things right now.
Can't help that his face is just like mine.
- Spitting image.
He has no idea that his father is watching him.
Collagen.
Still needs to get collagen.
Say: "Kora!".
Kora means "hey you!" and starts the same way as collagen.
Hey-gen.
Yep, collagen.
5 days ago.
His father trained him.
Spring onion.
Can he purchase what he's asked to get?
Gum.
Let's find a shop assistant.
He needs to purchase gum.
Excuse me.
He was able to ask.
Where are the "turnips"?
- Turnips.
- Sounds similar.
Turnips? Let me take you there.
They are heading to the vegetable section.
What a shame.
Mao, are you going to purchase this?
Gum.
Turnips (Kabu).
Gu
Ka
Turnips.
The confectionary.
Gum.
Turnips.
Why not make him get turnips then?
Since then.
Look right and left first and raise your hand.
He's progressed a lot.
I'm asking you.
It's collagen.
He understands how to go on errands now.
Also how to pay.
And the names of various products.
Alright and today it's collagen. right?
Chicken thighs, please.
Chicken thighs.
The 3 year and 3 month old Mao.
He's progressed a lot.
It's collagen.
He understands how to go on errands now.
Will he be fine?
Also how to pay.
And the names of various products.
Alright and today it's collagen, right?
Chicken thighs, please.
During the training his father made him buy chicken thighs.
Changed to chicken thighs.
How come?
Even though he was finally able to say collagen.
Please repeat it.
Chicken thighs.
Thighs?
This is a pork specialty butcher.
She thought he confused it with pork thighs so that's what she gave him.
He's watching it all from here.
Mama, open up please.
You can enter.
What did you purchase?
Chicken thighs.
No no, it's meat from pig legs.
Mao, are you having fun?
Yeah.
I understand you are having fun but
Mao.
You want to get it for papa, right?
- He's not listening.
I am about to get mad. Listen to what I am telling you.
There it is. That's right.
Come here.
She's getting mad.
She can get really scary during those times.
When he does things half-hearted
she will get mad.
I like that about her.
I want her to get mad more often but...
The mother isn't ordinary either.
I see.
She's a top athlete who aimed for the olympics in badminton.
But she retired when they married
and she continued fighting for victory as a mother.
But when it comes to raising her son she's lenient with him.
He's 3 but I still see him as a baby.
I mean
He's just like a miniature of this.
Which is cuter.
You're losing out.
Collagen.
Another try for collagen.
You can do it!
Go!
He's walking weird this time.
Collagen.
He's messing around.
He's gonna get something different.
Collagen.
That's unfair. She's saying it with him all the way to the shop door.
This time he can't forget, right?
Since he's already at the shop.
Right at the shop.
Collagen.
Collagen, please.
He was finally able to say it.
Please repeat it again.
Collagen, please.
Collagen?
Yep.
Collagen soup base?
Amazing. How nice.
No no no.
It's like moms wish made its way there.
Not only her wish but also her love has made it there.
I will take 100 yen.
He paid for it. His mother will be delighted.
I bought collagen.
You bought it?
Finally.
Thank you. You really helped me out.
To buy a mere collagen bag
it still took 34 minutes.
But his father is surprised by his sons development in these 34 minutes.
His development since he became 3 years old has been remarkable.
It's like he is breaking out of his shell.
Changing from a baby into a boy.
I want him to come out fast.
To be able to accomplish anything.
And become a boy who isn't prone to crying.
40 minutes have passed.
Time for a player substitution in the second-half.
Tanaka papa will switch with the mother and challenge Mao to a new errand.
This time it's further away.
Bye bye Mao.
Mao can you help out?
Yep.
What to get.
My favorite food is?
The errand is to get food that his father likes.
Chicken Nanban: fried chicken with vinegar and tartar sauce​
Chicken Nanban.
What type of meat is needed for it?
Chicken thighs.
Let's make a dance to help you remember.
Chi-ck-en thi-gh-s.
Hey hey hey.
Chicken thighs.
Nice. You dance well.
Chicken thighs, right?
Not enough.
That's right. Chicken thighs. We don't have enough.
And one more ingredient.
What vegetable looks like my face?
Which is pea green.
Cabbage.
That's right. Just like my...
Like the size of my face. Cabbage.
Cabbage which looks like his fathers face.
We are lacking it today.
Lacking in cabbage.
It's clever to use his body to help him remember.
What do you think, mother.
He's becoming hyper.
Is that not good?
Chicken thighs. Thump. What is it?
Chicken thighs.
Cabbage too. Thump.
But cabbages are big.
They are big but they have entered your head.
And the third item, mayonnaise, have entered too.
He's also getting mayonnaise?
For the tartar sauce.
Alright Mao, this is a good luck charm.
He should be more direct.
And now the mother is going to coach him.
Is she mad?
Please wait, it's mama.
Hello.
I think it's dangerous to let Mao out when he gets this hyper.
And because he's hyper...
So strict.
Please change your tone a bit
and tell him he needs to do it seriously.
And don't forget to put his jacket on.
Oh, that's right.
Yes, I apologize.
Come on, now.
She knows it won't go well if he's in a playful mood.
Mao.
Please listen seriously.
To turn him in a serious state of mind.
Stand to attention. Beep.
Papa he always does his best in rugby, right?
And in order to do my training
I want to
eat mama's cooking today
and do my best in tomorrows training.
He has training camp starting tomorrow.
Mao, you are a boy.
Yes.
That's why
I expect you to help us out properly.
Yeah.
Can you do it?
Papa believes in you, Mao.
His mood changed.
Yes.
This is the wristband that I always wear during matches.
Mao feels like a Japanese representative.
He looks so happy.
Papa will always protect you.
He's getting ingredients for chicken Nanban.
Chicken thighs, cabbage and mayonnaise for the tartar sauce is what he needs to get.
Off you go.
Yes.
Please do your best.
Okay.
Off you go.
Off I go.
Bye bye.
Do your best.
Bye.
He started sprinting.
His mother is peeking out from the blinds.
He's not long within sight.
Yes, he's not long within sight.
He started running the moment before I lost sight of him.
What is their state of mind?
I feel anxious when I can't see him. At least over there I could still see him.
And I didn't feel anxious.
I'm about to cry.
You are really on the verge.
I can feel his amazing growth.
Just previously it was the collagen thing.
Isn't it amazing?
It's amazing.
That he didn't complain and said that he can go.
His big sister is the one who taught him how to shop only 11 days ago.
There's no natto.
Mao, who didn't want to go, and as soon as his sister let go of him...
This was his state.
Amazing.
And they wondered if he could be relied on.
But in no time he has changed.
He has always done the railway crossing training with great joy.
Since he loves trains.
Unfortunately he's not seeing trains today.
Oh, it's passing behind him but he's not noticing cause he's on an errand.
Moments before in front of your eyes
is now a boy who just bought collagen.
That's right.
He has arrived at the large supermarket.
Poultry, cabbage and mayonnaise.
Take the children sized basket.
Will he remember?
Where are the vegetables?
That's great.
Vegetables.
Vegetables?
I will take you there.
The vegetable that is pea green.
The pea green one?
The pea green what?
There are so many.
Here and over there you can find pea green ones.
Is this pea green?
This is lettuce.
Isn't this much smaller than his fathers head?
And what else do you need to get?
Meat from chicken thighs.
Meat from chicken thighs?
He has memorized "chicken thighs".
It's the most important ingredient in chicken Nanban.
What will you make today?
Meat from chicken thighs and...
Pea green vegetable.
Pea green?
The fact that he could say chicken thighs but didn't say lettuce made the store assistant concerned.
What an amazing shop assistant.
Is it lettuce or cabbage?
Amazing.
Small children always confuse lettuce and cabbage.
Is he getting both?
Gonna be heavy.
Huh, what about daikon?
He was not asked to get daikon.
You are also getting daikon?
Heavy.
He's also getting daikon?
You can't carry this huge thing.
I can.
You can't carry it all.
The shop assistant is worried that he was not asked to get all these things for the errand.
Mao will carry this.
You will carry it?
He's carrying it like a rugby ball.
Cabbage or lettuce. Which one is it?
Lettuce.
This is...
Which one?
Which one is his fathers head.
The one like my father...
Is it this one?
He choose the cabbage.
He completely forgot the mayonnaise.
He prefers it to be heavy. That way he's guaranteed praises from his father.
But will he be okay?
Heavy. Heavy.
So tough.
The assistant to the shop manager ran over to help.
The cabbage fits perfectly in the ladybug. I see.
His father thought of everything.
Bye bye.
The chicken meat is also in his bag.
In his hands is the daikon he wasn't asked to get.
And this is how it usually ends with the daikon.
This is what happens.
He's dragging it.
Oh no no.
A gravel road.
No good.
Do your best.
He lifted it.
It's popping out.
Saved it from severe damage.
A train.
Waah, hurry.
The train is coming.
Hurry. The train is co...
He can still run with the daikon.
No reason for the staff to be worried. He's watching from a distance and with composure.
He really loves trains.
He's waving at it.
After this crossing he's almost home.
Another.
Another train.
Hurry.
He's going back to the tracks?
That poor daikon is on a journey.
We underestimated him.
With a height of 94 cm and a weight of 13 kg.
Without fail
this small giant is walking with all his might.
The Mao who has returned has the face of a boy.
Mao.
Do your best.
I'm home.
He did it.
Welcome back.
A try (rugby move) into his fathers arms.
You did your best.
You properly...
Thank you. You bought it?
Here is...
A hole.
The plastic bag also did its best.
It was able to bring the daikon all the way home.
However...
Why did you buy daikon?
Let me see...
Bought it since they had daikon available.
Since it was available?
Yeah.
Thank you.
No problem.
Let's also eat daikon.
Focus. Focus.
The father said: "Let's make grated daikon."
And the chicken Nanban
is a nostalgic Japanese taste his wife made when his team went to New Zealand.
Since he didn't purchase mayonaise they made ponzu mixed with grated daikon.
I see.
They made soup pasta with the collagen.
Thanks for the meal.
Todays chicken Nanban is exceptional.
Delicious.
Mao.
It's really delicious.
The collagen was hard to get.
The pasta is good.
Wanna try the daikon you bought, Mao?
It's what you bought Mao.
It's an acquired taste after all.
That was funny.
Yeah.
It's like a short movie.
That's right.
That was quite something. He went so many times.
His expression changed moment by moment.
The pride felt from having a duty.
How he went to the butcher in front of his house
and to think they went with the supermarket right after.
That's indeed unusual.
The way his father made him remember in a fun way with his body.
That was spectacular. We are like two peas in a pod.
I also do that to easily remember things.
When I try to remember.
But while it works for me the mother said: "No good".
And then he was like: "I'm sorry."
And after that his expression changed  instantly.
Like a switch being flipped.
And for our next errand...
An errand with a strict code and a warm embrace.
Fukushima ● Aizuwakamatsu
The thing that everyone knows in Aizuwakamatsu city.
Here the kids in primary school
have to follow a strict code.
The Aizukko Code
Specific to the town of Aizuwakamatsu.
This is the Aizukko Code.
What? What?
Empathize with people.
Say thank you and sorry.
Persevere and more.
Even when adults look at it, their backs straighten up.
Do what you must. Don't do what you must not.
The things you should not do, you must not do.
How wonderful.
Since the time of Byakkotai samurai the rules have been continuously passed down for the children.
When you ask both adults and children in this area their backs straighten up.
It is not just history, it is the honored code.
And when he breaks the code this boy immediately bursts into tears.
The youngest child, Yuuto, and his two sisters.
Second daughter
Oldest daughter
Yuuto
Before his bedtime his parents used to read him the declaration.
Second daughter
Oldest daughter
Mother
Father
And as he grew up he came to remember it by heart.
Having pride in Aizu town and listening to the elders.
Do what you must. Don't do what you must not.
The things you should not do, you must not do.
Though he still can't read.
The samurai Yuuto. He's been getting energetic since moments ago.
Yuuto please answer it.
Hey hey.
Remember to say "hello".
Hello hello.
It's his sister in primary school.
Memo
She is reading the script her mother gave her.
I forgot something at home so can you get mom?
She said that she forgot something.
She usually does forget but today it's just an act.
I forgot my sheet music so please bring it.
I see.
Just like in the script.
Yuuto, this is bad.
Um?
Momo said she forgot her sheet music.
Is it there? Can you take a look?
She uses them to practice the piano with her mother.
Found it. It's the sheet music that she uses to practice for the choir class.
That's not good.
Oh no.
Since it's noon we better hurry or it will be too late.
The 4th period ends at 12:05. There's more than 1 hour left.
I want you to take it there, Yuuto.
Will Yuuto go all by himself?
Because you should "do what you must", please do your best.
The code says: "Do what you must."
Please go, okay?
He won't cry.
Splendid.
Please wait.
You shouldn't go inside the school wearing a raincoat and drenched.
When I enter and take off my raincoat I should wipe myself with a towel.
Splendid.
That's right.
Must do what I must.
Isn't it "Do what I must"?
Things you must do and things you must not. It's difficult.
Since you should do what you must. Please do your best.
I will be waiting for you.
His sister also goes to her primary school by foot
but worried about Yuuto his mother found a route that has fewer cars passing by.
Yuuto, you are capable.
She also believes in Aizukko.
Will you fine going this way?
They have set up the premise for Yuuto's errand.
Off you go.
Off I go.
The youngest of a 4 generation 10 people big family.
Until now, everyone has done everything for him.
Sometimes shy, prone to crying and frights.
However...
He knows that today he must "do what he must".
I better hurry.
He should hand it to her during lunch.
I better go.
To Momoka. For Momoka.
Because she forgot the sheet music.
Remarkable.
Don't do what you must not.
Is our school really
all this way?
That's right. It's 2 km one-way. 4 both ways.
Is that right?
That much?
Thank you.
He's been told that he has to cross like this when he enters primary school.
His mother has been training him.
Momo is in her first year and has 2 years to go.
The shy Yuuto.
Can he approach the reception?
Good day.
He was able to.
Excellent.
This is Momo's...
Good day.
Mo...
What's up?
The third year student Momo
I brought her the thing she forgot.
Right now she's in a class
but I will open it for you. Please wait.
He arrived 30 minutes before time.
Amazing.
His sister is still in class.
Since I am wet
the towel is in the bag.
It's in your bag?
Just like his mother told him. Wipe yourself when you enter.
Great that you are on an errand.
It's a kid with common sense.
That's right. Put the slippers on too.
Let's go to the principal's office.
The principal's office?
Some might be terrified of such a prospect but
Yuuto has no idea what kind of room that is.
It's fine. He is being welcomed inside.
Sorry for intruding.
Makes you anxious.
It's the principal.
Good day.
This school has faced these tiny visitors
and boasts of doing so for over 140 years.
And the two successive female principal's.
Sheet music.
You brought sheet music?
Can I look inside?
Tightly.
It has been taped up.
So that it doesn't get wet.
In order to avoid getting the important sheet music wet.
She wrapped it in 40 plastic bags.
That many!
It finally came out.
Amazing.
Sheet music for the choir class.
Thanks.
He has waited 20 minutes at the roomy principal's office.
Respecting the elders.
Persevering. Just like the Aizukko pledge.
How admirable.
It's his sister.
She was called to the principal's office.
Excuse me.
Yuuto.
He arrived 30 minutes ago.
Thank you.
I came here by myself right away.
How remarkable.
A kind sister.
You did your best.
What a moving response.
But that's not all.
Huh? Wait. Where's the script?
The script?
Something is missing.
There should be a script here. Not just this.
Mama probably forgot.
Mama, you shouldn't forget that.
Since it's a musical there is the sheet music but also a separate script.
Her mother didn't know.
Oh no.
Mama probably forgot.
Mama, you shouldn't forget that.
Since it's a musical there is the sheet music but also a separate script.
Her mother didn't know.
Script
It's at home above the piano.
The script. What will they do?
It's fine. I will borrow it from someone.
How good.
You still did your best.
Thank you.
A kind big sister.
She's so kind.
His sister understands.
The hardship of a 2 km route, 4 km round-way trip.
Despite me coming by myself.
And then it ended up like this.
- Like this.
- He's so serious.
- He still brought it.
It's fine. Your sister was truly happy.
This is gut-wrenching.
It was a failure.
He doesn't feel accomplished.
But you were told you didn't fail.
He opens the door with a gloomy feeling.
Yuuto, welcome back.
There was another thing she forgot.
Eh?
Did you give her the sheet music?
That's amazing.
But...
There was another thing she forgot.
Is that right?
What else did she forget besides the sheet music?
This is it. Found it.
The script.
I'm sorry Yuuto.
She messed up with the preparation prior to today.
This is it. I'm sorry.
It's the same cover. What will we do?
Though his sister told him it's fine she'll borrow it from someone.
He won't tell his mother that.
Yuuto. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It's my mistake.
Though he did it properly he still feels gloomy.
Yuuto is not entering the house.
His mother has noticed Yuuto's wavering resolve.
Can you go again?
Will you go?
He will go.
It's 2 km.
Since it's you, Yuuto, you can do it.
I'm sorry.
Please do your best.
Must do what you must.
He finally understands the meaning of it.
Since it's you, Yuuto, you can do it.
You want to cry, right? You can cry.
His mother embraces him and lets him cry it out.
Sorry.
While crying he's still resolute and willing to go.
And when leaving the house...
He perfectly stops crying.
He departs with bravado.
The mother feels a sense of heavy duty.
She can't stand in the way of Yuuto's sense of accomplishment.
Must do what she must do.
The noon class starts at 1:30. That's less than 30 minutes left.
I better go.
The first time it took 40 minutes.
He won't make it if he isn't 10 minutes faster.
- Amazing.
- How does he have so much sense of responsibility?
Despite her feelings, his mother wants him to feel accomplished.
She must be stoic.
15 minutes left.
Do your best.
He's running rather than walking.
In the rain. He's made it half-way there.
This is like the face of an athlete.
It was rough and worrying.
Only 4 minutes left.
The rain has ceased.
Do your best.
He's almost within sight of the school.
She got a call by her mother that Yuuto is coming back.
He's coming back twice just for me?
His sister is in disbelief.
The school is right there.
What about the time?
Two minutes left. He can make it.
The crossing flags.
Even at such a time he doesn't just run.
Do what you must.
But...hurry. Hurry!
The bell will sound in one minute.
His sister is so full of anxious excitement.
Yuuto, you totally did your best.
I'm exhausted.
But I'm so happy.
It's the bell.
Do you understand?
But I'm so happy. Be happy.
Shaving 10 minutes off his last time.
He's at his limits.
He can't even celebrate.
His sister went back to the class right away.
Mother, he managed to deliver the script.
She's worried if it was alright to let him go twice.
She's anxious until she sees Yuuto's face.
Welcome back.
This face shows accomplishments.
You did your best.
Thank you. Did you manage to go all the way?
It was cold, right? I see. You did well.
I'm sorry. Thank you.
Do what you must.
Amazing.
Don't do what you must not.
You should not do what you must not.
Amazing.
You can't see on his face that he ran 8 km.
Really amazing.
What an errand, right?
Yeah, it was amazing.
Ebizou, you cried a bit, right?
I totally didn't.
It was amazing as expected.
His mother didn't intend it to happen but
they forgot it at home
but it was an errand to erase regret
and those tears she shed.
I don't know how to express it.
He's to be praised after the first run alone.
That's right. That's how it should be.
But if it was real the mother would go, right?
But if she went then the boy's sense of accomplishment would be diminished.
The fact that his mother didn't go is truly love.
That's right.
It's amazing how
it showed the soul of Aizu. (In Fukushima prefecture)
Amami you kept saying that Aizu was amazing.
To see his face become determined
and how he carried the guilt that he had to go again but said he would "absolutely go".
Right. So many things to it. His mother was the one who forgot yet...
Yeah so many things in the mix.
Yeah, that was a little heart-wrenching.
As we speak about it you are about to...
Let's move on.
I'm fine.
You can pull it back.
Both his mothers'
but also his sisters' bond was splendid.
When she says "I'm happy" and "Be happy" that really made me think
that their bond
has grown even stronger.
And for the next errand is the adventures of a girl.
Where both the father and the daughter are stubborn and they wont compromise.
There's a father who never gets angry but he's so stubborn.
His daughters always do what their father tells them to do.
The father is a 3rd generation member of the farm.
They produce dried kaki for luxurious gifting.
When talking about Matsusato's dried kaki
it's the high grade product that represents Yamanashi and shipped all over the country.
Looks delicious.
In the distant mountains of Koushuu
Yamanashi ● Koushuu
Blessed with sun and well-drained soil they grow delicious kaki.
In the koufu basin a strong dry notherly wind blows.
It's the optimal climate for making dried kaki.
It goes back in history.
In old woodblock prints the method of making dried kaki is depicted as well.
Amazing.
The time around late November is the most spectacular season of the year.
How picturesque.
The drying kaki color the whole town.
It invites a loving motif for photographers in the prefecture.
Big sister
Ririka
The little sister Ririka will go on her first errand.
She always copies her big sister.
Every year, at her big sisters elementary school, during this time
they peel the kaki
and learn how to prepare them.
Even households that don't make their own
the children all get to learn how to help out.
That's how the children are raised here.
Through ages the families have gathered at home like this
And they peel the kaki all day for an entire week.
Son of
great-granduncle
Granduncle
Daughter of
great-granduncle
Granduncle
If my sister helps out so will I!
Is she preventing her father from working?
Okay.
How many is this?
Let me see...
Fifth one.
No no, she's seriously helping out.
Time to change our gloves.
That's right or they will tear again. So please do it.
Just like a tissue box
there are 100 single-use gloves.
Thank you. I will take this one.
No more left.
Any left for me?
It's already empty.
There's none for your Papa, huh?
This must be the errand.
Can you go buy some?
The size is L(arge).
Do you understand L? What's it look like?
That's right. Single-use gloves.
Take this good-luck charm.
There a microphone in the charm her mother made.
You can do. Yes you can. So do your best.
Her mothers' wish.
So you can go?
Her mother who is a pâtissier is at work today.
I see.
At the hardware store she needs L-sized gloves and string to hang the kaki with.
At the drug store she needs to get snacks for 3 O'clock tea
and bandages for her father to wrap around his fingers.
I can do my best.
She's quickly off.
She's off in a light and good mood.
I can do it. I can do it.
Yes, I can. Yes, I can.
As long as it's for her father.
I can do my best.
Mom, she can definitely do it and do her best at it.
Ririka loves her dad so much.
Her father who is responsible for the farm after her grandfather suddenly fell ill.
Actually there's a different part to him.
He can be seen on the stage
with various famous artists all over the country.
He's a pro guitarist.
He made a band in junior high school.
He went to university in Tokyo and became a pro musician.
You can do. Yes you can. So do your best.
His fate has conflicted between what he wants to do and what he must do.
Ririka is always following her sister around and loves being babied.
I can do. Yes I can.
This song
Ririka's father made a song with her in mind.
Title is: The road of kaki leaves.
How wonderful.
The hardware store is within sight.
All the farms It's the height of dried kaki making time so it's more crowded than usual.
The cashier is a friend of her mothers from her preschool.
Did you come by yourself?
What will you purchase?
Gloves.
There are so many types of gloves here.
Did they tell you what the gloves will be used for?
Kaki.
Do you know the size of the gloves?
If it's L then is it fine with white ones?
White gloves.
We have these and these.
This one?
She picked the correct ones. The box with 100 L gloves.
You got it? Did you find the right one?
Will papa use them?
He's peeling kaki.
You are all preparing kaki?
And you ran out of gloves?
They tore.
They tore?
Were you asked to get something else?
And string to hang kaki.
And string to hang kaki?
In this area they have a special corner for drying kaki.
The tools change depending on the type of agriculture.
So just saying "string" leaves you with many options.
That's amazing.
Which one will do?
The thin or the thick ones. Which do you need? Thin?
White.
I see.
The one that her family uses is white.
For the white strings...
It says: Kaki strings.
These are specially made for kaki.
You can grip the kaki in between like this.
That's how we do.
That's how you do it? Then let's go with this one.
She's been observant when her father works.
It's exactly this type of white string.
What's this?
You can do. You can do.
You can do? You can do?
That's amazing.
You can do your best.
I see. You can do your best.
If you try you can accomplish it, Riri.
Do your best. High-five.
Off you go.
She did it. Yes, she did. She did her best.
And for the 3 O'clock tea time...
And also the bandages to protect her fathers fingers.
She has arrived at the drug store.
Here there's also a specialty corner.
Since everyone is preparing kaki these days.
A line-up with great additions for their tea break.
She was asked to get anko dango but they are sold out.
But there's anko in these too so they will do.
It's hard to make such a decision.
While considering it she gets the bandages first.
Remarkable.
For a guitarist their fingers are their life.
So he wraps them in bandage.
She found the bandages right away.
But she's lost in the many types.
Which one should I get?
She can't decide for herself.
She doesn't know any of the store workers and without asking any
she leaves the shop without purchasing anything.
How come?
She's not confident.
She has become a Ririka who: Can't do it. Can't do her best.
Despite completing the errand at the hardware store.
She carries a sense of defeat.
And it can be seen on her face as she returns.
Welcome back. That was quick.
Welcome back.
Amazing.
You bought gloves?
That's so great.
Even though she's being praised her face says it all.
That's expected.
You went and got some? How great.
Thank you.
Huh? Huh?
What about the dango?
There it is.
Did you go to Nakaya?
She did go but you see...
They didn't have dango?
They didn't have dango.
They only had the soybean ones.
They only had the soybean ones?
Then the green ones would've been fine.
See...you could've gotten the green ones.
Can you go again?
She looks so surprised.
I want to go with papa.
I'm busy.
When this is over...
Ririka can't go.
She said it clearly.
I'm tired.
You're tired?
But she's not exhausted yet.
I'm tired.
He's a father who
never scolds his kids or yells at them.
If they don't have manjyuu what else were you supposed to get?
I'm tired.
She has decided not to go.
He knows what she's trying to do.
Achoo.
What a nice sound
Nice old man.
We appreciate the gloves but we would also really like to eat some manjyuu.
Riri, thank you for the gloves.
But with the tea
I would like to eat some manjyuu. Please, Riri.
And with that...
Ririka, let's go outside.
Yeah, please go.
Let's take a break.
Trying to change her mood.
We are both pretty tired.
Since I play guitar my fingers are crucial.
You can just use a pick instead.
I see.
Then it won't be a problem.
What about this hand?
If the fingers on this hand are hurt then it will ruin the sound.
She lost the argument.
That's why they are needed.
What will you do if I trip and fall?
Then I will apply a bandage.
Ririka won't fall over.
I didn't know which type of bandage to get.
Ask a store worker loudly?
Eh?
I can't use a loud voice.
Then use a quiet voice.
Trying his best to reason with her.
Since it's you, Ririka, you can do it.
I feel like eating dango all of a sudden.
Then please go and buy some dango.
When mama is done I can go with her.
Then it will be late and everyone here will go home.
Seems hard.
Their conversation outside has been going on for 30 minutes.
Your extended family members are all doing their best with the Kaki. What about you, Ririka?
Ririka...
Her fathers insistence isn't wavering. He's stubborn.
What's that?
It's the drone filming them.
It's going away.
Oh no, I've been found out.
It's escaping.
Escaping.
Yeah, that's concerning.
Sorry for intruding.
Ririka, can you read this?
You can do it. Yes, you can. You can do your best.
Let's go!
Finally.
Remarkable.
Yes, you can do it.
Can you go?
And what if it rains?
Doesn't look like it will.
She's still making excuses.
Off I go.
Off you go.
Just like her father insisted.
She's on her second errand.
She's getting snacks for the 3 O'clock tea.
And bandages to protect her guitar playing father.
She's playing an instrument.
I was about to think that she wouldn't go.
You did well in revving her engine.
And her fathers new original song: "The road of kaki leaves".
It's a song born from the image of Ririka walking on her errand.
I can do it. I can do my best.
Do your best.
Can she ask the store worker this time?
Please do your best.
Where do you have dango?
She asked without hesitation.
Did you come to buy dango? Come with me.
I'm sorry but we've run out today. What to do? Will this do?
That's right. This one will do.
How many?
Six.
Six?
We are preparing kaki.
You are preparing Kaki at home today?
I see, I see. Then you need 6 indeed.
Even with a quiet voice she was able to convey it.
Since so many of her extended family have come.
Will you be fine if you get 4 of those and 2 of these?
Are you be fine with that?
She goes for it at her own discretion.
The store worker is hurrying towards the checkout.
She better mention the other thing.
And bandages.
Bandages?
She was able to say it.
This is a bulk pack. Is that fine?
Will you get this then? It has 100.
100 bandages?
I don't have the money for 100.
You don't have the money?
How many do you need?
Just one?
We don't sell just one.
You see... While it has 100 bandages in the pack it only costs 149 Yen.
That's cheap.
It's this cheap?
Will you get it then?
That's 628 Yen.
The bandages are for papa, right?
He plays guitar.
He plays guitar?
She's regaining her confidence.
Is it because he plays guitar that he needs to protect his fingers?
So he will use them to protect his fingers?
You are a bright child.
Please take this to papa, your mama and family members.
Thank you very much.
Even from behind she's beaming with confidence.
A huge difference from last time she came.
She was able to. She did it. She did her best.
A satisfied face.
She's walking back on the same road as before but there's a big difference.
Ririka loves the kaki season.
Because that's the season her father is home instead of away on the usual live tours.
Her father is waiting.
He's wondering about her face when she opens the door.
Welcome back.
This face.
Thank you.
Amazingly quick.
She made it for the 3 O'clock break.
You got lots of green manjyuu.
They only had four.
I see. But you were able to ask the store worker.
But it was with a quiet voice, though.
How amazing.
Thank you. Let's have some tea.
Enjoy these manjyuu.
Everyone, thank you for your hard work.
Thanks for the treat.
Thank you. You purchased these?
Delicious.
How great.
This is also a break to appreciate the work of Ririka.
That's true.
Is it delicious?
Welcome back.
Her pâtissier mother has returned from her job.
What did you do?
I went shopping.
Only once?
You went twice? Why?
There's so much she wants to tell her mother.
Let's go.
You see.
Daddy is so stubborn.