Translator/Timer/Typesetter:
Kay_guy01
Song Translations:
projecthello.com
Editor/Encoder:
SacredCultivator
Please visit us at:
http://www.hello-fansubs.com
HEY!HEY!HEY! Music Champ!
HEY!HEY!HEY! Autumn's Red/White
Huge Sports Contest!!
Onegaishimasu
Makihara Toshiyuki
Well, here we are again!
Hamada Masatoshi/Matsumoto Hitoshi
This time, it's a huge athletic meet
and these bad people here,
this group still remembers
so this time they're determined to win.
So they want to do it a second time!
The "We-were-scared-but-now-we-powered-up", Red Group.
Team Morning Musume!!
Down by 400 points, but could have had a upset victory, it's Morning Musume!
This time, new members have come!
At an average age of 15.9, these 13 members are quite young!
They've vowed revenge!
This time, the new leader, Iida Kaori-san
is making her appearance.
The new members... where are they?
They're in front.
The new members... these four.
Let's have a little intro from
Iida-san about then.
They look really scared right now.
You guys okay?
Umm...
These four are the fifth generation.
Please introduce yourselves.
I'm Takahashi Ai.
I'm 15.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
I'm Konno Asami.
I'm 14.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
Asami-chan?
I'm Ogawa Makoto and I'm 13.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
Lastly...
I'm Niigaki Risa and I'm 12.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
She's 12.
Amazing isn't it? She's 12.
Their teeth are really chattering though.
You could really feel the pressure
from the back there.
How is it everyone? Truthfully...
Please do really well okay?
So since Morning Musume has increased to 13 members
and Downtown is just the two of you,
so the number of people
seems a bit unfair right?
For us, we really don't need any helpers.
Is that right?
So the two of us is enough to battle.
Last time we had four people helping?
Four people right?
That was an even show.
That right?
They were the red and we were the white.
Right right right.
There's 13 of them right?
Yep, 13 of them.
And it's just two of us.
Well, anyway...
...please call them.
We've called on a lot of strong assistants!
So now let's bring them out!
The white group! Team Downtown!
First up, a performer who never fails
at anything athletic, it's Hiromi Go!
Adding in his skills with Downtown,
it's Kawamura Ryuuichi!
Skillful dancing and explosive
power, it's DA PUMP!
Balancing out with the other
young ones, it's w-inds!
Ready to help out in his sparkling
silver, it's DanceMan!
Ours are pretty great!
They're really amazing!
Speaking of athletic meets,
it's totally Go Hiromi right?
Awesome isn't it?
"He's a Pendant Killer!"
Hiromi is good, but DanceMan
I don't think we need!
Who is this guy? DanceMan...
Think he can fight in that!?
At least he's wearing his track jacket.
And so, Hiromi Go will start off...
I'm sure it was easy for you before, but how long
has it been since you've done a sports contest?
A while right?
A sports contest right?
When I'm training, I was exercising
three times a week so...
I see.
I'll be all right.
So umm... what's Hiromi
Go-san good at exactly?
Well...
things like ball-tossing...
Well I have endurance so...
But will your forty-year-old
shoulder pain be okay?
So this time...
It's okay. I'm good at running.
Ah, running is good then.
After recording this HEY!HEY!HEY!,
he'll take a small vacation.
Eh? Where to?
He'll be going to America.
Ah, so you're working after this!?
Some admirable work.
Just like HEY!HEY!HEY! right?
Kawamura-san told us he actively
participates in bowling competitions,
but what about sports contests?
Well...
I haven't done any exercising lately but
today I'll...
Talk a little louder!
If you talk louder, the mic wouldn't
have to be so close!
Microphone
Umm... today...
how much is Downtown gonna
keep pulling my leg?
And then, everyone from Da Pump,
when they begin a sports contest,
their fighting spirit increases!
It really does!
They'll show us how hard they try.
And then, your young brothers
over there, w-inds, also...
We're really full of energy!
Huh?
We're energetic.
What are you energetic about?
The sports contest...
This okay? Da Pump...
It's good that they're talking like that.
If it goes down, we're blaming you.
Don't let it.
And then there's the question, "Can
he even do a sports contest?"
We'd like to ask DanceMan.
Onegaishimasu!
So now we'd like to do the Player's Oath.
White group captain, Hamada-san!
And the Red group captain, Iida Kaori-san!
If you please!
Player's Oath
Ready... and...
Sensei!
We take the role of sportsmanship leaders!
And vow to compete fairly and honestly!
Red Group captain, Iida Kaori!
White Group captain, Hamada Masatoshi!
Battle #1! Ball-toss!
Well, Go Hiromi-san told
us this was his specialty.
Ball-tossing...
The fewest number will lose.
That's right! And doesn't that
side have fewer balls?
Think so?
Everyone made two a piece
by themselves at home?
Me and Hamada made some
and brought them!
At your own expense!?
Made them yourself didn't you?
Go-san, what's the key
to getting the balls in?
Hiromi Go!
Well, it's concentration.
Concentration?
Eh? This requires concentration?
Yep, concentration.
Well, the White Group has DanceMan right?
He's tall so it might be easier for him.
That's true. He's got height.
And on this side, the Red Group...
you don't have much height do you?
That's true.
It's kinda de opposite isn't it?
However...
we're young, so our speed might be...
enough to get them in.
They have a lot of unknowns...
Morning Musume.
So we don't know.
Ball-toss
- 1st Game -
Ready...
Both teams are throwing nicely.
The White Group seems
to be a little faster.
The White Group looks like they're
throwing a little quicker.
Lots of cheering.
The Red Group has good control.
Everyone in Morning Musume
is giving their best!
White Group? Red Group? Which will it be?
Each team is getting them in.
Eight seconds left!
Seven seconds!
And finished!
We couldn't!
Here we go! Ready...
Morning Musume's basket is empty!
Which means...!
The White Group wins!
The second game is a handicap match.
Underneath A and B are balls,
and you may only choose one.
Under one are regular
balls... under the other
are round things that aren't easy to toss!
So now someone will choose first and
let's go with ladies first.
From the Red Group, Iida-san...
please choose A or B.
Either one?
Either one is okay. Which
one will you choose?
Which one I wonder?
Which one should I do?
Go with A.
A!
Okay... B!
Then, please open up B!
What's inside?
Ordinary balls.
So that is the Red Group's.
Hamada-san...
This one...
So this is what White Team ends up with.
Ibaraki Prefecture's highest grade chestnuts
What's that?
These are...
These are the highest grade
chestnuts from Ibaraki!
Wait wait... wait wait...
This was 100% pre-arranged wasn't it!?
No,no. It's just what she chose.
So umm, from Ibaraki prefecture...
This is too weird!
Those pointy things will get in the way!
Unbelievable!
Yes, but...
Kinda strange that they said, "A!" but
she went to the other one isn't it!?
Absolutely 100% deliberate!
So for these chestnuts,
the White Group will...
Freaking unbelievable!
Shut up!!
So, if you win with your handicap,
you'll receive 200 points.
Hold on a minute! Those are dangerous!
Because if you throw and miss, then
the people on the other side
might get hit in the head right?
Can't believe you wanna do
the same thing with those!
Of course, for the safety of the White
Group, we've prepared gloves and helmets.
Is that acceptable?
But... we're not talking about just the head...
My shoulders could get hit! My shoulders!
My flesh is still exposed!
And now to get started
with the next battle!
Ready...
I'm getting worried.
Don't hit them!
Do your best!
It's a little impossible with the chestnuts!
The Red Group seems to be doing well.
15 seconds left!
The Red Group lost the last time but
that's not deterring them now!
The White Group is doing their best as well!
It's a close match!
5 seconds left!
4!
3!
2!
1!
And stop!
Stop! Stop!
This is no good!
And anyway, Maki, did you
even throw one chestnut?
So let's begin! Ready...
1!
Dangerous! Dangerous!
Are you okay!?
That guy! It was him!
You hit her! You hit her!
You hit a girl right before her wedding!!
You should be upset!
She doesn't even have a helmet!
Please be carefull where you're throwing.
So can we continue then?
All together! 21!
Ow! Ow!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
You did it again!
You hit me!
Before I'm married!
So from 22!
22!
23!
The White Group has no more!
Which means, Morning
Musume is the winner!
Please give me love... WA —
Mr.Moonlight Up Side Down
Mr. Moonlight
A bit of a saucy young man
With a bit of a lively step, going Up Side Down
OH BABY BABY, tonight is to Up Swing
Won't you dance with me? PARADISE
But comparatively, he's a crybaby young man
Everybody's a weak thing Up & Down
OH BABY BABY tonight we're gonna Up Date
Won't you sing with me? PARADISE
OH! If it's my lover, I wanna
keep close to them for 24 hours
BUT! That won't become lady work
Love is like a train that stops at each station
It halts to a sudden stop and won't go on!
(Mr. Moonlight) Gonna swear to you tonight
(Mr. Moonlight) As much as I can
(Mr. Moonlight) I'm gonna keep lovin' you
And incessantly, smiles overflow
For some reason, let's create happy days
With all the power we've got
And LaLaLa, affection overflows
LaLaLa, let's sing a song
"Oh! Are you saying your hearth is grieving?
Ooh, BABY, that's love... love sickness.
Surely, ever since you met me...
You probably fell in love.
Now, everything's okay now, I'm here,
Come on, let's dance!"
So young man, let's go without panic
That's right, life is taken Step By Step
Well, BABY BABY, tonight let's Forget
Won't you dance with me? PARADISE
OH! If it's my lover, I wanna kiss him
AH! Wanna kiss and kiss him
BUT they won't have the scent of a lemon
Love at times can start quickly
Love at times can break quickly!
(Mr. Moonlight) Gonna swear to you
(Mr. Moonlight) Perhaps, surely
(Mr. Moonlight) I'm gonna keep lovin' you
And LaLaLa, let's confirm
LaLaLa, our affection today, too
(Mr. Moonlight) Gonna promise tonight
(Mr. Moonlight) As much as I can
(Mr. Moonlight) I love you
(Mr. Moonlight) Perhaps, surely
(Mr. Moonlight) As much as I can
(Mr. Moonlight) I'll keep on lovin' you
Battle #2!
Three-legged obstacle course relay!
In this battle, where two contestants
tied at the ankle
must complete an obstacle course.
At the start, the three-legged
team must crawl under a net,
then grab a piece of bread off a string.
Then the two must crawl through a ladder
and then find and borrow whatever
item is on the paper.
Once completed, they can switch
off to the next relay team.
The winning team will be
rewarded 100 points!
The batting order for the Red Group starts
with the shorties Tsuji Nozomi and Kago Ai...
then the Ishikawa Rika and
Ogawa Makoto pair...
Yoshizawa Hitomi and Niigaki Risa pair...
Leader Iida Kaori and Takahashi Ai pair...
then Abe Natsumi and Konno Asami pair!
We'll see how well the old and new unite!
On this side for the White Group, Go
Hiromi and Kawamura Ryuuichi will start...
then the Shinobu and Yukinari
pair from Da Pump...
Da Pump's Ken and w-ind's Ryohei...
then w-ind's Keita and Ryuichi...
lastly, it's DanceMan with Matsumoto
Hitoshi serving as anchor!
So umm... why am I with DanceMan?
"Why" you ask?
The height difference is way off...
and DanceMan... at least make
him take his boots off...
And Iida-san, looking at these members...
it's the new members and...
are teamed up with the veteran
elder members, right?
Was it planned out this way?
That's right...
we wanted one thing to happen...
Morning Musume's power...
I got it... right.
Well, the pairing of the new members
with elders is pretty good.
It's like their will are joined together.
New members, please do your best!
And the two that are going first,
do your best even though you're smaller...
Right? Small kids...
Shorties, do you best okay?
On your marks!
Get set...
Lot of speed at the start!
The first is... it's both teams at the net!
Red Group seems to have some
trouble... can they catch up?
This pair is fighting hard!
Here's Go Hiromi and Kawamura Ryuuichi!
Good! That part is okay!
Ah! They've gained a small lead!
And now, they seem very
skilled... MoMusu okay!
Well, the White Group's
at the item to borrow...
The Red Group has just arrived!
Glasses!
Glasses
Ready... and...
You can just grab it!
Okay! Okay! You can switch!
Changed off okay!
Thick-soled boots
Well, the White Group has a huge lead!
White Group is already passed the
net and the Red Group is...?
Red Group, what do you need?
They still seem to be searching for it.
Thick-soled boots!
How's the White Group doing?
They've already taken the bread!
What's taking so long with
that? Please hurry!
What's it? Did you get it?
The thick-soled boots! It's okay!
The second runners!
Ishikawa Rika and Ogawa Makoto!
Scary face
The White Goup's found it perhaps?
Well, what could it possibly be? They
seem to have found something...
What could it be?
A pretty big...
Red Group has caught up!
They're right behind!
Their thing is...
Red Group needs to find their item quickly!
Foreigner
Smile a little...
Okay? Okay?
A foreign person? She's okay!
The foreigner is okay.
Please do it together!
It's the third one!
We're now on the third leg!
Yoshizawa and Niigaki...
Da Pump's Ken and w-inds' Ryohei are now
in the lead!
Both teams are giving it their all!
White Group is almost done!
What's the thing they need?
They've taken the paper and...
The Red Group is closing in!
Crew cut
What could it be?
They're searching for it...
Looking for a person with a crew cut!
And the Red Group?
The Red Group needs...
Might be nobody...
Watch
A watch!?
Red Group is looking for a watch!
A person with a crew cut!
You can't use yourself.
Please look for someone.
And the Red Group?
A watch! A watch!
They can switch to the fourth team!
The fourth team...
Looks like they found their crew cut!
Iida Kaori and Takahashi Ai-chan.
Looks like they did it.
The fourth team for the White Group...
w-inds' Keita and Ryuichi!
Red Group is almost finished.
Young people on both teams!
Keita's got the bread!
They've caught up, the White Group.
From here, we don't know who it could be.
Over 100 kilo person
Aaah~! Crap!
Anybody over 100 kilos!?
Cotton gloves
Cotton gloves! Cotton gloves!
Is there somebody here over 100 kilos?
Found him? Oh the guy from before...
The guy from before with the scary face...
Is this okay?
Cotton gloves!
White Group's cotton gloves are okay.
So this is the last team to go!
The White Group's last team to
go, Matsumoto and DanceMan...
The Red Group's Abe Natsumi and
Konno Asami are catching up...
Abe Natsumi and Konno
Asami are catching up!
They're through the net!
Will DanceMan and Matsumoto
keep the lead?
Konno and Abe have caught up with them...
Konno Asami... and Abe Natsumi
are trying hard...
Both of you guys do your best!
And they're off again!
And now, Matsumoto must search for...
Chest hair person
Someone with chest hair!
Chest hair!?
Anyone with chest hair?
Anybody at all? Anyone with chest hair?
And MoMusu? What must they look for...
2,000 yen bill
2,000 yen bill!
Anybody have one?
Here's the person with chest hair!
Now they need to cross the goal!
Goal! Goal! Please cross the goal line!
The White Group is the winner!
2,000 yen bill
And MoMusu? Did they find someone
with a 2,000 yen bill?
And the Red Group crosses the goal!
Thank you for all your hard work!
You guys did it didn't you!?
I'm so glad!
White Group is the victor!
That guy with the chest hair...
He had a lot didn't he?
There was that guy with the chest hair but
if you look closely, DanceMan's
got tons of it!
You had to use a different person right?
So that means, the looking-for-unappealing-people White Group
has won and receives 100 points!
Thank you!
Battle #3!
Kendo!
So, with the first half of the contest completed,
the White Group has a 100 point lead.
Could this be Red Group's weak point?
This is a challenge between two people.
Same rules as "Strike! Cover!
Jankenpon!" will apply.
The winner of each round gets 50 points!
Well, let's get started with the first people!
The first will be these two people...
From the White Group, Da
Pump's Ken-san and
from the Red Group, Goto Maki-san!
Thank you. Please stand-by.
Matsumoto-san shall preside
over the match.
Even though she's a girl, you've got
to do this with all your strength!
If you don't, then I'll raise the red one!
So, everyone along with
Matsumoto, please...
follow along okay?
So then, this will be the first match-up!
Goto Maki vs Da Pump's Ken!
And now this match... begin!
Ready... and...
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Goto Maki!
And he's safe.
You're bad at this aren't you!?
Let's keep going!
When he's safe, you don't
do that with the flags!
If you think about it, I've never
done anything like this...
Last time he should have tried it.
So here we go!
Ready... and...
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Goto Maki!
"Looks like a tie!"
Ken!
Ah, he stopped.
Yes and everyone's timings
should be a little better.
You should go at it harder!
All right here we go!
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
"Looks like a tie!"
Ken!
He seemed a little resigned.
The "bam" is supposed to be like that!
Like that... so go like that.
Like that!
So let's continue!
Let's go!
Ready...
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Ken!
Goto!
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Close!
Goto!
Goto Maki!
Goto Maki! Goto Maki's the winner!
The second match! From the White
Group, Kawamura Ryuuichi!
And from the Red Group, Yaguchi Mari!
Ready...
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
"Looks like a tie!"
Kawamura!
Too slow...
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Kawamura!
Yaguchi!
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
"Looks like a tie!"
Yaguchi!
Ah! Sorry!
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Yaguchi again!
Yaguchi!
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Kawa!
Kawamura!
Pretty good.
What about now?
So who was it just now?
No, no, no... I wasn't watching.
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Kawamura!
"Jankenpon!"
"Looks like a tie!"
Yaguchi!
"Jankenpon!"
Kawamura!
And now?
The white flag! Kawamura Ryuuichi!
Kawamura-san, you were pretty
easy on her weren't you?
Like... how do you say...
I have a gentle life towards girls!
Hamada obviously thinks differently.
DanceMan!
"Jankenpon!"
"Looks like a tie!"
After the commercial, the occurrence of a
huge incident in the "Strike! Cover!" Battle!
HEY!HEY!HEY!E Autumn's Red/White
Huge Sports Contest!
Next week, the occurrence of a huge
incident in the "Strike! Cover! Battle!"
And for this drawn-out fight,
the end has finally arrived!
Autumn's Red/White Huge Sports Contest!
Second part will be broadcast next week!
Don't miss it!