Our love
is eternal.
Shine...
Oh no.
Oh no, oh no.
Welcome home.
I'll make dinner right away.
I told you I'd be back at 8:00.
I'm sorry.
I've been feverish all afternoon.
Dinner will be ready soon.
You've been drawing manga, though.
Homemaker:
Kurasawa Kanae
Someone from Tokiwa publishing is
reviewing it the day after tomorrow.
Will you hurry up?
Oh, yes.
Kanae's husband:
Kurasawa Yoshihito
Don't make dinner tomorrow.
I've been invited to general
manager Tadokoro's house.
Understood.
Say...
Can I go to the hospital tomorrow?
Why not?
I have no cash.
I give you cash every month,
and you're already out?
Dumb woman.
Dear, you got a call.
General Manager Tadokoro:
Hey, hey, about tomorrow...
Score! I love you
I'm glad you're happy
She said dinner's ready, just a sec
Hey, hey, about tomorrow's
Spanish restaurant, I made
the reservation!! Can't wait
Score. I love you
I'm glad you're happy
I love you, too.
Just kidding.
You chose your wife poorly (lol)
I'll be home late tonight.
Oh, yes, you're having dinner
with general manager Tadokoro.
Yeah. See you later.
Have a nice day.
Give my regards to general
manager Tadokoro.
adultery divorce compensation
Filing divorce papers?
It's usually around one million yen.
The retainer fees, form preparation fees and
contingency fee will total about a million yen.
Many of people end up
broke because of them.
End up broke...
If you'd still like to go
through with it,
the retainer fees will be
100,000 to 200,000 yen.
I'll have to think about it.
Yes. Thank you.
Kurasawa-san, I read it.
Oh. How was it?
To be honest, comparing this work to
last year's newcomer award winner,
I just didn't feel it.
Oh, I see...
But, I'll have my senior
editor take a look at it.
No, no. I'll redo it.
A refill for your beverage?
Not for me, thanks.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize to him.
A refill for your beverage?
Kanae-san, you've changed.
What?
You seemed to be much happier before.
Before, when you encountered a guy like that,
Editor at Tokiwa Publishing:
Tabata Misato
you would say, "Oh, I can
use that in a manga!"
You were looking for material.
Did something happen?
Well, you see...
Lately, my husband...
A refill for your beverage?
Let's see...
I don't want a refill
for my beverage...
But can you pay me compensation?
One order of compensation... Compenー
Compensation?
Compensation for cheating on your wife.
Four million yen.
Four million...
You don't have to come to my restaurant
and cause me trouble.
I sent you an affidavit to fill out the
other day, but haven't heard back.
Is this the lowdown way
you conduct business?
What an interesting thing to say.
You have a Twitter account, don't you?
It's full of tweets
degrading your wife.
In terms of public and court opinion,
who would be viewed favorably?
The slandering cheater,
or the slandered wife?
Oh yes, and there will be further
compensation you will be liable for.
1.5 million yen, for
which you will be billed.
In total, that will be
5.5 million yen.
Thank you for your time.
5.5 million...
How can I pay 5.5 million?
I can't afford that.
But you have this
restaurant, don't you?
This is my precious restaurant.
600 yen for one cup of coffee.
The sandwiches are dry.
The proprietor manages the restaurant
to fool around with young waitresses.
What a corrupt establishment this is!
Or, would you like for
the court to decide?
All the details of your
adultery, what you did,
when, and how, will all have to
be reported in explicit detail.
It might get drawn out for years...
Please. Have mercy.
You see? See?
The one you should
apologize to isn't me.
Can you guess who is?
My wife.
Well said.
Divorce Chaser
~Let's Turn Your Tears into Money~
Divorce Chaser Epiosde 1
Play the "Dumb Woman" and Get Compensated!
Excuse me.
You're an attorney?
Attorney:
Hakamada Yukio
Yes.
Do you need counsel?
Yes, well...
Oh, no!
Can you follow me to my office?
But, I haven't...
Please, hurry!
O-Okay!
Hurry, please!
Hakamada Law Office
Tiger's Lair
Hurry. It's right here.
Please hurry!
Please, this way.
Hakamada Law Office
Please come in.
Yes.
Please wait there.
Have a seat.
No, thank you.
Want some sugar crisps?
Oh. No.
What?
So, are you the cheater
or the cheatee?
Just a second.
That face says it's the latter.
Am I wrong?
Well... yes.
Maybe a victim of domestic violence?
No, there's been no violence.
Oh, well. How boring.
Boring?
You know what...
I'll come back some other time.
Why?
Because places like this charge you
just for listening to you talk.
I've got no money right now.
Consultation is free here.
What?
The economy's tough, but he
insists on acting on principle.
You've come to the right place, though.
Hakamada-sensei looks like that,
but when it comes to practicing
divorce-law, he's crazy good.
All right.
Thank you for waiting.
First step, fermentation,
has been completed.
First step, fermentation?
Sensei is into baking bread.
You were in such a hurry for this?
The first step of fermentation is the
most important step in baking bread.
You could say this principle
applies to life, as well.
For relatives' weddings,
the first step should
be fermentation.
Please.
Okay.
So...
What can I do for you?
Um... Well...
My husband is cheating on me.
Cheating?
Give me all the details, please.
Yes.
I'm Kurasawa Kanae, 32 years old.
I'm a stay-at-home wife.
My husband Yoshihito works for
an advertising agency. He's 39.
We met eight years ago at work,
then we got married.
I quit working immediately
after I got married.
Right now, I'm an aspiring
manga illustrator.
I found out about the cheating
by reading his texts.
My husband has the woman's email
address under a fake name.
Didn't his cell phone have a lock?
No.
What a low-level coverup.
Huh?
He must really think you're stupid.
"She'll never find out."
"Even if she did, I could easily
talk my way out of it."
"Even in the worst case scenario,
it wouldn't be a problem."
That's probably the extent
of what he thinks of you.
Please, continue.
My husband is in charge
of all our finances.
He gives me an allowance of
40,000 yen per month, and that's all.
He's cheap!
Couples with husbands in full charge
of finances often go bankrupt.
It's amazing you lasted eight years.
But, he's shelling out a fortune
for his mistress, isn't he?
And it seems he's been calling me
"that dumb woman" to his peers.
That's terrible.
An impoverished vocabulary
when it comes to insults.
Sensei. Tea.
Me, too.
Yes.
By the way... are all
of you lawyers, too?
I am a private investigator,
Umemoto Kurumi.
Private Investigator:
Umemoto Kurumi
Investigator?
Like a detective.
Private Investigator:
Umemoto Kurumi
I'm intricately affiliated
with this office.
I'll be a helping hand.
I'm Shinozuka Rina.
Temp:
Shinozuka Rina
I'm a college student.
I help prepare documents.
I'm Toyama Yoshie.
Office Landlord:
Toyama Yoshie
I'm the landlord.
The landlord?
In other words, you have
nothing to do here.
Thank you for waiting.
I owe this office a lot.
You haven't paid rent yet,
have you, Sensei?
I can pay you last month's.
Let's start with the month before.
You'd better take her on as a client.
And when you get your fee, pay the rent.
You owe me for
investigation expenses, too.
My temp job payment, too.
Um...
Do you really plan on getting a divorce?
Yes.
You're prepared to fight if you have to?
With your husband, that is?
Fight?
Y-Yes.
I want to divorce him and start over!
Understood.
For now, please return home.
What?
What are you saying?
Aren't you taking her on as a client?
I know I might be stepping
out of my bounds, but...
This is of the most important decisions
you'll make in your life.
Please think it over.
What are you saying?
Why don't you think it over?
Sensei, why don't you
take her as a client?
You have no steady income as it is.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Dinner's almost ready.
Don't move.
What?
It's our wedding anniversary next week.
I'll be on a business trip,
so I can't celebrate with you.
Wasn't this expensive?
You've been helping with our
budget, so I could afford it.
Thank you.
General Manager Tadokoro:
About next week's trip...
Was your wife happy? Wasn't that a good
choice? I want a diamond for my birthday (lol)
OK you can expect that
Now we're set to really have
a great trip next week!!
Was your wife happy? Wasn't that a good
choice? I want diamond for my birthday (lol)
She's a dumb woman after all. She's naive.
She's a dumb woman after all.
I'm ready.
I'm ready to fight my husband.
I officially accept you as my client.
Please follow my instructions
for all of our upcoming actions.
Yes.
Please.
But, first...
What is it?
How much are the fees involved?
Shinozuka-san, please explain.
Document preparation: 50,000 yen.
Retainer fee: 300,000 yen when
negotiating terms with other parties.
Fee contingent on success,
call it a reward fee: 10%.
You need not worry.
This particular case...
we will get about five million.
Five million?
If you follow my instructions,
I guarantee it.
What do you need me to do?
I need you to continue playing
the "dumb woman" for now.
Keep playing the dumb woman,
and keep your husband's guard down.
For now, we let him swim freely,
and we gather evidence that
will give us an advantage.
We'll gather evidence regarding
when the infidelity began,
the days and times of his
trysts with his mistress,
and maybe even the number of times he's
had physical relationships with her.
Physical relationships?
What we need is reliable evidence.
Photos of him cheating, for example.
How are you going to
acquire such things?
Ye of little faith...
I'll let you in on techniques
I learned from the CIA.
The CIA?
From this.
"Iron Spy Woman, Marilyn"
Season 2, episode 3.
If you want to learn about the target,
first you have to know their car.
Car...
That's right.
Cars are filled with information.
First, the GPS history.
History Search
Diver Street 07 Jan 14
Shinagawa Royal Hotel 07 Jan 14
Sky Bridge 05 Jan 14
Minami Yurakucho 23 Dec 13
C'est bonjour Bar 14 Dec 13
Grand Hills 14 Dec 13
Karuizawa Golf Club 07 Dec 13
Karuizawa Garden Hotel 07 Dec 13
Yoyogi Station 07 Dec 13
Roppongi Sky Tower 07 Dec 13
After you gather the GPS history,
don't forget to attach the GPS tracker.
Once we pinpoint their date
location from tracker data...
We storm in.
We storm in!
This is for you.
Happy birthday.
Yoshihito's subordinate:
Aikawa Shiori
Thank you.
What a wasted opportunity!
Why didn't you snap the picture
as they went into the hotel?
I just couldn't do it.
I couldn't bear to watch.
Yeah...
I understand how you must feel. Here.
Kanae-san.
You did decide to go through
with the divorce, didn't you?
Yes.
And from that moment onward,
that your husband would
become a total stranger to you.
A person with whom you
would not grow old.
And you would be able to
separate yourself
from this stranger,
a person who infuriates you.
And you'll be able to get a lot of money
from that total stranger.
Everything you see is
going to turn into money.
Can you hear the fanfare?
Defeat your enemies
with a heart of lead.
These are perfect!
The mistress is Aikawa Shiori,
a subordinate at my husband's office.
The infidelity began
last year in February.
As to the physical relationships,
I have confirmed at least 24 times.
It must have been hard for you
to gather that much information.
But, when I think of him
as a total stranger,
I think to myself,
"This is material for manga."
Actually, I found myself
having fun at it.
I feel like a spy woman.
Not so fast.
Your actions were the most
elementary of the elementary.
It'll take you another 15 years of
experience to reach Marilyn's level.
Well, let's move
on to the next stage.
Please go ahead.
This time, I want you to cheer him on.
Huh?
I want you to cheer on
Yoshihito-san's love affair...
with all your might.
I'll be late again.
General Manager Tadokoro
is having me over again.
I see.
Have a great time!
Huh?
You're going out for drinks, aren't you?
You should have the
best time you can.
Well, yeah.
Have a nice day.
Do your best.
See you later.
Honey!
Do your best!
May I have a moment of your time?
We're searching for a lovely couple
to be wedding-ring models.
She called us a couple.
What can I say?
Please, come this way.
Please, come right in.
Here they are.
They're so cute.
We're actually not married yet.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's just you two seemed
so suited for each other.
But, isn't your wedding
fast approaching?
What?
I can tell.
I speak from much experience
in this line of work.
Is that so?
We're currently having a newlyweds campaign.
We're giving discounts
for wedding rings.
I want this.
I'm a pushover.
What a kind husband!
Whoops, jumped the gun
on the "husband" part.
But I sense the start of a happy family.
You make me envious.
Envious! Envious! Envious!
Excuse me, please mind our customers.
Those two are serious.
What?
If they were just fooling around,
they'd cringe at the word "marriage."
But Yoshihito-san is
behaving like a newlywed.
He even bought her a wedding ring.
I see...
But, now the ball's in our court.
How do you mean?
If he's serious about marrying her,
he'll be willing to pay
highly to get a divorce.
I see.
Also, because we've given
them the encouragement,
their love affair is at high tide.
Yoshihito-san may ask you
for a divorce himself.
And that will be our best chance.
Chance?
Yes.
I have something important
to talk to you about.
What?
I'm in love with someone.
I want to marry her eventually.
Of course I'll wait
until you're ready...
In that case...
Let's get divorced. Now.
What?
It's not an eventual thing,
you've already decided, right?
Yeah.
Will you let me draft
the divorce papers?
Yeah.
By using his guilty
conscience to our advantage,
he will let you draft
the divorce papers.
Divorce Papers
Contracts regarding the compensation fee, division of assets,
and other financial settlements.
Divorce papers specify all financial settlements
after the divorce is finalized.
We will draft it to our advantage.
That's why you wanted me
to cheer on their affair.
Now, the compensation you desire...
How much should we make it?
Is there some kind of standard for it?
Actually, there's a site that
will do the calculations for you.
Divorce Compensation
Number of years married: 8-under 9 years
Offending spouse's income: 5 million-under 6 million yen
Duration of infidelity: 1-under 2 years
Physical relations: More than 20 times
Status of marriage: Not on good terms
Divorce Compensation: 4,116,720 yen
Calculate
His age, years of marriage,
duration of infidelity,
number of of physical relationships...
By entering the data...
Within 2 seconds...
Got it.
It comes out to 4,116,620 yen.
Number of times of illicit affair: Over 20 times
Regarding marriage relationship: Not on good terms
Divorce Compensation: 4,116,720 yen
Calculate
Detailed.
The calculated sum is highly reflective
of the duration of the affair,
Compensation Calculation Site:
Calculations are based on length of illicit love affair, annual income,
the number of physical relationships, and other factors.
and number of times of
physical relationships.
It's quite a sum. But, what do you think?
That would be more than enough.
In that case, the compensation we'll
demand of your husband will be...
Divorce Agreement
Six million?
I agree to pay six million yen...
Yes. It was calculated
at a specialist's site.
First, you present him
with a higher figure.
This is ridiculous.
I don't have that kind of money.
Then, you move on to the discount.
The figures are estimates.
Of course you have to figure
living expenses with her...
How about this?
What?
When he lets down his guard,
you show him a convenient payment plan.
5 Million Yen [5 Year Payment Plan]
60 installments
I can agree to a five-year payment plan.
You'll only have to pay
83,300 yen per month.
83,300 yen a month...
I guess that'll have to do.
5 million yen...
Kurasawa Yoshihito
Kanae
Congratulations.
Congratulations! You got the compensation!
Thank you very much.
What do you think?
It's far better.
I'll show it to my superiors.
You don't even have to show it.
Cafe waitress:
Mizutani Sara
This manga will definitely
get syndication.
How would you know that?
I feel it.
I am never wrong.
Who are you?
Who, me?
I am...
Just a waitress at the cafe.
Here's your iced coffee.
But, I ordered a hot coffee.
Oh! I made a mistake.
I'll bring it right away.
Kurasawa
Tabata Misato
Today's Manuscript
My superiors loved it!
Monthly Man-day will run it
as a syndication next month!
Apartment Rentals
Sangen-jaya Station
Sancha's a nice area.
This one has a walk-in closet.
Can we wait on that?
What? Why?
The divorce settlement is expensive.
Compensation and all.
How much is the compensation?
Well...
about five million.
Five million?
Can't you do something about that?
I've already given my signature.
I'm going home.
Wait a second.
She sure is pretty.
Are you Kurasawa Yoshihito-san?
Who are you?
I'm Kanae-san's legal representative.
My name is Hakamada.
Attorney:
Hakamada Yukio
A lawyer?
Sorry to bother you,
but I've got the official divorce
agreement document for you.
H-Hold on a minute.
I cannot stick to this agreement.
What do you mean?
How could I pay compensation like this?
We've got living expenses to consider.
I understand.
However, you have already consented.
I admit to my infidelity.
But, Kanae and I were already finished.
I was miserable for so long...
day after day, without
any excitement...
I started hating myself
for growing old like that.
Things changed when I met Shiori.
It was just for laughs at first.
But when I was with Shiori,
I felt like a man again.
Then things got serious.
You're a man, too. Can't you understand?
I'm very sorry to say...
I don't.
Because I'm not a fool who
would cheat on my wife.
I'm sorry.
I know it's none of my business, but...
Before you set your life straight,
don't you have something
you need to do?
Goodbye.
Tokiwa Publishers
This is my superior, Ueki.
I'm Ueki, chief editor of
Monthly Man-day.
Please.
Nice to meet you.
I have made some modifications
to the previous manuscript.
Um...
Concerning the syndication...
it's been canceled.
What was wrong with it?
I can change it all you want.
That's not the problem...
Our superiors put a stop on it.
What?
Our advertising sponsor
put in their word...
they are our sponsor,
so it's out of our hands.
I'm so sorry.
I'm home.
My syndication by Tokiwa Publishers
was canceled today.
Oh, yeah.
Our advertising agency directs many
of our clients to Tokiwa Publishers.
We also have long-term relationships
with many other major sponsors as well.
I think it's going to be very difficult
for you to make a living in this field.
I knew it.
You're behind it.
Could you rethink the compensation?
This is terrible.
That was dirty.
Don't talk to me about dirty tricks.
That lanky-looking lawyer
fed you ideas, didn't he?
He's out to gouge me, isn't he?
Besides, this is a matter
between husband and wife.
Shouldn't it be the
two of us who decide?
Um, Hakamada-sensei.
May I have a little of your time?
Kanae-san.
What's the matter?
Um...
I want to rewrite the divorce agreement.
What?
I want to lessen the compensation.
Did your husband say something to you?
I know it's none of my business, but...
I cannot acknowledge that.
But this is a matter between us,
as husband and wife.
No, it is not.
When your husband had the affair,
he rejected the wholesome marriage.
From that moment on,
the two of you became
perpetrator and victim.
Adultery is viewed as
malicious intent by the court.
I view it as no different from a crime.
The adulterer should be duly penalized.
Hakamada Law Office
Hey.
Hm?
What happened with the compensation?
It went well.
I have no intention of paying
such a ridiculous sum.
I'm glad.
I'm not some domestic simpleton.
I'm a survivor of society.
I don't take things lying down.
I'm home.
How do you do?
The compensation has been modified.
Now you and I can start
living our new lives.
Divorce Agreement
10 million yen.
Ten million?
What's the meaning of this?
Regarding that, let me explain.
You...
We've already met.
First of all, regarding: "Ten million?
What's the meaning of this?"
Let me answer that question.
First of all, compensation is
measured by psychological duress.
Notwithstanding, by continuing to see
your partner in infidelity...
and bringing her into your home,
Kanae-san's psychological duress has
doubled since you made the agreement.
That will cost two million.
You have also acted to obstruct
Kanae-san's profession as manga illustrator.
The compensation for
that will be two million.
In total, the sum is now ten million yen.
Are you joking? I don't
have ten million yen!
Understood.
But, it was Kurasawa Yoshihito-san,
employee of the electronic advertising agency,
who acted to cancel Kanae-san's
syndication at the publishing company.
I will be reporting
this to your company.
Wait a second.
Please don't involve the company.
In that case, will you make the payment?
But...
In that case,
we will see you in court.
And I will fight you, for years,
even decades, however long
it takes, to make you pay.
You should remember this for the next
time you agree to a compensation.
There is something an
adulterer must first do.
That is to apologize.
The second thing to do, is apologize.
The third thing to do is likewise.
You will have to keep on apologizing.
And yet, notwithstanding,
you haven't asked Kanae-san's
forgiveness, not even once.
I have no intention of lessening the
compensation for a person like you.
But still, this sum is too much...
August 17th, Karuizawa Hotel,
Junior Suite, one night, 32,000 yen.
Expense List of Illicit Affair
October 3rd, Spain
Restaurant, 13,000 yen.
November 9th, Hokkaido Crab
Buffet Tour, 75,000 yen.
Just from what we know about, in six months,
you've spent over one million
yen for Shiori-san.
Considering that, the sum isn't
impossible for you to pay.
To this day, I haven't had any client
whose research was more thorough...
I almost wish she'd
come work at my office.
In contrast, to this day...
I haven't met anyone come up with a
more stupid scheme to
lessen the compensation.
Of all the men I have ever met...
you are a "dumb man"
of the highest order.
Sorry about that.
As to the rest, talk it
over at your leisure.
Please.
My husband consented.
He said he'll pay ten million yen
in a five-year payment plan.
I'm glad.
Usually when it goes to court,
the court generally agrees
on one to two million.
What?
In order for you to have gotten
the high compensation,
the agreement phase was critical.
I see.
What have you got planned for yourself?
My current apartment is costly,
so I'm going to find
another place to rent.
Hakamada-sensei.
You have been truly good to me.
It's nothing.
Goodbye.
Kanae-san's a different person
from when she first walked in.
But tougher battles are yet
to be fought. Right, Sensei?
Oh.
The bread is baked.
Hakamada Law Office
Hello.
Kanae-san.
Are you in trouble again?
No.
I have a different request today.
A different request?
Would you let me work here?
What?
My manga is about to get syndicated.
Please take a look.
This is it.
This main character looks like...
You will pay
the compensation!
It's Hakamada-sensei.
It looks like him.
Especially the goofy look.
He's an attorney specializing
in divorce compensation.
I thought if I worked here,
I'd always have material...
Well, you might find material,
but lawyers must keep
client confidentiality.
Of course, I'll
fictionalize those things.
You did say, Sensei,
that you would want me
to work at your office.
That was a figure of speech...
I approve.
You're hired.
Yay!
Toyama-san, you're just the landlord.
How many months' rent
do you think you owe me?
She can advertise your firm
in that manga, don't you see?
I understand.
Under one condition.
What is it?
This character...
can't you make him look more handsome?
Next episode...
Double adultery!
I can't forgive my husband.
Husband's double adultery!
Compensation can be collected
from the mistress, too.
Collect compensation from the mistress!
I was forced to see him.
And he raped me!
Look forward to the hearing.
The court has decided...
This drama is a work of fiction.