Watch your step.
Are you okay?
Take it slow, take it slow.
Hakamada Law Office
I won chocolate at pachinko. Want some?
Sure.
I want some, too.
Say, Kanae-chan, wanna go
get a drink together?
Assistant of Hakamada
Nonomura Kanae
It's only four o'clock.
I'm still working.
Temp
Shinozuka Rina
I don't think anyone
will show up this late.
Maybe we should invite Sensei, too.
He doesn't drink, though.
He'd be no fun at all if he came along.
I wonder what he does for fun.
Making bread, for sure.
He once said to me, completely serious,
Attorney
Hakamada Yukio
"Flour is my lover."
His relationship with his lover
isn't making any progress.
Office landlord
Toyama Yoshie
I wonder why Sensei never got married?
After all, he's a lawyer,
he's tall, and his looks...
Well, they aren't too bad.
You should marry him, then, Kanae-chan.
What?
Impossible, impossible.
No way, no way!
No way!
What's impossible?
What? Oh, nothing.
Excuse me.
Are you here for legal counseling?
This episode's client
Suwa Natsuki
I don't have an appointment.
Is that okay?
Yes!
No problem at all!
Sensei's schedule has been
empty for the past three days.
Too much information.
Please, this way.
Sensei, we have a client.
Yes.
Sensei, get tea!
Please.
Thank you very much.
Please tell me about
why you're here today.
My father...
is being deceived.
And how is that?
My mother passed away
about three years ago.
My father remarried a year
after that, to Chika-san.
I am financially independent.
Who my father marries doesn't affect me...
But...
Chika-san is younger than me.
What are their ages?
Chika-san is 27, my father is 72.
So she's 45 years his junior.
I'm jealous.
I want to be with a younger man, too.
Don't butt in, you two!
However, I suspect Chika-san
married my father for his money.
Why do you suspect that?
Chika-san buys brand-name
goods almost daily.
She goes on weekend
trips with her friends,
leaving my father behind.
Of course my father pays for them.
It's been approximately two years
since they were married...
But I believe he's spent at least
30 million yen on her in that time.
30 million...
Your father must be rich.
He's retired now,
but he ran his own
civil engineering firm.
I see.
So in other words, Natsuki-san,
you want your father to get a divorce.
No.
She's already begun
the divorce process.
The wife?
She is suing for five million
yen in compensation.
Five million?
On what grounds?
She insists my father
is cheating on her.
She has evidence, as well.
Caught red-handed.
Occasionally, there are old men
in their seventies who are still feisty.
But, don't worry.
Despite his looks,
Sensei's a specialist when it
comes to compensation lawsuitsー
I am sorry to say,
but I must refuse this case.
Why is that?
That man is the most
disreputable man in the world.
You know him, Sensei?
Yes.
My father, Suwa Kozo,
is also Hakamada-sensei's father.
What?!
Divorce Chaser
~Let's Turn Your Tears into Money~
Divorce Chaser Episode 6
Hakamada's Shocking Past Revealed!
If Natsuki-san's father is
Hakamada-sensei's father...
I am Sensei's younger half-sister.
You don't look like him at all.
My father divorced his
mother thirty years ago.
I know I shouldn't force
him into a case such as this.
But, I've discussed this
case with other lawyers,
and they all said it would be difficult
to avoid the lawsuit due to the evidence.
While I was searching for a lawyer,
I came across Hakamada-sensei,
a specialist in divorce issues.
Then, I found out he's is the son
of my father and his former wife.
So I thought he would be the only
one suitable to take this case.
Please, Sensei.
Please protect our father.
So he turned his sister down?
Yes, Sensei was quite firm about it.
Freelance Investigator
Umemoto Kurumi
He must have a grudge
against his father.
We've got trouble!
What's the matter?
Sensei's bread is delicious.
That's not possible!
You're right. It's good.
Not good...
You think so?
It turned out quite well
compared to his usual.
That's not what I mean.
If Sensei's bread is good,
it means he's very distressed.
You think so?
When the water pipes burst
and flooded his home,
he got quite distressed.
The bread he made during that
time was really delicious.
That must be what it takes.
I won't have any work to do if
Sensei stays in this condition.
I'm going home.
It's too bad you won't accept the case.
However, Father did want to see you.
I have no intention of seeing him.
Please tell him I said that.
What?
He left me and my mother.
I understand.
Goodbye.
Who do you think you're
feeling up, you perv?!
What happened?
This geezer tried to cop a feel!
You've got it all wrong.
I was brushing the dust off your butt.
The feisty old man...
Kurumi-san, that's him!
This is who?
That's Hakamada-sensei's father.
Huh?
What's going on?
What are you doing here?!
Hey, Yukio. Long time no see.
I have turned down your daughter's case.
Hakamada's father
Suwa Kozo
Never mind that.
I came to see you today.
I told her I didn't want to see you.
Oh, don't say that.
Let's toast to our reunion.
I don't drink.
You, too, huh?
You can make an exception today.
Right? Miss, bring
us a couple glasses.
Yes.
Don't order around my employees!
Look at you, running
this outstanding office.
Yeah.
I never offered you a seat.
A man is the master of his
own castle, as they say.
After I quit being a contractor
and started my civil engineering firm,
I sure had a lot of hardship.
I don't care about your war stories.
By the way, which one of
these are you diddling?
What?
Look at all these young women.
You must be diddling
at least one of them.
I am not like you.
Want me to guess which one?
This isn't a quiz show!
If you're anything like me,
you go for the good looks.
You.
Huh?
You're a bit large.
Can you move out of the way?
There. She's the one.
What? No, I'm not.
It's not you?
Too bad.
Are you single?
Yes, you could say that.
How about we go on a date?
No...
I'll be a free man soon.
No, that's a little...
That's enough!
Don't you have more pressing concerns?
You're being sued for compensation
for adultery, aren't you?
Natuski's the one raising
all the fuss, that's all.
I'm going to give Chika what she wants.
What?
I've got no excuses.
Besides, I'm a man,
I don't go chasing after
women that run from me.
Instead, I wish her nothing but happiness.
Her happiness?
Where do you get off saying that?
Have you forgotten what
you did to my mother?
That was thirty years ago, though.
Enjoy.
Anyway, let's make a toast.
I'll have a drink.
Yoshie-san, when did you get there?
I smelled fine wine.
By the way, I'm the landlord
here, Toyama Yoshie.
You're no ordinary woman.
You're brimming with hidden eroticism.
You know me well, daddy-o.
Care to try me out?
Sounds good.
Get out of here.
I have nothing to talk to you about.
We haven't seen each other for thirty years.
There must be tons of
stuff to talk about.
You neglected us for thirty years.
It's too late to play the father role.
You and I are complete strangers.
You're making this hard.
Get out.
Huh?
Now!
But the wine... I brought wine...
Get out. Get out of here now!
Get out, now!
What the hell?
Hakamada-sensei, can I
take this wine home?
Do as you please.
Sensei seriously hates his father.
Hakamada-sensei had a rough childhood.
That father of his found
another woman at work,
left home, and never came back.
I heard he never paid for compensation
or for child support.
So that's how it was...
His mother raised him all by herself
and saved enough to send him to college.
She passed away soon
right after he enrolled.
I don't blame him for holding a grudge.
Yoshie-san.
Could it have been it his parents'
divorce that influenced Sensei
to become a divorce lawyer?
Well...
Excuse me.
Oh, Natsuki-san.
Did my father come here?
He was just here.
Sensei kicked him out.
I see.
Hakamada Law Office
I've never seen Sensei so angry.
My father is prideful and awkward.
He must've said
inappropriate things, as usual.
I think his real intention was
to apologize to Hakamada-sensei.
Apologize?
Contrary to how he behaves,
he's contrite.
He regrets being a deadbeat
father to Hakamada-sensei.
I was hoping they could overcome
the bad blood between them.
But, it looks like that's
not going to happen...
Goodbye.
Natsuki-san, please wait.
Yes?
I have an idea.
Excuse me.
Hey, Yukio.
You again?
I told you I am refusing to take the case.
We're not here to see you.
I was waiting for you.
What?
I invited them to use this room
for divorce consultation.
Why must they do that here?
They are willing to pay
for their time here.
Please, this way.
I am Suwa Chika-san's legal
representative, Tsujimura.
Attorney
Tsujimura
Kozo's wife
Suwa Chika
I am Suwa Kozo's daughter, Natsuki.
And who is your legal representative?
We don't have one.
I had assumed Hakamada-sensei
would be your legal representative.
I will sit in on behalf of my
father for today's consultation.
You'll be saving money,
because hiring a lawyer for
this case would be futile.
Whatever, hurry up and start.
Your father's consultation has begun.
I don't have a father.
But...
Was this your idea, Kanae-san?
What?
That they hold the
consultation at this office.
So I would overhear their conversation,
and jump in to the rescue?
Well...
I don't fall for cheap tricks.
As I've already informed Kozo-san,
five million yen will be billed for compensation,
in addition to the property distribution.
Sounds fine.
We will not consent to those terms.
How is that?
Chika-san, you married my father
for his wealth, didn't you?
What?
What are you saying, Natsuki?
We have no money to give someone who
has already squandered his fortune.
You have no right to say that.
I have been a devoted wife.
What is so devoted about you?
I was told you constantly asked
for gifts, without occasion.
That's all right. I wanted
to give her those gifts.
They're beyond just gifts!
Two foreign cars,
co-ownership of a resort mansion,
and you took him to
that resort only once.
Who were you going there with, anyway?
Maybe you were the one
who was cheating?
You're just making that up!
Please don't bring up baseless claims.
And after he married you,
my father's health waned.
Were you taking good care of him?
Of course.
This is Chika-san's blog.
Chika's Blog:
Tonight's Loving Wife Dinner
You will see here a testament
to Chika-san's love of Kozo-san.
These are dishes, handmade by
her for him, every night.
You're a woman, you should
know how much work that is.
Say what you will.
I loved Kozo-san.
But Kozo-san betrayed me.
You're concerned, aren't you?
No.
I dropped my ballpoint pen.
It's in your front pocket.
There it is.
Be that as it may, we will not concede.
You want to battle it
out in court, then?
In court?
You can go to trial, but the
results will be the same.
We have solid evidence of
his illicit activities.
Those are...
I admit, I went to a hotel with her.
Father, stay out of this.
But, Chika, I'm telling you the truth.
I only did her once.
It's not a matter of
how many times, is it?
He's making a plain admission of guilt.
Please stamp and sign this.
Divorce Consultation Form
All right—
Don't.
Give us some time to think about it.
We'll give you one week, then.
The next time will be
our final consultation.
Understood.
Hakamada
Law Office
Was Hakamada-sensei listening?
He seemed quite concerned.
Forget about it. I don't
need that stubborn fool.
Father.
Bye, now.
They're gone now.
You could've at least seen them out.
I have no relationship with them.
And please, don't rent our office space
without asking me first.
What does it matter?
You don't have to take
them on as a client...
But you could've at least listened,
and given them advice.
Advice?
Then, there's one
thing I've learned.
What's that?
He is being deceived.
What?
Assuming he was telling the truth,
he said he was with his illicit
partner for one time only.
Yes.
Don't you think it's strange
that she could capture
an unexpected one-time
event like that on film?
That's true...
Do you think Chika-san and
her lawyer are scheming?
That is possible.
If you know that,
you could help your father!
It is difficult to prove
there was no illicit affair,
especially since he was photographed
coming out of the hotel.
I know you can do it, Sensei.
Please protect your father.
I have no reason to protect him.
He has been womanizing all his life.
My mother and I fell victim to it.
He should get what's coming to him.
But...
Also, he's willing to pay compensation.
The matter is out of my hands.
I understand.
I'll do it, then.
Do what?
I'm going to find proof that
Chika-san's story is a fabrication.
I'm going to ask Kurumi-san
to help me. Is that okay?
I don't mind, but...
I cannot have you neglect office duties.
There's nothing to do
at this office, anyway.
Um, Sensei...
Yes.
Your father forgot something.
He is not my father.
What should I do with it?
Shinozuka-san,
I'm sorry to trouble you,
but could you deliver it to him?
No, I won't.
He's your father, Sensei.
You should deliver it to him.
There's prescription
medicine in this, too.
You should hurry. He might need it.
Prescription Medicine
Mr. Suwa Kozo
Are you all right?!
Are you all right?
Ambulance.
Someone call an ambulance!
I am sorry.
That's unusual. You've never
requested a deadline extension before.
I'm very sorry.
I'm having writer's block.
Editor at Tokiwa Publishing
Tabata Misato
You can't get material
from the law office?
There's definitely material,
but the problem is that
Sensei is refusing to take on a client.
In that case, there is no problem.
What?
I can feel it.
Cafe waitress:
Mizutani Sara
Hello?
I found the woman in the photo.
Can you come right away?
All right.
I'm sorry. I have to go.
Huh?
Amazing! I feel it so strongly!
Um... she left already.
What?
Yukio.
Was it you that rescued me?
I didn't do it for you, particularly.
I would help anyone who
had collapsed on the street.
How bothersome.
I even had to hear what
the doctor had to say.
Don't tell Chika and Natsuki that I'm sick.
What's the point of being
prideful at a time like this?
You're a complete stranger, aren't you?
What do you care?
How is our father?
He had a minor seizure.
The doctor said he can be
discharged quickly, after he rests.
I see.
Regardless, he should stop drinking.
What?
Father doesn't drink.
He's never been able to drink.
What?
If he drinks, he falls
asleep right away.
He only drinks when he's really happy.
Let's make a toast to our reunion.
I don't drink.
You, too, huh?
I have seen him drunk only three times.
The first time was when I got
first place in a piano competition.
The second time was when his
firm landed a huge contract
for building a train station.
The third time was when
you passed your bar exam.
What?
Though he doesn't show it,
he's always thinks about you,
Hakamada-sensei.
After he found out your
were becoming a lawyer,
he would check the roster of
successful bar examinees, every year.
I once heard him quarreling with
my mother about you, Sensei.
Because he had spent their
money without telling her...
I think he anonymously paid
your college entrance fee.
That man wouldn't do a thing like that.
It's a fact.
I was at that acutely sensitive age...
My father would be concerned
about a child other than me...
Though I had never met that child,
there was a time I was jealous of him.
Oh, and Sensei. I know you believe
my father is a womanizer...
But, I don't think he's ever
cheated on my mother.
Now that, I can't believe.
He was probably just hiding it from you.
Do you think my father
is capable of hiding anything?
Hakamada
Though he doesn't show it,
he's always thinks about you,
Hakamada-sensei.
But, I know you can do it, Sensei.
Please protect your father.
I see you're immersed in your thoughts.
Yoshie-san...
When did you come in?
I've been here the whole time.
You've finally decided to help your father.
Huh?
Because the only time you listen
to music and knead dough
is when you're thinking
about your client.
I was thinking of a different client.
Oh? Was there another client in here?
Kanae-chan has been wondering...
if you became a divorce lawyer
because of your father.
I wouldn't dismiss that as incorrect.
If only I had knowledge of the law,
I could've sued my father
for compensation and child support
after he divorced my mother.
But, you initially went into
corporate law, didn't you?
How did you know that?
I love gossip, that's how.
You've forgiven your father, haven't you?
Oh, please. You're so lecherous.
I'll have to punish you next time.
Are you Murakami Kanna-san?
Huh?
Who are you people?
I'm a freelance investigator,
Umemoto Kurumi.
I'm her assistant, Nonomura Kanae.
Is that you in this photograph?
Kozo's illicit partner
Murakami Kanna
Can you explain to us why you went
to this hotel with Suwa Kozo-san?
I've already explained that to an attorney.
His name is Tsujimura-san.
We need to confirm
some facts on our end.
Please.
I was at a restaurant, and
Kozo-san started talking to me.
He bought me drinks,
then lured me to a hotel.
Are you sure it was Kozo-san
who started talking to you?
Yeah.
And was he the one who
lured you to the hotel?
It was Kozo-san.
Why are you asking?
You're personal acquaintances
with Suwa Chika-san, aren't you?
What?
No. I don't know her.
Well, that's strange.
Weren't the two of you in the same
escort service until two years ago?
I don't know her.
Hm...
Maybe she asked you...
...to lure Kozo-san to the hotel?
What are you people after?
We just want to know the truth.
Everything I said is true.
Now, excuse me.
You're not unfamiliar with
cases like this, are you?
You have a history of going
to hotels with married men.
Every time, they are photographed,
and get sued for compensation
within a few months.
That's more than just coincidence.
If you get me started,
I'll investigate all of your past deeds.
Once I've latched onto my target,
I never let go.
Because I am...
Freelance Investigator Umemoto Kurumi!
Will you speak the truth
at the divorce consultation?
I will.
Hakamada Law Office
I am attending Kozo-san's
final divorce consultation.
It starts at 2:00, at their lawyer's office.
Won't you come with me, Sensei?
No, I have to go somewhere.
And where would that be?
There's a kind of bread I'm interested in.
Why must you be so obstinate?
Thank you for waiting.
Today's consultation will
go well, I assure you.
We've gathered powerful evidence.
Thank you for all of your help.
Isn't Yukio coming?
He has other business to attend.
I see.
Would you care for more bread?
This is good bread.
It's made with domestic wheat flour.
Probably from Hokkaido.
Am I right?
No. It's from Canada.
I see.
Oh, one more thing.
I have a question.
First Conference Room
Have you reached a decision?
Yes.
We cannot consent to
this divorce agreement.
Don't be ridiculous.
Kozo-san is clearly guilty
of illicit activity.
Concerning that issue...
Chika-san.
You know Murakami
Kanna-san here, don't you?
What?
You were both in the same
escort service, weren't you?
Did you ask your friend Kanna-san
lure my father to the hotel?
To have the upper hand in
the divorce consultation?
I've done no such thing.
Can you prove it?
We have proof.
Then, show us.
For that...
please wait a little while.
Kanna-san is late.
This is bad...
She's not picking up.
When are you producing
this so-called proof?
First Conference Room
Please wait just a little longer.
Perhaps you are waiting
for Murakami Kanna-san?
What?
If it's her you're waiting for,
she won't be coming.
How did you...
Kanna-san contacted me the other day.
She was very distressed.
She said an investigator
you hired blackmailed her,
and was forcing her
to fabricate evidence.
That's ridiculous.
I understand not wanting
to pay compensation.
But your actions are tantamount
to the crime of blackmail.
She's not answering.
Let's forget about Kanna-sa.
We need another course of action.
It's too late for another
course of action.
Chika-san is completely innocent
with respect to this divorce.
Based on various information sources,
it is clear that Chika-san has
been a devoted wife to Kozo-san.
Please seal and sign
the consultation form.
You did what you could, Natsuki.
Father.
I'm going to go apologize
to Natsuki-san.
Kanae-san.
Please, don't do that just yet.
Hakamada-sensei?
Yukio, what are you doing here?
Who are you?
Sorry for not introducing
myself the other day.
I'm Hakamada, attorney at law.
I am his assistant, Nonomura Kanae.
You are Suwa Kozo-san's
legal representative?
No.
I'm just passing through.
This is a consultation.
Please leave if you
have no business here.
No, he does have business here.
He's the witness who I invited here.
Yes.
He has important information
pertaining to this consultation.
I have a question for Chika-san.
Me?
Did you really love this man?
Of course I loved him.
That's why I married him.
What's so good about this tired,
lecherous geezer?
What?
Huh?
He's prideful, he's selfish,
and, oh yes, his feet
smell utterly horrible.
Why would you want to
marry a man like that?
What's that supposed to mean?
When we first met, Kozo-san
was very kind to me.
"Kind"?
You mean he bought you a lot of gifts.
What's wrong with that?
He's vastly knowledgable,
and told me lots of interesting things.
Vastly knowledgable?
His brain is stuck at
middle-school level.
Sensei, what are you saying?
Did you come here to
talk trash about me?
Yes. Because you have
been nothing but trouble.
How long must you bear a grudge?
You've been a wuss ever
since your were a kid.
Take your quarrel somewhere else.
This is a consultation.
Pardon me.
In that case, one last thing.
Since you love him so much,
you know about his sickness, correct?
Sickness?
I told you not to tell her.
Since you seem to not know,
let me explain it to you.
He has had diabetes for two years.
But, you cared nothing about that,
and supposedly made him
plenty of rich meals.
I-It's because I didn't know.
Of course she didn't. I didn't tell her.
Understood.
Let's say you didn't
know he was diabetic.
But, despite being a couple,
you took no notice of
an obvious symptom.
Hey, don't you dare.
Suwa Kozo-san has erectile
dysfunction from his diabetes.
What?
Well, not really, you see...
While I was talking to his doctor,
I glanced at his medical records.
He hasn't gotten hard
for two years.
Idiot!
Don't be so explicit!
Maybe that's divine punishment for all
the womanizing in your younger days.
Shut up, Yukio, or I'll kick your ass right here!
Father! Please be quiet.
Now, would a man like that
lure a woman to a hotel?
He's a prideful man.
He doesn't want others
to learn of his weaknesses.
Do you think a man like that
would take a woman to a hotel,
and make himself
vulnerable to ridicule?
And by the way,
I spoke to the waiter at the
restaurant where he met Kanna-san.
He said he saw Kanna-san put
alcohol in his soft drink.
As you might know,
this man does not drink.
He immediately became inebriated,
which made it easier
to lure him to the hotel,
for the purpose of taking evidence photos.
Gold digging and lovelessness aside,
consider the action of framing
your innocent husband,
of scheming to steal
his fund for old age.
I know I'm overstepping my
bounds, but let me ask you...
What is it about you that
is a "loving wife"?
So, Hakamada-sensei came
to the rescue after all.
In spite of being such a sourpuss.
Thankfully, Chika-san has retracted
the compensation lawsuit,
and there will be no property
distribution, either.
I see. I'm glad.
Hello.
Thank you for everything
you've done for us.
Is Yukio here?
Sensei is baking bread in the back.
Wait, Father...
What you did was uncalled for.
What might that be?
I told you not to tell
anyone about "that."
I'd rather pay five million yen
than have it revealed.
Father.
Stop being so prideful.
Where would you get that kind of money?
I hear you're scraping the
bottom of your savings.
How do you plan to support
yourself in your old age?
And also...
it was what you did
that was uncalled for.
I was going to pay for my
own college entrance fee.
What are you talking about?
You spend money out of pride,
so now you're broke. Isn't that so?
Let me just say this...
Thank you for having done that for me.
I don't know what you're talking about.
But, hey, how about this today?
Like I said many times,
I cannot drink.
Just this one time, come on.
Shouldn't you listen to your doctor?
So, let's just stick to one glass each.
Yukio.
Thanks.
Huh?
You really helped me out.
And...
I am truly sorry.
I don't know what you're talking about.
They fell asleep so fast.
It hasn't even been ten minutes.
Father, you shouldn't be sleeping here.
Look at them side-by-side.
They look so alike.
They're father-son after all.
Horrible.
Water, water.
I'm so glad.
About what?
Sensei's been freed from
his decades-long grudge.
His parents' divorce must have driven
Sensei to become a divorce lawyer.
No, that wasn't it.
What's the reason, then?
I wonder...
You should ask him about that.
Thanks for the wine.
Next episode
I can't find a marriage partner
because of the marriage counselor!
Get compensation from a crooked marriage counselor!
A dishonest marriage counselor
like that should get punished!
Umemoto Kurumi's Shocking Past Revealed!
I can't forgive people
who look down on others.
This drama is a work of fiction
Win or lose, that's my responsibility.