Well... it's about another
compensation lawsuit.
The one caught cheating
was my wife, Shiori.
I am Honjo Yayoi-san's legal
representative, Karasuma Keiko.
We are suing for five million yen.
Karasuma Keiko is
Hakamada-sensei's ex-lover.
As I have already explained,
he doesn't stand a chance.
So for this particular case, I think
you should consult a different lawyer.
Because he doesn't stand a chance?
Those aren't Hakamada-sensei's words.
So, I'm going to help that client,
the way that you would do it.
I know I'm overstepping
my bounds, but...
you should be prepared to lose.
Kanae.
What's up?
Hakamada's assistant
Nonomura Kanae
We should fight this.
Kanae's ex-husband
Kurasawa Yoshihito
We can't take this lying down.
Did Hakamada-sensei change his mind?
No.
But, we don't have to rely on him.
There are other ways.
What other ways?
There is one indispensable person
you must have on your side...
First of all,
I need you to convince someone
to be on your side.
My side?
Your wife, Shiori-san.
I think that's going to be difficult.
Huh?
Like I said,
we've been living
separately for a while.
She hasn't answered my calls
since we last saw each other.
I see.
Kanae.
Kanae!
What are you looking for?
Evidence of adultery.
What?
We gather evidence that will
give us the advantage.
I'm looking for evidence that
will give us the advantage,
of when the affair started...
the days and times of the trysts,
and if possible...
maybe even the number of times he's
had physical relationships with her.
But how?
For example, check
Shiori-san's car's GPS history.
Shiori doesn't even have
a driver's license.
Then...
her cell phone and PC email history..
She took her cell and laptop with her.
Oh, I see...
Is evidence like that going
to help us at this stage?
I don't know...
but if we can get details about the affair,
we might find a way to counterattack.
Can I look in Shiori-san's room?
Sure.
You're very thorough.
You can get lots of information
from a single dinner receipt.
Is this the kind of thing you did
when you and I got divorced?
Sort of, yeah.
You've become strong, Kanae.
You think so?
Yoshihito's wife
Kurasawa Shiori
What's going on here?
Why are you snooping in my room?
Shiori...
I thought it was weird
that you went to that
Hakamada lawyer.
It's because you wanted
to see each other, isn't it?
I've had it.
Shiori. Shiori.
You've got it wrong.
Kanae was looking
for evidence for our case.
Evidence?
And what good will that do?
We need whatever information we can get.
Otherwise you'll have to pay
the amount they've set.
I don't care any more how
much the compensation fee is.
What?
You should pay the whole thing.
It's all your fault, after all.
You said you'd make all my wishes
come true if I married you.
You said you were going
to make me happy!
But you had to pay that
woman's compensation...
and because of that,
my life is a disappointment!
If I'd known this would happen...
I never would've married you!
You're completely full of it.
Whenever you open your mouth,
you only talk about money!
You were there with Yoshihito-san
when you got slapped with the lawsuit!
You saw the anguish on
his face, didn't you?!
Didn't you feel anything for him at all?
Shouldn't you be aware of the
serious consequences of adultery?!
The first thing an adulterer
must do is apologize.
And the second thing they
The third is more of the same.
You have to keep on apologizing.
However, as far as I know,
you haven't asked Yoshihito-san's
forgiveness even once!
You don't even try to learn
from your mistakes.
Of all the men I have ever met...
you are a "dumb man"
of the highest order.
Of all the people I've met...
you are a dumb woman
of the highest order,
the reigning idiot queen
of all other dumb women.
But, even someone like you
is still precious to him.
Yoshihito-san said he doesn't
want to divorce you.
Huh?
He said he wants to start over,
and have a good marriage.
What matters to you the most?
Give it some serious thought.
For crying out loud...
Why must his ex-wife do
all the talking for him?
The first time he seduced me...
was at a place called Le Breeze
in west Azabu.
What?
I'll tell you everything
about the affair.
If that will help our marriage.
Shiori.
I am so sorry.
I am sorry.
Fujisawa Yoshihito
Hello?
It's Yoshihito.
Sorry I sort of lost it back there.
It's fine.
Thanks to you, Shiori told me
about the man she was seeing.
Huh?
I'm relaying the information to you now.
Can you write it down?
Sure.
The first time they met was at Le Breeze
(French restaurant) in west Azabu.
October: She doesn't remember the day of
the week, but Takashi-san asked her out again.
For about six months afterward, they met
3 or 4 times a month at various times, and
sometimes more often, even once a week,
in Daikanyama, Shibuya, etc.
Attorney
Hakamada Yukio
Good work on the investigation.
I can launch a counterattack
with this material.
I need some more details.
Will you please call
Yoshihito-san and Shiori-san here?
Yes!
Divorce Chaser
~Let's Turn Your Tears into Money~
Divorce Chaser Final Episode
The Battle of Fate Between Attorneys! The Final Outcome!
I'm being sued for compensation?
Yes.
He must've found some kind of evidence.
Sieg Law Office attorney
Karasuma Keiko
Any idea what it could be?
No...
Shiori's illicit partner
Honjo Takashi
I always followed your instructions
carefully whenever I saw Shiori.
There should be no problem, then.
Well, it's not anything
I wasn't expecting.
Takashi's wife
Honjo Yayoi
When we first met each other,
Takashi-san said,
"My marriage is over...
Our divorce is a matter of time."
Then, after we started seeing each other,
"I reconciled with my wife recently...
We might not divorce, but do
you still want to see me?"
He asked me that.
I see.
There's a high possibility Karasuma
was advising him at that juncture.
Advising him?
This is only a conjecture,
but Honjo Takashi-san's
relationship to his wife
was already in ruins from
before he met Shiori-san.
They may have already
been discussing divorce.
Takashi-san would have then consulted
his company's advising attorney, Karasuma.
She likely advised him to use
his affair with you, Shiori-san,
to sue you for compensation.
So that's why he said he
reconciled with his wife...
You better not have acted
conspicuously. Did you?
I've been living my life according
to Karasuma-san's instructions.
Something bothering you?
No.
You're getting a divorce
like you wanted.
But if I can't get a
large compensation...
you're the one who'll get
the brunt of the divorce.
But that's not...
I know that.
By the way, how did you typically
keep in contact with Takashi-san?
I mostly just texted him,
but he used the phone most of the time.
That's to avoid a paper trail.
He must've been following
instructions from Karasuma.
That's why the texts looked like
Shiori-san was initiating the trysts.
Take me out for lunch today
Understood.
By the way,
do you have any photos
of you and Takashi-san?
Oh, no...
Takashi-san said
he didn't like pictures.
Also by her instructions, probably.
Preparing for the eventual hearing,
by ensuring there was no
disadvantageous evidence.
In other words, he was using
Shiori to get compensation?
Yes.
Most likely.
So, that's how it was...
Of course,
Shiori-san, you need to
recant your illicit activities.
But, Takashi-san is
not at all repentant.
Instead, he is trying to transfer
the compensation fee that he
should be paying to Shiori-san.
Unforgivable.
And Karasuma cannot
be forgiven either...
for having given such
instructions as a lawyer.
What are you going to do?
The most important thing is
to get evidence that the Honjo
marriage was already finished.
If we can get that,
they cannot sue Shiori-san
for compensation.
And in turn, it makes it possible
for us to sue them instead.
It sounds like it's my turn now.
Freelance Investigator
Umemoto Kurumi
Kurumi-san.
Looks like Sensei came
back to his senses.
Which means he'd want me
to do some digging.
Please do.
I will personally pay for your services.
Are you sure?
Yes.
And this time, I will lend
a hand in the investigation.
You will, Sensei?
If the current compensation lawsuit
is a planned conspiracy...
it will be difficult to find evidence.
Knowing how Karasuma works,
there's a high probability that evidence
is being thoroughly covered up.
We must go into this battle together.
Don't cramp my style, though.
The Resurrection
of Marilyn
Iron Spy Woman
Marilyn
Would you like to borrow this?
No need.
I have already studied it.
Iron Spy Woman Marilyn,
season 29, episode 6.
Huh?
She who controls information
controls the world.
That's how it is.
Why didn't you let me say it?!
Sensei is fired up.
Here you go.
One fried chicken lunch,
and one seaweed lunch!
Thanks.
Sure.
Oh, by the way...
Are both of you employed
at Honjo Industries?
You know where we work?
Of course I do.
It's rumored the men who
work there are gorgeous.
Seriously?
And that president Honjo.
He's got that mature, awesome look.
Might he be single?
The president's married.
He's a notorious womanizer, though.
I wouldn't recommend him.
Oh? Like how?
For example—
Hey.
You're talking about
our president, here...
Whoops, sorry.
See you later.
Hey! Wait a minute!
I hear they're great!
Excuse me, one fried chicken lunch, please!
Yes, here you go!
No, I don't have that.
Honjo
Did you hear?
The Honjos are getting a divorce.
I heard about that.
I knew it was coming, though.
What? They're getting a divorce?
Who are you?
We're newlyweds looking
for a place to live.
Their home was up for sale,
so we went to check it out.
Well, how about that.
But they're moving out
because of a divorce.
Sounds like bad luck,
doesn't it, honey?
My wife is fussy
about things like that.
Do you know the reason why
they're getting a divorce?
I heard it's because the
husband cheated on her.
What?! He was cheating?!
Cheating? Recently?
That man? He's been
playing around for ages.
Shh, Yamamoto-san, we
can't talk about that...
Oh, yeah. That's right.
I'm sorry.
They sure are thorough.
They've even shut up
the local housewives.
That's typical for Karasuma.
Kanae-san, please have a
discussion with Kurumi-san
and find another method
of investigating.
And what will you do?
I'm going to investigate
this area a bit more.
I have a hunch.
Understood.
And...
Is there a problem?
You can let go now.
Oh, that.
Well, I'm going that way.
What do you feel?
Where can I go get evidence that
this couple's marriage was over?
Cafe waitress
Mizutani Sara
I'm sorry.
I don't feel anything at all.
I... don't like being pressured.
I feel it.
What is it?
You are thinking,
"This gal is useless."
Bingo.
You're being watched?
Yes.
There was a tall man wearing glasses
in front of our house.
That probably was Hakamada,
our opposing attorney.
Is everything all right?
It's nothing to worry about.
As long as you have me as your lawyer,
the other party's lawyer is
strictly forbidden by law
from contacting you
without my presence.
If he broke that law,
he will disbarred by
the bar association.
You haven't done anything
conspicuous, have you?
I haven't left the house other
than to go grocery shopping...
I'm doing my usual household chores.
Fine, then.
Um...
How much longer must
I continue like this?
Just a little while longer.
"A little longer" meaning when?
Stop complaining.
All you have to do is obey
our instructions. That's all.
I understand.
Don't worry about her.
She can't go against my instructions.
However,
I heard someone was asking
my employees about me.
It would affect their work performance
if rumors about me were to spread.
Is there anything you
could do about that?
There are ways...
to shut them up.
Sensei.
Here's a tentative investigation
report from Kurumi-san.
They're definitely being thorough.
Supposedly, there are rumors
that Takashi-san is a womanizer,
and that he's cheated with women
other than Shiori-san...
But there's no definitive evidence,
and no one will go into detail.
Yes,
they've being covering things up.
We won't give up.
Let's continue with our investigation.
Sorry to barge in unannounced.
Karasuma-san.
Can we help you?
Oh, don't make such a stern face.
I've come here to give
you some news.
Since we cannot get consent
for the compensation lawsuit,
we are filing an action,
and will take the matter to court.
Taking it to court?
Your client, Yoshihito-san,
has already filed a suit.
Most likely, the two
hearings will converge.
What do you mean, "converge"?
Converged hearing
Holding a hearing in a single trial concerning the demands of both the plaintiff and the defendant.
It means holding one trial to judge
several conflicting demands.
Simply put,
it's a court battle of
our compensation lawsuit
and their compensation lawsuit,
all at the same time.
I see.
Can you handle it?
Since we're taking it to court,
you won't have a leg to stand on
if you have no evidence to present.
You don't need to worry about that.
Glad to hear it.
We'll see you in court, then.
Go easy on me, Hakamada-sensei.
She's so arrogant...
It seems she's quite confident.
But you have a secret plan, right, Sensei?
Secret plan?
You said, "You don't need
to worry about that."
Oh...
I just said that because I was mad.
What?
So, you have nothing?
Yes...
For now, nothing.
Yes.
Hakamada-sensei, I found it.
What?
There's a bartender who says he saw
Takashi-san and Shiori-san on a date.
Can you come here now?
We'll be there right away.
Yeah...
No mistake, it was these two.
I myself took an
interest in her at first,
because she's my type.
Then, this man showed up.
I heard him say, "If you go out with me,
I'll take you to Tahiti,
the Maldives, anywhere."
He started coming onto her.
Thanks.
And how did the lady respond?
She seemed happy about it, I think.
But, she expressed worry that his wife
might find out if they went on a trip.
And what did the man say about that?
He said, "Even if she finds out,
there's no problem.
"Our marriage is finished.
It's only a matter of time
before we get divorced."
That sounds like...
Are you certain he said that?
Yeah. There's no mistake.
Would you be willing
to testify in court?
Sure...
I don't mind.
I think we scored, Sensei.
You can win at the hearing now, right?
Yes...
Court of Law
What happens when hearings converge?
This time around,
the first case will concern the compensation lawsuit
of Yoshihito-san against Takashi-san.
So, Yoshihito-san is the
plaintiff in the first case,
Kurasawa Yoshihito (represented by Hakamada) → first case plaintiff
Honjo Takashi (represented by  Karasuma) → first case defendant.
and Takashi-san is the defendant.
I see.
So, Yayoi-san's lawsuit against
Shiori-san is the second case.
Hojo Yayoi (represented by Karasuma) → second case plaintiff
Kurasawa Shiori (represented by Hakamada)  → second case defendant.
Yes.
Both sides admit to illicit activities.
So, in this case, the
crucial point of argument
is whether the Honjos' marriage
Main point of the hearing → Was the Honjos'
marriage already broken prior to the illicit affair?
was already torn apart
before the illicit affair.
Awesome, Kanae-san. You know your stuff.
Yes.
I did a lot of studying for this case.
Regarding the couple
you saw at the bar...
They were Shiori-san there,
and Takashi-san there, is this correct?
Yes, there's no mistake.
Please share with the court what
you heard of their conversation.
The man seemed a little tipsy.
And he came on to the lady,
with offers to take her on trips.
And how did Shiori-san respond?
She said, "You have a wife,
won't you get in trouble?"
And how did Takashi-san respond?
He replied, "It doesn't
matter if she finds out.
Our marriage is over."
Anything else?
He said, "It's only a matter
of time before we're divorced."
From this testimony we can clearly see
that Takashi-san and Yayoi-san's
marriage was already broken.
And even if his words were
lies to seduce Shiori-san,
Shiori-san, who believed his words,
is not liable to pay for compensation.
That is all.
I have been to the bar
you work at, once.
It is a very nice place, isn't it?
Well, thank you.
By the way,
this is what it looks like inside.
As you can see,
they keep the lights extremely low,
in order to create ambience.
It is difficult to see
who is in front of you.
And yet, you claim
that despite this and the fact that
you've never met these people,
you still can identify their faces.
Well, I...
Objection.
The defense's statement is mere speculation—
No.
I have definitive proof that the witness
was unable to hear any couple's conversation.
What day and what month did Takashi-san
and Shiori-san meet at the bar?
It was October 17th.
I borrowed the shift schedule
from the bar's proprietor.
On October 17th,
Suho-san here was not at the bar.
Latter half of October
Heisei 26
Suho
Friday    Day Off
What?!
You're lying.
Couples with age differences
are not at all uncommon.
This means you saw another
couple on another day,
and got them mixed up.
Well, now that you mention it...
Hey, you.
Have some resolve!
Sensei.
One moment, please.
You saw photos of Takashi-san and Shiori-san
and claimed there was no mistake
they were who you saw.
But, like this lady says,
it's a dark bar, after all.
What?
Based on this testimony,
there is no evidence that Takashi-san
and Yayoi-san's marriage was broken.
That is all.
Damn, she got us good.
That witness was in cahoots with them.
In cahoots?
If we found strong evidence,
we wouldn't need to
investigate any further.
That's how they set it up, and used him
to play the unreliable witness.
I can't believe I fell
into such an obvious trap.
Hakamada-sensei.
There's still time before
the next hearing.
May I continue the investigation?
Yes. Please do.
Sensei, where are you going?
I am going to investigate, as well.
I leave the rest to you.
Understood.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the delivery.
You are Honjo Yayoi-san?
You...
May I have a word with you?
I have nothing to say.
Please wait.
Please contact Karasuma-san instead.
Aren't you forbidden by law
from contacting me without permission?
Yes,
I'm prepared to be disbarred for this.
Regardless, I must
know your side of this.
Please, leave.
Court of Law
I feel pathetic...
I couldn't find a single
piece of evidence.
All we can do now is believe
in Hakamada-sensei.
Huh?
I know it'll turn out well.
The bread he baked yesterday
was absolutely awful.
What you see here are
photographs of the Honjo couple.
They are even known by their neighbors
to be an intimately loving couple.
You liar. Not a single
person said that.
They would take trips
overseas every six months.
They dined at restaurants
twice a month.
They have many rules between them
to support their sense of marital bliss.
Such a happy couple, and yet,
because of one woman, they were
torn apart six months ago...
That woman, Shiori-san, who sits there.
Not true.
Takashi-san was the one who initiated—
There is no question, clearly,
that Shiori-san aggressively seduced him.
Looking at their texts.
It is clear from these that
Shiori-san was the active initiator.
Shiori
Takashi-san r u free next week??
I want us to go to Yokohama next time <3 There's a super yummy pancake place there.
Take me out for lunch today
Yes.
Understood.
But those texts...
Yeah, that's not right!
Please, you must calm yourself.
This evidence tells the whole story.
Shiori-san tore apart the
happy Honjo marriage...
and stole the smile
off Yayoi-san's face.
It is only natural that she
should pay for compensation.
That woman really pisses me off.
It's all outright lies.
But, look...
That is all.
Hakamada-sensei.
Can anything be done?
Counselor.
What you have presented is
completely erroneous.
And on what do you base your assertion?
This was not the first time Takashi-san
engaged in an illicit affair.
He has had adulterous affairs
several times with other partners.
Please present the
basis for your assertions.
And every time he did,
he deeply hurt his wife
Yayoi-san's feelings.
Their marriage was already broken.
Your Honor,
the plaintiff is speaking
from sheer conjecture.
Counselor, please clarify
the basis for your assertions.
I have no basis.
However,
there is one witness who can expose
Takashi-san's past illicit activities.
What?
What witness?
Honjo Takashi-san's wife,
Honjo Yayoi-san.
Yayoi-san?
What's this guy babbling about?
I request to question Yayoi-san.
Question?
He has requested to question
Yayoi-san directly.
Counselor,
what is your opinion?
There is no need for that whatsoever.
It is necessary,
to prove that Yayoi-san's relationship to
her husband was already broken.
Are you hoping Yayoi-san would state
something that would be disadvantageous to her?
This is meaningless!
Meaningless or not,
it is Yayoi-san's decision to make.
Yayoi-san,
you do not have to agree to this.
This is their ploy.
I want to know your side.
If you let this opportunity pass by,
you will end up a mere bystander.
Can you live with ending up
as a mere bystander?!
This trial is important!
It will determine your future.
But, even from the very first conference,
I felt nothing of your true will.
If you win the trial,
you will get compensation from
Takashi-san's partner in adultery.
But is that going to heal your wounds?
Who is it that you want to
really sue for compensation?
Whose apology is it
that you really want?
Yayoi, don't breathe a word.
All you need to do is keep
quiet and do as I say.
Do you have to do as he says?
You are a victim of his
illicit activities.
I will testify.
It is as the lawyer said.
Our married life was
already broken.
Huh?
Hey, stop talking!
Yayoi-san.
We were already making steady
arrangements for a divorce.
This was not the first time
he had cheated on me.
That's enough!
Why won't you obey me?!
Don't think for a minute that
I'll just do everything you say!
This man has been seeing other women,
even from the beginning of our marriage.
And every time he was caught,
he would say,
"I won't ever do it again,"
and lie to appease me.
And this pattern repeated
over and over again.
And all those times, not once,
did he bow and apologize
for what he'd done.
Why must I obey a man like that?
Why must I pretend I had a happy marriage
with a man like that?!
I am withdrawing my lawsuit.
Yayoi-san.
The one that I truly hate...
is this man, here.
Are you certain you with
to withdraw the lawsuit?
Yes.
Kurasawa Shiori-san, do you
agree to this withdrawal?
Yes,
we agree.
This concludes Honjo Yayoi-san's compensation
lawsuit against Kurasawa Shiori-san.
The court's decision of compensation
lawsuit case of Kurasawa Yoshihito-san
versus Honjo Takashi-san will be
delivered April 10, 2015, at 1:15 pm.
Do you know what
you've done to yourself?
Now you won't get compensation,
and you did it to yourself.
Your life after divorce
is going to be a tough one.
No, that will not be the case.
Yayoi-san can sue for compensation...
from you, Takashi-san.
Cut the crap.
Why me?
You have an obligation
to pay restitution
for Yayoi-san's incurred psychological
trauma from your illicit activities.
And there is compensation
with respect to the divorce.
That's ridiculous. Are you joking?!
I will fight it.
I'm not paying you anything.
You can fight all you want,
but you don't stand a chance.
Isn't that so,
Karasuma-san?
Something's wrong here.
Hakamada-san.
Did you see Yayoi-san
before the hearing,
and plant ideas in her head?
Because if you did,
the bar association will disbar you.
No such thing happened.
I did this out of my own volition.
That's not possible.
You're not capable of
standing up for yourself—
If you must insist, then show me proof.
Proof is your specialty, isn't it?
Karasuma-san.
I am no longer your client.
Not once did you lend an ear
to what I had to say.
I cannot entrust my future
to such a person.
Goodbye.
All you thought about was winning,
and you neglected the
most important thing,
the will of your client.
And this is the result.
Well then, goodbye.
You must be quite
satisfied with yourself.
A splendid victory in court,
and you avenged the grudge
you held for ten years.
Please don't belittle me.
I did not fight in this hearing
for something like that.
Then, and even now,
there is only one thing
I want you to do.
Goodbye.
You couldn't tell from
the hearing today?
There's only one thing you can do
to someone you've hurt, isn't there?
To celebrate our victory,
I will whip up champagne bread.
Champagne bread?
I'll knead champagne into the dough.
It'd be better to have them separately.
You'll ruin two ingredients at once.
In that case, how about
sweet bean bread?
I'll knead sweet bean into the dough.
The sweet beans are supposed
to be in the middle!
Hakamada
Law Office
Because she has withdrawn the suit,
you no longer have to pay
compensation, Shiori-san.
The property seizures and wage
garnishments have also been withdrawn.
I am positive the court will approve
Yoshihito-san's lawsuit against Takashi-san.
This time, it will be
approximately one to two million.
On top of that,
since they unjustly threatened
with seizure and lawsuit,
Shiori-san can demand compensation
for attorney fees, and so on.
She can make all those demands?
I expect your wedding
will be a great one.
Hakamada-sensei.
Thank you for everything
you've done for us.
Thank you very much.
I pray that you two will never
have to come here again.
Yes.
Are you sure you want to decline
the weekly serial offer?
Yes.
I've already decided.
Big chances like that are
very rare, you know.
My prediction came
true, as I knew it would.
What prediction?
What?
You don't remember?
I feel it.
You will lose something big, very soon.
What?
You were talking about me?
Yes.
But, I don't feel like I've lost anything.
I am going to continue working
at the Hakamada Law Office,
and continue the monthly serial.
That is what I want to do now.
As your editor,
I promise you I'll make
your work a big hit!
Thank you for always supporting me.
I look forward to working with you.
Yes.
Oh, and...
I've always been thinking this, but...
You don't have any
mysterious powers, right?
Why would you say that?
May I have a look at this?
Please don't touch it!
It cost me 3,000 yen online!
Cheap!
This thing is totally suspicious.
It's not cheap.
Kanae-san, you turned down
the weekly serialization?
She did.
What a waste.
But finally, the manga is
coming out in a single volume!
Wow, amazing!
Living on royalties, what a dream.
What percentage do manga
illustrators get?
Please don't jump right to money talk.
But, I'm on a roll.
The protagonist's reason for becoming
a divorce lawyer is revealed!
The story is going to keep
getting better and better.
And why did he become a divorce lawyer?
Because of a past
relationship with a woman.
Because the protagonist is
modeled after Hakamada-sensei.
Huh?
But, that wasn't my reason why.
What?
It's not?
What? It's not?
Then, why?
The reason why I became
a divorce lawyer...
This drama is a work of fiction.
What?!