Well then, let's start with today's first request.
As a matter of fact, this time, we've received the same request from various people all over the country.
Isn't that right, Sawabe-san?
Something really unexpected happened.
So, in case you didn't know ... at TV Tokyo, in a show called "Why did you come to Japan?" ...
...they talked to a 19y/o German couple.
It turns out they were huge fans of Tantei Knight Scoop!
So they came all the way from Germany to see Knight Scoop!
Just to see Knight Scoop?
- Yes, just for that purpose!
So did they make it to a taping?
- Well, it was a spontaneous trip.
They came over without knowing anything about the application process, so when they arrived at the recording studio, they weren't able to get inside.
Now after the broadcast, Knight Scoop fans were thinking: "Why don't you invite these fans?"
And that's when we started receiving requests from people all over the country.
So I, Detective Sawabe, took on the case.
Whether they were still in Japan, and whether I was able to find them - please take a look!
Something strange has been happening, take a look.
These are all requests! Strange, isn't it?
We were flooded by clients, so I'm wondering where we should go from here.
We should pay TV Tokyo a visit first of all.
Here we are, we've arrived at TV Tokyo! Shall we head inside?
Excuse me, we're with Tantei Knight Scoop ...
Where would I find the staff members of "Why did you come ...?"
- This way.
This is their staff room?
It looks like a changing room at the beach...
They're completeley isolated for that show.
I contacted you some time ago, yes? Ah, thank you.
Nice to meet you.
The German couple you interviewed, they said they really liked Knight Scoop, right?
Is there a chance you could show us the clip where they said they flew over for that purpose?
- Of course.
So it's these two.
Konnichiha!
- Why did you come to Japan?
It's really funny!
That's lovely.
They'd never expect we'd be watching this together with a Detective...
Would it be ok if we came along?
They're something else, huh? Even as otaku, they're really something else.
Osaka, konnichiha!
By the way, have you scheduled an appointment or anything like that?
Now! Off to ABC TV!
It's no use.
They're not even taping today in the first place.
They seem really
desolate.
Ah~, this is heartbreaking to watch.
That's a shame.
ABC, please!
How adorable!
Next, they revisited memorable locations.
Arrived at Nara Park.
So they went to places like that...
It's like they're on a pilgrimage.
How happy they are...
They're reenacting it.
Respect for the Detectives!
That means a lot.
Somehow, I'm also really moved by this.
When did you film this?
- Around the first half of April.
In other words, they're still in Japan, right?
They might be, just barely.
Do you have an idea where we could find them? - Sure.
We can try.  - Is that ok?
But ... but ... I can't speak English well.
You're useless as a director!
If they've left already, then we're done.
5 minutes later ...
I reached someone. - You did?
It seems they've been staying at a hotel in the Ueno / Asakusa area.
I asked them if they could meet with us again and didn't mention anything about Tantei Knight Scoop. I thought it might be a nice surprise.
Aaah, you're amazing! That'll be fun to see when they find out!
Heading to the hotel where they are staying ...
One of the staff members just went inside the hotel ...
... and she should come out with the two of them in a bit. They still don't know that we're here.
Ah, they're coming, they're here, ahh~, it's them!
How about we go see them in person?
Ah, excuse me. Hello.
Excuse me.
You've been doing an interview, thinking it was for "Why did you come to Japan?", so why did you?
You've cut your hair so much, I almost didn't recognize you!
We came to meet you!
- Thank you so much!
Knight Scoop has been getting so many requests because of you!
Thank you, everyone!
Look how nice they are!
How are you feeling right now?
- Very nervous!
Now because last time didn't work out, you'll finally be able to see Knight Scoop!
Thank you so much!
Sawabe-san~
- You even know my name? Wow! I'm really glad! I'm known in Germany!
So, do you have some time to spare today?
So how about we head out together?
For the two who've come to love Tantei Knight Scoop: W・E・L・C・O・M・E
So as a matter of fact, it so happens that Takeyama-san is also filming in Tokyo today.
We're going to head over now and surprise Detective Takeyama at his shooting location.
The weather is really nice today, isn't it?
We didn't tell Detective Takeyama anything about this.
Excuse me!
He, he, he!
- Konnichiha!
Do you recognize them?
They're famous!
You know about TV Tokyo's "Why did you come to Japan?", right?
They said that they really liked Tantei Knight Scoop.
- Ah, I've heard there was someone like that! - That's them!
You?! What did you come for?
Hello! I'm glad.
So on Friday, they'll attend a taping.
- Ah, is that so?
Fantastic! - We're really glad!
What was it you called the director again?
Thank you!
So ... do you have some more time left?
Then, should we go to Osaka?
To Osaka!
We've arrived in Osaka!
Osaka, konnichiha!
Do you know Tsutenkaku Tower?
Then how about we go there now?
Are there any other people you know, Detectives or otherwise? - Hayashi-sensei!
Oh I see, I see.
Ah, that's a place you know, look - Tsutenkaku!
Do you recognize him? Nonoyama-san!
Seems like he's really popular with you!
Actually, he's come all the way from Nagoya for you.
- Really? Thank you so much!
Isn't there something you want to show them?
Next I'll make it fly using telekinesis.
What a mysterious thing to be shown!
That's all from Nonoyama-san!
So we've arrived all the way at the top. Here, you can scream out whatever you're feeling right now.
I'm so happy, because we get to see Knight Scoop live!
Seeing their eyes light up like this makes me really happy.
But we're not done yet, there's one more place I want to show you!
Off to another place.
I wonder if you'll enjoy this.
We've made it, this way please. It's here.
Konnichiha, Hayashi-sensei!
Hayashi-sensei!
What's going on here? You gave me a call but I still don't know what this is about.
Hello. - Hello.
What's going on?
So they came from Germany because they wanted to see Knight Scoop.
They liked it so much, they decided to come to Japan.
Hold on a second, I should have some ...
- He told us to wait.
These were returned for a different purpose.
- Made by the sensei himself?
Thank you so much!
Hayashi-sensei, it seems you have the presence of an idol! Wow!
Those look delicious...
So good! - It's delicious!
You're a good chef.
- I'm a good chef? Thank you!
So today, in very short time, we've visited a lot of places...
So even when you return to Germany, will you continue to watch Knight Scoop?
And something we thought was just right for you to have when you return home ... the DVD box!
Let's also become Detectives!
And then, their dream finally...
... comes true
Their dream has come true! They've made it to a taping!
Now that your dream has come true, how do you feel?
Looks like you've made the director cry. Cry-guy!
What's it like, seeing Cry-guy in person?
I'm deeply moved, so thank you.
- You're all so funny!