Can you reach, without using your satnav,
the place you should go to?!
Can you reach a certain place
without using your satnav?
No-satnav race episode 2!
Tonight, we'll have a second round of the no-satnav race!
A public road race for a head-on battle!
They'll race without satnav and anything can happen!
And, for the grand finale, we'll see unexpected drama!
A finale with unexpected drama?!
TYPESET & QC BY Kedomas
TRANSLATION & EDIT BY Shion
VISIT SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM FOR MORE GAKI!
FOLLOW @SHIONNOTSUKAI ON TWITTER / FB FOR UPDATES!
AND IF YOU WANT TO SHOW SUPPORT, YOU CAN DONATE ON
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI OR PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI !
VISIT SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM FOR MORE GAKI!
FOLLOW @SHIONNOTSUKAI ON TWITTER / FB FOR UPDATES!
AND IF YOU WANT TO SHOW SUPPORT, YOU CAN DONATE ON
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI OR PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI !
40-yo comedians will race around the city!
Get ready for hard struggles with no satnav!
This show was brought to you by Kedomas and Shion
We hope you'll enjoy it!
An exciting, uncalled for miraculous ending!
Last group is going to pay up for everything!
A group of satnav-deprived adults
are brought back to public roads...
is once again brought back to the road...
It's the no-satnav race!
We're doing it again, yes!
It's exhausting, you know?!
He's right
But last time it was such a close race, wasn't it fun?
Last time's close race!
That was by pure chance
- Exactly!
I mean, yeah, we weren't planning that
Such a miracle won't ever happen again!
Right
- That's our once in a lifetime
This is most likely gonna end quickly!
But it was really fun for us viewers!
Oh boy, oh boy...
I've watched the news instead!
Counterprogram!!
No way!
Broadcast on 05/01/2012
Goal spot from round 1
Restaurant Gusto
Shinkoiwa, South Gate Shop
Last episode ended with a miracle
Everyone race to their goal in Shinkoiwa,
Three teams competed for the race!
It was a race full of turn-around,
as they only relied on luck and guts!
And the winner from the previous race...
The first team who shone the most was...
You did it! Congratulations!
Team Matsumoto
1st Place
It was Matsumoto's team, which made a big comeback
Really?!
"Pedestrian rule"  has been used 3 times
to achieve victory!
They won by using the "pedestrian rule",
by which they could ask pedestrians for directions!
Team Ohtake
Third Place
On the other hand Ohtake's team,
on the last place, had to pay for everyone's expenses
They had to pay for everyone's expenses by themselves...
We want you to enjoy this ride even more,
so we're bringing here some fantastic guests for you!
Here they are, please come here!
Hi!
Rola
Ruriko Kojima
Nana Suzuki
Hi guys!
- There they are
They're the most classic men's choice, aren't they?
That's not true!
That's not it at all! Not true!
Let's all be friends here!
You forgot to do that chin move!
The other day on FRIDAY!
Come on!
That's not it, I...
- Where's the famous chin move?
You're the worst!
Is that all it takes?
For this round too, we have some female guests
Rola
Ruriko Kojima
Nana Suzuki
- Born in Tokyo
- Doesn't have a license
- Born in Chiba
- usually moves around
by train
- Born in Ibaraki
- In-city driving:
zero experience
to thin down our men's foulness!
However, they're not familiar at all with driving around
You're an university student, right Kojima?
Yes!
Have you ever driven to a class?
Actually no, I don't really drive
I've never dared to drive around the city!
You won't fool me with that face,
it's the "I'll help you moving" face!
What?!
He's right, that's what those who help moving out always say
Straight out from the script
She's an expert on box-packing
- That could be, but not driving
None of them is a good pick for a team!
This isn't gonna be easy
Blue
Now it's time to make up teams
Orange
Black
3 Teams will join the race
We have three different colored cars for this race,
They'll draw a lottery to form three teams!
The girls will be the first to draw!
The girls will be the first to draw
Alright, let's start from our guests
Sure!
Orange!
So quick!!
So quick!
- Build up some suspense at least!
Why are you in such a hurry?
Take it slowly, come on!
- He's right
Feels like a race already
- Really
That's the kind of stuff Arita hates the most!
We're not dating, you know!
We're just friends
It lacked "TV appeal", so they'll draw again!
Rola's pull wasn't appealing for TV, so they'll do it again
Ready, and...
Ah! It's not the same!
Mine's orange!
- Mine's black!
We have prepared these for you guys
Team Uniforms
Have these jackets
This is so cool!
How many more races
are you planning to do from now on?!
Thanks!
- This is so cool!
Now it's time for the boys...
Now it's time for the boys to know their team
And as a result, here are the final teams
Team Matsumoto
Team Ohtake
Team Mimura
Blue
Orange
Black
Our previous race champions, Matsumoto and Otohara,
are on two different teams
On the other hand, Mimura and Miyasako,
who know their way around, are on the same team
Please, head to the car with your assigned color
Okay, bye-bye
- Bye-bye!
Alright, we're going!
It's time to get in the car!
They get in the car with the allies brought by fate
Time to choose each role:
Driver
Front Seat
Back Seat
Each team will choose the driver and wait for the start
And now, it's finally time!
- Alright, everything's set
And now, ladies and gentlemen...
Open up your dashboard, please
This one?
We opened it
Okay!
Is there something in it?
- Yes!
Inside the red envelope you can see
what's your goal you have to reach for today!
Alright then, please open them all!
Please, be somewhere I know...
Car positions:
Matsumoto
Amano
Kojima
Open!
King of Gyoza Musashi Kosugi Shop
What?!
Where is this?!
- Never heard of this place before!
Musashi Kosugi?!
Car positions:
Udo
Suzuki
Hotohara
Ohtake
Musashi Kosugi...
Musashi Kosugi?!
Car positions:
Mimura
Miyasako
Rola
What?!
- Oh man...
Do you know how to get there?
Musashi Kosugi?
Musashi Kosugi...
It's around Meguro, isn't it?
I think so
I-I'm not that lost, you know...
The goal they'll have to reach:
King of Gyoza
Musashi Kosugi Shop
The goal they have to reach is King of Gyoza,
the shop in Musashi Kosugi
As a reward for the first two teams,
they can enjoy a gyoza buffet for free!
Towards Kanagawa
Akasaka TBS
Musashi Kosugi
Imperial Palace
Shibuya
Meguro
Futako Tamagawa
This is the shortest route to the goal
Shortest route
By heading to Kanagawa, you can reach it within 1 hour
Musashi Kosugi is in Kawasaki town,
beyond Tamagawa, in Kanagawa prefecture
Nakahara
Highway
The key to win this race is whether
or not you enter Nakahara Highway
Alright, it's time to start the no-SATNAV rally,
objective: King of Gyoza in Musashi Kosugi!
This "Musashi Kosugi" thing...
What?! It already started?!
Musashi Kosugi...
Wait a moment, what should we do?!
Our best, I guess?
Take care!
- Where should we go?
I'm going over there
The three teams dashed out at once!
We're going left!
Have a nice ride, and be careful!
See you later!
Musashi Kosugi is...?
I don't...
- I really don't know
Wait, I think I know!
It's around Suginami, isn't it?!
It could be! I think I've seen that name before
Like, in those railway maps around the stations!
Musashi Kosugi... what's the closest station to it?
- Musashi Kosugi...
Wasn't there, like, a huge shopping district?
Or maybe that's Musashi Koyama!
Right, that one does exist too
It's a shame, I actually know how to get to Musashi Koyama
Should be around Meguro
Want me to go towards Musashi Koyama?
Why, is Musashi Kosugi close to Musashi Koyama?
I don't know, what do you think?
Hey Rola, you know what we're talking about?
Nope, no clue!
Isn't it around Kichioji or such?
Now that you say it, it could be
I don't know jack about Kichioji and what's around it!
Not even anything about Jiyugaoka
Last time it was more around...
- Wait, Matsumoto...
Jiyugaoka and Kichioji aren't close at all!
That's...
That's how little I know my way around...
Is that all you can bring us?
You're bad news, Matsumoto!
- What should we do?!
This show really brings out the worst of me, huh?
I've never been to this Musashi Kosugi place!
Musashi Koyama is around Meguro, though
Eh?! Really? Musashi Kosugi...
- A different one?!
Is Musashi Koyama around Meguro?
That's right
Then... aren't they close?
What? That's such a risky move!
I mean, they could be...
Do you mean like sister cities or such?
That's exactly what I meant, yes
I mean, they both took on this "Musashi" thing
We should... We should just ask the locals
But aren't there, like, dozens of "Musashi"...?
Akasaka TBS
Meguro
Shibuya
Suginami
prefecture
Shortest route
Their biggest obstacle for this race
is the trick behind the place's name
Musashi Koganei
Musashi Kosugi
Musashi Koyama
There are tons of "Musashi" around Tokyo
Their goal, Musashi Kosugi, is in Kawasaki,
but Musashi Koganei is in Suginami
That's why they can use the important
"pedestrian rule"
Pedestrian
Each team can ask up to three times
pedestrians for directions,
Pedestrian
They can ask pedestrians up to 3 times
but can they actually use this wisely?!
But the most crucial factor is how and when
to ask them for directions
Goal
Suginami Direction
That's what they think...
Team Ohtake
Between them, Team Ohtake is headed
towards Suginami, where they think their goal lies...
Huh? But Musashi Kosugi...
Aren't you all sure...
It wasn't around Kawasaki or such?
Are you sure?
Nice move
Kawasaki?
- It's not even Tokyo...
It could be
- I mean, it could!
I'm pretty sure it's around there, don't you think so?
But if we go there and we're wrong, we're done for!
If we go to Kawasaki, there's no way we can go back to Suginami!
Guess you're right...   - We gotta make a decision
Suginami and Kawasaki are too far apart
What should we do?
Let's see...
Let's ask some pedestrian then!
Wanna go already for it?
Yeah, let's start off with a bang!
Are we already asking?
I see, it may be the wisest choice!
Yeah!
- I agree
Let's go for it!
Suginami
Kawasaki
The team is looking for a pedestrian to ask
Team Ohtake
Following Captain Ohtake's orders,
they chose to ask around if it's Suginami or Kawasaki
The blue car got away from Akasaka, the starting point
Yotsuya
Current
location
Shibuya
Akasaka TBS
Shortest route
Musashi Kosugi
Team Matsumoto
is wandering around the shortest route
Team Matsumoto is just wandering around
somewhere on the north side of the route
What should we do? Real talk here...
- This isn't good at all...
If we go this way, we should reach Yotsuya, right?
We can ask somebody near Yotsuya Station, right?
You're right, we should
That's right!
- Yeah
Meanwhile, Team Mimura believes Kosugi
should be near Koyama, and so...
Musashi Koyama
Meguro
Current
location
Shortest route
Musashi Kosugi
Akasaka TBS
Shibuya
Team Mimura
believes Musashi Kosugi is near Musashi Koyama, and so...
They're headed to Meguro, with no time to waste
So, we're driving knowing where we're headed?
Yeah, I know where we're going
Really?
Well, I live in Meguro, so...
That gives me hope!
I always drive this road to get back home
- Oh, is that so?
Arita
Unlike Arita's house, right?
Come on, don't say weird stuff!
We're just friends!
What have you done together?
We played "minna no golf" all the time!
"Minna no golf"?
But when I told him I had to go home,
He wanted to play more and forced me to stay more!
- I see... did he?
With his jaw out?
Of course
Say, Rola... do you like strong jaws?
Don't say it like that, it sounds mean!
I really like him as a person, he's fun to talk to
But those aren't feelings of love
Is that so?
And I think I'm being clear on that
If that's so, what kind of man do you like, Rola?
I like, you know, men who have a wild feeling to them
- Wild?
Sugi-chan
You mean, like Sugi-chan? What do you think of him?
Nope, Sugi-chan is just a tiny old dude
That's what you think of him?
Oh boy...
Team Matsumoto has arrived near Yotsuya Station
Current
location
Yotsuya
Shibuya
Akasaka TBS
Shortest route
Musashi Kosugi
Team Matsumoto
Has arrived near Yotsuya Station
It's time for them to look for a passerby
Who should we ask?
Look at that couple, they're standing like
"if they ask us, we could help them a lot"
Ah! I see!
I mean, maybe they saw our previous episode...
Our first round! I see!
- You could be right!
Aahh! Wait!
- One moment!
Shit, now that we've called them we're done
- What should we do?
What should we do?
- You go, Kojima
We're counting on you, Kojima!
One of them, ok?
No SATNAV Rally
One team member can ask a passerby for directions,
but he/she isn't allowed to take any notes
Pick the guy!
Ask the man!
The man? The man?
Sorry...
Sorry, can I ask you something?
Do you know how to reach Musashi Kosugi?
Pedestrian cards
Team Matsumoto
IN USE
I think you should ride Toyoko line   - Toyoko line!
Toyoko line
Should be near Nansei   - Nansei!
Nansei
Isn't it near Shinjuku?
No, it's closer to south Shibuya   - I see...
Shibuya
Sorry! And thank you!
Thank you so much!
That guy is such an MVP
I asked him!
You did?!
Really?! You got it?!
We can definitely reach that place!
What? Where is it?
- Let's see
He told me that from where we are,
we should head towards Shibuya first thing
And in terms of general location, it's in Nansei
I have no idea where that is either!
Knowing it's "Nansei" doesn't help me at all!
Like, if it's like this, Yokohama is here...
- Where is Nansei?
We should first go to Shibuya---
Isn't it around Kawasaki?
He said it was along Toyoko line!
Tokoyo line? What's that?
That's where I wanted to go, Kawasaki
Yeah, we should point to Yokohama
- We could have done it, oh boy
Alright, let's head to Shibuya for now
Shibuya, you say...
But what should we do once we arrive?
If we move poorly, we'd end up in Komazawa avenue
We move towards Yokohama
Amano surely does know his way around Shibuya, huh?
Well yeah, I do
But I don't think it's the best thing to do
- We would have probably died if you weren't here
I'd rather go right into...
Hey! You can't do this! It's a violation!
Oh geez...
This isn't really something you should do
Amano!
Did I just sounded like him?
I mean, like Udo-chan, right?
That's how he always calls me
Team Matsumoto
They're headed towards Shibuya, for now
Team Matsumoto heads to Shibuya
after getting some precious info on its location
Meanwhile, Team Ohtake has arrived in Aoyama
Current
location
Shibuya
Meguro
Akasaka TBS
Shortest route
Musashi Kosugi
Team Ohtake
Arrived in Aoyama
Now they plan to find the right passerby to ask
Let's ask someone in Aoyama!
No-SATNAV Rally
One team member can ask a passerby for directions,
but he/she isn't allowed to take any notes
Who should we ask?    - Someone's coming
You should do it, Nana
Me? I'm going?
- Yeah, you're a girl, you should do it
I can do it, no problem!
Make sure to grasp some info
- Leave it to me
Ask that man who just stepped out the car dealer!
Let's do this
Should I just go?
- Go for it!
Excuse me...
We're filming a TV show, is it a problem for you?
Not at all
Can we film you?
Come on, please!
Alright, I'll ask him!
I'm doing it!
- Counting on ya!
Pedestrian cards
Team Ohtake
So, we're heading to King of Gyoza in Musashi Kosugi...
IN USE
Do you happen to know where Musashi Kosugi is?
We don't have a SATNAV, so we don't know where...
Musashi Kosugi? I have no clue
He doesn't know
I'm from Toshigi!
Where did he say?
You came from Tochigi?!
Actually, my workplace is in Thailand
- Thailand?!
- No way, I can't believe it!
Are you kidding me?
Did you ask someone who lives in Thailand?!
Thank you anyway
- Thanks
Oh boy, Nana...
- Get in
I didn't expect it at all!
What a surprise, huh?
You guys are so bad at choosing!
He said he's from Toshigi, huh?
And also Thailand!
USED
A precious card has been wasted
Due to a stroke of bad luck, they wasted a precious card
We still have two more tries
I think that...
We should follow my "it's towards Kawasaki" theory
- Hotohara...
We should enter national highway 246
National highway 246, got it, let's go
- Yeah, let's go
We're too much inside the city, after all
I agree    - Right
Let's go a bit further and ask over there
- Alright
Team Ohtake lost its gamble,
and now they're headed to Kawasaki
Shibuya
Akasaka TBS
Current
location
Meguro
Musashi Kosugi
Shortest route
Team Ohtake
Leaves the city and takes national highway 246 to go south
Current
location
Team Mimura
Objective: Musashi Koyama direction
Meanwhile, Team Mimura is headed to Musashi Koyama,
being that Miyasako is familiar with Meguro
Oh! That's Atré!
So this...    - We're in Meguro
That's Meguro Station
And now we're out Yamate Avenue
If I recall correctly, it's on the left after Yamate
I know this place
I think that's the right choice
Yeah, it should be towards Gotanda
What do you think about it, Rola?
Well, let's see... I don't really know!
What?!
Just kidding! I think we're good!
Can I exit from the right?
That's what drivers hate the most
When someone drives shaking around
Can the human-SATNAV Miyasako grant them the victory?
Shibuya
Meguro
Musashi Koyama
Current
location
Musashi Koyama
Shortest route
Team Mimura
Enters Yamate-dori avenue
Current
location
Team Matsumoto
Finally has arrived to Shibuya
At that same time, Team Matsumoto has arrived to Shibuya
Shibuya, again...
Yeah but we were the slowest last time too, right?
But in the end we won!
Let's go over there, come on!
- Over there, got it
2 cards left for Team Matsumoto
USED
Matsumoto insists on using their second card,
so they're headed to that certain place...
This is Hikarie, isn't it?!
It's Hikarie! That's exactly it!
That's right, this place...
It's the most crowded spot in Shibuya...
- That's right
Shit, who should we ask, Matsumoto?
Ah! This guy!
Ah, but he's carrying a suitcase...
Matsumoto?
He's an AMANO employee
I mean, the AMANO corp.
But he's "AMANO" like me, isn't this fate? Let's ask him!
Oh, 'cause you're both Amano?
No-SATNAV Rally
One team member can ask a passerby for directions,
but he/she isn't allowed to take any notes
Let's ask the guys with the AMANO bag   - That guy?
Come on, just go
- Are you?
Can I?
- Yeah, just do it
We can't ask just one guy, we should ask more people
Counting on you!
Yes, him!
- Go ask him!
You're holding an AMANO bag, can I ask you something?
Please come closer
It's the name of my company
The AMANO corp.? That famous one?
- That's right
What is it about?
It focuses on time recorders
Time recorders? Those things?
I came here from Fukuoka, today
From Fukuoka?!
Huh? What's wrong?
What's going on?
Huh? What now?
He said he came from Fukuoka
- What? Really?
What's the problem?
He's out!
He said he came from Fukuoka, after all
Geez!
Do we have to ask him anyway, now that we've picked him?
Can we change?
- You can't, ask him
No-SATNAV Rally
Once you choose someone, you can't change
Well, let's ask him, he may know it
- We have to choose him?!
Alright, we wanted to ask you something
- Well, we have to ask him...
Pedestrian cards
Team Matsumoto
USED
I'm asking it anyway
Do you happen to know where's Musashi Kosugi?
IN USE
Nope
He doesn't know
Huh?! What now?
- Well, thanks!
We're screwed     - No good?
He doesn't know
- That sucks!
I told you that suitcase for trips was suspicious!
- You were right
Amano!
Holy crap!
USED
A joker from Fukuoka
Amano felt this weird fate,
and now Team Matsumoto is in trouble
They only have a single pedestrian card left
After the tragedy, Team Ohtake heads to Shibuya as well
Akasaka TBS
Team Ohtake
Shibuya
Team Matsumoto
Shortest Route
Team Ohtake
Really close to Shibuya
Who's going?
Who should go?
Who's going to ask?
Can you do it?
Yeah I can do it, no problem!
We're counting on you this time
So, where are we headed?
Musashi Kosugi!
That's right, you got that
USED
Can Nana's charm bring them a useful hint, this time?
Time to use their second card
They can't afford to make another mistake
like the Thailand-based pedestrian they just met
Thailand isn't an option anymore
How about one of those salarymen?
No SATNAV Rally
One team member can ask a passerby for directions,
but he/she isn't allowed to take any notes
- You're right
Should I ask him? Hey, wait a second!
Excuse me!
Sorry, do you have few minutes for us?
We're doing a TV show, I wanted to ask you something
Is it okay for you?
- Sure
So...
Do you happen to know Musashi Kosugi?
I do!
You really know Musashi Kosugi?!
- Yes, I do
He knows it!
That's where my company is
Is that where you company is?!
I'm so happy right now!
Nana seems happy
- Good, what's going on?
I wanted to ask you in which prefecture it is,
or which station we can find near it
Pedestrian cards
Team Ohtake
USED
IN USE
It's in Nakahara, near Kawasaki city
Kawasaki city, right?
- Yes, Nakahara prefecture
Kawasaki city, Nakahara prefecture
Wait a second, Kawasaki city...
The closest station is of course Musashi Kosugi,
you can reach it with the Toyoko line from Shibuya
Toyoko line from Shibuya
Wait a second, too many informations!
- You can take it from here
Just head towards Yokohama
Yokohama, right? And it's in Nakahara...
- That's right
Direction: Yokohama
What bugs me...
Isn't how that guy is gonna explain anything
Yeah, if she gets back here...
I'm worried about Nana, can she remember anything at all?
That's the problem
Nakahara prefecture, Musashi Kosugi station
Correct
Is there something else I need you to ask?
Remember those two: Nakahara prefecture and the station
Ok, got it!
I really got it, thank you!
You really saved us!
- Don't worry, go for it
Thank you so much!
Nakahara prefecture! Nakahara, Nakahara!
A miracle happened, guys!
What is it?
It's in Nakahara prefecture!
- Get in, quick!
We hit the jackpot, guys!
Nakahara, you said?
So it's not inside Tokyo?
It's towards Yokohama, right?
It is, yeah
So Kawasaki should do it?
Yes, it's the same direction
That man was really the best we could find
Why is that?
I know you won't believe it
But he actually works in Musashi Kosugi!
Really?! You gotta be kidding me!
That's unbelievable!
For real...
Did he tell you in detail?
- Of course
We know there's a "Musashi Kosugi" station
- Alright, its station
That's all I got, but it should do it
No way, where do we have to go from here?
Huh?
What did he say?
He said we're fine as long as we head to Yokohama
No way, that's...
Yokohama is way too huge!
Did he tell you which avenue we should take?
Like, street names?
Or something near them?
But you didn't tell me to ask him that!
Like, which highway should we take...
But you didn't tell me!
We did, we did!
You did not!
Alright, let's just go
- Yeah, let's not waste time
As long as we go towards Kawasaki, we're good, right?
That's right!
- Alright, that's it
She's a genius, a genius!
I'm so glad I am!
She forgot to ask how to reach it
Team Ohtake
"Towards Ishikawa" - got some precious info
But now they know they should go
towards Ishikawa, instead of Suginami.
Meanwhile, Team Matsumoto left Shibuya
Current
location
Shibuya
Musashi Kosugi
Shortest route
Team Matsumoto
Took Meiji-doori and they're headed South
Current
location
And they're headed on South Meiji-doori
Now they're a bit closer to the shortest route
I don't want to lose!
- What should we do?
I don't want to lose, but I have no clue!
Me too!
Let's think again about what the first guy said
Yeah, he said...
- It's around Yokohama, right?
Info from the passerby
Team Matsumoto
He said Yokohama Direction, and to go
to Toyama line from Shibuya
Yokohama Direction
Shibuya
Toyama line
If we're gonna trust him, we should just
follow this road and we're in the right path
Is that true?    - Yes
Alright, let's go then, let's give it a shot
This is the same direction as Jiyugaoka, though
They chose to enter Komazawa avenue,
near the Toyoko line, which is close to the shortest route
Shibuya
Current
Location
Meguro
Nakahara
highway
Shortest route
Musashi Kosugi
Team Matsumoto
Heading to Komazawa avenue, intersected with Toyoko line
Current
Location
Team Ohtake leaves Shibuya too,
as if following Team Matsumoto
Shibuya
Meguro
Current
location
Nakahara
Highway
Shortest route
Musashi Kosugi
Team Ohtake
Going south to Yamate-doori
Trusting their guts, they're about to enter Yamate-doori
So, now that we're here...
Are we going right?
Both Kawasaki and Yokohama
are on the right, if I'm not wrong
Yeah, that's right
But where are we supposed to turn?
In Nakahara ward?
Nakahara ward...
Hey, isn't "Nakahara Highway" a thing?
Nice move, again
I hear that a lot
- I know Nakahara Highway
Right? It's not an unfamiliar name
- I heard of it
Like, in the traffic news...
- I guess it's...
Probably it's a highway in Nakahara ward?
I think it's possible, they have the same name...
Nakahara Highway, you mean?
I think that's it
- Makes sense
Are we really sure?
- I think so
So we should just move to Nakahara Highway, right?
But it's not around here, is it?
Udo's intuition served a nice move!
Shibuya
Meguro
Musashi Koyama
Musashi Kosugi
Shortest route
Team Ohtake
Got a hint from "Nakahara Ward", nice move!
He remembered "Nakahara Highway" from
"Nakahara Ward", it's the shortest route!
Team Mimura
Arrived in Musashi Koyama
Team Mimura has arrived in Musashi Koyama,
as they plan on using a pedestrian card
No one's around...
Shit, there's not a single soul in here!
Deserted.
Well, we should ask somebody anyway
Rola?
- Ah! There's someone there!
- I'm going, let me go
Go for it!
Remember, it's Musashi Kosugi!
Got it!
Excuse me, mister!
Can I ask you some directions?
Pedestrian cards
Team Mimura
Uhm, what was it...
IN USE
Do you happen to know where's Musashi Kosugi?
- Well, it's not here
It's not where we're now, you know
Mukashi Kosugi isn't here
Which way should we go by car?    - That way, I guess
Which road is it? Which number?
It's Naka...
I don't remember!
Ah? Really? Naka-something, right? Thanks!
"Naka... something" street
He said it's not around here at all!
Are you kidding me?!
He said we should head "Naka-something" from here
Eh? What?
- Naka...?
Naka-something!
Naka-something? What's that?
He said he didn't know and he left
Eh? W-Wait, gimme a sec...
- But he said...
He said it's not here, we're completely off
Completely off?
He said "this is Koyama, you know!"
So Koyama and Kosugi aren't close to each other?
Seems like it
Maybe it's Nakahara Highway?
- I was thinking the same
Yep, it could be
We made such a huge mistake!
Huge mistake!
- Oh crap, what now?
Team Mimura can't hide their panic after discovering
Team Mimura
"Koyama" and Kosugi aren't close: panic
That Musashi Koyama and Kosugi aren't close
Nakahara Highway draws near!
But they don't know it's the shortest route
They're actually the closest team to Nakahara Highway,
But the tension in their car is rising
Right now, the map inside my head is completely blank
I mean, I've never ever in my entire life
Moved from Koyama to Kosugi!
- Me neither
No SATNAV Rally
While driving, you can call
another team with your mobile phone
They decide to call another team
to calm down their uneasiness
Maybe if we go a bit further, we can...
- It's ringing
Who is it?
Black car
Black? Oh boy
Talking to another team to get more info
Hello? Have you arrived?
- Not yet, but we're almost there!
What about you, Rola?
Eh? We're lost!
- Are you lost?
That's right!
- Where did you get lost?
I have no clue what Udo-chan is saying
- Wait a moment, Rola!
I'll let you talk to my friend here!
Hello? Is it Rola?
Ah! Nana-chan!
Say, say, how is it going over there?
- We're on the right path, right?
Where are you guys, right now?
- Right now?
Well, I don't really want to tell you
We're heading the right way, so we can't!
Look! It says "Nakahara Highway" over there!
No way! Come on, tell me
Look! It's "Nakahara Highway"!
- We haven't arrived yet, but...
We're headed to somewhere which
should be the right spot, so we can't tell ya
Aw, come on!
Overwhelmed by joy
Yep
- Let me speak to Udo again
Yep, gimme a sec
- Sure!
Team Ohtake
While on the phone, "Nakahara Highway" has been spotted!
They found Nakahara Highway during their call!
Be careful, ok?
It's not the right time to chitchat with Rola
So they hurry up and hang the phone
to reach the shortcut to their triumph!
Team Ohtake
They hung up in a hurry
to finally enter Nakahara Highway !!
Team Matsumoto moves to Komazawa avenue
Meguro
Current
location
Futako Tamagawa
Musashi Kosugi
Nakahara
Highway
Shortest route
Team Matsumoto
Komazawa avenue: moving south
Everything seems to go just fine, but then...
I feel like if we go pass Nikotama
something good might pop out, you know!
"Kaminoge"...?
Should we head to Nikotama?
Nikotama, you say?
Nikotama has something to it...
which, you know, makes me spark!
What's the meaning of this spark?
I don't really know myself, it's a gut feeling
- Should we do it?
Team Matsumoto
Only 1 card left
The last one will be used in Futako Tamagawa!
They're now headed to Futako Tamagawa
Will they use their last card efficiently?
They  haven't realized they're already on the shortest route
Team Mimura is currently on Nakahara Highway,
they're drawing closer to a fateful crossroad
Musashi Koyama
Nakahara
Highway
Current
location
Futako Tamagawa
Musashi Kosugi
Shortest route
Team Mimura
Omori?
This way leads to Omori
Omori Koenji on the right,
and Marukobashi if we go straight
Should we turn or...?
- Tsunashima? It's Kannana road, isn't it?
Raise your hand if you think
Kannana road is on the left!
I do
Me too
If that's it, me too!
"If that's it"? Are we going right?
Let's go that way
- It could be after Marukobashi
So you think it's ahead?
- Maybe we don't need to hit Kannana road
Should we just go left for now?
Alright, I'm turning left
It's Ohta ward over there
Musashi Kosugi is in Ohta ward, right?
I have this feeling that I've heard before
about Musashi Kosugi being in Ohta
It does sound good, doesn't it?
It does, it does!
Futako Tamagawa
Musashi Koyama
Current
location
Nakahara
Highway
Musashi Kosugi
Shortest route
Team Mimura
Turning left on Kannana: a regretful mistake
That's of course a mistake
Current
location
The top team gets off the shortest route,
and the race faces an unexpected turn of events!
Current
location
Team Matsumoto
Once more, they head South from Komazawa avenue
Meanwhile, Team Matsumoto picked Futako Tamagawa
as the place to use their next pedestrian card
We're in Futako, huh
We're basically inside Setagaya ward!
Where are we now?
It's Komazawa Park
I'm thinking, maybe...
There's a big chance
we'll actually end up in some uncharted land
That would suck...     - Can't deny it!
I tell ya, I feel like I'm 70% sure about it!
- No way!
Now I'm not that confident anymore
It could be, statistically
- Of course
That's right, Team Matsumoto isn't on the right route
Hurrying to Futako Tamagawa to get hints
Meguro
Current
location
Futako Tamagawa
Nakahara
Highway
Musashi Kosugi
Shortest route
Team Matsumoto
Current
location
They haste their way to Futako Tamagawa to get a hint
Meanwhile, Team Mimura left Nakahara Highway
and they're about to find out something...
Team Mimura
They left the shortest route and they're wandering around
That's Musashi Nitta station!
Oh! Is that...?
We're close!
- It's Musashi Nitta, though...
We don't know if it's actually close,
I didn't know "Musashi Nitta" was even a thing!
Musashi Nitta, huh...
- But it should be good!
- I guess so
- It's still "Musashi"
Maybe we should ask around here too
Team Mimura just saw the sign for Musashi Nitta
They just found Musashi Nitta and they're going nuts
Captain Mimura himself decides to use their 2nd card
USED
Second card: it's time to use it
Will he bring his team some precious info?
Excuse me, can I ask you something?
Pedestrian card
Team Mimura
USED
Do you know where's Musashi Kosugi?
IN USE
Musashi Kosugi
is a bit over there!
A bit over there?
Yeah, I'd say... more than a bit
More than a bit?
How far away is it? 5 km or such?
- Yeah, that's about it
So if I go straight down that road for 5 km...?
- About 5 km from here
As soon as you see Marukobashi, turn left
-On the left of Marukobashi
I think that's where Musashi Kosugi is
I see, thanks so much!
Sorry I can't help you that much! Just go ahead!
Sure, thanks
Alright!
I did it!
Really?
- That man told me
If we go, like 5km straight from here...
We arrive to Marukobashi at one point
If we turn left as soon as we're there,
We should be around Musashi Kosugi!
Marukobashi? Was there such a thing?
- Yes, definitely
Marukobashi
Musashi Kosugi
King of Gyoza
Shortest route
Going past this bridge
leads you to the goal!
That's right, Marukobashi leads to the victory!
Musashi Kosugi is right before you eyes
once you cross the bridge and pass Tamagawa!
Team Mimura
Marukobashi is their goal
Thanks to Mimura's action,
the team draws closer to the victory!
Meanwhile, Team Matsumoto is in Futako Tamagawa
Futako Tamagawa
Current
location
Nakahara
Highway
Musashi Kosugi
Shortest route
Team Matsumoto
Futako Tamagawa: arrived!
They plan to use their last card!
What should we do?
We're in trouble, aren't we?
We can't waste any time
- How about that guy?
Mizonoguchi ahead and Komae on the right?
- Mh? What's that?
- I feel like we're on the right way
Do you recall these streets?
- I think so, can't remember
Go ask someone, Matsumoto! Anyone's fine!
- Alright, I'm going
- We're counting on you
Matsumoto Hitoshi will set foot on Futako Tamagawa
Matsumoto is about to set foot on Futako Tamagawa!
For real?!
Alright, I'm going
- We're counting on you
USED
Last chance!
Is this going to work?
Excuse me, I have a question
for that one bespectacled dude
Oh, sure, glad I can help
Pedestrian card
Team Matsumoto
USED
Do you... know where's Musashi Kosugi?
IN USE
Musashi Kosugi?
You don't know, do you?
- Musashi Kosugi is straight ahead
Really?!    - See?!
Straight ahead
Are you for real?
See? I told you!
- I'm so happy!
How far by car?
It's really close by car     - Really?!
How many kilometers?
I'd say... about 5km      - Are you kidding me?!
5km from here
Thank you so much!
We got really lucky, folks!    - Thanks!
That's amazing! Thank you so much!
Hope you'll spend a wonderful weekend!
Really?! For real?!
Is that true? Aren't you glad?
You gotta be kidding me...
We're only 5 km apart!
I can't believe it, let's go!
We're gonna be the first!
I must be chosen by God!
Can't believe it
This is unbelievable
Matsumoto, will you win again...?
Isn't this something?
It is
- Almost scary, I'd say
Futako Tamagawa
Current
location
Nakahara
highway
Musashi Kosugi
Shortest route
Team Matsumoto
The info they got isn't right!
But actually, this info isn't correct at all
If they don't turn left after the bridge,
they won't reach Musashi Kosugi
Will they believe the info they got?
They can't blame the pedestrian for it
It's up to them whether to trust the info or not
Meanwhile, something appears before Team Mimura
Nakahara
highway
Current
location
Shortest route
King of Gyoza
Musashi Kosugi
Marukobashi
Team Mimura
Right before their eyes
Huh? Is that Tamagawa?
T-Tamagawa? We haven't passed that
- I see...
Do we have to get across the river?
Do we have to?
Of course we have to cross it!
Yeah, that's right
Maybe everyone's afraid to cross it...
You mean like the previous episode?
Exactly
- Oh boy...
Ah! Marukobashi! That's it!
Oh! You're right!
- It's Marukobashi!
Let's cross it!
- Yeah!
Crossing Marukobashi and
entering Kanagawa prefecture!
Team Mimura
Team Mimura went past Tamagawa from Marukobashi,
and they finally entered Kanagawa prefecture!
And it's also in front of Team Ohtake in Nakahara highway!
Nakahara
highway
Current
location
Shortest route
Marukobashi
King of Gyoza
Musashi Kosugi
Team Ohtake
It's right before their eyes!
Oh boy, oh boy, oh boy!
Looks like there's some sort of blockage
Huh?
So if we cross this bridge...
- Mh? What? Ah, you mean if we cross it...
We'll enter Kawasaki!
- I think so, yeah
So if we just cross it...
Without hesitation, they cross
Marukobashi and enter Kanagawa Prefecture!
Team Ohtake
With no hesitation, they cross Marukobashi Bridge
and enter Kanagawa Prefecture
And then...
What should we do?
Let's ask somebody!
Right, we only have one card left
Alright, let's stop here!
H-How about here?
USED
Time for the long-awaited third card!
They stop the car to promptly use their last card!
How about you go, Udo?
Me? Really?    - Yeah
Oh boy...
We're counting on you
- Counting on you!
Alright
Excuse me!
Excuse me, good morning
Pedestrian card
Team Ohtake
USED
We have to go to Musashi Kosugi's King of Gyoza...
IN USE
Do you know how to get there?
King of Gyoza, right? It's not really that easy, but...
You have to turn right over there
At the traffic lights?
Turn right at the traffic lights
Yes, and then you end up near the station
You mean Musashi Kosugi's station?!      - Yes
Oh, he's pointing his finger
He's being really accurate!
That's great news!
It's close!
So, there's a gas station in here
Turn left on that, and it's immediately on the right
Turn left at the gas station
Thank you! Thank you so much!
Sorry for the trouble! Thanks so much!
Hop in, Udo-chan!
Seems like he told you every detail about it!
This is incredible!
That guy was spot on for this!
What? What did he tell you, Udo-chan?
We just have to follow this road
We're on the right track, it's this street!
Really?! We were right?
So, as you can see
At those traffic lights, we have to turn right...
Huh? Which ones?
The second ones, we have to turn right at those
And after we entered that street, we go straight
Burp
I didn't mean to burp, sorry!
Right now?!
Sorry, it's that...
It's because I spoke so much in just one breath!
So, we have to turn right on that...
Alright, for now let's just move over there, ok?
Yeah!
Yet another nice move from Udo!
Their last card was a huge success!
They haste their way to their goal!
Team Ohtake
They got the info not only for Kosugi's station,
but for their goal, King of Gyoza, as well!
Victory draws near
Meanwhile, Team Mimura is ready to use their last card
USED
It's finally time to use it
Should we ask?
Yeah, let's do it!
Yes
Musashi Kosugi...
Wanna go, Rola?
Sure
Who will be the fateful last pedestrian?
Hi! Can I ask you something?
Hi!
Hey, it's Rola!    - Yep!
Pedestrian card
Team Mimura
USED
We're filming an episode of Lincoln
And we're completely lost
IN USE
Do you know where's Musashi Kosugi?
Just turn right at the 2nd traffic lights you see
All we have to do is to turn there to reach it?
Turn right at the 2nd traffic lights
- That's right!
Thanks a bunch!
Yay!
He said we have to turn right at the
2nd traffic lights and we're in Musashi Kosugi!
Oh! That's amazing!     - Hop in, quick!
They follow a difficult road only a resident
would know, it's time to go!
Team Miyasako
They got some really accurate info!
Only a local would know the road
they're currently heading towards to
And then...
It says "Kosugi Building"!
Isn't that "Kosugi" from "Musashi Kosugi"?
- Must be it!
Aaaah!
We did it!
What?! Really?
It says "Musashi Kosugi Station"!
Musashi Kosugi Station has been found!
Team Mimura
Alright!
All that's left now...   - It's King of Gyoza!
We made it!
We can't ask anymore, right?
Yeah, we ran out of cards
But I don't think it's that far away from the station
- You're right
Come on, let's go, let's go, let's go!
I wonder where it is...
Finally Musashi Kosugi appears!
Now they have to search for the shop
Team Miyasako
Musashi Kosugi Station has finally been spotted!
Now they have to find King of Gyoza by themselves
And, at the same time, it's before Ohtake Team's eyes too!
Right before their eyes!
Team Ohtake
Isn't that a station?
That's Musashi Kosugi Station isn't it?
Musashi Kosugi!
Ah! Oh my!
Musashi Kosugi, that's it!
It's Musashi Kosugi!
Here it is!
Musashi Kosugi Station: Spotted!
Team Ohtake
It's Musashi Kosugi Station!
We have to turn left at ENEOS!
Turn left!
- Really?!
That's it! It's on the left!
On the left of ENEOS?     - Yes!
Alright!
- Looking good, guys!
We actually made it!
Marukobashi
King of Gyoza
Musashi Kosugi
Two teams in close game!
Unbelievably enough, two teams spot it at the same time!
But both teams ran out of pedestrian cards
Pedestrian cards are
no longer in their hands...
Team Ohtake
Team Mimura
They can only rely on their guts from this point on!
I'm currently right before today's goal,
the King of Gyoza shop in Musashi Kosugi
Which team is going to be the first one to show up?
Once they cut the goal tape and get inside the shop
Their triumphant success will be awarded with...
There's a banquet waiting for them!
An all-you-can-eat banquet to celebrate!
It's been two hours since they left Akasaka
The fierce battle is finally reaching its climax!
Who's gonna show up before the others?!
Ah! I see a car!
I can see a car!
*FIRST TEAM
Who's gonna be the first team to show up?
Heated Discussion! Right answers 'til the next morning!
The eight of them are offered a topic,
they have to debate to choose the right answer
They'll have a debate over a certain topic
until they can get to the correct answer
Which correct answer will they reveal tonight?!
Which correct answer will they reveal tonight?
Let's move on, here's our next question
What's the character kids love the most
which starts with the syllabe "to"?
Voice: Yuko Aoki (TBS Announcer)
Huh?!    - There are a lot, actually...
What's the character kids love the most
which starts with the syllabe "to"?
Tori (a bird)?
A bird?!
We're talking about characters!
That's just an animal
The hell is wrong with you?
It's a bird!
It's a bird! You know, they say it
A character?
I wish there would be more syllabes...
I'm not really sure
What do you mean?
I have no idea, really
What's wrong?     - I made my decision
I'm sure it's this one!
Wanna go first?
Sure, why not...
He didn't seem really sure about it
Ohtake
Mimura
Udo
Amano
Hotohara
Miyasako
Matsumoto
Hamada
Heated discussion!
Right answers
'til the next morning!
It's Tokoton Toshiko
Tokoton Toshiko
Who?!
What the?
Which character is it?!
What's that?
Tokoton Toshiko, it's a real thing
Ah, from the 4-panels manga?
Tokoton Toshiko?
And it's the most liked by kids??
I think that's the number one pick for kids nowadays...
That's the one barber shops have...
He's right
I've never heard my daughter say
Tokoton Toshiko not even once in my life!
That's why you were so quick at it
- I think it's this one
Ohtake
Mimura
Udo
Amano
Hotohara
Miyasako
Matsumoto
Hamada
Heated discussion!
Right answers
'til the next morning!
Tokoton Toshiko
I think it's this one
Oh! You're right!
Totoro
I wrote the same!
- I see, makes sense...
Totoro
It starts with "to" even if you add "Tonari no"!
- You're right
Well, the same goes for Tokoton Toshiko!
It's fine as "Toshiko" alone too
Of course it's not Tokoton Toshiko
"Toshiko" alone isn't the right answer too!
Toshiko...
"Tonari no Toshiko" works fine too!
You don't know if Toshiko is your neighbor, do you?!
I mean, are you sure she's not your neighbor?
- Shut the fuck up!
Totoro, huh...
- I think we got it, what do you think?
Toshiko~
I mean, everybody knows him, right?
Everyone is familiar with it, right?
Toshiko~
You seriously need to shut up
He's lost it
My Neighbor Toshiko~
Isn't that the main theme from Totoro?
Of course it is... Come on, next up
Come on, Hotohara
Ohtake
Mimura
Udo
Amano
Hotohara
Miyasako
Matsumoto
Hamada
Heated discussion!
Right answers
'til the next morning!
Tokoton Toshiko
Totoro
I went for Thomas
Oh! Me too!
Thomas
That one doesn't count
But it's "The Tank Engine"...
- Yeah, that comes first
Makes sense...
We didn't get a correct answer, right?
How about we go for Totoro?
No way, no way, no way, wait a sec
Are you gonna fight for your answer?
Well, if that's it...
How about the number of to's in it?
Number of "tos"?
You only have 2 "to"s in Totoro
But Tokoton Toshiko, on the other hand...
Has three tos in its name!
Is this what you're going for?
Are you that desperate?
The number of "to"s?
With "tonari to" it's a tie!
Something's definitely wrong with him!
Miyasako, please, beat me up for good!
Alright, Totoro wins!
Alright, I admit defeat
And so, the character starting with "to" kids love the most...
What's the character kids love the most which starts with the syllabe "to"?
Correct answer: Totoro
Is Totoro, that's the correct answer!
No-SATNAV Race
Second round - Big battle!
Big close contest for this 2nd round of No-SATNAV race!
No-SATNAV Race
Second round - Big battle!
I'd say... about 5km
Are you kidding me?!
Aiming for their goal by relying on passerbies!
Reach the goal by relying on pedestrians!
Their goal is King of Gyoza in Musashi Kosugi
It's been 2 hours since they started,
who will be the first team to show up?
Ah! I see a car! I can see a car!
Team Mimura
First team arrived!
The first car to show up is the black one,
the one belonging to Team Mimura!
Let's see...
There it is!
Where is it?
- It's right in front of us!
The parking lot is full!
I can't get inside the parking area
It's right there! Park over there!
Just go there
Come on! Quick!
- No, I can't...
It's fine!
- I don't think it is
Shit, no place to park here too!
It's full!
Full?
- But...
Why is every parking lot full?
Finally they spot King of Gyoza, their goal!
Finally
King of Gyoza
was spotted!
But every parking area around is full
Every parking area around it is full...
Around the same time, before Team Ohtake's eyes...
Ah! I can see it!
There it is! It's King of Gyoza!
- There it is!
I can see it! We just have to park the car now!
- Come on, quick!
I don't see a single parking spot
No way!
Two teams have found it around the same moment!
Two teams just found King of Gyoza
around the same time!
They stopped in two different parking spots
Who will be
the first team to enter the shop?!
Which team will be the first one to get in?
Who will be
the first team to enter the shop?!
We did it!
- Alright!
No way! We made it!
Let's cross it together!
Good job!
We did it!
You're the first team to get here!
Team Ohtake
First place:
We're incredible!
- I'm so happy!
We did it!
- We won!
Being the first team to arrive, you can eat and drink
everything on the table, as much as you want
You can also order more if you want to
Please, enjoy your banquet!
Thank you!
Cheers!
Yay, cheers!
Delicious!
Enjoying the taste of victory
Team Ohtake enjoys the taste of victory
And, a few moments later...
Alright!
Oh yeah!
Good job!
- Oh shit! We're second!
Second place goes to Team Mimura!    - We did it!
Team Mimura
Second place:
We did it!
yay!
I really thought we were done for!
Are you for real?
But here you are!
I got completely lost!
Same for you guys, please enjoy your banquet!
You can order as much as you want
That's great, isn't it?
Celebratory banquet for the 2nd team too
Everything they order is on the last team
Please enjoy the feast, Team Mimura!
Meanwhile, the tailender Team Matsumoto...
At the same time...
Shit, this road just keeps on going!
What?! That can't be good!
This isn't good news
Hey, isn't this Tomei Highway?
We're heading to Tomei now
Turn left and go back
- No way...
We're gonna end up in Aichi!
- We're doing really bad, aren't we?
The hell is going on?!
- Hey, Matsumoto!
You gotta be kidding me...
The team is getting further away from their goal
Musashi Kosugi is now far, far away...
And then, the sun sets
The banquet is over
By now, the banquet is already over
Both teams ate as much as they could
Both teams ate up to their fullest
Tired of waiting, Hotohara decides to call Matsumoto
2-times champion Hotohara hits up Matsumoto on the phone
I knew it would end like this
Yeah, I wonder where did they end up to
You've finished eating already?!
Matsumoto is in an unexpected place! & paying up
TYPESET & QC BY Kedomas
TRANSLATION & EDIT BY Shion
VISIT SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM FOR MORE GAKI!
FOLLOW @SHIONNOTSUKAI ON TWITTER / FB FOR UPDATES!
AND IF YOU WANT TO SHOW SUPPORT, YOU CAN DONATE ON
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI OR PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI !
VISIT SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM FOR MORE GAKI!
FOLLOW @SHIONNOTSUKAI ON TWITTER / FB FOR UPDATES!
AND IF YOU WANT TO SHOW SUPPORT, YOU CAN DONATE ON
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI OR PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI !
The party ends without Team Matsumoto showing up
Both teams ate up to their fullest
2-times champion Hotohara hits up Matsumoto on the phone
And so, Hotohara decides to call Matsumoto
Alright, I'll call Matsumoto
- I knew it would end like this
Yeah, I wonder where did they end up to
This isn't gonna be good news, is it?
Yeah, definitely
- I'd hate it...
Maybe someone already arrived?
Which one is it?
- Orange car
Orange car...
- Hello?
Hello? Where are you now, Matsumoto?
Well...
I think we're almost there, I guess...
Does he mean this shop? Or the area?
- We're...
Huh? So you're close?
Yeah, we're chatting about what we should order
Virtually, we're already there!
Please say something, Hoto-chan
R-Right, Matsumoto...
Yes?
Actually...
We're all already here at the shop
Are you kidding me?
Matsumoto, we already placed our orders
You're kidding me, right?
Not only that...ù
He said both teams already arrived!
The banquet has already started
- Really?!
No way!
Is this the ending part?!
How many minutes ago did you get there?
We arrived about 1 hour ago!
One hour ago?!
Isn't that the King of Gyoza?
Huh?
I think it's--- huh...
We just saw a King of Gyoza right now
Don't go away, please!
Wait for us!
I can see the shop! Isn't that it?
This sucks!
Is the shop like, under a railway?
It's in Musashi Kosugi, duh
Under a girder bridge, right?
- Musashi...
- Yeah, it's under a girder bridge
It says "Musashi Shinshiro"
- "Musashi Shinshiro"...
Ah, sorry, we're in Musashi Shinshiro
Where the hell is that?! Never heard of it!
Where are you going?!
Wait a second, are you kidding me?
Wait for us, we're definitely getting there!
Hey, you!
Hoto-chan!
30 minutes later
And then, 30 minutes later...
TRANSLATION & EDIT BY SHION | TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS  | FOLLOW ME ON: TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI OR FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI | IF YOU WANT TO SUPPORT THIS NO-PROFIT SUB PROJECT, YOU CAN DONATE ON KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI OR SUBSSCRIBE TO PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
Team Matsumoto (last) finally arrives!
Now we'll reveal how much they'll have to pay
This show was brought to you by Shion
And, of course, by our Kedomas
Are you kidding me?!
This is just 2012 promo stuff I'm not gonna translate!
If you love what you're watching, please share your love for it <3
No way...
- I can't believe it!
This is a joke, right?
The total is 61.335 yen
This isn't even funny anymore
- How much did they eat?!