Translation by typesoshee
Timing & Typesetting by BassGNT
On tonight’s “Lincoln,” we present in full the incident that stirred all of Japan!
May 4th, Saturday, 1PM
Setagaya Kinuta Studio
Ten days ago, Japanese internet users were in a tumult.
The incident that was even covered by Yahoo! News...
We present the whole truth tonight!
The members are made to wait in a renewed classroom set of “The Lecturer".
Hey, everyone, look!
He opened the door so hard
he surprised himself.
It’s like how an animal reacts.
He can’t gauge himself.
He went “boom!” and he’s the one most freaked out.
He was the closest to the door.  Because the “boom!” was closest to him.
Quiet!
Changed to a teacher position from today
Mr. Hamada Masatoshi
Hamada is the teacher? Mr. Hamada?
Good morning.
He used to sit with us together, right!?
Ok, I mean, good morning, but, you’re always sitting here, right?
From this time, this is “The New Lecturer,” so…
But if Mr. Hamada is the teacher, then that’s going to be for real.
A real lecture?
No… I’m going to be your homeroom teacher.
And for every episode a special lecturer will be coming.
So there won’t be that strong… “pressure” coming from the homeroom teacher then?
That will depend on the time and place.
Can't say there won't be.
That can’t be helped.
What…
The classroom has been renovated and improved.
Everyone’s uniforms, as well, from those dirty tracksuits you had before.
Like private school.
It’s like those nice ones that rich kids wear, right?
It looks smart.
And now for our special lecturer.
Please come in!
Who is the new lecturer?
Bam!
Ok!
The other door, the other door.
Our teacher is Miss Rola!
Tonight’s lecturer, looking surprisingly good in a teacher’s outfit is the 23-year-old Rola.
Today's special lecturer
Miss Rola
What sort of lecture will they receive from a teacher who is twenty years younger than them?
I am angry today!
You’re not angry at all!
I am! Huff, puff…
The teacher is angry. Listen properly.
You’re angry at us?
That’s right!
We haven’t done anything to be angered at.
You have!  First, here I go.
“First, here I go….”
The teacher is speaking!
Ok. This is my name.
Rola
We know…
You’re pretty famous.
I say “Rola” more than “Saijo Hideki”. Really.
Starting from Miyasako, please introduce yourself.
Whoa, that’s scary.
A self-introduction?
Yup.
Like where do you live…
Personal information like that!?
The teacher told you to do it!
Personal information like that in a self-introduction!?
Your address! Say your address!
Mr. Mimura! A self-introduction.
What food do you like?
Um, sukiyaki
I love sukiyaki, too!
Really?
Do you dip it in egg when you eat it?
An explanation of sukiyaki?
Really nice.
Matsumoto!
Tell us like where you grew up…
Like where you grew up or I mean,
Ok, where did you go for Golden Week?
That’s totally different!
Thas has nothing to do with that!
Where I grew up?
What he did for Golden Week, is what you’d like to ask?
Yeah, I'm curious!
For Golden Week?
I was at home at times, I went to the park as well at times…
Huh? Which park?
I don’t know the exact name of the park.
It wasn’t a famous park or anything.
Oh, really. Did you like jump-rope or— were you playing a lot there?
It’s not like he went there alone!
What did you play there?
Well, I mean, I brought my daughter there...
What, you have a daughter?
Do you know absolutely nothing about me?!
Wow!
That’s cute!
Why would he go to the park alone to play jump-rope at his age?
That’s really nice.
Rola, on her A-game, thoroughly teases the members at her own pace.  She then reveals the topic of tonight’s lecture.
What I am angrily huffing and puffing about is...
Yes, what is it?
She’s going to write.
Yup.
Just erase it if you want to.
She has long legs.
Do you know this?
Twitter.
Yeah, Twitter. Heard of it.
In English, it’s “Twitter.”
Whoa.
What’s that about?  I didn’t know you had that kind of thing going on.
That’s right.
Are you all on Twitter?
People who are on Twitter?
Just Miyasako?
Just me?
I have been on Twitter before!
I’m not on it anymore!
So that’s just Miyasako, then.
The others aren’t doing it.
I really have no clue how it works.
I see!
Teacher, what are you "huffing and puffing" angrily about?
Because everyone isn't on Twitter !
Who wouldn’t be on Twitter in this day and age?  That's what she’s angry about.
You’re all behind the times.
So today I’m here to force everyone to get on Twitter !
Social media evolves at a dizzying pace.
The Lincoln members have not been paying attention and have been left behind by technology.
This cannot continue!
So this episode, Rola’s lecture is: “Let’s all start Twitter.”
Japanese Twitter Users With The Most Followers
(as of May 4th, 2013)
Ariyoshi Hiroiki
Son Masayoshi
Shinoda Mariko
Rola
Kyary Pamyu Pamyu
Rola is actually one of the most popular Twitter users in Japan,
having the fourth-most Twitter followers in Japan after people like Ariyoshi and Son Masayoshi.
Rola, with her credentials of 1,440,000 followers, brings a revolution to Lincoln!
And then...
Everyone, don’t be like Mr. Matsumoto, ok?
Matsumoto embarrasses himself with his first tweet!
I want to tweet!
You’re tweeting too much.
Their trials and tribulations of using Twitter for the first time!
These middle-aged comedians have avoided the internet until now –
we document their foray into Twitter.
It’s unbelievable that Mr. Matsumoto would be on Twitter.
The Twitter incident that believe-it-or-not was taken up by Yahoo! News – here we present in full.
Because I love Lincoln
A breath of fresh air to Lincoln: Rola’s "The New Lecturer."
The
New
Lecturer
~The Rola Episode~
So why are you on Twitter, Mr. Miyasako?
There was a TV program that…
that asked, would you try this for a segment?
Oh, that’s how—
That’s how I started and—
and Hoto quit after a while.
Why did you quit?
I hadn’t gone golfing in a while so I tweeted, “I want to go golfing.”
Then I got a reply from someone I didn’t know who said, “That’d be wasted on a guy like you.”
So I got pissed, threw it away,
.
and I quit.
No wonder he quit.
Yeah, that’s uncalled for.
That’s how I quit.
That makes sense.
No way you deserved to have that, come on!
No way.
That’s the thing.
That sort of thing could happen, which is
why I don’t really want to do it either.
Oh, really.  I see.
Other than Miyasako, it seems that people have a negative view of the Twitter experience.
So Rola starts by teaching the positives of the Twitter experience.
So these are the positives of the Twitter experience according to the teacher.
Yes.
Take a look.
Circle number one:
Don’t need that part.
You can make friends.
Circle number two:
You get information.
Like current events, political things— you would want to get the news about that, right?
You can really get updated on things like that.
It’ll tell us about that?
Yup, it will.
Circle number three: You can become popular.
What? Really?
Become popular?
Among whom?
Among the people who are, like, walking around on the street.
I think there are more people who aren’t walking around on the street.
Miyasako, the only one of us on Twitter, would you say these are right?
Yes, things that you really wouldn’t know about.
For example, I might say “I went to a really good ramen place.”
Then replies like “This other place is good”, “This place is better,” information like that comes right to you all at once.
In general, most of it is messages of support!
Most of it is positive.
Yeah, it is.
How often do you tweet, Miss Rola?
Hmm, I haven't tweeted at all these couple of days.
And then you’re telling everyone to “Go, go do Twitter!”?
That doesn’t make sense.
Don’t you tweet a lot?
It doesn’t seem like simply tweeting a lot will always increase your number of followers.
What are show businesses personalities on Twitter with a lot of followers tweeting about?
Translation by typesoshee
Timing & Typesetting by BassGNT
Let’s look at the tweets of popular Twitter users.
Now, everyone, are you curious about what
Miss Rola tweets about?
This is Miss Rola, the fourth most popular Twitter user.
It can be short, right?
That’s right.
Mr. Miyasako, what does this part here mean?
That’s where a follower, a regular person, is asking a question.
This is what someone wrote to me.
Don’t say it first!
Oh, sorry.
Someone said “If you use English first, you lose,” and you replied with “Ok” .
So you lost there as a joke, ahh.
“I’m starting to go bald.  What do I do?  Rola, tell me!”
Ahh! Just stick something on there~.
How crude!
Well, there is some truth there!
Yup.
Lastly, “What is that on Mr. Gushiken’s head?"*
*Gushiken Yoko is a former Japanese boxer.
Broccoli!
This is like ogiri  !
This, this is the fourth most popular Twitter user.
Fourth place in the country.
It’s like ogiri, so, it’s tiring, you know?
To see what popular users are tweeting…
For example, this person.
Oh, RG is popular!
Believe it or not.
He’s popular for his “Did you ever notice”-type of jokes.
“A ‘Did you ever notice’ joke for this once-in-a-decade cold wave we're having, please!”, someone tweeted him.
RG replied,
“The news on TV tends to show shots of people slipping on frozen sidewalks.”
So you can just give a straight answer.
For us in the business, it wasn’t that funny.  But for regular people, maybe…
It was a very RG-type of joke.
“A conveyor belt sushi ‘Did you ever notice’ joke, please.”
“Tends to expand the possibilities of mayonnaise.”
They’re getting better!
One more person.  Please take a look at this.
Oh, Wakky.
Oh, Wakky is on, too!
Wakky is popular for his face bits.
You can post photos, too?
Yes, you can!
I see.
“I’m feeling down this morning.  Cheer me up!”
Wakky replies with the title “Face!”
He looks like he's giving it his all.
He put some time into that!
Eww.
He's giving it his all!
Even if I could do that face,  I probably wouldn’t do it!
“Nothing much happened today, so can I get a 'nothing' face?”  He replied with “Face!”
That’s definitely a "nothing" face.
Other than those, there were requests like,
“Please give me a face that will energize me” and “Congratulate me on my birthday” to which Wakky gave his faces with full effort.
He put this much in
and he has 18,000 followers.
Even after giving it his all like that?
I haven’t done anything in years.
He has less followers than Hoto.
Even though he’s putting that much effort into these?
But it's amazing!
It’s hard to tell what really works.
So as everyone knows, Miyasako is also on Twitter. You want to see Miyasako’s Twitter as well, right?
Yeah, I want to see Miyasako’s.
Miyasako is the only one of the members that's on Twitter.
Let's take a look at his tweets, with special narration.
I tweet about once every few days.
Location-tion shooting from the morning.
The great weather makes the location-tion shooting great.
I’m excited about what I might encounter-tion!!
I've been saying
-tion-tion repeatedly,
but not because I actually think it’s funny.
It’s just that I haven’t gotten any sleep so I just feel like thaa~t
thaa~t…
Mr. Matsumoto, you have a "nothing" face...
You saw this a while ago, right?
First of all,
can I have a chat with the guy doing the narrating?!
Sit down.
Settle down!
That’s not Miyasako?  I thought it might be Miyasako’s voice.
Come on, that’s not my voice!
It sounded similar.
I only feel ill will from him.
There’s more.  Take a look.
Going for a haircut now.
I always think about going for a really different style,
but in the end I just settle with something safe.
Because I’m scared of the waiting time of being bummed until my hair grows back.
Am I a scaredy-cat?
Eww! Eww!
Scaredy-cat?
Hot, hot.  I feel hot.
Gross.
You can write this much if you want, too.
Disgusting.
It’s a tweet!
Tweets are known as whispers in Japanese.
Right!  Even a short —  what’s that?
It’s disgusting, isn’t it?
Keep that locked up inside yourself!
It’s not like I was specifically telling someone that.
It’s an example.
It’s supposed to be like talking to yourself in a way...
There are those like these and those like — one more here!
I've had enough, come on.
Between shooting, a chapter in my life: Drinking an ice coffee at
the Starbucks at North Shore, Hawai'i.
Eww!  Eww!
Killed it!
Hey!
A picture post!
Narcissistic!
What do you think, Miss Rola?
Gross!
Aloha...
It’s aloha.  In Hawai’i.
Isn’t the aloha thing like this?
That was Stan Hansen.
If you’re gonna do it, do it right.
I shouldn’t have tried something I'm not familiar with...
There are mistakes like these as well!
I made a mistake -tion.
I made a mistake-tion!
Ok, already!
So we’ve shown you many examples.
By the way, we also have Hoto’s.
These are fine.
They’re normal, right?
“Today at Kumamoto. It’s been a while. I’m excited. I want to be kind.”
“Today, work at Okinawa. I’ll do my best. I’ve had to go to a lot of places this week. But it’s fun, so it’s all right. I want to be kind!”
“In Sapporo. The weather is… I’m bummed. Can’t be helped. I want to be kind!”
That has nothing to do with the weather.
So he puts it at the end as a kind of signature!
There are a lot of people who do that.
A signature phrase at the end.
So it’s your signature!
Yes, as a signature.
So if you type in “I wa”— the rest appears on your screen.
Since it's your signature.
Yes, it comes up.
Finally, we have the members start Twitter.
First, registering an account.
So now, we would like everyone to register!
That’s ok, right, teacher?
Yup.
So we’re really going to do it?
Here, everyone.
An “account,” right?
That... sort of thing, yeah.
The teacher doesn’t really know…
Is it already done for us?
Won’t this become quite a stir in the news?!
It will!
We’ve never done anything like that.
That all the Lincoln members started Twitter ?
Yeah, fine, everyone just get on Yahoo! News for that!
It will really get on Yahoo! News.
It really will get on the news.
Yeah, it will.
I think it really will.
To start Twitter, enter these four items.
The username, like Miyasako’s “motohage” (meaning ex-baldy*), is like your nickname on Twitter.
*Miyasako is known for losing hair and then getting hair loss treatment
It needs a sense of style, so we ask the teacher to give them out.
Because you’re bald, “Matsu Matsu Baldy.”
So Mr. Matsumoto, you’re Matsu Matsu Baldy.
This has to be in Latin characters, right?
Now, for Mimura.
Umm.
“Hentai Mimura”
With “Mimura?”
The teacher is telling you.
You’re already putting in “Mimura” in there.
The teacher said it. Please put in “Hentai Mimura.”
Ok, for Amano.
“Forever Alone Amano”
I have to put my name in there, too?
They then took each other’s photographs that will be shown next to their tweets.
Lemme see!
I made it with “tu,” but that’s ok, right?
This is wrong. Wait.
Is “tsu” better?
Do you not know English?
You’re being laughed at.
No, I mean, it doesn’t have to be “tsu,” right?
No, “tsu” is better!
Really?
Yeah.
Thus, everyone’s registrations were completed.
Initially registered with “tu,” Matsumoto re-registered with “tsu.”
Otake is “Take Take Baked Potato,” Hotohara is “The Three Kappa Brothers,” and Udo is “Udo Udo Acorn.”
Next are the members’ commemorative first tweets.
Now we will do everyone’s commemorative first tweets.
Here we go.
First, write something like “I started Twitter!”
How do you do it?
We push the button that says “tweet?"
But it’s on Miyasako’s page right now!
Yeah, we’re on Miyasako’s page.
How do you do this?
Wait, wait, on my page, see --
Please wait for a moment.
We are currently doing the first tweet!
Just for a moment.
After this, Matsumoto embarrasses himself with his first tweet!
Now we will do everyone’s commemorative first tweets.
Here we go.
We can write anything we want-tion?
-tion?
That’s my thing, ok?
"-tion" is forbidden!
He said it. That’s Miyasako’s thing.
Everyone nervously enters their first tweets.
This will go out to everyone?
Yup
It’s nerve-wracking, doesn’t it?
Yeah, it is.
Star comedian Matsumoto’s first tweet is this:
Here’s Mr. Matsumoto’s.
Mine is normal!
Here it is.  “I have debuted.”
That’s so ordinary!
I don’t know!
This isn’t good?
That’s no good!
This is bad!
No, no, no!
I don’t understand!
Ah!~
Then what do we do? What do we do?
After the panicking Matsumoto, Mimura’s first tweet is:
Let’s look at Mimura’s then.
Ok.
Ok.  “This is the real Mimura.  I will do my best!”
Wow. That wasn’t funny!
That was me making a declaration!
Miss Rola, is this good?
This is better than the last one.
It has two phrases and feels fine!
It has two phrases so it’s ok.
Yup.
Let’s look at Amano’s.
Mine…
Here.  “I am starting Twitter.  This is the real me.  I am 43 years old and I like cooking and female broadcasters.”
Really good! Totally not ordinary at all!
Ok, let’s look at Udo’s as well.
“Amano~!  It’s the real me!”
Why are you tweeting at me?
Just tell me here.  Don’t tweet at this distance.
Good, good.
Hoto’s.
“I’m tweeting after a long while.  I want to be kind.”
This sort of thing, right?
It's good!
Now, Otake’s, too.
With Otake’s style.
“I will start.  I will start?”
He already quit!
Your premise is that you’re quitting!
I feel self-conscious.
This is embarrassing!
Everyone,
don’t be like Mr. Matsumoto, ok?
A bad example.
I feel this feeling of rejection.
I feel like I’m going to get a rashes as a reaction to all of this.
It’s annoying to have to think up something!
I don’t like how even something like this feels like work!
Yes.
We have already started with this
there might be reactions out there.
You might get tweeted at!
Are there any?
Sorry, I’d like to tweet, “I have retired.”
You’re retiring after three minutes?
Thus, they debuted on Twitter. But this is just the beginning of their Twitter lives.
Next:
We finished our first tweets so let’s all take photos!
First, let’s take a photo of Mr. Hamada!
Huh?
I’ve got nothing to do with this.
Let’s all take whatever photo of Mr. Hamada we want and then post it.
Take them in different poses.
Why do I have to get my photo taken by these kids and put on Twitter?...
That’s really close!
The lower lip? Very nice.
This is nice!
What do you mean it's “nice?”
Can you wink?
Scary. I got a scary one!
Adding a caption to a photo of Hamada and then tweeting...
First, Otake’s photo of Hamada:
Translation by typesoshee
Timing & Typesetting by BassGNT
“This is Mr. Hamada when he isn’t pissed.”
He’s totally pissed.
This is Mr. Hamada when he isn’t pissed?
So this is Otake’s.
So this sort of thing.
Here’s Mr. Matsumoto’s!
“This is our gorilla.”
This sort of thing, everyone.
That’s quite on the human-side!
He loves ketchup!
########################
The members’ photos have been posted on to Twitter.
This is what you call a monster.
###########################
However,
Miss Rola didn’t want to just teach how to use Twitter.
The real subject of this episode will now be presented to the members.
Now, we will have a competition on who will get the most followers.
We do these frequently?
How long should we do this?
About one week!
Longer than one week, but first, just one week.
Does something happen if you get last place?
There will be a batsu game for the last place!
Good thing I’ve been doing Twitter.
Miyasako has already been doing Twitter, so he’s not part of it.
But Mr. Otohara will be part of it!
It’s “Ho-”, ok!
Of “Ha hi hu he ho.”
Yes, Mr. Hotohara.
So Hoto —
What happens for me?
The 60,000  followers I had?
It’ll be a perfect handicap for you!
Hey. That’s enough from you!
Thus, a one week competition of who will get the most followers starts.
Tweets get sent over the whole world…
What kind of tweets will they make?
Did Mr. Hamada hit you?*
*There is a Japanese TV meme that because of Hamada’s celebrity power in show business, if you are a newcomer and Hamada comedically hits you on TV, that moment will be your ticket to success and fame.
#######################
First, the members’ strategy is to have Miss Rola spread their tweets to her 1,440,000 followers.
Did Mr. Hamada hit you?*
Not Otohara but Hotohara.
I want to be kind.
###############################
###################
#######################
Did Mr. Hamada hit you?*
Not Otohara but Hotohara.
I want to be kind.
Rola’s stylish glasses are cute!
I want to be kind!
###########################
####################
###############################
###################
#######################
Did Mr. Hamada hit you?*
Not Otohara but Hotohara.
I want to be kind.
Rola’s stylish glasses are cute!
I want to be kind!
Ro-la! I-t’s! U-do!
########################
###########################
####################
###############################
###################
#######################
The members begin to tweet to Rola.
Did Mr. Hamada hit you?*
Not Otohara but Hotohara.
I want to be kind.
Rola’s stylish glasses are cute!
I want to be kind!
Ro-la! I-t’s! U-do!
Rola. Roller?
####################
########################
###########################
####################
###############################
###################
#######################
Did Mr. Hamada hit you?*
Not Otohara but Hotohara.
I want to be kind.
Rola’s stylish glasses are cute!
I want to be kind!
Ro-la! I-t’s! U-do!
Rola. Roller?
I’m a little hungry.
What’s good for this sort of thing?
###############
############################
####################
########################
###########################
####################
###############################
###################
#######################
Oh, I got something from Mr. Matsumoto.
You got something, right?
Here.  “I’m a little hungry.  What’s good for this sort of thing?”, he says!
Uh oh! Uh oh! Why did she say it like that?
Why do you seem to have this thing against Matsumoto?
Here I go. I’m going to do it! Everyone’s going to see it.
Once Rola retweets the members’ tweets to her followers, reactions to the members’ tweets come in quickly.
We have a reply to Mr. Matsumoto from a regular person!
“Is this the real Ma-chan?”
Wow.
Yes!
Let’s reply to this!
Wow, that guy’s lucky.
Would it be bad if I was abusive towards him?
What sort of abuse?
He said “Is this the real Ma-chan?”  Why would you reply to that with abuse?
I just did it.
To “Is this the real Mr. Matsumoto”:
The real one. I want to be kind.
My thing.  “I want to be kind,” that’s my thing.
Oh, really?
You didn’t say that.
Miyasako said before that “-tion” is only his thing.
I said the “-tion” thing is only my thing.
You didn’t say “I want to be kind” is only your thing!
But, wait,
isn’t that the rule?!
Sorry, sorry about that.
I just, didn’t really understand...
For people who don’t know what’s going on here they must be like
“What the hell is Matsumoto saying?!”
I got tweets as well, saying...
“Rola, you’re following too many fake accounts!”
They’re not trusted yet!
We’re not fake!
If you say “They’re real,” that would increase our followers?
Yes.
It’s going up.
Wow.
Wow, Mr. Matsumoto.
Otake is already at 300!
They trust you.
Wow
Wow, it went up again.
It went right up to 460.
500, wow.
The number of followers is already increasing.
The members are embarking on a one week experience never done before.
Ok, everyone, good luck on your one week!
Your followers will decrease if you don’t tweet, so tweet everyday.
And if I see them and think they’re good, I’ll retweet them!
There you go.
So that means that that will increase your followers.
Ok, bye everyone!
You’re leaving just like that?
Bye, take care!
Good luck on your one week!
Everyone’s beginning Twitter now starts to create a stir!
At the dressing room after shooting ended, Otake takes a photo of Miyasako in his personal attire.
Got it. And then?
My leopard-skin is gonna be posted!
What caption will Otake add regarding Miyasako’s unique style of clothes?
It’s sent.
That's sent?
Rod Miyasako Stewart
There’s a worry whether it was sent or not, you know.
Then...
10,000 people.
The leopard-skin went to 10,000 people.
10,000 people?
It amazes me. I don’t really understand it,
but to think that at this moment, a lot of people are looking at it!
Meanwhile, at Matsumoto’s dressing room…
So it means there might be replies to this.
I’m a little hungry.
What’s good for this sort of thing?
#################
##############################
A reply has come to the tweet from before.
I’m a little hungry.
What’s good for this sort of thing?
How about a pastry?
################
##############################
#############################
To do that, I go, here, right?
To “How about a pastry?”  I do this, right?
And then I press tweet?
Yes, on the upper right.
Like custard?
How about a pastry?
I’m a little hungry.
What’s good for this sort of thing?
Like custard?
#############################
################
##############################
#####################
Oh, the tweet is sending.
Yes.
Just from this conversation about pastries…
It’s already at 17,000 people. Wow
It’s at 17,000…
Oh, it’s coming in.
What kind of tweets will Matsumoto make in the future?
And then...
“I’m gonna be tsukkomi-ing.”
Mimura’s “I’m gonna be tsukkomi-ing” tweet…
I’ll make it “I’m gonna be tsukkomi-ing something crazy vicious! Christmas!”
It’s so bad they might just take me out of the competition.
I’m gonna be tsukkomi-ing
something crazy vicious!
Christmas!
I’m gonna be tsukkomi-ing something###
crazy vicious! Christmas!###
Like the saying,
“Regret never comes
beforehand,” you know…
I might regret this.
Like, “No, no, I was just joking.”  “I was just joking about the ‘Christmas’ part.”
Now, I’m going to send this to Amano.
Amano~!
Can I come over now?
Amano~!######
Can I come over now? #######
Still using it like texting…
This is fine, right?
Yesterday’s homemade char siu!
Can you guess what I used this to make?
Yesterday’s homemade char siu!#########
Can you guess what I used this to make?  #########
Meanwhile, using his cooking skills, Amano tweets in a quiz form.
In reply to this…
Here.
The char siu.
So I should enter “char siu rice bowl” to this?
Unfortunately, it was ramen.
So I should enter “ramen.”
Yeah, yeah.
No, then I’m just doing this with you!
Not between us, tweet about your own stuff!
I’ll spread the word, then, to everyone.
Wow, there are a lot of replies!
Because I spread it to everyone!
That makes it sound like it was thanks to you!
Retweet means to spread it out?
Yes, retweet means to spread it out.
Wow, Mr. Matsumoto is tweeting!
He says “The correct answer was Yo-chan Squid.”
He’s already really into it.
He’s giving out quiz questions.
Mr. Matsumoto’s giving out quiz questions!
Meanwhile, at Matsumoto’s dressing room...
3, 2, 1, OK.
Got it.
was taking a picture of himself in the middle of changing.
A photo in his underpants.
From a different angle…
and just in case, another shot.
What will Matsumoto tweet...
“Surprisingly, zebra pants.”
That’s fine, right?
Tweet.
Ok, there we go.
Matsumoto actually gives out a fan service photo.
And with this photo, the number of his followers increases dramatically.
Starting from that night, the members began to tweet regularly.
Trying a smile after taking a bath.
Trying a smile after taking a bath.#####
Showing a private side that they don’t often show,
Trying a smile after taking a bath.
Trying a smile after taking a bath.#######
When exposed to a new culture, I get sleepy.
I’m going to sleep.
When exposed to a new culture, I get sleepy.##############
I’m going to sleep. ####################################
Trying a smile after taking a bath.
Trying a smile after taking a bath.######
When exposed to a new culture, I get sleepy.
I’m going to sleep.
When exposed to a new culture, I get sleepy.##############
I’m going to sleep. ####################################
I have all these same ones. One of them is red.
I have all these same ones. One of them is red. ########
or describing something in their home,
I have all these same ones. One of them is red.
I have all these same ones. One of them is red. #######
*Himura Yuki is a comedian known for his impression of sumo wrestler Takanohana Koji as a child.
My one-year-old daughter has an 80% chance of
getting glued to the TV when Mr. Himura comes on!*
I want to be a kind, child Takanohana.
My one-year-old daughter has an 80% chance of
getting glued to the TV when Mr. Himura comes on!* #####
I want to be a kind, child Takanohana.#################
or making some sort of mysterious report,
A year has passed since I got a
mole beside my left nipple! Amano~!
A year has passed since I got a#################
mole beside my left nipple! #####################Amano~!
A year has passed since I got a
mole beside my left nipple! Amano~!
A year has passed since I got a#################
mole beside my left nipple! #####################Amano~!
An aristocrat bachelor’s night. I think I’ll get a good
sweat going for this evening.
An aristocrat bachelor’s night. I think I’ll get a good#########
sweat going for this evening.   ##########################
Furthermore, on Amano…
This is horrible.
When Mr. Matsumoto, right off the bat,
gave me an ogiri question, I thought, “Come on.
With this many other 'boke’s, don’t go to me.”
What I made with my homemade char siu
yesterday by the way was char siu noodles!
What I made with my homemade char siu####
yesterday by the way was char siu noodles!##########
To Amano’s tweet about making char siu noodles,
What I made with my homemade char siu
yesterday by the way was char siu noodles!
What I made with my homemade char siu####
yesterday by the way was char siu noodles!##########
Ogiri time. What flavor is it?
Ogiri time. What flavor is it? #########
Matsumoto suddenly gives out an origi question.
Mitsukan pork bone broth soy sauce flavor.
To this, Amano answers referring to a TV commercial that he himself appears in
The correct answer is… Mitsukan pork bone broth
soy sauce flavor. Amano~! You got it!
The correct answer is… Mitsukan pork bone broth ###########
soy sauce flavor. Amano~! You got it!#
and gets a “well done” from Matsumoto.
My mind was seriously running on full cylinders that time.
I was thinking “This is gonna be hell
if this keeps going on!”
And Matsumoto as well…
I’m drunk.
Shows himself getting a bit tipsy with a cute tweet.
This cute tweet from Matsumoto greatly increases his follower numbers.
By the next day, Matsumoto starting Twitter is picked up by the news
This here “I’m drunk” (Matsumoto’s tweet), right?
This is quite precious!
Really.
It’s unbelievable that Mr. Matsumoto would get on Twitter
I think a lot of people out there are thinking the same thing.
There will be a lot of interest in this.
When I said to my daughter,
“P down,” she said, “Huh?
What does that mean?”
It means “Sit down.”
I want to be a kind Osaka dialect.
As it becomes a societal phenomenon, Hotohara, in no hurry, tweets heartwarming moments of his family.
Amano.
What?
I was thinking of putting in a photo.
Ok.
If I do that, followers will take a look at it.
Ok, Amano.
Gee, what is this?
Here… and this…
Amano~!
Amano~!-“Now!”
Today’s glasses are like
Takeyama’s of Cunning!*
Looks like it-now!
Both of them good-now!
*Takeyama Takanori is a TV personality in a comedic duo called Cunning.
###########################
Now!
I want to tweet!
You’re tweeting too much!
This is the man who got into this the most. Mimura Masakazu.
Oe, how are you? I, am going to bed.
Oe, how are you? I, am going to bed.########
On the night of the first day, after tweeting to TV Tokyo broadcaster Oe Mariko,
Oe, how
Oe, how###
this conversation also, for some reason, was picked up by Yahoo! News.
Oe noticed!
In the middle of work. Can’t tweet.
Amano, are lava flow baths good? I mean, Amano~!
I’m connected with Becky!
Oe noticed!################
In the middle of work. Can’t tweet.
Amano, are lava flow baths good? I mean, Amano~! ####
I’m connected with Becky!  ###
Furthermore, tweeting 20 tweets right from the start,
Hey, Otake’s wife is on TV.
Tweeting on a mountain road, ughhhh!
In the car, sleepyyyyy!!!
I wanna faaaaart!
Hey, Otake’s wife is on TV. #############
Tweeting on a mountain road, ughhhh!############
In the car, sleepyyyyy!!!###############################
I wanna faaaaart!####################
he reaches 220,000 followers by the next day.
Hey, Otake’s wife is on TV.
Tweeting on a mountain road, ughhhh!
In the car, sleepyyyyy!!!
I wanna faaaaart!
Hey, Otake’s wife is on TV.##############
Tweeting on a mountain road, ughhhh!############
In the car, sleepyyyyy!!!#################################
I wanna faaaaart!######################
This egg sandwich is super good!
Translation by typesoshee
Timing & Typesetting by BassGNT
Inspired by his duo partner, Otake also…
Golden Week just ended so the sky of Tokyo was still blue.
I got it.
“Golden Week just ended so the sky of Tokyo was still blue.”
To that, someone quickly replied, “That has nothing to do with Golden Week, lol.”
But that’s not what I meant.
That’s where the fun of tweeting begins!
What?! The expert speaks!
This is where it starts!
Because during Golden Week,
the factories in Tokyo are closed,
and because there are fewer cars,
so the sky...
becomes blue.  People from other
areas might not understand,
but this is Tokyo trivia.
That’s what I meant.
So tweet that!
What was it again?
That’s how you feel out the communication!
Then they’ll say,
“Oh, Mr. Otake said something good,”
and then you get more followers!
I see.
But unless you see more of the reaction first…
because there might be people out there who
get it, so the rebuttals might come quickly.
Why, you just told me to tweet it right now!
Cancel!
You observe it for a while.
You have to understand what the followers are feeling.
There aren’t many that are replying right now!
Because you haven’t waited!
Thus, while the members were forced to start Twitter by Rola, they were enjoying it for the time being.
Then:
The competition over follower numbers revealed amazing numbers.
The results of the Twitter follower numbers competition!
It has been one week. It seems that you all were tweeting a lot.
# of Tweets
###########\
Udo
Amano
Hotohara
Otake
Mimura
Matsumoto
Udo###
Amano
Hotohara
Otake###
Mimura
Matsumo
Just one person!
That’s right.
Who got extremely into it
Yes.
Who was really feeling it.
This right here felt like my hand.
He’s definitely going to continue tweeting
even after the competition ends.
Are you going to continue?
Am I not allowed to continue?
No, no, of course you’re allowed to continue.
Let’s take a look at some of the exchanges the members had that became popular.
This tweet by Matsumoto was how it began.
I didn’t have anything to tweet about,
so being almost Hamada’s birthday, I tweeted,
“Like I got anything to do with that!”
This is where the hell started.
Everyone would— the members would tweet all these things.
These would normally go to Hamada.
But Hamada’s not on Twitter so they all came to me!
“Congratulations, Mr. Hamada!”
Since Mr. Matsumoto is the closest to Mr. Hamada.
I see.
Mimura sent one, too.
“Thanks, Mimura.  Such a happy occasion.  Like I got anything to do with that!” I tsukkomi-ed again.
A play-along tsukkomi.
The play-along tsukkomi, it keeps coming.  Udo ,all over here.  “Happy Birthday, Mr. Hamada!”
After a while, I got tired,
and I was saying “Like I got anything to do with that!”
But it still wouldn’t stop.
It still wouldn’t stop, so I just gave up and said, “I’m gonna go buy a present.”
You were broken.
He just went along with it.
But it still kept going.
It still kept going.  Here, from Amano.  From Hoto, too, I think.
Here.
“Completely late.”
“Congratulations.” There was no use, so I thought if it comes to this, “It’s a party! Don’t tell Hamada.”
“Going to bed.”  The End.
That was a sign meaning “The End.”
This whole time was really tiring.
That day was a rest day for me.
I couldn’t rest at all!
So the members had some pleasant Twitter exchanges.
There is a message from Rola for them.
Boo!
Yay! How are you?
I can’t be there today,
but I’m going to present, um, the batsu game for the person with the fewest followers now.
Last place will…
have embarrassing photos of them tweeted by everyone!
Start taking photos of the last place person and upload them.
I think Mr. Otohara will be in last place.
Mr. Otohara will be in last place~.
That’s wrong.  It’s “Ho-”, ok?  It’s “Ho-.”
See you, bye!
The batsu game is this.
Here.
The face bit?
Wakky’s thing.
Do these face bits with maximum effort.
Nine of them?
Well, all of them!
The batsu game is to do an impression of Wakky’s face bits and have them spread out on Twitter.
Once they’re circulated, there’s no taking the photos down.
And now, the competition over getting followers over one week:
presenting the first place person, who attracted an amazing number of followers:
First place is:
The first place finisher’s amazing numbers actually set a new record in Japan.
Wallpapers of the opening animation are now available on Android.
Don’t forget to watch hilarious videos from Lincoln.
First place is:
Mr. Matsumoto. Wow. In one week!
Matsumoto’s followers are still increasing and have passed 520,000.
He is the only person in Japan to have passed 520,000 followers with just 39 tweets.
Now, second place is:
Yes!
There it is.
If it keeps going like this, this is gonna be crazy.
But, really,
Miyasako’s one million followers?
That’s what's really amazing.
But that's a longer time.
You just had one week.
Third place is:
Mr. Otake.
Not bad.
300,000.
Well, Otake didn’t tweet that often.
Who will receive the batsu game!?
Fourth place is good for me!
Fourth place is:
Yes!
Uh oh.
This is bad.
So it’s one way or the other way.
We’ll uncover them in one go.
What I heard is that it’s surprisingly close!
I don’t even wanna—
This is bad!
It’s as of 4PM today.
Down to the wire.
The two left are Hoto and Amano.
Let’s uncover them in one go.
The one on the bottom is the last place person.
Open!
It’s Mr. Otohara!
It’s “Hoto-.”“Ho-.” It’s “Hoto-!”
Rola was right.
It was close.
It was as Rola said it.
The difference is 7,000 and change.
You’re right.
Wait a minute!
I… when Rola was here… the 60,000 people.
Oh!
She said “That’ll be a good handicap for you,”
and it pissed me off,
but won’t the 60,000 get added?
So it hasn’t been included.
Yes, Mr. Hotohara.
So Hoto —
What happens for me?
The 60,000 followers I had?
It’ll be a perfect handicap for you!
Hey.
That’s enough from you!
That hasn’t been included.
170,000 followers!
There might be some overlap.
If he’s going to be that desperate about it,
I’m fine with it!
Huh?!
What is this?
Which do you want?
It feels like you were just told by Amano
and you’re just doing what he says!
Do you want to take the handicap or not?
I’ll take it!!
He has taken the handicap.
So you’re gonna take it.
Understood, so the last place person is Amano Hiroyuki!
I was 700 behind Udo.
Which do you want to do?
The bottom left, please.
Ok, the bottom left.
Maybe I was a face bit-type of guy all along?
I’d like an original work!
Making me think… You’re really horrible.
If he really wants to do that, then.
We’re never gonna finish!
Nice, nice.
An original.
Yeah, an original.
This one isn’t that…
Why the hell.
For those who are continuing, please do continue tweeting.
Thank you very much.
Translation by typesoshee | Timing & Typesetting by BassGNT
Good work everyone!
How was it?? I wish I could be there!
#######################################################################
Ok, bye everyone!