Subbed by: Otviss
Next up is
Mommy
Yeah doctor, this hurts as well
It does? I see, I see.
This, ya understand?
That, right?
Ouch ouch ouch...
I wonder how this'll be
You've got quite the physique... It's hard to tell whether it would work on everybody right?
So hang on...
This hurt?
Yeah a little bit.
How about this?
Oh this doesn't raise at all. You've got adhesion here.
This is seriously a frozen shoulder..
(50 year old's shoulder)
A frozen shoulder?
How old are you if I may?
55..
So it's a frozen shoulder then...
Despite having muscles...
...you have no strength
Hahaha..
You're right, I don't
Yeah, you have no strength
You do appear to have muscles though
That's because people who train and have bulging muscles like this,
their mood is a little weak...
THAT'S BECAUSE they work out only to show off
Hahahaha! You've been very disrespectful for a while now!
He's dissin' ya!
He sure freaking is!
Heal him.
Just heal me doctor.
Well "Just heal me", when...
...this shoulder hurts here, this hurt before..
In contrary, the ankles right? I'll just put a needle in real quick.
Ouch ouch ouch..
Putting one in...
..makes this shrink right? Your cervical vertebrae.
Kind of becomes like that... And here I'll put a needle in the side of your ankle.
Ugh...
Alright, lift your arm back
Uh...
Feel any pain? What about here?
Oh!
It got better by just doing that right?
Just two needles in the Leg??
It feels better compared to before
I mean, I still have some pain but..
Back of your hand alright?
Here it comes..
There's a pressure point on the hand here ya know
Huh? On there?
Haha, you're putting that fat needle in there?
Oh god I get it, I get what you're saying now..
How should I explain it, It's not like a stab...
It's pounding..
Yeah, it's like a pound
But if it's pounding throughout that means it's healthy right?
Yup yup...
Ohohoh!
Doctor, let me know when you put them in
Ooooh!!!..
Putting one in your neck now
Aaghh!
Oh it's in, it's in!
Hang on, ITS FREAKING IN THERE
It went way too far in!
Waaaaay too far in. Oh god, its hot.
Raise your hand please
Oh wow!
It raises with ease..
So this way doesn't quite raise properly does it?
Before
No, it still hurts.
Is this for real?..
It's scary how far in it is..
Yeah...
If we want more of a therapeutic effect
We need Yaito (Moxibustion)
We probably need a really huge one
How about sitting a little bit more to the side..
Hahaha... He's getting nervous
Huh? We're gonna do Yaito?
Super Sadistic Acupunture
②
Piping hot Yaito
A little bit more on the side please
We're gonna do Yaito?
Let's just all do it...
No one wants to do Yaito
Let's all do it..
Are we done with the needles, Doctor?
Uh no I still..
I have the Tsuuden (Electric current) left to do
So we're not quite on the same level as daddy are we?
It's like currents. Electricity!
You're gonna use electricity?
Yeah, we're moving on to electricity.
I'm getting the full package..
So today...
It's a special course!
It still hurts right?
Does it?
I mean if it fixes it..
..I'd like to try it.
Crap, they're small..
Why are they so small?
Do they do anything?
Of course
He's putting them in where the others were before
Oh really?
Watch out, it's hot
It's not hot, It's not hot..
It's not?
Only thing that's hot is my heart, not these.
Lamest thing I've heard..
That's okay, that's okay
Let's focus on the arm..
I might be a little frank but my heart is kind
Wow, there's smoke coming out..
Woah!
Huh? You've already started!?
It's already started.
Say something then... Ouch ouch ocuh
If I tell you, you'll just stiff up
Doctor, you've put needles in right?
No no, they're yaito
Yeah, Yaito. It's only fire ya know.
It's like stinging
Yeah, it stings a lil' bit
I'm gonna do Yaito on these just briefly
Oh it's warm..
It's warm!
Oh, OH! Ho- Doctor, that was really HOT!
It's just sudden. It's stimulating
Ouch! Doctor please! I'm saying its hot!
Hahahaha!
I said it was freaking hot didnt i?
It's cause I kept bumping into to you
Hahaha! You hit him with them
Ugh, stop it with that!
It was sooo hot
Okay, whatever I hit you, Anyway
Matsumoto-san.
Try standing up once and shake like this
How is it? Your shoulders?
Considerably better!
We don't have a towel though...
Sit down for a bit. My...
Putting the towel here. This is most certainly a frozen shoulder.
Matsumoto, Frozen shoulder he says.
We should...
...do the Tsuuden on the bed
We going to the bed?
Oooooh!
You've got some Adhesion here
The adhesion hurts...
Aahh!
Here we go!
OUUUCH!
Come on doctor!
Doctor!!
Go for it Doctor!
Ugh that hurts so freaking much!
Doctor Zai, Doctor Zai!
Yup!
Oh Doctor...! OHhh!!
"Oh god"
Alright, raise your arm
Raise your arm
Where there's adhesion, it hurts like crazy.
It really freaking does
Yeah absolutely.
Much better right?
I'm telling you it FEELS BETTER
Sit sit sit. Well perhaps...
If I wanna cure this, I'd have to do the Tsuuden in the bed
The currents?
Yes.
Alright, let's do the currents. We'll prepare it.
Let's do it!
Super Sadistic Acupunture
③
Shocking needles
Your hurting shoulder on the top please
Facing upwards
So like this?
However, your back...
Wow, this is amazing..
So here's the shoulder bone. I'll put one needle in...
Wow, He just puts them in without any hesitation either...
I started getting interested in Acupuncture when I was a kid...
Hahaha, to the very end of the needle..
Sadako! You saying useless things over there...
I.. Agh!
Holy crap, It's so far in
Aaahh!
It's so far in. Don't move so much!
Doctor, You sure are overdoing this...
Haha he's quick.
Doctor please...
Wow he put them in quickly
Oh no the electricity...
Woah, he's gonna connect them to electricity
The electricity is really pleasant!
Oh it's gonna sting!
The needles are short aren't they?
Nowhere near short...
To me they're short
Wow...
Today when I brought these short needles with me
my wife and I had a disagreement
Your wife?
If ya put those needles in Matsumoto, He's gonna get scared and whoops they're gonna give away, she said
Your wife isn't being very polite about me is she...
The wife watches your show regularly you know!
Haha, He said it right here
Be quiet please. I'm gonna put the electricity on.
Wow!
Wow, it's all in there..
Shit it's moving!
It's moving, it's moving!
Does it hurt?
Oo...oo...
It's better to use the electricity is it?
Oh yeah, much better
Oh he's gonna do Yaito?
He brought something out
I'm very worried that Matsumoto isn't healing properly.
Wow, It's burning
Huh?
He's like... really burning something
This is super pleasant ♥
He's like burning a torch or something
Hang on seriously..
Is this a festival?
Seriously, stop it
I can't see what's going on from here
Uh, its a torch!
Oh crap, you're right. Don't freaking show me!
This is really refreshing
So, close your eyes. I'm gonna do some on your eyeballs.
NO! You gotta be joking!
Doctor please, Just wait with that! WAIT WITH THAT!
No no, just here see?
He's just gonna fry your eyeballs
Yeah it's super nice
Super nice right? Hear that? It's nice!
This is really refreshing
So, close your eyes. I'm gonna do some on your eyeballs.
NO! You gotta be joking!
Doctor please, Just wait with that. WAIT WITH THAT!
No no, just here see?
He's just gonna fry your eyeballs
Yeah it's super nice
Super nice right? Hear that? It's nice!
Doctor, are you being completely serious?
Are you serious?
Super Sadistic Acupunture
④
Sizzling Onkyuu
I'm just going to do Onkyuu (Moxa cautery​)*
If you move he's just gonna bump into you
No moving about alright?
Doctor, Where are you looking?
It's not good if you look somewhere else
You touched him with the incense before
So after I do this...
...on the adhesion mass here, his blood circulation will be better
His blood circulation becomes better?
Is it warm?
Ye-ah, It's warm.
That's because
we're feeling the same feeling right now
That electricity stuff is finally over...
But just from that short time ya know.. It's..
Yeah, for sure..
It's sensational...
Wonder how long It's been available. 4000 year history?
4000 Years...
Well actually...
You say 4000 years, but this Yaito actually flourished
1000 years ago in Japan. I'm taking the needles out by the way～
It hurts so much when you take them out.
Whazzat!?
This is just scary
A beautifully high pitched "Whazzat?"
Doesn't hurt anymore does it, Now when he said that.
Stand up please
I wonder, I wonder. If it's a good result.
Aah. Ahh!
Uh, It's considerably easier!
Before
After
Really?
Wow, he's really able to move about
How will it be tomorrow though Doctor?
It'll be good tomorrow
Today, it went well didnt it?
So now you gotta think "Oh that's good that it went well"
If you think about how tomorrow will be, it'll get worse
Then those anxiety feelings will show up again
So "Tomorrow won't be good" will result in it being bad.
The feeling of "Tomorrow I'll make a mistake" is kind of...
Basically negative feelings aren't good.
Exactly, exactly.
Tomorrow will be better and then "Aa～ that's good"..
Alright, this is it for me today
Thank you very much!
This was good.
That was scary...
I'm sorry, it hurt a little didn't it?
Doctor, the medical fee for today is...?
That'll be 3000 Yen* for 30 minutes.
*About $27 or £21
All in all 3000 Yen? That's sooo cheap!
30 minutes??
Yes
I felt longer than 30 minutes though...
Wow, he came prepared with a wallet and all
Quickly putting it inside
I always have my wallet with me
Haha "Always have my wallet with me"
Thank you!
Okay! Bye bye!
Kenji, that was awesome
Good, wasn't it?
What an acquaintance​...
Yeah it was
I'm amazed
Going to things like this ocassionally can't be bad
Yeah, if you feel a little exhausted he'll fix you up quickly
Alright, that was the first reward. We have more though!