Mom got taken away!
Translated by: Otviss
For more, please visit: http://tofupandas.tumblr.com/matsumotoke
The Matsumoto family's
Day off
Hey, what the hell are we actually doing today?
No no no...
He said it!
Because it's getting a little warmer now
Yeah
We are going to go to
Oh..
all of the Osaka circle line stations in this series
How many stations are there again?
Shouldn't it be
Beyond 10 stations by now?
So it's 10 stops now huh?
Yes
Yeah it links to
Most of the major routes
So, this time it's..
Nishikujo
This again..
I know about kujo though,
cause I used to live there
So it's next to that?
Yes, right next to it
I wonder how it is now though
Nishikujo is pretty much
in between Hanshin and JR so,
there are plenty of stuff under the elevated rail
So let's enjoy ourselves
I really do like areas under elevated rail
It's only 3 stops from Osaka station
so It's still within the central city area
And after US(Universal studios) also set up there
It has changed a lot
The entrance is right there so..
Oh really?
So how about we just go there?
I wanna go!
Haha no no..
US doesn't count as within the circle line so
Why is this show
so interested in like
taking us to remote areas
all the freaking time?
Nishikujo is not a remote area though!
Hahaha!
It's not a remote area..
We are never ever taken to places like
Universal studios or the Abeno Harukas
Do you want to go there?
I do!
Heck, if you say that, let's go then...
You wouldn't go on
Jet coaster though right?
Ah, the one at Universal studios?
Yes
What would you think about back drops?
What the hell is that?
A thing that goes backwards
Why the hell would you want us to do something like that
We debuted to go forward
not backwards
Yeah we've always been going forward!
Calm down you guys...
You're too vigorous!
So this time they
aren't gonna cut us off at
10.000 yen again right?
Actually, this time
the prices are kind of cheap so
Let's set that limit then
Shall we?
Yes, let's
Matsumoto family budget
Limit at:
10.000 Yen!
Okay, lets go then!
Oh, and since there
Are so many
little shops lined up this time
We gotta be self-disciplined
and look for like...
Shops with originality
Huh?
Well there are
plenty of shops competing
to stand out
What you on about?
There's gonna be lots of
Moody geezers around...
Well, despite that
Let's look for some good grub shall we not!?
This is,
He's kind annoying now
Kind of pissing me off yeah
This is the map we prepared
Thanks!
This is the so called "Gourmet town"
under the elevated rail in Nishikujo
Hmm, There's a tunnel alley it seems
Exactly
Hmm..
You can't talk about Nishikujo,
without mentioning the keyword "Gourmet"
Gourmet huh?
Everytime we do these things
there's always a way to tell
the local speciality
of the places we go to
but this time it's not so evident.
So if we use this "Gourmet" keyword
what exactly would that mean
Yeah
What in the world is "Harami 9" right?
Wow...
It's definitely Harami(skirt steak) but
like what do they do with the
Skirt steak...
That's why, I want you to
look at this map and
solve the mystery
Clam grab grilling...
I want to try that!
It makes you wanna try it right?
Just in what way will
they prepare it for you?
Yeah but the clams,
The clams that you take...
This is seriously messed up but
When I hear "clam grab grilling"
I imagine they grill the clams
while you're still holding them in your hand
Hey, is that gonna happen?
You guys be careful alright?
You sure are taking it literally
Are they gonna grill them in my hand?
They are definitely not...
Let's go find out if
actually grill them in your hand
That's what it's all about today
If they grill it or not... what the?
Why are you staring at me for?
I kinda felt you bombed with that joke
Listen, Udon..
Udon no Hentai(Obsession)!
What is... Right?
I wonder what that means?
Udon no Hentai (Pervert)
Does that mean they are gonna
do rope bondage with the udon noodles?
Wow, that's harsh
We definitely have to cut it there..
It's no good if we don't stop filming
Those would give a lot of strength for sure!
Hahaha..
We're not..
Yeah? What is that..
You get curious
You definitely do
Here's one that's ridiculous
Which one?
"Great taste, Great entertainment? - A brothers bar"
Great entertainment...
That's just too exhausting
It's probably a
Store the Nakagawa brothers have been to
You got it
The Nakagawa brothers...
Those dudes
are in Yoshimoto you know
I wonder what that means.
I guess
we're going to find out right?
9:1 dream rice bowl
What the?
What is 9:1 right?
"Magic flour, Hachimi?"
Huh?
Not ichimi, not shichimi, but hachimi huh?
Firstly, which one are we starting with?
Hmm..
Ah, what about the clams?
We going there?
Yeah the clams are kind of...
The ones you grab and get grilled?
And get grilled? Yeah, we don't
know if they're gonna grill 'em like that yet though
We don't know that
I love clams
Ah, its probably like you get to
grab them yourselves right?
Yeah maybe, cause I'm imagining
they grill only the ones...
You manage to grab,
am I right?
Oh! So how bout we make a game
out of the one who
manages to grab the most.
WOULDN'T THAT BE INTERESTING!?
Come on, I was just saying!
I wanna see the face
of a failing comedian
I'm not failing!
I'm not messing around!
Alright, got it
Let's go!
We're going to Nishikujo!
Well then, we're here in Nishikujo
We've arrived!
It's kind of amazing
Couldn't we pick a place
with a bit more sun?
It's cold
It's shining in the completely wrong place
Look up there please
There's the elevated JR(Japanese railway)
And then Hanshin(Electric rail) as well
Oh! I see I see..
That's how it is yeah
It's really convenient
Exactly
Seems like a very nice and convenient station
You said it.
Namba is in walking distance as well
I see
Nishikujo is freaking nice
It's kind of nice isn't it?
I wonder why we
haven't been here before huh?
Well..
It's because of the circle line..
Hahaha..
We didn't know about any weird
planning like that. Since when?
I've said it so many times now
Yes but for how long has
has the camera been rolling though?
Constantly!
Huh!?
Yes, constantly!
I didn't know about that
They've always been on!?
They were here weren't they?
The two camera men.
They've been here all the time.
Wow you're right!
They were here from the start
I'm a big fan of these guys now
Hahaha!
Why would they film a fan?
Let's get going then!
to the clam grab grill!
I'm really hungry
Grabbing some clams...
It's here?
It's in the under rail passage
The clam grab grilling
Kenji, I'm freaking hungry
There's also the Udon transformation place
Yeah, if that name gave us so good vibes
maybe we should start
from there, no?
Wow, the entrance is really cool!
"Gold town"!
This is cool!
Woah!
This is good!
Nishikujo parlor
This is really... Oh wow, what's this?
If we find a good place
along the way let's go there
Sure thing
Why is..
Is this really the right way?
Hm?
Must be here. There's no other path
This isn't a dead end?
Wow...
Oh, we're out again!
What the hell's the matter with you
Ugh..
But...
But..
Clams, where ya at!?
No the.. It's...
This is all there is
You're right..
This is all there is, ya know
It's definitely on the outside
Maybe this way, huh?
This place is certainly...
Interesting
Yeah, it's nice
Sure is
Wow, they're already drinking
They are drinking like crazy
From lunch time
There are gramps who drink during
lunch time for sure
Kenji, I said I was hungry
Look, It's the bicycle from
Knight Scoop!
Ah.
The one at the back right?
Haha, you got it instantly.
Why is that always there by the way?
It's a part of the set
It's constantly there though
Yeah it is.. and uhm
a horse too
and a horse yeah
Oh, here's another one!
There are tons of 'em!
Perhaps it's here?
Look, Hormon!
"Yamato charcoal grilled hormon"
I guess that sounds good
However, the shop
Kenji mentioned...
ADD TEXT ( DONE)
Uh, There's a monster!
Huh? A monster?
Oh crap!
Wait, are we okay?
Oh come on, we're fine
No no no I don't want too, it's scary!
Flip it over,
Flip it over it for me!
It's just a normal frog you guys
Hahaha..
What the? This is so off-putting
The frog is standing on two legs!
Ah, look here!
It's cause there's a frog shop here
Ah, that's why
What the hell is that anyway, Frog shop
Didn't know there were shops like that
My gosh, this is so creepy
Huh? What?
Odds and ends shop
No that's not...
Huh?
Mommy!
Mom!
Hey, Mom!
Mommy!
He's being kidnapped!
Mom's being kidnapped!
This is bad, this is bad!
Hey, Mommy!
Here please..
Mom is being taken away
Mommy, stop! This is not good at all!
Huh!?
Ah!!
Oh wow, Tamura Kenji! ♥
But, he's kidnapped..
No no no, this is our mom!
They kidnapped my mommy!
They took my mom away...
What's this all about?
It's locked!
Eh!?
Oh no...
Tamura Kenji decided to join us, everyone!
What the hell?
Mom, what are you doing?
Mommy....
Finally, we took them here
We brought them, everyone
Mommy, what's all this?
What are you doing?
What's going on here?
I don't know a bloody thing
Wow, I'm so happy!
What's this all about?
It's karaoke!
There are snacks even..
Hm? Did you say something?
♬After so many times, so many times
Please, we apologize but...
This situation...
I have no idea what's going on
Wait, you mean mine?
Who's song is this?
She's really good
Sorry but, I just heard my
father comes here often.
Hahahahahaha!!
I apologize
Woah, this surprised me!
Huh?
Is this for real?
That really surprised me
Thank you so much for coming. Thank you!
Don't worry, I'm under your care,
I'll try to behave.
I'll behave
Uh.. yes, thank you thank you.
You're so cool ♥
Thank you very much...
I also just found out, This is my
Son's friend's grandmother.
The world really is small!
What is this place, I'm at loss for words.
"Karaoke snack"
"Karaoke snack" right?
Please sing a song!
Please..
Please sing once, one song only
Otherwise we're not getting outta here
That's messed up, It feels too weird
Just one song please!
We just started filming...
We'll start with one song..
We'll start with one? No this...
The matsumoto family:
From dad
1 Song!
He's gonna sing to represent his dad
A representation of his dad!
To represent
my Dad?
I can't figure out who works here and who are customers...
The two over there are the owners
Wow I can't believe it..
"Kimi wa habara yori utsukushii"
Go daddy!
Thank you very much..
His dad always
sings this one
Wow, thats really...
Thank you so much everyone!
Thank you, thank you.
Thanks everyone
We have to go now
Let's get going
Sorry for intruding
This was truly remarkable,
Thanks for having us.
Please take care of my dad
next time he's here
Thank you.
Thank you for coming!
Thank you very much
Sorry for intruding like this..
Thank you
That was just...
That was shocking
Absolutely amazing..
What in the world just happened
That was seriously scary
My heart was racing from
the moment I came through that curtain
Yeah that curtain was scary for sure
I guess kidnapping is a real thing
I guess that was some real customer service, huh
That really surprised me, I'm
disoriented once again
Huh? I'm telling you is this way
Did we walk too far?
Clam grab grilling...
Well you could say,
I was already grabbed and
ready for more
But ya didn't get grilled
But it was close, It felt like we
were all being grilled in there
Are we really going back here?
Yeah, I guess here..
Alright, going back then..
We haven't found a single shop yet
Ah, but this is kinda...
Look at the sign over there
"Number 18 OK Road"
Ah...
Number 18 OK?
Ya bet
Huh? Is this right?
This is not within reach at all.
We haven't been to a single place,
I'm freaking hungry!
IT'S HERE! LOOK!
Eh!?
Which one?
You're right! It says it right there
One time for 200 yen! That's cheap!
Ah crap!
Let's do it!
So we can only do it once huh? Uhm so...
Hello there
Hello
Are ya doing clam grab grilling here?
Yes we are
Really? We finally found it
Who's gonna go then?
How about mom goes first..
My fingers are too short
Mine aren't such a big deal either
Yours are way too short
You've got boring ass hands
How about you?
Yeah I guess Kenji..
My hands are big, yeah
Alright, alright...
If you could do it with both of your hands...
We can do it with both!?
For 200 Yen!?
This hospitality is over the top!
Eh, so how am I..
I just do like this?
Not like that no,
grab them from above please
Wow, it's packed full
Can we do it with one hand each?
That's completely fine
Hey, mommy
One hand each
Yeah
Both of ya grab with the
strength of each hand and then you
push your hands together
so that you can take the ones in between too
Wow you really know
how to do this, huh?
Ah I gotcha!
So I do this so we can combine..
Okay and then...
We're gonna get some in between
cause we can only do it once right?
This is gonna work out perfectly
Let's go lets go!
Can ya do it?
So first...
Shit thats cold
Yes it is
No no, if you do it like that
It's not gonna work
Yes yes yes exactly! The ones in between too!
Oooh!
Exactly like that!
Faster faster! And then down in the bowl!
You did it!
Yay!
This is what we took!
We managed to grab quite a lot didn't we?
This what ya managed?
Very clever
Alright then!
You think we're good?
We did it.
It's a lot
And then you're gonna prepare it
for us right here right?
Yes, exactly
We did it, guys
Let's go
Let's head in
Hello
A hidden pub under the elevation
Rare cuisine
"Kameman"
Yoshimoto comedians
also come here often
Lots of fun events!
Oh wow
they do all kinds
You're right
Saikoro steak. one time for 780 yen
If ya throw a 6 you get 300grams!
I wanna do that～
They have Oaiso rock, paper, scissors too
If you win you get 10% off
Wow!
Why don't you try it?
Wow this made me happy
What's this about like, is this
a gambling themed store?
Yeah like..
How do you want the clams prepared?
Alcohol steamed or butter fried
Wow
This should definitely...
I mean we can only pick
one or the other right?
Half and half
Half and half is...
Okay? Really?
Alright we'll do half and half then
Now I'm happy
Don't forget this is only 200 yen, we have money left
"Kameman"
Clam grab for 200 Yen
Left:
9800 Yen
You're absolutely right, this is cheap!
Today we have a limit of 10.000 yen so..
Yeah
We're kind of using the money wisely I think
Yeah, you're right
Do you want to do the steak dice?
Steak dice as well
Are we okay with that?
780yen for one time
If ya throw a 6 we get 600grams
Let's do it!
This one isn't good, 50 grams see?
Yeah if you throw a one we'll give you 50 grams of meat.
Even if we pay 780yen?
Yes, the price for competing..
Let's do it then
Let's go
Since me and Kenji
did the clams last time
We'll let you do it this time
Alright, I'll do my best
Hey, she's even
bringing you something
Hey it's Cee-lo!
Yeah
It feels like the
bad luck from last year
Is not quite gone
It's definitely still there
The dice is letting me start from one though
Wow...
So you're saying it won't show?
Yes it won't
If you were to be speculative right?
It definitely won't show, let's go
Okay here it comes
300 would be amazing
Alright!
5!
That's good!
Then for comparison
If it was my turn then maybe...
What the hell? That's no good!
If I'd done it
we would have had great success!
I'm glad you did it this time
We were lucky
That was risky
That was close for sure!
Really close
We are noticing your clumsiness
How embarassing～
"Kameman"
Clam grab for 200 Yen
Saikoro steak for 780 Yen
Left:
9020 Yen
We did it though
200g certainly is big
Should we have some drinks?
Yeah for sure, let's drink
And now, if we win
Rock-paper-scissors
We get 10% off
You're right
That's awesome actually
What's up with this store?
How about a "Free Jack Highball"?
Huh?
A what?
Oh, "Freezing"
It's "freezing"
Cause it's chilled
Japanese-style
They have 和 high ball too
Zero sugar, Zero purines, not sweet
That's nice
Should I get this maybe...
Me too!
和 high ball is good
4 和 high balls from wheat liqour please
"Kameman"
Clam grab for 200 Yen
Saikoro steak for 780 Yen
和 high ball x 4 for 1680 Yen
Left:
7340 Yen
Okay!
I'm glad we
didn't go to that Udon shop
I'm happy we have that ahead of us
Yeah I guess so
I want to go to the Udon place too
Did we...
How do we find that place then?
Well since
we found this place now so
It's going to be easy to find the others
Cause now we're in the "Number 18 OK" right?
What I really wouldn't
want is going by
that karaoke bar...
Exactly
Never ever in my life again
There's a possibility
We're gonna pick that one again
This is the entrance to the Number 18 OK so...
Oh I see, I got it...
Alright, I got it now
Here you are, sorry to have kept you waiting
Thank you very much!
Yay!
Cheers!
Wow, that's delicious
Delicious
Right? This is good
It's really not sweet at all
This is good!
I can drink tons of these
This is good for yer body
You get a lot of
Yoshimoto people coming here right?
Yes, we get plenty actually
Who was the first one that came here?
Well first...
We had Yoshida Yutaka here...
Oh really? Yoshida?
And then Matsura Shinya as well
Wow
People say this place is good
and they keep on coming do they?
Wow, all of them are new comedians
Oh it's here!
Bon appetit, Alcohol steamed clams
Alcohol steamed clams
Wow, it smells amazing
Wait, this is half?
So this is what we.. huh?
There are some green onions in there
Wow...
There are some "Field mustard flowers" as well
Field mustard..
Field mustard huh?
Wow, this truly is amazing
You can put the shells in here..
Thank you very much.
The staff are certainly friendly aren't they...
Absolutely..
Ooh! This broth is nice!
Oh wow, this broth is so nice
Right?
This is delicious!
As a savoury food this is a 100 points from me
The best!
The clams are also nice and chewy
Huh!?
Why the hell are you
Scooping into the trash bowl
No, Its cause
Mom put
shells in
my bowl already...
How embarassing～
His clumsiness is too obvious
Yes
Sorry for intruding, here is the
butter fry version
Butter fried clams
Wow
Huh? Did we order this?
This is a 100 yen ya know
This juice is great...
I'd love to make pasta with that
With this?
I'd love to mix this
and that together
Wow..
It would be great
Clams are truly amazing...
This broth is just perfection.
I'm beaten, this is delicious
Very
This place is truly great
Hmm...
This place must be crushed in the evenings right?
Crushed?
You mean packed right?
Yeah, packed!
Packed?
It's okay you didn't get it
This guy is the strange one
Yeah it's okay you didn't get "crushed"
Ah okay, Thank you
I can't imagine anything else
But during these hours
there aren't that many though
This place is cheap too
Yeah
Very sorry for the wait,
Here's the saikoro steak..
It's cause dad threw a five...
Exactly, cause he threw a five..
Hang on, for 700 we..
780 yen!
Very sorry for the wait,
Here's the saikoro steak..
It's cause dad threw a five...
Exactly, cause he threw a five..
Hang on, for 700 we..
780 yen!
This is a lot!
Saikoro steak 780 Yen (200g)
Is this for real?
Hmm?
Should we lower this maybe...
Oh this...
So tender..
This is crazy tender you guys...
Is it?
Is it really?
Wow that's tender
This is so tender!
This is amazing, what meat is this?
It's a little stiff... Isn't it thigh meat?
It's tender!
This is freaking delicious...
Yeah the taste of lean meat..
This is some luxury meat right here..
Wow, this is just amazing
This is remarkable,
truly delicate...
Mmm!
The sauce is good too!
Yeah you're right
Uhuh
Right?
Yup!
Wanna do rock-paper-scissors!?
Yeah let's go!
Let's do it
If we win we turn the 2790yen
to 2390yen
That's...
400 yen! That's about one of these
So.. you for the clams and steak..
Huh? For real?
Let's order
Let's do it. Win okay?
Pick the staff member of your liking..
We get to do it with whoever I want?
Yes
Sadako, who you gonna pick?
Well obviously, the good who looks unlucky
That person!
That's reckless! Get outta here!
You are the hopeless one!
That's the boss yer talking to
How unexpected...
Seriously, knock it off..
There's no one as lame as you
What the hell is wrong with you?
I thought we
were were supposed to
enjoy ourselves
with the cute staff
Sadako vs Owner
Serious Rock-paper-scissors
Only one try!
That's the real boss you were talking to
If you win we pay 2390 yen
Because it's a 400 yen difference
you better win!
Rock-paper...
Wanna do rock-paper-scissors!?
If you win we pay 2390 yen
Because it's a 400 yen difference
you better win!
Rock-paper-scissors!
That was a cheap win..
We won and made it cheaper
Yay I did it!
We certainly got off cheap!
This is big. This piece here..
Hey big bro! I actually contributed
something to the family for the first time!!
Next time
A calling! Perverted udon