Subbed by: Otviss
Wow, It's the first time I taste anything like this. It's delicious!
Matsumoto-san...
This is tea...
Huh, hang on a second!
This is so scary!
STOP IT!
STOP FILMING!
Hand over the tape!
This is Yoshimoto's now. Sealed up.
No cause, This... this is.. th..
Kokeshi!
You outdid yourself Kokeshi!
She didn't do anything
Kokeshi didn't do anything
Must have been a joke right?
Well obviously, it freaking killed didn't it.
Haha, cause you said you were gonna do this yesterday right?
Sure, I'll do this bit tomorrow I said..
I'll do this tomorrow I said and..
..Kenji was all like you're gonna bomb and
I was like nah, I feel like i'll go with the flow here
It worked didn't it?
Mommy, you're sweating
You're sweating like crazy
It's been constantly hot...
I'm digging in..
They look similar!
I'm certain there are other customers who've done the same mistake
That's true
Right?