When it was first soaked in the sake it must have been shit scared...
It all started with this comment
Sorry this isn't a funny story at all but I was watching some some stuff on BS
and it looked SO GOOD!
Mom's top "want to try" food...
Thinking I would love to go. Can't we go there with this show?
For what? What looked good?
Japanese blue crab!
Japanese blue crab
They like soak them in sake
Different from normal Japanese blue crab!
and then they take this drunken crab
and a dude grills it for 3 hours.
This old guy is horrible isn't he?
The name is drunken crab!
Then they crack it open
and the stuff inside...
The crab innards right?
It looked so damn good
Matsumoto family & Drunken Crab
A hearty budget of...
80.000 Yen!!
4 is ahead! 4 passed them!
Yeah it'll definitely make it!
In order to fulfill mommy's dreams, a big horse racing competition!
Keep going! It can make it!
So close so close so close!
However, an unexpected event awaited them...
Wait, hold on
Huh? Hold on!
He's holding a ton!
Wait a minute...
A ticket that daddy bought secretly with his own money
"#4 takes the prize"
100,000 Yen!
Got him 450.000 Yen!
He bet 100,000 Yen...
We got 450,000 Yen (4000$)
This bastard kept it a secret
Let's go get some crab!
Let's get 100,000. 100,000 Yen for crab
～Let's go get some crab～
A budget of 100.000 Yen!
The richest holiday in Matsumoto family history begins
Subbed by: SugaDuck and Otviss
For more, please visit: http://tofupandas.tumblr.com/matsumotoke
The Matsumoto family's
Day off
We've now arrived in Himeji!
We've finally made it!
Let's go and get the drunken crab mommy wanted!
Although it's all thanks to Dad..
Yeah that's true
It's all because...
...Dad decided to be dishonest with us about that bet
No, no, no I wasn't being dishonest
Okay that's good
We officially won the bet in a fair way...
Alright that makes me happy
We can use the
that daddy actually gave us
100.000 yen
The horse racing right?
I think this is the first time?
For us to have this much cash on hand
Since we had money, we were both able to get these
Yeah! Thanks Dad!
Yayyー
You actually bought these?
Yeah. But they were pretty cheap though...
5800 Yen! (50$)
That's SO expensive!!
2 x crab gloves crab ● hat: 5800 Yen
Left:
94200 yen
If this was a normal "Matsumoto Ke" episode
That's already half our budget ya know!
You spent it on that for real?
Yeah...
Huh? Vacations are supposed to be like that!
Agreed!
That's scary
We still have a lot of money left
We have 100.000 Yen!
That 100.000 Yen is legit mine though
That was actually yours yeah..
But I'm your child!
Dude you better watch it..
I'm a good crab, a good crab～
He's super pumped isn't he?
Today, we're going
Yeah, let's go
The crab is already drunken
It's already drunk?
Well..
Like super drunk?
It's already drunk...
Already? Wow..
Yeah, so since it had to stay soaked for quite a while...
...It's already drunk.
Seriously?
It's probably walking forward by now. Cause it's so drunk.
2 hours ago
So in terms of time, It's been soaked
in the sake ever since you passed Gifuhashima in the train.
What a dummy～
He's so dumb
And aren't we gonna... be taking a ship today?
Yes, we're going on a boat.
From here
Yeah, we can't go there by car
We're going to be going to a place called Ieshima
Ieshima?
We can only go there by boat
I won't get seasick?
We already got something for seasickness so it'll be okay!
Are you for real?
How much I wonder…
Let's go let's go let's go
Let's go!
Regular Liner
towards Ieshima
How much will it be shaking…
Your mom and I aren't good with big movements
It'll be okay
This is going to make me not talk is that alright?
I can't sit the opposite direction of travel. It makes me feel sick.
See, look at this
Wow!
That's big!
It's slightly smaller than what I imagined
This one's huge though!
This is the first time I've been on something like this
People from Ieshima use this too so... Like high school students.
May I see your
Tickets please
We'll purchase it.. How much would that be?
For how many?
4 passengers
You can purchase it here?
A round trip ticket
costs 8000 Yen
WHAT!?
Well uh…
Now this is really starting to annoy me, given our situation.
～8,000 Yen! 8,000 Yen!～
You seriously bought those for something that didn't get any laughs at all
How much did you freaking spend?!
So we pay here?
Yeah, we pay here...
Wow, I've never...
I've never seen this much money in here on this show.
Yay!
There are hundred bills!
Stacks of bills
So, we're gonna spend 8,000 Yen right here. Is that okay?
2 x crab gloves crab ● hat: 5800 Yen
Himeji port 〈 〉 Ieshima port fare (round trip): 8000 yen
Left:
86200 yen
2,000 Yen per person
Can we board now?
Yes, please go ahead
Yay
Hello there
Liner connecting Himeji port and Ieshima
Time taken -  roughly 30 minutes
It's used for commuting and trips to school
An important utility
Everyone here are like waving goodbye to us
Here, use this. Wave with this!
Huh?
I'm telling you.. no one knows what the heck this is for
Hahaha!
They don't know why we have this...
But they like it!
If you do get seasick, tell me just in case..
Yeah I will but...
I got something that you can put on as soon as you get seasick
You put it on?
Yes
Eh, what do you put on？
This…
If ya put these on
it'll fix your sea sickness right away
So it has water to balance your vision...
Glasses that won't make you sea sick: Boarding ring
The blue liquid always stays leveled and cancels the imbalance between sense and vision
Yeah, exactly
In cooperation with the french navy
I mean the French Navy endures the strait of Dover...
Waves crashing... They all wear this
They don't get seasick?
Well it's more like..
It'll fix it if you do
Dude it's already moving so much
Huh? Hold on!
No it's like a car making a sharp turn. We're going straight now It's fine!
Ugh, this is scary...
Off to our destination of drunken crabs!
It's gonna be good...
It's gonna be so good
It's gonna be good
I'm super excited
Today is going to be a full course crab meal.
I made reservations as "Matsumoto Ke"..
Does the island have other gourmet places?
like a place to snack…
They do they do!
Plenty of delicious places!
Let me know if anyone needs these...
This was
11,000 Yen
My what a bargain
Eh?! You bought it?!
Yeah...
Huh? What's wrong?
This is super necessary!
Yeah, we need it!
Hold on hold on...
We didn't have 100,000 Yen in the wallet so...
Oh, well yeah, we spent money from that...
Huh? 1  2  3  4  5  6...
We've got 70.000 Yen...
Well of course! We spent 5800, 11000
2 x crab gloves crab ● hat: 5800 Yen
Himeji port 〈 〉 Ieshima port fare (round trip): 8000 yen
"Cosmomarin" A boating ring: 11000 Yen
Left:
75200 yen
and then 8,000 Yen on those things...
What the hell are you doing?
Come on, let's not be stingy!
100,000yen..
Dude, you..
The crab and the people watching us are probably laughing at us
Have you ever seen anything this fun before!?
No no, maybe we could've spent that money to stop by to snack somewhere
But with those on, even on a roller coaster you'd be fine
Haha, he's getting seasick!
Eh, are you kidding?
From your own talking?
You're the one that brought this up!
This is really...
It's moving so much
This is actually pretty unpleasant
This is awful isn't it?
The sound too...
I'm actually doing fine
I'm completely fine..
These actually..
..make things so much better. I'm serious!
Let's try those glasses on.
Maybe I'll try and see..
Please.
Ohh I see I see…
Right!?
Seriously?
This is actually pretty fascinating..
It's seriously good!
Dad, it's good, it really works!
But I'm not seasick..
Wow!
You get it?
It starts to feel super refreshing
That much though?
For real though,
Maybe it's just a placebo effect?
No, I get you. I totally get what you're saying.
It starts to feel refreshing
Refreshing! Yeah
It helps me even see so much better!
Good isn't it?
I can see so clearly!
I can see you're wearing panties!
See!?
Wasn't it worth spending 10,000 Yen?
Nah, I'd rather get it on my own time
What's this what's this...
Dang... This is so cool
Yeah! It makes me a bit sick when I take it off
It works as promised..
If this looked a little more fashionable..
..Then it'd be perfect
Yeah the design is kind of..
You look like some kind of charismatic artist from England
Do I look like I nag about complicated things?
Exactly, Exactly
I'm glad I tried these out
That's good that's good..
Interesting. Maybe when the waves are more violent they are most effective..
Yeah, maybe you're right
It would be cool if Matsumoto Ke could go abroad somewhere though right?
We've been saying that for a while now though..
Like get everyone's schedule for New Years and plan something together.
Yeah for sure!
Like?
Like where?
Yeah...
I wanna go to Hollywood!
Ugh.. That's just, well..
I don't think we can earn enough for a hollywood trip from horse racing
No? Too expensive huh...
You know...
We should just do like a before and after
Like if it's really warm and we go adrift
And how we fall into the ocean..
And then how we get washed in. Like a before and after!
Then we should just show that all of the members
have acquired special abilities
And when we leap like this we can go wherever we want..
This place looks like something that would achieve that too right?
Then we'd be able to go anywhere we want
Yeah, that'd be good
So let's just make an episode about us obtaining special powers
Getting struck by lightning...
Yeah, like an incident that triggers that
I guess lightning would be the most probable
Lightning…
Ya know, they have those electric...
The really strong electric device… Whatcha think?
We're all doing it right?
No, just you
No, no, no I...
You can just get the powers and if we hold you directly
Then we can go anywhere!
Yeah exactly hahah!
What the hell
You wanna try?
What do you mean "You wanna try?"
This won't give me anything!
Why is it with that?
You do that long enough and get special abilities
That's the scene we're going for
This is just a rehearsal
I think that'll be really good
We'll shoot it again for real but right now...
We need to rehearse it a few times
Rehearsal:
Kenji Obtains Special Powers
with Electrocution!
If I can get special powers with something like this, I'll be a super star
How many times have we been doing this?
Ready, action!
Alright let's go! 2018's first electrocution!
Dude you can't drop it
You have to hold it
"You have to hold it" you say....
Also,
The windows are starting to fog up
We can't see the view!
Now, even during these past 30 minutes, the crab is getting
more and more delicious
The crab is getting drunk
Meanwhile in Ieshima...
The crab is starting to show signs of the sake...
It's just barely starting to get drunk
Do you guys know why they choose to use sake?
Why do you think?
Why?
To drunken… Why they get the crab drunk
Eh, why?
Why do they soak it in sake?
I just thought the components of the sake brings out the flavor of the crab
That was my thinking
Apparently, crabs...
can cut off their own arms when they feel like they're under attack.
They just cut them off themselves
In case of an emergency?
If that happens, the flavor of the crab
will start to escape right? if we just cook them normally.
So to prevent that, they soak the crab in sake
To kind of blur their instinct to protect themselves..
To distract them…
So they won't be scared
Yes, exactly. Then, so that they don't get alert
they grill them on very low heat so they don't notice
The crab doesn't even know
when it dies
I guess in some way
They have animal cruelty in their minds when they cook them
In a respectful... so they don't get scared
It would seem so, yes
Making sure their last moments aren't stressful
Although I bet they were scared to death when they first got caught
Either way
Yeah I'm sure they were a little panicked
when they were first soaked in sake
Yeah, I bet they were super scared
What? What? What is this? What?
Ah! Bitter! It's bitter!
It tingles! It tingles!!
Oh! We're arriving!
We're here
Ahhh so cool, is it this?
This is Ieshima
It's pretty big!
The island floating in the Seto Inland Sea: Ieshima
Population of about 3000 people
Number of tourists have also increased in recent years!
Boasting fresh fish!
Thank you so much
Eh? There's a bunch of people!
What the heck is this
It looks like all of Ieshima is here
What a crazy scene
What should we do?
I kind of want to see the map so let's go look at one!
Let's go look at the map
This you see, is Ieshima
Right now, we're in Maura Ko
Right there
And then came in here
And the place we're going to go now
is Shimizu no Hama
That's a pretty long way to go
Yes, that's right
Is it walking distance?
About 20~30 minutes on foot
That'll take us a while huh
Takes us a while...
It'll take us a long time. You don't really want to walk
all the way over there right?
Eh, what do you mean?
We have no choice but to walk
Do they have something like this?
What is this?
This is nice
Max 4 people!
We can go on it
There's a 200kg weight limit on this one, we can't take it
"Weight limit 200kg"
Sadako 90kg
I'm 90kg!
Then 180kg together...
Man...
These jerks…
What the hell is that
That's so irritating
Go lose some weight!
We don't have enough to rent 2 huh?
Then why don't we just go into this town a little
and find someone that can take us to Shimizu by car
What?
Wanna do that?
But there's 4 of us is that okay?
We won't fit
It should be fine. People on these islands usually have big cars
Let's go searching
For someone
we can catch a ride with
in the port area!
So let's look around the town first then we can find someone
Sure!
Let's go let's go
This is such a big welcome
It's pretty small island-like
Yeah yeah
See look at this helmet! The way you can just leave it here
No one even thinks about taking it
They won't steal it
This is like... really nice
Nice isn't it?
I can't explain. This feeling
Isn't this so nice? Just this atmosphere
It's great
So nice
This vending machine is something else too
How nostalgic
Can you still buy stuff from it?
It's so thin!
It's leaning on its side!
Since we have the money, let's give it a try
Let's try and buy!
It's not going to come out! It's a waste of money!
Wait... is it even plugged in?
No! Don't dont!
It's not plugged in!
But he have so much money!
NO! I'm telling you, it's not plugged in!
I just told you it's not plugged in. Why the hell are you still putting in money?
Dude, the thing is not plugged in!
Guess It doesn't work...
It didn't work...
I just told you its not plugged in! Ya guys idiots?
Well, I guess we should just leave it here then...
Why the hell!
My.... my hard earned money...
Are you guys stupid? I've had enough
What should we do? Who will give us a ride?
This is so nice
I really like places like this
Very nice
I like it I like it. It's nice
There's a lot of children
Let's see if this one works, the money...
Let's give it a try
It says out of order!!
Let's test if it's really out of order. We don't know for sure
Can you not read? Out of order!
Like 10,000 Yen would fit in there stupid!
10,000 Yen wouldn't fit anyway...
This is my money!
This whole thing
scared off the kids and they all went somewhere
A bunch of geezers fighting or something
Oh, excuse us
Hello there
Haha, What do you mean "hello there"
Oh! They're drying octopus!
Woah! What the heck
There's so many
Eh what? That's crazy
There's fish too!
They have a bunch of dried octopus and next to it, it says "MACKEREL"
Mackerel is over there
The mackerel is over there right?
How.. what is this?
This is octopus that's been washed and boiled
Eh? Just boiled?
So you boil it, and wash it and…
No, not dried, you eat it just like that
Oh you're not drying these?
Then why…
They're just being cooled down here
Oh to cool it down?
Oh is that so?
Like this
Wow, this is from Ieshima?
Mom!
Ieshima, yes
Wanna eat?
Are you sure?
The daughter was like "mom," and handed her a knife
so I thought she meant "finish them"
What kind of place is this
Ehhh!?
Did you want to eat it here?
You don't mind?
I love octopus so much
Slicing them like this is the best
Ehh? You guys don't sell them like this do you?
It's sold in wholes right?
No, we sell them by slices too
Can I try this right here?
Yes, please go ahead
Just like this?
Delicious innit?
IT'S SO GOOD!
SO GOOD!
What is this seasoning?
Huh? I mean all I did was
add just a little bit of salt, that's it.
It doesn't even need soy sauce or wasabi
Right?
This octopus is the best!
The meat closer to the end tastes the best
And this is of course all caught here right?
Yes indeed
That was so good
I'll uh...
I'll be taking this... thnk you sho much!
Woahh this is a good picture
Sorry to bother you, thank you so much
Sorry to bother!
We really appreciate it, thank you
This really makes you feel like you're in Ieshima
That was a nice scene. I was pretty surprised though
That was unexpected huh
It was so good
They don't even have soy sauce and wasabi. Eh? What's this?
Huh? Is this a gasoline stand?
Huh?
This... you get gas from this?
Like all the motorcycles..
Well I mean not everyone but...some do, I suppose
Really? What about the money?
I don't drive so I can't really be too sure...
But I've seen some people use it before
Are you sure?
You call the…
You tell the person up front?
I think so
Like the air for the bike tires from back in the day
Something like that right?
It would seem so
I think so, yeah
Hmm.. that's pretty interesting
They're selling an Alphard (Toyota) for 1,000,000 Yen*
*Roughly 7000£ or 9000$
Should we... buy someone some gas?
Good idea!
That guy over there
D'ya need any gas?
Are you really going
to buy me some?
My name is also
Matsumoto
We are the most inconvenienced ones aren't we?
Are you low on fuel?
We don't know how to use it so we'd like to know!
How do we pay?
Have you done it before?
Hello, we would like to put in some gas
How much would gas you would be needing?
How do you pump it?
He's just about to run out!
He was just barely makin' it!
Put the gas in!
It's fine! It's just some gas!
It moves? Huh!?
Fascinating!
Oh it's at zero now!
We're so lucky!
He's pumping it while turning it!
You can't find this anywhere else?
No, no no!
There's nothing like it!
We just put in 4.7 liters
And how is the math done?
The total is done here…
It says right there
750 Yen
Sadako just give him…
Yep, 750 Yen
Dad's treating you so...
2 x crab gloves crab ● hat: 5800 Yen
Himeji port 〈 〉 Ieshima port fare (round trip): 8000 yen
"Cosmomarin" A boating ring: 11000 Yen
"Tsubata Auto" Gasoline fee: 750 Yen
Left:
74450 yen
Sorry for the sudden request
Thank you very much
Take care then!
Thank you!
That was so nice
He kind of looks like my ex comedy partner
There's a car! Someone's in there
Excuse me? Sorry to bother... Good evening
Maybe he's in the middle of working?
May I ask you what you're doing?
Heading home
After a jog
Oh is that so? Can we hitch a ride?
Do you think we can?
May I ask you what you're doing?
I'm heading home after a jog
Oh is that so? Can we hitch a ride?
Can we?
Uhm... with Matsumoto-san right?
Hey there
Hello
Do you think we can?
I think so...
Is 4 people okay?
It doesn't seem like all 4 of us can go...
I've never felt so guilty towards the staff before
Guys I'm sorry...
I really want you to try it!
The deliciousness is so intense it's like an explosion
100% delicious!
Woah, those are huge!
Wooooahhh!
Next time
Catchy catchy Jumpy Jumpy That's a fun food～♪