"Only" - The commercial shooting, filming and audio were to be recorded separately.
Ok, that's a wrap!
Good job, thank you everyone!
To the guard, Kyutarou-san and to Mentor Suzuki Hirome-san
Good job both of you, thank you very much!
And Hamada Masatoshi-san, good job, thank you!
- Ah, thanks, good job.
Hamada-san, you did it on first try, thank you very much!
We'll have a cast party, if you'd like to...
Ah, sorry but I was planning on going back to Osaka...
- Of course, no problem!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Wait up!
What is going on?
It's not over yet!
It's not?
We haven't recorded the audio yet!
I'm very sorry!
Come on! Don't screw up, you fool!
What now?
Let's record "Only", I'm very sorry!
It's ok.
It's the last thing left to do and we're done.
What were you thinking?
Sorry! Let's record "Only"!
Then let's-
You have to put your soul when doing these things, you fool!
Let's record-
You first wear the helmet and then you get on the bike, you fool!
Ok then, let's-
If you would buy a TV,
you'd place it in the corner of the room, you fool!
What were you thinking?
I'm very sorry, really.
Is it ok if we do this?
I was going to Osaka-
It's just that if we only don't record the "Only" ad, it won't
feel like we've completely have finished it, you see?
I see, I see.
- I'm really really sorry.
- No problem at all.
Are you... Are you angry?
No, not at all!
When I see you on TV, you seem a little scary...
I think "Is he really like that"?
No, not at all...
Is it really ok then?
Really, don't worry.
You can remove the wig if you want.
Ah, may I?
We'll only need to record the voice
Ok, got it.
Ok, let's do this everyone...
LET'S RECORD "ONLY"!!
Pay attention, please.
Is this ok?
Yes, we'll record with this.
So, Hamada-san, I'll queue you the lines
And after I queue, then please repeat the lines.
Ok, understood.
Let's see...
"Jumbo Cup Noodles"
It's the product we have so that's your line
So say it once for us, please.
Understood.
Are we ready?
We're ready to go, ok, ok.
Jumbo Cup Noodles!
That's was great.
Thank you very much.
No, you put your felling into it.
Thank you, thank you.
That was amazing... I hope it's not weird to say this...
It's ok, it's ok.
The volume of your voice was perfect.
Oh no, come on. I'm just-
Thank you very much.
Can you do it again? "Jumbo Cup Noodles"
One more time?
Jumbo Cup Noodles!
I just... I heard some sound from outside. Watch it!
Like... A helicopter, see if there's one nearby, please!
A copter...
There's a helicopter flying off!
It's ok, here-
Do you guys hear the helicopter flying?
Isn't it flying?
It's not-
I'm sure I heard it flying so...
But it's fine here in the studio.
It gets on my nerves, I know I shouldn't worry about this...
It's difficult, Hamada-san.
My heart races...
It's ok, don't worry. Let's continue.
Let's go with "Jumbo Cup Noodles"
What? One more time?
Jumbo Cup Noodles!
That was great.
That was really great, full of energy.
Let's see...
"Chicken flavor stock now available"
The chicken flavor stock came out recently.
It's very popular.
I want to make sure we show that.
I see.
- Let's go.
"Chicken flavor stock now available"
Thank you very much.
Now, let's see...
"Mini chicken stock now available"
Let's try it, please.
Mini chicken stock now available
Let's try going faster.
"Mini chicken stock now available, furthermore, the grainy type!"
Grainy type, right?
Good, good!
Thank you.
Just... This is kind of an experiment but...
Could you try "It's grainy type!"
"It's grainy type."
"It's grainy type!" let's go with that.
How should I?
Say "It's grainy type...!"
Like "How nice!"
"Ah! It's the grainy type!", like that.
Ok...
When you're ready.
It's the grainy type!
"It's that grainy type!"
It's that grainy type!
"The grainy type... of grains available now!"
The grainy type of grains available now!
"Shochu grain of grains available now!"
Shochu grain of grains available now!
"Available nooow!"
Available nooow!
That was great!
Try to make it more lively
"Available noooow!"
More lively.
"Available now", right?
Available nooow!
Ah, nice!
Now, "Curry flavor available now."
Curry flavor?
It was released, yes.
Let's try it once.
But... is that correct? The product-
It's ok, the curry flavor will also be released.
It's not being produced yet, but I'd
like to record it all at once so...
Hamada-san, please don't...
The curry flavor will be released... So please let's try it.
Curry flavor available now.
Don't, don't do that. It overlapped.
Once was enough.
You did... this "come on" movement...
No, no problem.
It felt like you wanted one more.
No, no, that's scary.
It felt like you wanted it again...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I screwed up.
Please do your best!
Curry flavor available now!
Say it to the microphone!
Ah, sorry, sorry.
Curry flavor available now!
That was great, Hamada-san.
Now, "Curry flavor available, also with 30 percent more!"
It's a bit long, but...
- A bit.
Sorry, let's give it a try.
"Curry flavor available, also..."
It's "Curry flavor available, also with 30 percent more!"
Just... be quiet over there! There is some sound coming in.
Is everything fine?
We're recording here!
PAY ATTENTION!
So, Hamada-san, do it.
Curry flavor available, also with 30 percent more.
Too long, Hamada-san!
Try to keep it three seconds long, it'd be nice.
Three seconds...
Try to make it more lively.
Hamada-san, what's wrong? You were odd, right now.
Let's try again, more lively.
Curry flavor available, also-
SHUT UP OVER THERE!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
Hamada-san is recording! Hamada-san!
Yes...
Do it right!
From the 30 percent part, try to do it manlier.
Do your best.
Curry flavor-
Wait! Wait for the queue!
You haven't been waiting the queue lately.
Curry flavor available, also with 30 percent more!
That was great, Hamada-san.
Aren't we done?
Just, just a little more.
"How much spicier can it be?", if you would, please.
You see, curry flavor is spicy so...
By saying "How spicier can it be?"
We're trying think like an entertainer from Kansai would.
Hama-chan.
Please do it.
How much spicier can it get?
Now... "Spicy like that even I can fucking eat it!"
"Spicy like that even I can fucking eat it!", please.
Is that ok?
Try to be energetic this time, we want to make it sound like
"Spicy like that even I can fucking eat it!"
Spicy like that even I can fucking eat it!
Nice, nice. Let's try the next.
"That's freaking spicy, I've never fucking eaten anything like this!"
How was it...?
"Spicy like that even I can fucking eat it!"
"I've never fucking eaten anything like this!"
Say "Fucking eaten" twice, please.
Spicy like that even I can fucking eat it...
I've never fucking eaten anything like this!
Fucking eaten!
That kind of lost energy in the end, Hamada-san.
It was fine.
Doesn't it feel like... We're not evolving right?
No, it's fine, it's fine.
Since I don't have much time,
I'd like if we could hurry up a bit.
What do you mean by that?
Do them all at once.
How many lines are there yet?
Around forty ofr fifty.
There's not that much!
There is not that much.
No?
It can't be that much, we can't do that much.
If we don't finish in an hour, that's it.
But it'll be a challenge to go fast like that,
I might need to comment sometimes.
Yes, but if we go fast... We-
What, you want to go from last to first then?
Which do you want?
Yes, well... The one from before
The regular flavor, I'd like to do it.
The regular one, right?
It' not relevant right now, right?
I feel like right now...
It's not relevant right now?
For this commercial, it's not relevant, right?
The curry flavor and the grain type.
I don't know but...
The grain type special release is near.
Sure but it wasn't even made yet, right?
No, not yet. It's still in development.
In development?
So we didn't need those lines?
No good?
That's weird...
Why is that?
"That's weird!" let's record that one.
Go, Hamada-san. Let's record "That's weird!"
That's weird!
Hamada-san your laughter. It got recorded. What is wrong?
It's weird... That..
"Let's record it once, That's weird!"
When Hamada-san said that line
I felt we could save it for later
Because it was really good.
It felt real.
And it's what I want.
Short like that was fine?
It was fine.
So will you use it then?
We will not.
Even if we don't use, it's still worth something!
If Hamada-san don't want to...
Can I call you Hama-chan?
What?
Hama-chan, you see.
You see...
You're creating a weird atmosphere.
- No, I'm not.
Let's just record it.
You are the one being weird.
Why is that?
You made me say that line even if you won't use it.
We're out of time!
Out of time?
Let's do it, then.
It has nothing to do with the product, we're late.
It doesn't, does it?
Will you use it or not?
Will yes don't use-
- What?
We will.
WHAT IS IT?
Hamada-san...
Please, come on Hamada-san!
- What is your problem?
What the hell is your problem?
What is it, Hamada-san?
What is your problem?
Please, come on Hamada-san
- Don't do that!
Don't be annoying.
What is it, Hamada-san...
- Don't do that!
What is it, Hamada-san?
Hurry up already! What are you doing, stupid?
"Win a hugging pillow!"
We are freaking late.
- Win a hugging pillow.
Hamada-san... "Win a hugging pillow!"
Win a hugging pillow.
Just said it.
But that... It won't work for the ad...
I'll say it then you repeat, ok?
Ok, ok, let's go.
"Win a hugging pillow!"
Win a hugging pillow!
"Win a curry hugging pillow!"
Win a curry hugging pillow!
"Enter a curry hugging pillow winning spree!"
Enter a curry hugging pillow winning spree!
"Only people who have a curry hugging pillow can win!"
Only-
Wait, isn't that strange?
Why?
You need one to win?
That's it.
You can't know if this person has one or not.
It what is says here, that kind of information will come to us.
It's fine. Hamada-san, don't worry about it.
But I'm here to the ad and I have no idea of what we're doing.
We've thought this through, so don't worry.
"Only people who have a curry hugging pillow can win!"
Only people who have a curry hugging pillow can win!
"A curry hugging pillow has been won!"
A curry hugging pillow has been won!
What was that I had to say?
What did I just had to say?
What?
That... "Has been won!", what was that?
Ah that... It was won before... One time.
By who?
A consumer.
Don't worry about that, Hamada-san.
I don't see Hamada-san merit anymore...
...This was supposed to be faster.
I'm sorry.
"Win a curry hugging gorilla!"
Win a curry hugging gorilla!
"The curry hugging gorilla roars!"
"The curry hugging...  gorilla roars!"
"We're out of curry hugging gorillas, win a curry hugging mole!"
We're out of curry hugging gorillas, win a curry hugging mole!
"I won a curry hugging mole along with other people
who missed it, I want to win a curry hugging gorilla!"
What the hell are you saying?
Please let's do it.
This one?
"I won a curry hugging mole along with other people
who missed it, I want to win a curry hugging gorilla!"
I won a curry hugging mole along with other people
who missed it, I want to win a curry hugging gorilla!
Hamada-san, thank you very much!
Please wait a moment! Please wait!
Boss... With all the respect...
Instead of curry flavor, duck flavor would be the best!
You! What are you doing?
The curry flavor was boss's idea!
I know that, but...
That spicy taste, it would be better with duck flavor.
Stop saying-
Wait, wait a moment.
What is your name?
I work for Nishiya, my name is Sekiya.
That was not what we had agreed upon, was it?
We're very sorry!!
I will take care of everything!
Jumbo Cup Noodles...
...new flavor...
let's change it to Duck flavor!
Boss!!
It's been a while since I last saw that happen.
Your name was Sekiya, right?
Yes!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much!!
Everybody, thank you!
Let's go with Duck flavor!!
Yeah! Let's go!
Hamada-san, excuse-me.
Please sit down.
Hamada-san, one more time...
"We're out of duck hugging gorillas, win a duck hugging mole!"
Let's do it.
The only difference is "duck".
Is "duck" fine?
Yes, "Duck hugging gorilla..."
Let's do them all at once.
So you can go home....
From "Win a duck hugging pillow!", say them all at once.
What?