WDT Project
Timers: Bipedal, KannibleKlown, Saltpacket Translators: Xueshi, BabyStand, Funtonite, Otviss
When we sit here together like this,it means it has started again
It seems the period for it has come around again
Yeah,yeah
It seems to be of no advantage to us when we end up mixing with that person
Apparently he came just for this
Is that the case?
Whether he comes via shinkansen or planes, I'm not really sure
Just pay your own way here
If they paid their own way here, it would be acceptable
In fact, just don't come
Yeah, don't even come
Hey you guys...
What, what, what
That was a very slow revolution this time around
Who decided to make it turn anyways?
We don't know, probably someone from above
Whatever Hamada-san says, the programme will make arrangements for it so...
EH?! Was that how it goes?
We were waiting for it to turn
That is indeed the case
Well, this spring
Wednesday's Downtown
4th year running
Congratulations
This episode, certain theories from past episodes
is what I have brought forth today
Here it is:
Theory: Wednesday's Downtown quite often starts with a theory and ends with quite an unrelated turnabout
I see
Ah, that seems plausible
Yeah, yeah
It does happen
Like you run into something more interesting along the way
Yes, well said
But as this show's main MCs
In the end, the orange resulting conclusion turns up doesn't it?
Taking a gander from just that
The beginning theory
If it was the two of you, you be able to tell which initial theory it was
Not so sure about that....
I would like to take a small objection about this..
What is it?
You said Programme's MC but in actuality, I'm not really casted as one
I see, but Hamada-san is actually an MC though
Hamada-san should definitely know since he is the MC
But the main attention is normally over there where the panelists are
All I really do is scream "'kay 'kay"
Your job can't possibly be just to say "'kay 'kay"
"'kay 'kay, Take it away" is what I usually do
Now, let's begin the theory guessing quiz
Both of you together
How well do you really remember?
How much of it do you remember?
Let's go with this initial theory resolution
I present to you
Conclusion: Kuro-chan is a liar
So what was the beginning theory to end like this?
Eh? The beginning theory was way different?
Yes, the beginning and the way it concludes is different
But this is from when we first found out that Kuro-chan is a liar
Wasn't it that?
Pigeons...
The one when we release the pigeons or something like that
And Kuro-chan has to make it all the way back
Yes, yes, yes, during that time
Well, no, that's not correct
The one where shit was stuck on him
Wrong
Not even close
Eh? Wait, really? This is too hard
If it continues like this, this is...
It was a surprise prank
It was one of those Dokkiri-style theories Hamada-san loves
During the viewing, Hamada-san was cackling away
It might be?
One of those 'XXX is the scariest' theories
'XXX is the scariest after all', which one?
Most scary...
In the house
Theory: 'Returning to your home where there is a stranger waiting' is the most scariest theory
Ahhh, It's not that one
Can I bring up something?
I have no recollection of it
Hamada is absolutely no good
He is not saying anything
He doesn't even remember which possibilities to even guess
When you guys were recollecting,nothing came up for me
'What are you guys talking about?' was what I thought
Kuro-chan is a liar
The beginning theory was:
Theory: 'When you awake and there's someone beside you' is the most scary theory
Whether the situation of 'When you awake and there's someone beside you' is really the scariest
In several comedians' homes, we planted a strange old man and waited for them to wake
It was the most terrifying
The last to be targeted was Kuro-chan
This guy again
He's here
This is gonna be good
While he is away , we have begun planting the hidden cameras
They should be very well acquainted with this room already
I am walkshing back to my home
As always, Kuro-chan announces his activities on Twitter
"Walkshing back"
In accordance to his actions, we are on standby
His alibi/whereabouts is SO out there
From Shinjuku to my home is a bit far, I am going to do my best-shinyoo
What the heck is he talking about?
From Shinjuku to Shinagawa, if one were to walk, it would take around 2 hours
That's quite far
It is time. The staff await outside for Kuro-chan.
After waiting around for 30 minutes,
That's a taxi?!
What's up with that?
A taxi has stopped in front of Kuro-chan's home
Is this for real?
Just in case, the staff hide
As it turns out, the one who stepped out of the taxi is
Kuro-chan
Wa, scary
Ah, so he lied
A mystery remains as to why he needed to claim that he walked back home
What was that lie even for?
We were close to running into him at his home
The same goes for exposing his lie right now
After he reached home, the tweet that he composed was
He's actually writing one
Soon, I will be reaching home.
My head is filled with the melody of Sarai.
Whose sake is he even lying for?
Scary
A Tweet formed by pretense and malice intent
Our cameras have full footage of the entire on-goings
What a thing they have managed to capture
This is awful
And its now 1 am
In a certain sort of way, he's amazing
They shot a completely different thing
For some reason, he is going through his mail in full nude
No way!?!
Scary
Disgusting
The next day he has work starting early in the morning yet...
He seems to have no intention of sleeping
In that case, just go outside and walk
And next,
Chinsuko
Chinsuko!
He's eating chinsuko
unexpectedly
You going to eat?!?!
Chinsuko Squat
Whether he intents to lose or gain weight, its hard to tell
Next, he raises his iron dumbbell up and..
A selfie?
He's going to take a picture
Since I can't sleep, I am doing muscle training-shin
What was that about?
But, the iron dumbbell is soon
placed back into its initial position once the picture has been taken
Just stop this already
Just stop this trainwreck already
At this point, he has finally made his last lying tweet of the day and heads towards slumber
The main act is from here onwards, wasn't it?
He goes to sleep with the lights and TV still on
From herein out
With that being the case
Ehhh.. he leaves his things like that before sleeping?
We were indeed distracted, finally we return to observe our theory
He did leave it in that messy state
In the end
Scary, scary, this is going to be frightening
He's waking up
Ah this is terrifying
They finally met eye to eye
Eh? Eh? Eh? What's this?
Eh?
That burping got to me
Something weird came out of his mouth, how distasteful
How was it?
About what?
About what exactly?
Eh? Wait a minute...
Ehh What is this precisely about?
We have already grown accustomed to his reaction due to seeing it like 100 times
We decided to ask about the other thing which really interested us
That was indeed tough
We looked up your Twitter account and was piqued by
You mentioned that you walked back home to your home from Shinjuku Station?
Look at those eyes
Yes
You brought up the fact that you were going back home!
Don't bring it up
You didn't actually walk back, did you?
Ah, give me a moment, my piss is coming out
What did you mean you pissed yourself?
You didn't walk back home, did you?
Eh? What do you mean? I totally walked back
You returned via taxi, didn't you?
That's a bad face he's making right now
That's definitely a villain's face
Indeed
Just give me a second, erm...
Such things happen too
We were watching
eh.
It's not a lie but...
Your lies are too conspicious
You're mistaking me
It was a play,play wasn't the word I am looking for,how did I explain myself clearly?
Do you at least acknowledge the fact that you did not walk back home?
What do you mean by acknowledging the fact?
I'm not lying
Ah I understand now, it's okay
We have footage of you leaving the taxi anyway
So as it turns out, Kuro-chan is a liar
By some mishap, we happen to chance upon Kuro-chan making up multiple lies on Twitter
The following series which features Kuro-chan
This was the origin and inspiration of it all
Let's go into the next question with enthusiasm
Next, is this
It turned out to be a wig
Eh, what's up with the ending
This might be quite difficult
Wasn't this about the old guy being interviewed and the ..?
It's not concerning an old guy
The opener to this ending was:
Theory: Impossible to find a forehead that is narrower than Hirukawa's in the world
What we were looking for was a forehead shorter than 2.5 length to the eyebrows
Does someone really exist which has a shorter forehead length?
In the process of searching for someone...
We found someone in Osaka
Are you shopping?
I'm returning from work
Ah, returning from work?
Near the end of May....
Everywhere you look, hippopotamus teeth
A small-forehead woman has appeared, but is more than we hoped for
That is really something
That's one in a million
Which feature do people notice?
For real
What would you say your most distinguishing feature is?
I wonder...
I don't want to seem like a lame old person, so I try to stay hip
She seems to think we were asking about her outfit
We're looking for the narrowest forehead in Japan
If that's the case, I'll slide this back a little
It's moving?
It's sliding!
This is it
Well, that's...
Huh?
Oh no
Is it a wig?
It's a wig. This is my real forehead, though.
That's still halfway down though
It was a wig
What is this?
Continuing on
Chiba is getting some on the side
The theory that gave birth to this somewhat different result
That is
Theory: "If you spilled tea at a Yazawa fan's house, they would never dry it with a Yazawa towel"
On this crazy Yazawa fan's way home
We tried our experiment of intentionally spilling tea
And finally we interviewed him
My phone number is also Yazawa
If you take the last 4 numbers
"8-3-0" can be read as "ya-za-wa"
He's fixated on 830
But "8-7-4" is a more accurate number for the 50 year old fan*
*"8-7-4" can be read to sound like "has no teeth"
So true
Hey!
A Yazawa fan for 38 years
That's just
What are you even saying?
A toothless man with loads of merchandise
That's awful
He doesn't have any friends, does he?
When we asked to take a look
That's so lame
I actually have another place
Oh?
I'll show you the way
It's just for your merchandise?
He's having a laugh
It's just for merch
Wow, amazing
I rent it just for that
Don't you have other expenses?
That's why I rent the room secretly
Is it okay for your wife to know this?
It's fine
So, we went to the room secret even to his wife
Ah, it's like that
This is my other place
Amazing
Could we see inside?
Already you can get a feeling
No way
Right as you enter, even
I made this actually.
You made this?
Yes
He made it
That's cute
But before the Yazawa love can flow
So cute
Hey Chiba-san
Are you messing around?
No that's not it, this is
Well... I just kinda stuck some stuff and...
What was that?
No no no no no
I'm not messing around, nope nope nope
You looked guilty as hell saying that just now
What?
The confusion on his face is obvious
The marks of a woman are even more obvious
On top of that
You've got Snoopy
Well, you see that's
It's cute. An awfully feminine design don't you think?
It could have been a present
That's bad news
While we're on the topic
Seriously?
That curtain earlier
Oh yeah
Can't possibly be homemade
Wow, this is incredible!
This is seriously cool
This is my pride
So, how much is the rent for this place?
About 70,000 yen
That's not cheap
Is someone splitting the rent?
Why would you ask that?
And things like this were slipped in with the merch
Chiba-san, is this your handwriting?
Ah. Yes this is my writing, of course.
An itinerary for a live show at Budokan is written on the white board
This is too muc- huh?
But this handwriting is crazy suspicious
That's weird
For some reason, even Christmas plans are included
You really did right this, then?
What were you feeling when you drew this?
"Let's go to Budokan~♥"
I'll write it now
What a weird stroke order
Why is he writing like that?
A super weird stroke order
What is this?
That's amazing
It's like he's painting
What now?
Where's the other half?
Ah, that's wrong
No good
Chiba is getting some on the side
That totally didn't match the theory
That was exhausting
It really was exhausting, I mean...
Moving on, let's try to answer the question
Wasn't that enough?
Our next theory
He couldn't beat a demon without a pheasant
Oh, I think I know this one
You know this one?
Could Momotaro really rely
Wait really?
Go on
On the dog, monkey, and pheasant to actually help?
Well, you're a little mixed up
Should I try saying that again?
Yes, one more time
Once more- Hamada, you haven't said a damn thing
What's that about?
I don't know a single one of these things
You're always here, though
You can't tame dogs, monkeys, or pheasants with dumplings
First is the dog
Here
Do you want it?
He's taking it
Dogs are omnivorous, so it makes sense
He ate it
He's hungry
He cautiously accepts the dumpling
Where's he going?
But because it's hot, he takes it to the shade to eat
Then, he somehow recruits a monkey
Do you want a dumpling?
The pheasant won't be won over
Momotaro, with just his dog and monkey, set out for the Island of Demons
I've come to defend the peace!
Come on out, demons!
And then
Oh it's Kukki!
What happened?
What's going on?
Kuu-chan?
Scram
Get out of here
Hold on
The monkey ran away
They just left him there
People with freaking Shonan license plates
Ain't going to impress no one in Yokohama
He couldn't beat a demon without a pheasant
What kind of ending is that?
Actually I was pretty close to the actual theory
You were pretty close
Isn't this guy the worst?
Hamada, at least pay attention. Just focus.
What is going on with you?
Well if you're sitting here thinking of things to say every time, you'll remember
No no no no
I'm always left over there, you know
All I ever do is say "Welcome!!"
Well, Hamada
You sound so proud to be completely neglecting your job
What do you think you get paid for?
Don't just repeat yourself
I wasn't
Please teach me to negotiate a job
Noooooo way
That's a sweet deal
Please pay attention, Hamada, just once
Switching the entrance and exit theory, continued
Theory: "The youngest and oldest are evenly matched"
This theory tests what happens when you pit the youngest and oldest athletes against each other in various events
First up is Judo
Representing the oldest
Tadayuki Morimoto, 84 year old ranked 8-dan
Wow
That's impressive
Representing the youngest
Yeah, but
A 5 year old studying Judo in Kumakogen, Toki Sasaki
As expected, this is the ultimate age difference
Really?
The match is beginning
Ah it's starting
He doesn't look happy
He doesn't like this at all
Does your tummy hurt?
Does his tummy hurt?
He doesn't feel good
What's this? Young Toki is holding his stomach and leaving the ring!
Maybe he needs to pee?
What? Is something wrong?
What happened?
Before the match can start, Toki leaves to go to his family
Why?
He suddenly begins to cry
You're kidding
Fighting an old man he doesn't know is scary
Oh, he's a stranger
It's because he's a stranger
That's so sad, though
At this point, Morimoto approaches the staff
He's going to talk to him
He's describing it so dramatically
Look, he's a 5 year old kid
You shouldn't be making fun of his judo
He's pissed
You're doing all of this to show on a variety show
I see what you're going for
Oh he's super pissed
But this really goes against the spirit of judo
Fair enough
He hasn't had any time to learn
But I've been doing this for 64 years
Yes
Making a kid fight me after just 6 months is impossible
Right
He got crazy angry with us
Obviously
So this match ends with forfeit
Oh I see
Are you done?
A few days later, we brought him back with a different opponent
Wait, he's doing it now?
He came back
This time, the opponent is just old enough to compete nationally
Interesting
Way different
This is something
Kanagawa 5th grader Koshiro Sanada
Oh no
This...
He's much better qualified
Morimoto shouldn't have any issues taking him on
He should be fine
Sorry for calling you here a second time
It's fine
Well, he came didn't he?
I didn't think you would, though
He was really mad, though
I won't give up
That's all I'll say about it
Really?
You aren't giving up?
Really
I won't give up
He'll have to retire
Which basically means I'll lose
I see
At last the match starts
I don't like this, regardless of what happens
Actually, Sanada-kun is a powerful figure getting 2nd place in the national tournament at age 11
On the other hand, Morimoto at 84 years old
won his gold medal 8 times at the World Masters
Who will win is totally unpredictable
Well, this kid seems pretty strong
Start!
The match starts
First, Sanada circles in from the right
There it is
There is a physical size difference,
but Sanada-kun is not shy of strength, even for adults
Wow, this is really like a normal match
Good, good
Sanada, who has brought down 100 kg opponents at Nationals,
That's pretty amazing then
versus the 84-year old Masters gold medalist Morimoto!
That's it
Amazing
Release!
Gramps, don't give up!
Keep it up, grandpa!
Morimoto who said he will not be thrown
Gramps is getting tired
This match may turn around at any second
This is really about stamina
This is an interesting matchup
He's staggering
If he gets thrown..
In terms of stamina, at 84 years old, Morimoto is at a considerable disadvantage
Thought so
Doesn't have much strength
Right, if it takes a long time
He can't do it
And afterwards, as the two fighters grapple
the match shows some movement
Morimoto falls! will he get pinned?
And Sanada does the reverse scarf hold!
Sanada, who was taken down
Pins down his opponent!
Morimoto is pinned!
I give up
Suddenly the oldest, Morimoto, has given up!
With this, Sanada, the youngest, has won the match by ippon with a reverse scarf hold!
Wonderful!
That was a great match
That was really something
For me, it's not really about winning
Oh really?
If the kid can make progress from here on out
there's value in being present and competing
it doesn't matter whether I win or lose
So, the result was "doesn't matter whether I win or lose"
And, there was one more judo plan with a different beginning and end
Theory: "Giant Shirota and Shinichi Shinohara are almost identical so they'll have a par match"
This match stems from just finding
their specialties based on similar appearances
A memorable moment in our first mixed-rule showdown
Competitive Eating Judo
The rules are
1 minute and 30 seconds each of competitive eating and judo, 3 rounds each, for a total of 6 rounds
The one with the most full points is the winner
By the way, in judo ippon is 1 full point
And in competitive eating, one makizushi roll will count as one full point
In this match we can get an idea of their strength in their specialties
At the end of round 2 there was only a gap of 1 point making it a tight game
And the last round begins with the competitive eating block, the opener to the judo
Uh-oh, this is not the time you want to eat
They really don't want to eat
Oh no, they're really thirsty too
Will Shirota pull away again?
Will Shinohara be able to eat?
They've become unable to eat huh?
Shirota really needs to make up the points
Start!
Eat, eat!
The referee prompts them once again
Shirota's not having anything
Barley tea in one hand, unable to move!
You'll lose!
If you don't eat you'll lose!
No, no, no!
Shirota, are you all right?
Just...
I'm kind of out of breath
Finally both fighters have reached for the makizushi!
It would be bad if he doesn't have at least one
Since there's no way Shirota can get a point in judo
Shirota crams down a makizushi!
He gets one makizushi down!
He needs to make it up here
Uh oh, it seems like he's having difficulty swallowing!
It'd be funny if he got a point in judo
He needs a 5 point difference
We've never seen Shirota like this!
This is intense!
You won't have time!
On the other hand Shinohara!
Can't eat either!
In this one-and-a-half minute round, each of them
have a normal meal of 2 and 1 makizushi respectively
It's a normal meal!
and the final eating round ends
This is not good
Just two!
Their point difference is two. Can Shirota make a clean break?
Shinohara's stamina has run out
This is the last duel!
Shirota, go get him!!
Shinohara didn't do anything but he got a full point!
A very important point!
The rest is abysmal. Shirota has 1 min 20 sec
This is interesting!
Another point!
one minute left!
With no other choice, Shirota has to win this point!
run away!
You can do it!!
Come on!!
He drags around!
He won!
Shinohara wins this showdown!
Start!
Therefore, "One can't eat right after exercising"
I can do one more!
There's more!?
We're gonna keep going
This is plenty enough
This one!
Please do your job
"It turned into an uncharacteristically wholesome plan"
What is this one?
This one's pretty hard
Not ringing any bells?
Here I go!
This program
doesn't ever get wholesome
It does, here and there
Here is the answer.
Theory: "Professionals impersonating teachers will have students die of laughter!"
Oh, this one!
This was a good plan
Yes, it was
This theory turned unintentionally heartful:
The setting was:
Fuji Gakuen Middle School in Yamanashi prefecture.
And these are the pros in charge of the teachers impressions!
That lineup is surely something!
The pros visited the school in order to gather information about the teachers
First, when inquiring some of the school alumni:
Oh I see
There's this teacher, called Oomori sensei
What's his subject?
Science
When he gets mad, he gets like super agitated
An goes like this
All they way up, suddenly?
That's right. His intonation too.
Next, the pros will watch the lessons live
So you understand that "other" is singular, right?
She raises her tone at the end like "NE"
She talks quickly, and then "NE"
As if she were following a rhythm
Oh, like this
Wow, look at the chalk
This can be funny
This might be possible, right?
Yeah
Also...
Come in
So, the teachers came too
Hello!
The pros will meet the teachers firsthand
Oota sensei, you seem like a very serious teacher
Do you ever laugh out loud?
Well, not really...
What's the funniest thing you last at recently?
Well, after gathering gathering info about the teachers, we head back to TBS
They are joined by the two that were unavailable, and discuss
What should we do?
Shall we decide who is going to wear a disguise?
Let's see first... who can get the main roles
Right
That looks so hard
Depending on the looks, voice tone and such, each pro was assigned a teacher
Kannatsuki will impersonate the eccentric Yamaguchi sensei, ex- member of a "poop seminar"
Also, "bad diction" Oomori sensei, will be impersonated by Hori
Mikan will impersonate Ebara sensei, who can't stop saying "Who can try?"
The serious but also good at dancing Oota sensei will be impersonated by Ehara
And Mirakuru will be in charge of Nakayama sensei, who hisses after finishing her sentences
"Denture" Kanekatsu sensei and "Bald gag" Okuwaki sensei will also appear during the show
Looks like a medley
How did it turn out?
The clueless students are gathered in the multi-purpose hall
And then...
These days you've all been slacking off!
That is why you're all here
There's a teacher that has something to say to all of you
Us teachers have been holding back!
The students, after being fooled to believe they were being scolded, will meet the impersonators!
Every teacher is each
going to have a few words
with all of you here
Hello
After the unexpected appearance, they still don't know what happened
It was like: "what's going on?"
Wait, this guy looks a lot like me!
Who are you?
No, who are YOU?
I'm Yamaguchi!
I AM Yamaguchi
No, I'M YAMAGUCHI
I'm Yamaguchi
If you really are Yamaguchi, tell me. You were in a seminar back in college, right?
Which seminar?
Turd seminar
A turd seminar!
They're laughing a lot!
The real Yamaguchi has eaten bugs right? Which insect did you eat?
A stink bug
A stink bug!!
After realizing what's going on... they burst out laughing
They find it hilarious
And then...
There are many other teachers that are also angry!
Oomori sensei!
The resemblance is amazing
They achieved an amazing resemblance
One, two, three
Why the pinky, sensei?
So, I want you to remember the important things needed for a flower to blossom
There's one, two and three of them
Hey, sensei, that's weird... It's pretty strange
Stamen and pistil... Please remember that...
Remember that!!!
Remember that, I mean it!
You can remember it!
They find it hilarious!
Sensei
You all...
Your diction is terrible, so we have no idea what you're saying
My dihsshion?
We have no idea what you say when you get mad
Isn't there a teacher with a better diction in this school?
WOW, WOW
They're going "WOW"
Hi everyone
They really look alike
So the other day we left it at page twentyfiiiiiiive
We will continuuuuue...
Like a one line joke
They're laughing like hell!
They really are
When comparing "the other"
They're laughing their heads off
When comparing "the other" to..
... "the othersssh"
And then...
He appeared
They started laughing right after the entrance
What about the real person?
In spite of the circumstances, he remains expressionless
What the hell!
He's never laughed in his life
They're the same!
What's with your right hand, sensei?
Your right hand!
And your mouth? That's a duck face
The contrast is hilarious
I'll dance now
Apparently he dances for the school festival
And the last one to make entrance is...
They're really similar
Indeed
Today I'd like to talk about my favourite team: Nippon Ham
Ssss...
Dot, dot...
That's a lot of dots!! Too many of them!
Dot dot dotdotdotdot...
Ssssss
No one's saying it right...
Should we have Okuwaki sensei say it?
It's Baldiewaki!
And finally they will go for Kanekatsu sensei's motto: "Nice, nice!"
What do you think about the whole show?
It was... "nice, nice"!
"Nice, nice!"
I'm better at nicenicing!!
It's obvious I'm better!
I AM BETTER
I'm "nice,nice"!
Someone should decide who's the "nice, nicest"
Hey you, come here
Sensei, how was our impersonations?
"Nice, nice"!!
Thank you so much
And like that, the impersonation show achieves a huge success!
Were you surprised at the beginning?
You might've thought "What's going on?" or something
But then...
He's crying!
Why are you crying?
They're dying from laughter
They're literally dying from laughter
I don't know...
Is it because you're happy?
Why??
I don't really know
Is it that you are overflowed with joy?
I think he's just overflowed with joy
Don't you feel like really we accomplished?
Yes, I really do
First time feeling like this
The best in 10 years
I think we did really well
Students
Teachers
And also
The impersonators
Everyone was filled with joy and laughter
It surely was a great day
In a few words: it was an unexpectedly a heart-warming show
Next up,
"There are some weirdos in this world"
Which theory was the entry for this verification result?
People that get "Japanese style toilets" installed in a new construction is seriously next to 0.
So we did a survey amongs contractors that do toilet installation around the country.
We discovered a newly built home with a Japanese style toilet in Nara Prefecture.
It's in Kansai!
This surely looks like a home that fancies the "Japanese style"
Yeah pretty much
No way!
Could they really have installed a Japanese style toilet?
Definitely new!
This is dangerous
Beautiful
Newly built too
This is dangerous
We're with TBS Television.
Please come in.
"Please come in"
The husband didn't want to show their face on TV
Didn't want to?
We're immediately shown to the toilet in question.
TN: The sticker on his face says "Japanese Style".
I can't believe it.
It's on the second floor.
This is not good
On the second floor?
Yes.
This is a nice house.
Wow it's really Western-style!
In here.
No way! It's a Western-style door!
Tamura, ya fool!
NO WAY!
WOW!
WHY!?
They had one...
It's sparkling!
A super pretty Japanese style toilet.
It's really pretty too!
It is!
I can't believe it
It's beautiful
Still brand new!
However, why do they have one in the first place?
It's special
Right?
Yeah, the reason.
It's for a very surprising reason
They even have a freaking outlet in the back!
So why did you get a Japanese style toilet installed?
The hell does it say "Japanese style" on his face.
So, I have a son that's gonna be in high school
and he really insisted on getting one installed
Why!?
My son yeah.
Like a manic.
Until the point of, if we don't get one I'm out of here.
What a strange guy.
Somehow, the "tradition" was strongly demanded by their high school son.
Why?
Really?
This is a real plot twist
Yuu?
Come down for a bit
So the son's face is good to show huh!?
Their son. Yuuki, 15 years old.
Hunk
He's handsome.
Yep
Why does it have to be Japanese style?
Well uh, there's always been one in the house since I was born
and I got so used to it that I can't use a western one.
You gotta try it!
You had one in the previous house?
That's right.
Doesn't it cause a lot of trouble?
Yeah, there aren't any if I go outside
Right
If I got to like department stores
So in times like that, it's kind of bothersome
So what do you do?
I just hold it in... earnestly
That can't be real.
When was the last time you went on a western style toilet?
I wonder. I just can't remember any time
We are used to the fact that, if a western one isn't available we go to the traditional one
Right
But for Yuuki, it's a firm rejection.
It's opposite
What's bad about them?
Does the family use it?
No one but myself no.
So it's only for you?
That's right.
They have another one!
It's only my room
It's downstairs
Have you ever used a washlet?*
*TN: An electronic toilet seat with bidet functions.
No I haven't.
You gotta try it!
Should we have you try it?
Alright, only one time.
And so, he enters the family toilet for the very first time.
His first wash toilet experience in life.
No, he's got to have done this before!
He has!
Sure enough
AGH!*
*TN: On wash toilets like these there's a bidet function that sprays water from a retracting arm inside the toilet.
That's just harsh
Stop pulling my leg!
OOGH!
Ouch ouch ouch!
Cause it's his first time!
He said "ouch".
How is it?
Unpleasant
Be careful with the pressure
In conclusion, "There are some weirdos in this world"
Gotta lower the pressure
Next up,
"The average grip strength of men in their 50s is 46kg."
Which theory was the entry for this verification result?
Theory: Hiroshi Itsuki has a strong grip
What kind of theory is this?!
This is just messing around
Enka singer Itsuki Hiroshi, gripping his fists for 45 years
Could his grip be stronger than the average male of the same age?
This is not what it's about
Yeah
But when we requested the person apperance
Right, they asked him
they naturally refused
Hello
A Hiroshi Itsuki look-alike
That's so unrelated
How long have you been impersonating Hiroshi Itsuki?
He does it well though
31 years this year.
Wow!
That's long for sure
He's been holding his fist for 31 years.
Does Itsuki Hiroshi's grip strength exceed 39.7 kg that of an ordinary male in their 60s?
Does he have to karaoke?
♫ Yokohama Twilight
♫ In a small room in a hotel
♫ The lingering scent of the kiss
♫ was the smoke of cigarettes
♫ Blues
Not yet
♫ Whistle
No
He's reaching the top now
♫ A woman's tears
It's coming!
This is it!
♫ That person went and gone
Oh he did it?
He shouldn't be holding it up like that
right
♫ I'm not coming home anymore
He's really into it
What about his grip strength?
They made us listen quite a lot of that
It was 41kg
Right?
It's over 39.7kg
He slightly exceeded the average grip strength of an ordinary male in their 60s
As expected, Itsuki-san.
Your grip strength is stronger than average
Oh really?
Yes.
The average grip strength of someone in their 60s is 39.7kg
I just turned 56 years old...
Say what?
By the way, the average grip strength of men in their 50s is 46kg.
What the hell?
Onto the next one, the last.
This one!
"The result left a bad aftertaste"
THAT'S ALL OF THEM!
THAT HAPPENS ALL THE TIME!
It's on all of them, all the time
Come on, not all of them
Not all of them are like this
Today too!
Now too
No way
You've got a bad aftertaste now?
This is the one:
A crime scene psychic can tell what happened just by entering a room
This was uh, miles away
Right right
And at the end, the psychic
was like "The spirits are angry"
"I don't know anything, but I know that"
I got all 3 items flawlessly wrong
I just couldn't catch them at all
And because of how variety shows are planned out
I had times were I thought "I wonder how this will go".
Which is why I'm sensing that the deceased are angry
And with that, the result left a bad aftertaste
What the hell!?
Check out our Facebook and Website for more Wednesday Downtown! This video was subbed by a community run project called the Wednesday Downtown project. Thanks for watching!
Next time on Wednesday Downtown: It's a Kochikame verification special!
Divers treat the guest by putting fish on their hooks!
Downtown golf showdown!
As well as a mixed rule competition as appeared in Kochikame
Is it possible to hide nudity with plastic wrap?
Two whole hours of Kochikame verifications!