TYPESET & TRANSLATION BY SHION (@FGRNDNOISES)
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
For our next theory I wanna talk about conspiracy theories
They're all over the internet, but they're mostly groundless
And that's how their rumors often end
But among them...
There's a theory which isn't a distortion, it's a terrible truth
And I'm here tonight...
- Really?
To present it to you
What? Is this ok?
The theory I've brought with me
Is this:
Theory: Matsumoto Hitoshi is a Russian spy
I'm already calling bullshit on it
And the audience is already like "ehhh?!"
Is that Toshi from X Japan?
They're like "you are whaaaat?"
Didn't know we had Toshi here
Who cares about that
I've misjudged you... you filthy traitor!
You're a spy from Russia, aren't you?!
"Filthy traitor"...?
Of course you are
What the--?
Doing whatever you want in the showbiz
Tricking us all
What are you trying to bring to Mother Russia?
I'm not Russian
Stop playing dumb
I've brought with me lots of evidence
Really?
Let's verify them together
Scary...
Let's start with this song, please listen
Coming up...
The real meaning hidden inside the song "Chicken Rice"
Coming next
The real meaning behind "Chicken Rice" will become clear
Man, this is freakin' scary!
Let's start with this song, please listen
"Chicken Rice", written by Matsumoto Hitoshi
Screw the Akasaka Prince Hotel...
What about it?
As I thought, I'm still alright with just chicken rice
So, you know this is a Christmas song written by Matsumoto
- What about it?
- Yeah, what?
- It's such a good song
Yes...
Such a good song, that's what I used to think
But there's actually a hidden message in this song's lyrics
Added by Matsumoto himself
Really?
Let's start with this song's title, "Chicken Rice"...
"Chicken" can also mean "Coward"
ChickenwwwwwRice
Coward
While "rice" is "kome" in japanese
Kanji for "rice"
And the kanji for "kome" appears in "beikoku"
In other words, "U.S.A."
Beikoku (U.S.A.)
I see...
It's about U.S.A., not rice, folks
This song you've listened for all these years...
Is actually
A diss track in which he claims the U.S.A. are cowards
That's the truth
Now you know it
Open your eyes, army of Japan
No way, no way
Not only that
He also wrote "screw Akasaka"
Screw Akasaka
Yeah, what about it?
And do you know what's in Akasaka?
The U.S. Embassy
U.S. Embassy
Minato ward, Akasaka district 1
In other words, he's implying we should destroy the U.S.A.
"Let's gain control over the U.S.A.!"
Scary!
This is incredible
Do you see it now?
Amazing!
But that's not all
You know December the 25th is Christmas
Chicken Rice is a Christmas song (December the 25th)
December the 25th
But in Russia that's not it
Really?
On 25/12/1991 the Soviet Union collapsed
Foundation day of the Russian Federation
And the Russian Federation was founded
This song is praising that
Everything matches, it can't be just a coincidence
He's making all these coincidences match!
I'm not buying that
That's sly
But this is not the only song by Matsumoto with hidden meanings
- Eh?!
Please, listen
Oh my
Ugly
This is the rap part, huh?
Yes
This is Hamada's big hit song
"WOW WAR TONIGHT"
It's also the only song featuring Matsumoto, and has this mysterious code
But it's not a code
At a glance, it may seem it spells "ugly Hamada"
Ugly
But if you change the order...
Huh?
It's getting creepy
Big explosion
It reads "U.S.A., big explosion, M"
(Matsumoto)
The "M" stands for "Matsumoto"
You can't do this to me
Man, this is freakin' scary!
It's a secret code
It's freaking me out
You're part of a terrorist group, aren't you?
You suck!
Gimme a break, I'm getting scared here
Scary scary scary
Shocking
- Now...
These are not the only things which connect Matsumoto to Russia
Take a look at the following pictures
The picture on the left side is the protagonist
Of Matsumoto's first movie, "Big Man Japan"
"Big Man Japan" - Daisato Masaru
On the right side, it's a statue in Russia
Called "The Motherland Calls"
Russia's "The Motherland Calls"
Two peas in a pod!
This statue is very important to Russian people
Who knew that?!
Russia's
"Big Man Japan"
"The Motherland Calls"
Daisato Masaru
And look at them: they're identical!
That's nonsense
You can definitely tell he used it as a model for his character
Really?
They're really the same
Have you really deceived us all?
This is bad, really
This is gonna get me in trouble
- You're the bad guy here
His love for Russia appears in other works too, not only music or movies
Even in his skits!
The fuck is wrong with you? Geez
Watch you language?!
I don't care you're my senpai, you spy!
Spy! Spy! Spy!
He's a spy...
My "love for Russia"?
Please, take a look at this
Kathy Tsukamoto
What now?
This is a famous skit from Gottsu Ee Kanji, "Kathy Tsukamoto"
I love this one
Yeah, we all laughed at this
Me too!
How is this--?
In this series, Kathy always ends up making a mess while cooking
That's right
What about Russia?
There's an episode in which you can witness his loyalty to Russia
We have a video proof for that, take a look:
Today we're making boršč
Oh, boršč... like the russian one, right?
That's correct
But you know, there are lots of types of boršč
So much that I have no idea which one I should do
I thought about it and yeah, let's not make boršč today
- Sure
So... you won't do it?
Correct
Consider this:
This skit is made of a total of 16 episodes
The only time where he never touched anything was during the boršč episode
I see!
In every other episode, he made a mess
Yeah, he threw stuff around
- He always made a mess
He didn't touch anything only when it was about boršč
That's a sign of respect for Russia
- Makes sense
Scary stuff
This proves he can't make comedy out of his beloved Russia's traditional cuisine
There is evidence in some of his books too, take a look:
This is Matsumoto's "Visualbum"
They're compilations of original skits by him
As you can see, each jacket
Features a different fruit
In order: apple, banana and grape
Apple
Banana
Grape
Yes
What comes after red and yellow, usually?
Just who would pick purple?!
What about that?
It's apple, banana and grape
Matsumoto, why did you choose them?
Just tell us
I--- I just took some fruit
And lined 'em up there
Such a stone-cold lie
Even colder than a Russian winter
Take a look at this:
Russia's most imported fruit in quantity:
Apple
Banana
Grape
These are Russia's most imported fruit
Banana
Apple
Russia's top 3 imported fruit in quantity:
It's apples, bananas and grapes
Incredible!
He's a spy!
Unbelievable
He's definitely a spy
Just admit it already
No doubts
We're not even talking about exports here, it's about imports
Did anyone know that? Only he knew that!
No, that's my first time hearing that
- Imports? Incredible
He knows because that's what he used to eat in Russia
That's the hidden message
Man, that's scary
- I'm shocked
What do you think, Ogi?
Well, usually in tv dramas
When they say "you're a spy!" to someone, this person laughs
Or sometimes they drink poison or such
It just feels like this right now
Hey
Did you just try to drink poison?
He's a spy...
However...
Matsumoto is actually being controlled by the real mastermind
Who's the mastermind behind Matsumoto the spy?
You mean someone is pulling his strings?
In other words I've been hired?
- Yes
However...
Matsumoto is actually being controlled by the real mastermind
You mean someone is pulling his strings?
In other words I've been hired?
- Yes
And that person...
Is YOU!!
That caught me off guard
It's you!!
Wasn't expecting this
Me?
This is the scariest part
What are you talking about?
I've been laughing the entire time
I have a strong suspicion you might be a Russian spy too
Take a look at this picture:
Osaka's Expo'70, USSR Pavilion
This is a picture from the USSR Pavilion for Osaka's 1970 Expo
There it is!
Mh? What's that?
I knew it
And what was your father's job during this year, Hamada?
Well
He was a building painter
Correct
We also know for sure
That your father painted the USSR Pavilion
That proves Hamada's family has always been connected to the USSR
What the hell?!
This one makes more sense to me
They're definitely connected
That would grant him special access, right?
He painted it 'cause it was his job
Think about it:
Matsumoto has been downgraded to a Russian spy
Downgraded, now?!
There's no way a guy born in Amagasaki could become a Russian spy
He needed some kind of connection
And that connection was Hamada and his dad
Who were already connected with the USSR
In other words, Downtown...
- This is crazy...
▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀
Russian Spies Comedy Duo
Is a Russian spies comedy duo
Scary!
Chilling!
Do you feel relieved now?
Makes sense...
Feeling relieved?!
I mean, you've always been on TV bearing this feeling of guilt
You should thank me
You should at least say Спасибо to me
thanks
Wait a sec
How could I even do all those things to begin with?!
Yeah, right
With that being said...
All of this was just a farce
But just like this...
It's pretty easy to get lured by rumors or urban legends
So you should always be careful while surfing the web
Today I'm ending it with my own awareness program​
What the hell is this finale?!
I just thought about it
TRANSLATION & TYPESET BY SHION
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TWITTER.COM/FGRNDNOISES
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
So, there's a moral?
- Of course
What the hell is this ending? I hate it
Don't worry, I don't think you two are spies
Rest assured
So unpleasant...