Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Onigoe Tomahawk!
-Surprising!
Thank you, we are Onigoe Tomahawk
Scary
-An oppressive feeling
Hamada has a lot of people like us around him
Standing by his car
-You idiot!
So, I think everyone here should be aware of this
Our style usually involves arguing
It's interesting
-Very popular with everyone
So we have brought a theory about argue-style comedy
If managers suddenly give you a Onigeo Tomahawk-style "you're so noisy!" routine while fighting with another manager, will the situation turn serious?
This is scary
If it is said by the agent who is always around
You'll think, "He doesn't really think that, does he?"
It also depends on how the relationship is
If it's a playful relationship
-Yes
Indeed
So next
Shut the hell up!
The real manager prank
And
The area of Mutsumiso is still the best value for money in Tokyo
The all-time worst-selling comedian CD ranking
If managers suddenly give you a Onigeo Tomahawk-style "you're so noisy!" routine while fighting with another manager, will the situation turn serious?
So
These two participate in the capacity of determining the quarrel
Awful
The same amount of stress felt in general should be released
If they can see someone seemingly really taking something to heart
They'll be convinced that its real
We are looking forward to this development
So, the the first target to endure verbal abuse from their manager is
Diane's Tsuda
By the way, this time the project
Good choice, good choice
Don't fight, don't fight, don't fight!
You're so noisy!
You're turning into an old man!
I don't really think so!
But lately, when you're tired you look like Mino Monta
You're so noisy!
The person assuming Sakai's role is a fake new manager who has been working for just a few days
Next
I don't really think so!
The person playing Kin's role
Is Tsuda's real agent
His real manager
This time you were responsible for writing the script
-Yes
How is it?
Conveying Yoshimoto's feelings of Diane's Tsuda to him
I hope he will take these words back home with him and think about them behind closed doors
Really?
Tsuda arrives at the scene of the fake recording
It's for his own good
It's okay to be honest with Tsuda
Spraying alcohol furiously...
Looks mad
Spraying way too much, right?
It's cheap alcohol, right?
It's not like that, Tokyo people don't do it like that
Just looking at this makes me feel angry
So
Can we take some pictures first?
Tsuda is taken out of the room
At this time, a conflict brakes out between the two managers
So realistic!
They've been instructed
When Tsuda returns to the room and attempts to break up the fight
Yes, yes, yes
The "you're so noisy!" will be triggered
It'd be a shock
Go back quick!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
What's up? What's up?
What are you doing?
You're so noisy!
What the hell!?
Tokyo Yoshimoto doesn't need you at all!
What the hell are you talking about?
-Go back to Osaka!
Who the hell is this guy!? What's going on!?
He's angry
Shut the hell up!
What the hell!?
Tokyo Yoshimoto doesn't need you at all!
What the hell are you talking about?
-Go back to Osaka!
Can't blame him, he didn't even do anything
Who the hell is this guy!? What's going on!?
How...
I don't really think so!
They said he was the "Next Chidori"
But he can't beat Kamaitachi so he should just stay at home and live stream video games
What?
I'm shocked...
That's too funny
What? Is something wrong?
I'm shocked...
What's going on here?
What's going on?
Ah, he laughed, must've realized
He seemed to be angry before but now he's just embarrassed
With the inclusion of Kin's part, he realized something was up
The truth is revealed
He realized
The managers worked hard
Whoa, you surprised me!
What? How?
What the hell?
Seeing the manager and the newcomer quarreling like you two...
Wha...what?
You were a little angry at first, weren't you?
Super angry...really super angry
This goddamn newcomer, for a minute I wanted to smack him
I really almost did it
Really a little angry, right?
Did you write the script?
Yes
-What the hell!
We had some other ideas
-Tell me
Since Oda came on the scene you're of no use anymore
That's the thing I care most about, okay?
Tsuda cares a lot
The next target is
Panther's Ogata
It's the first time we've targeted Ogata, so i'm looking forward to it
Will he realize?
He's aging surprisingly quickly
More and more wrinkles
If there are no more pranks, he's done
If pranks cease to exist, then Ogata is finished
He could be pranked to pay a loan back for 70 years
That's why he's funny
Because he should have noticed so many times
It's really impressive
-Who wouldn't notice
His outlook or something is also, how to say, childish?
In short, he's an imbecile
-Yes, yes, yes
The places he loves to eat at are also really disgusting
Enough guys!
This badmouthing continued for 10 minutes
Ogata arrives at the scene
When he leaves the room, the two agents begin their fight
The managers are impressive
Looks like a real fight
Looks superb
What will Ogata do?
Can't stop it!
What will be the result?
Wait wait wait
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Stop, both of you!
What are you doing? What are you doing?
You're so noisy!
You have never made people laugh by yourself!
Eh?
I don't really think so!
If you weren't in Panther, your ability would be similar to XXX
So why are you so up yourself?
Why would you say such a thing?
Why fight?
I'm very sorry
-Sorry
Are you arguing about me?
-No, I was just too impulsive
Is he angry?
It looks like he didn't realize it was our lines
Not realizing the connection with Onigoe, he is instead traumatized
We've been rude
Do not say such hurtful things so early in the morning, its bad for the heart
I am very sorry
You too, what was that just now!?
I made a mistake
What do you mean a mistake?
I got a little overheated
Why on earth would you say something like that early in the morning?
"Early in the morning"
This is Ogata's style
When's a good time to say it?
Hurry up and realize
Is that what you've always thought?
He doesn't know much about you
What are you saying, I don't get it
I was just being too impulsive
If it was impulsive, can you say it again calmly?
Even if it's the truth, you can't say it?
I know it better than anyone!
I can't believe he accepted it
Although the content is right on the money, he hasn't realised the connection to Onigoe
The truth is revealed
He knows, right?
What?
What's going on?
What the hell is this?
You have worked hard
Ah...
Ah, this is you guys' routine!
After seeing them, Ogata finally realizes
You guys...are really good at criticizing!
That's our style after all
Which program do you think this is?
That... well...
So many times already...
This is how you're paying off your loans, right?
-You're so noisy!
The next target is
Komiya
He's too popular for his own good
-Indeed
His attitude towards his agent is very worrying
He is very...
His concept of male superiority is a serious issue
Very serious, especially in this day and age
Although he can be superficially pleasant, to the bone, he is mean to women
Komiya, with a suspicious air of misogyny
Will he join in?
What will be the result?
He's laughing
Laughing so hard, eh?
Girls or...
Not stepping in? What the hell!?
For some reason, Komiya is laughing a lot
This is a bad vibe
What's going on?
No action at all
Are you okay? Are you guys okay?
What? What's wrong?
You're so noisy!
What's wrong?
You can't be compared to Degawa and Kano because you're just pretending to be a decent guy!
Huh? What's going on?
-I don't really think so
You pretend to be a good guy, but when you participated in the song section of M-1 last time
You acted the fool on purpose just to get people to tease you
Eh? What's going on?
His expression has started to change
I am very sorry
I'm very sorry.
-Don't apologize
I think he noticed.
-He should have sensed something was wrong
Isn't this Onigoe's routine?
You've worked hard, Komiya
-Thank you for your hard work
Did what we wrote upset you?
Your smile suddenly disappeared at one point
Well, you have a point
Why didn't you do anything to stop the fight?
I couldn't help but laugh because my manager here was acting in such a lame scene
You should learn from the previous generation of Kano and Degawa!
Look how hard they work!
I don't see them as rivals, okay?
The difference between Degawa and Kano is that I have Aida with me
I have Aida with me
Is he on the same level as them?
Aida?
-Yes
Don't put it like that
The manager is laughing
The next target is
Still so strict with his manager
Panzetta Girolamo
He won't understand
This one should be the most difficult to get it
After all, he's not a comedian
This is his manager
Handsome
Does Girolamo know Onigoe's routine?
I don't think so.
-Oh
It's really not good
Girolamo, who does not know the original routine, will be faced with the manager's verbal violence
What will be the result?
Why is there a smile at the corner of your mouth?
Is everything okay?
Why are you fighting?
You're so noisy!
Who? Me?
You've lowered the reputation of all Italians in the minds of Japanese people!
Do you wanna smack?
Scary scary scary scary
So scary!
-Super scary
Suddenly said "do you wanna smack?" ...
-Whoa...
You've lowered the reputation of all Italians in the minds of Japanese people!
Do you wanna smack?
A sudden approach
Not good, not good, not good, not good
I don't really think so!
No way!
It's fine that he's a womanizer
I just don't want him to end up like Ishida
Is everything okay?
Ah, he's laughing. Great.
-He's smiling!
This is a first for me
Seeing HORIPRO people fight each other, I just wanted to cool everything down immediately
Because if the people at the top know about it, you might be fired
Let's go have a nice meal together!
Treat us to a cheap and delicious meal
Because the salary at HORIPRO is not that great
Girolamo, takes a sharp turn from "unpleasant" to gently defusing the situation
This is the most frightening aspect
So the truth is revealed here
He seems like the type not to be messed with
Ah...that's how it is
Do you know us?
Can't remember the name
You got shouted at, right? "You're so noisy!"
And suddenly said "do you wanna smack?
-We were sweating in front of the screen!
We were thinking "if a fight happens what do we do?"
At first I was really about to snap
But what he said was so ridiculous I couldn't help but laugh
Thankfully, a fight and being unable to televise this segment were avoided
It was touch and go for a while there
The last target is...
Sorry to make you wait so long
This is gonna be bad
TKO's Kimoto
This candidate is too good
Instead of letting us say it, we'll leave it to the manager to deliver it
This is a wakeup call
Feel like i'm about to see something I shouldn't
Managers really shouldn't say this sort of thing
But we are taking this opportunity to put everything out there
I hope this will help her to unload
A man who cares a lot about hierarchical relationships
What will be the result?
I didn't say it!
What's wrong with you?
As if it was my fault!
What do you want!
Wait wait wait
What's wrong? What's wrong?
You're so noisy!
Eh?
It's disturbing to be in charge of you at Shochiku!
-I don't really think so
But I hoped that you would take off like UNJASH's Kojima did when he left
But I haven't seen any improvements and just think that Shochiku is finding it harder to deal with you!
Eh?
Scary!
Scary scary scary
I'm very sorry. That was a little...
-A heated moment
I'm sorry for being too impulsive just now
Between managers, there's a little...
-What's going on?
Didn't realize?
Hasn't he seen our routine?
Despite having experienced it previously, he fails to realize the connection to Onigoe
Instead, he simply became irritated
Eh? Anyway...that...anyway, you know
I think it's good to have momentum
But after all, things have just begun, so...
Its a temporary thing, we have to be able to deal with it
This is the first time i've seen you like this
Lecture time!
So, he launched into "long-winded lecture that looked gentle at first glance"
Later
I'm really sorry
An apology is nice
This is the end
It's only natural
So that's what you think!
Unsurprisingly, he lets his real manager off
Okay, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah
I don't really agree with what you said
But it's good to talk about things
I really don't want to go in
Anyway, lets get back to it
Lets sit down
Although rude things have been said
-Yes.
Hm
The truth is revealed
You've worked hard
Thank you for your hard work
Do you know what's happening?
It's a show, right?
You didn't realize?
-Realize what?
That this was a bit like our routine?
I didn't... oh, the way you argue
-That's right
You didn't get it even with the second part?
-Not at all
You can see how big of a problem this is in my mind
It was so spot on
It felt like she finally said what she really wanted to say
And that name appeared
Is it too much to same that I envy him?
In summary
His target is Kojima
What's with the photo?
What kind of prank is the last photo?
It's outrageous, isn't it?
-What an outrageous prank
That part is not related to us
That's right.
-Yes
Girolamo is scary
"Do you wanna smack?"
-It's not easy to say that
I've never even said "do you wanna smack?"
Sounds like an enka singer's B-side
"Do You Wanna Smack"
You two chatting was also pretty bad
I'm sorry.
-Yes, it was
Because I didn't know it would be shown
-Yes
It'll definitely be shown
Those words were the most honest
After watching the broadcast those people should really take it to heart
When was all over, the staff said something that made us panic
Eh?
"All Kyojin's part cannot be shown"
The manager said it couldn't go out
The manager thought it'd be a problem
-Yes
We thought to ourselves, "this show has gone too far..."
Let's welcome the next presenter
Audrey's Kasuga!
Twoos!
Here we go. Thank you all
So, let's get to it
Straight to the point
If I don't get to the point, something big will happen. I know
This is the theory I bring you today
The area of Mutsumiso is still the best value for money in Tokyo
I lived in an apartment there for 20 years
The landlord hasn't been displeased with all the location shooting there?
No
This is the thing I appreciate most as a comedian
One time in the morning, for Wednesday Downtown
Someone came and banged on the front door outside, tried to smash it to bits
The landlord was laughing down below
He was the one laughing the most
The area of Mutsumiso is still the best value for money in Tokyo
So
Twoos！
Loud voice
Also wearing a mask
Good morning, everyone
One morning, a full of energy Kasuga visits the area of Mutsumiso for the first time in a while
I come and go when doing business in this neighborhood
Go back and see how it looks
Why?
To see how its doing
After all, I lived here for 20 years
Although I don't have this experience
I imagine it's like having a child with your ex-wife
A common scene in TV series
Watching from outside through the kindergarten fence
That feeling?
A long-awaited meeting with the loving and compassionate Mutsumiso
Kasuga is in high spirits, but
Ahhh
There used to be mailboxes here
It's gone!
The mailbox that used to be by the stairs
Dismantled
Here's the box
Moved to the entrance of each room
And
Ah? Is this door new?
Ah?
A new fan
Says "WEATHER COVER" in English
Imported goods!
Ahhh
A water heater!
Doorbell
Lights in the corridor
Small fire extinguisher
Kasuga moved out about a year and a half ago
Although it has undergone some renovations
Ah?
No change
Only the room where Kasuga stayed 201 remains unchanged
Somehow only 201 is the same
Cultural heritage treatment
Also, a long-awaited reunion with SIINA Miura, a second-generation artist living in the area
Who moved to Mutsumio a year and a half ago
Here, he is asked about his feelings of living here
How is it?
You've experienced all seasons by now
Nice, right?
-It's nice to live in
-56y/o building
-No bathroom
-With toilet
It's very, very nice.
-Right?
The first winter was hard, right?
Yes, the first winter I thought it was so cold
Sometimes when you get up you exhale white breath
Frequently
You get used to not having a bathroom
Completely used to it
Washing once a week was perfectly fine
In summer
-Summer? Wow!
Listening to their conversations, the merits of Mutsumiso were still unclear
Despite the atmosphere alone apparently making the area great for both old and new residents
So, we conducted a questionnaire survey locally
Which revealed an average monthly rent of 39,000 yen in Mutsumiso
To find whether places that are cheaper than this exist
We sought comedians proud of the affordability of their places
Is there anything cheaper than this?
There should be
To find better deals that Mutsumiso
The first place we travelled to is Nerima-ku
Ah? There's a guy staring at me. Is that him?
Hello, good morning
-Morning
The first comedian with super low rent is
With 14 years expereince, Royal Mizoguti
Mizoguti
The 1st floor is the store
It's a store
Mont Reple 6
This has probably never been shot before
It's the first time
First time shooting in your place?
-First time
The address is clearly printed
By the way, Mutsumiso is a great choice when it comes to location shooting
Standing by for a shoot
Covered up?
The address is blocked with white tape
This is for an on-location shoot
An interesting sight
Here
-Yes
What is this?
First of all, this is concerning
-Sorry
I have no sense of time
Warning myself not to be late
So you posted this
Does this work?
Nothing works...
-Then take it off!
It scares me a bit
Excuse me.
-Please come in
So many words
And air conditioning
The size of this room is 6 tatami mats plus 1 kitchen
When you walk into the entrance hall, you will see...
There are a lot of notes
-Yes
Have the life of a popular comedian
What is that sort of life like?
I'm not sure
It's better to take it off
By the way, the most recommended thing in this room is
Decent bathroom
What's that?
What is this?
There is a toilet. What is this?
And shower
-Yes
With washstand and shower
This can be moved
Wow
First time I've seen that
The wall there is a bit...
It's peeling at the corner pretty badly
What's up with that?
When it rains heavily and there's strong wind
Water seeps in through the cracks
This is not good.
-It's not good
To what extent does water seep in
To the carpet
With water-related advantages and disadvantages
The rent for this six-tatami plus 1 kitchen is...
This is the point
35,000 yen
With shower
-Yes
They crossed their arms at the same time
Like a master and a disciple
Then let's decide
Which is the best value: Mont Reple 6 or Mutsumiso
It is the current resident Miura who decides
Mutsumiso
-Very good
I think this place is very good
But Mutsumiso is bigger
The location is also better
All things considered, Mutsumiso is better
To find a better deal than Mutsumiso
Next, we travelled to Setagaya-ku
Is that the guy?
Is it you? The one who wants to fight against Mutsumiso?
What's with this greeting?
The second artist with extremely low rent is Samidare Taro
Go in like this?
-Yes
Walking 30 meters down the narrow alley
This is the place.
-Here?
Ohara House
Very neat
It was refurbished a year ago.
-Really?
Before it was entirely made of wood
I feel like i've been here before
I've heard you've worked here before
Ah right
Indeed, it was actually 6 years ago for an investigation...
It's here
-No...
Completely different
No... really?
-Yeah
The mixed structure of wood on the first floor and iron on the second left an impression
Looks like a shed
That feeling
Were there residents last time I was here?
Was it someone else?
-Another comedian
What about now? Are you the only comedian here?
Just me now
Yeah, because it's cheap
Comedians will be drawn to it
Are the other rooms empty?
Only one or two are empty
Isn't this corridor sloped?
Its tilted
I've been living there for 4 years so I don't notice it anymore
Really? It's super titled!
To this side
Seriously tilted this way
Particularly titled
You get used to it
6 years ago the corridor was tilted
Won't you fall over like this?
But it's just a corridor, let's forget it.
-Yes, it's nothing
It's just the corridor
Well, it's just a corridor
You said the same thing before.
-Eh?
The same thing six years ago?
-Yes
Whoa, so I haven't grown at all since then
In Ohara House
Samidare Taro lives in Room C, a one-bedroom six-tatami apartment
With refrigerator
-Included?
Air-conditioned
-With air conditioning
Also has a TV
-The TV comes with it?
Awesome
Impressive
Although the conditions are generally good
There are rats in this building
You've seen them?
-Yes
When I come back they scurry away
Escape through a gap there
No measures?
-Look here
Rat trap stickers?
-Yes
Have you ever caught with this?
Yes
What was the state of the rat? Was it stuck?
Two to three of them were stuck
-2 to 3?
Too much
I really struggled when getting closer
It's scary.
-It's a little unacceptable
Can you hear the voice of next door?
If they're on the phone you can hear their words loud and clear
An alarm clock goes off, I don't know if its mine or...
That's awful
Public bathrooms with public toilets
Ohara House comes with its own furniture and its rodents
Its rent is...
30,000 yen
Whoa!
30,000?
It's furnished, it has a shower, a toilet and a washing machine
But the decision rests with Miura
Out of Ohara House and Mutsumiso
Which is a better deal?
Mutsumiso
Very good
Is that really what you think?
The public area is a bit too big. You'll have to run into a lot of people
I care about that
But this was a tough matchup.
-Neck-and-neck
A very interesting matchup
To find a better deal than Mutsumiso
Next we went to Meguro-ku
Is that him?
Good morning
The third artist with extremely low rent is Squeeze Iwao who has been performing for 3 years
What is it with these names
Really nonsense
Over here
Where?
Here
-Here?
It's here
Yes
-Here?
Here
It's here
-Here?
Here?
Isn't it quite big?
It's not a question of whether it's big or not, right?
It's not a matter of size. Look how amazing it is here
Don't you think it's cool?
I'm not sure it has the right feeling though
Kind of looking forward to it
-It's a great place
Have a look
I'll open it
It's like a Ghibli movie, right?
The landlord lives on the 1st floor.
-Oh
The 2nd floor is an apartment
Looks like a student place
Climbing the steep stairs
It doesn't seem like this era at all
And no lampshades, just bare bulbs
Is this a darkroom?
Like a movie
Great
Very nice, very excited about the interior
Glad you like it
Here, please come in
So narrow!
So narrow
So narrow inside
Particularly narrow
This confinement-like room is only 3 tatami mats in size
This is a detention center, right?
Is this the room where Tony Ooki was locked up?
Has a prison vibe
This looks like the type of place that Wednesday Downtown locks people up in
Indeed
You don't feel enclosed? Just 3 tatami.
-No, I don't
There's no bathroom
TV can only watch channels 8 and 6
Why why?
Can't get a signal?
To watch TV, the window needs to be opened and the angle of the antenna adjusted
A 5 minute walk to the nearest station
But there is no bathroom. So, the price is...?
How much is the rent?
18,000 yen
So cheap!
Really? 18,000 yen?
Really?
Facing the super cheap house of just over 10,000
Miura can't help but hold his head in his hands
His decision was...
It's over, right?
Mutsumiso!
This was a tough choice
Its mainly the TV...
By the way, which one would you choose, Kasuga?
This place
After all, it's only 18,000 yen
TV is not worth 20,000 yen
By the way, this is the cheapest rent in Tokyo according to the staff survey
Are there any places cheaper than 18,000 yen?
9800 yen
9800 yen？9800 yen？Monthly？
In Edogawa Bridge
-Edogawa Bridge
16 minute walk from Waseda
-Long
A room that looks like a hallway
This is also attractive
It is the real 1st
In summary
If you want to move into the best house in the city for 9,800 yen, please contact us before it's too late
Interesting
What do you think, Okada?
If there's rats, ah, its difficult
Every day as well
-Every day?
Every day there is a rustling sound when opening the door
Occasionally they get stuck
What do you think, Kendo?
Kasuga, seeing you do location shoots
I'm always very moved
The wobbly-walking Kasuga
Yes, it looks better after editing
Its even worse during the recording
Next is everybody's theories
Magical Lovely!
-Too early!
-Thanks
Magical and lovely
-Yes
That's right, thank you
Without a doubt, we are Magical Lovely
Comedians bringing out songs is pretty common, right?
Hamada has
-From time to time
Not really from time to time, but yeah
Your husband too
-Yes
My husband sings pretty well, but his partner sings like shit
You are too biased towards your own husband
That's why it only sold 30,000 copies
That many?
-That's still pretty impressive
There are many popular artists who have released songs
First of all, please listen to this
Harisen
Reached #195 in the charts
With "Song of Friends"
The theme song of a Keroro movie
Should've sold well then, right?
Isn't that great?
-Yes, it is
Only 400 copies were sold
Not even enough to full the Lumine theatre
Not enough to fill Lumine
No way
I thought to myself, what are my peers doing?
Surprisingly, despite the popularity of Harisen
They only sold 400 copies
So, this time, we bring a theory about comedians' CDs
The worst selling comedian CD in history is Harisen's "Song of Friends"
There's people from Keroro Gunsou in it too, right?
-Yes
And fans of it
-Children and so on
These people add up to 400
It really is "Song of Friends"
Lyrics like grapefruit
-Not many friends either
What does "like grapefruit" mean?
Like... is there such a song?
I think there was a song called "Song of Friends" before
What does everyone think?
Don't pass it off to everyone else!
We have also done a song
-Really?
A song called "Bayashi"
-Never heard it before
Of course, no one downloaded it
It didn't even come out as a CD.
-Ah right
The worst selling comedian CD in history is Harisen's "Song of Friends"
So, before announcing the list of the worst sellers
Let's take a look at the top ten comedian CD sales over the generations
That's good to know
No. 10 to No. 4 is shown above
Born from the popular variety show "Urinari
Songs from here make up the bulk
Next in 3rd is
Tunnels
Tunnels' "Here Comes the Rattlesnake" with sales of 1.4 million
Next in 2nd is
Them again
"Timing" by BLACK BISCUITS with sales of 1.48 million
Impressive
So Unari shows its power again
The biggest success is
There it is
Caused a movement, eh?
As you know, it is H Jungle, which is our Hamada
WOW WAR TONIGHT with sales of 2.13 million
Now we know the top artists list
Let's take a look at the worst selling CDs
First in 10th
COME ON BABY" by GO☆TO, also known as Goto of Soccer Time, with sales of 1079
He released one?
-Goto did
Next in 9th is
Oki KODAMA-HIBIKI's "chi" with sales of 1068
Next in 8th is
Kenji Hirai songs covered by Ken Hirai, 954 copies sold
Could've sold more
7th place is "Proposal in Daejeon" by Tetsu and Koto's with 824
This is too humiliating
The cover shot is quite good
6th place goes to Kano Eiko's "Welcome! Handsome Man☆Heaven" with 626 copies sold
Seems like it'd sell well
But a year and a half later he scored success with 50TA
A huge difference
The next one was super big
Next in 5th is
KERO! and MARCH 2008" by Kozuki Tsuchida and Kanako Yanagihara with 523 copies
Impressive
An unexpected collision with Keroro Gunsou
By the way, Keroro Gunsou has worked with many comedians
Among them, there is also the odd pairing of Ogawa Naoya and Iwasa Mayuko
Next in 4th is
Kajiwara sung the theatrical theme song of the Battle Team series
New Horizon
-Yeah
Finally, its time to look at the top three
3rd is
What?
The ED song "I Hate the Night" from the anime Gegege no Kitaro
Performing this song is
An old acquaintance, Hidekazu Nagai
2nd is?
2nd
Harien's "Song of Friends" with 398 copies sold
Not even 400!
So at this point, unfortunately, the hypothesis has been disproven
Finally, the number one lowest selling comedian CD is
What's this?
The group 5uppers born from the theater "5up Yoshimoto"
"Each Story", with 363 copies sold
5uppers?
-Never heard of it
The hell?
Gross!
With SEAMO as producer
From more than 100 artists, these six were selected to form the group
Unfortunately, their sales were low
In summary
5uppers only made 380,000 yen
I think the Goto one is interesting
He also did it
-He's pretty into it
Seriously?
-Seriously
He's good at guitar too
Scary
Only sold about 1,000 copies
What do you think Nonomura?
The 5th place Tsuchida and Yanagihara is the most unbearable
There's nothing to say
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03