WDT Project
Timers: Kannibleklown, Phantom Translators: Zebestt, Mugicha, GakiNoSuitGuy, Xueshi
Hello and welcome to Wednesday Downtown everybody!
Here is our first guest, come out please!
It's Fujisaki Market!
Hello! We'll be in your care!
The crowd is like...
Yes that's bad.
Even I'm a bit like 'huh?'
La-la-la-la gym?
Don't you remember that?
Ah they do!
That was 10 years ago!
10 years!?
It's been that long.
When you look at the crowd's reaction...
...we're definitely guys from the past.
Completely.
We brought something related to what makes 'one hit wonders' like us very happy...
...a theory about "Where are they now?" programs.
Eh~
Here it is!
Theory: You can't point it out if someone completely different showed up to a "Where are they now?" program.
Yes!
That's what it is.
What do you mean by "you can't point it out"?
Since years have passed since you last saw them, and faces can change as well...
...we thought that it would be hard to notice.
I see.
Going "you're not that person!"
Yes.
So you're saying they wouldn't notice, right? It's not that they are doing it out of consideration
Yes, and...
...even if they notice it, they wouldn't be able to say it out loud.
Oh it's what this program is famous for: Nobody gets anything out of this.
After this, in a "Where are they now?" shoot, a complete stranger shows up!
Can they really not say anything about it?
Hello-ssu
Also...
The theory that people who have signatures even though they're not famous are kinda weird.
We look into half-entertainers' signatures.
And then...
The theory that if you make people living in a peninsula draw a map of Japan, their own peninsula will stand out.
Theory: You can't point it out if someone completely different showed up to a "Where are they now?" program.
What kind of people are
chosen I wonder?
With that, our first targets are...
It depends on the
person too, yes.
This is "Where is that nostalgic person now?"
Right?
Ginshari
And the fake person they will meet is...
The person that you will meet is Kakefu-kun.
They're wearing an
outside version of
their usual clothes.
Oh I see.
I used to watch it!
That's a good one.
This type of segment's classic, from 30 years ago...
*Masayuki Kakefu played for the Hanshin Tigers 1974-1988
...Kakefu-kun, who was really famous for looking like Kakefu from the Hanshin Tigers*
This was a good choice.
You won't be able to tell right?
You are familiar?
Of course, I was born in 1980 so...
...he was a really big star as a kid actor.
It's amazing.
If you think about it though, wouldn't his face be completely different?
But that type of face doesn't really change.
You think he stayed the same?
If you talk about change, it should be completely different since it's a stranger.
So we'll see if they
can say it?
We quickly go to meet with the fake Kakefu-kun.
Right?
That's a good spot.
Does this mean he's doing voice acting or something?
Oh really, "Voice Acting Academy"
Oh if it's a place like this...
Waiting for Ginshari is this gentleman...
It's a completely
different person!
...with a setting that the actor is trying to find work in voice acting.
This is quite questionable!
With that...
Is it here?
Isn't that him? Right there in the middle? Definitely!
He looks a bit like the current state of Kakefu-san.
At this angle...
It's 100% him!
The one talking now?
Absolutely!
Undoubtedly.
If you pass each other on the street, you wouldn't see it.
You won't go like "Wait-"
Will they question it?
Of course not.
I'm not living thinking about Kakefu-kun all the time.
It's really easy to see though isn't it?
But they're believing it.
They are.
As we said, the face doesn't change that much.
They are taking the 100% changed Kakefu-kun...
...as completely real.
It's an entirely
different person.
Wooaah this is it, the smile!
They're into it 100%
Truly nostalgic!
Ultimately, they end up feeling nostalgic from a complete stranger.
This is impossible.
Embarrassing.
Their first meeting.
They have no intention of questioning his authenticity.
Really, the theory was
right it seems.
Could you please if I might ask?
Yes, I understand
It's a stranger though.
You didn't have glasses back then right?
Right.
Could you please take them off?
You made a good choice
with this person.
Isn't this amazing?
This is it!
You're exactly the same!
This face!
Getting super excited for a fake.
You're shaking hands with an unknown old man.
By the way, the real Kakefu-kun looks like this...
This is a 9 year old video but...
The general aura is similar.
...he seems to still be the owner of a convenience store.
Oh I see, right.
The fake one looks
more like Kakefu-kun.
It's easy to tell them apart like this.
At this rate, we won't be found out so...
...we go with a pretty out-of-the-box fake scenario.
I currently have five kids.
Five kids.
Five? You have five kids?
Yes.
Come kids!
This...
You kids don't look like Kakefu-kun do they?
What's up with
this geezer?
Of course, they're all strangers.
They don't look similar.
Introduce yourselves then.
I'm Masayuki, I'm 12 years old, nice to meet you.
Masayuki?
I'm Mayumi, 11 years old, nice to meet you.
Mayumi?
They're Hanshin
players' names!
I'm Kouichi, 10 years old, nice to meet you.
I'm Akinobu, 8 years old, nice to meet you.
Yes, thank you.
I'm Yutaka, 4 years old, nice to meet you.
Aren't they all named after Hanshin players?
I know Mayumi, but the rest?
Akinobu right?
Okada Akinobu
You really know their first names!
Masayuki?
Kakefu's full name is Kakefu Masayuki right?
Yes.
Amazing!
They can't seem to be
getting away from
this good feeling.
With them not questioning the reality of the situation whatsoever we can stop filming.
He isn't wearing
the hat.
They are only pranking
these guys?
With that, here we reveal the plan.
In reality, this isn't a "Where are they now?" program but...
...it's Wednesday Downtown.
They all become like
this when they hear
those words.
Hold up for a minute, are you for real?
What kind of trick was it?
That's right!
I can't find the thing.
I don't see it.
They were too smooth.
With that in mind...
...wasn't there anything weird with today's shoot?
Ah, they asked them.
Eh?
The kids are all fake maybe?
It's not just the kids, but the entire thing. Then we explain the theory.
They're not seeing it.
The theory is: You can't point it out if someone completely different showed up to a "Where are they now?" program.
Someone else?
Eh-eh?
Wait for a sec...
This person isn't Kakefu-kun at all...
Who the hell are you!
You really were yapping back there too!
Really?
This is so embarrassing.
Making him wear the hat and going "That's it! That's it!"
Eh- What is this?
What kind of prank is this?
The theory will definitely pass!
Yeah!
Somebody who questions it would be weirder!
Going like "You're not Kakefu-kun"!
This is a great success.
Then, how will it be going for a more recent person...
...and lowering the quality?
The target is...
"Where is that nostalgic figure now!?"
There he is!
Punk Boo Boo's Kurose
That last one was
too hard then?
So today we'll...
Yes it was.
...be meeting with a nostalgic figure-
Ah- sorry, excuse me, sorry.
Who "that person" is going to be...
...I currently don't know.
That crow sure
knows how to caw.
Really, yes...
...can we not shoot somewhere with less people passing through?
He's really unlucky.
The fake person Kurose will be meeting is...
Kurose-san will be meeting...
... Hamada Brittney-san.
It's not that old is it?
The gyaru?
Since I'm currently homeless...
About 10 years ago, Hamada Britney had a break as the homeless gyaru manga artist.
That kind of thing
is hard to guess.
Ten years ago huh?
We prepared a fake person, with the setting that she's working at this pet shop.
But it's kinda hard.
I wonder if the fake
person is a gyaru?
Ah- There she is!
She is?
I can see traces of her.
Traces of her?
A bit, yes.
She hasn't changed too much.
Looking from far away, he seems to be feeling the vibe.
They keep making
themselves believe
even more.
How will it turn out?
I'm sorry, good day.
Hello-ssu!
Wiss Chihassu!
There it is!
This is so forced!
She's so different.
Are you Hamada Brittney?
Yes-ssu!
Yeah- there it is!
It's completely fake!
So nostalgic, this tension!
Hello-ssu!
You're bad.
Your makeup is so different from back in the day!
Did it give me out?
But if you look at it closely...
...you have the vibe.
Of course man!
On top of not looking similar, the acting is also bad.
If you look at it knowing she's not similar at all but...
...for some reason Kurose seems to not notice.
By the way, the real Hamada Brittney currently looks like this.
She manages a company based in the catering industry,
She seems to have
toned it down.
Certainly seems so.
as well as writing a manga series.
You didn't have a home, right?
Yah
I told you guys, I was homeless back then.
That's right!
Her speech pattern
is crazy.
What are you doing nowadays?
You can't tell by lookin'?
I'm a pet breeder, yo!
Hamada Breeder
You're Hamada Breeder now!
Despite the awful acting, Kurose seems convinced.
Even the awful manga slips by him.
And thus, the fake and dubious recording finishes without incident.
It's so obviously fake.
This is nuts.
So we explain the project.
That person...isn't Hamada Brittney
NO FRICKIN' WAY!
Nice to meet you.
Ehhh? You're not?
Nope, she's not.
No way...
I didn't even know.
What did Hamada Brittney look like again?
Since it's nothing more than a tricky prank
She became much paler.
We made the last person easier to tell apart.
Our next target is
It's a nostalgic 'Where are they now?' segment!
Fujimon would definitely
be able to tell.
A veteran entertainer, familiar with pranks from Lincoln, Fujimoto Toshifumi.
He's quite finicky
with details.
You're right.
And the impostor that Fujimoto is about to meet?
I definitely couldn't
tell the difference.
A psychic magician with 40 years in the business, who rose to popularity during the supernatural power fad in Japan:
The spoon bending guy!
Uwaa they picked a great guy!
It's harder with
foreigners.
Uri Gellar.
This is a bit...
What'll they do?
Uwaa you really did it! The spoon spoon guy!
He remembers the
guy, that's good.
And so, our target arrives at his appointment with 'Uri Gellar'.
The guy should obviously
be foreign, right?
It should be obvious.
Hello!
Just like with Korean faces...
Ah, he'll probably get it.
He's totally different!
It's nice to meet you!
This is so obvious!
So that's how it is.
We're just going to pause filming for a minute.
He kinda has the
right aura though.
We're in your care today.
What did he find?
What was he looking it?
So what's the reason for you coming to Japan this time?
He came to promote his new song, which is now on sale.
There's no excuse
for believing this!
Eh? Right now you're...
Sorry, um, what do you do now?
He just sings.
A mega-suspicious imitation Gellar.
Um, right now,
are you able to show me your psychic powers?
I'm sorry, I can't today.
Not today.
Hmm... I see...
A request for one song is accepted,
but the spoon bending is completely denied.
And so, the promised new single, "Shimauta".
This is so strange.
His face is
gradually dropping.
C'mon man, hold it in!
He can't take it.
Because the song is so bad, Fujimoto can't help but laugh.
"I really want people to buy my CD."
Yes, of course.
The atmosphere is
so awkward!
But I wonder what the
impostor is thinking?
Well... it was certainly something.
I don't know what either
of them are thinking.
It's a well-matched opposition
between these two.
We now reveal the prank.
He should think it's all pretty suspicious,
but did Fujimoto notice that it was an impostor?
How did the meeting go?
Is Uri Gellar okay?
How do you mean?
I mean, this will NEVER sell!
So he doesn't seem to doubt that it was Uri Gellar himself.
The truth is...this isn't a 'Where are they now?' program.
It's Wednesday Downtown.
It came around too fast!
They hooked me in too quick!
So what was this about then?
What kind of theory do you think it is?
I have absolutely no idea.
Theory: If a completely different person appeared on a 'Where are they now?' show, you couldn't point it out.
But the guy was a foreigner!
So it was kinda uncomfortable then?
Ya obviously!
What was uncomfortable?
The crappy song!
So there you have it, 'Where are they now?' pranks are inevitable.
Don't you think the difficulty was too high?
I don't think so.
Because the ideal thing here
is that Uri Gellar will get loads of girls.
So how was it everyone?
Well...
Because I'm kinda suspicious of you guys
I want to see them do that thing.
I wanna know if you're the real deal.
Do some of your 'la la la' thing.
Yeah, please!
Please believe us if we do it.
They're the real thing.
Eyesight testing exercise~~~
It's the working version.
You didn't laugh though.
The quality of laughter confirms that you're real.
Please stop that!
Continuing on, our next presenter is this person, please come out!
It's Hakata Daikichi!
Thank you for having me on.
He's the real deal.
Yep, I'm the real deal.
It may be sudden, but by your feet
There should be a pen and paper.
Ah, yeah I was wondering about that.
Could you write your own autograph for me?
Please make it out to Yoshio-
Ah, my real name is Yoshioka Hironori.
The joke's over, so let's return to the writing.
Autographs huh
My theory is related to autographs, so I want to see yours.
Okay everyone, please show us your autographs.
That's it.
Oh, you really wrote an autograph.
You've written "To Yoshio Ka-" at the top
Ah, because I didn't have enough time.
Please stop playing around with hiragana and write it in kanji.
It's too informal.
I'd like to hear everyone explain their autographs one by one.
I'm really sorry, it's different from my original autograph.
I shortened the kanji for Matsumoto Hitoshi.
And this used to be a 'DT', but I can't really see it anymore.
Ah, you write a 'DT' as in Downtown?
So it used to be much clearer?
I used to write it much more clearly, yeah.
Okay, moving on to Asao
Since I'm an athlete, a lot of kids ask for my autograph, so I write it in hiragana.
When did you decide to write it that way?
I decided to play beach volleyball in 12th grade
So while I was commuting on the bullet train I'd practice my signature.
And so, the theory I have brought with me this time is this:
Theory: "Although they're not famous, they have their own autograph - cringe"
Isn't that okay?
But there are people
who write their names using only kanji.
It doesn't count as an autograph
They write out every stroke.
Yeah, they're not all swishy like autographs.
Shouldn't the "cringey" part be "that hurts"?
Well you see the "cringey" part
I'm leaving the 'cringe' parts up to you.
You're waiting to hear "That's so cringey!" from us.
I see, I understand.
Theory: "Although I'm not famous, I have my own autograph - cringe"
I think it's cringey.
An autograph: an entertainer's proof of identity.
You get restaurants with
loads of autographs like that.
Firstly, to the entertainers: When did you come up with your autograph?
I've never thought
about it before.
Our investigation starts with a look at comedians
and the location of this investigation is Yoshimoto's comedian training school.
Ah, the training school.
I wonder if they
have autographs?
Do these pre-debut entertainers have autographs?
Is there anyone here who has an autograph?
Ahh, so there are a couple.
Oh you already have your own signature?
Only 6 out of the 54 have an autograph already.
The majority haven't made theirs yet.
I would find it embarrassing.
Since I haven't had my debut I haven't needed to autograph
Look at the guy
behind him.
so I would find it presumptuous.
It seems that most of them develop an autograph when there is such a demand from fans.
For these 6 people who have developed a signature, let's hear their backstory.
There's an oddball there.
I thought of it when I struggled with a comedy sketch.
Since you were struggling with a sketch you thought of it?
Yeah.
5 years ago
when I entered the underground idol scene I thought
I will continue to protect it.
When I went to the villain's assembly...
There are all kinds of reasons but
some of them were quite cringey.
What about those who aren't comedians?
When did sports stars develop their signature?
Pleased to meet you.
The comedian Ikeda Tetsuya who has participated in 150 high school baseball matches.
Let's ask him about his autographs during high school.
Did you have your own signature when you were a high school player?
I could see him
writing many.
So do I.
I never saw anyone sign anything.
I wonder why.
So he didn't
have any.
When it was the birthday of Watabe
from Unjash
we all signed a card for him
to give him as a present.
We had been playing for years
but among us no one autographed it.
We simply wrote our names with kanji.
Nakamura went to the same high school
so did Yasuda.
These two also wrote their signatures on the gift.
Both of them used kanji.
Even if they were
famous at the time.
Even if they were already pro
they didn't have a signature?
Indeed. They did not.
It seem that for baseball players they don't develop a signature until they start going pro.
What about people working the company
and who have celebrity-like tasks.
How is it for announcers?
Do announcers have their own signature?
Since we often need to express gratitude
I think that everyone writes autographs
but there are many who don't have quick and stylish signatures.
In block letters they simple write:
TBS Announcer X X
Indeed, if we look at the autographs of the female announcers at TBS
then there are some who have thought of a composition
but most of them write their company name and then their full name.
But among them one draws all the attention.
The announcer Hayashi Minaho.
Her signature like a long time comedian.
She's doing it.
She really does have one.
We unfortunately couldn't ask her directly about it.
It makes me curious.
I see.
Mean.
This is way too mean.
We now understand more about the basics of these signatures.
It takes off from here.
Let's get back to the main topic
Are there people who aren't celebrities who have a signature?
Multiple times winner of the Japanese award for stylists - the odd duck: Matsumoto Takuma
I would like to inquire
He's a stylist, right?
do you have your own signature?
While he is an amateur he does have experience being on TV.
Does he have his own signature?
I wonder...
Can you show me your signature?
This is it.
He totally had one.
Perfect.
Totally.
Seriously?
I finally understood the title.
When did you make this signature.
Back when I was a little boy and practicing writing.
What do you mean?
Dare I say that
that already back then I was thinking of becoming a person who people wanted an autograph from.
That's actually a
great backstory.
One could say it's a bit perplexing?
Somehow I would end up on TV
I had this weird confidence.
Really?
The age at which he developed his signature is a bit odd
but his dream of appearing on TV came true.
And charismatic shop employees who gather a loyal shopping crowd have their own signature because of it.
It seems that among the general public there are some who also have their own signatures.
Let's begin a quiz on non-performers who have some relative fame and see whether they have their own signature.
"Barely a celebrity: Do they have a signature or not?" quiz.
First off...
Excuse me.
Pleased to meet you.
Former member of the House of Representatives.
She's definitely
has one.
This is all of a sudden but
I want her to.
can I have your autograph?
My signature?
She's so energetic.
Sure.
I'm happy to be asked to give an autograph.
I think she has one.
Please write it here.
Since...
I was a member of the parliament until recently
I have't written many, to be honest.
I'm getting nervous. It's a bit embarrassing.
Until last year she was living the life of a congress woman.
When asked does she have her own signature?
Asou, please give us an answer.
I think she does have one.
She must be getting used to being asked several times.
I wrote it.
Can I ask you to show it?
I've never shown it on TV but here it is.
There's a heart.
Found it.
That's 'larious.
What the heck.
When did you make this?
Since there's a
heart in there.
It's a bit embarassing but
when I was in high school I thought of it.
This kind of thing shows
during that period.
When did you have the chance to use it?
In high school I really liked Amuro Namie.
When I saw Amuro Namie's autograph
I tried to copy it with my own name.
Have you written this autograph while you were in the Diet?
If I wrote this while being in the Diet
I would be told: "Don't get too cocky."
So I didn't write it during that time.
So I still haven't used this much still.
Next up is...
Professor Kishi Hiroyuki.
May I ask you
to give me your autograph?
Autograph.
Lately he's been appearing in variety shows.
He doesn't have
one, right?
His main job is as a university professor.
Please don't have one.
However, does he have his own signature?
Yuki, please answer.
I don't think he has one based on his reaction.
Please show me.
I simply just wrote my plain name.
It's average but
drooping a bit.
He doesn't have one.
Is it drooping a bit?
My handwriting is just sloppy.
When I stay at a hotel and have to sign
I wrote like this.
So this isn't an autograph, right?
It's not.
Since I am a commoner.
I despise fools who aren't comedians and think they need their own signature.
Swift decapitation.
Next up...
Yeah, the previous person.
He was so straightforward.
Excuse us but this is TBS.
Mister Sasuke: Yamada Katsumi
Please give us your autograph.
Why are they asking
him at his entrance.
It's the same Yamada Katsumi as on the shows but
I wonder...
I think he has one.
Let's see if he has his own signature.
This one is difficult.
Please respond, Fukawa.
It makes sense if he has one. He has one!
Please show us.
It's this simple thing but...
He totally had one.
He totally did have one.
What did you write?
Yamada Katsumi. So here is Yamada and here is Katsu.
He really has thought
about everything.
And this one is a bit strange but it's "mi".
And here I wrote: Mr. Sasuke.
What about the other Sasuke All Stars members?
Don't they write their
autographs too?
Yes, everyone after appearing and getting tons of support
develop their personal signature.
Even the young ones who have...
appeared 2-3 times on Sasuke.
Or within appearing 4 times
they start developing their signatures.
One step ahead, right?
You think it's a bit too rash?
Yes, I do think that.
You aren't there yet, you punks.
I think that some of them are aren't quite on that level yet.
Let's survey more people who are only half-celebrities.
The next half-celebrity is
Quiz master - Furukawa Youhei.
I don't think
he has one.
Can you please show it?
He had one.
And it's quite cute.
How did it become like this?
Since my name is Furukawa so I wrote Furu and Kawa down here and with the line on the Furu I wrote quiz and then I...
Following that...
He sure took a
lot of effort for
that design.
Endou-san
Ah, good morning
Head of the Japanese Arm Wrestling Federation: Endou Mitsuo
Can you show it to us?
I wonder what
it looks like?
Here's how it looks like
"Your body's resilience is your heart's pride."
His favorite motto was there, but it still retains its original form.
It wasn't that distorted.
It isn't thrown
off-balance.
Following that...
OSU
Mister-OSU
Wada Kasumi-san
Mister-OSU, do you have a signature?
OSU
Which does that OSU refer to?
IT'S OSU.
Here it is: OSU
The start and end are surrounded by OSU
But it wasn't much of a signature.
Can I inquire about this unique stamp?
This stamp is?
I had it made.
So it's an original stamp?
Yes, yes, OSU.
The stamp writes out OSU.
OSU
Made from sperm whale.
As if a stamp of the CITES treaty.*
*Also known as the Washington Convention.
An old reference just like Mister-OSU.
And now we will return to the quiz.
Pleased to meet you.
Aah, I wonder
if he does...
Good morning.
In the outer sphere of the celebrity world:
This one is difficult.
the café located near our filming studio.
It would be odd if
he had one but
it could be fun.
The owner of the café.
He always asks me drop by!
This might be sudden but...
could you give me your autograph?
What?
Please.
I bet he doesn't
have one.
He has become slightly famous since RG (Razor Ramon) has been impersonating him.
Then I wish
he has one.
However...
Fujita Nicole, please answer.
Against the odds he might have one
Could you please show it to us?
He did!
No way!
When did you develop your autograph?
When was it...
I basically never had to write autographs.
I was asked by a talent way back in the past
so I started developing one just for fun.
What is unusual is that he doesn't use his full real name.
Of everyone in the panel, Hamada, please answer.
What is the full name of the owner?
I don't know his full name.
It's something like Fukuda something.
I only say Fuku-chan.
Oh, so you call him Fuku-chan.
How should this be read?
It's simply pronounced Fukuda Yukihiro.
I tried to read it.
But I wrote it a bit artistically.
Therefore the correct answer is Fukuda Yukihiro.
And for the last one...
Excuse us.
Yes...
Hello.
Often appearing in comedy sketches,
the mother of Tanaka from Ungirls: Tanaka Mieko.
Could I have your autograph?
Autograph?
Yes please. Your autograph.
That's fine.
After all she does
appear on TV a lot.
While it's true she has many appearences she's still considered an amateur.
Matsumoto, please answer.
Considering her response so far she probably has one.
Please show us.
Here it is.
She totally had one.
What's written there?
I wrote it with kanji and romaji.
Tanaka (田中) and Mieko.
I've had it since I was young.
It seems everyone
has one.
Does your son know
that his mother has her own autograph?
I don't think he does.
He would probably go: "Why does mom have her own autograph?"
And he would probably get angry.
And that's it. In the world lots of amateurs seem to have their own autograph.
How does it make you feel?
Only Kishi refuses to have one it seems.
While watching it only Kishi-sensei conveyed my feelings.
Who was the most surprising one, Nicole?
It might be the owner.
I was surprised to know he had one.
It seems that both of Downtown
call him Fuku-chan, right?
Hamada seems to really know him well.
I speak with him informally.
I thought he was over 1000 years old!
Has he passed 1000 years?
It could look like it.
But you are all the same age?
I wonder what has have to happen in someone's life
in order for someone to look like that.
I wonder how someone becomes like that.
But something like that makes a thing like coffee taste better.
And let's not forget the stamp
made from a whale's tooth.
That one had the strongest impact.
Next up: Let's explore the theories that various people come up with.
And this time the presenter is...
It's Tamura Kenji!
When I say the word "peninsula"
you might all think "which peninsula", right?
The Hokkaido peninsula.
That's not a peninsula!
It's an island.
You picked the wrong person
for asking such a question.
It feels like I set it up for such a response.
For me it's Chita peninsula and Noto peninsula.
Noto peninsula, right? There's even a song about it.
Therefore, here is the theory that I am bringing to you.
Theory: "Locals who live on peninsulas, when asked to draw their place on the Japanese map, would exaggerate their half by a bit."
Wouldn't that naturally turn out to be the case?
So that's how you perceive it?
After all when asking Japanese people to draw Japan on the world map.
Japan will obviously be prominent.
With that being said let's return to the present:
Will the locals indeed exaggerate their peninsula?
I'm not so sure about the fact that you still stumble on your lines today.
This time, I will be bringing... Huh?
There are a lot of good places to visit and good drinks are plentiful.
And they are kind people, aren't they?
I fully understand, so...
What was that exchange about?
Theory: "Locals who live on peninsulas when asked to draw their place on the Japanese map, would exaggerate their half by a bit."
With that being the case: Firstly, let's go to the most prolific peninsula in Japan.
It's the most easy to understand and outwardly protruding Noto peninsula.
But before this, for the purpose of our theory, we asked people who lived in Tokyo to draw a picture of Japan.
Shikoku, chuugoku, Kyushu, Okinawa, Hokkaido
He drew the most
minimum outline.
Along the coastlines, don't you remember there were some peninsulas?
I don't know much about that.
Regarding geography I am not so familiar with it
I mean other than the outline of Japan nothing much comes to mind.
If I had such a good memory to begin with, I wouldn't be called a pig-head.
And I wouldn't be loitering jobless in the streets.
There were no peninsulas and no work to be found.
If that's the first person to start off with...
As we continue with the investigation...
This is Tokyo.
It's pretty nice.
Shikoku and Kyushu.
He drew Boso peninsula and Kii peninsula
but he has completely ignored the western Japan sea side.
Others drew without any peninsulas.
Most people in Tokyo drew without any peninsulas.
Furthermore...
I can draw a map of Japan.
Only Japan, right?
This is Shizuoka.
Is it Shizuoka?
Yes.
It's protruding a bit.
What are those 4 things?
Shikoku. (The four islands)
Shikoku isn't split into pieces
Shikoku - are they islands?
Aren't they split apart?
Too cruel
towards Shikoku.
Aren't they like Hiroshima?
Of the 20 people in Tokyo who included a peninsula in their drawings...
only made up 3 of them.
Back to our main question:
Asking the people living in Noto peninsula to draw a map
Well it's obviously
going to...
Will they really exaggerate their peninsula?
You chose to shoot
that person?
Are you a local?
Yes, I am.
I was born and grew up here.
She will definitely draw
their peninsula in.
We would like you to draw a picture of Japan.
Raised in the peninsula.
Japan? Sure I can do that.
Indeed, there was exaggeration of their peninsula.
Kyushu itself was bigger than usual.
Well it is the place where I live so, I made it stand out a bit.
Following that, this person too...
This sure is flustering.
What the heck is that?
Here is Noto peninsula as it should be on the map, like so.
Sado peninsula and here is Noto peninsula.
Over here is Hegurajima.
Indeed, they exaggerate the area which they are living in
to the extent that one would believe that the center of Japan was their peninsula.
I wonder if her son
is living in Naha.
How did it come out?
It became a bit too big.
Since this is the important part.
It came out big because it's the important part?
Continuing our investigation.
Where is the Noto peninsula?
It's very easy to tell.
Here.
Ah, there.
Isn't the Noto peninsula a big too large?
It's big indeed.
That's how it naturally comes out.
For people in Tokyo they do not draw the Noto peninsula however...
as expected for people living there . There was an emphasis in their drawing.
However on the east side
they draw it clearly.
What about
an even smaller peninsula?
The next place we will explore is where Namahage is famous
Akita Prefecture - Onna Peninsula
Can I ask you to draw a map of Japan?
Map of Japan?
Yes.
This is how it goes.
Aomori prefecture should go like this.
Since I'm old and my sight is bad I can't draw so well.
Wait, what did he say?
However even with a small peninsula it appears on their maps.
And then thereafter...
What about the Onna peninsula.
It's right here.
It's sticking out.
It's here.
Yeah it sticks out.
I drew it.
I see.
Since we are in Akita prefecture I guess it is overrepresented on the map.
And the guy looks like a certain male figure.
The peninsula they live on clearly appears on the map.
Stop it. It ain't me.
For everyone who lives on a peninsula
exaggerate their own place.
However...
Hello.
Ah welcome.
Do you want some candy?
Eat some candy, here.
What?
Eat candy.
Candy?
I don't need any.
Do ya dislike candy?
No I like it.
You like it? Do ya?
Yes.
Is this your hometown?
It is. I was born and raised here. Hehehehe
I will live here until death. Hehehehe
Hokkaido #####
What!?!?
Hokkaido is diamond shaped.
How do you feel about the drawing?
This looks strange.
Why didn't you draw Onna peninsula?
What!?
This is Onna pennisula right here.
Her voice is high.
Because I lack common sense.
Lacks it.
I'm without common sense.
These two lines should be connected.
This is the ocean around it.
It's the ocean that's around it.
Around it?
The ocean... it's the ocean...
Our conclusion is that besides a person without common sense they do draw it with emphasis.
Please stop with the close-up on peoples mouths.
Besides people who lack common sense.
Without.
How was Hokkaido?
It was different indeed.
I was wondering if this is also a peninsula.
Where?
Oh this thing?
This one?
I was wondering the entire time.
If you ask him "what peninsula is that?" he will tell you something incredibly funny.
What peninsula is that?
This little thing?
The peninsula of TamuTamu
Eeeew.
Why give me that response?
It's your fault for asking.
Matsumoto.
Don't leave your juniors out to dry.
Next time... the sumo match that occurred last month.
Let's recruit teams where their collective weight is under 170 kg.
To learn more go to our website.
Check out our Facebook and Website for more Wednesday Downtown! This video was subbed by a community run project called the Wednesday Downtown project. Thanks for watching!
Next week we have a theory about finding the contact info of comedians only by inquiring through their ex-partners
And the former girlfriends of comedians will suddenly appear.
Won't this clip cause major concerns?
Furthermore...
Do you think you can win?
Osu
Mr. Osu will appear in a national karate tournament.
How will it end?
Let's look into for how long people in different age groups can go out?