It's gonna be like this
Really?
-Yeah it's just like before
Still gotta do things like this
The person coming today is the same as before, right?
Probably
The guy from Osaka
Then let's get him out, please
It's this one
This one is more trouble
Why do you talk as if you don't want to see me
It's a 2m 4cm one
No, I'm 188
That's pretty tall!
Well, there's no time to lose
Today the theories are all the same theme
There is a theme that unexpectedly comes up a lot, what do you think it is?
There are a variety of topics
Eating contest?
There are quite a lot of eating contests
-Indeed
It's actually music
So, we have selected some and formed this project today, which is this:
Music Theory Day
We are taking inspiration from TBS' music special "Music Day"
So, we bring you an episode full of musical theories
First of all, do you remember this project? Please take a look
It is possible to create feel-good lyrics just by using the names of comedians
This is an old one, ages ago, right?
-I don't remember it at all
Hey, do you remember? Did we do this?
You probably forgot since you've seen so much since then
This was on 100 Seconds Doctor Academy
※Dr. 100 Seconds Academy is a former Downtown show
No, no, no, no. How is that possible?
It's a theory
It was 6 years ago
How could anyone remember that?
Music arrangements with only the names of comedians
An attempt to form a song with a good feeling
That was the theory
This time we replaced the second verse of a song with the name of comedians
After the original first verse, the changed second verse comes up
After listening I may remember
6 years ago
Bearworm
New York Skyscrapers
A shooting star is a messenger
Like this? We did this?
Always from here falling in love
Maybe I was off during this period
My home in Downtown
Dangerous nights
※Knights written as "nights"
Unstable nights
If you have the chance to come a second time
Hi-Hi you're such an idiot!
The real kids are already a middle school student now
※Real Kids member Yuuki resigned from Yoshimoto in 2014 due to his debt crisis
Goodbye light of youth
There are so many different people!
Gorgeous high heels
Comfortable asian silk
Wagyu's cola cake
Replicas of the giants
X-GUN's bike, kawasaki motorcycle
Bearworm sings well
ZUN ZUN ZUN
"Hello Keisuke" "Hey Taku-chan"
Same gender are really congratulatory
This was the first verse from that time
The second verse is by Koga Ken
Nature in the Grassland
Rainbow in the blue sky
Isn't twilight under the rainbow great?
Don't know any of them
They're all combos right?
Australian Vacation Quiet Couple Time for Two
Well...a little niche
Map Messy
So old!
Suddenly, into the jungle
Pocket Monkey
Koala, panther, woolly-nosed wombat
Koala became that?
With two pistols BANBANBAN
Chasing light trucks
Hey, that kind of name...
Monster Engine A-Slip-Smoke
Thank you, President of Japan
Good singing
ZUN ZUN ZUN
Here we go again.
-Don't need them again
Who are you guys? Boyfriend
Love triangle is not impossible ha
The story is finished
That's it. Do you remember?
No, I don't remember at all, even after listening to it
Even with the photos below it...
Yes
He said "so old" when Messy came up
※The group formed in 1979 and disbanded in 2008
That I don't agree with, what do you mean old?
The others were more recent
Then suddenly there's people even older than us
But he really has no memory of it
We were both so unimpressed
So why bring this back now?
Next on Music Theory Day is...
Regarding the "Who do you think you are" part of Hikaru Utada's First Love, the theory is that everyone at karaoke sings "Who will you be thinking about daha-"
This time we were assisted by this KTV
And firstly talked to some visitors
We are looking for people who can sing First Love well
And launched an investigation under the guise of a singing test
The singing is viewed with a fixed camera
And so, the test begins
The last kiss with the flavor of a cigarette
Don't need this part
-It's quite long
Will she really say "da-ha"?
Where will you be tomorrow?
Very good at singing
It's the part after this
Who will you be thinking about daha-
Coming! Coming!
She sings "daha-"
Must feel a bit stupid
The second person is...
This woman
Where will you be tomorrow?
Too interesting
So emotional, singing so powerfully
This person will definitely sing wrong, right?
Who will you be thinking about daha-
It's like they're going to "da ha" supermarket
Also sang it
Next
Who will you be thinking about daha-
Very cute these two
Don't sing it wrong! Don't sing it wrong!
Wrong
The friend of this one also takes no issue with the singing
By now, three people have sung incorrectly in a row
100% rate
After that the investigation continued
Sure enough, most people sang "da-ha"
Let's listen to Utada Hikaru's First Love again
Who will you be thinking about daha-
She also says "daha-"
To be faithful to the original song, you'll have to sing "da-ha-"
So, what about  other artists who have covered First Love?
First is this person
May J
Let's verify
Where will you be tomorrow?
May J is good!
Be careful, May J
Don't sing it wrong!
Who will you be thinking about dala-
Surprisingly sings "dala-"
Next is the talented Taiwanese singer, Lin Yuqun
Who will you be thinking about dala-
Two people in a row singing "dala-"
Has "dala-" become mainstream in covering this song?
Next is the well known cover from Tokunaga Eimi
Where will you be tomorrow?
Who will you be thinking about?
Be careful
Brother, please!
A normal recitation
Next is...
JUJU
Where will you be tomorrow?
Who will you be thinking about dasa-
Dasa-
This is a joke, right?
This one's awesome
Surprisingly, the majority of covers sing "dasa-"
Anything's fine
What about the one we all know well?
Otomo Kohei
What is the synergy between Otomo Kohei and "daha-"?
The last kiss with the flavor of a cigarette
A bitter and tiresome fragrance
Where will you be tomorrow?
Careful!
Here's the important part
Who will you be thinking about dayo-
Careful
Dayo—
Not all of them are "da-ha-" but also "da-la-" "da-sa-" and "da-yo-".
Next on Music Theory Day is...
The lyrics of "I'm going to Tokyo" by Yoshizo is exactly the same as that of an existing village.
The theory was as follows:
We contacted 183 town halls throughout Japan...
...and conducted a survey on the synchronization rate with the lyrics of "I'm going to Tokyo" and ranked them.
So, is there really a village with a 100% synchronization rate?
So, we asked a man with the likeness of the original singer...
...to provide a word-for-word version of "I'm going to Tokyo".
Firstly
In fifth place is Nagano Prefecture, Shimo-Ina-gun, Sagi-mura
In addition, all of the videos played along with the song were filmed on location in Sagi-mura.
There's TV...
There's radio
Not many cars on the road
There's piano...
There's no bars...
There are police patrolling...
Got up in the morning and took the cows for a walk for over two hours.
There's phone...
There's gas...
Buses come five times a day.
I'm tired of selling shellwood.
Going to Big Tokyo.
For Tokyo, go to Iida Station first.
It takes an hour to drive...
There's guitar...
There's stereo...
I've seen this guy before
There's tea stores and restaurants.
Closed but still there.
There's young people...
Elementary school, middle school, all just one school together.
There's a pharmacy...
No movies...
Tourists unlikely to visit.
No ballroom...
No peeping toms...
Do you know about laserdiscs?
No, I haven't been.
Laserdiscs, who are you?
Although there's a karaoke...
...can't sing without a reservation.
No evening papers.
No magazines.
Occasionally a notice board is passed around.
Only two signal lights...
...our village has electricity.
But shellwood is for sale.
Got a hot spring.
The hotel has a hot spring.
Youth is regained.
In summary, the synchronization rate of the lyrics is 37%.
Next is tied in fifth place...
...Watarunakiki Village, Shimajiri-gun, Okinawa.
Next
Second place is also a tie between two villages
Nosakogawa Village, Yoshino-gun, Nara Prefecture
And Tokyo Aonoshima Village. The synchronization rate is 40% for both.
So, the place with the highest synchronization rate with the lyrics of "I'm going to Tokyo" is...
Kagoshima Prefecture, Kagoshima County, Mishima Village.
Located about 40 km south of the Satsuma Peninsula.
Mishima Village, spread across three small islands, wins 1st prize.
There's TV...
There's radio...
Not many cars on the road.
There's a piano...
No bar...
One policeman patrolling...
Got up in the morning and took the cows for a walk for over two hours.
There's phone...
There's gas...
Doesn't even have any busses.
I'm sick and tired of Mishima Village...
Going to Big Tokyo.
Going to Tokyo, got to go to Kagoshima first.
The ferry takes four hours.
There's guitar...
There's stereo...
African drums are also popular.
There is no coffee shop, but there is a bed and breakfast.
There's 20 young people in their 20s.
There's no high school, not even one.
By the age of 15 all students leave the island.
No pharmacies...
No movies...
Occasionally a boat comes.
No ballroom...
No peeping toms...
There are laser discs available.
The karaoke only has 28 songs.
Only 28 songs to choose from.
Newspapers come four times a week.
No island-wide broadcasts...
No traffic lights, seriously...
But then again, the power is always on.
But in Mishima Village, but in Mishima Village...
...there's a hot spring.
Although there's a hot spring, there's no locker room.
There's nothing around it.
In summary, Mishima Village's lyrics synchronization rate is 44%
In all of Japan...
...even the closest villages only has a synchronization rate of 44%.
So what if we expand the scope to villages around the world?
Will there be a village with the exact same lyrics as "I'm going to Tokyo"?
Expanding the scope of the survey to the world...
...for the village that best fits the lyrics of "I'm going to Tokyo"...
...the world's top ranking is...
Laikipia County, Republic of Kenya
Samaritan Village, Bois-Rob region, Neri County
That's quite a find
-Yeah
What exactly is its lyrics synchronization rate?
That's it!
Absolutely.
The live video shot in Kenya reveals the details.
Can't even see any wires.
It's true. You can tell just at a glance.
No TV...
No radio either...
No cars either...
No piano...
No bar...
No police patrol but there are warriors.
Get up in the morning, take the cows and basically walk around all day.
No phone...
No gas...
Not even a road where a bus can run.
I'm sick and tired of Samaritan Village.
Going to Nairobi.
To Nairobi, first through the roadless wilderness.
Drive for six hours...
No guitar...
No sound...
No African drums, no instruments.
No coffee shop...
No meetings...
The village is full of young people.
Grandma, grandpa, I can't tell how old you are.
No pharmacies...
No movies...
Apply aloe vera to minor injuries and pains.
No ballroom...
No peeping toms...
What are laser discs?
Karaoke even less likely.
Singing is ceremony not entertainment.
No newspapers...
No magazines...
It is said that there is no writing in the village.
No traffic lights, seriously.
My village does not even have electricity.
But this is Samaritan Village, but this is Samaritan Village...
No disputes, no wants, no needs.
No disputes and nothing to do.
Drinking in the daytime.
To sum up, the lyrics synchronization rate of Samaritan Village in Kenya is 77%.
Next, remember the theory related to Yoshizo's commercial songs?
I think I remember this one.
-A commercial song?
Workman and New Japan House were both used for commercials but only one is remembered
Seems familiar
You may remember one but not the other
I'm used to living in my house~
That's New Japan House
And Workman
Eh... really?
Really?
-Yeah
Then listen to it.
-Okay
New Japan House, please listen
It's coming back to me
It appeared every now and then
Walking and singing.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah
Mmm, I know it
So you don't remember Workman?
But after listening to Workman it might come back to you
Workman is this one
Really?
-Incredible
It can be said it's different
From here it's very...
Ah yes
Everyone, Workman together
-So it is
Hamada you can sing along if you listen to it
If you listen to New Japan House first, you won't be able to remember
It's Yoshizo cutting corners
It's not that
Next on Music Theory Day is...
After being scolded, it would be hard for Yaguchi Mari to let out her "sexy beam" when "Koi no Dance Site" is playing during karaoke.
When thinking of Yaguchi's time in Morning Musume
Her signature "sexy beam" move always comes to mind
This time, Yaguchi is given a lecture by a friend
Wow so mean
An actress with whom Yaguchi has a close personal relationship
Her angry must be scary
They are very close
So, Yaguchi and her friends start singing karaoke together
Good atmosphere
Really good vibe
Finally, time for the lecture
If you don't know anything about current affairs
You should have the self awareness of not studying hard enough
But I don't think you have to tell me that
Why do I feel the need to say this?
I don't know. You...
Have I done something to you?
What i'm saying is the staff's opinion, not mine
Surprisingly, Yaguchi rebuts and a heated argument begins
This is bad
So serious
And even if you say that to me now
What can I do in my work from now on?
I don't know
I should refuse work?
This argument continued for a period that cannot be broadcast
Finally...
I don't want to do this either
Yaguchi begins to cry
Next
Forget it, help me choose the song
Even if Yaguchi is in this state
Why did she choose this song?
Will she still do her signature move, the sexy beam?
How could she
Every time you fall in love, heartbeat Bon Bo Ba Bon
That's right, the first page of life
No, still crying
Crying
If she's told the truth she won't be happy
Just update it with the sexy beam
Quickly!
It is completely impossible to do it
Of course
So, the program team entered to explain the situation
I hate this
I really hate this
Sorry
Its over...
Wait
This one is terrible
I'm so sorry
I don't think that way at all!
Their friendship has deepened
I'm really sorry. I'm really sorry
I don't want this either
Why is it still 1 2 3 4
Next on Music Theory Day is...
No one will notice different lyrics to a famous song played as BGM
The investigation was conducted at this coffee shop
First of all, the first song is
TUBE's "Ah-Summer Vacation"
Is the chorus changed?
To change the lyrics of this song
The singer will be BETU, who has a similar appearance and voice
It'd have to be, otherwise it will be exposed immediately
These targets were called out on separate days for fake interviews
Fujimoto is very sensitive
The song is played while the person waits for the interviewer
Can they detect that the lyrics have been changed or not?
Chris may also realize
Chris knows a lot
After all, he loves ballad songs
First, the normal lyrics
I saw you through the bamboo curtain in Shonan
Everyone turns and has you in their eyes, feel so good
He's listening very carefully. Is it okay?
Because the vocals are very close
The three people have not yet discovered that it is someone else who is singing
From here, the lyrics will start to change slightly
First of all, "Ah-summer vacation" of Level 1 chorus will become slightly different lyrics
Change here?
They'll be found out, right?
What will change?
Dangerous to do it here
Ah Love summer
I see
It's like this
After all, it was a very subtle change that all three ignored
Next is Level 2
The second verse has a summer feel, but the content is completely different
Night falls, yukata and fireworks
The unicorn will undergo a test of courage at night
There are still swimsuits on the beach and swarms of surfers.
I can't see through your eyes, time goes by
Chinese cold noodles or runny vegetarian noodles
The back keeps shaking as if to tell something
Just continuous summer vocabulary
Five-person family, a watermelon is not enough to eat
Glistening lipstick, wet and writhing, I've got you
The smoothie that was eaten at the festival
The tears buried in the sand are good to forget
Whose cover is this?
Who's cover?
So quick
Impressive
Really!
The fireflies are so beautiful.
Hesitation is gone and the bellworm are crying
Chris realizes
However, the remaining two do not react
The next Level 3 lyrics all become winter
This will definitely be noticed, right?
Winter Love, is the snow going to melt?
Hold me tight, isn't it a dream? Such a beautiful meeting
My love will even melt the ski slopes
Every summer I fall in love
Doesn't work, it not Maeda's voice, i'm not feeling it
Pink snow, Lovers are Santa Claus and hearts are dyed white
It's all right to hold me in your hot skin
Ah, New Year's Day
Ah, summer vacation
Uncle will give you a red packet, baby
Some tired of swimming, chest cool baby
This is a spoof version, right?
Fujimoto did not react at all
What New Year's Day? Don't be ridiculous!
And so we reveal the truth
We are from Wednesday Downtown
What did you put in this?
Didn't put anything in it!
Why suspect such a thing
How could I not notice it?
I know "Ah-summer vacation" ah
I feel sorry for Maeda
Then, the two who didn't respond are also informed
It's getting cold. When did it become winter?
Sure enough, didn't notice at all
But Fujimoto...
I noticed it!
But I just thought a funny cover version came out
I didn't not know if it was the original singer or not
Can you not do this sort of unexpected thing, please?
Indeed
It's true that if you change the meaning of the lyrics completely, someone will notice
Next we try another song
Eiaki Tokunaga's "Radio on the verge of breaking"
The lyrics will be written by...
Why?
Hollywood Zakoshi
The targets are these three
What will be the result?
Ito
There are many imitation artists
HanmaKanma
HanmaKanmaHanmaKanma
What is this?
HanmaKanma? Whose version is this?
What does it hope to convey?
What's the meaning?
Is this pirate radio?
After all, there are many covers of Tokunaga's works
Is there such a version?
HanmaKanma version?
Always singing HanmaKanma
The result is that HanmaKanma was exposed instantly
Your singing sucks if you don't have teeth
We go out into the street and talk to people who have no teeth
Excuse me
Excuse me, we are TBS
Seriously TBS?
-Yes
Any proof?
A wise man
"It's okay to sing a song"
We will provide these participants, who are willing to open up their hearts
With the opportunity to join a toothless karaoke contest
First of all, the first person without teeth is
I'm Fumio Shima, 67 years old
Sloppy speech
I have only 2 teeth left
Thank you for having me
Participant No. 1
Shima Fumio, who has 0 teeth on top and just 2 on the bottom
A nice close-up
Q. What is the reason for the loss of the teeth?
Mostly because of fighting and tooth decay
A frivolous and wasted youth
Always a fight at the drop of a hat
Little things like bumping into you while walking
And so on ... when I was young, I was like that
It is indeed hard to understand what he's talking about
Yes, if it's not subtitled...
But the issue is still the singing
-Yes
His speech seems to be somewhat impaired
Will it affect his singing?
No need to write "2 teeth"
Shima, who usually works in the warehouse as a sorting agent
After work, he goes to a small bar he often visits to drink with the female owner
This is his only pleasure
So, please listen to this song brought to you by Shima
"Love Can Can" by Misora Hiba
Can he get the "Can" out?
The rain falls on my body
I'm not sure if I'm happy with the way things are going.
People are really sad, with a sad existence
I can't believe they shot all of this
This show is the worst
Where does he chew?
Even so, the past still creeps up on me
Life is incredible!
Very good at singing
Very good, good singer
The singing is unexpectedly good
Accidental?
How many points will be scored?
Thought I could...
Can't understand what he's saying
This time the scoring will be done with special mixed rules
What are the rules?
Given that fewer teeth can be detrimental to singing
The number of teeth will be subtracted from the karaoke score
The final score will be determined with a toothless handicap
Since Shima got 80 points in karaoke
After subtracting the number of teeth
His final score is 78
Incidentally, the number of normal human teeth is 32
In other words, even if a person with a full mouth gets 100 points for singing
In the end, the most they can get is 68 points
I see
This makes it easy to understand
It is not a question of whether it is good or not
The No. 2 contestant in the Toothless Sing-Off is
0 above, 4 below
Tatsuo Ueno, who retired to work in a restaurant, aged 66
Even with teary eyes
You can't stop me
Nowadays, there are no more
The view from this side is normal
Only this side can you see the teeth
Things that can be lost
Not from this side
The tempo is great though, right?
Love is everything
Now I could swear
Saturated with love
So intense, so intense
Ueno-san scored 90 points at karaoke
After subtracting 4 points for 4 teeth, he gets a total of 86 points
Next is contestant #3
2 above, 4 below
What the hell!?
Nobuo Hata, who runs a small bar for a living, is 76 years old
How could you leave it like that?
Men's Fountain Festival
Also good at singing
The singing is also very good
Really good
Born to carry and believe
Keep the camera away
It has nothing to do with teeth at all
Celebrate, celebrate, celebrate the festival
This is great!
Can get the sounds out right
The smell of the land is engraved in my heart
The young man's hands are an irreplaceable treasure
Don't need teeth!
I'm happy
Participating in this program has given me confidence
The score for Sanaka Hata is 91 minus 6 for the number of teeth
He receives 85 points
The highest score so far
But Ueno goes down a place because of the toothless handicap mechanism
Unfortunately, he ranks 2nd
Next is contestant #4
0 above, 5 below
Masao Kiyomizu, 72, who works as a security guard at the construction site
The neon lights of the streets are beautifully interlaced.
Yokohama Green light, Yokohama
A bit off
Open your ears!
Unfortunately, the karaoke score was not as good as it could have been, with a total of 70 points
And so, he's ranked in last place currently
It is very clear to hear
Next is contestant number 5
6 above, 0 below
Akiha Masamune, who works at the construction site, 59 years old
Don't panic, bride Samba
Women are always mysterious
Good taste
Akiba was the only contestant to select this style of music
He scored 80 points
Finally, the last toothless opponent
Mamoru Kaneko 49 years old
He's young
0 teeth
He lost his teeth in his 40s
Only the gums are left
How come?
Q. What is the reason for the loss of the teeth?
Uh... why...
Always fighting
A bunch of rebels
Q. Did fights cause all of the total loss?
This led to broken teeth
Apart from fighting
Well, there was a little bit of abscess leakage...
Q. Is there anything you can't eat?
Something I can't eat...
No
Losing the first at 27
The straw that broke the camel's back
Surprisingly, it was down to soba
Listen to this song brought to you by Kaneko, who doesn't even have a single tooth
I can't even sing the popular songs of the day, so old-fashioned
「SINGLE BED」
It's been a year since I left you, trying to become a good man
But at this age, born with a naked heart
Even if you learn to dress up and change your car, the result remains the same.
Hugging dreams and your time in a single bed
The two people who used to laugh at each other because of boring little things
How many points will he get?
Well, I was nervous
Kaneko comes in 4th place, and the final results are as shown
So, teeth have nothing to do with whether one can sing well or not
It's hard to remember music ones
After all, we prefer to see others being bullied
Bullying is bad behavior
When I drank with you once, Matsumoto, I remember your tone of voice being very firm
The next theory is something that was proven 6 years ago
No one can understand the chorus of SADS's "Forgetting the Air" the first time hearing it
Do you two remember?
Possibly...
Can't understand what he's singing, right?
-Yes, yes, yes
I remember this very well.
-Really
6 years ago, we sought to see if someone could understand it instantly
At that time, the studio guests were invited to undertake the challenge
Only understood the last part
Isn't the last sentence "can you hear my voice?"
At the end, right? I heard that one
No one could understand it the first time
Too difficult
Under the caramel-colored sky, I can hear the song
Can you hear my voice
I'm calling it quits
The correct answer is as follows
Under the velvety sky, you can hear the song
Avoiding bullshit nonsense, I can hear my voice
Did he really sing this?
Bullshit nonsense
This...
Isn't it just bullshit?
He really sings it like this
Yes, yes
I remember this one
This theory was tested
So lets verify another song
This time, there is a bonus for you two
If you guess correctly the first time, you will get 100 million yen
It's only fair to be excited
It's ridiculous to the extreme
If it was 100,000 instead
Totally uninteresting
Then let's change it to 1 million
It's okay, right?
Do you think we will agree to that?
So we found a song that surpasses "Forget the Sky"
Can you guys tell what the lyrics are in one go?
That overflowing with loneliness
Memories of me in retrospect
Repaint the field of view
What?
It ends "give it to him", right?
That's it... the end is "give it to him"
Is the song "Your Damn Tiger Teeth"
"Give Him Your Damn Tiger Teeth"
Get your tiger teeth
And give it to him
What kind of lyrics are these
He didn't say "give him your tiger teeth"
To the old man with missing teeth?
-Yes, yes, yes
The old man with missing teeth turned his head when he saw an old man with missing teeth
"Give him your tiger teeth"
Why is SADS singing this kind of song?
It's a song written for Ueno Shopping Street
That's not correct
Let's hear it again
-"Damn you"...
Listen carefully once more
Repaint the field of view
Why did he have to keep saying tiger teeth
I can't hear anything else
"Be serious, dammit!", right?
That sounds too weird
According to you, the lyrics have always been very unreasonable
This is his world view
Yes...
-Let's announce the correct answer
Please watch this
Repaint the field of view
Giving beauty to the feathers as if they were sharp blades
So it's a sharp blade
What a shame!
Blade...
-Blade and Tiger
No no no no...
Although the world view is cool and unique, people can't understand
So hard...
After singing this, you'll forget how to sing "Workman", right?
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03