Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
This 'aint bad
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Someone gonna come out?
It's Magical Lovely!
It's Magic Love!
-It's us
Your collar looks a bit damp
I've never worn this before
It suits you so well!
I want to wear it for the rest of my life
Didn't we win the championship in M-1?
Do you remember the segment we won the championship with?
The S&M tax one, right?
That was Football Hour
-Oh
Your statement is a bit problematic
Did you see it?
The bicycle bell, right?
-That's Tutorial
This isn't a guessing game!
What about you?
How do I say it? Is it the one with the hoops?
Ah, that's the one
I'm hanging on by a thread here
What's so concerning about this?
We won the championship with this segment
This time we brought this hypothesis based on the routine we performed in M-1
This is it
In light of Magical Lovely's "ring" routine, even on a shaking train, Noda Crystal should be able to keep standing without using the hoops
So that's it
This is it
-A remarkable hypothesis
After half a year, we finally made this project
What does everyone thing, does everyone here regularly ride the train?
I usually use it.
-I don't use it much
Do you ever ride the Yamanote Line or something like that?
Never, right?
-No
Never use the Yamanote line
-So you never use it
As expected, since when did you stop using it?
When I became a big shot
It's true. I don't see many big names on the train.
-I guess so
Next: Don't grab the rings! The Noda Crystal Championship
This is not good.
-This is too difficult
And
Excuse me, can I?
-Of course
If a random old man suddenly appears to give advice
And then later appears the recording site as a director
Will the comedians hastily change their routine?
In light of Magical Lovely's "ring" routine, even on a shaking train, Noda Crystal should be able to keep standing without grabbing the ring
Probably not JR
Not JR
Don't grab the ring! The Noda Crystal Championship
They all went to Chiba!
You're in the zone, Noda is in the zone!
Like the segment we performed in the M-1 final last year
This time we will challenge whether its possible to not grab the ring on a shaky train
Why's he there!?
This time, in addition to Noda Crystal
There are also the following four players who have expertise in physical strength, balance and railroad knowledge
This lineup is awesome
How do you feel, Noda?
I really do not need to grab the ring
I'm just here to show you that.
-But you fell on the floor, didn't you?
I was in a bad state that day
Let me introduce the rules
Everyone will stand on a 45cm diameter platform in the carriage
So small
The challenge is to not fall off the platform from the starting station to the end station
The stage for implementing the validation is
A local route in Chiba Prefecture known for its violent shaking, Kominato Railway
Kominato Railroad this tram itself is very old
The shaking is the same as that of the Showa era
There are a lot of corners.
-I see
And so, they get ready
Shakes a lot
So small
They'll all be out super quick, surely
This is too small
It's small.
-Much smaller than I thought
How do you feel when you step on the stage?
So small
It's small.
-Too small
The moment I stepped on this platform, I didn't feel good
But I think, in a usual train ride, you usually have a small amount of space
Why are you still wearing a jacket?
Why are you not showing your muscles?
So maybe its not too difficult
What are you doing here?
How do you feel, Orakio?
No problem at all
I rely on my sense of balance
Yeah, he's a gymnast
I won't even move a bit on this
Looks so strong
Yamada seems pretty suited too
What are you doing?
Pretty impressive
He absolutely can't
From the first to the last station
A total of 18 stops, the estimated travel time is about one and a half hours
Who will be able endure until the end without grabbing the hoop?
Who? Noda has to win!
-Yes
So, the Noda Crystal Tournament begins
It's my tournament
So this is the Noda Crystal Tournament?
It's moving
But now the car is still very slow, right?
I do not want to grab the ring!
Quite slow, quite slow
OK OK OK OK OK
If its like this, its fine
If it suddenly speed ups, what should we do?
-Its unpredictable
Can feel a sense of gravity
The sense of vibration is transmitted to the centre of the foot
The horizontal shake is also very strong
It's tough
Gotta stand for an hour...
It's difficult
It's faster than I expected!
It's pretty fast now
This is bad!
So this is how it is!
So hard
Shaking so much
Look at the rings, they're shaking so much!
So shaky!
Yes, you can watch the rings
Moving up and down a lot too
I can't.
-This is really hard
The thought of standing like this for a long time is tough
With more violent shaking than expected, everyone is shocked
Never seen anything like it
Then
We're going into a big turn now
I wonder how everyone will deal with it
One minute after the departure, the train reached a big turn
The whole thing is tilted
Definitely can't keep this up for an hour
It's too hard
I can't.
-Might not be able to hold on
So hard
Ah!
This is very difficult
Noda's in trouble
It's really shaky!
This is really impossible
Its impossible
Once the energy is not concentrated its dangerous
All they can say is its impossible
Even to one station is hard enough
Oh, no
-Eh!?
This guy sucks
-Too bad
No, wait.
-Are you serious?
What are you doing?
1 minute and 33 seconds into the game
Haven't even reached the first stop yet
Unexpectedly, Noda Crystal is the first to fall
How dare you grab the ring, just don't grab anything, fall straight to the floor!
That's too dangerous...
No, Noda!
What is the point of this verification now!?
I'm glad you guys are holding it together!
Your routine wouldn't even be finished after this amount of time!
Honorable Mr. Noda, so soon
I can't do it
Sit down
Absolutely impossible
It is not absolutely impossible to do
Everyone is holding on, Yamada and the others
Absolutely not.
-Yoshikawa is still going
Can't even last one stop
Our main character is gone
-Noda!
With Noda gone, what are the rest of us still doing here?
Coming to a stop?
Stopping time, stopping is not good
Stopping is indeed quite scary
Whoa!
It'll happen like this
Ah, not good!
This is so tiring
It is true, this is common when entering the station
Ok, got it
We've passed the fork point
This kind of fork in the road is very dangerous
We've arrived at the station, coming in there was a lot of shaking
Will it shake here?
We've stopped now
Yoshikawa is still going
Shoji, it feels so tense here
I don't really train here much
Who'd use this part?
It's time to go again
It's too fast, isn't it?
17 stops left
It's still early
Everyone pay attention!
Noda, you!
It takes a while to pick up speed to begin with
Go home, you!
Isn't it a little too fast?
It's really too hard, isn't it?
Get off at the next stop!
It's too hard, isn't it?
It's too fast. The car is still picking up speed.
It's overtaking!
So scary!
Next we will enter a big turn
Turning in this state will be tough
A big turn
This is a relatively fast state to turn in
We're all shaking in the same way
Hold on!
Yes, everyone is in a similar state
Are we there yet?
See, I told you! Yamada can't do it!
Don't say "I told you Yamada can't do it!"
Are we there yet?
Yamada has fallen!
Yamada! How come?
Carelessness
Six minutes into the match, Yamada drops out of the race
How do you feel?
It's not a usual type of shaking
I kept my balance like this
So my legs are at their limit
I see
It's only been two stops?
It shouldn't take long for everyone to fall, right?
I'm exhausted
Is it tiring?
Quite exhausting
It's gone. It's gone.
-So fast!
The departure is so fast!
Yoshikawa is surprisingly tenacious
After that, the fork in the road that produced the violent shaking just now reappears
Focus
So
By the way, here's the thing, the fork
If you fall it should look like this!
I do want to do the same
Yamada didn't do it either
This is it
This is the effect you want
Damn
What a beautiful fall, Shoji!
Nine minutes into the game, Shoji drops out
On the way to the third station, more than half of the people have fallen behind
It's too fast
One stop at a time.
-Is this project really okay?
Gymnastics practice is worth it
Left, retired Orakio
And Darling Honey's Yoshikawa
He seems to know this line
In fact, in the interview before the start of the competition
I know Kominato Railway better than anyone else
The degree of shaking, the turns, I know it like the back of my hand
No problem
How many times have you ridden it?
This railway...
50 times or so
Awesome!
50 times?
-Yes
So it's no accident that Yoshikawa has made it this far
Thus, its a battle of body vs mind
The two sides both tolerate the shaking for the next 15 minutes
It's pretty shaky.
-Yes
Ah not good
So shaky!
Is it really that shaky?
Even the rings are shaking loads
More shaky than expected
You'd surely fall
Ah!
Yoshikawa has won!
Yes!
So happy!
Darling Honey's Yoshikawa wins the championship after 23 minutes
Impressive!
However
Well, I was wondering, can I continue to the end of the line?
I am alone
Eh?
Haven't we got the railway under contract now?
-Yes
This is too wasteful
So the next step is out of Yoshikawa's interest
How much can the record be extended?
What the hell is going on now?
A person who looks like a train conductor standing in the middle of a shaking train, what is this?
After that he continued his lonely challenge alone
And lasted an hour in the shaking train
So strong
Finally
Oh wow, so dangerous!
Yes!
Darling Honey's Yoshikawa - Complete Railroad Domination!
Awesome!
Thank you for your hard work
That's awesome
Can't even stand up anymore
He's become a ring, just like in our routine
I really have no desire to try this again
It's really too tough
Thank you
He's not even in the same dimension right now
So let's move on to the second round
Eh?
Don't talk as if we all know about it
We didn't even know there was a second round
Yes, in fact, Kominato Railroad is the first round of the challenge
The total score of the next round will be added to determine the final winner
How about the bottom 60 points?
This score is really not reasonable
The venue for the next round is
Ladies and gentlemen, we have arrived at the site of the second round of the competition
Quite far away
The second round...
There's no train here
The second round is to ride this
That one
Eh?
Bus
This also has rings, right?
The second round is to take the bus that runs a cross-country route
There is no bus that runs this kind of line
This is not the same as the shows you watch when you're a kid
The second round of the race is to take the cross-country bus line for 2 minutes
Holding the side, sitting or falling will result in a loss of points
These are the rules
Although it is a competition, its more like a punishment game, right?
How many points are deducted for falling down or holding onto something?
Touching the handrail or the body of the car results in minus 5 points
If you accidentally sit down, you lose 15 points
If you fall on the ground, congratulations, minus 30 points
If I fall twice, I'll get a zero?
-Yes
Am I a 100?
-Yes, 100 points
And what is the score of the person behind me?
It's me. I have 90 points
I'm upset there's only a difference of 10 points between us
My advantage is too weak, right?
Fall twice and you're at the bottom
Your love of the railway is now useless
I've lost all motivation
So, the challenge is from lowest to highest score in the first round
One by one!
First, Noda Crystal takes on the challenge
Noda, are you ready?
My goal is a perfect pass
Please
To maintain a score of 60
Good
Show us how cool you are
Like walking to the stage of M-1
Looking good
Wow, it's so narrow!
To avoid injury, there are some protective measures
Next is the second round, Noda's challenge.
Start!
Come on!
Padding all around
So caring
What a gentle program
Immediately after the start, the first challenger is greeted by the snake area
What'll happen?
The vehicle is now moving
It's not easy
Too fast!
Sitting!
Then held the armrest
Contact!
Awful
Sitting!
Don't mess around here
Seriously, it was super unsteady
Contact!
Contact! Contact!
The whistle doesn't stop
Sitting!
Contact!
He's losing points!
-It's bad
Next is to pass through the longitudinal bumpy area of the big bulge
Now it's 0 points, right?
Not fell over yet
Contact!
Fall!
Straight down
Contact!
The last section is the highest difficulty
The score's already bad enough
Sitting!
Score continues to decrease for sitting for 3 seconds
3 2 1 Sitting!
You can't even stand up.
-Stand up!
Can't stand up really
3 2 Contact!
Still holding on
-What's wrong with this guy?
Contact!
Fall!
The End
That's hard to top
Looks like a tough fight
It's bad. I'm going to throw up
His face is bloodless
Really, you look pale
Noda, if you want to throw up, there is a bucket over there
How do you feel, Noda?
As it went on, it becomes a battle to not vomit
-Is that so?
Noda's score results are as follows
His meager savings from round one were squandered in a flash
Final Score -265 points
What are you doing here?
Next is Yamada's challenge
Do we have to see Yamada, can we not?
Contact!
Although there was partial contact, he did not fall completely
Although he avoided a significant decrease in points, there wasn't much point to watch
Awesome
Next is Shoji's challenge
Lowering the body's weight appears to be a smoother start
Contact!
Picked himself up with his face!
His head hit it!
Contact!
Fall!
Look at his face, he's not faking anything
Because he is trying to win the championship
Contact!
Fall!
That hurts
Grounded and multiple bursts of contact
Contact!
Fall!
Two instances of contact!
Contact!
Fall!
Sitting!
So dangerous, so dangerous
So, the results...
So fast!
Contact!
The End
Seven falls lead to a large reduction in points
Better than Noda
Yamada is only -40 points
Next, Orakio used his natural sense of balance
Like Yamada, there were few deductions and points to see
So, Orakio overtakes Yamada for the first place by using the first round score difference
The high score is not very impressive
The guy who wants to win is the most boring
Finally, Darling Honey Yoshikawa's challenge
If he can keep losses within 120 points, he can win the championship
What will happen?
No problem, right?
He's the lightest and looks the most unstable
Contact!
Not resistant to gravity?
That's how it goes
Contact!
Buses are not Yoshikawa's area of expertise
So with his advantage nullified, he incurs consecutive penalties
Sitting!
He's down
-Sitting down is no good
Ok!
Contact!
Fall!
Down, down, down
Only 40 points left
Contact!
You can do it!
Fall!
It's not the same person as the one on the train just now
The winner was Orakio
In summary
What a way to end it
That's him!
-It's Orakio
The winner of the championship was the least interesting, what is this farce
But the one who had it hardest on the bus was Murakami, right?
I did it six times.
-Every time
You'd want to throw up, wouldn't you?
-It's really not good
So, Matsumoto, could you do it?
No problem
Next time please have a go then
How can there be a second time for this shitty project?
No?
-No second or third time?
Even the winner got cut out!
Here's the thing
As the creator of the game, you're definitely a major weakness
Orakio realized that if you hold on with your hands, you won't fall
The points were saved, but the footage was lost
Too cunning.
-He exploited a loophole
Let's welcome the next presenter
Hello everyone
It's Yoshimura!
What's wrong? What's wrong?
It's okay, right? You still have enough time?
Without further ado
So, did everyone have to show their routines to scriptwriters and show staff when they were new to the business?
Sure
You would have gotten a lot of advice at such times
The theory I bring today is this:
If an old man, who later appears as a director on a set, critiques your routine, will you hastily make modifications according to their comments?
It's this
Super interesting
I see
This is it
This situation is rare
It happens in dramas, right?
Yes, yes
Yamazaki, what would you do if a strange old man suddenly told you how to improve something?
I wouldn't change it
What if in a few days that person appears as a person of status on the scene of the TV station
Do you mean the current me?
Yes, yes, yes
Or I just joined the industry and am longing for my shot at stardom?
The time of longing
I still wouldn't change it
I wouldn't give in
What about now?
Now i'd change it immediately
What would Downtown do in such a situation?
An elderly gentleman
Just a random elderly gentleman
It'd depend on the situation
If it was a charming old gentleman it'd be fine
It's different if it was just some tootheless old man
That's not a gentlemen
That's just "old"
Is a gentleman's status determined by the number of teeth he has?
If an old man, who later appears as a director on a set, critiques your routine, will you hastily make modifications according to their comments?
So the first group called to a coffee shop for the fake program meeting is
Nishkikoi
Seems like they type who'd go with it
TBS is expending effort regarding variety shows
-Good
The fake program prepared this time is
A comedy contest
If they win, they'll get a regular spot on a show
Set to be a big project that TBS executives attach great importance to
Eyes wide open!
Such a stern expression
Speaking honestly
This is a good chance for exposure
If there is a place for us...
It's that...
The trend of the times, right?
That we can also have such an opportunity
For groups wanting to improve
This is an important program that has the potential for growth
They'll probably change their approach
If possible
Can you perform something now?
Let me film it
-Here?
The store said it's ok
So
Hello everyone
So noisy!
They perform a routine at the cafe while being mindful of the surroundings
And they have yet to notice the object of later concern
The old gentleman who will comment on their routine
Ah-
Lots of effort
Really
It's a big opportunity after all
And so, the routine is over
Finally its time for the enigmatic old gentleman to come forward and make some suggestions
Excuse me, I have to take a call
The old guy's gonna appear now?
Once the staff member leaves
The elderly man advances
Excuse me
Eh?
I just took the liberty of listening to your routine just then
Good acting
Sorry
Seems like a nice guy at least
Sorry to bother you
Very interesting!
But I think a little change would make it more interesting
Sometimes you meet people like this
Impressive
When you say "Hello everyone" at the beginning
Stick out your tongue
Suggestion 1 Stick your tongue out when saying hello
How about making a funny face?
Hello everyone
Like this
What is this?
Ah...
Facing the random old man sticking out his tongue
The two awkwardly smile
They're nice guys after all
And
When do you that bit
Learn it well!
You don't seem to be doing anything
You could also just spit your tongue out
Crazy guidance
He loves the tongue thing
Follow the rhythm
Suggestion 2  Both stick your tongues out
Talking so much!
The "wow" at the beginning
Unique taste
Nice people, smiling and listening
A suggestion that Watanabe also sticks out his tongue
Then
It's a koi, right?
Suggestion 3  End with a leaping koi
After that, further suggestions for improvement are made
Listening closely
It'd be fun to do it like that
You'll become as famous as The Drifters
Finally, he leaves with the statement that they'll reach comedy heights if they follow his advice
The old gentleman's instruction is over
Really like a weird old granddad
They listened very carefully!
Thank you
What's wrong? What's wrong?
What kind of mood is this?
Scary
It would be off putting, right?
Said it was scary
He instantly...thought of so many pointers
Could he actually be a powerful person?
The kind of person you pay for help?
So vulgar!
I see
And very neatly dressed too
A gentlemen
An man that's easy to imagine soliciting a fee for his help
A week later, the two will the old gentleman again unexpectedly
It is completely the plot of a TV series
Will they recognize him?
Will Nishikoi actually add a sticking out tongue to their routine?
The second group target is Joyman
Very serious
Of course they are going to perform the usual rhyming rap routine
They put in a lot of effort
So, we fast forward to the advice
Excuse me
I just listened to your routine without permission.
-I'm sorry for disturbing you
I think you should change it
I think it would be more interesting
Tough to say
Really?
At the beginning "What's wrong with this guy?
Can't say "you're annoying"
That's what you said, right?
The response should be a bit more exaggerated
A bigger reaction
Be more suprised when saying "What's wrong with this guy"?
"What's wrong with this guy?"
Skilled at acting
It's scary
Suggestion 1  What's wrong with this guy~ (Over the top)
This... everyone will be shocked
An exaggerated "what's going on with this guy?"
Right at the start
"Sorry for the sudden appearance. I'm really sorry."
What's wrong with this guy?~
They'll be surprised
Do it to this extent
It's tough
Of course the action should be exaggerated
And for the rap part...
"Lemon Tea Milktea The Tokyo Big City"
This place is slightly...
I'm embarassed
Eh?
Taking out some notes he made while watching
Rewrite the lyrics
For example
-Are you a rapper?
Suggestion 2  Change rap lyrics
Coin toss
The obverse is lemon tea, the reverse is the corrupt Tokyo city
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Endless Donation Party
※Donation party: A party held for a fee to raise political funds
Why be so controversial
Endless parties, save minorities
Save minorities, fallen diversity
Not bad
A powerful message
Very sharp!
The meaning is a bit strong
Is there such a meaningful routine?
Older but aggressive in dissing those in power
Joyman doesn't know what to do
Super interesting
Take this if you want
I can't believe he gave it to them
His notes are passed over
End of suggestions
Will it be changed?
This note is a bit scary
And finally
Men should just shut up
That one...
Nowadays
Equality between men and women is also very important
Saying to them that this paragraph emphasizing machismo is no longer in line with the times
This is the reason
Change the part of "men" to "office workers"
Suggestion 1  Change "men" to "office workers"
He suggests changing the routine to a work theme instead
A big change
And
After changing to the office worker version
You should wear a suit
Suggestion 2   Change to a suit
After indicating to them suits are good
The suggestions end
Then let's change it like this
When the identity of the old man is revealed
Will these three groups scramble to take his advice?
So, a week later
Nishkikoi came to TBS
Go to the TBS managers' lounge
They greet the executives
So
We are Nishkikoi
Very much looking forward to today's show
We'll do our best
Please feel free to play
Thank you
This kind of atmosphere is common
We're full on energy today
Definitely nervous
After the usual greetings
Please say hello
Director Morita
I like both of them very much and highly recommend them
They've noticed
Thank you
The two are surprised to see a familiar face
A look of "it's that guy"
He's worked on many TBS shows
Let's not talk about that
I've seen them all
A clear vibe of "it's him"
"It's him"
Go for it!
Please take care
We managers are looking forward to
Not saying anything
They'll surely change
Please take care of us
In the face of this miraculous reunion, what does Nishkikoi think?
Surely they'll listen to him
Did you notice?
Hmm?
Did you see it just now?
The last one... the old grandpa
Don't call him an old grandpa!
Did you see
-Yeah
Did you recognize him?
It's that guy, right?
What should we do?
That old grandpa had a lot of comments
Don't call him an old grandpa!
I think it's better to...
More or less remember a little, right?
It would be better to add his suggestion
Would it be better to add it?
-Hmm
It would be better to add it
Of course it is better to add
In line with the theory
Hasegawa hastily proposes to adjust the routine as suggested
But
What did the old grandpa say?
Something about coming out
Don't remember
What was it in the beginning?
Don't say "old grandpa"!
They keep saying "old grandpa"
Sticking out the tongue?
Badmouthing him
Dancing or something?
Tongue?
I think the old grandpa emphasized sticking out the tongue
Right?
That's what he said back then, right?
It seems that neither of them can recall the exact circumstances...
Later, a formal video recording of their routine is made in front of the director
What will happen?
Will Nishkikoi favor the audience or the powers that be?
How are you?
What would Downtown do?
If someone suggested you to do something
I don't think we would change it
I'd want to but he wouldn't allow it
Really?
Hamada...
He can't be forced to do anything
Will Nishkikoi add the suggestions to their routine?
How are you?
Hello everyone
No manners
Changed it!
Full tongue out
Hasegawa sticks his tongue out in an exaggerated fashion
At the same time
Thank you all
I ah...
He's looking
He glances in the direction of the director from time to time
Looking at the powers that be
Confirmation of satisfaction
He's laughing
He's happy with it
If dancing to the end means winning the lottery
Later, Watanabe on the side
Please, Aki
I am cheering for you
The recommendations were fully adopted
Almost
-Damn
And finally
Thank you
Very thorough changes
They took all the suggestions
So, we reveal the truth
Eh?
I see...
You'd have to change it
Although I do not know how many sets of data you have now
I'm not sure if it'll be completely verified
Did anyone not change?
Maybe?
-Was there?
Looks like a person caught speeding
Saying "everyone does it, right?
Next is Joyman
Come and say hello!
This is the Director, Morita
We are Joyman
I really like you guys and highly recommend you
Unlike Nishkikoi just now
It's unclear whether they recognize the old man
The greetings are over
Did they notice?
Go for it!
A fleeting hint
The president with the crutches?
You saw him right? Have you seen him before?
No, right?
Don't you remember?
Maybe i'm misremembering
Just as we were saying hello
He came out
The president gave me a look
Did this
Just a little bit
Is it a hint that "it was me at that time"?
Little small movement
You'd notice this kind of detail
I may be wrong about this... but
Very observant
His hand always swung the same way
It was our movements
So that's it, right?
No idea
Pretty impressive
Still has the notes!
The lyrics notes given by the old gentleman at that time
This really is not appropriate to throw away
Takagi has it in his wallet still
The one with deep connotations
Will they change their routine as suggested?
Here we go come on
First is the initial reaction of Ikegaya
The advice given was an exaggerated version of "What's wrong with this guy~"
Sorry for the sudden appearance. I'm really sorry
What's wrong with this guy~?
No change
How about a rap?
Lemon tea milk tea...
The next part of Takagi's rap
Let's flip a coin to decide
Ah toss a coin to determine with heads and tails?
The obverse is lemon tea, the reverse is maternity
Pregnancy?
No change here either
Sticking to their own ideas
Every Tuesday and Wednesday Produce
So sad
Anteater, eating raw fish
Failure
Bye bye, volcanic ash
Get lost!
Thank you everyone
Awesome
Totally ignored
Ah thank you very much!
The show ended under an unusual low atmosphere
You'd really pity the old man
Director
In the lounge waiting...
Still in the lounge?
Ah, you scared me
Scared the hell out of me!
Scary!
What?
Why's he in there!?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
-It's okay
Thank you for visiting
Has to ask why?
I think you can probably guess what i'm thinking
So scary
I don't think its working
We brought the notes with us
Really?
Should we have done what it says here?
Well... yeah
Well...
I'm just one person
You can decide
So scary
Super scary!
Please keep up the good work next time!
Terrible, terrible
Sorry, sorry, sorry
This time is a bit of a pity
We at TBS
May not be able to provide you with support in the future
Eh?
Blacklisted!
Well, keep up the good work!
So scary
Please continue to work hard in the future
Ok ok
He said something very serious to us
Can only say "I'm really sorry"
The director who applied the pressure and the one who complained about the power in the rap seem like different pople
Power harassment!
Very angry
Angry or not doesn't matter now
Angry...
He even went to the room
The truth is revealed
Some light music too
What is this?
Wednesday Downtown
The hell?
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow
Today we were blacklisted by TBS
Blacklisted today
And finally, CoolPoko
The magnitude of this change is quite large
Will they wear a suit?
Completely adopted the recommendations
It's all changed!
Not good
Hello everyone, we are CoolPoko, back from running in the field
Really awful
It turned out to be an inexplicable segment of office workers pounding rice cakes
Too much
Minister, let's go
Please
In Summary
Some comedians will adopt the suggestions~
That's impressive
This is the result
I didn't expect Joyman to be the most strong-willed
Yes, no concessions
No concessions at all
The advice for Nishkikoi was at least still comedy-relevant
Stick out your tongue or something
But the Joyman one was too much, right?
Maybe if the proposal was less serious they'd go with it
Yeah
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03