Subbed by: Mei.ka~
Everyone's Theories as Chosen by Koyabu.
The next one is...
The theory is: after being scolded, it would probably be hard for Yaguchi Mari to let out her "Sexy Beam" when "Koi no Dance Site" is playing during karaoke.
Please no!
When you think of Yaguchi during her
time as a Morning Musume member...
You think of her "sexy beam".
And today, the person who will be scolding Yaguchi is...
Good morning!
Oh, that's scary.
Tono Nagiko, who hangs out with Yaguchi in their private time.
She looks scary here.
But seems like
they're friends.
Neither Yuguchi nor best friend Yushin knows anything.
Right.
Without further ado, let's get onto the karaoke.
TN: They're singing UFO by Pink Lady.
UFO
Looks like a good time.
The time has finally come to scold her.
Like, you should be talking about current events.
Honestly, I think it'd be better if you noticed
how much you haven't been studying.
Tono-san, you're not telling me about this, right?
Why, do you really have to talk to me about this?
No, I don't know.
So on the job -
Wait, did I do something to bother you?
This is what the staff saying, not me.
But that...
For some reason,
With Yaguchi objectifying,
this has started to turn into a heated argument.
Wait, this is really scary.
She's going all out.
So, with whatever you're telling me,
What am I supposed to do with future jobs?
No, I don't know...
Then I'm turning down the job this time.
Alright.
Okay?
With this, they can't even turn their attention towards the TV.
Their serious dispute just continues.
Until finally...
It doesn't mean that I'll do things that I wanna do.
Yaguchi ends up crying.
With that...
Well, never mind then.
Put on "Koi no Dance Site".
No way!
So, with Yaguchi in this state...
Tono-san's amazing.
Why would
she do it?!
Will she still bring out her Sexy Beam?
Tono-san's amazing.
It's the only thing
she can do!
Every time I fall in love, my chest goes Bon Bo Ba Bon
She won't do it.
No, I believe in her.
What?
Will she?!
She has to.
That's right, I'm updating
What will happen?!
I feel so bad.
No, she's crying!
She's just been crying!
Life's website with my SEXY beam (SEXY beam)
Go! Let it out!
Do it!
There was no way that she'd say it.
There was no way!
She didn't do it!
Well, obviously!
There was no way!
Now it was time to reveal the joke.
Man, I hated this!
I seriously hated this!
They're Friends...
Very good friends.
I'm so, so sorry!
Thank god...
Hold on!
This only made them
better friends!
I can't believe this!
I'm sorry, Tono-san!
None of it was true!
Now they're even closer!
I'm sorry! I really am!
I hated this!
God! Thank god!
Take out that "1 2 3 4"!