Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Who?
-Who's here?
I'm looking forward to it!
-Who is it?
It's Welcome to Koga!
We are Welcome to Koga, hello everyone!
It's Koga Ken!
Ah, thank you.
-WHAT ABOUT ME!?
Oda's here too, it's not just him
We are a group called Welcome to Koga
I was going to talk about you soon
Usually there is no separate introduction, right?
It's not bad, is it?
Why don't you just say Welcome to Koga?
This is the first time we were asked to come, and I'm really glad
Speaking of the theory we bring today
When you think of me, usually musical segments come to mind
Famous music theories of this program include
The chorus of the song happens to be a tearful difficult one
Yes, yes, yes, it's been done
Does that ring a bell?
-It does
This time we have a new version of that theory
The latest theory is "Song X Tears"
Please take a look
It is impossible to cry while dancing the Matsuken Samba
I see.
-This is a good theory
What do you all think?
Ah, what else can be said?
No, no, no, that's too much
The results are unclear, we need to see it first
Please chill out, Matsumoto
This is not only an upbeat song, but it's also the type that makes one feel ashamed
It's not shameful
-Stop it! Stop it! You can't say that!
There is no shame in it at all
And so, the challenge of crying Matsuken Samba unfolds
And
The "Make Your Partner Do a Double-take" Championship
It is impossible to cry while dancing the Matsuken Samba
This time, all the challengers will be challenged to
The Matsuken Samba II, which is synonymous with upbeat songs
They will have to dance and sing at the same time
For 57 seconds from the beginning of the second verse to the end of the chorus
Will they be able to cry?
And so
Thank you for having me
Ogata
The first challenger is
Panther's Ogata
May I ask what method you are going to use to cry?
Before I used cheating... the thought of my wife cheating on me
It was messed up
Something similar was done before, right?
On Wednesday Downtown?
-Yes
So I'm going to imagine my wife cheating on me
That's all I can do, if I want to cry
Really?
By imagining the infidelity of his beloved wife
Can he smoothly shed tears?
Not bad, not bad
Letting go is good
It's really good. It's good
Bang the bongos, play the samba, and dance the Southern Carnival
Pretty good
Not bad, very into it
Good appearence
No matter who you are, let's party together and start sweating glitter
Nice, nice performance
This is where it really starts
In the hot wind, I'll put my body on the line and keep dancing until I'm satisfied
It's brewing. It's brewing
The waves also sing the samba of love, and the heart is filled with this rhythm
What's going on now?
Yeah, it's hard to say
O-le Ole Matsuken Samba O-le Ole Matsuken Samba
Still dancing well
So funny
Really serious dancing
Not bad
Ah, fall in love, my friend, let's dance together, Miss
Only 20 seconds left!
Even forget to sleep and dance until dawn
No time!
Put more into it!
The dance is good
Samba Viva Samba MA-TSU-KE-N Samba O-le!
The dance is really good
Really pretty good
Still hasn't cried?
Ah no time left!
It's impossible!
It's not going to work, is it?
-It really doesn't work
No, no, no, it's not working
It's not possible
Impossible!
Of course
Can't do it! Dammit!
Defeated by Matsuken!
That's for sure!
The power of Matsuken Samba is similar to that of an excavator
Absorbing all the sadness in the world
The Devil's Song "Matsuken Samba"
What the hell is the devil's song?
The next challenger is
Who?
Thanks for having me
Doesn't seem like the crying type
Suzuki Mogura
May I ask when was the last time you cried?
Watching the movie "Major League" was particularly moving
※1989 comedy film based on MLB
Can't see it at all
Seriously?
Major League?
Yes, Major League, that's correct
That film came out quite a long time ago
Yeah
Indeed ... but I watched it in a small booth
In a small booth films feel more close
Doesn't crying affect the mood?
I was able to adjust immediately!
What are you talking about?
The mole (Mogura) who switches moods instantly
Can he switch quickly between laughing and crying?
Looks like a rich person
Will he cry?
Bang the bongos, play the samba, and dance the Southern Carnival
Impressive
No matter who you are, let's party together and start sweating glitter
Something fell
What?
It's not easy to cry now
Seriously
Too much concern
In the hot wind, I'll put my body on the line and keep dancing until I'm satisfied
The waves also sing the samba of love, and the heart is filled with this rhythm
What is this situation?
The belly is too big, the belt is gone
O-le Ole Matsuken Samba O-le Ole Matsuken Samba
Well...it's hopeless, right?
Ah, fall in love, my friend, let's dance together, Miss
Even forget to sleep and dance until dawn
Samba Viva Samba MA-TSU-KE-N Samba O-le!
Ah but the eye sockets are wet
Can he cry?
Impossible, no time left
5 seconds left
Such a shame
This has been dropping since the beginning
Yeah
You'd be concerned
If I step on the microphone I may have to pay 200,000
Such distractions kept recurring in my mind
So I couldn't do it!
The next challenger is
There is no chance for this one, right?
Thank you for having me
Plus Minus' Iwahashi
May I ask what method you are going to use?
At first, I was thinking to remember my four grandparents who have passed away
But the flavor of Matsuken Samba is too overpowering, I think
Yeah
So that made me think "maybe cry tears of joy"
So i'm going to try shedding tears of joy through the power of Matsuken Samba
Good idea
Maybe i'll cry that way
I see
Either way, just cry
That's my strategy
Well ... as long as you can cry then its fine
This might be a good idea
But he may not be truly ready to cry
After all, he has to be really joyful
Bang the bongos, play the samba, and dance the Southern Carnival
This idea could work
You just have to mobilize the emotions
Like you're going to receive some kind of award
No matter who you are, let's party together and start sweating glitter
Yes that's true
If so, he may be successful
In the hot wind, I'll put my body on the line and keep dancing until I'm satisfied
Eyes as wide as a cow's balls
This is truly a different approach
A despicable approach
The waves also sing the samba of love, and the heart is filled with this rhythm
His eyes must be very dry
Such dry eyes
-Definitely a good way to get dry eyes
Aren't tears of joy required?
O-le Ole Matsuken Samba O-le Ole Matsuken Samba
This wont lead to crying, right?
Maybe you can't just rely on emotions
Indeed
Ah, fall in love, my friend, let's dance together, Miss
A purely physical approach
Even forget to sleep and dance until dawn
Is his dry eyes ready to cry?
Samba Viva Samba MA-TSU-KE-N Samba O-le!
So scary!
There's no time left. It's hopeless
Will anyone succeed?
There is not much hope
Not much hope indeed
A vile "dry eye" battle
Although physical means were used to try to shed tears
It still failed
This is not good!
You were happy right, doing the dance?
After all, we were dancing to such an upbeat song
But I still have to try and cry
You can all try, try at home, and then you will certainly feel what I feel
It's a great song!
What are you doing?
The next challenger is
Thank you for having me
Matsumoto Akiko
Hard to tell
Strange choice
May I ask what method you are going to use?
Although they are no longer alive
My parents always looked forward to seeing me on stage or on TV
They were very happy for me every time
While recalling my parents
I'll concentrate on the idea of making them hear, making them see
Should you think of them when dancing a dance like this?
And that will make me cry
Ah, they were singers
So it's like this!
Cute!
Really cute, ah so cute
Looks like a little kid
Bang the bongos, play the samba, and dance the Southern Carnival
It isn't clear yet
She's so suitable for this
No matter who you are, let's party together and start sweating glitter
Is it okay to dance this?
Cute
Seriously cute
Super cute!
Big round eyes
In the hot wind, I'll put my body on the line and keep dancing until I'm satisfied
Is the feeling there?
Can she cry?
She's a professional, after all
The waves also sing the samba of love, and the heart is filled with this rhythm
I hope Akiko can succeed at least
O-le Ole Matsuken Samba O-le Ole Matsuken Samba
Dancing very seriously
Very swift movement
Impressive
Really impressive
Ah, fall in love, my friend, let's dance together, Miss
Even forget to sleep and dance until dawn
There is a chance, there is a chance, there is still time
Samba Viva Samba MA-TSU-KE-N Samba O-le!
Eye sockets are a little wet
10 seconds
No time!
Ah, no time!
Is it impossible?
She tried her best, at least
Nice expression
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
No need to apologize!
By the way, Harada Ryuji came to challenge
Eh?
Really?
My uncle's son?
He came to my house the day before the meeting
It was Harada's mother, my husband and me
※Ryuji Harada was invovlved in an infidelity scandal
We conducted a "who gets the car" meeting
For the testimony of her sister-in-law, Harada said this
That 4WD car
There's no need to talk about such things
It wasn't so much a meeting as it was a session
Session?
-Session
What?
It's not a meeting when people are just getting together
I see
What was the topic of conversation?
I've ah...forgotten
You start like this!?
Did we need that part just now?
Not bad not bad
After all, he's an actor, so maybe he can cry
Yes, after all, he is an actor
Depends on his abilities
Seems to be the most likely to achieve success so far, right?
Bang the bongos, play the samba, and dance the Southern Carnival
Not the sound I imagined
No matter who you are, let's party together and start sweating glitter.
Dance is a bit general
Although the melody is still very steady
But the dance is...
In the hot wind, I'll put my body on the line and keep dancing until I'm satisfied.
Here we go. Here we go
It feels like it will work
I want to see it succeed
Suddenly into it
The waves also sing the samba of love, and the heart is filled with this rhythm
The possibility of success is still there
Not bad for an actor
Yeah, it's good
O-le Ole Matsuken Samba O-le Ole Matsuken Samba
It's not going to work, is it? Can you cry?
Almost 20 seconds left
Ah, fall in love, my friend, let's dance together, Miss
You can do it!
Even forget to sleep and dance until dawn
Running out of time!
Samba Viva Samba MA-TSU-KE-N Samba O-le!
Ryuji!
Work harder!
10 seconds left!
Ah, there's no time.
What the hell is up with you?
No, no, no, you're too strict
Too strict
And so, the last challenger is...
Thank you for having me
He can do it
TKO Kinoshita
He can always cry
It'd be strange if he couldn't
-True
TKO Kinoshita
I still have strong emotions
I think I can shed a tear
It can be done
May I ask when was the last time you cried?
Recently i've been crying a lot
That's true
The last year i've been crying more than ever
Benevolence appears
So may I ask what method are you going to use to cry?
He can do it!
I have a 20 year old daughter
She's 20?
We haven't seen much of each other lately
Since when?
Probably before everything happened
After I resigned from my agency, I created a Youtube Channel
Although I deserved it
My apology video got 450,000 dislikes
Japan's most disliked video
I didn't want my daughter to see that video
Then I called my daughter and said, "Daddy will work hard"
"It may be harder now, but you have to work hard." After saying that
My daughter said, "I also disliked the video"
Disliked it?
Not bad, he can do it
Adding all these memories
Indeed.
-Yes, yes
Use your memories!
Hopefully he can vent it all here
Bang the bongos, play the samba, and dance the Southern Carnival
Very loud
Quite suitable.
-Nice
No matter who you are, let's party together and start sweating glitter
From here
Here is the important part
In the hot wind, I'll put my body on the line and keep dancing until I'm satisfied
Come on, come on, get in the mood
Think quickly
The waves are also sing the samba of love, and the heart is filled with this rhythm
Think fast!
O-le Ole Matsuken Samba O-le Ole Matsuken Samba
He's got it
Emotions are evident
Do it!
Feels like it will work
Ah, let's fall in love, my friend. Let's dance together, Miss
How's it going? Any luck?
Even forget to sleep and dance until dawn
You've gotta cry!
Feels like it will work
Samba Viva Samba MA-TSU-KE-N Samba O-le!
No time left
No time!
Did he cry?
Cried?
What?
Just cry already!
Did not cry at all
I had to dance and sing and think of my daughter
Too busy!
Ah but after a long absence in the studio
My emotions are all messed up
Matsuken Samba is still seeking challengers!
Too tough!
Yes, no one was able to do it
It's true.
-What do you think?
If Matsuken dies then maybe someone will cry
No no no, it doesn't have to go that far
This is not the kind of project you do when someone's died.
It'd be impossible for them to pass on
Do you have any candidates in mind?
I think child actors should be able to do it
Little actors
-I guess so
They can get into it easier
What about overseas actors like Steven Seagal?
I can't imagine him crying at all
Why would he accept a job like this?
No matter what, his expression remains the same
No expressions at all
It seems that Seagal's wife hates him
No, no, no one knows that
That's bad
She's sick of waiting for Seagal to start conversations
Let's welcome the next presenter
Rare
Laughing Rice
It feels like it's been a long time since I've seen these two
This show
Twice or so.
-Twice?
The show has been running for a long time and you've only appeared twice?
Yes
It's your first time standing here, right?
First time, yes
First as presenters
What was the previous project?
A long time ago
The judge is very good at stopping himself from laughing
A theory that a judge will never laugh
We performed a sketch in front of a judge
The worst reaction ever
Really?
It was indeed very cold
Let's put that aside for now
Although a bit abrupt
In the past, there was a "something you can't help but look at twice"
Do you remember, Downtown?
Something was written on the green room
Written by Osamu Tezuka
Yes yes yes
It was too niche
This time brought the hypothesis about double-takes
The "Make Your Partner Do a Double-take" Championship
Maybe easier than before
Yes, because there is an understanding
What do you think, Cookie
When looking at Meruru's mouth, I saw a lot of silver teeth and couldn't help but look twice.
-That's awful
I don't have any
It's a shock, isn't it?
Please stop lying
They're showing, it's best not to open your mouth
So awful
If the tattoo on Hamada's back disappeared, I wouldn't be able to not do a double take
Hey, you
Oi!
The "Make Your Partner Do a Double-take" Championship
I'll make him unable to not do a double-take
I'll give him something he can't help but do a double-take at
I'm confident
He's pretty aware of his surroundings
Tsuda?
-Yes
A favorable situation or an annoying one
I'll use both of these types
In this way, I should be able to achieve my goal
Can't stare at it
Staring doesn't count
Can't help but look twice without saying anything
I'll make him look three or four times
I'll make him look six trillion times
Six trillion times!
These five will concoct scenarios impossible not to look at twice
And will target their partners
And so
The first challenger is
Diane's Yusuke
Each challenger prepares two seperate scenarios
What is the first?
Complimentary meal service
The only complimentary meal in the lounge is white rice
White rice
We often talk about bento
"How's the bento? How's the free food" etc
It makes people angry
We often talk about it on the radio
He'll definitely pay attention to it
I think it will work
And so
Yusuke personally places the white rice in the best position
I think it will work. In this position
Can Tsuda not help but look at it twice?
You don't have to open it to know
He's coming
Here we go, here we go, here we go
He's put his bag down
Where's he going?
Probably to the bathroom
Then, after coming back from the toilet
In position
Going well
He doesn't notice the white rice as he instead goes over a fake script for 3 minutes
What's he doing?
Wiping his eyes...
What is this rubbing method
Ah, he looked twice!
Indeed
Tsuda looks twice with a frown
What's up with that look
Slightly pissed off...
He's probably angry because he feels like he's being looked down on
And after that
Very restless
This guy's eyes are so fierce
What's wrong?
-What's wrong?
It's gotten weird
What's going on? His movements are so disgusting
Say something!
He's looked so many times!
Seriously so many times
Picked it up
What's going on here?
Before even picking up the white rice, he looked at it a total of 13 times
Thus, the first round is a success
Success
Next is Yashiki's challenge
Wada Akiko looks after us
I'm using her name
There will be graffiti on a tag with her name on it
Yashiki prepares the prop himself
A little sloppy will be better
So cheesy
Then
This is his room
He's always in this room
So it should be more familiar than most rooms
Being wary of noise
It's common to look at who's next door
So you'd be surprised to see something like this
I see
Envoking the actions of Shimada, will this plan succeed?
Don't talk about "power harassment"
He's here, he's here
Will he look twice?
Once
He just glanced as he slipped straight into the room
But
What?
What's happening?
Does this count?
Can't help but look again?
The time in-between is too long right, it doesn't count
Not this kind of twice
He looked twice
But not in the sense of a "double-take"
So this attempt is a failure
Probably too scared to hang around there
Otherwise he may be considered to be involved
If she suddenly appeared
Next is Laughing Rice's Nishida
Tetsuo likes Buddhism
He has a lot of prayer beads
Because he carries his own beads
He'd probably be conscious of other people having it too
Like "that's a huge one"
You couldn't not notice this one
Good idea
I'm choosing this one
Can't miss it
Isn't this Samoan stuff?
And so, Tetsuo is invited out to a meeting about a fake fireworks show
Notice the beads, Tetsuo
※Singer
Dressed up like Naoto Inti Raymi
Slowly the giant prayer beads appear
Huge!
This is obvious, right?
What will happen?
How do you enjoy fireworks?
I don't use my phone to film it
And I won't let the people with me do it either
From the beginning to the end of the fireworks
Watching it through the screen
I've seen people like this
I think its really a waste
And so, the beads are shown to Tetsuo
Giant prayer beads that could be considered a small firework
Will he look twice?
Do you have a recommendation for a fireworks convention?
How can I put it? The famous place...
There's major fireworks conference
Did he look?
He saw
He saw it
Is this considered a look?
Looked then looked again
Looked twice.
-Beautiful
Although it is impossible to tell from the live monitor
He did indeed look twice
And
The three major fireworks are Toura and that one, right?
Where else?
Possibly due to being shaken up inside, he's suddenly speechless
That shocking?
I feel like I'm watching something I shouldn't...
He's even playing with his hair
After the prayer beads came out
The vibe got kind of weird
Possibly due to terror
Tetsuo doesn't dare to look at the beads again
It's power is too strong
It's too big.
-It's scary
Next up is Cookie
He has a habit of staring at people
So we should have someone stare daggers at him
He's very good at glaring at people
Considering his overactive eyes
Overall the best choice is
Shizuru's Ikeda
Really?
Ikeda will be brought into the large lounge where Rossy is having a meeting
Later
Begin
Staring daggers at Rossy, LETS GO
He looked
The camera angle is too good
Can't not notice!
Go on, go on like that
Didn't realise
Keeps looking over here, wait a second
Eh?
He only looked once
Keeps looking over here, wait a second
He's laughing
So tough
Sorry, it was too tough
-No need to apologise
I'm really sorry
In short, this time it wasn't possible
Yeah, sorry
Let me punch you in the stomach
Next is Lalande Saaya's first attempt
This time is special
Nishida respects Yamazato of Nankai Sweetheart
So, as the person who acts as an assistant to the host
Nishida will be selected
The plan will be stated on the whiteboard
As the focus is Nishida himself I think she'll notice
He'll be excited
It's deliberately not written at the top
It looks like people have been crossed out and Nishida's left
In this case, it's more difficult to not look twice
Very practical
At a whiteboard that someone forgot to erase
Can he not help but look twice?
Please wait here
-Thanks
The writer-director should be coming soon
One moment, please. Sorry.
-I'll wait
Hasn't looked at the whiteboard
For the next 10 minutes he doesn't look at the whiteboard
He's not looking
Good things are written right there!
Indeed
And then
He looked
Beautiful
Nicely done!
A textbook double-take
Laughing too
Followed by constant staring
Looking for ages
Keeps snickering
Always looking
Very nice
Kinda scary
And
Taking photos
He'd definitely do this
Very happy. Click, click, clicking!
He looks so pleased with himself
So
The results of the first round are shown above
And so begins the second round
An even bolder section
First up is Lalande Saaya
The second scenario
This time is the opposite scenario
The worst-case scenario
In the corridor
Suddenly there will be loads of holes in the walls and a lot of charms on the side
And so the second attempt to elicit a double-take
That's creepy
What will happen?
Will it work this time too?
This is super scary
Suddenly seeing a large number of talisman paper
Here we go, here we go, here we go
You'd have to look at something like this
He looked once
Not twice
-This is the kind of situation where you stare
Because the scenario is too shocking
He can't help but hold his breath
Standing still and staring
I see
And so, the truth is revealed
How do you feel?
What?
-How about it?
The last time you just stared
Something on the wall?
This time it's "get your partner to do a double-take"
I see
The first time you did a double-take, the second you just looked once
Ahh!
Very disappointing
So, Lalande wins one and loses one
Next is
I have confidence this time
Yes, this time you have to go for it
Seeing someone kneeling with female high school students on the side of the road
This time will involve Makkun of Bakkunmakkun
Why Makkun?
Makkun is the most likely person to do this, right?
You are bad!
Kneel down?
For a high school girl
It feels like a real scenario
Will Rossy look twice at Makkun kneeling?
This is miserable for Makkun to do
What will happen?
Why did Tsuda wipe his eyes like that?
It was horrible
Super gross
It wasn't like wiping crust, more like chasing a runaway tick
And so, the Makkun kneeling double-take challenge begins
What will happen?
I'm really sorry. I have a family
The police are coming
Don't be so loud...
I'm sorry.
-I don't care
No no
What?
I'm sorrry
He looked
He looked twice
Indeed a double-take
You'd have to look
Looked once and then...
Looked twice
Although it took a little long
He couldn't help but look twice
I'm really sorry
No, no, no. Please wait
Ah, he looked, looked for the third time
The truth is revealed
Rossy
Thanks for your hard work
What the hell?
Thank you for your hard work
What what what?
Great! It worked!
What worked?
Ah, great!
What is, what is, what is, what is, what?
Did you see?
I saw, it seems that someone is being scolded
Who is being scolded
I don't know who it is...
Eh?
A fierce-looking guy is being scolded by a student
Didn't look closely
Seems like a very Tokyo thing to happen
It's Bakkunmakkun's Makkun
An impressive person
It wasn't what I thought it would be, but you couldn't help but look a few times
Anyway, thanks for passing!
So, Yasei Bakudan also get one success and one failure
Next is Laughing Rice's second attempt
To what extent will Testuo look?
Hello everyone, I'm Tetsuo of Laughing Rice
Sorry
Why do you have phlegm at the beginning?
Cough it up before appearing on camera!
The reopening of the Nara Grocery Store
Testuo participates in a fake on-location shoot
Tetsuo is a special tourist ambassador for Nara
So he's interested in Nara more than the average person
"Nara's getting a new train station"
We made posters about it
And posted it in the store
He has to walk this way
He'll be surprised if he sees it
Indeed
No one else would look
Decision to open Nara Station
Eh?
Is that it?
It's a good thing
Didn't look twice, just stared
Stared
Just stared...
Is it that surprising?
The truth is revealed
Did you look?
What?
Have you seen it? Have you seen it? Have you seen it?
What what what?
Didn't see anything very interesting?
Saw something awesome
But i'm scared. I'm consistently scared
I'm scared, the prayer beads were huge
Still thinking about it
It was scary
No, the prayer beads were so big, so i'm still scared
People with such large prayer beads are very scary
And it's not easy to talk about it
Because of the prayer beads
Cared so much
Testuo failed to take much notice of the poster
Constantly thinking about it
So far it's all one win and one loss
No two wins in a row.
-That's right
Next up
Simple and straightforward from the outside
The other party of a meeting is young master poverty
※A manga character who used to be a young master of a high class family and then fell into poverty
But if you see it all at once
You'lll just stare
So it needs to be reflected in a mirror
Just barely visible
Maybe it's better this way
"Huh? Is that real?"
Make him be unable to not do a double-take
This time I want him to look twice beautifully
With this as the goal
And so
Good morning, thank you very much today
Please sit down.
-Excuse me
I'm a choreographer.
-Please take care of me
It's important to be able to see it straight away
In short the first look is very important
Then
And so
It's easy to get sleepy
This and the teachers...
I don't know if I can ask
Won't look twice?
What is this?
Eh?
Can you calm down a bit?
This and the teachers...
Noted
Shimasa seems to laugh
But does not look twice
The truth is revealed
Sorry, thank you very much
Come on, what is this?
What do you think it is?
Gotta be Wed, right?
Abbreviated to "Wed"
This was to get people to do a double-take
I glanced
The moment I saw a naked body
I had a vague feeling it was this
Wednesday Downtown?
A tired feeling swept over me
How about over there?
The lounge before the meeting?
That one too?
After a while you went to see it again, right?
What the hell
I really wasn't sure about that one
The first time I was scared so I pretended not to look
We occasionally star in "Leave it to the Son!"
So it'd be impossible to even say "there's a sign like that in the lounge"
I just pretended not to see, I was too scared
New York didn't get even a single one
What will happen with Diane?
The hope of continuous success falls to Diane
Here we go
This is a very popular matcha smoothie
Looks good
This screams "goigoisu"
Enough of that
Right?
The overall feeling is a bit anxious
This happens a lot
The trap for Tsuda in the fake food outing is
Why is this product popular?
The trick is two-fold
In the cafe
There will be a weird sumo wrestler and his entourage
Although the followers are fat
The actual sumo himself is very thin
An extremely thin guy will walk in
I think he'll look
The first time has proven that he will not be able to resist looking twice
This time will be successful
First he'll look, and then...
I hope it'll be on this level
Will Tsuda be able to resist looking twice?
Actually
Please come in
Welcome
Ah, he looked
It's much better than the first
Welcome, please feel free to sit down.
Tsuda can't help looking twice in a row
And so the truth is revealed here
Ah! It hurts!
I caught my finger
What are you doing?
-What are you doing?
Thank you. Thank you.
-What?
So redundant!
I knew it was too weird
What is this?
Why did you pinch your finger? What?
But you achieved the achievement
Achieved?
Yes
This is the "make your partner do a double-take" championship
Did you notice that you couldn't help but look twice? Was it conscious?
No memory at all
Unconscious?
-Yes
Super thin...
I just couldn't work out this weird occurrence
Shouldn't it have been a bit more topical?
And so, the winners are Diane
I see
There we go
Tetsuo was carried away by the prayer beads
Afraid of the beads
What's wrong with that? When you see large prayer beads, you stop talking
It is really unsettling
As I was talking a lot about fireworks
I suddenly thought "oh, is there fireworks on it?"
What?
So it was scary
It could suddenly explode.
-Indeed
What would I do if it suddenly blew up?
How is that possible?
You think too much
Cookie's ones
Casting errors...
That Makkun was not recognized is the biggest mistake
Originally, I invited Ishizaka Koji
It's impossible for him to do that
Who would do it?
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03