Welcome to Wednesday Downtown
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
It's New York!
Are you gonna be like those lying on the street in New York today?
Are we like that?
They don't agree
-You usually seem a little slack
We are working hard today
-Full of energy today
I'm working so hard together I even got a Matsumoto-style haircut
The hair is also wrong!
It's more like Bito Takeshi
Who is Bito Takeshi!?
How can Bito Takeshi and Matsumoto have the same hairstyle?
This is the same Matsumoto
It's obviously the same as Bito
Well, then its the same, in short i'm full of energy
Without further delay, we bring you the latest version of the "Someone is Here" series
Hamada loves this one
He's super happy now
He wants to watch this while eating a burger
This is his side dish
-His absolute favorite
We've kept you waiting then
Absolute favorite
It's this:
There's Someone in the Third Row in the Back Seat is Occupied Prank
This is it
If it's really good, if Hamada laughs too much, his face might break open
His face will snap
We might see it happen
So, after this, the pranker in the back seat
Also has someone behind them
And, the machines that are so niche they have achieved zero sales
And, when pretending to catch a big fish, up to 5 people can be pulled into the water
There's Someone in the Third Row in the Back Seat is Occupied Prank
About four years ago, we did a "there's someone in the back seat" prank
So it was 4 years ago!
So scary, this one
A normal reaction
The target of the prank was someone sitting in the passenger seat with someone behind them
Indeed scary
A simple setup
The face of the pranker is too horrible
This time, there will be someone in the third row behind the person that thinks they are pranking the person in the first row
The reverse prank is like this
So, the first target is
Einsetin's Inada
Who is called for the "back seat is occupied" prank
Due to being a scary-looking comedian
He is asked to be the setter
So, he quickly gets into the back seat
The target in the passenger seat is...
Anthony, who knows all about it
My phone seems to have been left there
I'm sorry, I'll be right back. Can you give me a minute?
Okay, okay.
-Sorry, sorry
Being lured away, Inada's chance appears
Tough for Anthony too
A great expression
So creepy
-Scary
Get ready to be scared
An arguably unsettling expression
He's looking in the rearview mirror
Checking
After getting into position
Here we go
Ah I see
A great image
Here we go!
A good composition
The Trifecta Prank
Will he realize?
His focus is ahead
I really hope he notices
Of course, Anthony won't pay attention to Inada
And probably because his attention is on the front row
He doesn't pay attention to behind him at all
His body is so far forward
A stalemate occurs
An endless wait
So, after 5 minutes
The man in the third row also pokes his head forward
He's offside
But Inada still fails to notice
Both sides are waiting to move forward
The distance after 10 minutes begins to close
He's moved so far forward
So
It scared Anthony too
Almost touching
The truth is revealed
Wait a second, wait a sec, let me calm down
Ah, so scared...
Gross, I want to throw up
Disgusting, I want to throw up
I'm exhausted
I still don't understand what's happening
Wait, I need to calm down
Ah...ah... my brain has turned around
So we explained the whole thing to him
Ah~ like that...
Typical Wednesday Downtown
And so, the next target is
Anthony must be tired too
Kasuga
Audrey's Kasuga
Kasuga has a lot of patience
Indeed
He's good at waiting
However, like Inada, his focus is also ahead
And is completely unaware of the behind
An interesting image
So, for this man who is known for his endurance
30 minutes passes
Quite a while
It's not easy for anyone
This guy is good
Perseverance
And so, little by little, the third row moves forward
To this extent
They're almost side-by-side
Right next to him
Finally
Quite forward both of them
This reaction is too real
That's it!
A huge surprise!
The truth is revealed
Not as much of a response as I expected
That's because of my professionalism
He'll realize if I react too much
-I'll realize?
After the "Oh!", I was planning to continue with Anthony
I felt something behind me
But I didn't turn around because I didn't want everything to be revealed
As expected of WedDown!
After testing this a few times
We explore what happens when the person in the passenger seat is also unaware of what's going on
Double-prank style
This time the targets are these two
A great lineup
What will happen?
Here we go.
-Scary enough
Nice expression
Here we go. Here we go
It also depends on who notices first
Indeed
Here we go. They're all here
What the hell is this!?
3 offenders with different crimes
The crimes committed are not of the same kind at all
The total silence of a prison van
And so it continued for 15 minutes
Not realized yet?
So close!
For some reason, Sakai begins combing his hair
At this time
After all, there are two of them
For Sakai, there are two more people
Meaning unknown
What is it?
Sakai and ...
What's going on?
It is indeed necessary to ask what's going on
Wants to get out first
What is it?
Sakai, who was completely baffled by the situation, gets out of the car voluntarily
However, the man behind has not yet been noticed
So, of course, the prank is not yet over
Such a long "oooh"
A long sound
Eh?
Eh...?
What's going on?
No...
-Still in the car...
I also don't...
Something's going on...
Eh eh eh?
What's going on?
Eh? Why can't I open this door?
Eh, what... eh?
Not good not good
I'm completely confused.
-I don't know what's going on either
The truth is revealed
A very small mask
There's another guy back there? You saw it?
I saw both of you
Eh?
Behind... eh, didn't you see?
Sakai mistakes the project for something to do with psychics
Something's gone wrong!
So, the last group of targets is
Midori
These two
This time, Shizuru's Ikeda was the setter
Seems to be watching some kind of video
It's break time after all
There is also the possibility that the back row will realize first
Lilly is concentrating on watching a video of Kamaitcahi
And Moriyama is concentrating on Lily
A stalemate occurs again
So
Eh...
Although one of them knows, the other one doesn't
What? What?
It does get confusing!
What?
No, no. What's the deal?
This one seems to know something
Eh...
What? What?
No, no. What's the deal?
What is this project?
Indeed
There is definitely some kind of prank
So, Ikeda
Ikeda
He's like the Mona Lisa
A demure face
So funny
He is wondering why the truth hasn't been revealed yet
That's great
This is awesome!
Jumped
Bounced to the right
That was close. A dive to the right
Run, run, run!
Why?
This is really scary
Scary indeed
Eh...
What are you looking at?
What?
Lilly saw both
Eh...
Which side are you on?
What did you say?
What is the situation of these three people?
He's been...
The truth is revealed
"He's always been there"
Wait for me to calm down. What's going on?
Super scared
-Lips are quivering
Moriyama
Eh, this...who...that...
What's going on with his mouth
Eh... who is being pranked here?
First time
What's the matter with your mouth?
When words of joy, anger, sorrow, and sadness are coming to me like crazy
My mouth always twitches and doesn't stop, it's been like this since I was a child
Really, it's genetic
※After the broadcast, Moriyama's relatives contacted him and said that their family members were really like this, and he tweeted that he imagined the whole family at his funeral with quivering lips
This one is the scariest
Can't stop shaking
In summary
You'll be scared to shaking
This is great
What do you think?
What the hell is this result?
In short, it is shaking with fear
The result is that this guy is the last person to be set up, right?
This lip is the most frightening
That's awesome!
It's genetic
The guy in the third row was probably also scared, right?
"Is there someone hiding behind me too?"
He doesn't dare to trust
Maybe he checked at the start
Let's welcome the next presenter
It's Chocolate Planet!
The Chocolate Planet Constellation!
Yes, we are the Chocolate Planet Constellation
Ok
You should correct him
I'd like to ask, what is Chocolate Planet's strength?
Kawashima, what are our strengths?
Parody, right?
Thank you very much
Feels like a trap
In my opinion, its small props
Ah, that's true.
-The small props used in our routine are all made by me
I made this "no contact ring"
You put it on your finger to press the elevator button without having to touch it
It's suitable for now
-Yeah
This one passed the first stage of the Good Design Award
{Good Design Award", the highest award for Japanese design, was established in 1957 and is one of the four major design awards in the world
Did you create it?
-I did
So this time, we bring a theory about creations
It's this:
There are businesses that are so focused on niche areas that they don't even sell a single piece of machinery
This is it
Well, focusing on too niche areas, not a single piece of machinery sold
There must be
-There must be in this world, right?
I think so
-Not even one?
I actually made a very niche machine
This is it
Never seen it before
We have all had screen cover fall on the floor, right?
There are times when you can't pick it up, right?
Especially when there are no nails
-Especially
The machine that solves this problem
If it falls, you press this like this
The cover is picked up
With this
Don't be afraid
-No more fear. No more fear of having no nails
It helps elementary school students
A machine that can help elementary school students
No fear
-Yes, yes
What's wrong?
Matsumoto-san said "no fear", you shouldn't just reply with "Yes, yes".
The machine
-No fear
The second time it was dropped he picked it up easily
What's going on?
-This needs to be considered, right?
What's wrong? What's wrong?
-You didn't use "no fear" at all
If you drop it, you can't not pick it up with this "no fear"
He picked up again directly!
There are businesses that are so focused on niche areas that they don't even sell a single piece of machinery
First of all, FUJI SEIKI of Fukuoka Prefecture
The rice ball salt-spreading machine: Salt-spreading Machine No. 5
It's quite big
Salt injection port
It sprinkles salt on the surface of the rice balls on the conveyor belt
Flips it over and sprinkles it inside once too
Salt injection port
A machine for sprinkling salt
Awesome
As it is an excellent machine that can perform precise portion adjustment in 0.01 gram units
It is sold at
4 million yen
Eh?
4 million yen?
The price is high, but it has the performance to match
The development cost of this machine is about 100 million yen
100 million?
-Yes
Salt spreader developed with substantial funding
How many units have been sold?
A total of 1,336 units were sold
Awesome
It's already paid for
Really sold a lot
Yes, the rice balls sold in convenience stores and supermarkets
A best seller!
All need to be sprinkled with a small amount of salt
There are about 500 factories nationwide that make rice balls
Almost all factories have bought this salt spreader
I see
An overwhelming market share of about 90%
It is really a best seller
Awesome
That's awesome!
All the rice balls we eat will pass through this salt sprinkler
Factories that actually use this salt spreader
Every day we ship 20,000 rice balls to large supermarkets
So its impossible to salt each by hand
What are you talking about?
So it's deadly without a salt spreader?
-Without a salt spreader, it's a disaster
A realistic statement
So, this machine for salting costs 4 million yen
Has sold more than 1300 units
Very impressive
Next is the TADASHI manufacturing facility in Osaka Prefecture
Special machine for cutting off the scales of mackerel: The bamboo mackerel scales removal machine
What is this?
The mackerel has pronounced hard and spiny serrated scales near the caudal fin
Sliding the mackerel down on the prong scale remover
A blade is set up between conveyor belts
Look so healing
Automatic scale removal
In terms of its use
It removes the need to remove scales when making sashimi and dried fish
And what is this machine used for?
This machine is a special machine for processing fried mackerel fillets
The application is very narrow
Yes, the use of a fairly narrow range of machines, whats the sale price?
3 million yen
Three million?
-Yes
Another machine the same price as a car
How many units have been sold?
Sold 50 units since the start of the sale
Still selling quite well
Did you get your money back?
I haven't got my money back at all, and I still haven't
To fill the development cost of the scale remover
The new items now in production are
For making chicken wings wrapped in rice
It's a machine that makes chicken wings wrapped in rice
A little confused about what he was talking about
You can still understand a little bit, right?
Next is DREMAX in Saitama Prefecture
Strawberry root removal machine M-HT15
This is not good
Put the strawberries one by one on the rotating turntable
Its quick
The circular rotating blade then removes the root tip
This ah...
No, right?
This machine can cut the roots of 30 strawberries a minute
That's good
The effort needed is unordinary
Can't it all be done mechanically?
Because the strawberry is divided into the upper and lower part of the part it still require human input
The price of this semi-manual strawberry root cutter is
That's a lot of work
Not fully automatic isn't good
1.2 million yen
1.2 million?
-Yes
I thought it was a bargain considering the amount of work we had spent
Really?
-Really?
Isn't that a good price?
-No, not at all
Don't the buyer companies have anything to say about the selling price?
They say it's too expensive
Considering the operator's fee, it is a bit expensive
Why's he angry?
How many units have been sold?
Sold 18 units
It's selling well out of all my products
So I have a feeling that it will be a big hit from here on
This one will be popular
Really?
-Yes.
People who use it say, "I can't stop using it"
This is the initial development stage, right?
By the way, this company is engaged in fruit and vegetable cutting special machinery manufacturing
So that's it
The most recommended items now are
White potato slicing special machine
This is a special machine for white potato slicing
It is priced at 6 million yen
Still expensive
How many units were sold in the end?
It's fast!
Sold 8 units so far
8 units
8 units...
-Yes
Does it pay for itself?
I've earned a lot with this
Really?
Made a lot of money?
-A lot
Can you make money with this?
He said "money".
-Really?
Evaluated as a "groundbreaking product," additional orders are now coming in
It's true, it's true
Is it true?
-Seriously
There are many business machines that focus on niche areas outside of the food processing industry
This person is very interesting
There is a TTN company in Osaka that develops
It's all from Osaka!
The Pawn Tapper special printer writing tower tool man
※Buddhist written in Sanskrit on the top half and Chinese characters on the bottom half
Writing Tower Toolman
After the dedicated software starts
After entering the name of the preceptor and the name of the giver
It is very easy to print the text on the pawn tapper
A unit priced at 800,000 yen is a relatively high price
It has sold
Sold about 500 units
Well, in this industry, I think there is an overwhelming market share
All of them are pawn tabas
So that's how it is
So, we asked the abbot of Shinnyuji Temple who actually uses this machine
Wi-Fi capable
Color can also be printed out
Color printing
Pretty easy to use
This machine I have here is the third one i've bought
Leaving aside for the moment that the color funciton is a mystery
It does reduce labor
You have to write more than 10,000 a year...
If you use this, you can do it all in a week or less
There's loads so its convenient
I see
Yes, although it is focused on niche machinery
It will surely sell
This is a machine for sweeping aside feed for cattle: JUNO
Push feed
Very interesting
About 1000 units were sold in Japan
He's using the strawberry thing!
-What are you doing when you're on the phone?
Well, I think the dairy farmers will buy it
Doesn't work
Can you concentrate on the phone?
There is also this special machine for making paper neat, the paper bashing machine
Sorting only?
Products developed for printing companies and book production companies
Overseas sales network also available, total sales of 10,000 units
Awesome
Very good sales
Really?
Feedback from actual use is...
Our company is a reference book producer
If you try to make the paper neat by hand
It takes about 15 minutes or so
It takes 5 to 6 seconds to finish with this machine
Awesome
It would be disturbing without it
In addition, 30 units have been sold of a machine that makes sandbags
There's even this kind of thing
And about 300 units sold of one for growing shiitake mushrooms on logs
This is also very time consuming
There is a demand for machinery regardless of the area
Machinery for breaking up haystacks
But in the midst of all this, this Fujiki agricultural machinery of Osaka Prefecture
Osaka again!?
Mulching the insulation film of an arched greenhouse
The developer of a large number of agricultural machines specializing in only one area
Mulch stripping machine
Special machine for digging pits for seedling planting
There have many machines with less than 10 units sold
Electric clamp for stem removal of ginger
What the hell?
Specialized machine for pulling out posts
That just looked like scissors
So
On the shore of the beach
It prevents clams from escaping
We've made special machines for pulling clam nets
This thing doesn't work. The number of sales is 0
It's true!
0 units?
-0
It exists!
Can't sell any?
-No
A special machine for pulling a net to prevent clams from escaping
Finally found a machine that did not sell
To prevent escape
Therefore, the theory has been proven
Can we have a look at that machine?
That machine is no longer available, its been thrown away
Dismembered and thrown away
This statement...
Too much of a nuisance
Angry?
In summary
There are machines that have not sold but they have not survived
That's it, what do you think?
Strawberry, strawberry, that machine
-Yes
He moved his hands a little too late
That's because the operator's skills didn't keep up with the machine
It cut the root too much, right?
-Too much
The tasty parts are cut off
The part near the root 1mm seems to be poisonous
-No, it's not.
Don't talk such nonsense
-Eat all of it directly, it's not poisonous
Scale removal machine
-Yes, there is that one
It didn't make its money back
They should make a cost recovery machine
-Cost recovery
This is all your fault!
-Is it us?
Completely
All of them?
10:0
-So emotionless
I think it should be at least 6:4
Now is everybody's theories
Tonight's presenter is...
Tamura Kenji!
Seems to be super-level, he's on TV everyday
This is the only national program i'm on!
So, let me ask you all
After watching so many variety shows
-Yes
When going out on location and having to save someone who was about to fall into the sea
Wouldn't everyone go along with being dragged into the sea by the other person
1 or 2 people
It is reasonable to say that this is the limit
If you use two hands
This...
Wouldn't it be fun if we could drag more people into the water
No, no, no...
-I've always had this in mind
I don't know, is it possible to do it?
That's why I brought this theory.
-I see
Let's witness it together
If you act as if you are about to be dragged into the sea when a big fish is hooked, you can pull up to 5 people into the water with you
Acting?
Isn't that what happens when you catch a big fish?
-That's how it is
Shouting "no good, no good" and so on
There should be someone to come and help
"No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Then the whole group of people dragged into the water
See how many people they can pull in with them, right?
Up to 5 people?
Is 5 people possible?
Saying, "No, I'm going to fall..."
Then falling in
It'd surely be funny
It feels like something will happen...
It feels like something will happen
If you act as if you are about to be dragged into the sea when a big fish is hooked, you can pull up to 5 people into the water with you
This time, the stage for verification was on a boat that departed on the tide of the Miura Peninsula in Kanagawa Prefecture
Three comedians are tasked with dragging people into the sea with them
And gave fake program announcements to their close juniors stating "they can't go home without catching sailfish"
Under the guise of this, they will attempt to take people into the sea with them
The first challenger is
Thank you--Hello, everyone...
Here he is, Ogata
Panther's Ogata
I believe you are usually the one who gets pranked
-Yes
I'm super happy
I really want to be the party responsible for pranking
For physical strength, I absolutely won't lose in terms of my waist and legs
After all, I used to play soccer
I was a midfielder
The attacking strikers were flattened by me in one fell swoop
So i'll definitely drag all the people down cleanly
It is true that the focus is on the physical strength
And Ogata will use his centripetal force to take down these juniors
They look the type to be beaten easily
Are these guys trustworthy?
The relationship of trust is very strong
Anyway, they're gentle guys, and I think they're going to come running to my rescue
Can he successfully drag people down by exploiting his seniority?
The choice of people is important
The Ogata-gun!
Thank you——
The first thing is to make a decent opening
Any tips? Tips for bringing in the fish
When hooked, it creates a lot of tension
So you all need to focus your strength together...
In this way, the captain subliminally plants the idea of all banding together
On the day of the storm, we set sail for our mission base
Ok ok let's go
-You got it?
Yes yes yes
If you fall into the sea in this condition, it is really dangerous
So we have to help each other
So
Remember to shout "HIT" when you catch it!
Under the captain's command, the group started fishing for sailfish without any suspicion
HIT
How does it feel to be a sailfish?
Eh, did you catch it?
I can't believe it. I can't believe it. It's heavy
Then, Ogata establishes the rule that all members must gather after "HIT"
It's gone
Gone?
What the hell are you doing?
Next, Ogata gets to work
Wait a minute, this is in the, oh!
Hooked!
Sailfish. Sailfish hooked!
A one-handed grip on a pre-designed weighted fishing rod
It feels right
This is where the sailfish show begins with all its might
Pull it up!
It hurts. It hurts. Hold me fast
Hold on, hold on, it hurts, it hurts
They can't let the sailfish take the boss away, so they do their best to protect Ogata
It is really strong!
But five people in this state
Can he do it?
It's hopeless, right?
Next
Dangerous, dangerous, really dangerous
All the power is at the front
Wait, that's dangerous!
So unreasonable
It's too unreasonable...
He simply wants to jump, right?
It's not reasonable!
Ogata tries the strategy of taking himself and the rod toward the surface of the sea
He's gone mad
The body is tilted more than the fishing rod, creating such an amazing image
However, it is worthy of a group of fools led by Ogata
With no sign of doubt, they assist with all their might
Won't Ogata go down first?
After that, it was a stalemate for 2 minutes
What kind of location shoot is this?
That's dangerous!
Pulled back by his group, the mission is declared a failure
Next
Can you take it easy? The fish is off the hook
"Be gentle and supportive"... like an idiot's lecture
That was really dangerous just now
They were stronger and protected me more than I expected
Truly protected him
Who made the most effort?
Nedate
He had such a tight grasp on me
He's as strong as an ox
The fact they went this far to save me makes me happy, but also a little angry
Thus, he understands that dragging people into the sea is not a simple matter
One more time... can you give me one more chance?
Sure, go ahead
Ogata starts his 2nd challenge
Elsewhere, the 2nd challenger is
TKO Kimoto
Centripetal force is indisputable
I am very confident
Kimoto, who is known for being strict with his juniors
Will use a battle plan that uses the fear of seniors as a weapon to drag people down
We're gonna catch today!
So
This group begins fishing
HIT——
In order not to arouse suspicion they first carry out the normal fishing process
Caught a squid
Let's get started!
Kimoto launches the real challenge
The opening point is very well chosen
Whoo-hoo! Hooked!
Wait a minute
Very large
Ah...
At this point is good
Compared with Ogata's group
The Kimoto group's willingness to gather towards their leaders is significantly lower
Didn't come at all
Somebody help!
What should be done?
OK, please!
Even with a personal distress call, the rate of gathering is still sporadic
The force of support is also noticeably weak
The result:
Tugging at people
He uses his own initiative
Had to use this trick
I can't do it myself
Help me a little bit. Help me...
He is forced to pull his juniors himself
So
Three, come!
Ok
Launching a final sprint with a one-handed grip that is unimaginable for catching a sailfish
This is so weird
One hand is also too strange
That's dangerous!
That's not good enough
You don't see this very often
Shinomiya is the only one dragged into the water
Not great
But Shinomiya fell down
Kimoto could not hide his dissatisfaction with the dismal result
It's so dismal
So
Why did you let go?
Hands...
I am very sorry
On board the ship, a lecture begins
I didn't ask you to apologize...
Next, the last challenger is
Very powerful
Alco & Peace's Hirako
My 182 cm 97 kg physique is not for nothing
Played for Tohoku as a football player in high school
Tackling, pushing, squeezing, in short, trying to slow down the opponent
This type of movement is necessary for this
If the max number of people that can be brought is 5
Then the goal is certainly 5
5 targets including his partner Sakai
Hirako will attempt to drag all the people down with his own power
What you catch is not a fish, but your own weak heart
Yes
-Understood
Don't really buy it
The challenge starts
Looks pretty cold
Ah HIT HIT HIT HIT HIT HIT
Wait a minute, it's heavy!
So heavy, so heavy, so heavy, help!
Support!
Both sides of the waist. Come here. Come here
1 here, 1 here
Wait, wait, wait, wait, it's really heavy
Wait, wait, wait. It's really heavy
Reel it!
Not my legs!
Not the legs, hold the waist!
Reel it quick!
Reel it!
The legs are dangerous, my waist!
It's true you'd ask "why aren't you reeling it in?"
Reel it!
Despite being shouted at, Hirako will never reel it in
It'd make you angry!
Not the feet, not the feet, but the waist
Aiming to pull down 5 people on the first try
Carefully assigning each person's position while figuring out the best formation
Why don't you reel it in?
Reel it!
You should reel it
Wait a minute, the line will break ... so heavy
Reel it first!
Can this really be reeled in?
It can, it can
Okay, hurry up and reel it
Please reel it quickly!
On the other side, Ogata didn't even make it into the water
Nedate!
Yes?
Looks like a tuna documentary
Because you are too strong
Yes
Be more gentle next time
Got it!
He uses an inexplicable reason to assign the strong enemy to the further location
Then, before Nedate's arrival, he uses a lightning-fast operation
Aiming to pull down 4 people at the same time as the maximum
Wait a minute
Nedate is excluded
Good acting skills!
Great acting!
Hooked - HIT !
Yes, the best performance
While Nedate is...
He's coming!
The battle plan works as Nedate's arrival is delayed
Nedate is coming!
What to do?
Dangerous!
One by one, one by one, one by one
After approaching
So
You can do it!
Nedate...
Would like to see it again
Fell into the sea at the same time as the enemy Nedate arrives
He could have got three
He tried his best though
With this judgment, two people were successfully pulled down
Nedate downed!
It's really dangerous!
Super dangerous. Are you okay?
On the other hand, the Kimoto Army is...
Try again?
You too!
Same as in your live performances
At the place where you should be rushing
As soon as something went wrong you retreated
Already lecturing about other things
Yes, it is.
-This is the key moment!
It's...
-Right?
Bringing lecturing to a level that has nothing to do with fishing
So unhappy
When the customary Kimoto lecture is well and truly over
Let's fish!
No energy
It'd definitely be like this
The 2nd challenge begins
I can't catch...
Because the atmosphere is not very good now
Here it comes-
HIT
Already saying the atmosphere is bad
Assemble!
The lecture had an effect
The Kimoto army come to support more actively than the first time
Little tighter?
But
Please let go
The youngest junior, Melody Kobayashi, tries to remove his hand
"Please let go" was very clear
Next
Shinomiya again?
Just like earlier, he ends up taking only Shinomiya with him
Melody
-Yes
Melody, you just said "please let go", right?
He heard!
Kimoto's group is bad
It's already the worst atmosphere ever
This fishing trip is not fun at all
Kimoto and I hosted a radio program together
I feel like I really shouldn't listen to his advice from now on
Back to Hirako, who's been in a stalemate for 7 minutes
It's hopeless
Why?
Make a wall, make a wall
Here I am... make a wall in my place
What? A wall?
Guiding them to the front with enigmatic instructions
He successfully distributes everyone equally around him
It's dangerous, Hirako!
Finally, with everyone in place
He's so irritating, this guy
So annoying!
So when Hirako decides to fight
Get out of the way!
Working so hard!
Move your foot away!
My feet are dangling!
Then after 10 minutes of struggling with the false sailfish
The moment has finally come
Move your feet away. Move your feet away
Move your feet away
The last two fell down!
Awesome!
So natural!
It was really an accident
Scary!
Awesome!
Perfect
So strong!
Surprisingly, he acheved the desired goal and successfully dragged all five people into the sea together
So impressive
Brilliantly, he validates the theory
Thank you, Hirako!
On the other side, Ogata, refusing to give up, continues
Fighting with a style beyond imagination
It has become another competition!
What is this situation?
Then
That's not the main idea, is it?
Who wants to see it like this?
It has become tasteless
In summary
Hirako achieved success
What do you think? Sure enough, pulling down five people is a wonderful scene, right?
Mayama?
Very moving to see it finally happen, just like catching a fish
They didn't catch them, just let them go
The last two people naturally fell down
Yes
The posture was very natural, just like a crane machine
It was very interesting
I see
Next time see if it can be done with a bungee jump
What a dangerous idea!
It's a one-person thing
Only those who take the lead will be saved...
Have them hold on to them would be fun, right?
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03