Welcome to this week's Wednesday Downtown!
Thanks for having us!
Let's kick it off with our first presenter. Come on out!
Please welcome Bakarhythm to the studio!
Pleased to be here!
Thanks!
Yes?
For a second I thought you were some brainy high schooler.
Is it the suit?
Uh, thanks.
A programmer, a genius programmer.
About time we had a student on here.
Last time I presented,
The segment was "Early Bird Escape Game," remember?
It aired about two years ago.
We crossed an escape game with an early morning wakeup, and it was quite funny.
Bando Eiji-san freaked out on Kotouge, which made a splash online.
"...Freaked out on?"
Learn to turn down gigs, you idiot. Have some self-respect.
You're right...
Of course work's gonna be hard to find!
This time, we're mixing the escape game with something a little different. Here it is:
Parent-Child Real Escape Game
Parent-child?
Seems they'll bicker.
This time, we've gotten rid of some of the more unclear elements...
...so that parents and kids will be able to work together and solve the puzzle.
What'd you think, Matsumoto-san? Ever solved a riddle with your daughter?
Yeah, uh... probably.
For example...?
As a parent and child. Ever cooperate on a project?
No, yeah...
Like... uh, building a house.
No, that's not what I meant.
Building a house?
There's no way.
That's not a kid activity.
After the break: comedians and their kids challenge the escape room!
Stop!
And...
"Rest of Your Life in Prison vs. Deserted Island"
We ask the studio the truly divisive questions!
Then...
I'll protect you no matter what.
Kuro-chan's romantic reality show: Monster House!
I like you so much~
Parent-Child Escape Game
First stage:
Avoid the pits and escape the maze!
To reach the goal, the blindfolded parent...
...must rely solely on the direction of his child.
Three teams of comedian parent-child pairs will be participating.
Comedians, huh?
Our first participant, brought here without knowing a single thing:
Who is it?
Who's that?
Alco & Peace
Hirako Yuuki
Hirako-san!
What? Scary...
What?
Daddy!
Seems scary...
Over here!
Cute!
So small!
Mitsuki?
Over here, over here!
Ah, he knows her voice.
What? Mitsuki? Mitsuki??
Daddy, you're blindfolded so this might be dangerous...
So blunt!
Moving on...
Where am I?
Akatsu
No, don't let go-- don't let go!!
Daddy~!
Cute!! She looks like him.
Nodoka?
You know right away by the voice.
And finally...
Freaky! Where am I?
Woman Rush Hour
Nakagawa Paradise
Ah, that's right!
Your eyes are closed! Can you guess who I am?
Rintaro? Rintaro??
The oldest kid.
A boy.
Yup!
I'm waaaay over here!
Over here!
He's so happy!
You say "over here" but where's "here" to begin with?
Now that the contestants recognize their kids...
This seems fun for the kids.
PARENT-CHILD ESCAPE ROOM: FIRST STAGE
Won't it be too hard?
OBTAIN THE KEY AND ESCAPE THIS ROOM
Key?
How am I supposed to get the key?
ONLY YOUR CHILD IS PERMITTED TO REMOVE THE BLINDFOLD
The only one who can take off my blindfold is my kid...?
Who will be the first pair to escape?
I wonder...
Mitsuki, where are you?
Give me one more big shout, please!
Here! I'm over here!
"Here I am!" or--
She's getting a little teary.
Oh, jeez.
This way-- is it the way daddy's finger is pointing?
She's just a kid after all.
Daddy, if you get a Game Over, you might die.
If Daddy gets a Game Over--?
"You might die."
That's kid logic for you.
If I get a Game Over I'll die?
He'll die in front of his kid...?
Yeah.
Is it ok if I head over to meet you, Mitsuki?
Yikes, dangerous!
Yeah.
This way? Is this the right way?
That's wrong!
This way?
This way!
That way?
That way!
It's ok if I head this way?
She's 4, right?
That's not it! That's not it!
Which way?
Because she doesn't know her right from her left...
This would be hard for a 4-year-old.
She can't tell, huh.
...her directions are limited to "this way" and "that way".
It's even harder to indicate left and right in the reverse.
That's gotta be tricky.
This way?
Yeah!
Straight ahead just like this is ok?
He'll bump into the wall
I'm going this wa--
He takes his time at the starting line...
...and already 5 minutes have passed.
So that's the strategy.
Stop!
This way?
Yeah!
Straight ahead?
Yeah
Daddy's going this way.
Okay.
Good, good.
Tell me which way you are, okay?
Okay.
Watch out--!
Stop!!
Naturally, the parents are not aware of the pitfalls.
Why'd she say stop there?
Fun's not over yet, dummy!
Ya see?
It's because you didn't listen to me!
That's right. You told me to stop, didn't you.
Yeah.
By the way, restarting from the falling point is allowed.
How sweet!
Oh, so that's allowed.
This is to shorten the length of the game by preventing huge time losses.
Can't be too unreasonable.
But then...
What a cute sweater.
It might be too dangerous to play anymore...
What?
Playing is dangerous!
Huh, what? What's wrong, Mitsuki?
"Dangerous"
"Playing is dangerous."
Mitsuki, what's the matter?
Playing is scary...!
What? It's not scary, don't be scared!
Mitsuki, don't cry! Daddy's right here.
It's because he fell.
Look! It's your daddy~!
It was scary,
watching him fall.
Ah, that makes sense.
I wanna go back to mommy's house...!
"Mommy's house"...?
Let's go back to mommy's house together!
They live together!
Current state of affairs:
"The game is too dangerous to continue."
Maybe not, haha.
They don't live together?
"Mommy's house."
Meanwhile, the Akatsu clan...
Quick!
Huh? There's pitfalls here?
Nodoka?
...discovers the traps from the get-go.
Can you tell me? Tell me which way to go.
Ah, right.
Right?
Ah, she knows.
Yeah.
Man, they sure look alike.
This way?
Yeah, that's right.
Knowing left from right, Nodoka-chan is able to give precise directions.
The team makes sure-footed progress.
She's gotta know when
to say "stop" or else...
Right! It's all about the stop.
Furthermore...
And then one step forward...
Just one step forward is good?
Yeah.
Smart cookie!
There!
Oh, nice! Very nice.
Here?
What a clever kid!
Yeah.
Even her "stop" timing is perfect.
She's doing great!
The resemblance is crazy.
They continue towards the goal.
Hurry, now.
And the father-son pair of oldest participant Rintaro and Paradise...
Ah, I see the resemblance.
Six years old, huh?
Now move forward without falling.
I can't find my footing!
Oh! They're doing quite well.
Like this?
...have yet to make a mistake.
Stop right there!
Stop?
The key's right there.
Key?
Ah, I see.
Ooh, got it!
All that's left is to grab the key and cross the finish line, but...
You're super close!
Just one more step.
Ah! No good!
Uwah--
This is a toughie.
Eh, what's the matter? Can't reach it?
Whatcha gonna do?
What do you think I should do?
This part in particular
seems really tough.
Ok, then to the side.
Here?
Yup.
What'll he do?
Go straight ahead.
Don't turn! Don't fall!
I got it.
Ya know what, just grab the key.
OW!
He's being goofy.
"Ya know what?
Just grab the key."
What gives?
Meanwhile, Team Hirako...
What a little rascal!
I'm a raptor!
Does she like that? Ah!
It worked!
Thanks to some cheering up from her favorite dinosaur...
Amazing.
That's something else.
...they restart the game.
There's no pit there.
Can he even get the key?
Nodoka, tell me, is the key, uh...
The packing peanuts
are sticking to his back sweat.
Is it hanging above one of the holes?
Yeah, yeah.
If I jumped, could I grab it?
Yeah, yeah!
Really now?
Yup.
What a pickle...
Might not work 'cause
he can't see.
Hold on a second! Don't go that way!
Go back?
Mitsuki, don't cry don't cry don't cry!
She's gonna cry again!
Do you want daddy to become a T-Rex?
She really loves dinosaurs!
If that's what it takes!
Got it! I can kind of pull on it...
What's the deal with that?
That's it!
That's it! You got it!
Yeah!
Oh, he got it!
I got the key!
Finally, Team Paradise snatches the key!
And then...
Clear!
What? I cleared it?
A job well done lands them in first place.
Their time: 17 minutes, 11 seconds.
Ah, I get it! That's what this was.
Good stuff!
Rintaro wants to do it too!
Why would you want to do this??
In second place, Team Akatsu.
A successful escape in 24 minutes, 47 seconds.
That's one sweaty dude.
And rounding it out...
Ahh! Mitsuki!
Mitsu~ki~!
Thank you!
Adorable.
*smooch*
This'll give me a cavity.
Team Hirako clocks in at 36 minutes, 20 seconds.
Too sweet for ya?
And so the first stage comes to a close.
Our leaderboard as it stands.
Moving on, the second stage:
Relay the Message! Escape from the Memory Room.
I see.
We can choose from these four questions.
1. Where was this photo taken? 2. What's the title of the song?
3. What's the name of this item? 4. What is this person's name?
You know what?
Say, Rintaro,
Do you think you could crawl through that hole?
That's right. The answers to these questions...
The kids go through there?
...all lie in another room only accessible to the kids.
ehh~
They must accurately describe what they see to their parents...
...and get at least 2 of the 4 questions right in order to escape.
I see!
The lacrosse stick...
Can they do this?
Could ya go in there for a sec?
In here?
Can you fit?
This kid rules.
Scary!
When you've got it, head back here, ok?
Gotcha!
Makes me want one.
Head back to me once you know the answer!
Was it a picture? What was it...
How're they gonna do this?
Daddy!
Ah, there's music playing, what's going on?
I just gotta look for that photo, right?
They can't talk to one another.
Going straight for the snacks.
Hey now...
What? What? What?
AHHH-- ouch, OW OW OW
Why??
It hurts! This hurts!!
Electricity?
Wait, wait! What's going on??
OUCH! OW, wait! Wait!
Snack trap!
Eating the candy set up as a distraction...
...activates the electric current connected to dad.
That's rough!
Are they all gonna eat?
Everyone's getting zapped!
That hurts! That HURTS!
She's unfazed.
No, what? What kind of gimmick is this?
What's the deal?
They all went for the candy.
Scared... I'm scared!
Ow! Ow, ow...
Why? What?
Why? I didn't even do anything.
Over there... someone was there, right?
Yeah, a person was there.
Real quick, could you go back and ask "what's your name"?
I see.
Team Akatsu's plan: start from question number four.
What's your name?
Hmm, I'm afraid I can't tell you that.
Short sketch! Daruma-san ga Koronda!
Daruma-san ga... COLOMBIA'S OVER HERE??
wonder if she can
explain this...
Here! It's Colombia!
What's your job?
I'm a space pirate!
A space pirate...?
Correct.
That's good!
How'd it go?
He had a really cool voice.
A really cool voice?
What did his face look like?
He was handsome~!
Handsome, huh?
That's handsome?
"Handsome!"
He said he was a space pirate...
Space pirate?
They've got this.
By any chance did this person...
Was his face white?
Yeah, it was white.
It was white!
He's got it.
You don't say!
I think he was at mommy and daddy's wedding...
Yeah...
Ah, yeah.
This person's name is...
Gor?Geous-san!
We did it!
His peculiar occupation serving as a hint...
So it was Gor-san over there!
Team Akatsu breezes through.
Really now!
Just one more question until escape.
Also aiming for question four, Team Hirako.
Uh-oh...
That's gotta be scary.
A scary person was there?
What kind of clothes were they wearing? Can you tell me the color?
He was wearing purple clothes...
A guy wearing purple clothes...?
It was scary!
Number four... Gor?Geous.
Gor?Geous??
Purple clothes-- Gor?Geous!! It was Gor?Geous!!
You're amazing, Mitsuki-chan! Wow!
Gor?Geous, he came to mommy and daddy's wedding.
What's with the weddings?
He's everywhere!!
A "who woulda thought?" connection leads to a two-way tie.
Is this guy everywhere or what?
There was a pirate over there with a "Space Parrot"!
A pirate... with a "Space Parrot"?
That's good!
He's just about got it
Yeah.
And the face? What was his face like?
It kinda looked like a lady's face.
You mean he was wearing makeup?
Yeah.
You should know by now!
He had lipstick on!
Lipstick... it's a comedian, right?
He's got plenty of clues.
The guy who has that star over his eye...
What was his name again...
Yeah! On his face!
Can he not think of the name?
He had a star on his face?
Over his eye, with white makeup and a little mustache drawn on...
Who was that again...
It's a comedian. That guy with the globe.
Oh god, I can't remember his name! This is frustrating!
Dad can't remember his colleague's name.
Augh, that's rough.
Can't get it, huh.
Team Paradise's next target: question two.
SAY-SAY KOOEY NE~?
Ok, good good good good.
What's this?
SAY-SAY KOOEY NE~? DO DO DO DO DOO DO
SAY-SAY GOO-RI NE~? DO DO DO DO DOO DO
What song is this?
Say-say goo-ri ne, do do do do doo do...
What is this...
Say-say goo-ri ne... wait, I don't--
Now I'm wondering what it is.
I don't know what this is!
What a performance!
It was a song I've never heard before!
Say-say goo-ri ne...
By the way, here's the correct answer.
SUSHI KUI NE~?
LET'S EAT SUSHI~?
Ah, that's tough.
Well... I mean...
Now that I'm hearing it...
SAY-SAY KOOEY NE~? DO DO DO DO DOO DO
Though he did an exceptional job at recreating it...
They can do it!!
Once again, dad hobbles the team's progress.
This kid is so cheery
That's not all...
It looked a lot like one of those nets you catch bugs with.
He's smart!
What else can you tell me about it?
It kinda looked like a broom, too.
Like a broom?
They make brooms with nets?
Just answer it...
It was in that movie "The Cat Returns".
Daddy's never seen "The Cat Returns".
When she goes "watch out, kitty!" and tries to catch it, it's that thing.
He's not gonna know...
He's got a great memory
Isn't that a bug-catching net?
In the feature film "The Cat Returns"...
...this lacrosse stick actually does make an appearance.
Come on, dad!
There's not much more information Rintaro-kun can give.
Well, of course.
Smartie!
It's something you use in sports...
That, uh...
Dammit, I don't know what that sport is called.
What's with this guy! He's pissing me off.
Once again, the answer eludes this ditzy dad.
What's it called...!
Team Paradise moves onto the final question.
It was like... the Sphinx was in it.
Pyramids, too.
It was a photo.
Oh! Egypt!
Awesome, Rintaro! Nice work, wow!
Thanks to his son, the team finally gets one right.
But this question...
Where is it...?
Egypt!
Tsuki-chan! We can go home!
Egypt! Sphinx... yes!
...was easily answered by the other two teams.
Due to its very low difficulty.
It has now been 15 minutes since Team Akatsu's escape.
Wait, for a second--
SAY, SAY!
Say, say... koo-ri ne... doo doo doo...
Say, say... kuri... ne... doo doo...
LET'S EAT SUSHI!
Yes! We did it!
You got that right for the most part!
The final results are as you see here.
1 hour.
Though the oldest gave a valiant effort, coming in first is Team Hirako.
And there you have it.
At first it seemed like anyone's game; the variation of skill was good.
What a lovely little segment.
You would never think that they're all having affairs.
They're not, and even if they were...
Isn't the likelihood pretty high?
T-san, what did you think?
That one kid at the end who pointed out the Sphinx...
I wouldn't even be able to answer that.
"Damn, that's one smart kid" I thought.
He knew his famous landmarks.
The whole time I was trying to remember the name.
Even the four-year-old... amazing.
Well, uh. It's ok.
That's bad news if you don't know the answer!
I suppose. What about you, KenKoba?
"It's too dangerous to play anymore!"
I wonder what caused her to come to that conclusion?
Yeah, I wonder...
"Uh-oh, dad's in danger" maybe.
She doesn't want to see him get hurt.
For sure. Kids are very protective of their fathers.
My daughter, for example. She hates Hamada.
"The bad man's gonna get daddy!"
Please welcome our next presenter. Come on out!
It's Koyabu Kazutoyo!
He's riding a bike.
Thanks for having me, guys!
This time around I've brought something new.
"Octopus vs. Squid: 50/50 Split". That was the survey we conducted in the studio last time.
Squid ending up winning 60% of the votes that time around.
Of course it would, yeah?
So, we were unable to prove the theory. However...
...this time, we asked 100 people on the street...
...in the hopes of achieving a perfect 50/50 balance in answers.
We'll be asking questions straight from the panelists.
I've come up with a few.
First off, T-Pablow's question. Here it is!
Life in Prison vs. Life on a Deserted Island: 50/50 Split
Ooh, that's a good one.
We can have a lot of fun with this one, I think.
Which would T pick, I wonder?
Keeping in mind the goal is to split the answers.
Ah, yes, that's right.
I do expect the answers to be even, but I've thought about it.
I suppose I'd pick prison. A deserted island may not be so great.
You've never been to prison. How about a deserted island?
I have. Well, sort of. It was semi-deserted, only about 12 people on the island.
It was that kind of place.
So it's not a deserted island...
More of an island community.
There's people! There's only 12 of them, but they're there!
It was only kind of deserted.
They didn't have any cops, no electricity either.
No electricity on the whole island?
How'd you end up there?
Well, I'd been wanting to get out of my hometown for a bit...
So, that's where I headed.
You mean you ran away?
Yeah. Kind of sort of, a little bit.
Don't downplay it!
You ran away?
That's crazy.
On that island, we kind of...
You all gathered?
That's right.
All us mischievous people gathered there.
That's unbelievable.
I want to hear more stories from this guy.
Life in Prison vs. Life on a Deserted Island
Let's investigate if people are split exactly 50/50.
Both are undesirable situations, but...
While you lose your freedom, your basic necessities are met in prison.
On the other hand, you have your freedom but no basic necessities on a deserted island.
Will it actually turn out exactly 50/50?
Which is better, life in prison or life on a deserted island?
Life in prison.
Why do you think that?
There's food, clothes, and shelter.
As expected.
Prison.
Because there's everything you need there.
Right, a popular opinion.
Deserted island I suppose.
I kind of grew up in the countryside, so
I think I could survive alright.
Prison.
In prison, I might be able to have a dog and a boyfriend.
I think there would only be women.
Will the guards be women too?
I definitely want to go to the deserted island!
You can dry plants and make clothes from them.
It's a good theory.
I've thought about it a lot.
What is this?
Yeees.
Thank you very much.
Could you touch right here?
Ah, what is it?
This here is part of my body. My glasses I mean.
Ah, is that so?
It's okay?
What is she talking about?
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
It hurts. It's become part of my body.
Oh my.
Can I touch it one more time?
Yeah, that's fine.
Ah, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow. It hurts.
Oh my.
Because it's part of my body.
What a lively woman.
Thank you very much.
What an encounter.
After that, we continue our investigation.
Thanks lady.
How shocking.
Prison would be better, wouldn't it.
I'd pick the deserted island.
The women prefer that.
I'd also pick the deserted island.
The women like the island.
Life in prison.
I pick life on the deserted island.
And so, after 10 answers, it's a surprisingly clean 5 to 5.
It's looking good.
It seems promising that the theory may be proven.
Truly.
Between life in prison or life on a deserted island...
...which would you choose?
This guy's been.
To juvenile detention.
He did bad things.
What did he do?
Unexpectedly, we discover someone who has been behind bars.
Well, they do exist.
There are people like that.
Why were you put in juvenile detention?
For fighting.
It was before I was 18, I think.
I was against at least 10 people.
And it was just me.
I was fighting and stabbed someone.
How many months were you there?
I was there for around 3 months, I think.
It may have been a bit longer. I can't remember.
The man with experience chooses...
Prison would be better.
A place without other people would be really...
It'd be lonely.
They might be bad people, but at least there's someone.
So softly spoken.
And so after asking 100 people around town, what is the result?
What is it?
Prison.
Life on a deserted island.
It's looking good.
Prison has 42 people and the deserted island has 58 people.
So that's how it is.
Close but not quite.
It was a good one, wasn't it?
It was.
Alright, let's go on to the next one.
Next we have Kendo Kobayashi's theory. Here goes.
When being questioned by the police,
what's more awkward to have in your pocket:
Bra vs. Revenge Notebook: 50/50 split.
What is this?
That would be awkward.
That's tough.
Would you have those in your pocket?
Of course not.
No, but if you had them...
What kind of situation is this?
Truly.
They'd say "You, what's this?".
You wouldn't be able to respond.
You'd be lost for words with both these things.
I only want to hear from guys on this one.
Next, we have Nicole's theory here.
Winter Clothes in Summer vs. Summer Clothes in Winter:
People are split exactly 50/50.
I see.
I think will be exactly 50/50.
Wearing normal winter things like a coat or a muffler even though it's summer.
That situation against
wearing a tank top or a cami in the winter.
I thought it'd be difficult to pick which one to be stuck with for life.
What's wrong all of a sudden?
Next, we have Ookubo's theory here.
Not being able to take your watch off for life
vs.
An agency will message you twice a day confirming your existence:
People are split exactly 50/50.
Eh, what's this?
What the heck?
These don't match at all.
Indeed, they don't really go together.
My thinking was that you normally take your watch off as soon as you get home.
And then you take your bra off.
Don't ask us.
So I thought, it'd be really annoying if you couldn't ever take it off.
Your watch until you die.
And something similarly troublesome would be
having to keep receiving these messages.
Which would be worse, a watch or a bra?
Your watch or bra?
Can't ever take off.
Which would be worse?
Ahhh.
That's a good one.
No, no...
That's a better question to answer.
You're like a big shot producer.
That's easier to grasp.
First, let's investigate what's more awkward to have in your pocket while being questioned by the police:
Bra vs. Revenge Notebook.
Is it a 50/50 split?
Which do you pick?
Going for the bra.
A bra, right?
The bra?
You both pick the bra?
It's the bra.
Actually, I've experienced this once.
Eh? With a bra?
My girlfriend comes over to play and sometimes she forgets things when she leaves.
That situation can happen.
And my friends will come over and
I'll be like "what to do?" and hide it in my pocket.
And occasionally when we go somewhere, it'll come out.
And I'm like "uhh..."
"Ah, this is awkward... what's this?"
Bra.
Huh, is that so?
When doing laundry, my sister's can get mixed in.
If you're talking about bras being in your pocket...
I was ordering a coffee and when I took my wallet out
a bra came out.
That is awkward.
That's horrible.
It was seriously the worst.
That would be.
Girlfriend forgot
Mixed in laundry
Prank
With three people with three different experiences...
...there are surprisingly people who've
experienced having a bra in their pocket.
So, it has happened.
Why'd you pick the revenge notebook, buddy?
I've carried a bra one time.
And it wasn't that awkward that time.
You've had a bra while being questioned by the police?
Sometimes, I'll be carrying the store's window display bra.
I'll have the bra in a bag.
Surprisingly, we've found someone who's actually been questioned by the police.
That's amazing. A perfect match.
I was able to somehow explain it that time...
...but I'd imagine a "revenge notebook" would be really awkward.
So picked the "revenge notebook".
Revenge notebook.
The revenge notebook, right?
That's surprising.
Do you actually have a revenge notebook?
I have one at home...
I have a "revenge notebook" or more like a "dark notebook".
He has one?
Oh, that's scary. What's in it?
So, what do you write in it?
Like, "how I'd want that person to disappear from society."
And so, the result of 100 people is?
That's scary.
Oh, it's full.
The bra with 75 people and the revenge notebook with 25 people.
This is like a batsu game.
The bra wins by a large margin.
So, it does.
Next up,
Let's investigate Ookubo's theory.
(Watch for life vs. Existence checking messages)
What is this, seriously?
Which do you pick?
It's hard to understand.
This.
It is a little confusing.
I don't have a boyfriend or anything, so I'd like someone to check that I'm still here.
Amazing, isn't it?
I'd rather not be able to take off my watch.
Around 1 month ago...
...my ex-boyfriend asked "where are you living now?" and "when are you free"?
It gave off existence-checking vibes.
It was annoying. I thought "Seriously?"
The existence confirmation.
I think the existence confirmation.
And so, the result of 100 people is?
Is it 50/50?
Oh, but...
The watch with 42 people and the existence confirmation with 58 people.
Well, it's pretty good.
It's not bad.
Next we have Nicole's theory.
(Winter Clothes in Summer vs. Summer Clothes in Winter)
Having to wear summer clothes in winter.
I sweat a lot.
There are people like that.
I also get heat rashes.
Right.
I think winter clothes in summer is better.
Winter clothes are cuter.
I'm president of the Don Quixote Lovers Club.
Ah, is that so?
I'll pick the first one.
Winter clothes in summer. I see.
He's definitely the only one in it.
And so, the votes continue to be fairly balanced.
That's surprising.
After hearing from 99 people,
it's amazingly 49 to 50.
This is?
The last one?
This last person may make it exactly 50/50.
One person. This is amazing.
How will it actually unfold?
Seriously? Please, please.
This is amazing.
Will the theory be confirmed?
Isn't this amazing?
It's amazing.
Which one?
Summer clothes in winter.
Unfortunately, while the theory wasn't confirmed...
So close.
Close, isn't it.
...it was basically confirmed.
Yay.
That's amazing.
Nicole was very close to getting it right.
Right?
I was really surprised.
Why do you sometimes insert suggestive people?
Stop it. Seriously.
Suggestive you say?
People that can only be called suggestive.
Is that so?
Well, we only heard from random people.
Are they really random?
Yes, they were actually random.
You were like "That guy! Let's go!".
No, no, no.
Wait a minute, we haven't seen mine.
How come you haven't shown mine?
I was thinking that.
They did it, didn't they?
Did they ask it?
Did they not use mine?
Well, about that.
Let's see Matsumoto's theory.
Let's see Matsumoto's theory. Here it is.
TBS vs. TV Tokyo:
which would be more annoying if it disappeared: exactly 50/50 split.
This is good, isn't it?
We can't say anything actually.
Don't say "Good, isn't it?". You can just say "Uh huh".
We can't say anything, but...
Why can't you say anything?
Because we don't influence like you do!
It's not about having influence.
I think for ordinary people, particularly young people,
I thought this was perfect.
I see. That's what you mean.
But I think it'd be fine if TV Tokyo went away.
I've never appeared on there.
Ah, you've never been a regular there...
Hamada, you been looking during this?
You can't look at that right now.
Because it's TBS. If it was Fuji TV, it would have lost completely.
That's true.
"That's true"...
Can you say "yeah" to that?
Let's investigate: TBS vs. TV Tokyo:
which would be more annoying if it disappeared: exactly 50/50 split.
Which would be annoying if it disappeared, TBS or TV Tokyo?
Ah!
I watch a lot of anime...
Ah, see. There's anime.
It'd be annoying if TV Tokyo went away.
TV Tokyo for me.
"Pokémon" is on there.
That guy watches Pokémon?
And so, quite a few anime votes go for TV Tokyo.
I see. So, it's about anime.
TBS I think.
TBS.
It'd be annoying to lose.
They're cute.
I like their dramas.
Many people like dramas.
TBS.
That's right.
I like dramas like "HanaHare".
TBS has more dramas.
It does have a lot.
But from women, TBS earns the drama votes.
That's right. Dramas.
Initially, it's a close match.
Oh, that's amazing.
However,
However?
It has shows like "Can I Follow You Home?".
Ah, that's a good one.
They have lots of variety shows with funny premises.
Makes sense.
I really like "Goddotan".
Variety shows are expected.
The show where they drain ponds is amazing, isn't it?
Due to the popularity of variety shows, a lead starts to form.
Huh, this is bad.
TBS is channel 4?
That's Nippon TV.
8?
8 is Fuji TV.
10.
It's not 10 at the moment.
There are people like this?
Sadly, there are people who don't even know what channel TBS is on.
These young girls...
However, amongst them all.
Basically, the only TV channel I turn on is TBS.
Oh, is that right?
I feel like that's what I naturally put on.
What is this?
So, if it disappeared...
...if TBS disappeared, I don't think I would watch anymore TV.
You liar!
Really?
Amazingly, we've discovered a die-hard TBS fan.
A proper salary man.
If I turn the tv on, it's always TBS.
He's definitely lying.
It's not the case, right?
What shows do you like?
Let's see.
"The Monday Late Show".
Wrong channel.
And so, the result is:
Oh, that's scary.
It's scary.
TBS with 45 people and TV Tokyo with 55 people.
How real.
There were some lively characters, right?
They were wonderfully lively.
Liveliness...
I don't know! I've only just heard all this.
No, no. Not really.
It's the same as before with the bra and the watch.
The staff are like "He's going to say something edgy, right?"
No, you've got a paranoia problem.
Earlier in here, you were like "croissant or red bean paste bread?"
What's funny about that?!
Because I didn't say that.
Stop itttt.
What's that?
What? Are we going to show this?
Stop itttt.
What are you doing?
Are you lost for words?
Please welcome our next presenter. Come on out!
It's Tamura Kenji!
Thanks for having me on, everyone.
I'm here and that can only mean one thing, folks.
The legendary segment.
And here it is!
Are you guys seriously happy about this?
Super popular.
Is this what you guys are really into?
Hamada-san...
What do you care what kids are into these days?
No, but the girls...
I would think the female audience members would hate it.
You'd think they would!
Everyone cheered!
In this segment, six young men and women live together
and romance and drama ensue.
So, uh... how's that?
This is getting crazy buzz on Twitter. I was shocked.
Everyone's talking about it.
Because it's been a while, let's do a quick recap.
Kuro-chan and Rion went on a date in Odaiba.
Jumping right in!
During the date, Kuro-chan tried to kiss Rion.
Of course, the attempt wasn't successful. Meanwhile,
Taiga and Ran were also on a date, and on the way back, she planted one on him.
As for Taiga, you're all familiar.
That was Taiga's first kiss.
Out of the blue, he has his first kiss.
You never know when it'll happen.
What stories shall unfold this time? Let's find out!
The Monster is running wild.
I have no idea what'll happen next.
Could you go inside Monster House?
Absolutely not!
I wouldn't be able to handle Kuro-chan.
He's too much.
So chic.
Morning!
I slept great.
Hm? You slept well?
You were like, "I slept great~!"
You came back pretty late last night.
God, why is he always like that?
Too early for this.
Yeah, might have been late.
"Might have been late"? You mean you couldn't tell?
Before I realized, it had already gotten late.
What were you up to?
There's this app, and me and someone I met on there, well...
Hold on a sec!
What do you mean?
I've never heard of meeting someone on an app.
Ah, it's for hookups.
Hookups??
For real?
Did any sparks fly?
Nah, not really.
No, huh?
He was super pushy.
Yeah, because it's a hookup app. Scary scary scary...
An app?
He's definitely used one.
Meeting up with someone from an app is scary.
Ever meet up with anyone creepy?
Once or twice, I guess.
I guess Ayumi
uses dating apps.
Of course you'll meet creeps. Actually, a while back...
She's so casual,
it's awesome.
I was supposed to meet up with this girl, but a guy showed up instead.
What? You've met up with someone?
Not me, no, but there used to be this thing called Star Beach...
...and uh... what Star Beach was...
It was basically a place to exchange info and make plans to meet up. But that freaked me out.
There was a friend I had on there who really wanted to meet up with this girl.
They made plans to meet up, and as he's waiting he goes outside for a smoke...
And what he didn't know at the time was that a dude was watching him from a building.
Freaky!
A guy was?
So he's waiting, and he's waiting, and the phone's not ringing so he waits a bit more...
And from above I hear someone yell "DUMBASS"!
Scary! Did you go home?
It annoyed me, but I was more baffled than anything. Then I went home.
So... it's your story after all.
She realized.
No. Nope. This happened to my friend.
You're talking
about yourself.
It was definitely you.
It was totally Kuro-chan!
No way! That kind of stuff never happens to me.
What a liar.
What an ominous opening...
At least deny it faster.
Right away, yeah?
Sure looks fun.
I'm a bit worried for Ayumi...
Don't watch the pachinko balls fall.
How many times are
they gonna show that?
What a great parody.
I wanna watch, but I'm scared.
How's it going lately?
I'm got some new roommates.
Oh yeah, that's right.
We're sharing a house.
It's your first time with roommates, what're they like?
Well since it hasn't aired yet, I can't really get into details, but...
...there's one boy who's a bit younger than me... and one a bit older...
...and a famous person.
Do I know them?
Oh yeah, you two would most definitely know him, he's well-known.
Wow! I wonder who.
Famous in a different
way, though.
Is he hot?
He's one of those looks-personality gap types. He's very sweet.
He's a [comedian], so that's...
That's misleading.
You know...
Chore Board
Living Room: Kuro-chan & Rion
Doesn't that mean Rion's with him?
Kuro-chan, do it properly.
I am!
Looks like fun.
Rion, do you cook at all?
I was really into it once, I can make a bunch of stuff.
What can you make?
Nothing special... like hamburgers.
What else... oh, I can make cabbage rolls.
Wow, that's impressive.
If I liked it, I'd make it.
So hey...
What the hell is that t-shirt?
I'd love to eat your cooking sometime.
Seriously?
Yeah, seriously! For real.
I'd love to give it a taste.
Disgusting.
Then next time, ok?
You will?
It's a date. Make a bento, will ya?
It might not be that good!
Nah, it'll be tasty for sure.
It'll be fun. Show me a fun time, ok?
What kind of "fun time"?
Rion-chan sure
is a nice girl.
She's making it?
She's making it as promised.
It's hot...
Morning.
Nope! You can't come in the kitchen.
Eh, what?
I'm making lunch. Ah! Don't don't don't dont!
Back hair, back hair!
Uwah, nasty!
Ooh, show me...
It's poking out of his tank top...
You'll just have to look forward to it.
Look forward to it? Gotcha, I gotcha.
You look so cute. Can I really not look?
Good morning!
Ugh, what the hell.
It's gonna be fun, isn't it~? Let's look forward to it.
Yeah, I'm excited.
You know, I don't really have much experience making bentos...
He's pretending to take selfies!!
He's filming her!
He's not taking selfies?
This is my first time really making one.
Really?
But his face, look...
He's taking pictures of her!!
He took a picture!!
What the hell is this technique?
He... he didn't take a single selfie!
This guy is out of control.
That's sneaking photos.
Wait, he took another one!
When she turned around!
Scary face, scary face.
Oh, my!
Nice out, isn't it?
Oh man oh man oh man.
Isn't it?
It's a bit warm out too.
You're right.
OH OW OW OW OW OW
Ahh!
You're all dirty! Are you ok?
I flew, I flew!
You sure did!
First hit, third hit.
Go for it! Go!
Oh, wow! Wow wow wow!
Oh jeez oh jeez.
A--Ahh!
He's looking, he's looking!
He looked! He looked!
He REALLY looked!
That was awesome! You went so far.
This guy saw her underwear!
That was seriously great.
This jerk...
Wonder if we'll find anything...
- Anything specific?
I won't know until I see it.
It'd be nice to take some pictures.
Yeah, some photos with everyone.
Isn't that one too big?
Good vibes.
No good? But this way you'd be able to see more.
What do you think?
This works.
Right? White or blue, which is better?
Blue... actually, the white one.
Looking good over here!
So two white and one blue. Yeah?
Let's do it.
Here I go... Rion's homemade bento, open sesame!
Go ahead!
Your face right now...!
Oh my god, is this supposed to be me?
That's your mustache, and those are your eyes...
It's adorable!
It's making a scary face.
Really, and I mean really, this makes me so happy!
I'm glad.
Awesome! I'm so happy right now, seriously!
Eat it, eat it.
It's ok to dig in?
Rub a dub dub
- Thanks for the grub.
Cheers~!
Hamada-san, please
watch carefully.
You bet I am.
Delicious!
You mean it?
What a relief! I didn't know if you'd like it.
It's very, very good! Oh man, this is so awesome!!
Ahh, thank goodness.
Just eating food you'd made would make me happy.
That makes me happy to know...
She's the gullible type.
That this day would finally come...
She can't say no.
For sure.
Could... I go "ahh"?
This is the stuff that
inspires envy.
In a lot of ways he's
really incredible.
Eh? This might be difficult.
Ah.
I wonder if I'm gonna be good at it.
Not quite honest... yet
very forthcoming.
In such a natural way, too.
I'm all embarrassed!
Yummy! Out of this world yummy.
He's staring.
You seemed kinda bashful as well.
Did I?
Ahh, really, real-- wow! Oh man, oh JEEZ this is just so much fun and I'm just WOW thank you!
He's being sincere.
Not even kidding.
He won't stop talking.
I wish I could have this kind of fun forever, ya know?
His true self!
This guy...
This is gonna be awkward.
Yummy.
It's sweet!
So, the other day when we got dinner...
On the way back, uh...
About the kiss, like, what was that about?
He's weirded out.
Taiga's adorable!
Because I'm into you.
That's why.
Is that so?
That's the wrong approach.
yeah
...did you not like it?
No.
I didn't hate it or anything like that...
This is stressful.
More like I'm just confused.
Well I mean, I thought it would be fine.
To kiss you and stuff...
So I guess I'm wondering how you feel, Taiga...
How I feel?
Like, what are you thinking, and stuff?
Me, personally...
...a relationship...
is something that builds over time...
...and I can't suddenly go putting labels on things.
That's right.
So I guess what I'm trying to say is right now...
...I'm not really thinking.
It was his first kiss after all.
I'm not really thinking we can go out.
I see.
Glad we talked.
I'm really sorry.
Seems she got rejected.
Oh god, what the hell.
Wow! This is great.
He's got his head on her lap...
Feels good when you move around a bit.
You good?
It's embarrassing with people around...
Is she ok?
Yeah...
Oh, wow...
My head fits here perfectly.
For real.
Sure is fun to be a guy on a date...
What's she feeling right now?
Uuhn~
What even is this?
Rion, you might not remember but...
...and I said this back in Odaiba too...
...I'll protect you no matter what.
This. This line.
Thank you.
That's awfully reassuring.
That's his signature phrase.
Ugh, this is exhausting.
Cheers!
Nice work today, everyone.
Alcohol's in the mix now.
Yummy!
Standing and drinking just isn't my style.
Right?
I could fall asleep like this!
Nah, that'd be weird.
If this suddenly became a Sleeping Beauty situation...
I could, though.
Sleeping Beauty...?
Hey, so I've been wondering...
...how's it going so far? Your love life.
Well, I've got stuff going on...
With Ayumi-chan, right?
He went and said it!
So?
Well...
We're getting to know each other.
Me and Ayumi.
Say, Ran-chan, what's your type?
It's probably...
Gotta have things in common with the guy...
...or else I won't be like "Oh! I like this dude."
It doesn't matter if he's handsome or not.
You go by feeling?
Yeah, that's what I think.
What's with that face?
I drank quite a bit.
Gonna hit the sack soon.
Sleepy?
Good night!
Not good not good.
Night!
His face was super red.
He was caught so off guard, hilarious.
Think he snores?
Yeah, he's probably super loud.
So, uh...
It seems you've got a good vibe going with Rion.
Nah, nah.
Not like I have with you, Ran-chan.
What a scary guy.
He knows just what to say.
You say that, but you went on a date with her.
He's just feeding her lines!
Yup.
It might be too late to say this...
...and you're right, we did go on that date...
...we went on a date but...
...but the truth is that, when we moved in...
...the person I liked the most was you, Ran-chan.
Really??
Yeah.
Aaand that's a lie.
He's lying.
I know you don't feel the same way, you said so yourself.
So even though I was thinking "ah, she's cute".
She thought he was gross.
That's right.
Yup.
"Maybe it's better if I don't get too close."
You said I was gross, after all.
Ah, I-- I did say that, but, you know...
When it's like this...
...it's actually kinda nice.
After I turned you down...
...I was really a wreck.
I was scared you'd get mad, and I didn't wanna cry in front of you...
Nah, that's just the way it is. Women aren't into me.
I don't think that's true at all.
No no no don't
say stuff like that.
Hell of a statement...
N-- No, that can't be right.
Even the monster
is taken aback!
Right?
Not good, not good.
Can't it be?
For real, not good.
You mean it?
Yeah.
Ok, well how's this:
Hold on, what's he doing?
Here.
Wanna hold hands?
I guess it's possible?
Here ya go.
RAN-CHAN
Whyyyy?
Wha?
So hey. It's not like I, you know...
I don't wanna come right out and say it but...
I really do like you.
Eh? What?
I really do.
He said it so fast.
Not a fan of this distance.
I'll protect you. I mean it.
What the hell!
He said it again!!
"I'll protect you" again!
He says it immediately.
What does he mean
by "protect"?
And I know it's a long shot, but...
Yeah, what's "protect"?
This distance is bad news...
All this time, I've been holding back my feelings but...
I like you the most. You're my type.
Ahh scary scary scary!
She's drinking too much.
I'm not just saying that either, I'm super into you.
No, no, no, no, no.
Bad, this is bad.
Even the way we're holding hands.
...or if we kissed. We don't have to go out but...
I can kiss you.
She can...?
Really? You'd kiss me?
That's bad! If they kiss...
I can.
STOP STOP
STOP THIS RIGHT NOW
Don't do it!
Look! Look at him!
RAN-CHAN!!
I really do like you.
DISGUSTING!
AAAAH!
That's why I said stop!
Please god, STOP!
No, I can't!
Really, now?
I said STOP!
His face!
I can't watch!
This is really...
Let go, hands off the girl.
Now...
Just-- OH HIS THUMB!! GROSS!
I just really like you...
SHUT IT DOWN!
AhhhhhHHHAHHA!
Done. I'm done.
What are we gonna do...
Everyone's screaming.
Nope nope nope nope nope.
NO, NOPE!
No way...
This intimacy is NO GOOD.
Yeah.
He's SNUGGLING.
For real...
No no no no...
What are you doing?
For real, you really get me. You really get me.
Enough. Enough of this.
Go back to your room.
Your room, go back to your room!
Go to bed. Go to bed.
It's not too late!
I like you so much.
Someone come in, please.
They're gonna do it again.
This is so bad.
Army, someone call the army.
SECOND TIME!!!!
HE DID IT AGAIN!!!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
NO NO NO, NO!
Aw, jeez...
Jeez...
This is no good for me.
I seriously like you.
Not good.
BADBADBADBADBAD
BAD!
It's bad, it's really really bad.
RAN-CHAN
You're drunk, Kuro-chan.
What are they DOING?!
I'm not drunk.
Yeah, you're drunk.
Am not~
You so are!
Maybe... but I'll remember this.
Raaa~n...
I'm drunk, too.
Tomorrow I might not remember this.
It's no good if you don't remember!
Guess I've gotta kiss you again.
Yeah, guess you do.
Don't forget, ok?
This is screwed up.
Enough already!
Seriously! Enough of this!
It's getting late.
That's enough.
Hot, it's hot.
I've gotta get up early tomorrow.
It's hot in here.
What is this?
Enough, enough.
Don't forget, ok?
I won't.
Go back.
Go back to your room.
Go back!
Because I won't forget either.
I'm sorry if I do.
Go back!
Your room,
go back to your room!
No~pe. If you forget I'll have to kiss you again.
I'm sweating so much.
What's with the sweating?
I wonder...
This unpleasant sweat.
Good night.
Thank god.
Go, leave.
No more, no more.
Good night Ra~n!
Night!
This guy, seriously.
Scary scary scary.
Uwah that's where she was sitting!
Her seat! That's her seat!
He's smelling it.
He's smelling it...
...where she was sitting.
Not good! This guy smells seats.
Shut up!
Is he thinking about
going for the cup?
From where
she was drinking?
No way!
I told you!
He's turning it!
I knew he would do that!
This guy, I knew he'd do it!
He's a maniac!
Smelling...
He's doing it all.
He's got all his bases covered.
From top to bottom.
Uwah, the smelling!
He's gonna do it all.
Smelling-- is he done?
What a conundrum!
He must be so happy.
Super psyched.
I sure like her.
Don't forget...
Don't forget, me!
Don't forget!
I kissed her...
No, hold it, hold it.
He did it all.
Wild.
Ran...! Ran!
He inhaled so hard
he choked.
He's wheezing!
What is going on?
That's enough, ah!
He poured it in Ran's glass.
He must be on cloud nine.
He already did this!
He's turning it around.
Wouldn't it be mostly his?
It's YOUR damn spit.
It's yours.
You've gone around once already.
He's laughing again.
What is WITH this guy?
What a long scene.
Must be nice, Kuro-chan.
What am I gonna do?
The journey of love.
Exhausting!
Thank god it's over.
I'm exhausted, oh man.
Same here.
No, this is-- this is, uh... what exactly are you showing us?
For some reason I'm drenched in sweat.
What is this?
Same, I've got the weird sweats too.
It's like it suddenly got hotter in here.
But that's not for no reason, you know?
Definitely.
Totally.
Anything can happen when young single people are living together.
Ahh, about Taiga-kun right?
Yes.
Taiga seems to have turned down Ran-chan.
That's right.
That was a bit... you know?
You'd get jealous.
That's true. What's your take, Okubo-san?
Girls get jealous, and she'd definitely want to get to him before Rion.
But all of a sudden, the Monster Magic got a hold of her...
The booze, yeah?
And she was drinking.
He has that certain something.
If he were a good-looking guy, I think he'd be even more popular with girls.
I see.
His persuasive energy with women is crazy.
'cuz he's persistent.
You've got a point.
I see, I see.
To be able to look into someones eyes and say that...
"I'll protect you."
I'll protect you...
...protect? What am I being protected from? What does that mean?
What does that mean??
In fact, he's the number one threat out there.
Next week! Cigarettes in a Minor's Bag!
How will these comedians handle it?
Oh, wow! These are awesome.
And!
Elevator Quickchange Challenge!
Can you change clothes before the first floor?
Also:
The show airs today.
Can't wait!
Monster House, episode four:
"I like you the most."
The worst...
No, no, you've got it all wrong!
Catch past episodes on Paravi!