Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Thanks for having us
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Anyone there?
There is, of course there is
It's Shoji Tomoharu!
No shouting
Mikitty! No spray version
-An original
Because of the epidemic
-Epidemic Limited Edition
So folks, it's not too late
The lecture series, we all like it, right?
There is such a series
I'm bringing a new perspective on the lecture series today
Really?
Are there any more?
This is it, please take a look
While lecturing someone, it's ok to add Nagabuchi's lyrics
So that's it
Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi, I really like his stuff
Kakuta, do you like him too?
-I like him
A lot of his lyrics are like tenets of life
I also like him a lot
So wouldn't it be a good idea to mix his lyrics in while lecturing someone?
His words themselves are all very good
-No doubt about it
The problem is how to blend them in
You can't do it when flirting with someone, right?
No, no, no, no.
-Indeed
He has a song called "Captain of the Ship" which is 13 minutes long
You can just use all of the last seven minutes, right?
-Yes
Really?
-It's true
It's all about uplifting sentences
-Yeah, yeah, yeah
It's all about "live and let live" and "you must finish"
Are you that obsessed?
What? What's wrong?
You're really the worst, seriously
No, no, what he's saying is weird
It's because his lyrics are really inspiring.
-That's right
If the person realizes, the lecture will end immediately
Also,
If you have a strong will, you can control your body even after falling asleep
And
There are no residents whose nearest station is "Meibijo Station" on the Tokyo Monorail
While lecturing someone, it's ok to add Nagabuchi's lyrics
So the first challenger is
Thank you for having me
Moriyama
As per the theory, the contestants will choose from the following 10 famous songs written by Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi
Moriyama's choice is
In terms of what is better to include in a lecture
Nagabuchi's "Dragonfly"
Seriously?
The famous song "Dragonfly", which became a household name as the theme song of the drama of the same name
Came from Osaka to Tokyo resonates with me
This song is also very much in line with my own situation
So the most suitable for my current situation is "Dragonfly"
※If the lyrics are spoken incorrectlythe score will be reduced
This time, the lyrics are divided into ten levels according to the difficulty of adding the lyrics
Is it possible?
Must be tought
With a time limit of 30 minutes, the highest score wins
The shorter the lyric, the less the score
But if in the process of lecturing
Yeah
They will be disqualified if the other person points out the lyrics
To the north to the north is only 3 points
Normally you wouldn't point out something like that
The juniors who are the targets are
Kyon's Cotten, a Tokyo-based junior
A junior of Moriyama's for five years
It's probably not a bad choice.
-Is it?
This kid seems quite innocent
Probably a good target
You think he won't realize?
-Yes
And so
A fake project of "2-shot talk with comedians who are close"
Kyon is called to participate
While waiting for the official filming, the "Dragonfly" lecture begins
Dragonfly lecture
How many lyrics can be mixed in?
How is Nishimura?
He's good
Ah but...
I saw your show...
Really? Thank you.
-It was fun
I liked that part
What?
That high school girl
Ah Sachiko? Thank you
Is that a character you use in the theater?
No, that's just for the screen
You should continue with the character
Eh——
Since it's popular its best to run with it
Really?
You should definitely keep using it
Yeah
But to have a persona isn't enough
As if standing there with an irrelevant face
Yeah
So impressive, so natural
And he agreed
I want to grow up to be a person like you in Tokyo
What do you mean mean be a person like me?
From the masters to the seniors who are near the same level as you, everyone supports you
No, no, I'm not that good
I just
I'm just praying to stay true to myself
Oh so cool
He said cool
Didn't notice? He even said cool
Risky move
Although the lecture itself is a little weak
So far, Moriyama has not been discovered, and the lyrics of "Dragonfly" have been added naturally
Samurai SLICE
※In April 2021, Samurai SLICE moved from Yoshimoto, Tokyo to Yoshimoto, Osaka
They've come to Osaka, haven't they?
Came to Osaka and were immediately invited to the theater there, right?
It's great that they dared to move to Osaka.
-Yeah
What they are doing now
Will they keep a loser like me in mind?
This is a bit too much, right?
As long as they don't notice it's fine
Keep in mind?
What do you mean keep in mind?
I usually look up words I don't know when I come across them
This is bad
Keep in mind...
But Samurai SLICE's performance in Osaka was also very good!
Very good, really interesting
So, especially in this world
It makes people feel like sitting on pins and needles
Sitting on pins and needles?
What does it mean to sit on pins and needles?
Moriyama is really a man of culture!
You are too uneducated, okay?
Nagabuchi's unique use of words and phrases, which are not used in everyday conversation, arouses suspicion
Indeed, so unique
Unexpected, Moriyama experiences a crisis
So many words i've never heard today
But it seems the lyrics don't immediately come up when searched, so he's safe for now
Checking immediately when encountering
But you create things like this
Where are you going to fly next?
To win the King of Conte
You yourself are also  counting the nights you can't bear  to cheer yourself up
I actually counted
Only 5 minutes remain
What kind of person is this
He was a good choice.
-Yes
Kyon is very underdeveloped in regard to detecting "Dragonflys"
And so, Moriyama pushes ahead
Sure enough, after listening to you face to face, I really think you look very happy
Yes
I think you look like a happy dragonfly
A happy dragonfly?
Too much too much
So funny!
If you were compared to a dragonfly
Is the happy dragonfly Nagabuchi?
Really, do a good job!
Moriyama Disqualified
So at this point, the truth is revealed
Betting on a big one
Are you lecturing? Moriyama?
It wasn't a lecture
I was scared when this kid kept checking things
I was so scared that I couldn't breathe
The next challengers are
Thank you for having me
Oasis' Okubo
How about Miyuki Nakajima?
Using Miyuki Nakajima's famous song "FIGHT!"
She lectures I AM Noda, a junior
The phrase "FIGHT!" is a good one
I want to say "please keep fighting" to him
I think it should work
How will it turn out?
It was a few years ago, right?
You once asked me for advice
You and I talked once, didn't we? Over a drink.
-Yes, yes
That's when you said you wanted to work harder and wanted to enter the R-1 and so on
But you've always been so comfortable with the status quo. How old are you?
I'm already 44.
-44
If you don't put more effort into it, it'll be too late
How can I put this
Shivering in the cold water trying to swim upstream
I've never seen you work that hard
What kind of person talks like that?
It's good to have fire in your belly
You're not too old
When the sun shines on the surface of the water, can you see the fish underwater glittering
Yes, yes, yes, very beautiful
The glow is the fish's scales that have flaked off after being injured and are floating in the water
Impressive
Ah, that's it
The more damage you suffer, the stronger the light will be
You haven't even been hurt, have you?
-No, I haven't
Okubo cleverly integrates the lyrics into the dialogue
And they resonate with Noda
Great! He's moved!
The fish are going upstream
Very determined
Have you been watching a lot of National Geographic or something lately?
-Yeah I have
Are you still borrowing money?
-No
That was a long time ago
A guy I met in the theater company when I was in my 20s
Isn't there a way to get an easy loan, like the ones posted on telephone poles?
He fell into that trap
Then people came to his door
Said that he and his family would never have a place to stay again
What? Did the debtor tell him that?
-Yes
Is this a lecture?
I'm just trying to discourage you because it happens
I won't cause anymore trouble
He didn't understand it though
And so
Great, not found out
I actually witnessed you
Witnessed?
You saw?
-Yeah
Eh? When?
Yesterday, on the steps of the tram stop
The concept has changed
It seems like you can't hold your head up when you walk
I was so shocked that I ran away
Eh? Eh?
Felt scared and ran away
But in Shinjuku...
-In Shinjuku
Shinjuku?  -You weren't there?
Eh, I wasn't in Shinjuku yesterday
I was just scared for no reason then
I thought "how did the Noda I knew become like this?"
It wasn't you?
She continues
I came across a male producer or someone of a slightly higher status than us
I was invited to drink with him
I just thought I'd be better off if I were a guy
Then I may not have to try so hard to please men
I wish I were a man
7 points?
-Streak
Adding this is impressive
So strong
All of it?
The score is super high
Still hasn't realized
Okubo executes a beautiful combo
Is it just because Noda is an idiot?
Immediately afterwards
Surprisingly, you and Takeda have a good relationship.
-Yes, we're very close
After all, he has a junior high school education
Is he just a junior high school graduate? No, he went to college, didn't he?
Is that wrong?
Is that wrong? I wondered
So I'm wrong?
-He'd be happy if you remembered
It's not right, he went to college
She forcibly attempts to add "after all, he has a junior high school education" to the list
What are you talking about?
-Yeah
At this point there were still five minutes left
Seriously, you can do it, FIGHT! FIGHT!
I will, I can do it
FIGHT!
What you are saying is...
No, no, no, sorry
I really did not expect you to say this
It's been really enlightening
Not only does he fail to notice the lyrics, but he also receives a rewarding lecture
Okubo's impressive performance nets her 86 points
Awesome
The truth is revealed
The lecturer is an important choice
Hello
Is this Wednesday Downtown?
You look really happy
Wait a second, because...
No, is this for real?
Don't be so happy, tell us what the theory is
Don't just think that being on this show is great
That...
This time is the real lecture
"How to use fish as a metaphor for a sense of futility"
This outlook is accidentally interesting
The next challenger is
I also came to participate
Shoji Tomoharu
Captain of the Ship" by Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi
I want to see this one
This is my choice
This will be quite tough
Among the many tracks of Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi
I chose "Captain of the Ship" because it conveys an extraordinarily strong will
He will lecture his junior, Garittochu's Kumagai
Kumagai also knows that I am particularly fond of Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi
I sang this song several times when we went to karaoke
Will it be too obvious?
Might be tough
So this is a bit worrying
Have you decided what you want as a moving gift?
No, you don't have to be so polite
Just say, just say
Don't act like you're embarrassed to ask
-OK
I'm serious.
-Okay, I get it
"What do you want as a moving gift?" The answer is too slow
Thus begins the lecture
You have concerns about interacting with everyone, and you're limiting yourself
The lyrics start from here
I feel like you do
You should say what you want to say
Even if someone frowns and says you "love to be in the limelight"
it's much better than saying "you are a good person"
Even if someone frowns at you and scolds you for being in the limelight
So it's wrong here
Those long-winded arguments will also follow you later
You'll make seniors and juniors worry about you
Not up, not down
Nor to the right or to the left, you just keep going
and not to the right or to the left you just keep going all the time
Two versions
Before you say believe in me, you must love the self that can always believe
Before releasing the words that you believe in me before you must love the self that can always believe
Happiness is not something to be but something to feel
Are you underestimating me?
-No, really
You despise all human beings, not just me
I really don't underestimate the human race
Don't underestimate humans
What were we before becoming comedians
Human beings
-Human beings, right?
We're human, right?
-Yes
Hot blooded
In the end, you and I are just human beings
Don't look at human beings with such rotten eyes
You've been dead for almost 3 years
I can't believe it's been as long as 3 years...
Live well
-Yes
Live on, live on, live wonderfully
Ok... Ok...
The passionate lecture continues
30 minutes have passed
The truth is revealed
Really?
Didn't realise
How do you feel after listening to Shoji's words just now?
He is so angry, has he been under a lot of stress recently
Talking about life and death, it was a bit much
When explaining himself, what he was saying seemed pretty good
The scores are as follows, Okubo ranks first with FIGHT!
Wonderful
What do you think Asahi?
Sure enough, at the end of the day, everyone was overwhelmed by passionate emotions
The fact that they were lyrics didn't really matter
They just paid attention to the emotions and didn't realise
So, you could get "Yosoro" in there?
※Nautical term meaning "keep going straight" also appears in the lyrics of "Captain of the Ship".
"Yosoro" is impossible, right?
How can you do it without "Yosoro"?
That's too tough
If you added it, the score would be very high
That'd be like giving the song's personal details out!
Kakuta, as a fan of Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi, do you want to try it?
It was amazing, but I don't want to do it
Watching was enough
In addition, additional versions of this lyric project were made prior to the broadcast of this episode
You are so unbelievable
And so, the second one will also be broadcast in the near future
Let's welcome the next presenter
It's Chocolate Planet!
Spray-less version of Ikko
Don da ke!
What are you guys up to?
So much to do
How long are you guys going to mess around
Hey, stop!
Stop everything!
Sorry
So let's get straight to the point
Have you ever dozed while standing up on the subway?
Yes, quite often actually
Maybe once
Although you're dozing off
Whilst being shaken around
You won't let go of your hand, right?
-Indeed
When you doze off, you'll move but your hands are still...
I've never seen anyone collapse.
-It's rare
There is no such person who dozes off, right?
Eh? What type of person?
One more time.
-Just dozing off
There are no such people, right?
No way
That's dangerous
So we bring you this theory
If you have a strong will, you can control your body even after falling asleep
For example?
You'll keep holding onto the ring because of the will to not let go as its dangerous
Please take a look at the VTR
If you have a strong will, you can control your body even after falling asleep
This will be verified by holding a rope connected to a basin
Very simple construction
The theory is valid if the test subjects can sleep for 1 hour continuously while not letting go
Impressive to be able to sleep under these conditions
By the way, whether they're asleep or not will be judged by a brain specialist
The first challenger is
Midnight challenge
Hello everyone, thank you for having me
A man that must be mentioned when speaking of tenacity
Yes
Yasuda Dai Circus' Chief Yasuda
Looks like it might work
Do you have a battle plan?
Wearing pajamas
Just keep my brain asleep and right hand awake, right?
So that it will not fall
Only retain consciousness here
You can't do it
Only here is awake, the brain is asleep, it can work
Simple to say at least
Seriously?
The challenge soon begins
Is it that simple?
I'm gonna fall asleep by sheer willpower
Letting only the brain sleep
What does it mean to fall asleep by willpower?
After maintaining this posture with his eyes closed for 10 minutes
A strong alpha wave has appeared
The moment this wave breaks
He will have fallen asleep
The Chief is just one step away from sleep
Later
He's asleep
That's impressive
The clock starts from here
The Chief, as declared beforehand, continues to hold the rope firmly after falling asleep
After 5 minutes
At this point
The hand holding the rope relaxes for a moment
Before gripping again
And
The same phenomenon continues with a certain frequency
Now he is in a very unusual state
He's drifting between the sleep state and awake state, these two types of brain waves are appearing simultaneously
Is it rare?
Yes, i've been doing these tests for 35 years
It rarely happens
The Chief is indeed a unique individual
The Chief actually achieves the seemingly impossible state of "half asleep and half awake"
But the position of the basin gradually lowers
17 minutes after falling asleep
The basin descends to here
At this point
It's making a "hiss, hiss" noise as it drops
Finally "hiss, hiss" and it dropped
Nice hit
Looks like he just woke up.
-It's true
Good morning
I messed up
Were you holding the rope in your dream?
I think I was confusing reality and dreams
I had a dream that I couldn't sleep because I was holding onto a rope
The next challenger is
Awesome
Thank you for having me
Hello
-Hello
Sunshine Ikesaki
Ikesaki held the line with his eyes closed for 20 minutes
Sleeping well
He's now asleep
Sleeping nicely
As before, he successfully keeps the rope steady
Looks like a sleeping chimpanzee
This is not an animal experiment
But if you look closely
Little by little, the hand is loosening
You can see the rope moving slightly
Thus, the basin gradually descends
After sleeping for 40 minutes
The basin is almost touching his head
At this point
Slowly
Turned into a hat
This is...a bit of a strange result, right?
Let it fall down!
Not how I thought it'd go
Unfortunately the least harmful interaction between man and basin in the history of variety shows
I thought I'd fallen asleep and woke up
So I better pull it up
Eh
So boring!
Indeed
But very real
The next challenger is
Thanks for having me
The third challenger is Audrey's Kasgua
Confident?
Just need to keep it like this, right?
Nothing difficult, right?
But confident... it's difficult to say if I am or not
I was told to do so so I will do it
That's my Wednesday Downtown approach
They're always saying "wait"
And telling me stuff like "don't sleep while answering questions"
So i'll definitely sleep with this in my hand, of course!
So good
Kasuga thinks it's a simple job to do only what is required
A look of self confidence
But after 1 hour with closed eyes
There is no sign of sleep
Must be tired after an hour
Can't sleep
It's just been an hour now. You haven't fallen asleep, right?
Didn't fall asleep
You can't start if you don't sleep
Well, yes, yes, the timer starts only after you fall asleep
Too aware to sleep
I'm sleepy...
It's been...about 3 hours
Oh really?
Still can't sleep?
I'm closing my eyes and saying "must sleep" in my mind
Isn't this how it goes?
It's making me more sleepy
I'm getting there
The staff want him to sleep quickly
Afterwards, he still can't sleep
And so came the morning
No way
It's already 6am
-Oh
You need to get to your next job
He talked a big game
So you're disqualified
Damn it...
I guess it's too tough for me to fall asleep
In this way
Please call me again
Very impressive
There are other things that I can do
A touch of sadness
I'm sorry
The final challenger is
Hello
-Hello
Thank you for having me
Magical Lovely's Noda Crystal
If you drink
You'll fall asleep faster
Sleeping wine
-Yes
Noda also belongs to the group that cannot sleep in new environments
So he has some chilled whiskey to get him off to sleep
That's better
After 10 minutes
At this point
He's asleep
Quick
As he's sleeping, the challenge begins
But
So quick!
Hurts doesn't it
Surprisingly when falling asleep he pulled the rope down hard
And the rope broke causing the basin to fall
The result was unexpected. In short, the challenge failed
I don't even feel the pain...
But it scared me to death...
Ah, no
Did you let go?
You're annoying. I don't know
So humiliating...
Don't do this
This is Downtown's show... how could I do this
Noda, are you drunk?
They're watching
Now I'd like to have a good sweep.
-Really?
Sweep
Eh
You seem to be stuttering
-Unclear, I know
Eh, is this going to be shown?
You want to show this type of result too?
-Yes
He seems to have drunk too much
Actually drunk
Originally I wanted to sleep until... drink until I fall asleep
So humiliating...
Don't do this, everyone stop, don't shoot
Otherwise no one can go home
Damn...
No one can go home
What are you talking about?
What's going on?
-What are you upset about?
I looked sharp when I turned up...
So when everyone that came today... no one can go home
What happened
He's crying
Too much pressure
What's wrong with this guy? The verification is over. Enough is enough
What's going on here?
I can't drink wine...
Can't drink and still
-Yeah
I thought everyone couldn't go back home
Drank to have to fall asleep.
-I thought I wouldn't be able to sleep
If you cannot sleep until the morning we cannot go home
Cute, didn't realize he had such a side
We've got enough footage, it's fine
But you fell asleep at least
-Yeah
So that everyone could get home ok
Understood, thank you very much
I'm sorry, I'm so busy...
-Sorry...
Sorry... everyone is busier
I just have worries, I... just like to think too much...
Sorry, everyone, please go to bed
I can't have the big shots scared because of me
I'm sorry...
Well, everyone is working
Not entirely incomprehensible
Ah... I screwed up
Not going home at all
It's okay. It's okay. You didn't mess anything up
-I'm sorry...
Noda shows an unexpected side
But what exactly is his state of mind?
Everyone is in a bit of a bind
When a little more sober, we re-listen to what he has to say
If you know that others suffer because of you, you will cry
They are also raised by decent parents so they know not to cause other people trouble...
Aren't most people good like that?
I don't know
I hope everyone can be like that
I'm sorry
-I'm sorry
Thank you very much at this late hour
Thank you
What kind of project is this?
To sum up, although accidents occurred frequently
The winner is Sunshine Ikesaki with 41 minutes and 12 seconds
What does everyone think?
Four out of four
-Yes
What sort of mood should I have been in watching the last part?
I've known Noda for a long time but i've never seen him like that
But he is a sensitive person who takes care of others
The staff is in a difficult situation due to not being able to start until the person falls asleep
It's hard to fall asleep in the first place, isn't it?
-Yes, it is
So the staff really had their work cut out for them
Falling asleep in that situation is very impressive, indeed
Kakuta is suddenly very serious
It is not possible to treat Noda Crystal as an ordinary good person
Have you been drinking too?
No I haven't
Don't cry!
Now it's time for Everyone's Theories
The next presenter is...
Tamura Kenji!
Thank you
Isn't this everyone's favorite man?
You've won a prize
Everyone's favorite?
I have never met anyone who hates him
I'm like curry
Is that so?
Let's get to the point
I brought a theory related to the station of the monorail
This is it:
There are no residents whose nearest station is "Meibijo Station" on the Tokyo Monorail
※Tokyo Monorail：A Tokyo-based railroad company that operates only one route, the Haneda Airport Line
What do you think?
Kakuta, do you know of this station?
I know, because people...
Whenever they go pass they think "I don't think anyone lives here"
Passing by while thinking?
-Yes
I don't think I remember anyone ever getting off there
But the station exists, right?
Yes, it exists, Hamada
It is a station located near Haneda Airport
The station is surrounded by airport-related facilities and factories
The people who work there?
-Yes
There should be people who use the station to commute
But is it the closest station to anyone's home?
If so, there should be people leaving from there in the morning
Indeed
And so, a survey was conducted around the station
I'm really sorry about today, Hamada
I cut my bangs too short
So the circle is a little small
Can't even speak clearly...
It's summer, so its natural for it to shrink
There are no residents whose nearest station is "Meibijo Station" on the Tokyo Monorail
We immediately went to the station to find out...
The station is there
As said, the only buildings or factories near the station are those related to the airport
No residential-like structures were found
So we headed in the direction of the residential area
And didn't encounter anyone while walking for 8 minutes
But 8 minutes is an acceptable range
Finally we found passers-by
Excuse me, we are TBS
Do you live near here?
Yes
What is the nearest station to your residence?
Tenkubashi
You don't use Meibijo?
No
After that too...
Tenkubashi
The nearest station to the residents here
The old man just now...
As you can see, it's Tenkubashi
Was that necessary?
Because he also uses Tenkubashi
It is true that no one lives closer to Meibijo
Eh? Is the theory true, then?
It was proven almost straight away
Incidentally, there are other stations in the area
Haneda Airport Terminal 1 Station Terminal 2 Station, etc
A total of 4 stations are located in the hinterland of the airport
Of course, since there are no residences around here either
So again, there are no residents whose homes are closest to these stations
Then the survey was extended to the whole of Japan
Surprisingly we found a similar pattern
First...
Umijigaura Station on the JR Tsurumi Line in Yokohama City
This station is actually located in the hinterland of the Toshiba factory
It is a station for Toshiba employees only
Since there are no residences within 2 km, it is not the closest station to anyone's home
Following the model of corporate stations
There is an unmanned station in Toyoura-cho, Gadatabata-gun, Hokkaido
It is located at the connection between the mountain and forest tunnels
A "small front station" that barely shows its face in a gap of only 80 meters in total length
There are no roads around the station, and the only way to get to the station is by train
If you want to walk from the station to the road
You have to walk for 1 hour in the mountains
In terms of anyone living there, you have to go another 6km down the road to get there
Of course, no residents would consider this to be the closest station to their homes
But why exactly is a station located here?
Because this place was originally a single line open to traffic
If the trains weren't staggered, the efficiency of transportation would be affected
And...
The tunnel is very long
It was used by steam trains previously
So there had to be a place for the smoke to go out
Only a specific amount of smoke could be exhausted while the trains are staggered
That's why this was set up
For the above two reasons, the signal station was set up during World War II
Now it is no longer used
After the end of the war, it was used as a fishermen's colony for about 100 people in the coastal area at the foot of the mountain
The station was upgraded to a passenger station, "Koboro Station," with the privatization of the national railroad in 1962
But
Since there are almost no schools and stores, no one has lived here for a long time
Thus, there exists a small station that no one uses
Why does it still exist today?
In fact, in 2015, JR Hokkaido expressed its intention to abolish it
However, in view of the fact that many tourists came to visit the station at that time
Toyoura-cho is trying to hold on to the station no matter what, and is actively working on maintenance and management
That's why it has been kept until now
The unique railroad structure has captured the hearts of secret area lovers and railroad fans
Although it's a station that one can't even walk on
It's a potentially popular tourist attraction
There are many other stations like this that are like secret places
A view of the rapid flow of the Kinkawa River is available at the "Lookout Seiryu Station" in Yamaguchi Prefecture
So straight!
Kushiro Wetland Station located in the middle of a large wetland in Hokkaido
Next: In Shizuoka Prefecture
Oodai Lake-san Station" was built in the middle of the lake
Of course, this station is definitely not the closest to anyone's home
But it is relatively popular with tourists
Passengers come from all over Japan to enjoy this beautiful scenery
Although these places are not used by residents, they are perfect as tourist destinations
Such stations are located all over Japan.
However, there is a "Furunan Station" in Hoyan-cho, Ten Shiro-gun, Hokkaido
It is a station that is not even a tourist attraction
Conducted by JR Hokkaido
According to a survey, only a few days in a year has visitors
The number of passengers at Furanan Station
From the 27th year of Heisei to the first year of Reiwa, it was 0 for 5 consecutive years
In other words, this station is not used by any residents or tourists
As far as you can see, this station is surrounded by pasture and grassland
Almost no one lives near the station now
With the development of personal transportation, the number of people using the railroad decreased
Thus it eventually hit 0
So what exactly does this station exist for?
The features of this rare station have attempted to be put to use
And ways to attract tourists and keep the station have been sought
Have you done anything to increase the number of tourists
We made a mascot with the theme of the secret station
Yes, there is a mascot named " Furfur Meow" at Furunan Station
The inspiration for "Furfur Meow"
Surprisingly...
Was the storage cabinet on the platform
Even if there is nothing, mascots can still be born
Thus, the theory is confirmed
Yes, it holds
But because it was established too quickly we had to go a bit further
And delve deeper into the existence of such places in Japan
Serious content that runs counter to Wednesday Downtown
I think it's good once in a while
It's bad to finish on saying something is bad
The mascot at the end is disgusting
Saying that...
-It's just a mascot
It's cute!
What do you think, Kakuta?
I feel like i've learnt something
You have learned something, right
Every now and then, a nice theory pops us
-Yes
Occasionally...
It's shocking to see
"Wow, it's actually a nice theory," etc
You realize halfway through
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03