Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Viking's Kotouge!
Eh... it's that XXXX
Can you say such a thing on TV?
Today is the 5th edition of a highly popular project
5th Sushi Master
It's been a long time since we've done this
Indeed, it's been a long time
Yes, it's making a comeback after four years since 2017
It can't be that popular if it's been four years
It's not really popular
If it's a prank thing, to avoid suspicion
It's understandable that it would need to be put on hold for a while
But that's not the case for this one
Did you get a bribe from the sushi underworld?
No, I didn't
There is no hidden agenda between this show and underworld sushi
After four years, new songs of the sushi master will be challenged
And
I slept over at a comedian's place
When hearing amazing gossip, you'll drop what you're doing and focus on listening
The same as Taiko no Tatsujin, participants eat the ingredients that are sent to them in rhythm with the song
This game is Sushi Man
Three members will challenge a level at once
But even with some heavy hitters
LEVEL 4 has yet to be completed
A challenge that has still never been overcome
Who will be the first in four years to take on this challenge?
Who?
Can they do it?
Three comedians who consider themselves big eaters
Can they eat that well?
Are they confident?
I always eat very quickly
I have confidence in my appetite
As for speed, as a fireman, you sometimes need to eat quick and rush out
Usually, I can do 50 or 60 plates of revolving sushi
Fish Kingdom
Please eat sushi!
Food Group - Ⅱ
Magic Pocket
Gari Gari-kun
Cod roe
Wow
The five levels are as follows
In three-player mode, Fish Kingdom, is skipped as this level has already been cleared
The challenge starts from LEVEL 2's "Please eat sushi!" Start the challenge
This is a fast-paced song
-Very fast
The sushi's here!
So quick!
As team work is very important, will they be able to work together?
Really tough
Tuna medium brisket, small fins, and bamboo fish, welcome
Star eel, sweet shrimp, pickled mackerel, sea bass, welcome
So fast!
Scallops, abalone, red scallops, sea scallops, welcome
Impossible!
Bonito, red trevally, sea urchin, salmon roe, welcome
Quickly quickly!
Not good, but close
Our sushi place is number 1 in japan!
Please eat sushi! Please eat sushi! Please eat sushi!
Take it, take it!
Drinking tea, drinking tea, have a sip of tea
What's wrong with you?
Sweet ginger, sweet ginger with some sweet ginger
Come on, sweet ginger is coming, sweet ginger is coming!
Eat quicker!
The head of the octopus round and round
Pick it up!
Squid with triangular ears
Here comes the snapper
Snapper in love with wakame
The pig on the right isn't taking anything!
Flounder holding a red thread on the porch
Chewing so slowly
Our sushi restaurant is the number one in Japan
Actually not bad
Please eat sushi! Please eat sushi! Please eat sushi!
Not bad, not bad
7 Guan left
They could do it
Have some tea. Have some tea. Have some tea
Get the tea!
Sweet ginger, sweet ginger with some sweet ginger
Sweet ginger's coming!
Impressive
"Please eat sushi!" is over!
Much faster than I expected
It took some time to figure out how to open my throat
To swallow the food so quickly
It took a while to get used to it, yeah
What nonsense are you talking about?
On to LEVEL 3
Not saying anything of worth
Instead of challenging a previous stage, a new challenge is undertaken
Let's cooperate and win together
What is the new tune?
A total of 16?
What kind of food is it?
What is the tune?
Haven't heard it
Captured by you on the day we first met
Tatsuro Yamashita?
-Sounds like it
But I couldn't say anything
Don't underestimate it!
It'll suddenly come
Seems quite slow-paced
Two people standing in front of a doughnut store
Oh, what is this?
-Donuts
Doughnuts are not easy to eat
A youthful mood rushing up the ramp
Ah, I'll only eat doughnuts with yo
Not bad!
Ah, I want to eat doughnuts with you
Too big!
Ah, sweet kisses like doughnuts
Pretty good
Ah, a future of doughnuts for two
Can't they use slightly smaller ones
I am the twisted twist donut
You are the sweet icing doughnut
And finally, a whipped cream donut
Pigs!
Ah, my heart goes out to you doughnut
Not good not good
Ah, I like you so much donut
Still 7?
This is too hard
Ah, I'll only eat doughnuts with you
Pigs! Pig! This pig doesn't eat at all
Ah, I want to eat doughnuts with you
Ah, sweet, sweet, sweet doughnuts
It's too big!
Not good
-Who's gonna eat the last 3?
Ah, sweet, sweet, sweet doughnuts
Pigs!!!
That's the last one.
-It's doable
Come on!
-Success!
Not eaten all of it
It's not in your mouth!
What is the result?
What the hell?
Too much
I'd like to have some creamy ones
The ones that come up are just fried, aren't they?
I can't swallow it!
One or two is not bad
The powder just sticks around in the back of your throat
What the hell is this guy talking about?
The other two aren't saying a word
Why is it this guy explaining every time?
Suffering donutization of the oral cavity with the mouth's moisture being sucked up
The comedian team are defeated at this point
The next challengers are
Hello
Two plus-size performers and one known for her big stomach
Yoshimoto's female comedy team
Tough to say if they can do it or not
Whats the most amount of sushi you've ever eaten?
Impressive
It's easy to see from our body size
I eat about 6000 calories every day
That's how much I eat
Wow
Here we go.
-It's started. We can do it!
The female team begin the "Please eat sushi!" challenge
Tuna medium brisket, small fins, and bamboo fish, welcome
Star eel, sweet shrimp, pickled mackerel, sea bass, welcome
Two at once!
Not bad
Super quick
Scallops, abalone, scallops, sea scallops, welcome
Don't lose your chain, you idiot
Bonito, red trevally, sea urchin, salmon roe, welcome
Get it!
-That was close. The rhythm didn't fit
Our sushi restaurant is the number one in Japan
Good, good, good, good.
Please eat sushi! Please eat sushi! Please eat sushi!
Dangerous. Dangerous. Come on!
Just hurry up and get it!
Two mini tanks with goalkeeper Utsunomiya
The perfect match to take out 25 kanzushi
Have some tea. Have some tea. Have some tea
Sweet ginger, sweet ginger with sweet ginger
What the hell? Hurry up and eat sweet ginger!
The head of the octopus is round
The purple pig isn't doing it in time
Have some tea. Have some tea. Have some tea
Sweet ginger, sweet ginger with sweet ginger
Sweet ginger sweet ginger sweet ginger quick quick
That was close
OK
"Please Eat Sushi!" is over!
However
Have you been picking what you like to eat?
Yes, the distribution is not balanced
No, it's all her fault
She ate all the good food
I only got ginger and wakame and stuff
But we got through it
I'm so happy.
-It was a breeze
Which LEVEL 3 stage will be chosen for the female team?
Food Group - II
What is it?
① Bento Box Song
What is this tune?
Festive tunes
It is a festive tune
A small bento box
Oh this one
Stuffed with two nori rice balls
The rice balls are so big
Chopped ginger and sprinkled with crushed sesame seeds
Ginger again
Carrot, cherry, shiitake, burdock
Hurry up and get the mushrooms!
Lotus root with holes
Ok ok
The tall bee-doo vegetable
34 plates left
It's even easier than before
② Song of Mushrooms
Mushrooms?
The little mushroom grows well
Here comes the mushroom
Apricot abalone mushroom, danmao mushroom and crab flavored mushroom
Get it! Get it!
Tiny mushrooms growing strong without panic
Tasty little mushrooms eaten in one bite
Tiny mushrooms growing well without panic
Can't swallow anymore
Swallow it quickly!
Chewy apricot mushrooms love to jump on the teeth
She's just watching the food pass
Tiny mushrooms growing strong without panic
She's working hard!
Hot little mushrooms eaten in one bite
Still relatively easy
③ 3 Dango Brothers
There are still 19 plates
Dango？
-3 Dango Brothers
You'll choke
Not good.
-This is harder
A wooden skewer with a string of dangos
Get it! Get it!
Three in a bunch standing side by side, dango dango
Get it quick!
Drizzle soy sauce over the top, dango dango
One person can take two skewers
3 Dango Brothers
Enjoying flowers in spring, enjoying flowers
Looking at the moon in autumn, looking at the moon
They can rest in between
All year round, dango dango
Ok ok ok
3 Dango brothers, brothers
That's it, purple one!
Dango dango
Good good, not bad
3 Dango Brothers
Last 3
Dango
And so, the female team complete the stage!
This is a good team
Passed LEVEL 3
Awesome
What is it?
They now embark on a new challenge, LEVEL 4
Why was that included?
A new song is chosen
What is it?
What will happen?
46?
④ Yodel has had enough
All-you-can-eat barbecue buffet
Eat until you're full oh yo lo lo lo hey
So much
German sausage to your heart's content
So big!
Eat until you're full oh yo lo lo lo hey
Cow stomach, cow tongue, cow stomach, cow tongue
Full on beef stomach, beef tongue and beef sirloin
Get it!
Pork liver, pork liver
Roast pork liver and veal chops
Oi, purple one!!
Dipping sauce dipping sauce dipping sauce
Dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip!
Dip, dip, dip!
So much dip, what the hell?
This one is too hard
This is really hard, too much
No... I can't stand drinking dip
Because they could not withstand the surging dip eight consecutive attack
The female team lost at LEVEL4
As Hamada said though, that girl really isn't good
So the next challenger is
Hello
Who?
A big eater?
Two people who both eat 20 pounds of food on Youtube
The Hungry Tummy Twins and
The big eater presenter Asako Tani
A new generation team of gluttons
The big eater team skips the previous levels
And start at LEVEL 3
① Bento Box Song
It's the bento box song
Food Group - II is chosen
Ah, nervous
They should be very capable, right?
A small bento box
Stuff two nori rice balls into it
Chopped ginger and sprinkled with crushed sesame seeds
Carrots, cherries, mushrooms, burdock
Lotus root with holes
Good rhythm
The tall bee-doo vegetable
They're awesome!
As expected of professional big eaters
LEVEL3 is easily completed
Passed it
As expected
Thus, they pass to LEVEL4
Will they pass it?
What is this song?
All-you-can-eat barbecue buffet
Ah, meat!
Eat until you're full!
Looks easy for them
Don't eat so slowly
The dip is waiting in the back
Eat until you're full oh yo lo lo lo hey
They gonna win?
Cow stomach, cow tongue, cow stomach, cow tongue
Full on beef stomach, beef tongue and beef sirloin
If you don't take it quickly, there'll be something left
Pork liver, pork liver
Roast pork liver and veal chops
Get it! Get it!
Dipping dipping dipping
Dip dip dip dip dip dip
Here comes the dip. Here comes the dip
Ah, missed one!
OUT
Too difficult
This team also loses at this stage
They worked hard
The final challenger is...
I've come to eat
The strongest team
Legends
The Legendary Big Eater Trio
To some extent, this is a game
I think it requires swallowing ability more than anything
For LEVEL3, they tackle the donut song that the other group were helpless against
Can they handle it?
Why is he sitting?
He's too tall
Captured by you on the day we first met
Can't fit into the shot
-Oh yeah
Isn't this Taro Yamashita?
But I couldn't say anything
You understand
Oh, here we go
There it is
Two people standing in front of a doughnut store
They look so happy
A youthful mood rushing up the ramp
Here we go. I'll take care of the next one
Ah, I'll only eat doughnuts with you
Ah, I want to eat doughnuts with you
Ah, sweet kisses like doughnuts
What's he doing?
He's having a sit down
Finally got one
Ah, a future of doughnuts for two
Every mouthful is so big
I am the twisted twist donut
You are the sweet icing doughnut
And finally, a whipped cream donut
Cream doughnuts
Ah, my heart goes out to you doughnut
Here we go
-Impressive
Ah, I like you so much donut
Ah, got it
-Really powerful
Ah, I'll only eat doughnuts with you
The first two are pretty much enough
They can do it easily
-Last five
Ah, I want to eat doughnuts with you
Ah, sweet, sweet, sweet doughnut
They're enjoying themselves
Last two
Ah, sweet, sweet, sweet doughnuts
Easy
As expected
They're certainly big eaters
DONUT SONG complete!
Easy
-Easy
Honestly not difficult
Why so quiet?
How loud do you want it?
Next, they challenge LEVEL4
The so far unbeatable "Yodel has had enough"
Can they pass?
Who knows
I know this, i've sung it at karaoke
All-you-can-eat barbecue
Eat until you're full oh yo lo lo lo hey
Move your hands, so annoying
Grab it already!
German sausage to your heart's content
Awesome
Eat until you're full oh yo lo lo lo hey
Cow stomach, cow tongue, cow stomach, cow tongue
Full on beef stomach, beef tongue and beef sirloin
It's so awesome
-How awesome
Pork liver, pork liver
No meat can reaches him
Roast pork liver and veal chops
Dipping dipping dipping
Dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip!
Come on, get a little more
Awesome!
Impressive
So difficult, dipping sauce
Full on pork, chicken and squid
Eat until you're full oh yo lo lo lo hey
Roast corn, cabbage and onion
Roast whatever you want hey
Rice, rice, pickled radish, pickled cabbage
Dessert, fruit, almond, tofu, whatever
Good, good!
Dipping dipping dipping
Beer is extra
So strong
Invincible!
They did it!
The first clearence of Sushi Master LEVEL4!
To be honest, I basically didn't eat anything
Really?
Indeed
-Only pig liver and fruit
Basically, you two did it
Next is the most difficult, LEVEL5!
With three songs to choose from
A carrot
Carrot
Two cool mops
Three yachts
It's hard to eat carrot
Four sesame seeds
Take your time
Five rockets
Six turkeys
How is that possible?
OUT
It's impossible
It's too big
In summary
the challenge of 6 turkeys has been upgraded to LEVEL10
It's not suitable
Too crafty
In the end, it was too much
This is too difficult
Its shocking
Hamada was constantly talking about the purple pig in the middle
People are not livestock
An expression that others purposely avoid
Hamada is behind the times
Really is
This shouldn't be done
He's from the time that mobile phones were all like this
Telephones were carried
Let's welcome the next presenter
Who is it?
Impulse's Itakura
Let me ask something
Do you like gossip?
If I have to say, I think I do
Today's topic is related to gossip, and it's this:
When hearing amazing gossip, you'll drop what you're doing and focus on listening
I see
Given the ease of hearing real gossip in the industry
This time, we chose a coffee shop inside TBS to verify the location
It is indeed easy to hear
Would you listen to it?
Indeed, if someone is talking while i'm waiting
I'll certainly listen
Yeah
Actresses often talk to the makeup artist, right?
-Yes
Makeup artists talk a lot
It's true that make-up artists have a lot of material
They love to spread gossip
When hearing amazing gossip, you'll drop what you're doing and focus on listening
Therefore, this time
We called the test subjects to the coffee shop inside TBS under the guise of a fake meeting
The agent calls them to inform a change of location
They must get to a new location as soon as possible
In this case
Even in spite of this, will they stay and listen to gossip?
We will verify if they can be forced to hang around and listen
The first target is
Kamaitachi's Hamaye
Attempting to keep him in place is his partner Yamauchi
What kind of gossip are you going to use
People in the industry and actresses sleeping with each other
I'm going to use this type of scandalous content
So, here's the gossip conversation next door
Their TV series finished, right?
There was a celebration party after it ended
The relationship between us heated up
After the party, you know, one thing lead to another
I went to an actresses' place
-Really?
What? Really? An actress?
Isn't that impressive?
Awesome, what the hell?
Who?
I'll tell you later who it was
At this point, the strategy is to use a key name to hook him
And keep the target rooted firmly in place
Totally listening
I have a feeling he'll stay to hear the name...
He'll definitely be super interested
The one always in those TV commercials
A superb one
A little glance
Already listening now
Also confirmed the other side's face
This is the bait, right?
Wondering what the other side looks like
Which is when his agent begins contacting him
-Hello
Sorry, there is a slight change in the meeting location
Changed to a meeting room on the fourth floor
They are already there, please go there too.
-TBS?
Yes
-Fourth floor of TBS?
Yes, the fourth floor of TBS
Sorry, please come quickly
My coffee just arrived, please wait a few minutes
Oh... OK
Please come soon.
I'll be there as soon as I can
Deliberately stirred the ice cubes
Iced coffee just came or something
That's no reason to put off a meeting
I'll tell you what happened
We played bingo at the party
Coincidentally
I got a prize
You mean at the celebration party for the show?
-Yes, the most recent one
As the gossip is very detailed
The name has yet to be disclosed
No intention to leave
Thus, 7 minutes pass
So long
Making them wait so long?
Then say "I did before too, but don't tell anyone"
Like they had a relationship with someone else too
Before, in other circles too
How should I put it
With other actresses too...
-Seriously!?
Had a lot of luck recently
Wait a sec
In another group?
With a different person?
-Yes, yes.
What, another actress?
Not so loud!
-Are you kidding me?
Impressive, right?
Not moving at all
To what extent?
To what extent? I'll leave that up to your imagination
Stop messing with me
Turned around to see the face again
I'm not
This is definitely a "this guy, really?" look back, right?
An unacceptable look
As if to say why can this guy do it but I can't
Basically, with people in the same circle
It's really been a long time
I'm more active
-Oh shut up, you're too lucky
It doesn't mean anything though, usually the other side is acting
How can I put it? I didn't even really have to do anything
They did all the work
Stretching now
Seems a bit fidgety
Just leave already!
The staff are still waiting for you
Pinned in place for 10 minutes
The iced coffee is all gone
-Really all gone
Another phone call from the agent to hurry him
Surely he'll have to go this time
You haven't arrived yet, have you?
-I was just leaving. I was just leaving. Sorry
The other side seems to have other things to do shortly
Just asked if we can change the time
The other side seems a bit...
I've finished my coffee
Fourth floor?
Fourth floor, please come quick
-Okay, okay
Go go!
Although he said on the phone he was leaving, however
Get up and go!
Tell me about it. I'm sure it won't get out
Not going anywhere
Is it ok to say...?
You've pretty much said it all already anyway, so just get on with it
With a feeling that the name will soon be disclosed
Will he go or not?
Five minutes pass and he's still there
I'll tell you if you treat me.
-No problem
Really?
-This one's on me? No problem. It's on me
You want to go? Let's go
Can I have another drink then?
Giving up
Ok ok
With the promise of another drink, he grows impatient
Have another drink
Understandable
And gets up to leave
He can't exactly ask
16 minutes
So, the truth is revealed
How long do we have to wait?
Shame on you
How long will the staff have to wait?
So embarrassing
What what?
Listening to gossip the whole time!
No, no, no. What are those two people doing?
This is too humiliating
So much attention paid to an AV star
-They're gone...
What's going on here?
Waited so long!
Ah you surprised me
Do you know what this is?
-Wednesday
Wednesday Downtown
- Yes, Wednesday Downtown
It can only be this one. This is TBS, after all
So the verification was explained
You'd definitely be interested!
You can't say you wouldn't
-Why wouldn't you leave?
I intended to leave as soon as I heard one piece of information
But they just wouldn't reveal a key point
So, Kamaitachi's Hamaye stays for 16 minutes and 28 seconds
A long record!
Way too long!
The next target is
Tsutsumishita
Listen to me, this is a big deal
-What?
A show may be shelved
A TV show?
-Yes
Really? What's going on?
The performer didn't show up yesterday to shoot
Seems concerned
5 or 10 minutes is understandable
But they still didn't turn up after 2 hours
-Really?
Listening intently
When hooked on the gossip, the call is made to state the location change
The challenge beings
Guess what?
-What?
They were arrested.
-Arrested? Really?
Why? Why?
-Drugs
You'd definitely listen
His expression is too funny
Who was it?
-I'll tell you later
Why are you acting like that?
-No, no, isn't this a bit too big of a deal?
So concerned
Not moving at all
Looks like a cop
Holding his coffee, he listens for 5 minutes
What's up with his hair?
- Listening so carefully
I used to see him at the shooting site with red eyes
You had a hunch?
-A premonition I guess
Complicated expression
Everyone was talking about it being a possibility
And the makeup artist noticed something
Bruises on their arm
Don't spread it
A makeup artist with whom I have a good relationship was doing his makeup
Well...
This is a bit too hard to believe
At first they thought the bruise was because they were filming an injury scene
They thought it was painted at first
But it wasn't at all
-So it was real then
A real bruise
The expression is too funny
Listen way too carefully
So funny!
Seriously listening
Doesn't that guy have a girlfriend?
Not to mention his girlfriend, he has a wife.
-Really?
Then isn't it over?
His eyes are moving
Too good to not listen to
This guy is so simple
He's in another world!
He's searching
Searching on Google
Trying to find the answer online with the clues he's just heard
Of course, it's impossible to find it
After that, 6 minutes passed
At this point
It's almost time to go
Looking at his watch, Tsutsumishita finally gets up from his seat
14 minutes and 55 seconds
It's already 15 minutes
Okay, I said tell me the name
-Really?
Unexpectedly, he comes back
What are you doing back?
Regardless of whether it's fake or not, what is he coming back for?
Although I would like to tell you, it's difficult to say
I can't be the one to say it
Guess.
-Eh...
If you guess right, I'll tell you everything
As he understands the answer is a long way away
Given up
He leaves again
What happened?
What do you think work is?
Haven't you figured out to be grateful for work?
Don't you get it?
I'm very grateful. Of course I'm very grateful
But this is a great topic
What a horrible look in his eyes
If its work, you should go straight away
Impossible, everyone will be like this, right? You'd want to continue listening to it
No, you think that since you said you were here, when you were informed of the change of location
You'd be giving in to the other party
So it's okay for you to stay here and listen for a while, right?
I don't think I'm giving in to the other person
With 15 minutes and 21 seconds, they take second place
Hamaye is still in a strong position
Magical-lovely's Murakami is the next target
I'm focusing on a super painful topic about young artists
How to say...
The hot topic backstage is usually this
But before that, something happened that caused a lot of headaches
What?
There was a special casting call for new performers
You've mentioned it before
That's right
A new performer did something stupid.
-Who is it?
Who? You may not have heard of them. It's a young artist, I don't know if they've been on TV
I don't know if he's ever been on TV, but the way he wore the mask was so eye-catching
Who is it? Is it a group?
It's a group.
9 Street Retro
9 Street?
9 Street
9 what?
9 Street Retro
He's listening very carefully
He looked back
This time, the name of the junior group that he might be interested in is disclosed first
The battle plan is to keep him with the promise of a stupid act
The call to change location takes place
The 4th floor conference room
The challenge begins
They did it again, put the show on pause
Oh really
It was really unfunny, seriously
Someone came, Kyo I think it was
It was terrible
Super awful
He really did something stupid
A stupid thing
They called his manager
Called the firm?
Really dumb as hell
Which office?
Although Murakami also seems to care about the gossip
After receiving the call, he left his seat after only 40 seconds
Basically left right away
Seriously!?
Hello
What the hell?
What's going on?
It's too fast
I'm serious
I guess I should've stayed
Did you care about what happened?
-Of course
This is your favorite topic, right?
-I like it a lot
Then don't leave. Keep listening
You know I don't want to make anyone angry, don't you?
Don't you know that?
So you think of not making people angry first?
The final target is...
Morita, a famous gossip lover in the entertainment industry
You give the impression that you like to gossip a lot
Yes, he does
Kojima of our firm
I don't think he does it anymore...
It's impossible for Morita not to listen
He loves it
I'm sure he'll be interested and keep listening
He's the type that actively seeks out gossip
The gossip prepared for Morita is...
Speaking of which, some time ago
I slept with a comedian
Eh, wait, a comedian?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Really?
Who? Who? Who is it? I'm curious
Well...
I'll tell you the name later
Eh, wait, I'm so curious
Wait a minute
He's already looking
He wont be leaving anytime soon
Oh really?
Yes, yes, I would like you to come to the fourth floor.
-Got it
Wait, wait, wait, wait
What's going on?
I was on a program
Was out of town for a day
We got to know each other very well when we talked
So we exchanged Lines
In order not to miss any important gossip
Morita is firmly stuck in place
And so five minutes passed
He wants to see what they look like
It's the 4th floor.
-Okay, I'll be right there
The other party is waiting. Please come down quickly
Okay, okay
Hurry up
Then
Not sure if this is the kind of thing I should say
-Out with it!
Famous then?
-Probably...
Ah, he's picked up his bag
Actually, there's one more person
Actually, there's another comedian
-Wait a minute
A bit scary...
I'm super curious
Who? Tell me one
I'm so jealous
He put his bag down
Because now there are two "suspects"
Hey, hey!
What are you doing? What are you doing?
A little bit...
In the table over
I'll send you a Line
He's sending a message
It's from Morita
Please wait a little longer. I'm receiving gossip now
A tone like it's part of the job
Stupid, hurry up and come to the meeting!
Saying that you are receiving gossip is not something you should say
He thinks its work
-That's his job, in Morita's opinion
Didn't you just say there was another person?
-Who is it?
Actually, it's that person's partner
-Really?
Wait, you slept with both of them?
-Yes
An unexpected "combo meal" of information
Morita can't leave without it
And
A microphone is their avatar
If you look at it, you will know, right?
Can you guess the name?
What type are they?
What type?
A Kansai vibe
Their look is really Kansai.
-Oh, Kansai faces?
Kansai face?
He's thinking
With the sudden appearance of a riddle
Morita racks his brain
Wait, just now...
-What's wrong? Did he send you a message?
Excited? Which one is it? The first or the second?
He said a live broadcast will be over soon and asked if we could meet afterwards
Big clue, live broadcast
Which one is it?
This one
Thinking carefully
Programs are spinning in his head
Wait, the other one also sent a message
Eh, so exciting, so interesting
Good performance
How about meeting after the live broadcast?
Do both of them want to meet alone?
They want to meet afterwards. It should be a one-on-one
Stuck in place for 16 minutes
At this point
Which one?
Which one do you like more?
It's really time to go
Which one?
If I have to say...
The one who plays dumb
Which one's that?
The one who says stuipid stuff
He's shaking his leg
In a hurry
Waiting for the name still, he reaches the peak of his impatience
Said nothing
Too good to not listen
Then I'll give you a hint
The combo name has "ma" in it
Who comes to mind?
Hearing this
Usually a name would come to mind
"Ma"... who is it?
Ma mi mu me mo?
Is it only "ma" or is it "ma mi mu me mo"?
Sorry, thanks for your hard work
Eh, who is this?
You were talking about comedians, right?
-Yes
I've been listening
Is it Mitorizu?
Mitorizu
Why do they come to mind?
I can't say
-I don't mean anything by it, just wondering
I was just listening, sorry
Is it Mitorizu?
-I can't really say
Can't say
So the truth is revealed
If you do not hurry to the meeting
What are you doing?
Wait a minute. What's going on?
-People are waiting
What's going on here?
Hurry up and go to the 4th floor!
-I'm going there now. I'm going there
What's going on here?
The meeting is about to start
You're being rushed but you won't rush over
Why don't you leave?
No, I'm going to go, although, but I love gossip
It's more like...
When work is being done
-Yes
This is also work
When all is said and done
It's work, too. That's how it is
Its as important
In terms of the weight of the work
-What is the weight?
If you look at the content of the conversation, this side obviously carries more weight
Therefore, the first place winner is Morita
The power of gossip is indeed great
So that's how it is
What do you think?
Morita is a master of gossip
Really, when you meet me in the hallway, if you say, "Tell me something."
Gossip comes up straight away
It's true
Very impressive
I feel more trustworthy now after watching this
Is it really like this?
Aside from the promise of a name
The type of gossip is important for the setup
Doesn't matter if its implausible
I think it's perfectly fine to use an actual name, right?
True
Just censor the name or something
After all, it is not true
Indeed
For example, "Hamada cheated with such and such"
I think it's okay to say
Yes, it's okay
That's a bad example
But I think it's okay to say a name
We have also finished filming a second edition
The wives of comedians having affairs
Look forward to it!
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03