Timers: IngloriousBee, ShiratoHaki, Besseyy, Spectral-K, Phantom Translators: Zebestt, SugaDuck
WDT Project
It's Wednesday Downtown! Hello everyone!
Okay let's meet our first presenter, come on out!
It's Viking's Kotoge!
Who the hell are you?!
I'm Kotoge damnit!
No no no, that was the worst one ever
You've done many weird things alot of times but...
...this was it.
Okay everyone, this show's popular corner...
...the "there's someone" series, you might remember.
For example, "There's someone when you open"...
...is the scariest thing that could happen after all.
"There's someone in the backseat" is the scariest thing that could happen
"There's someone when you wake up" is the scariest thing that could happen
There can't be any left though?
About that...
...always hearing "no more, no more left" but there were!
Really?
Here is the one that I've brought this time
Theory : "There's someone in the bed" is the scariest thing that could happen
That gotta be scary!
That is...
That's definitely scary
All in all, this is the stuff that Hamada-san loves!
This is a bit that we do just to see Hamada-san laugh his ass off.
Because he loves others' misfortunes, doesn't he?
After this, we'll watch the "There's someone in the bed" prank loved by Hamada
Also...
The theory that if one member of a trio leaves and you're left with the dummy...
...you can't go on, with Jungle Pocket.
And then...
We'll also search for the "bean tanks" of Japan, who are smaller than 150cm and fatter than 100 kgs.
Theory : "There's someone in the bed" is the scariest thing that could happen
Our first target is...
...Panzer's Ogata
This time, with help from his wife...
...we're testing the theory whilst he's alone in the house
And we've hidden an unknown gentleman inside his bed
That's scary
Standby is OK
That guy's scary as hell
Ogata who returns home, suddenly...
Ahh what the..!?
THIS IS BULL...
This is fun!
Ahh what the..!?
THIS IS BULL...
He flew out of the room out of fear
This is fun!
He even ran all the way out outside of his house
Excuse us..
He went outside!
So he went all the way out
Wai- Hold on
Scary~
This isn't some kind of assault?
It's fine?
He ran outside barefooted into the snow out of fear
He couldn't understand anything
Not to have the neighbours worry too much, we head inside.
Wah this is funny
That's scary as hell man!
That guy's act.. he can stop now, its enough!
Say something like "Heyoo"
He's really keeping it straight
Ogata-san, I think you've had alot of pranks pulled on you but...
...ranking those pranks by scariness what rank would this one be?
Of course it's number 1!!
It's number 1, it made me jump and run away
As foreseen, this was clearly the scariest of them all
Our next target is...
Amakou Inter's Seiko
Oh god! Oh damn!
She starts to change her clothes, unknowing of the weird man hiding in her house
And then on to the bed...
Nobody wants to see that anyways
She got completely paralysed!!
She got paralysed altogether
Of course that'll happen
Haha she's completely frozen
I can't, this is too much...
Wha-
What?
How was it?
What the hell is this?
What is this??
She can't even stand up
She went like this
My head hurts man
What show do you think this is?
What show?
Yes a show
A show? There are shows like this?
It's Wednesday Downtown
There aren't. you're right
Exactly
Downtown?!
Downtown...
How would you rank this prank by scariness?
It's no.1 of course!
What the hell...
There aren't no damn pranks like this
I hate you Downtown...
Just go somewhere quickly!
That's my beloved bed ya know
I haven't got any men over yet either
Why the hell are you the first man to sleep in my bed?!
Of course, it seems to be the scariest prank ever pulled on her
It's as funny every time
Yeah really
And, our next target
There he is!
Matenrou's Anthony
Shooting in his house is not allowed by his agency...
...so we have called him for a fake show and made him enter this hotel room
By the way, the hotel's futon is thin and a person in it would easily be seen...
...we will do the prank burying the man inside the bed itself
The man who has been part of all the "There's someone" series...
...has confirmed all theories "presented" to him...
...as "scariest ever"...
...what will happen...
That (hiding) guy's perseverance is amazing as well
Anthony, who felt something was off about the bed...
WAHH! WHAT THE-
UWOOAH!
Why the hell did you come back?
WAHH! WHAT THE-
UWOOAH!
Why the hell are you going back?
He checked one last time
What are you confirming?
How was it?
There's no "How was it?"...
Do you understand what's going on?
Wednesday Downtown
Wha- what's this bed?
It's special made
By the way, considering all of the "there's someone" pranks...
...how scary was it?
I'm telling you...
I can't put them in ranking
Since "Mr. There's someone" can't put them in ranking, that means...
...next we have this man
Jungle Pocket's Saito
Before, he got the "There's someone when you open it"...
This is probably the scariest
...said Saito, however...
...will this surpass that?
He checked in to a hotel before a film shooting
After just a minute in after the entrance
...the following happened
Ooh...
What? that's quick
Wah...
Oh the pillow...
How was it?
Do you understand what's going on?
Is it the same thing with that time? With the curtain?
Yes, the "There's someone when you open it" prank
Was it scarier than the previous one?
So scary...
SO scary
This is no good...
Compared to "Someone being there when you open",
"Someone being in your bed" is way scarier
And thus, it was verified to be the #1 scariest scenario
Theory confirmed
Lastly, we test the theory with that guy, just in case
Him again, huh
After outside sources telling us that the house was empty, we start to set up the room
They can enter so freely!
However, since Kuro-chan carries out most of his activities on the bed, we couldn't hide the guy in his room
Just for this time, we made a makeshift mattress with a hole cut out -- reverse massage table style
Meanwhile, Kuro-chan has finished work, and is headed to dinner by himself
"I'm so hungry, it's dinner time!
Mackerel and negitoro bomb! (minced tuna bowl)
Substitute rice with negitoro bomb!
Healthy Dynamite!!"
He's so lying
As always, Kuro-chan appeals his healthy meal. However..
After his appearance on another TV show, Meii no THE Taikoban!*
*Meii no THE Taikoban! Is a Japanese medical variety TV show about celebrities' concerning health issues
"Kuro-chan's blood sugar level is:
Immediate hospitalization-level (of seriousness)
You're in a situation where losing consciousness and passing away is only a matter of time
His blood work results were serious enough for him to be hospitalized immediately
Currently, he is consuming things that consist of low sugar content
Or he was supposed to be. However..
See? I told you
He was actually eating rice, miso soup, quail eggs, and butter-fried enoki mushrooms with his meal
"Within the past 2 weeks, I've drastically changed my eating habits and health awareness.
So, I pulled a fortune slip and got 'Great Blessing'!
I can really tell that God is watching over me.
I'm gonna do my best!"
Yes indeed.. "God" is watching
We have taken upon God and the doctor's role, and punished this liar
Eh, eh what?
Eh, what....
Eh, I don't understand
Eh, who are you?
Since abnormal things happening in his own house has become a normal occurrence, (from this show)
his reaction is a little weak
In that regard,
We overdid it
Eh.. what?
Eh, what the heck happened to my bed?
Putting the bed situation aside, we move on to the diet case
Recently on Taikoban, you got a harsh lecture from the doctor right?
Yeah on Monday
Meii no THE Taikoban is airing every Monday. However,
ever since his last appearance, even the doctors from the show
have been following Kuro-chan's lifestyle habits on Twitter
It seems like you had a very healthy meal today
You didn't eat rice today?
Today.. I haven't eaten rice, yes.
You're not lying, right?
No, I'm not lying
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure
I see...........
Quail eggs..
Rice and miso soup.....
Mackerel..........
Butter-fried enoki mushrooms...............
You haven't eaten those, right?
If it was my misunderstanding, then I apologize
There was a detective again?
Last time we aired, after the show when the cameras weren't rolling
you're really in a dangerous position
It's so bad it's something that shouldn't be managed by you alone
All the doctors (on this show) met up to talk to you
and even then, our words did not go through you
I was extremely shocked
You're not lying, right?
You're keeping your physical health in mind, right?
Wait..hold on a minute
You're lying, right?
Wait, hold on hold on hold on
If you're lying, we're going to report to the doctor
No, you can't do thatー
They're so naggy
No seriously
I don't know what kind of specialist they are, but they're so naggy
Our words did not go through you
I was extremely shocked
There's that woman who fake cries too
In conclusion, he should just die
Upon further investigations, we concluded that he should just die
That's what we came to, huh
I guess so
Seiko's bit was crazy!
She was like
Amazing how people can move like that
She pulled her back and fell
She legit pulled her back and couldn't move
You really can't stand up when that happens, huh
That made my head hurt..
from laughing so much
Fujii-san what did you think?
What's scary is that Hamada-san was like, "Those sheets are in the way"
Like an evil mastermind plotting was so scary
He doesn't plan on stopping
His evil thoughts just come out subconsciously
to promote fear even more
Introducing our next presenter, come on out!
It's Kosaka Daimaou
A pretty rare appearance
Yes indeed
This is my first appearance and I'm shaking like a new-born deer
What the heck
This is sudden but,
I was originally doing comedy in a trio
I think many people don't know this
Yeah, I didn't know you were in a trio
This time, I wanted to bring up something that relates to us trio comedians
this theory is what I brought
Trio comedians: If one person leaves and one is useless, the duo won't last
Hmm.. I don't have experience with a trio so..
Right, indeed
Usually in a trio, one or two are useless
How was it for you guys? Did you guys all decide to break up?
It was actually one by one, like Satomi Hakkenden*
*Nanso Satomi Hakkenden was a literary novel from the Edo period about 8 samurais that descended from dogs
Like 2 people remaining?
Oh I see
One by one
Kind of like that, yes
Who are you going to use to verify this theory?
I have a team that is perfect for this theory
Seriously?
Here they are
Jungle Pocket
Otake....It's gonna be Otake
I mean this theory is basically made for Jungle Pocket
If Saito-san were to leave,
Oota and Otake would remain
If Otake can last with Oota
Is what we're trying to prove, yes
I was expecting us to ponder a little more on who's the "useless" one
Everyone was quickly set on who is was so it shocked me
Theory: Trio comedians - If one person leaves and one is useless, the duo won't last
First and foremost, we begin by explaining our investigation to the two as facilitators
Oh Otake is gonna be the facilitator
'We're going to set up the prank as "Saito-san leaving the group to become a pin-genin"*
*Pin-genin is an comedian that goes solo
In the scenario, Oota-san would have to go on with Otake-san
In this case, when Saito leaves Jungle Pocket,
What kind of role is Otake supposed to play?
we investigate to see if Oota can continue as a duo with the "useless" Otake
This time he's the facilitator right?
To be completely honest, continuing the duo with Otake-san
is pretty rough
Uh..well..
He said it so clearly
Is it me or am I being a little disrespected here?
Uh, well well..
If you ask if it's rough or not...then I guess it is rough, realistically
An uncommon prank setting where the facilitator gets his feelings hurt...
Well actually, there are a lot of times where they're on their own when I'm working alone
Like during live events
There are times where we work just the two of us
Oota did say that it was pretty rough when it's just the two of them
He said "Yeah it's pretty rough when it's us two"
I've never heard that from Otake but
Oota said it was pretty rough
That's the first time I heard that...
I've never heard that before...
As expected
When something like that were to actually happen,
do you think Oota-san would continue to work with you?
Well how should I know
I don't know. I guess we'll have to see
I think there's a 50/50 chance
I seriously have no idea what he would choose
50/50 huh ....
Well well well well..... 50/50 huh
Speak with other people that have experienced group break-ups
Talk about actor aspirations during public interviews
Saito's pin-genin wishes are revealed by other senior comedians
Announce break-up
In order for this prank to be realistic and efficient,
Before the break up of the trio is announced, Saito's pin-genin wishes are going to be flaunted as shown:
First, the trio break-up senior comedian -
Taketo from B Course
will start talking to Saito despite being unacquainted with him
talking about break-ups in a sincere, intimate manner
to purposely raise suspicion about Saito leaving the group
Good morning
You had a live recording today?
Yeah, Hiruneta
Oh, Hiruneta
Did we have a meeting?
Yeah, I wanted to meet a little
Oh, thank you very much for the meal last time
Oh no worries at all
Sorry, I'll catch you later
If you want to discuss things again, let me know
Yes, understood
Saito, can I see you real quick?
Yes
Thank you for your hard work
I would wonder what happened
Did he go ask for advice about something?
Who?
Well, uhh, a-a-a-advice...
Not used to being a facilitator,
the "useless" genin hardcore stutters
He said, "If you want to discuss something again"
To Saito?
Yeah
Advice?
Advice..I don't think he would
Oota starts to question what happened
Then..
Next step: During a fake magazine interview,
Saito talks about aspiring to become an actor
and how he can't let go of his passion
Who would be someone you aspire to become?
Who is that person for you?
For me, it'd be Tsutsumi Shinichi*
*Tsutsumi Shinichi is a very well-known actor that has won many awards
Eh, you want to be an actor?
Well I originally came into this industry to become an actor
As an actor...
My desire to want to progress alone is pretty strong, yes
Well, I suppose
What you want to be and reality is a different story
Third step:
A senior that is close to both Oota and Saito -
Matsuoka from Chocolate Planet
will reveal that Saito's wishes are leaning towards
wanting to be a pin-genin
Hmm, I see
I was drinking with Shinji (Saito) last time
Oh really
He seemed really depressed
He was like,
"If I decided to go on my own, what would you think?"
You mean, like a pin-genin?
Something like that. So I said "what do you mean?"
He was like "If I'm alone, then I can see it" (his future)
"What do you mean, you can see it?" I asked
What is that supposed to mean
What does that mean?
I don't know, but he was really pushing the subject
I was like, really? That sudden?
I mean he's been in a lot of movies and dramas lately
Well he makes it seem like he really wants to do that kind of stuff
The acting stuff right?
Lately, yeah
He was talking about some musical
The Little Mermaid
Nope, he didn't make the cut
If he were to be in that,
he would've been working with them for a year
They would be on tour for a year
Yeah, going around the world for a year or something
He's trying to do something by himself
That's disturbing...
With 3 of these suspicious role-play
Oota begins to take notice
of Saito's sudden odd behavior
At last, the main event:
Announcing the trio's break-up
The set-up (acting) is pretty good
Will Oota decide to continue to be a due with "useless" Otake?
This day, Oota was instructed by his manager to meet at Yoshimoto's head office
We have something that needs to be discussed
Saito-san, if you would explain to the 2 of them
It's something that should be discussed in our presence
Eh?
Uhm..
I've been thinking about this for a while
Well, to be frank,
I would like to break-up,
and for myself to go on as a solo
Eh, what do you mean? Then, eh...
Well..
I came to Tokyo because
I wanted to be an actor
I was fortunate to be able to be in dramas and movies
And of course on top of that,
being able to succeed in the Owarai industry
was because of you two
Eh, you mean you're going to be an actor?
I want to continue to work hard as an actor
I think for myself to continue being a pin-genin
is extremely disrespectful to you two
You're serious....
I mean you're already in a bunch of movies and dramas
That's something you can still do while being a comedian
I have a strong desire to work
alone as an actor, not a comedian
That's what I want to do
I'm so sorry. I'm terribly sorry
Dude, that's so tough...
Everything is so sudden
What the hell
Otake you don't need to add in unnecessary commentary
Being thrown into this situation, Oota can't hide his shocked expression
20 minutes after, as the conversation comes to a halt,
Because I want to pursue this seriously,
I want my focus to be solely on this
So, that means you've completely made up your mind on this
I thought it'd be disrespectful to you two
to bring this up while I was still being indecisive
I only wanted to tell you when my mind was set
To put it in another way,
He thought "If I don't put enough thought into this,
then it would be extremely disrespectful for them"
Yeah, I know that. He just said that himself
Yes.. so that's what he means
He already said that!
An unexplained, unnecessary follow-up
Now, we asked Saito to leave the room for brief moment
to pick their brains even more
Do you think they believe this whole thing?
Yes
I think they completely understand that my decisions are pretty solid
What do you think about Otake-san? As a fellow facilitator?
Otake is really a burden
He is so bad at acting
This...
This really is a sudden turning point
Rough.....
So...
So what's going to happen to us then?
From a business stand point, it's going to be a disadvantage
Business is out of the question
Jungle Pocket as an item will no longer exist
That would be correct
Why?
WHY!?
Should we tell him? (Otake to leave)
Yeah we should really tell him soon
What the hell is he saying this whole time?!
Nothing but a burden facilitator #2
was forced to leave the room
Hurry up and get over here!
What the hell are you saying man?!
You've been saying irrelevant crap this whole time!
He's been saying he wanted to be an actor for a long time...
We don't have the right to be an obstacle in his life
He's that kind of person
Oota's manliness and courage moves Saito
Although unwillingly,
Oota agrees to grant Saito's wishes of breaking up
That being said, now we tackle the real question
Indeed
This is really emotional
Will he be willing to continue to work with the "useless"?
We're going to move on with the process as a break-up
and you and Otake-san would continue to work as a duo
Is what we were thinking
You mean continue together with Otake?
He's already laughing at the idea
Oota is laughing!
I don't know.... would people even want to see that?
"Is there even a demand for that?" is too harsh!
That's too much
Tsk, uh...
He just clicked his tongue!
Duo....with Otake...
What the hell? Are you kidding?
Seriously!
Me and Otake?!
Is that even possible?
Yeah yeah, it's possible
It's not that I don't like Otake.. it's just..
Otake.. mmm...it's..
It's not that I don't like Ota...ke..
What is concerning him?
It seems like he doesn't like Otake
*Reminder: Pin-genin is a solo comedian
Pin-genin....*
Pin?!
Maybe pin...
Even if I become a pin-genin, there won't be a lot of job offers
That was close
Ughhhh this is so rough
Too rough.....too rough..
For now, your decision to form a duo or not
...is kind of important so I wanted to ask it.
Going pin huh...
Isn't he saying he's going pin?
Is he getting closer to going pin?
But you know...
12 years ago, the three that formed a trio at NSC*
*NSC is a comedy school
They got their break thanks to Saito's personality
With their ace gone, can Ota go on to form a duo with Otake?
In all honesty I believe in him
In the end...
...what will his decision be?
Will Ota decide to go on as a duo with Otake?
Well I mean, I kind of...
Well I mean, I kind of have to do my best with Otake
That means he'll do it right, he definitely just said it.
On second thought...
Don't say it's impossible man
But it'd be impossible to do it alone too...
So that means that you'll be doing it together if I understand correctly.
Yeah with Otake
With Otake...
You don't sound enthusiastic about it...
Can something be done with Otake? With me and him?
This does definitely not feel good
Of course you don't
Uhm I mean...
If that doesn't work out...
...We don't have to go on forever right?
Why the hell, he is already thinking of breaking up?
Again he doesn't sound excited, what's wrong with him?
I mean there's nothing to do but do my best with Otake
He said it
Okay then, this means we're moving forward with you and Otake as a duo
Yes
As a duo right? Yes?
Alright!
Thank god...
After nearly worrying himself to death...
Ota has decided to form a duo with the useless Otake
That means
They're revealing the prank
Oh Ota~~
Goddamn man...
You really got worried didn't you?
You really were thinking about it, Ota
Wait, hold up. Is being in a duo with me that unappealing?
You were really worried, sorry man
No no no no no
This is freaking bullshit
Ugh this is so strange
That really pisses me off
No no, I'm telling you you're acting weird-
I'm sorry but I'm the one that's gotten hurt the most from this situation
You're not the one that got hurt
NO ONE GIVES A SHIT ABOUT YOU
Am I not the one getting attacked all the time?
What is this?
There's an agenda isn't there. What is it?
This is for Wednesday Downtown...
This was to test the theory that if you take one out of a trio and leave the person with the useless member
they won't go on to form a duo
Can we say that you will go on?
Man...that's one weird theory
I'm sorry, but I still haven't agreed to that theory
Like "Can he come together with the junk guy?"
Are you really gonna shine light on that real of a part of human nature?
But I mean, if you think about widening the possibilities from now on...
...we have to think about leaving Otake behind as well.
That means, even if it is with a useless person, you form a duo for a bit
He REALLY thought about it
However, it came to continuing together. What do you think about it Nicole?
I kind of got teary eyed at his agony
Thank god there's Saito-san with them
It's good that they're a trio like that
Now let's have them come out please!
Oh they're here
It's Ota and Otake!
That's a preschooler kind of mistake
Hold up, you can't even turn and come out here?
Sorry, I didn't know how it was setup
I didn't know how the footing was set
The step yes, I'm sorry
Ota really went like uhhngh
The real worry was that Saito was going away
It's real though, even today...
....Saito isn't here right...
He's at the Budokan*
*Budokan is a big concert hall
...he's gone because of some musical related work he's doing
In that situation when he tells you he wants to become an actor alone...
...isn't it super real?
There was alot of pre setup
Lots of setup
Otake your feelings must've been really weird right?
This segment was really hard on me...
...I'm kind of an accomplice to it but...
...I'm not really fully an accomplice either
It gave me alot of bad info about what Ota thinks of me
Don't talk for so long, I'll end up laughing
Don't talk for too long, it's enough
If he goes on too long, you'll laugh
Please hear me out a bit though
Let's do a prank where Otake has to leave the trio
That won't happen probably
We've been a trio for about 12 years and 4 times we've thought about kicking him out...
Next we have the corner where we bring you theories from around the world
Viewers' Theory Corner
Tonight's presenters are...
It's Daian
We'll be in your care
It's been about half a year
Your second time right?
Yes it's our second time
Eeh~ I thought it was your first
Didn't we have any impact on you?
Twins?
We would've stated it more if it were the case
We've been told that we look alike but have no blood relation.
Let's move along then, the theory that we've brought you today is this!
Theory: We can find Mame Tanks with a height under 150cm and weight over 100kg...*
*Mame tank refers to disproportionate body types with overweight body, and short height
...if we were to look for them.
Mame Tank huh? That's a word I haven't heard in a while...
I think that you can find them...
...while going around the city
Osaka has an image of having these types of people
That means that there are alot of them in Osaka right?
If you go to some downtown shopping street most of the people there are like that
No way
So that means the theory is proven
We don't need it, they're not even rare then
There actually weren't that many
Pick one for god's sake!
In reality there weren't many of them
It feels like..
It feels like they are but actually aren't
We're testing the theory that we can find Mame Tanks with a height under 150cm and weight over 100kg if we go out to look for them
With that, let's start our investigation
Immediately
We're with a program called Wednesday Downtown
Yes yes yes yes yes
Do you have some time?
Oh it's ok yeah
Can we shoot your face?
Nobody is looking for me so it's fine
Just behind there
Yeees yes yes yes
He accepted the interview with a high-pitched voice but...
We weren't allowed to put out numbers concerning his weight and height
Also...
Could you please share you weight?
Oh no- It's kinda difficult
No waay- that's impossible
Maybe it's because of a complex about their physique
We're not finding anyone who would let us show their face, let alone share their measurements
That means
Stopping the search in the streets, we go to the net to find them
We try to get our hands on anyone who might be like that..
The first one, working at a maid cafe called "MuchiPocha"
Hanashiro Kokoa with a height of 157cm and a weight of 120kg
She wasn't under 150cm but she was a complete Mame Tank, when we talk to her...
About when did you start putting on weight?
I was only about 47kg in high school but...
...after my graduation, I stopped doing sports and in the blink of an eye I became three times my old weight
Next we have Ihashi Gouta from DDT Pro Wrestling
He has a special body with 158cm in height and 136kg in weight, however...
Isn't this physique a disadvantage for pro wrestling?
Uhm, of course being tall is better but...
...doing a Moon salto and other similar flip-style moves is easier
There are things that I can only do because I'm small
And there's this person working at this bar
Named "Japan Worldwide Debusu Club"
Looks like a nice place
Height 163 cm, weight 120 kg
Louis Vuitton
Even just walking around
I'll receive a whole large pizza
A random person gives it to you?
Yes, a complete stranger
They just give me items that they have on them
Additionally,
With gaining that much weight
does it affect your health in any way?
When I get my physical exam, my blood glucose level is normal
A physician once performed an exam on me, and said I'm a miracle
Did you ever get a nickname?
To this day,
I've been called "Mame Tank" or "Fatty than can move"
We found someone that was nicknamed "Mame Tank"
However, didn't fit the criteria of being under 150 cm, and over 100 kg
We struggle to find the person that fits the mame tank appearance
However, in that bunch
Would you mind telling us your height and weight?
Right now, I'm at 148 cm, 110 kg
There she is; mame tank
However, her weight used to be
90kg about a month ago
She says she quickly gained 10 kg within that month
How did you gain so much weight in a span of one month?
Because of rice
Ever since I've been eating 3 cups per meal, I eat at least 10 cups per day
My height is 150 cm
Weight is probably 115 kg or more
Having her 3-size (bust, waist, hip) all be 140 cm,
she'll be categorized as the cylindrical body type
Height 145 cm, weight 101 kg,
she's the super tiny mame tank
This is.....
As suspected, the mame tank body type that fits
our criteria exists here and there
Further more, we found someone that wasn't under 150 cm,
but had the highest BMI index
During this investigation, we found an extreme mame tank
This is that person
She's injured
She looks really injured
Osaka's chubby Cabaret King
Takenokonosato-body type
Kitty-san
Her weight is...
How many kg?
With the same exact height as Watanabe Naomi
But weights 60 kg more
An extreme body
What happened to your wrist?
I fell from the stairs in the store
And I went to the hospital,
and tried to get an MRI
but was told that my body is too big
That means you didn't fit inside?
I couldn't fit in the machine so it wouldn't move
because of my weight
On top of that, was unable to fit in a wheelchair
and unable to use crutches as support
She really worries the doctors -- even more than Kuro-chan
I was stopped like this
and was like "this is going to be a little difficult.."
With that said,
People with mame tank bodies, please be careful of your physical health
What did you guys think?
Surprisingly,
there were a few (mame tanks to be found)
Yeah........
Check out our Facebook and Website for more Wednesday Downtown! This video was subbed by a community run project called the Wednesday Downtown project. Thanks for watching!
Up next week: Theory - Buy 10,000 Yen worth of items to keep you warm
and compete in an endurance game in -15° C weather
Then, Top animal playground equipment ranking
And, Theory: In a "You're the one who's going to sing?!" situation, would you be able to tsukkomi?
Theory verification involving Hamada as well!