Timers: Besseyy, ShiratoHaki, Phantom Translators: Hikarii, Otviss, Magichalo, SugaDuck
WDT Project
Welcome to Wednesday Downtown everybody!
Okay, here is our first presenter, please!
Daikichi Hakata
Hello everybody!
I'd like to start by saying congratulations for today
An extremely good project was completed
Really?
The neck of this program has support from children
which is why it's been good
We're not really receiving support from children right?
Well then, where do you think it is?
There isn't any really
Well there should be a Junior Corner
where a small mixture of laughs are happening
That'd be hard
This time we'll be focusing on Elementary school students
We've been wanting that
Well let me ask you, have you every done a ding-dong ditch when you were small?
Ah, I've never done it before honestly
There wouldn't be many people who have
Well you say no, but how about if you pressed the doorbell on your friend's house and ran
You've definitely had those experiences, correct?
This program will be looking at ding-dong ditchers
but with an addition of mixed rules included
Mixed?
Here it is!
On the run from a Ding-Dong Ditch
This looks good for kids
The idea of an escape game was something
we thought of borrowing from a popular program
Just like that?
Could you do something properly yourself?
This was really aimed for children however
The neighbors will become Hunters and have 5 rules to them
The homes will have a doorbell
So the people inside the houses
They can't run away right?
As to whether there is someone there or not
There's a lot of game rules for that
So that's how it is
Coming up, will they be able to escape from the neighbor hunter?
The escape from Ding-Ding Ditch
Also..
The London Boots 1&2 as a duo name is lame, isn't it?
We'll look into the theory of the
lamest duo names, London Boots 1&2
Determined by the rankings of lame duo as chosen by young comedians
And then, Sachiko Kobayashi
will become Karashi Kobayashi, and we'll see if people will notice
in this installment of easily mistakable misread characters investigation
The escape from Ding-Ding Ditch
This time, the stage is a 3-story
99 room student dormitory
Amazing
all occupied by university students
All students
The occupants whose rooms are rung up will become the Hunter
who will chase down the Challenger
That's tough
On this day, about half of the residents were home, and the other half absent
This means that half of the rooms that will be rung
will not produce a Hunter
If you manage to escape the Hunters
If you are able to ring the doors of all 99 rooms
Would this even be possible?
you have surpassed the challenge
And now, the challengers
Ah, these people look right for it
who are confident they can run and escape
are these 5 people
In this escape, the plan was to go wait and hide
until the coast is clear
But eventually the number of people will increase right?
Exactly
Do you want to have a look inside?
I want to try and see
This challenge will be done individually, one by one
Everyone will get a preview of the architecture of the building
so that they can formulate a strategy
There's not a lot of blind spots, is there?
There isn't, right?
Once the hunters get their eyes on us, they'll have a habit of chasing after us, correct?
It'd be wrong to aim for the fences
You'll definitely be seen
Hey, this straight alley is really good, ain't it?
This alleyway
You'll be able to get a lot of bell rings here
Not sure if it is good
I'm counting on you to go first
I'll do it
Who..
How long does it take you to cover 100m?
Currently, it's about 10.6 seconds
Eh, this person?
That's so fast!
Appearing in a fake program
The former athlete and model
Moses Yume, from Amagasaki
For this fastest comedian
Oh, he's from Amagasaki?
who's undertaking the challenge in this building
There are few hiding spots, and room after room could be a trap
Our first challenger will be Sanshiro's Komiya
What's your plan?
My plan is to do the alleyway on the ground floor first
and do the sides straight after
Komiya will attempt to do the straight line section on the ground floor
Will his plan work out, or will it be a struggle for him?
This is so scary, but I have to go for it
This is impossible
I'll start from the end here
That's why you really should stop blundering
Yeah
So scary!
Ah I'm so terrified
It's too scary
Is doing that okay?
This might be good!
Wait, what's this now?
Oh no!
Ah that's impossible!
So fast! That one person was too fast
Isn't the hunter too fast?
Komiya, who had gone for the straight path on the ground floor
had quickly ran into a fast running hunter
There was no way
The first round recorded 7 rooms rung
Sorry, sorry, so sorry
That hunter in room 104 or something is unnaturally fast
He was fast
Is he the fastest out of the residents?
But they're just students
When I looked behind me, my eyes went bloodshot
Ordinary people will be able to tell from the TV
Hey, you didn't even bring back any data for us
We can't use that
That why, I'm sorry
The next challenger is someone who has an established reputation in running, Non Style's Yusuke
He must be fast
Hey now
Awesome
Is that what he gets called?
I will, just from observing Komiya's run
do things a little differently
I'll head up to the second floor to press the button, then fall back to the first floor
then press a button on the first floor, and head down to the ground floor
If I separate the floors like that, I think that I'll be safe
That sounds great
Doing that method sounds good
So in other words, you're pushing the button and running away?
Stop that, you idiot
Going with the plan to separate the floors, and hiding from the Hunters on separate levels
So brave
This time, will he be able to escape the Hunters this way?
Just this time?
Then it doesn't matter if he gets caught
Ah, he's going for it
Ah, that's great
It's going great
First, he pressed on two of the rooms on the second floor, and quickly came down to the first floor
This might be good, really
He still has more to go
Then, returning to the second floor..
99 rooms, correct?
Oh, that's good
No one's there
He is able to get 2 more rooms
No one's home
No one came out, right?
They must be running away from home
It's amazing that there was no one home
I'm a bit tense that I'll have to run soon
As planned, the effectiveness of operating between floors for Inoue,
now moving onto the ground floor..
This area is dangerous
There's definitely gonna be one here
Ah there's one
Wow, he's fleeing
The hunter is a bit slow, maybe
This is.. eh?
That hunter's going very fast
There's already one on the first floor!
What happened to the one from before?
Shaking the hunter off, he is somehow able to hide underneath the staircase
They'll be looking for him..AH, like that
However, these two Hunters have their sights on Inoue
This is so bad
They're getting around
Ah, he's just walking around easily
He's not running at all
It's impossible
They're there! On the first floor!
The number will increase
Here, Inoue hides again underneath the staircase
However, a Hunter comes down from those stairs where he's hiding
Keep hiding, stay hidden!
This is bad
He must've heard him nearby
No way, no way!
Even with his skill of running and hiding during the Ding-Dong Ditch
he leaves with a record of 6 rooms
The next challenger will be Nana Suzuki
It's scary, really it's so scary
I can't press it, I'm so scared, what do I do?
Nana Suzuki's special skill is "Being filmed the longest"
I'll press it and run
It's there, it's there!
She's more troublesome than the Ding-Dong Ditch
She's a nuisance
Following on..
Yes, yes, keep running
It's fine
Where did she run off to?
After pressing the doorbell just once, and running far away while screaming
This is Nana Suzuki's 'Hit and Away' strategy
What the heck..?
And then, going back up a floor
This one shouldn't come out
That one should be empty
I'm scared.. AHHH!
No, I'm scared
No one came out
There's no one
Good
She's doing good
She's going back?
Staying near the stairs
I'm scared, should I press it?
AHHH!!
Ah, hide. Go hide!
That's scary, very scary
No, no way, get away
Secured
Why did she press it?
It was terrible, I was blocked off there
No more!
Chased away by the hunter
and on her way back, Suzuki Nana gets trapped
lastly, pushing another button
It was terrible, I was blocked off there
And now looking at the three challengers so far
It's still so bad
the aim for highest record is still anyone's game
And now, our next challenger is Shoji Tomoharu
Consolidating all the information from the three unsuccessful attempts
they aim for the homes that are absent of Hunters
The plan to empty out the nest, how will he succeed?
This one is okay, there's no one in there right?
No one
There's no one
He can do it
Just in case, he went away anyways
He's getting startled
The next target is the empty residence at the end of the second floor
Ah this one is safe
Yes, good good
Having the information compiled up to now as a basis
Shoji stacks up points from the absent houses
Yes, relying on this
This one is fine
However, this young man
A hunter had come out from the room he thought was absent
So there was one
However he is able to pass through the hunter to the first floor
And then..
He's good
This one will have one too
So scary, cool
There was one in there, run, run!
She's coming
So there was one there
Geez, what were you doing?
There was one there!
Not noticing the hunter that he was defeated against, he had soon been captured when he turned back around
So there was one there
However his record, now sitting at the top, is 18 rooms
Who captured you, the girl?
The girl
So that must mean that I was, probably here
I can't calm down anymore
Exactly
And lastly, the final challenger, who's gotten the most experience about the hunters, Moses Yume
Ah, so he knows about Hunters
Experience with Hunters
I'll try my best, there's 5 I know for sure I can securely ring
And then, I'll get all the hunters to traffic each other
You'll create some traffic?
Yeah, I'll be trying that
I'll be going at it like a Black Panther
"Going at it like a Black Panther", What kind of situation has him imagining such things?
"In any case, I'll try my best" he says. What will be the result of this?
In any case, I'll try my best
Starting from the corners
They are..
Not home
If they come out, it'd be pretty bad. He's being too light-handed about this
He's being too light-handed
He's confident about his running abilities
This one is not home
This one was tried out previously
Not home
Starting off with the homes he's got a grasp of,
Moses clears 5 homes
It's scary how calm he is
All right, after this I am unsure of
Shall we do this?
From here on, we will see the fastest man in the world of entertainment
The result?
No one's pressed this one yet
They came out
It was a girl, right
It's a girl
That's a dangerous place to be
If he takes a look behind him, they'll be chasing him
If one comes out, it'll be dangerous
He's pressing it
He's coming, danger!
After this, I'm just gonna rack it up
He's being carefree
As expected, he's fast
So fast!
He's quick!
He's going quickly
Is he pressing it? Oh, no way
That's good. he can do it
This area is big
The man who would not lose to anyone in a one-on-one
Moses Yume
Currently, with 19 successful rooms rung
And with merely 4 Hunters released
A big record is expected to appear
Oh no!
However..
This is bad
It's bad, it's bad
You're gonna get caught between them!
Oh no
It's terrible
That's not how I imagined you'd get caught
Just like Nana Suzuki, who was caught up in a dead-end
He finishes with a 22-room lead
This is just impossible
True to the Black Panther, he was quick
But his head was a bit slow to bring around
That's cruel
Don't say such silly things..
With all the data we have on this side
you didn't use it just now?
I only remembered this side
Ha ha, I don't have a brain
What did you even mean when you said "I'll traffic the hunters"?
As expected, with all the might of one person, going for all 99 rooms proved to be impossible
So, while we're here, we'll have the 5 people take on the challenge at once
Shoji, Inoue & Moses will start on different floors
and take on the straight line approach
while the remaining two, Suzuki and Komiya take on each of the other sides
Will the 5 people be able to clear the 99-room challenge?
Get ready..
Start!
I don't know, I'll press anyways
Oh no, no way!
Don't press it, don't press
Gotcha
No one comes out of those rooms
Wow, it's paying off
Ah, he's hit a dead-end
Oh no, oh no!
No way out of it
Ah they came out
There's quite a few there now
Without noticing the Hunters from the other floors, Suzuki Nana is captured where she stands
The only one's left are Moses and Shoji
Run, run!
Ah so bad
Impossible
Caught like this again?
There was no way to escape
Definitely doesn't have brains
Soon after..
In total, you pressed 40 rooms
About half
21 rooms on the second floor,
9 rooms on the first floor,
and 10 rooms on the ground floor
I really wanted you to do more
My blood was burning up, I'm sorry
What even..
But really, what kind of blood do you have?
Carnivores, the blood of carnivorous hunters
Ah, so only running?
Oh, shut up
Ah, so that's how it is
It was a little bit too difficult, right?
It was difficult
Maybe not 99-rooms, but setting about half as you goal
and having the residents that come out from the rooms
be seniors
Exactly
Like, grandpas and grandmas
Our next presenter is..
It's Kotoge from Viking
What's so funny?
I didn't think of anything
Please think of something then!
Start thinking, and we'll get along
So we can enjoy each other, you should give me a welcoming
Are you a soybean?
No I'm not!
Just a one-off thing, sorry
What's with you coughing right after making such jokes?
Sorry
No big deal
Today, I bring you a theory about
the names of comedy duos
Here it is!
Theory: The lamest comedy duo name is "London Boots a-1 a-2"
That's not true! (Note: That's his comedy duo name)
It's true.
That's not true at all.
Consider it for a moment.
A comedy duo called "London Boots a-1 a-2" is lame as hell!
It's tacky!
So dated it's from the Stone Age.
You don't think it sounds cool?
I kind of get a feel for what you mean.
Right?
Even just the "London Boots" part is tacky.
Uncool.
On top of that they have to say it like "And a 1, and a 2"!
London Boots 1 2 has to be the lamest duo name ever!
Shut up already.
You think "Viking" is that much better?
The "VI" part is in katakana and the rest of it is hiragana. Wth?
Ah, yeah, that's lame innit?
So lame!
Look at your own name for lame!
No, no, you're wrong.
He's right.
Yeah, it's true.
There is a meaning to it and before "Viking" WAS all in katakana
but my partner Nishimura said, "'Viking' could also sound like 'bike', isn't that nice?"
So that's why.
So there IS a reason to it, lame as it is.
"London Boots and a 1 and a 2" has NONE.
Everyone is saying so.
Why are you so quick to agree?
My own mother is always saying the same thing.
Are you kidding me?
With that said, does anyone here have a comedy duo name they think is lame?
"King of Comedy"
Oh, King of Comedy! Right.
Why that name?
It's quite lame.
Sorry! It's all I could think of.
That's perfectly fine.
I think the television broadcast wanted to hear that
The lamest comedy duo name is London Boots a-1 a-2
This time we asked 200 young comedians to answer a survey asking for the lamest comedy duo names
This is how the ranking was made
Will London Boots a-1 a-2 really top them all?
First up is #10 on the lamest comedy duo name ranking
ANZEN Manzai
This duo is currently popular thanks to Miyazon's airheaded character
Looking at the surveys from young comedians
"Simply put, 'ANZEN Manzai' is just a lame name"
Manpukufu-fu Matsumara Hormone
Who the hell is that?
"Why would you put 'manzai' in the name of your duo? Uncool."
Shining Stars Hirota
"I've never seen any comedy duo desperate enough to announce they do comedy in their name"
Kagishippo Sachi
Everyone commenting have tacky names themselves!
We went to tell the actual duo the results...
In a survey of "Lamest Comedy Duo Names"
ANZEN Manzai ranked 10th
Why's that?
It's in upper case letters even.
Isn't using two alphabet systems cool?
There isn't another comedy duo that does that.
Why is it bad?
You felt it was cool?
We did think it was cool...
We can't go wrong with English letters and kanji together..
It's kind of like food, I guess?
Why did you guys go with the name "ANZEN Manzai"?
We thought it sounded great at first
The sound that starts from the "N"
Like "Downtown"
We thought having the same pattern would help us sell
Then added Anzen(safe) to "Manzai" like it's a brand.
Since we wanted to be a 50-60 type bet with our manzai
It's a safe bet and good fun
We wanted to give off this kind of feeling.
A wonderful explanation. Coming up in the lame comedy duo ranking in 9th place
Ameagari Kesshitai (Post-suicide rain squad)
The surveys from the young comedians that came in say...
"Since they are popular everyone got used to the name, but it still sucks."
- Mikazuki Manhattan's Nakamine
That's certainly lame.
"I don't understand the meaning and it's difficult to say."
"If one of my juniors had this name I'd encourage them to change it."
- Tokyo Haco Club's Boutique Ayumi
There were people who said it was good the duo is popular, but the name is lame.
And in 8th place?
Ushiro City (Back City)
"Trying too hard to be romantic just makes them sound lame."
- Semi-Retire Itou
"Their choice of expression is lame."
- Crab party's Nakayama
Onto the 7th place in the ranking
Saraba wa seishun no hikari (Gone is the light of youth)
"Higashiguchi used to be my senpai in a university club."
"I remember when the duo picked their name. Everyone in our club's faces turned pale."
- Charming fried rice's Kawahara
Onto the next one. Who is at 6th place?
London boots a-1 a-2
6th place!
6th place, really?
Hey, 6th place is still bad.
And just like that the theory was disproven.
"[And] a-1, a-2 is the lamest thing ever omg."
- Tokkibutsu's Ota
"Who is 1 and who is 2? Asking who's who is lame."
- Tsukurokun
Well, there are cases like that..
It troubles them.
Other information we have regarding this matter are..
"When you come out asking Who is 1 and who is 2? there is no incentive to answer."
Semi-limited Express' Kubota
Next on the "Lame Duo Names Ranking" in 5th place is...
Fruit Punch
Fruit Punch unfortunately ranked 5th
We've done it.
Of course "Fruit Punch"
is a lame name!
Whaat? No way!
We have a written comment
"It sounds like something you tack onto a festival name as an after thought"
The person who wrote this
was Secret Sniper's Mr. Fujiko.
From Secret Sniper..???
Fujiko did??
His portrait looks like a wanted poster.
What is the meaning behind the duo's name?
We thought it was nice how fruit punch can make kids smile.
Like at a birthday party when there's
fruit punch, there's smiles all around.
Do you get what I mean?
In the Lamest Comedy Duo names Ranking, next on 4th place is
Koro koro chiki chiki Peppers
4th place
That's quite high
So what's the origin?
What it means is
We kind of thought that "Red hot chili peppers" were cool...
We thought it was a long but a catchy name.
Now we're being called korochiki but
I kind of like it though.
We kind of disputed over what name to pick.
Nishino won a rock-paper-scissors game with "korokoro chikichiki peppers"
What name did you want us to have again?
"Mitarashi" (Seems to be)
Hella lame!
We have finally reached the top three of "Lamest Comedy Duo Names Ranking", However, before that...
Young performers picked the top 10 Coolest Comedy Duo Names.
Below the top three are as shown.
At 9th place is "Gone is the light of youth" who ranked 7th in the lamest.
We wanted to show them the results.
And when we did..
Oh really?
It's kind of like a "lame but cool" scenario, huh?
This is a new genre for sure.
What is the origin behind your name?
The origin is that
From Peamans' Standard comedy duo,
I get along with with Minamikawa.
When we got together to form our duos,
he said, "I'll make something for you."
"Write down 2 movies you saw yesterday and choose 1."
"Gone is the light of youth" and "For me to take revenge"
Through elimination, we were left with "Gone is the light of youth."
Coming in at #3 on the Coolest Comedy Duo Names Ranking
Tokyo03
#2 was
Chidori
due to the names' simple & smart sound
And so, the #1 comedy duo that young performers voted as having the coolest name
Good morning.
Mornin'.
Yasei Bakudan (Wild Bomb)
In the Coolest Comedy Duo Name Ranking, you guys were #1.
Why's that? No one else was cooler?
Whaat? It's that cool?
"THE PUNCH" seems like a cooler name, I feel like.
"THE PUNCH" sounds hecka cool.
What the heck are you saying, Rosshi..
With that said, how did you guys come up with "Wild Bomb"?
When we were around... 15 years old?
For our school's cultural festival we wanted to do a skit.
We were practicing the skit by Lake Biwa
and an old man we didn't know came to us.
He suddenly pointed,
saying, "Wild Bomb."
So then, when we returned home
I thought, "What a weird guy.."
Then 5 years later I was watching Yoji Desu Yōda
and the guy that was hosting it was Matsumoto Hitoshi-san
So we're like the duo that Matsumoto Hitoshi-san picked
Then about 15 years later we met,
He's lying so much
he was like "Oh you came back home"
"You came back home"
Matsumoto-san said "You came back home"??
This guy really pisses me off
Returning to "Lamest Duo Name Ranking",
At last, we announce the top 3
First, #3 is
Ari to Kirigirisu
A veteran duo that made
a breakthrough on Vocabula Tengoku in the 90s
I don't like that they used "to"
If they used "to" (in hiragana), then it wouldn't have been bad
says Metro Tengu Miyama
Others have also chimed in about the lameness of the "to"
The duo has since ended
and are working successfully as individuals
The "to" that caused a commotion no longer exists
That's an unfavorable way of expressing that
Now, #2 in "Lamest Duo Name Ranking" is
Batsu Gun
The way we have to read the "X" as "batsu" is lame
Says Kaoiro Yoroshi Waroshi Tsuzuki
It's hard to understand at first
The fact that we have to read it as "batsu" is asking too much
Says G-pan Panda Ippei
"Batsu" and "to" put aside,
On to #1 in "Lamest Duo Name Ranking"
Doubling 2nd place's score
Is this duo
Lamest duo name that the younger comedians chose
#1 doubles 2nd place's score
is this duo
Hello, good afternoon
Non Style
Non Style-san, you guys got #1 in "Lamest Duo Name Ranking"
Why??
You guys shone through all the others
I don't think we're #1 in that...
Pretty lame
I guess so, it can't be helped
The reason why they think it's lame
"For having a name that insinuates
not having a style and being open-minded,
the comedy skits are very structured and obstinate"
Said Onion Gorilla's Hosono
Who is that?
The most popular sentiment was
"I don't like how they use English to act cool"
Using English can be pretty lame, yes
Said Dog Rhino Beetle's Adachi
Okay so who is that? He has a weird name
That's actually clever!
What was the name's back story?
I had a band that I really liked at the time
called "Hi-STANDARD"
I really liked them. They were called "HiSta" for short
So I wanted to make it "Something-something- sta"
If it were to be abbreviated
Then, after doing some research
We read that having "N" in the name will be successful
Then let's have something that has a "N" and ends with "-sta"
Then we came up with NON STYLE
Ugh, That's all so lame
Therefore, NON STYLE's name and back story was super lame
Non Style huh...
Now that you mention it...it's pretty lame
By the way, What was going on with "Wild Bomb"?
Those guys seriously need to watch what they say
They kept lying SO much
Who the hell would take a stroll along Biwa Lake?!
What did you think, Ryo-san?
6th place, huh
I was wondering if we were going to be in there somewhere
I just had a feeling somehow
I actually understand Ameagari(Post-suicide rain squad)
Ameagari is terrible
To me, they're #1
They're comedians but have the word "death" in their name!
That's crazy huh
The "Suicide squad" is just so disgusting
Now that you mention it..
And that he has a bowl cut...
Up Next
Gathering theories from around the world
It's "The viewer's Theory Corner"
Tonight's presenters are
Daiyan!
We've come to leave our territorial scratch marks
You guys both have irritating faces
We have good faces
We have good, comedian-like faces
It's rare to see a duo with both mono-lids
No I have double eyelids
Who cares
I have double eyelids
No one cares!
You're the one that brought it up
What do you mean no one cares!
Everyone, last time we had the
"No one would notice if the word "Sagami" got switched to "Sumo" Theory
Takeyama-san was-ah the one-ah that presented that
Why are you talking like a baby?
I'm always like this
That's pretty problematic if you're always like that
Yeah, the usual
Takeyama-san presented this
But I disagree
Takeyama-san, you're wrong. There's more than that
Tonight, we bring you this theory
"No one would notice if Kobayashi Sachiko got replaced with Kobayashi Karashi (Mustard)" Theory
Urg....I don't know
This is it!
This is for sure
This one is more probable
I often write her name wrong like this too
You write it?!
Kobayashi.
Where would you need to write her name down?
Even she herself wouldn't notice
The opposite might happen too. Trying to write mustard, but writes Sachiko instead
I bet that happens
Like when I try to write "Ou Yang Fei Fei" but write "Ou Yang Nira Nira" instead*
*Ou Yang Fei Fei is a Japanese Taiwanese Singer
That doesn't happen
Now, let's see the VTR
VTR..
Now, let's take a look at the VTR
VTR GO GO !
Theory: No one would notice if Kobayashi Sachiko got replaced with Kobayashi Karashi (Mustard)
With that said, this time
Kobayashi Sachiko team has fully cooperated with us
Seriously?
Helping us change concert programs and posters
from Kobayashi Sachiko, to Kobayashi Mustard
Oh, I see
Would the customers notice?
Wow they really helped us
That's an actual poster
Ehh but this is...
Senior citizens start to arrive minutes before the concert
But these people are all fans!
However..
It IS her name
Is this for real?
They probably only look at her face
They don't show any signs of noticing
And among those fans,
So low, low!!
there are some that don't even see the poster entirely
Completely out of their peripherals
This is really bad ya know
So now, we try
directly asking the fans
Are you a fan?
Yes, I'm a fan
A fan of whom?
Kobayashi Sachiko-san of course!
There's a poster behind you
Nice, isn't it?
See, she's only looking at the face
Sacchan is so nice
Is there something odd about this poster?
Weird? No there's nothing weird about it. It's amazing
I've been watching her ever since I was little
Even for someone that's been a fan since her younger years,
she doesn't notice the "Karashi"
We continue to investigate
Looking at the poster, do you see something off about it?
Nothing odd about it, still the same as before
As she is, beautiful
What do you think about this poster?
It's so amazing, Sacchan. So beautiful
It doesn't say Sacchan!
What do you think about this poster?
It's very nice, I kind of want it
A person who has noticed has not been found yet
Now, we try to give them a big hint
What do you think about the letters?
Letters?
Letters....
Is it like... written with a spray?
Not one person has noticed the "Mustard"(Karashi)
At this point, the theory was quickly confirmed
Ah, that's true
Just in case, we tried the opposite situation
"Karashi Mentaiko"(Roe and mustard) at an onigiri store
was changed to "Sachiko Mentaiko"(Roe and Sachiko) to test the theory
Now this has some awkwardness to it
Yeah, this feels more weird
Would they notice?
Welcome~
Karashi Mentaiko Cheese..
It goes unnoticed
And further,
Karashi Mentaiko Cheese
It's selling so much
The cheese is bringing all the popularity
However, no one notices "Sachiko"
What does this one say?
"Fresh and tasty,
spicy mustard cod roe...
Is what it is, yes
Is this something different?
We figured no one would notice if
"Karashi Mentaiko" got changed to "Sachiko Mentaiko"
Oh you're right!! It's Sachiko Mentaiko!
Did Sachiko-san make this??
This Sachiko has nothing to do with it
And after this,
we validate additional word changes that can go unnoticed
And now,
we test other phrases that can go unnoticed when changed
First up,
No one would notice if "Toilet"
got changed into "Tray"
And when we open the "tray" door, inside
you see a bunch of trays
Are they stupid
Will people really notice?!
It actually says "tray" huh
Completely passes by, and goes into "tray"
And then,
Tray?
She completely read it, but mistook it
Where were you headed?
Tray....
A bunch of trays...it looked like "toilet"
And next,
Trays huh...
As suspected, the level of difficulty of "toilet" to "tray" is extremely high
Tray huh..
The success rate was 100%
Misread Series: Up next is,
"budou" (grape)
turns into "hofuku" (crawl)
"Yamanashi Hofuku" and,
"Seedless Hofuku"
Will there be anyone who notices?
I'll have two of these small grapes over here
It went unnoticed
And further,
Which one did you purchase?
These over here
What are they called?
"seedless grape"
Which ones were you thinking of?
These "grapes"
I was thinking of buying them
"Grapes"?
Yes
This kanji says "budou"
Right? It says "budou" right?
It says "Hofuku"
Ahh so that's what it is
There's the "army crawl"
What does that have to do with grapes?
We were thinking no one would notice
if we changed up the words
That's it?
That's it??
She has a point
She really told us
We just ended up disappointing her
Either way, no one has noticed the "hofuku"
And yet,
2 young men lingers around "hofuku"
we inquire them for further information
We're from Taiwan
Taiwan?
A Taiwanese person who only uses Chinese characters
Surely, would these people notice?
Can you tell us what this says?
Yes, we can
"Budou"
The same
The same kanji
A prank that works even for Chinese people
Now trying the opposite,
would people notice if "Hofuku" turned into "Budou"?
This time,
newbie comedians that were called to simulate Lincoln's annual Sports Tournament
challenges in an obstacle course
And what awaits them at the end is
"Budou Zenshin"*
*Supposed to be "Hofuku Zenshin" which means Army Crawl
The objective is to reach the grapes at the end of the course
in this simple prank
Will they read it as "hofuku" as we suspect?
They wouldn't think anythings going on
Hofuku?
Hofuku? Oh okay okay
Army crawling!
As expected, it was impossible
What was that last thing you guys did?
Army crawl
What did the sign say?
It says "hofuku zenshin"
Eh, what?
Well it actually says "grape crawl"
It's a new activity where a grape is the goal to the obstacle course
We just got super dirty
for like no reason!
The black guy was like "It says grapes"
Black guy...
You should be the #1 person to miss it
Did you notice that?
Yeah it clearly says "grapes"
You should be the one to not notice!
Where are you from?
Uganda
In conclusion, Ugandans are very sharp
What did you guys think
The guys didn't notice huh
It even says in such big letters
Do you have anything else where people might mistake words?
You know the F-Liner Train?
F-Liner, yes
The Fukutoshin Line
That always sounds like "Ukraine" to me
Oh it sounds like it
Yes, it sounds like it
Not, it looks like
We're doing the ones that "looks like"
Sounds like is something different
We wanted something where you can misread it
Well...
It's better than not saying anything
DVD 8th and 9th edition now in stores!
with 29 entries of Viewers' Theories
And in 9th edition, Mr. Osu
And a project that started the Poor Boy series
and including unseen footage
with a remix of the opening song with GEISHA GIRLS and PUNPEE
Comes with a CD of the live recording
and a El Chicken Rice BearBrick application sheet
Check out our Facebook and Website for more Wednesday Downtown! This video was subbed by a community run project called the Wednesday Downtown project. Thanks for watching!
Up next week: The third episode of best anthem singing
high school girls will be judging the most popular songs
And then,
Theory: Even if someone is wearing your belongings, you won't really notice it
We test this theory by bringing many personal items from homes
and also, Theory: Mr. Osu says "osu" even when he's sleep-talking