Alright our next theory is
What the hell is this?
Reverse Prank: If you keep reversing it, you'll become suspicious
What, I don't get it
Reverse prank...
You know what a reverse prank is right?
For example if Kato was pranking Hamada
But Hamada already knows about it
So Hamada becomes super angry
And Kato becomes scared
And the roles are reversed, a reverse prank
After Hamada gets mad, he starts crying
He keeps crying and crying
Hamada's thinks
"Eh? He's seriously crying"
And then it's on Hamada
But Hamada also already knows about this
So this is reverse reverse
Right, and then another reverse
And Hamada gets mad again
And then they wonder
How far does this go?
Of course they will!
This isn't a theory!
That's exactly what's going to happen!
Really?
Reverse Prank: If you keep reversing it, you'll become suspicious
Viking's Kotouge Eiji
First, we pretend some fake show
Alright let's begin
Let's meet this weeks special first-time guest
Come on!
Haraichi's Sawabe Yuu
This time, these two prank specialists
Will reverse prank each other
And now, in this room the challenge starts
First Kotouge will prank Sawabe
So you two will be in a room together
At some point you'll leave the room
During that time, Kotouge will switch your chair out
Okay
Then
When you return and sit down, it will break
Ahh, that's a classic one isn't it
This is reverse prank, so you have to play along
Oh, I see, okay
I should be surprised
Sorry
Go ahead
Hello? Yeah
What the heck this is this room
It's scary, this room
Broken Chair
That's an evil face
Wha, ow ow!
Pranked~
What the hell is this!
Don't "hahaha"
Such an idiot~
Then Sawabe will feign an injury
And when Kotouge gets close, he'll get sprayed with water, a reverse prank
But of course, all of this has already been explained to Kotouge
Then Sawabe sprays me
oh I see I see
And I play along right?
Right
For the reverse reverse prank, he lets himself get sprayed
I'm bleeding...
No way, really?
Woah sorry
Around here...
The acting...
Seriously? Sorry sorry sorry
Look
Oi! Sawabe Oi!
Sorry the blood, I'm bleeding a lot
So stupid
Reverse Prank Success!
What the heck?
It's been decided
What reverse prank?
I wasn't hurt at all!
Seriously?
And then, mud will fall on you
Okay
This a reverse reverse prank
A reverse reverse prank...
You're kidding me!
Then after that, you'll get a towel
That towel will stink
And it will have some black ink
Here for the "blood"
If you wanna complain, look what you did to my face
Yeah I got you kind of dirty
Ah it stinks!
What what? Your face is all black
What the hell is this, so gross
And now, the reverse reverse reverse prank is over
That will be Sawabe's last prank
Then
Yeah
There's still more?
After that, is the real prank
Hmm...
Then, that prank will be
An object near the room entrace will explode when Kotouge presses a switch
After the towel, shouldn't they have come in? The staff
They come in now right? Enter the room
They haven't come in still
If they don't come in soon, the smell will stick to me
The staff?
None none none
There's no more right?
There's nothing left
After this what could there be?
Yeah yeah, I guess that's true
Pranked~
Reverse reverse reverse reverse pranked~
This sucks...
This sucks, seriously
But actually...
Then you'll go towards the door
At that time, a nearby object will explode
He knew
Kotouge will press a switch
Sawabe's acting is great
But Kotouge will think this is the real prank
Right
I have to pretend I don't know
Sawabe has known everything the whole time
Now the actual last one is this
Sawabe will press a button to light sparklers above Kotouge
A reverse reverse reverse reverse reverse prank
What a scary picture
He already has no hair
This will be the last one
That's the end of it right?
This is the end
You should've expected the explosion prank
No why would I think of that
What is this?
Over here is a switch
Who... Did the staff do this?
Fireworks Switch
I had no idea
Hot! Hot hot!
He disappeared!
He disappeared for a second
You could see his skeleton there
Eh?
Hot!
Wait a second, I thought it ended with the explosion
Wasn't that the last one? Seriously
Eh?
Seriously?
Reverse reverse reverse reverse reverse prank success!
Now the prank is actually over
After this we test our main theory
Whether or not they'll get suspicious
Of course
After the explosion are fireworks
The finale ends with fireworks
That was incredible
Wait Sawabe, that's it right?
Tell me that was the real one
I'm seriously, I'm serious here
I'm done, that was the last one
That's why I was surprised, seriously
I'm also done, I've pulled them all
You're serious?
I am
The order is—It's you isn't it?
Sawabe, I'm seriously done
I don't have anything else
Why the staff still haven't entered, I don't know
That's why I'm thinking "There's still more isn't there?"
You're getting too suspicious
I can't trust you!
You still have something don't you!
I don't! I ended with the fireworks
No you still have something...
What the hell, you still have something!
No no, you still have something
I don't have anything
You still have something right?
Bring it out
If you have something, bring it out!
There's nothing!
There's is something, yeah?
What are you doing
No you're wrong
Wait wait wait
You've got something like this don't you?
No no no
Wait wait
Sawabe, you, oi!
Let me check
There's nothing, Sawabe!
You you you, oi! Sawabe!
Do you have nothing?
The suspicion continues for over 10 minutes
There's probably nothing else, both of us
Yeah, it looks like we're both finished
Let's go together
Geez, what is this
We're gonna hold hands?
What are you doing
What are you doing seriously
I'm not doing anything
Nothing right?
This is scary, this dark hallway
We're going?
Yeah
Let's open it quickly
Ah you surprised me
C'mon geez!
If you pull a reverse reverse reverse reverse reverse prank, you'll become super suspicious
Of course you would
As expected, they became suspicious
Yeah, that was funny
Sawabe was great right
Sawabe's acting was great
Kotouge was terrible though
When the fireworks went off on Kotouge
You could see his skeleton
Maybe I was seeing things
Like the electric shocks in anime
Translation - Tekno Typesetting - Teknova Timing - Teknonavi QA - TeknoProasheck