WDT Project
Timers: Shiratohaki, IngloriousBee, Otviss Translators: Tamaio, Magichalo
Welcome everyone to Wednesday Downtown!
Thanks for having us!
Let's welcome our first presenter, come on in!
Kannatsugi!!
Thanks for having me!
How unusual
Yeah, a little bit weird
He often appears in the video presentations
I often appear in the videos in my disguise
The style he's rocking
and the clothes are weird
I look weird? Should I then wear some uniform?
Before presenting today's theory,
I would like to ask a question to all of you
Have you ever done a teacher's impression
back when you were students?
Yes, of course
I think so, yes
So, you have, right?
I had this teacher who always spoke with her eyes half closed
Half closed?
She was a classical literature teacher,
"The novel Taketori monogatari was..."
Are you serious?
I am!
How can the teacher go like this?
All the time!
If right now someone from the same high school is watching, they're probably laughing
That kind of teacher
If we impersonated their gestures and habits
Ah yes, yes
I see
It would be hilarious
Since I'm a professional impersonator
I started doing impressions of my teachers
Your beginnings
I see
and everyone laughed with them
Got you
I became a professional
So that's how you started
And this is the theory I brought to you today:
"If a professional impersonates real teachers, their students will die of laughter" theory
Wooow
That has to be funny
If it's already funny when a regular student does it, imagine a professional!
That's right
It has to get laughs!
I'm sure about that
We're professionals after all!
If you fail at that, you'd become useless, right?
Hey!!
Coming up next: professional impersonators try to take on teachers!
Will they get tons of laughs?
Also, "the stronger the tsukkomi, the funnier it gets" theory
"People won't notice if a famous song with changed lyrics is played in a store" theory
"You become powerless when holding a urine sample" theory
"If a professional impersonates real teachers, their students will die of laughter" investigation
Die of laughter...
Today, we will visit Yamanashi,
where FujiGakuen Middle School is located.
They have a class per each school year
and approximately 60 students enrolled
Quite cozy in there!
And these are the pros in charge of the teachers impressions!
Amazing!
That lineup is surely something!
The pros visited the school in order to gather information about the teachers
First, when inquiring some students who already graduated:
Oh, I see
There's this teacher, called Oomori sensei
Oomori sensei...
Oomori sensei
What's his subject?
Science
When he gets mad, he gets like super agitated
And goes like this
All they way up, suddenly?
That's right, his intonation too
Oh, the intonation
Could you do an impression of that?
"Oh my, what are you doing??"
"I have no heart, I'm telling you"
This might work, I get it!
He's always had a bad diction
Bad diction?
Since he has a bad diction, you can't understand him, huh?
Next, the pros will watch the lessons live
So you understand that "other" is singular, right?
She raises the final "NE"
She suddenly raises the final NE
Amazing!
The NE
As if she were following a rhythm
Right, a rhythm
Oh, this guy
Ah, this one
His diction is unique
Wow, look at the chalk
This can be funny
This might be possible, right?
Yeah
And then, regarding Oomori sensei:
We can exaggerate this a little bit
I see now
That's right
And now, Mr. "Slipping Glasses & Bad Diction" Oomori
Has been chosen to be impersonated
Also...
Come in, please
So, the teachers came too
Hello!
The pros will meet the teachers firsthand
What impression do you think will make the students laugh?
Well, I am bald so...
Bald...
I'd emphasize that
I see
So you've actually made fun of it before
That's correct
So, more precisely, how could we play with that?
When I enter the classroom
I go like "How's everyone?"
It also makes a nice sound
Now, you seem to be a really serious teacher
Do you ever laugh out loud?
Well, not really...
What's the funniest thing you last laughed with?
And with that, Oota sensei, who can't remember the last time he laughed,
has also been selected to be impersonated!
And now...
Hello!
Kanekatsu sensei...
you have the "nice, nice!" catchphrase, right?
When a student is doing well, I say like "nice, nice!"
"Nice, nice!". Oh, I think we can use this
Kanekatsu-sensei, and what about your dentures?
Well, whenever I start shouting...
Oh, wow
This is so good
That is funny
After gathering all the information about the teachers, the pros went back to TBS
They joined the other two pros who didn't participated before and held a meeting
What should we do?
Shall we decide who has to wear make up?
Let's see first...
who can get the main roles
Right
That looks so hard
Depending on the looks, voice tone and such, each pro was assigned a teacher
Kannatsuki will impersonate the eccentric Yamaguchi sensei, ex- member of a "poop seminar"
Also, "bad diction" Oomori sensei, will be impersonated by Hori
Mira will impersonate Ebara sensei, who can't stop saying "Who can try?"
The serious but also good at dancing Oota sensei will be impersonated by Ehara
And Mirakuru will be in charge of Nakayama sensei, who hisses after finishing her sentences
"Denture" Kanekatsu sensei and "Bald gag" Okuwaki sensei will also appear during the show
Looks like a medley
After deciding the roles, they start preparing the content
So exciting!
I would like it to be realistic, like when I did it as a student
Ah, staying true to the character, right?
I'd like us to do our best without distorting the characters too much
Right, right
Since his personality is so strong, he should appear at the end
I agree
Yeah, after a while
And how should we introduce the teacher's catchphrases?
When Mirakuru appears, she would go like "suuuh",
and a fart cushion will be heard in the back
But wouldn't the catchphrase lose power?
I've never prepared anything like this
I know, right?
Our first time...
In order to "To make the students die of laughter",
It's so tough!
They are serious about it and the preparation goes on until late at night
On the next day...
They get together once more and start rehearsing
They keep improving the content's quality
And they finally wrapped it up!
If they went like "woow",
That would be terrible
The reaction that impersonators hate the most
Like "Ooooh"...
If they don't laugh, right?
Let's make them not go "oooh"
Let's make them have fun
The clueless students are gathered in the multi-purpose hall
These days you've all been slacking off!
That is why you're all here
There's a teacher that has something to say to all of you
We've had it with you guys!
The students, after being fooled to believe they were being scolded, will meet the impersonators!
I want every teacher
to have a few words
with all of you here
You can cut the air with a knife
Hello
After the unexpected appearance, they still don't know what happened
It was like: "what's going on?"
Wait, this guy looks a lot like me!
Who are you?
No, who are YOU?
I'm Yamaguchi!
I AM Yamaguchi
No, I'M YAMAGUCHI
I'm Yamaguchi
If you really are Yamaguchi, tell me. You were in a seminar back in college, right?
Which seminar?
Turd seminar
A turd seminar!
They're laughing a lot!
The real Yamaguchi has eaten bugs right? Which insect did you eat?
A stink bug
A stink bug!!
After realizing what's going on... they burst out laughing
They find it hilarious
And then...
There are many other teachers that are also angry!
Oomori sensei!
The resemblance is amazing
They achieved an amazing resemblance
One, two, three
Why the pinky, sensei?
So, I want you to remember the important things needed for a flower to blossom
There's one, two and three of them
Hey, sensei, that's weird... It's pretty strange
Stamen and pistil... Please remember that...
Remember that!!!
Remember that, I mean it!
You can remember it!
They find it hilarious!
Sensei
You all...
Your diction is terrible, so we have no idea what you're saying
My dihsshion?
We have no idea what you say when you get mad
Isn't there a teacher with a better diction in this school?
WOW, WOW
They're going "WOW"
Hi everyone
They really look alike
So the other day we left it at page twentyfiiiiiiive
We will continuuuuue...
Like a one line joke
They're laughing like hell!
They really are
When comparing "the other"
They're laughing their heads off
When comparing "the other" to..
... "the othersssh"
And then...
He appeared
They started laughing right after the entrance
What about the real person?
In spite of the circumstances, he remains expressionless
What the hell!
He's never laughed in his life
They're the same!
What's with your right hand, sensei?
Your right hand!
And your mouth? That's a duck face
The contrast is hilarious
I'll dance now
Apparently he dances for the school festival
And the last one to make entrance is...
They're really similar
Indeed
Today I'd like to talk about my favourite team: Nippon Ham
Ssss...
Dot, dot...
That's a lot of dots!! Too many of them!
Dot dot dotdotdotdot...
Ssssss
Who should we call next?
Should we bring Okuwaki sensei?
It's Baldiewaki!
And finally they will go for Kanekatsu sensei's motto: "Nice, nice!"
What do you think about the whole show?
It was... "nice, nice"!
"Nice, nice!"
I'm better at nicenicing!!
It's obvious I'm better!
I AM BETTER
I'm "nice,nice"!
Someone should decide who's the "nice, nicest"
Hey you, come here
Sensei, how was our impersonations?
"Nice, nice"!!
Thank you so much
And like that, the impersonation show achieves a huge success!
Were you surprised at the beginning?
You might've thought "What's going on?" or something
Who was the closest to the original?
Oota sensei
And...
He's crying!
Why are you crying?
They're dying from laughter
They're literally dying from laughter
I don't know...
Is it because you're happy?
Why??
I don't really know
Is it that you are overflowed with joy?
I think he's just overflowed with joy
The funniest thing was that
Nakayama sensei's impersonation was on point
And Egara sensei too
They really got her essence
It was so funny that I'll probably won't be able to stop laughing during the next class
I know, right?
They'll sure laugh during the next class
It's the funniest thing I've ever seen
It was really moving...
Don't you feel like really we accomplished?
Yes, I really do
First time feeling like this
The best in 10 years
I think we did really well
Students
Teachers
And also
The impersonators
Everyone was filled with joy and laughter
It surely was a great day
In a few words: it was an unexpectedly a heart-warming show
That was something
They found it hilarious didn't they
Even one student was crying in the end
He actually was
He was crying so much that his hands were SOAKED
The back of his hand was soaked
Is that really possible?
They were confused in the beginning
Yeah, that's right
Right, the atmosphere was quite intense
Can't you participate in school festivals or something?
In schools, companies, and such...
I see...
It seems you can do it in another occasion
I'd like to see it again!
But the preparation is difficult as HELL
It's good to have such a moving show, since the BPO is after us
HEY
They're not after us
OK, let's continue! Here comes our next presenter!
Hellooo
It's Kaminari!!
Hello!
It's our first appearance so let us introduce ourselves
My name is Takumi Ishida, member of Kaminari
I'm Manabu Takeuchi, member of Kaminari
You were supposed to say something stupid!!
I can't help but hitting him
It's amazing to watch it live
Thank you. We usually do the hardcore tsukkomi
This is the theory we brought!
The stronger the tsukkomi, the funnier it gets "theory"
I'm not really sure about that
You get it, right, Hamada? After all, you're the founding father
The hardcore tsukkomi founder
But "the stronger the funnier..." part... It depends on the circumstances
Not long ago, on a different show,
when you guys, Kaminari, appeared there
You weren't hitting very hard, right?
The NHK one?
In the NHK case, during the morning assembly they told us: "Hitting is forbidden"
Why? What happened?
It seems that since it's an educational TV they told us not to use violence
Then why would they call you?
If it's ok not getting hit, I'd like to appear on that show too
"The stronger the tsukkomi, the funnier it gets" theory
In this occasion, they'll use as a base their representative "senryuu" manzai
They introduced their manzai to people who might be good at "strong tsukkomi"
This is the structure of their "senryuu" manzai
Give me one about "glasses"
I got it already
"While actually wearing them; I looked for them all confused around; where the hell are the glasses"
Ah, quite funny indeed
You had the glasses on the forehead the whole time you were looking for them
Right
It's actually quite funny
I know, right? I'm good at senryuu
That was really something
By the way, That wasn't 5-7-5. That was 7-9-7!!!
1. Takumi introduces the senryuu topic
2. Manabu says something stupid as an answer
3. After playing along for a while, Takumi calls him out (Tsukkomi)
For the second half, the situation is changed
How about you try reciting one?
Ok, say a topic and I will give you one
Alright: "Motherly love"
"Motherly love":
"Breakfast..."
"Rebellious age"
"Working night shifts"
I'm quite bad at senryuus!
They will use this senryuu manzai base for the theory
But, "the stronger the tsukkomi, the funnier"... Is it true?
He hits pretty strong
Doesn't he?
The first challenger is..
Glad to have you
Glad to be here
Professional Wrestlers: The combination of Super Sasadango Machine & Kota Ibushi
Strong start
Oh, they appear here?
This program sure likes Sasadango
The Boke will be played by Sasadango
The Tsukkomi will be played by Ibushi who is a man of many skills such as his flying kicks
They'll quickly learn the way of Manzai comedy from Kaminari
Now that you say that, there were too many characters.
Well, something like that
Here on the right side surface. This is the best spot. This place makes the best sound when hit.
Ah, I see, I see
It doesn't matter how you hit them
Just like that.
AH! SORRY!
After that, what kind of retort will a Professional Wrestler combination do?
That was expected
Hello, we are Professional Wrestlers. Nice to meet you.
That was cool
So, truth be told
I've noticed I'm actually better at Senryu poetry than I am at Wrestling
So, for one, let's try the Champion Belt
Champion Belt? Let's see..
I got it!
Yes?
I forgot
I was wearing the Champion Belt
..and I cut my hand on the sharp part
That was quite interesting
Thank you
The belt
Yes
the center is sharp, isn't it?
Quite
Something like that would usually happen
Indeed
Now that you say that, there were too many characters.
That was one too many
That was two hits!
Next up
The referee
Referee
I got it!
A job that you hit the floor
About the referee, right?
Yes, about his job
You did it again
Well that's how it is
But this time, you were too short!
Next one
The rope
I got one!
So far they've been decent
Holding the rope, I spun it around at high speeds and did a double skip
Yes, yes
You hold the rope, and in one jump, you skip twice
Yes
Exactly
Could you try it?
One.. Two.. Thr-
I don't mean a skipping rope!
Bu bu bu bu
Would you shut it?
Ah, I gotcha!
Saying all those things
let's see you try
giving a Senryu poem
I see
Alright
Could you give me a topic?
Well
The concerns of a Pro Wrestler's future
Concerns of the future?..
Concerns..
Jeez, are there any?
Pain in the legs
Pain in the back
No
Back pain, back pain..
What did he do?
There's no way I could do a 5-7-5 with that!
Don't do anymore Senryu poems
That's it!
Thank you
The crude conversations
matches well with the strong, yet splendid retort
that did well to make the entire place laughing
Now, continuing on..
We have the master Razor Lemon RG taking on the challenge by pairing up with professionals of different genres
Yeah Yeah Yeah
What's happening with his head?
Hello, nice to meet you
So, truth be told I've noticed I'm actually better at Senryu poetry than I am at comedy
What's this?
Awesome
So can you try doing one about American Football?
I can
when locked in a scrum, by secretly letting go of my strength,will it have an impact?
Not bad
It could probably work if there were a lot of you if you tried.
He's waiting for it!
Ah this feels good
Scary scary
But I understand what he meant
Now that you say that, there were too many characters.
Too many..
there were too many characters
Ah well
Next up, a Kendo athlete
and an SM dominatrix as well take the stage for the serious role with RG
and then
Hey, listen up
everyone's been very strict on the Senryu poems, could you please give me one of your own
Ah okay
Could you give me a theme?
Ah, "The feelings of a police dog being kept by humans", if you would
This is a hard one
What's up with that?
Watch out
When you're on the run
this is hard
When they see the chance, they'll bite you at your throat
Go go
What is this?
This is bad
What's wrong?
There's no way I could do a 5-7-5 with that!
Don't you try...
What's going on
...to do senryuu ever again!
I'm done!
Thank you
No you're not
It was over the top
It was great
A manzai that was changing dramatically
matched with strong and fun serious roles, that make up the comedy duo
The next challengers are..
We're looking forward to it
Uh-huh
Death Match Wrestlers: Kenji Fukimoto and Jun Kasai
They sure like using wrestlers
The serious role will be played by Death Match's top combatant
blood-shedding and Japan's number 1 extreme wrestler, Jun Kasai
What you've appointed for us on the broadcast
We'll make you regret
We'll cause accidents
What the?
Hello
Welcome
We are Death Match Wrestlers, nice to meet you
So, truth be told
I've noticed I'm actually better at Senryu poetry
than I am at Death Match
Woah, that's cool
Then, could you give us a poem about being reckless
I've got one
That was fast!
If you are called reckless
you'd very much hate the fear of pain
but until you see your grandchild, you don't want to die
Pretty interesting
That would be true
That would be the real intention
His back is astounding
Now that you say that,
there were too many characters
So scary!
Well then, up next, try one about ambulances
Look at the scars on his chest...
I've got one
So fast!
Another member complains
Yes yes, exactly
Ambulances readily go back
but that is just a common misconception
He pulled it out!
He carries a lot
He's keeps pulling things out
Wow, that was actually weak
But this time, you were too short!
What?
Let's see, next
try one about blood-shed
I've got it
No longer worried when you're at a hospital with 5 stitches
yes yes
What is it this time?
That was a proper 5-7-5 poem
As expected for Senryu poetry
Scary scary
(Can't be shown due to Compliance Programming)
If you keep telling me my poetry's off, let's see you give an example
What, me?
"The feelings of a parent whose child came to watch a match"
This is difficult
Blood is dripping
wondering if they'll be okay
Wait, no
It's my job
If I don't do it, I'll be fired
Hmm, this too is wrong
Painful memories
will be born however
No, this too is also wrong
What are they doing?
Very high up
Yeah
AARGH
All you could hear were shrieks
There's no way I could do a 5-7-5 with that!
When the retort is too strong, it puts people off instead
Exactly as expected
It's no good if you go too strong
Too strong of an reaction is unpleasant
You were totally horror-struck
Exactly
The ones who brought forth this theory shouldn't be afraid
If you saw it live, it's just as bad
From a female point of view, how did you think of it?
My hands were sweating and I was getting goosebumps
They were also swearing like hell
It was so extreme, didn't real blood start to come out?
But even with me normally, having Hamada as the serious role, I've had blood come out before
We were doing a sketch about detectives
And he was supposed to interrogate me
so he's like: "Spit it out!" and I'm like: "No way"
There was a pen on the table, and he grabbed me like this and went
BANG onto the table
and the pen went in!
Blood was dripping out
and obviously, I spat it out
Real quick
Next up
We will introduce more theories around the world, and verify them
Here on Viewers' Theory Corner
Tonight's presenter is..
Koyabu Kazutoyo
It's good to be here
Here's a quick verification I did the other day
"Otsukare-sama deshita"
The theory that if the "O" and "shita" are present
Anything could go in between
Ah, indeed
I remember that
That is indeed the case
But this time, an everyday occurrence
I bring you, "When you hear it, but don't notice it" Series, Part 2
I see
Here it is
The theory of restaurant music: Changing the lyrics of famous songs
and seeing if anyone will notice
We'll see if this will work.
It'd probably depend on how you do it
If they didn't know the song, they might think those are the lyrics
For the songs, if they only know the first couplet
they might think that they just don't know the rest of it
I see
So, we've tested the theory. Please watch!
Verifying: Theory of not noticing the different lyrics to famous songs being played inside restaurants
This is gonna be interesting
This time, the research has been conducted at this cafe
The first song is..
Great song
Tube's song
"Ah~ Summer Holidays"
Let's change around the singers
Who is it?
The singer for the changed song not only has similar appearances
but also his voice is very similar, Bu-Tube
It's an imitation
The targets are these three people, where the fake song was played on different days
They don't seem motivated
Fujimoto is quite sensitive these kinds of small changes
During the time they are waiting on their order
I have a feeling Hashimoto wouldn't get this wrong
the song with changed lyrics was played
Will we see if they have noticed the changes made in the lyrics?
Chris will know this
Chris knows a lot about this song
Chris likes this song
If you listen to it often, you'd be fine
like this guy
The very similar imitation to the song
has left these three clueless that it is a different singer
I see
Eventually down the line
small changes are made to the lyrics
First is Level 1
The hit line "Ah, Summer Holidays" is changed
Eh, they're changing that?
I would notice it
What is the result?
Isn't that risky?
Is this only Level 1?
Isn't it too obvious?
"Ah, Summer Holidays"
"Ah, I love Summer"
Ah I see
Like that?
Ah, like that way
As expected, the subtle change to the lyrics has gone through the three
Next up is Level 2
The second lyrics are still related to summer, but are totally different
The night was night, watching fireworks in yukata
The Kabuto Beetle goes on a test of courage at night
My eyes can't keep up as time goes by
Surfers in swimsuits gather down by the shores
The shadows shake around like they're bowing
Cold dishes, perhaps flowing noodles
Just like that?
Using those kinds of summer words
The shining rouge is wet and trembling, I've got you
One watermelon is not enough for a family of 5
Ah? No way
It's not weird?
You can forget about the tears buried in the sand
That shaved ice that was eaten at the Summer Festival
Whose cover is this?
Whose cover?
That's impressive
Hesitating to be left out, the crickets cry too
I wouldn't be able to tell
Your yukata is like a dream, as pretty as fireflies
"Whose cover?" he said
Here we see that he has noticed it's not the actual artist
Ah, incredible
It is
The remaining two people aren't particularly showing any reaction
Now onto the final level 3
The chorus of the song will be entirely Winter-based
It'll be noticed this time
Hold me tight, was our meeting in a dream?
Winter Love, is the snow melting? My fingers are freezing up
It may just be a number in Summer, but I love you
I want to love you as much as the snow melts from the slopes
Chris already knows
This isn't it, if it's not Maeda, I don't feel motivated
It's all right to burn ourselves from our embrace
My lover Santa Claus is making my heart turn white from the snow
He hasn't moved at all
Ah, Summer Holidays
Ah, New Years
Exhausted after a small swim, my chest is cool baby
Grandpa is coming to give us our New Year's gift baby
This is one of those parody songs?
I'm pretty sure he never said "New Year"
He knew too much
Right?
Now all will be revealed
We're from Wednesday Downtown
What did you put in this?
Nothing's in it!
Why is he suspicious about the drink?
How could I not notice it?
I know the song "Ah Summer Holidays"
I feel sorry for the original singer, Maeda
I see
I apologise
We also reveal it to the two people who didn't react
It's about cold
It's the original, right?
As expected, he didn't notice anything at all
I never imagined
that my first time on Wednesday Downtown would be this way
I apologize ..
However, with Fujimoto
I noticed it
But..
I thought it was like a parody song or something
I see, I see
Was this a joke, or maybe it wasn't?
Could you please stop with jokes I don't understand?
As expected, when the lyrics were entirely changed, people noticed
Ah, I see
So, how about this pattern
We will change the lyrics from Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi's "Dragonfly" to Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi's "Bubbles"
Continuing on, how about this pattern
we will change the lyrics from Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi's "Dragonfly" to Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi's "Bubbles"
The targets will be these three people
The one on the right is a musician
The results..
Tearing up the asphalt
The stinging wound
with every footstep I make
made me unable to sleep
I wished to continue living as myself
On the night I was taking a whizz, a crying face
Ah, where are you, happy dragonfly
Crying in sadness, I throw myself off
The lyrics work well
I would help
Where have you flown off to?
wanting to be more of myself
Ah, these are different lyrics
Oh, happy dragonfly
But here I am, emotionless in the city skies
Impressive
I stick out my tongue and laugh
How many bubbles will be blown I wonder?
Ohh
No way, this isn't "Tonbo"
I had a feeling it was strange, that's why
it wasn't very good
I noticed the whole thing
There wouldn't be anyone who wouldn't recognise that
Not even one person
However, these two people still haven't noticed
Really, they may be ignoring it honestly
Lastly, we'll go by this pattern
Hideaki Tokunaga's "Fragmented Radio"
will be arranged by this artist
Hullo, hullo
Why?
The song will be arranged by Hollywood Zako Shisho
These three will be the targets
What is the result?
Not many girls
What is he doing?
It's still continuing
"Hamma Camma", who's version is this?
You already know who
What kind of message is this?
Is this a compliment?
Is this really out?
The fuck is that guy singing
There must be lots of covers of Tokunaga's song
Lots of them
And there's this version?
"Hamma Camma" version?
It's just "Hamma Camma"
And with that, as expected, Hamma Camma was noticed
That's how it is
A surprise, wasn't it?
Me and everyone else
was very astonished by this
"Fragmented Radio" was replaced by
"Hamma Hamma"
"Camma"
and not "Hamma Camma Hamma"
Okay everyone, here's another quick one
Have you ever been in a state where no matter what happens, you'd be unable to resist,
or there's ever been a time where you felt helpless?
There would be, right?
There has been
You haven't, Izumi?
Like when holding off going to the restroom?
Is that what you mean?
You can definitely hold it in
I can even hold it for two hours
What are you talking about?!
I thought there'd be a better one but you totally missed it
Okay you've got her
What the hell is feeling powerless holding in your pee!
He's locked on
Think about it a bit! You ain't gonna get paid just sitting on your ass cuz you got a pretty face you idiot!!
So sorry for you
Feel grateful for your parents and grandparents
His emotion are a bit...
Now, I bring you this theory based on that
The theory of being helpless when you're carrying a urine sample
We did some verification if urine
does make you helpless, please watch the following
What kind of verification are you doing?
We investigate the theory of being helpless when you're carrying a urine sample
Is there a point to this?
For this we have 4 celebrities being called out to a specialized hospital prior to a fake health examination
Komiya's in this
The doctor's room is directly 10m from the toilet
While they're carrying urine, they will run into 4 obstacles
The first person is..
Sanshiro's Komiya
The urine that was deposited..
Sorry, this didn't have your name on it, could you please take a seat over there?
is left in the nurse's care..
and is swapped out for tea and returned back
Ah they swapped it
Ah that's great
I see
The first obstacle faced is..
Thank you for waiting
Please hold onto this and wait
What would you do if there was a woman next to you?
This definitely is bad
Ah this situation exists
Please excuse me
He keeps it hidden
Continuing on is Trendy Angel's Saito
Ah Saito's here
Sorry, excuse me
Please hold onto this and wait
Do I have to wait?..
As expected, it is left in a place that can't be seen
Now with Masaya Nakamura
What's with his face?
he placed it between his legs
Then there's Ebisu who is surrounded by two women
What would you do if you were surrounded?
He places it somewhere that can't be seen either way
He's embarrassed
Understandable
As expected, are they embarrassed for it to be seen by females?
They all pretend as if the urine is non-existent
Komiya
Yes, coming, excuse me
Good luck
Ah, excuse me, Komiya
if it's okay with you, could I get your autograph?
Ah, yes, that's fine
Sorry
Ah, is one-handed okay?
Yes
Are you okay?
It's fine
After this, more obstacles will happen in their urine-holding state
Urine surprise investigation
Moving on to..
What happens if another bystander drops their loose change?
Sorry about this
That's very painful
Ah I'm sorry but
I'm carrying a urine sample, so excuse me
Saito's excuse of the urine sample has let him through
Next up is Ebisu
What should I do
I'm so sorry, thank you very much
He places the urine down and helps
He's very nice
Sure is
Furthermore
the other two also help pick it up
Really?
So kind
Next up
What if the painting on the wall were to fall down?
It spilled, didn't it?
It did!
It leaked out
He spilled both the urine and the glasses
Woah, what is he doing?
It's just tea at least
Um, should I go in?
Following up is Ebisu
Having those kinds of reactions
Go in further
Ohh
Ah, that scared me!
But it didn't spill out right?
What is this?
Oops, hold on, I got it on my hand
A decent amount of urine spilled out
Ow
What's this
And now lastly..
What if the seat inside the medical room breaks?
Yikes, there's no prevention for this
Wow WoW WOW
Ah he protected it
That was a close one, Doctor
Ah I'm glad
Please pass it to me
Is there any left?
A little is left, sorry, it spilled out
Ahhh
Ebisu san...
Are you alright?
I'm okay
Please take a seat here
Sorry, doctor
This is painful
I'm so sorry
He got it on the doctor
Oh, you're here
Wait a minute.. what's going on?
Eh, what? Is this a hospital? What?
Eh, this wasn't a physical checkup?
No, it wasn't
What, come on~
I didn't eat for this
I didn't eat since 12 yesterday
Therefore, if you are holding urine, you are only somewhat helpless
I see
You're only somewhat helpless
This segment, you got inspired from ASKA right?
Well, um
Even if they got the hint, it would escape them
Like if they were told the urine was swapped out for tea
That'd be impressive
But, that'll be a Win-Win
That would be a Win-win, and you would lose
I'd have nothing to do with that
Next time
Check out our Facebook and Website for more Wednesday Downtown! This video was subbed by a community run project called the Wednesday Downtown Project. Thanks for watching!
If comedians are mistaken for strangers, how would they react?
Hyper Lemon
Furthermore
I'm not as bad as this person
A showdown between Matenrou's Anthony and AnzenManzai's Arapon
That will determine who isn't the number one entertainer
Finally, we present a theory on crimes
that have never been recorded