THIS PROGRAM WAS PRODUCED
UNDER THE SUPERVISION OF MEDICAL EXPERTS,
TAKING INTO CONSIDERATION THE HEALTH
AND SAFETY OF THE STAFF AND CONTESTANTS.
Gather round,
elite warriors!
THE YEAR 1986
Charge!
In 1986, a colossal battle broke loose.
THE IMPENETRABLE CASTLE
A castle so impenetrable,
only 8 out of 127 battles
have ever seen its halls.
8 WINS, 118 LOSSES, 1 DRAW
WIN RATE 6%
That dreadful castle has reemerged
in the Land of the Rising Sun.
JAPAN
RESURRECTION
THE YEAR 2023
Charge!
Takeshi's Castle is back.
Fortified with extravagance and fortitude,
packed with new games,
it's the palace of your dreams!
WHO WILL EMERGE
AS THE BOLDEST WARRIOR?
NO TIME FOR FEAR
I'll bring justice upon you numbskulls!
Have a look and see for yourself.
TAKE NO PRISONERS
Victory is ours!
I'm gutted.
Tear it down
to take home...
ONE MILLION YEN
I will destroy you!
I made it!
Here we go!
Fall, fall till you can fall no further.
Struggle as you may,
he has you in the palm of his hand.
DANCE...
The man of the hour
that you've all waited for...
IN THE PALM OF HIS HAND
ARMY VS TAKESHI
Takeshi's Castle.
TAKESHI'S CASTLE
The army has sent a force
of about 100 strong warriors
to bring down the second fortress
protected by Naomi Watanabe.
Even the toughest athletes
from the Sasuke race were no match.
One by one, they were thwarted in battle.
Furthermore, due to unreasonable rulings
by Kyoko Hamaguchi,
the battlefield plummeted
into complete chaos.
On top of that, General Tani
has been kidnapped,
and Captain Kimura is still
nowhere to be found.
The pressure continues
to bear down on the army.
Fifty-seven warriors remain
after the third stronghold.
The road ahead forks in two
with more battles to follow.
THE SECOND FORTRESS
NAOMI CASTLE
This looks like a sci-fi movie.
-It's extravagant.
-We don't cut corners at Takeshi's Castle.
-Of course, we have a reputation.
-That's right.
This next game is a fan favorite.
-It's the Strait of Gibraltar.
-The famous game.
-It's very well known?
-Indeed.
Let's get started with
the Strait of Gibraltar.
I finally escaped from that carbon thing.
What do you call those?
It's super resistant, you know?
Anyways, I got away.
-And I'm back on the battlefield.
-Why didn't they reshoot this?
FROM GENERAL TANI
HOW DARE YOU ABANDON YOUR DUTIES. EXPLAIN.
This sketch is terrible.
-You've got to be kidding.
-He's committed to the script.
Is he deranged?
THE STRAIT OF GIBRALTAR
A staple that is as popular as
the Dragon God Pond is finally here.
It's the Strait of Gibraltar.
MAKE IT OVER THE BRIDGE
TO WIN THE GAME
What will be different
in the new and improved version?
That looks cool. I want to play.
That's got to be fun.
What are you saying?
You would fall in a second.
-But I want to try it.
-Me, too.
ARMY CAPTAIN
SUBARU KIMURA
Amazing job in making it this far, army.
Do you still have energy left?
Are you sure?
You, the stout one in the back.
-Are you pumped? Really?
-I am.
-Represent, Post Office Team.
-Uchiyama made it.
Your fighting roar trailed off
at the end there.
Make me believe it.
-Are you pumped?
-Yes, I am!
-There you go. Nice.
-I'm here for all the postal workers.
All right. The next challenge
that you'll be taking on is this,
the Strait of Gibraltar.
This looks fun. I'm so envious.
All right, then.
We'll start the game on my command.
Are you ready?
Charge!
Let's conquer this battle!
This is the Strait of Gibraltar.
And we, Nasunakanishi, will be reporting.
-Also, this is me without glasses.
-No one asked for that.
Protect that ball.
STRAIT OF GIBRALTAR
DIFFICULTY RATING: 98%
The Strait of Gibraltar.
TAKESHI'S ARMY
EIKO KANO, COMIC
Not on my watch!
I'll make sure every last person falls.
-The ball is ready for launch.
-A word, please, Zakoshisyoh.
-You can count on me!
-Shut up!
-That bridge is quite high.
-In a flash.
Why? But why?
Postal workers of Japan, watch this!
-You got this.
-You got this!
FUTTSU POST OFFICE TEAM
SHUNSUKE KANEKO (40)
-They must be excited for this.
-So you have to hold the ball.
CARRY THE VOLLEYBALL
TO THE OTHER SIDE TO WIN
-He's bouncing on the bridge.
-So that's how they do it.
-That's a lot. They didn't do this before.
-This is new.
It's hard to resist that-- Wait a second!
Well done, good job.
-I feel bad. He didn't even get to try.
-It's too difficult.
Takeshi's army interferes
by bouncing the bridge.
The army will need a considerable amount
of an ability to balance.
-That was awful.
-Not fair.
This is the worst game.
When will I bring them down?
The moment is now.
-What was that?
-The gull.
FUTTSU POST OFFICE TEAM
KATSUHIRO WATANABE (42)
-I'll try my best.
-Doesn't he seem promising?
-Remember to jump carefully.
-Uchiyama is expressionless.
He must be nervous.
Oh no, resist the fall!
-It's too hard. Besides, the water--
-Makes it slippery.
-Why did he rush?
-I think he wanted to get to that rock.
-Because they interfere.
-I see.
Next up is Takao Uchiyama,
the postal worker who ended up
swallowing a lot of water in Block Block.
Why did we even bring you!
FUTTSU POST OFFICE TEAM
TAKAO UCHIYAMA (42)
-Uchiyama, you got this.
-He's up. Let's go.
You can do it, Uchiyama.
Uchiyama...
-Watch out. Take your time.
-I don't think he'll make it.
Steady, steady. Good job.
Uchiyama...
-Don't swallow any water. It's dangerous.
-I'm sure he will.
-Uchiyama... It was too late.
-What a frustrating fall.
Uchiyama lost his balance
while being hosed down,
and ends up falling face first
into the pond.
And unfortunately, swallowed
a ton of pond water again.
A lot of water came out of his mouth.
Our next challengers are...
YOYO &amp; SACO
-We've known each other for a long time.
-We're drinking buddies.
-Are you amped for the next round?
-Are you?
I'm willing to break a bone for it.
-Wow. And a little scary.
-Her dedication is intense.
Both from Osaka, YoYo and SaCo have been
drinking buddies for over 15 years.
Today, they're bringing that
Southern charm to Takeshi's Castle.
They're definitely gyarus.
Do you think they were drunk
when they applied?
"We should totes do it."
Keep your balance!
-They're going easy on shaking the bridge.
-That's nice.
TAKESHI'S ARMY INTERFERES
WITH BALLS AND WATER ATTACKS
-Use the momentum.
-She's doing well.
And here we have the golden ball.
If you make it with this ball
that gets thrown in randomly,
you'll go home with a grand.
-Is there only one of those?
-Oh no.
-She fell.
-They must've got to her.
I think I was able to display
my Osakan grit.
-You got this. Go, buddy act.
-Go.
-Stop it!
-She says exactly what she feels.
Make it past if you can!
The water pressure is pretty strong.
-I can't!
-Don't let it get to you.
-It must be scary to run.
-It's cold!
She said it's cold, don't you hear her?
Get through if you can.
-She's on the move.
-Good, go!
-Stay calm.
-That water is too much.
-They came for her legs.
-That water is frustrating.
-Take it easy, Kano.
-Right?
-This is too easy.
-Kano!
-This is all your fault!
She says it's all your fault.
-He really didn't like that.
-Kano...
Next up is Sengoku, a former star player
from Japan's national soccer team.
When it comes to defeating warriors,
no one is more efficient than this stud.
EX NADESHIKO LEAGUE PLAYER
RAIMU SENGOKU (25)
1, 10, 100, 1000%,
I'm Raimu Sengoku!
-She acts like a comedian.
-That's her tone?
-She's lots of fun.
-Everyone is excited, too.
-She got it.
-Okay, nice.
She's got strong legs.
-And amazing balance.
-Impressive.
You're so cool!
-I'm cool? Yeah, I know.
-She's dropped her center of balance.
Oh no, oh dear.
That's an intense attack.
-But she's resisting.
-Impressive.
It kind of looks like performance art.
-She's taking it.
-And screaming the whole way.
Oh no, they're aiming at her crotch.
It's directly towards her crotch.
-But she's doing great. She's resisting.
-Incredible!
They're trying to trap her.
She head butted the ball.
-Wow.
-Interesting.
-Keep your balance.
-She's invincible.
Oh no! She's holding on.
She's got great balance
and head butts like it's nothing.
Watch out, watch out!
-So close.
-What a great job.
-Push through!
-That was fantastic.
She lost balance leaning forward.
Hey, hey, hey...
I know we're enemies,
but I salute your performance.
Do you?
-She didn't budge.
-You hung in there.
-I did.
-Where did they get you, again?
Don't point. Stop that.
Sengoku faced the attacks
from Takeshi's army head on.
Because of her magnificent sportsmanship
and head-butting skills,
she was given the Fighting Spirit Award.
She deserves it.
Next up is a beloved idol
of the melon industry,
Melon Yamaguchi.
-I'm the best musk melon.
-You got this, Melon. Make us proud.
-I can't believe Melon Yamaguchi is here.
-Nice.
IDOL OF THE MELON INDUSTRY
MELON YAMAGUCHI, RIPE AGE
Shouldn't the idol of the melon industry
be a melon?
You're doing great.
-She got far pretty easily.
-She's good.
-She's fast.
-It looks easy for her.
That's right, get to the other side.
Whoa, she might make it.
-Wow.
-It's really wobbly.
-Oh dear.
-It's bouncing too much.
-This is tough.
-It's the cash prize ball.
Go for the cash prize.
-Maybe that's too much to ask.
-Too hard.
The golden ball is coming.
Get the golden ball.
-Whoa.
-Isn't her core strength amazing?
-It's great that she made it this far.
-Wow.
Keep going. Go!
-Wow, look at that.
-It's a face off.
What a sight.
-That was so close.
-But what a great job.
-She got so close.
-Well done.
Melon Yamaguchi is impressive.
-That was a close match.
-Right.
-How frustrating.
-Tenacity wins.
Well done, Zakoshisyoh.
Melon bravely blazed forward
and was one step away
from reaching the goal.
In the end, Zakoshisyoh merciless
interference plunged her into defeat.
The next challengers gear up after Melon
set the momentum for a lucky streak.
It's that guy. What was his name?
Jordan made a near win
with impressive athleticism
in Block Block.
Let's hope his surf boarding skills
give him the balance he needs to win.
I WILL CONQUER THIS NEXT ROUND!
WORKS IN THE E-SPORTS INDUSTRY
JORDAN ORIEN (28)
Wow.
Everyone, get him!
This guy is resilient.
The attacks are merciless.
-It shows that he surfs.
-He can handle being sprayed.
This is a great advantage.
-You got this.
-It's too easy for him.
-The bouncing doesn't affect him.
-He's got this.
No problem.
-Keep going!
-Yeah, his upper body stays stable.
-Okay!
-I think he'll do it.
He might win.
Will he get the cash prize ball?
-He's not wobbly at all.
-Amazing.
Look how his head stays level.
You can do it!
-Wow!
-Amazing.
-What happens from here? Okay.
-Takeshi's guards won't fight back.
Wait a minute!
He did it!
-They're friends now.
-That was easy--
-Wow, look at that.
-Fantastic!
-Crap!
-Hurray!
-We did it!
-Wow.
Jordan made his way slowly
while keeping astonishingly good balance.
He finished with a friendly fall
onto Zakoshisyoh.
He is the celebratory first winner
of the Strait of Gibraltar.
-He's so excited.
-So energetic.
WORKS IN THE E-SPORTS INDUSTRY
JORDAN ORIEN (28)
You did it. Nice win.
YAY!
That meant, "Yay"?
Following Jordan's victory,
the army intensifies their determination.
TEAM SHIMANE MOM FRIENDS
MIKI TAKEBE (46)
NORIKO TANAKA (43)
One step at a time.
FIGURE SKATER
NARUMI TAKAHASHI (30)
Her posture is too low, I can't get her.
CELEBRITY IMPERSONATOR
JUNICHI KOISHIDA (41)
SAMURAI ROCK ORCHESTRA
MAKOTO KIMURE (25)
FAIRY OTTER
CHIITAN
You're doing great, hang in there!
HEAD OF CONSTRUCTION COMPLIANCE
MASAKI KATO (51)
Stop spraying in weird places.
Then finally, these guys
were up for battle.
-Here comes Team Sasuke.
-These guys are tough.
The team that dominated Block Block
with superb athleticism,
the active competitors of Sasuke.
-They look like mercenaries for hire.
-True.
The first warrior to face
the Strait of Gibraltar is...
KITAGAWA ELECTRICS MANAGER
MASASHI HIOKI (41)
-Isn't this what we've been training for?
-Yeah!
-It's an easy task for us, right?
-Yes!
Hioki was the first to conquer Block Block
and began a winning streak for his team.
Can he win in this round
and spark a lucky streak again?
Good luck!
Please beware, you won't get past us.
As the manager for Kitagawa Electric,
I'll do my best. Here I go!
HIOKI FAMILY: KOKOMI, MAYUMI,
MIYUNA, RYUSEI
You got this!
-Come and get it.
-You're doing good.
He's moving at a good pace.
He even looks cool when falling.
-What? Wasn't that too soon?
-Yeah.
Hioki could not resist the hosing attacks
from Takeshi's army,
and sadly fails this challenge.
Not only did he not change the tide
for the team,
he didn't even make it halfway.
How could anyone complete that?
That ended too soon.
Dad!
TWO-TIME COMPLETE VICTORY IN SASUKE
YUJI URUSHIHARA (43)
With their first teammate failing
to create good momentum,
the Team Sasuke members
can't seem to find their flow.
Compared to their success in Block Block,
their track record is night and day.
Even Team Sasuke falls on hard times, huh?
COMPETED IN EVERY SASUKE
SHINGO YAMAMOTO (47)
This challenge is not their forte.
SASUKE ELITE
TOMOHIRO KAWAGUCHI (40)
Shockingly, eight out of nine
Sasuke members failed.
-I feel great.
-I bet.
Morimoto, don't let us down.
Can the last warrior stop
this streak of bad luck?
It's Sasuke Jr.'s turn.
Yusuke Morimoto, two-time champion
of the Sasuke race.
-Come on, Sasuke Jr.
-Following his success in Block Block,
can he finish Takeshi's Castle
with gold stars?
-He did so well back then.
-I did it!
Bring home a win for us!
-Here I go!
-Go get em'.
-Let's go!
-You got this!
I, Shinya Sugiyama,
will be reporting in this round.
Yusuke Morimoto will now face
the Strait of Gibraltar,
with the pride of Sasuke and the hopes
of his team riding on his shoulders.
TWO-TIME SASUKE CHAMPION
YUSUKE MORIMOTO (30)
-I'll win no matter what.
-What a peppy personality.
-We're counting on you.
-Just try your best.
His teammates are trusting Yusuke
with their hopes and dreams.
He takes his first steps.
The bridge is a mere 60cm wide.
He receives the ball from Captain Kimura
and is off to a good start.
With his left leg forward, he shields
himself from streams of water,
-using his back.
-His legs are stable. He's tough.
-Volleyballs fly at his legs.
-He's taking hits.
You're right.
They almost got him in the head.
He seems unfazed,
but Zakoshisyoh is shaking the bridge.
He jumps to cause even more waves.
This is the most the bridge
has bounced all day.
Can Morimoto get over the stone?
Yes, he can.
But the shaking does not stop,
but Morimoto stays calm.
THE GOLDEN BALL IS SHOT AT RANDOM,
CATCH IT TO WIN A GRAND!
-I want him to win. Please win.
-And he catches the golden ball.
The ball and water attacks intensify.
The bridge is becoming wobblier
by the second.
-Wow, really?
-But Sasuke Jr. proceeds nonetheless.
In Sasuke, he's the last to play as well.
The last warrior left.
He charges over that last stone
with gusto.
-Fantastic! He made it!
-He beats the game!
-Go, Sasuke Jr.!
-Yusuke Morimoto,
has defeated the Strait of Gibraltar!
-Sasuke Jr. is fantastic.
-He was able to fulfill his team's wishes.
-Captain Kimura is also over the moon.
-Well done!
100,000 YEN CASH PRIZE GRANTED
This is what champions are made of.
He takes the cash prize.
Team Sasuke was on the brink
of an all-out fail.
But as if he were a rugby player,
Sasuke Jr. flew over two stones
and charged to the end
with the ball in hand.
-Our savior, Yusuke Morimoto, has arrived.
-That's beyond amazing.
Including the awardees,
three people completed
the Strait of Gibraltar.
Now, onto the next stronghold,
fearless army.
-Sasuke Jr. is out of this world.
-He's truly fantastic. So good.
He's so cool. He took home
the cash prize, too.
It was truly a perfect win.
Remember,
"1, 10, 100, 1000%, I'm Sengoku!"
-I never knew that's what she was like.
-Me either.
-She was funny.
-Well, I hear that,
-soccer tends to attract weird characters.
-Really?
-Oh, her talent agency is Shochiku Geino.
-Is it?
Shochiku is known for hiring characters.
-A wide variety of them.
-That's true.
Let's call our count.
Hey, Count.
Well, that was fun.
But you know,
Sengoku and also Melon Yamaguchi both,
-belong to Shochiku Geino.
-It that right?
They might put on a good show
if we put them in the Slip-and-Slide Quiz.
-In the consolation games. Okay.
-They might do better in that arena.
But you know what? What I thought was
really interesting is--
Thanks so much. Goodbye now.
-He's still speaking.
-That was just aimless mumbling.
I couldn't understand
where he was going with that.
The next game is
similar to a chicken game,
but you have to stop within a certain
distance of the finish line.
We call it
Bridge Over the Battlefield
This game relies
more on luck than techniques.
Let's see what innovations have been
made to the game.
First, let's have a look at the trial run.
TEST PLAYER
EIKO KANO, COMIC
-Okay.
-Hey, Kano is back.
Count on me.
This handsome guy
will get the job done in a jiff.
He's pumped.
STOP WHERE THE ARROWS ARE ON THE WALL
AND YOUR BOARD MATCH EXACTLY
You have to stop exactly on the dot.
You see there's a white arrow
on the board he's riding?
-That has to line up with the other one.
-This is a fail.
-The rules are that strict?
-And, you fall if you fail.
-Stopping over those rollers is tough.
-I see.
In the new and improved
Bridge Over the Battlefield,
the two arrows have to match up exactly
to win.
Also, you now fall from a higher height.
It's designed to be near impossible.
-I don't think anyone will make it.
-It's hard.
Well, all I can say is...
I haven't fallen for work like this
in a while and I'm a bit emotional.
This brings back memories.
-Comrades, thanks for gathering.
-What a great voice.
Are you ready to give it your all today?
Very good. Little girl in the front,
-are you feeling pumped?
-Yes.
Hold on, are you sure?
Prove to me that you're in it to win.
Okay, well done!
I want as much energy from everyone.
The next challenge you will take on
is Bridge Over the Battlefield.
-What's that?
-In this game, courage is a necessity.
-They have to face that obstacle?
-Gather all the bravery you have in you.
I believe in every single one of you.
Let's get started.
Charge!
TAKESHI'S ARMY
HOLLYWOOD ZAKOSHISYOH, COMIC
-It's me, Zako, again.
-He's back.
TAKESHI'S ARMY, PRO WRESTLERS
TOMOAKI HONMA &amp; TOGI MAKABE
-Oh, wow.
-If you think you can stop yourself,
I'll throw you right off the ledge.
Just like this.
Nice. They just showed
what they're gonna do.
BRIDGE OVER THE BATTLEFIELD
DIFFICULTY RATING: 142%
Charge!
I'll stop right on the dot.
Hammer-cammer!
He's super excited.
KAWASAKI CITY ELEMENTARY TEACHER
HIROSHI ONODA (35)
Nice start. Let's go team.
-That's a nice try.
-He hit his leg.
-Stop there.
-He's going too fast.
-The teacher fell.
-Hammer-cammer!
"Hammer-cammer."
-We got it.
-That's his favorite phrase.
ADVENTURE RACER
JUNKO TOKUMOTO (34)
-I'm having a beer after this.
-All right!
Great start.
-Here comes Zakoshisyoh.
-It got her leg.
-You're so close to a tasty beer.
-She might make it.
-Aw, no...
-Stopped too soon.
-That's terrifying.
-His voice is scary.
I guess that beer won't
taste so good after all.
How terrifying.
-No beer for you.
-You can barely understand from this far.
The length or the distance of the fall
aren't the only new features.
There's also Zakoshisyoh
who will interrupt your flow with a push.
Next warrior is the one who came up with
a flirty plan that worked like a charm,
Hamaguchi's favorite, Tsujimura CEO.
You put up a nice fight
during the daruma game.
Thanks, it was
because I had a good tactic.
As an entrepreneur,
my strategies are on another level.
-That's how I won. The only reason.
-That's the reason?
Charge!
I'm the best!
It's him from earlier.
Now that's too fast.
CONSULTING FIRM CEO
RYOTA TSUJIMURA (41)
That interference was awful.
Zakoshisyoh, that was absolutely unfair.
Zako did him wrong.
He had to aim ahead
but he couldn't even get there.
-There's no way to prevent that.
-That's simply unfair.
What happened back there with the red bar?
I was preparing myself to be pushed...
-Didn't I move backward?
-I've never seen anything like it.
-You were pushed back.
-I thought so.
Thanks to that,
I didn't make any distance.
It was a picture perfect back pedal.
IDOL GROUP KITTYCAT MEMBER
HANNA YOSHIDA (14)
Junior high student, Hanna,
takes a shot.
-She's doing good.
-I'll go easy on you.
-He went easy on her.
-That's nice.
-Can she make it?
-She might be too light.
It'd be scary to fall?
Will he go easy on her?
But I have to do it. There you go.
She flipped midair.
-She flipped a few times.
-Have you no mercy!
Damn it!
-He's terrifying.
-Like a monster.
He looks like a monster.
-A real life monster.
-Charge!
I'll give it my all!
Go, go, go!
FORMER RITSUMEIKAN CHEERLEADER
HARUNA FUJITAKA (24)
All right!
This looks promising.
Nice. Looking good.
-She seriously might make it.
-She's got this.
-No way. Really?
-She didn't make it?
-Here they come already.
-Don't push her.
-Don't push her!
-You don't want to be pushed?
-She says I can't push her.
-That try was a fail?
-How strict.
-I say that was a win.
-She was this close.
-Just this much.
Fujitaka was a few centimeters away
from nailing it.
In the end, she fell gracefully
like the nimble cheerleader she is.
What a beautiful dive.
SPARTAN RACER
AKIO SHIODA (37)
-Our next warrior is...
-I am confident.
I'll stop right on the arrow.
TEAM SPARTAN RACERS
Team Spartan Racers, who were the quickest
to finish The Border Wall,
are up for battle next.
Can these warriors,
who are said to compete
in the toughest races in the world,
beat this game?
Three, two, one, Aroo!
Aroo! Aroo! Aroo!
Aroo! Go!
Can they really do that?
That's not fair!
The bar of doom is working overtime again.
Shioda was thrown off course
by Zako's fatal push.
SPARTAN RACER
MEGUMI TAKAGI (41)
Our toughest athletes continue
to give it their best shot,
but they have no defenses against this
game and its impossible new rules.
-No!
-Don't push her!
-Don't do it!
-That's right, don't do it!
Good job!
Will there be a warrior
who can make miracles happen?
DECATHLON RUNNER
KEISUKE USHIRO (27)
PRO WRESTLER
HIROKI SAKAI (47)
COLLEGE FITNESS HOBBYIST
TAKARA MATSUDA (19)
TEAM MOM FRIENDS
ITSUKO
KAWASAKI CITY ELEMENTARY TEACHER
KOTA SAKUMA (29)
That was so close!
FEMALE COLLEGE STUDENT TEAM
MIRI KATO (21)
POLE DANCING WORLD CHAMPION
KEIKO TAKEMOTO
IT COMPANY CEO
YASUYUKI HATTORI (46)
FORMER RITSUMEIKAN CHEERLEADER
HARUKA KOSUGI (24)
Don't give us that look!
-And we're down to our last warrior.
-This game is tough.
-Who applied to this competition?
-My husband.
My husband appeared in this show
over 30 years ago,
and he made it to the final stage.
34 years ago,
Date's husband sadly failed
in the go-cart round.
-Today, his kids are here to avenge him.
-Wow, that's great.
We'll get through this, no matter what!
What great kids.
They're in it for their dad.
Charge!
I'll do my best!
HERE TO AVENGE HIS FATHER
DAI DATE (14)
-You got this!
-They're going easy on him.
-That actually helped.
-It might work in his favor.
Yes, nice! Hang in there.
-He put the brakes on.
-A little bit more! A bit more!
What? No.
A little bit more! A bit more!
-So close!
-He didn't make it.
-He lost a shoe.
-That was very close.
The younger brother, Dai,
started with a little too much momentum.
But Zako's doom rod
actually helped him out.
He slowed down to a good speed,
but couldn't reach the bullseye.
So close, yet so far.
Hope you're ready.
Better luck next time.
You were so close.
-Was I?
-Yeah.
-You were just a hair away.
-I see...
You slowed down just enough
when the bar hit you.
-I see...
-You make a great sad face.
Oh no...
Jou, the older brother, gives it a shot.
But sadly, also fails.
HERE TO AVENGE HIS FATHER
JOU DATE (18)
They were not able to clear
their father's name after 34 years.
-This game is so difficult.
-We all failed.
-Oh no...
-No one won. That's it.
-Really?
-No warriors remain.
-Oh, no!
Really?
-No way.
-No one?
-Princess, we got them, didn't we?
-So, it happens.
We did, indeed.
We did, but...
-I did want to see someone win.
-Me, too.
-It would be a miracle.
-Right on the dot is near impossible.
And Zako could stop your momentum.
We're on the same team,
but I even thought that was too much.
By now you know the drill.
Coming up are our three consolation games.
This is the final life line for warriors
who didn't make the cut.
I'll return to the battle.
KITAGAWA ELECTRICS MANAGER
MASASHI HIOKI (41)
-Further down!
-That way!
Go back! Go back!
No!
-You're covered in mud.
-He's fuming.
Are you sad now?
ELDEST SON
RYUSEI
I've never seen dad like this.
TAKESHI'S ARMY
AMA-WRES KYODAI
FORMER RITSUMEIKAN CHEERLEADER
HARUNA FUJITAKA (24)
That was quick!
DECATHLON RUNNER
KEISUKE USHIRO (27)
SPARTAN RACER
MEGUMI TAKAGI (41)
TAKESHI'S ARMY
SAKI YAMATO, IDOL
KAWASAKI ELEMENTARY TEACHER
KOTA SAKUMA (29)
IDOL CAFE WAITRESS
YOYO
TEAM MOM FRIENDS
MIKI TAKEBE (46)
PRO WRESTLER
HIROKI SAKAI (47)
Oh no...
He's got it!
CELEBRITY IMPERSONATOR
JUNICHI KOISHIDA (41)
Takeshi's army wins.
My enthusiasm for Takeshi's Castle
is just like my socks.
Not there. Trendy joke, right?
14 warriors head to the next stronghold
for a chance to fight in the final battle.
Coming up, pick the right walls
and break through them to reach the goal
in this game called
Faraway Wall to Freedom.
In the beginning, only one warrior would
face this challenge at a time,
but later this evolved to include
the entire army.
-I remember that.
-Yeah.
Let's see what improvements were made
in the newest version.
-Isn't that grand?
-This is intense.
TAKESHI'S CASTLE
Army, I'm proud that you made it this far.
Do you still have your wits about you?
They're starting to look
like warriors to me.
The next challenge that awaits you is
Faraway Wall to Freedom.
-This looks fun.
-Amazing.
-Don't hurt yourselves. Can you make it?
-Looks splendid.
Okay. Well then, charge!
Do your best!
TAKESHI'S ARMY
KUROCHAN &amp; WATARI 119
-We won't let you through.
-Kurochan.
Never!
Hey, there's a fortune teller.
-Let's go talk to her.
-What's this about?
MYSTERIOUS FORTUNE GRANNY
I'm the Fortune Granny.
-Why don't I tell you about your future?
-This is shady.
Can you tell us if we'll succeed
in protecting these walls,
-without letting the army through?
-Please tell us.
Well, let me take a look
into my crystal ball and see what it says.
-This feels like a dream.
-Why don't you take a peek, too?
-What is this?
-I have a weird feeling about this.
-Please tell us. More?
-Look more deeply.
-That scared me.
-What is this?
Only at Takeshi's Castle.
-What is the point?
-What is this farce?
-Why did you scare us, Granny?
-I'm shocked.
What are you trying to accomplish?
"What are you trying to accomplish?"
Great question.
-Break free.
-Faraway Wall to Freedom.
-You hit me.
-Sorry.
We will be reporting on the ground.
FARAWAY WALL TO FREEDOM
DIFFICULTY RATING: 95%
I'll do everything in my power to win.
Watch me.
-Charge!
-Good luck!
FIND THE RIGHT PANEL TO MAKE IT
THROUGH THE WALLS
-So there's eight of them.
-And they're hard walls, too.
Stay calm.
7/8 WALLS LEFT
THEY CAN MOVE ON
EVEN IF THEY FALL INTO MUD OR POND
-There are a lot of obstacles.
-You fly into mud.
-Have they always been that solid?
-That takes a lot of energy.
-I remember this part.
-What a dirty trick.
-You got this.
-Keep going!
Only three walls out of those
eight panels are tear able.
-And they all have mud behind them.
-The probability is low.
-This is what life looks like, in a way.
-That's true.
-Good, good. Oh no!
-There's a net.
-That's a thing, too?
-Just when you thought you made it.
-So you have to backtrack.
-They do? Okay.
-You can't pass-- Who's that?
-Don't get caught.
TAKESHI'S ARMY WILL APPEAR RANDOMLY,
GET CAUGHT AND FAIL
-A lot of people actually hate Kurochan.
-They're coming. Oh no!
Kurochan will gobble you up.
I've got you.
FAILED
Mud everywhere.
This is so much fun.
Let's meet our next warrior.
Hailing from
the Female College Student Team,
Kato, who proved herself in
the battles at Ueda Castle, is back.
Will she make it to the final battle
this time?
I made it this far,
so I believe I can do it.
-Good luck!
-Charge!
Okay, put up a good fight.
Look, she's starting from the far end.
-She fell into the mud from the start.
-Look at her go.
You're doing well.
-Okay, well done.
-She's all muddy.
-That mud makes it harder to walk, too.
-You got this.
-That must be tiring.
Get to other side, keep going.
This will wear you out.
-She's almost out of energy.
-That seems tough.
-It's the net.
-Everyone gets caught there.
That net...
It's human nature
to want to keep straight.
They tend to avoid the furthest archways.
-Oh no, here they come.
-Oh dear, run, run.
-This is not good.
-No!
-She's getting away.
-Run, run.
Watari is after her.
-Here he comes!
-Yay! She did.
-Good job.
-Keep going! Oh no!
-She isn't moving.
-They keep coming.
-Run away.
-Can he cross the wall?
-Did she make it?
-Kato!
FAILED
-Was it a net?
-Look, her face is blue. Code blue!
Not only do you have to crawl through mud,
but you also have to ditch Takeshi's army.
The army struggles against
this horrid game.
It's like watching a nightmare
come to life.
-Kuro got me.
-That's right. Goodbye.
PARKOUR ASSOCIATION LEADER
JUN SATO (30)
Oops, I missed a spot.
Goodbye to this side, too.
PRO WRESTLER
HIROKI SAKAI (47)
Are you okay? I found a victim!
Are you okay? Brace yourself.
Are you okay? You okay?
Let me see your face.
Please open your eyes!
This is exhausting.
Very depleting.
But also so fun though.
FEMALE COLLEGE STUDENT TEAM
EVE HANIUDA (22)
What the heck.
I couldn't do this.
-Oh, it's a lady.
-That pool seems deep.
You're right. It's quite deep.
I've got you.
Let's bathe together.
Here, this is how you end.
STRAIT OF GIBRALTAR WINNER
JORDAN ORIEN (28)
Jordan, who won in Strait of Gibraltar,
also gives it his best shot. But...
I'm going to get you. Come here.
Come on. Come here.
-Come here!
-Jordan, no...
-There, I've got you.
-That's too bad.
-He fell prey to Kurochan.
-Goodbye.
As everyone continues to struggle,
one person steps to the plate.
-If you land like this, you're done for.
-Right.
You'd be stuck like this.
It's Masashi Hioki from Team Sasuke.
-He failed in the Strait of Gibraltar.
-Hioki is back.
He couldn't save face with his family
in the consolation games.
But he returned to the battlefield
by receiving the Fighting Spirit Award.
-Okay, I see.
-Number 82, Masashi Hioki.
Thank you so much!
I'm so relieved... Why am I crying?
My family is cheering for me like they do
when I'm at Sasuke.
So I want to win and make them happy.
What a nice family.
But I won't be swept away
by emotions that easily.
It might be time to throw in the wrench.
Would you believe it?
An additional rule is being introduced.
The mysterious fortune teller
will drum up some fishy fortune.
Her bogus stories will confuse the army.
Will they be okay?
I'm seeing something. Here it is.
-Your lucky color is white.
-My lucky color?
Move towards the color white
with all your might.
Thank you!
-Charge!
-What does it mean?
-Is there a white wall?
-I'll do my best.
-There's a white curtain.
-I'll make my kids proud.
But if you choose white and it's a trap,
that's the worst.
-I would be pissed.
-Go, go. Get away!
-Choose the white one.
-That's not white.
-This isn't good.
-Are there white curtains?
-I got this.
-Oh no.
What? This isn't good.
Great. Okay.
6/8 WALLS LEFT
Some walls have white and others don't.
-Good job.
-Why is this pool so deep?
Isn't it too deep?
-That spot is scary. It's too deep.
-It drains your energy.
The pools are different depths.
Our staff is truly deranged.
Why is it that deep?
-This one is shallow.
-Super shallow.
Nice. No one is chasing after him.
-Here they come.
-The army is coming for him.
-They're on their way?
-Oh, no.
-Here they come.
-This part gets harder.
In a lucky turn of events,
Watari gets stuck in a pool.
Now is your chance.
Run, run, run!
-His legs--
-He seems tired.
Keep going. No, that one has a net.
-He's hitting all of them.
-They're all duds?
One wall remains.
Will he make it?
Just one more wall.
I will catch you!
Wait right there!
-He did it!
-He made it!
-Did he win? He made it?
-What's the verdict?
Wow. Awesome!
-Dummy, don't let him go!
-There's mud at the end, too?
-He did it!
-Great job!
-Hurrah!
-He's drenched. I'm kind of emotional.
-This game is tough.
-I'm touched.
-He must be exhausted.
-Did I make it?
Hioki did it.
-Dad proved himself.
-I did it!
-It makes me cry.
-The kids must be happy.
-Kurochan was closing in on him.
-He just barely made it.
-This is a miracle.
-That archway that he stumbled into...
-That was so close.
-happened to be the right one.
His endurance from competing in Sasuke
and his family's love,
has carried him to the finish line.
-I did it!
-Oh, they didn't know.
-They didn't see it.
-He's covered in mud.
-I couldn't let my family cry.
-I'm so happy.
-We're so happy.
-What a cool dad.
-I did my best. Let's have a last hurrah.
-Isn't this great?
Hurrah!
-How beautiful.
-Dad just gained brownie points.
The warrior to follow
Hioki's performance is...
Sasuke Jr. has completed
all of the challenges so far.
He's taken every measure in order
to achieve an all-out victory.
Since there are pools of mud and water,
my goals are to
not slow down there and use my energy
efficiently to last the whole race.
Also, I'm aiming to remain calm
when Takeshi's army chases me.
With the final battle on the horizon,
this round is just a stepping stone
for Sasuke Jr.
I see it.
-Your lucky number is...
-Oh, the Fortune Granny.
-three.
-Three?
-Is that a hint?
-Okay.
With two Sasuke championships
under his belt,
the final battle of Takeshi's Castle
awaits ahead of the challenge
that is the Faraway Wall to Freedom.
Sasuke competitor, Yusuke Morimoto,
30, will now shoot his shot.
The fortune teller said
my lucky number is three,
so I plan to attack from
the third archway on the left.
-Here I go.
-Will he make it?
He approaches the first archway
with speed.
-How powerful.
-Look at the height on that jump.
He landed on his back.
Every limb, covered in mud.
And he bursts through the center
of the panel.
-Wow, look at that.
-He doesn't need so much momentum.
The third archway from the left.
He passes the third wall.
Here we see that Takeshi's army
is after him.
He flies past the fourth wall
and into the fifth,
but it throws him back.
And another fake portal.
The next one is a win.
He charges at his first pick
and is pushed back.
He can't find the correct archway
and is chased down.
Yosuke Morimoto is disqualified.
FAILED
-Thanks for you hard work.
-Our shining star,
Yusuke Morimoto meets a shocking defeat.
His dream of an all-out victory
at Takeshi's Castle ends here.
They got Sasuke Jr.
Our last warrior is
an ex pro soccer player
and celebrity, Raimu Sengoku.
Will the strength that she cultivated
in soccer carry her to victory?
I'm sad to say
I haven't won any games so far.
But here I am.
If Takeshi's goons pop up in front of me,
I'm screwed.
But when attacked from the sides,
I can get away.
I'm a fast runner.
I can see it.
-Your lucky color is red.
-Red?
-Okay!
-Go for red.
Do you see red anywhere?
1, 10, 100, 1000%,
I'm Raimu Sengoku!
I'll believe in fate
and follow the color red.
-"1, 10, 100, 1000%, Raimu Sengoku!"
-Believe in red.
Wait, what?
Ouch. Really?
-Try a different door.
-But red... No way.
-What a trap.
-Ow.
Oh no, be careful.
-She said "Aw."
-Are you for real?
So she needs to avoid red.
-There, she got it. She's losing stamina.
-I feel sorry for her.
-You got this, Sengoku!
-You got this!
We're watching you, Sengoku!
What a sweet senpai.
-Well done.
-Good job, Sengoku.
-She's exhausted.
-I'm sure.
-The mud really slows you down.
-So true.
-Red!
-She's going for red.
-That wasn't it.
-Hey, it's a trap!
This is the worst.
Red is not the answer.
-It's true.
-Poor thing.
Crap, the goons will be here soon.
-White.
-You're going to try white?
-What a relief.
-This pool is too deep.
-It's deep enough to drown.
-Show them what you're made of.
5/8 WALLS LEFT
You wouldn't think you'd need
a life jacket for a game like this.
-But it's that deep.
-It is.
-It's annoyingly deep.
-And she's swallowed lots of mud water.
Do you hear her hacking?
-Sengoku...
-Come on, you got this.
-She's making leeway.
-The goons will be here soon.
-They will.
-But she seems too tired to run.
She looks exhausted.
-It's the net.
-Go to the next one. You can see it.
-She must be at her limit.
-But she saw it.
Summon your grit.
Try the one next to it.
Nice!
-You got this.
-They'll be here soon.
Here they come.
Just two more walls.
-Come on, hurry.
-Hang in there!
-Quick, quickly.
-Oh no.
Turn around. Hurry, hurry.
-Oh no, not good.
-She didn't check this time.
That's good. Run, run.
Oh no, not that way.
-She found it.
-Go, go!
-Oh no...
-He missed. This is your chance.
-Here's your chance.
-You got this!
-She made it!
-She did it!
-That was close.
-She did it.
Hurrah!
That's the finish line!
She was thwarted by the fortune teller
and tested by deep pools of mud.
But nonetheless, Sengoku never gave up
and pushed through.
She used her remarkable speed
to out run Takeshi's army,
-with an impressive win.
-She's fast.
-Did I do it?
-She must be exhausted.
TWO WARRIORS REMAIN
-Is she okay?
-Oh, dear.
-She might be feeling sick.
-Did she swallow too much water?
That might be it.
Two warriors made it past
Faraway Wall to Freedom.
And now, the final battle awaits!
That was great. What did you think?
This might've been the most demanding
game among them all, endurance wise.
-True.
-I think we were too hard on Sengoku.
She got that false hint to follow red.
But she is one of only two finalists.
-How cool is that.
-I agree.
Well Princess, it is finally time
for the last battle.
YABUSAME
COMPETE FOR A CASH PRIZE OF A MILLION YEN
You'll protect the castle
with your very own hands.
-What, little ol' me?
-Of course.
The army has fought tooth and nail
to get here.
-Let's humble them in a big way.
-I understand.
-Let us demolish them.
-Sounds perfect.
Let's check in with the count. Count?
I hope you're ready to do your job.
Don't let them get a leg up on you now.
-Don't worry, we have the Princess.
-Yes, we're going out with a bang.
Good. Now, the most important thing
to remember is defenslings.
Sorry, did you say "defense?"
-That's what I said. Defense!
-Thank you.
-I didn't hear him correctly either.
-You didn't?
-Holding down the fort. Got it?
-I do.
Yeah, so... Try your best, okay?
I'm having a hard time, too,
but I'm trying my best.
-Thank you.
-Thanks.
-Defense. You got that?
-Defense? Of course, I'll protect us.
1, 10, 100, 1000%,
I'm Raimu Sengoku!
I'll carry your hope into the last round.
Thanks for your support.
Hioki, Team Sasuke is counting on you
to conquer Takeshi's Castle.
-Go make history!
-Here I go!
Let's go!
You got this. Hurrah!
Carrying the fervent support
from fallen comrades on their shoulders,
the remaining warriors make their way
to Naomi's Castle.
The Princess will now arrive
onto the battlefield!
LADY OF THE SECOND FORTRESS
NAOMI WATANABE
-Here she comes. Princess Naomi.
-Hi.
It's finally time for battle.
I'm so excited, I can barely wait.
Also, I must say, it's so freaking hot.
FILMED IN AUGUST
-There's not much we can do.
-The arena is hot.
Please take a look right ahead of you.
-The warriors are waiting for us.
-There they are.
Look how boastful the Captain seems.
I am captain of the army,
Subaru Kimura!
-In the flesh.
-He's so cool.
How's it going? By the way, we plan on
crushing you to smithereens.
Well, we brought
the sharpest warriors of the lot.
Your sharpest warriors, huh?
Just you wait, they'll reduce
this loathsome castle to dust!
That's one rowdy captain.
-Princess, please say something back.
-Okay.
Listen up, twerps... I will destroy you!
Not if we get to you first!
-We've only heard from the captain so far.
-What do the others think?
What about you, warriors?
Show them what you've got.
I'll destroy you!
I will destroy you!
-So loud. She can really project.
-They are pumped.
All right then, shall we settle this?
-Yes, let's.
-All right!
The final battle of the night
is called Yabusame.
Both parties will board their carriages,
but only the army's will be mobile.
From there, they will aim at the target
on the other person's carriage.
The army wins if they can get
a ball into the red basket.
Takeshi's army wins
if their ball hits the blue banner.
But if both succeed, it'll be deemed
a draw and neither wins.
Let's now bring out
the artillery carriages.
-Here it comes.
-Wow, this is amazing!
Here it is.
-How cool is that.
-This is what the castle is about.
-It's arrived. Let's go see it. You first.
-Okay.
The driver's seat is yours,
Princess Naomi.
I won't let you down.
You look great in that.
-This is exhilarating. Oh, yes.
-Isn't it?
Up first is former pro soccer player,
Raimu Sengoku.
WON 1/3 GAMES,
RECEIVED FS AWARD TWICE
With her athleticism
and winning personality,
victory has been smiling down
on this lucky girl today.
-Are you nervous?
-Yes.
I might actually throw up.
This is a lot.
ONLY ONE WIN IS NEEDED
TO RECEIVE A MILLION YEN
-Let's win this together. Go get 'em.
-Thank you, Hioki.
-Here I go. Okay!
-You got this!
Can she manage her nerves and succeed
in bringing down Naomi's Castle?
-You'll want to face this way at the end.
-I see. Got it.
The first round is a fierce battle
against Princess Naomi.
Who will make it out alive?
YABUSAME
DIFFICULTY RATING: 200%
We will now begin
the first round of Yabusame.
You got this! Fight!
Go, go, go!
Shoot, shoot!
-Did it make it?
-I did it!
Did you get her?
THE ARMY FAILS
THE WINNER
TAKESHI'S ARMY
-Nailed it.
-You got it.
Sengoku got a hit close to the target,
but wasn't able to pierce the bullseye.
It was a close battle.
On the other hand, Princess Naomi was
off in the beginning, but she was able
to course direct for a win.
She shot down the army's target
on her sixth launch.
-You lost. That was intense.
-Yes, I did.
I was thinking that if I win,
I might get booked
for more gigs in entertainment.
-There was a lot riding on this for you.
-Right.
-I'm frustrated. Right.
-You made it this far, but still.
-Where's your talent agent?
-He left for another gig.
-Captain. Captain!
-Yeah?
So, what are we going to do?
-Did you see what happened?
-I sure did.
I saw it but... I could barely understand
what was happening.
All right, Himura, you're up next.
-May I? Then, excuse me, Princess.
-Make us proud.
-Be careful out there.
-Yeah, I almost lost last time.
Besides, your opponent is from Sasuke.
You're right.
It's Sasuke versus Takeshi's Castle.
-All right, let's go.
-Go get 'em.
I never thought that my teammates
would disappear one by one,
till I was the only one left.
I've been able to make it this far
with the support of my family.
All that's left is to focus everything
I've got onto that target.
-I'm going to seize victory.
-Let's do it!
WON 2/4 GAMES
RECEIVED FIGHTING SPIRIT AWARD ONCE
Next up is Kitagawa Electric manager,
Masashi Hioki.
Will he be able to avenge
his Sasuke comrades,
and live up to his family's anticipation?
Please give us a victory chant.
Let's go. All aboard!
Let's get this show on the road!
The army is in high spirits.
Meanwhile, how is Himura
from Takeshi's army?
You think I'll be okay?
You've got this. Take 'em down.
-Show 'em what you've got.
-You'll do okay.
-I'm feeling anxious.
-Please get it together.
Don't you dare be nervous.
Himura is feeling timid.
This is your chance!
This will be the very last battle.
Let us begin the second round
of Yabusame.
Go, go, go.
How's he doing?
He did it.
-How's he doing? He did it.
-He's close.
Look, it's torn to shreds.
THE ARMY FAILS
-Seriously?
-For real?
THE WINNER
TAKESHI'S ARMY
-We won!
-Hurrah!
Crap. None of them went in?
Hioki hit the rim on the target
with multiples shots.
But sadly could not hit the bullseye.
On the other hand, the timid Himura
got the target on the third try,
and even hit it again
on the fourth and sixth.
He brought the army to their knees.
-That was close.
-It was.
-Their ball made it this far.
-Why do you have that?
-They hit your target?
-There's a ball here.
Wow. You were about to lose.
Surprisingly, in the midst
of the army's rapid fire attack,
one ball bounced back and made its way
into the carriage.
This shot doesn't count,
but Himura was close to losing again.
-Well done.
-Great job. Nice.
Can we call him Mr. Takeshi's Castle?
What do you think?
-What a pointed question.
-I think it's too soon.
-Mr. Takeshi's Castle's Army Reserve.
-Army Reserve?
-Well, Princess Naomi.
-I'm so happy.
-What a wonderful victory.
-Well done.
I felt nervous before the battle.
But I kept my cool and hit their target.
The army put up a good fight, didn't they?
-They were skilled.
-They made me anxious a few times.
-But we did it.
-We sure did.
Well then, Takeshi's army
takes home the win!
We did it!
We won!
-Fireworks!
-Wow!
This is Takeshi's Castle!
-This feels great.
-It sure does.
What a pathetic lot.
You let two warriors make it
inside the citadel?
Naomi is a dried up hack.
Pathetic... Absolutely pathetic.
Coming up next episode,
a global array of warriors.
The army of about 100 of the strongest
warriors will face impossible hurdles.
And that popular game will return.
They lost that many in one blow?
-And this man is back in the ring.
-I got it this time.
Will there be a warrior
who will survive long enough,
to bring down fear upon Takeshi's army?
THE ARMY BEHIND THE SCENES
You gotta rush at the blue.
THEY SHARED TACTICS WITH EACH OTHER
Even if you make it,
you start falling immediately.
Its fall is pretty long.
You actually have time to aim the jump.
Just jump into the mud
when you go to catch it.
THEY WORKSHOPPED STRATEGIES
WITH ONE ANOTHER
Ball is coming. Dodge.
Looking good.
THEY CAME BATTLE-READY
WITH CUSTOM-MADE MERCH
Please don't stare at me so hard.
I might drop the ball,
but I'd never drop a parcel of mail.
That's a gem of a comment.
THEY SHARED THEIR EMOTIONS
-Thank you.
-Well done.
Let's get through this together!
THEY COMFORTED EACH OTHER
We will conquer!
THE ARMY WILL NOT GIVE UP
ANY TIME SOON!
That feels great.
Why do I feel like
an elephant being bathed?