Welcome to Wednesday Downtown
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Who is it?
It's FUJIWARA!
Stay tuned for our content!
-What?
-Didn't you hear?
What?
-Who's the old man?
It's your fault, right? It's your problem
I want you to be louder
Getting old
-Yes
Today, we bring you a new work in the program's usual "Someone" series
That's great to hear
Hamada loves this one
-Really loves it
He likes to watch it while eating donburi
Some new elements have been added to the "Someone" project this time
The theory we bring is this:
While panicking that there is someone in the house, if another person suddenly appears and asks "is everything okay", you cant help but ask for help from the latter
As before this will take place in the home of the target
What happens when a person seemingly comes to your rescue when you are in shock
But they're also in their home, right?
-Yeah
Seems like a criminal act
You'd panic, right?
-Yes
Think carefully how horrible this would be, being faced with two people
It's scary to think about
It's tough to imagine
-I can't think how bad it'd be
Regardless of how many people there are, you'd attack, right?
Who?
-To whom?
In short, in the midst of the shock they'll first think to protect themselves by getting something
Then they'll be cornered if someone else appears
That's too much
- You'd be scared!
You'd probably just stand there frozen
It's too scary to think about
So, the first target is...
Tom Brown's Michio
This time the ambush in his room is this suspicious old man
Too scary
When they are frightened, another suspicious person will come in through the front door
Just the right amount of terror
Will Michio ask him for help?
So scary
What what what?
Horrible
When scared to the point of having weak legs
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
That's definitely how it'd be
Is are okay?
Eh? Who?
I heard voices
There's a weird person standing there
Aren't you also?
A stranger?
-Yes
Scary
Who is this person?
First, Michio confides in a stranger that there is a stranger in the house
So, do you live next door?
I heard voices so I came to see what's going on
This would also be scary
Just happened to be close?
-Yes
Sorry, thanks.
-It's okay
Just like the theory, Michio opened his heart while forgetting the unauthorized entry
I'd just be even more scared
And
He grabs a frying pan just in case
Got a weapon
Hello
Can... can you come out?
What... what's wrong? What happened?
What's the matter?
There really is someone there, and with a pained expression too
What's with this comment?
Very good
Are you lost?
Nice guy
You should say something!
Let's calm down first
You too!
Are you on my side?
Are you going to help me?
Yes, of course
Thank you
So
What to do?
First... get out first
Get out first, I'll call the police, okay?
Doing the right thing
Not talking
Can I touch you?
"Can I touch you?"
Very daring to go in
Excuse me
Is it okay?
So gentle
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Okay, let's go
Can you help me?
-Yes, of course
Helping him
Sorry
Ah, I have Coke
Uncle, uncle, have some coke
A nice guy
-Coke?
Coke
Why are you giving him a Coke?
Tea would be better
Let's go to the station first
After they exit the house we reveal the truth
Me? Me? Me? Me?
Who else could it be?
Thank you for your hard work
Is it me? Oh, thank god
It's me
-Yes
It's about me, isn't it?
Great!
So, we told him what the theory was
But
He said we'd go to the station together, and I did ask him for help
Although suspicious, he seemed like a nice guy
Honestly, I thought he was reliable, so I felt okay about it
And, to be honest, I have confidence in my own strength
If he had attacked me from behind, I could have taken him out
So i'm relieved he didn't do anything
The next target is
Very human
Shinichi
Here we go, trash
This time people the ambush occurs in the toilet by the entrance
Super scary!
This candidate is an interesting choice
So, soon
Whoa, wait a minute! I'm scared!
A scary expression
What!? Scared the hell out of me. Who?
Right at that moment
This is bad!
Are you okay?
Scary!
Wait! Who are you? Don't just let yourself in!
I heard you shout
-Who are you?
Scared the hell out of me, who're you!?
Don't just come in!
What's going on?
Someone's here!
His brain has shut down due to fear
He's super on edge
This is horrible.
-Is someone here?
Yes, through that door right there
Ah, scared the hell out of me!
Don't know each other?
-No, I don't
What's he mad about?
Don't come over here, i'm so scared
I'm scared to death, who the hell are you?
He's afraid of the person
I'm shivering, my whole body is shaking
It's disgusting. It's scary. So are you!
Not only did they not ask for help, they treated the second person as also suspicious
And
I can't even walk a step, I'm really scared to death
Seriously, you stay away from me. Who the hell are you to enter my house?
Bluetooth has entered pairing mode
Seriously!
Pairing mode now
Disgusting!
So, we went over to reveal the truth
A terrible face
Again!?
Wednesday, right?
-Yes
Ugh, I was really, really scared
I was shivering, really disgusting
What about the second one? The guy who came in after?
"If someone else comes, you can't help but ask them for help"
Ask for help from him? He's scary too
2 strangers in the house at once, 2 is extra scary
It's scary.
-Yeah
Randomly coming in and encountering people is awful
I thought I was going to get my ass kicked
So, the next target is
Daishizen's Roger
This time the person is lying in bed
However
He put the chain lock on, so we couldn't get in using the key
So, it became a simple prank for an extra cautious person
Roger is as cool and calm as usual
But he's a strange guy
Getting ready
It's starting
So
Hey? Sorry
Hey
Uncle
What's this for?
Hey
Talking like an American cop, he receives no response
So cool
But he is shaken
Closing the door first
Got an egg pan
What?
So, he re-enters
Uncle
Uncle, get out
What's this?
Uncle, you understand, right?
What?
Uncle
Wait, stop, stop
Hey, stop
What's going on?
Go slowly, stop!
He's not even a foreigner.
-Roger is scary
Keeping his distance, he drives the suspicious person out
Sweating
Here, we revealed the truth
It was supposed to be like this, but the other person couldn't come in
What's going on?
Yes
-Ok ok ok
It's messed up...
So, the next target is
Bike Kawasaki Bike
The person is hidden in the toilet
And this time the second person doesn't enter through the front door
But actually the balcony
A significant change to further test the theory
So, 40 minutes after returning home
He finally goes into the toilet
Closed the door
Are you okay?
What?
What happened, I heard you scream so loud
Someone...
Someone?
-Yes
No, no, no...
You... who are you?
Calm down. What's going on?
-Who are you?
Who are you?
What's happening?
-Who are you?
As unexpected visitors appear BKB temporarily seeks refuge in the washroom
Wait, seriously, I'm calling the police
Calm down
No, there's someone in the bathroom...
Is there anyone in the bathroom?
He's not a family member?
Who are you?
-It's okay
I heard a voice. That's the guy, right?
Don't, oh my god, what is going on?
Who who who... you two... who are you both?
It will definitely happen
Where did you... where did you come in?
Yeah, where did you come in?
No, no, i'm asking you
Seriously, where'd you come in?
Who... who... are you
I am on the 3rd floor
How can you come in on the 3rd floor?
You too
Scary as hell
A drama
You're the one who's scaring me!
Don't reply in such a smooth way!
It's a three-way skit
He starts retorting to the suspicious people who didn't see themselves as a problem
We reveal the truth
Wh... wh... wh... what
"Forget to doubt and ask for help"
Won't ask for help, not at all
Won't ask for help
But I'm relieved to be able to communicate
Looks like a nice guy on the outside too
But it scared me to death. Suddenly, there was someone in the toilet
And then suddenly appeared a BOY
BKBKBKB
Doing it with glasses on is a little weird
So, the next target is
I'm exhausted
Cotton Kyon
The last target is Cotton Kyon
A person is hidden in this position in the living room
This time the second person will also appear from the balcony
What is the result?
Running towards the balcony
Runing to the entrance is better
Are you okay?
This is bad, this is bad
-Are you okay?
What is it?
-This is bad
Who are you?
I heard a sound and came to see what's going on
You wait
Wait a minute
What's happening?
"What's happening?"
Who are you?
I heard a lot of screaming. Is everything okay?
First of all, I thank you.
-It's okay, it's okay
I thought something terrible had happened
Where did you come in?
Thank you
First of all, he thanks the man who suddenly broke in from the balcony
Afterwards
Who are you?
No reply?
Don't know each other?
Don't know him
How old are you?
Definitely elderly
No shit
It's scary.
-Scary...
Ignoring the balcony man, his focus is completely on the green screen old man
And
What to do?
So, what... take him out
Okay, let's go
What? What is this scene?
That... that...
Do you know each other?
Not at all
What exactly are you...
A memorable line
That's a good line
The intruders who broke into the house in the form of "Worthless Nobodies" has left
It's like a live performance
Thank you for your hard work
This is too deadly
What a way to get things done!
Do you know what the theory is?
-What theory?
The old man was standing there, super scary
There's another guy, right?
-Yeah
What do you think of that guy?
Saviour
We explained the content of the theory for Kyon
"Can't help but ask for help"
Bingo
He became a superhero in my eyes
In summary
The man who breaks into the balcony on the 2nd floor will also be seen as a superhero
Ok
What do you think of this theory?
Interesting
Everyone reacts differently
What would happen if Superman appeared?
Wearing a Superman suit?
Completely dressed as Superman?
-Yes, yes, yes
Asking "Is everything okay?"
-S written on the chest
You'll laugh, right?
The atmosphere will be eased, right?
How scary, Superman suddenly comes in from the balcony
The first thought would be "He's wearing a Superman suit!"
The first reaction would be "Superman's here"
Let's welcome the next presenter
It's Onigoe Tomahawk
Isn't this the newlywed Onigoe?
You don't have to do that
-Both married now
We got licensed on the same day
Hmm? The same time?
The same day and same hairstyle
Hair style is different
-It's the same as before
※She shaved her head in 2013
She didn't even shave it that short then
Wasn't that bald then
Anyway
So without further delay this time we have brought
The program's favorite "King of Appetite"-related project
Programmer's favorite?
-The show's favorite
Please take a look
Blitz! Neighborhood Refrigerator
What do you mean?
-The content of this project is
Its the same as the original "Blitz! Dinner in the Neighborhood"
With no appointment, we suddenly raid ordinary homes
But it's not to eat people's dinners
Instead, they have to eat everything in people's refrigerators
Eh?
-Finish everything
What a messy project!
I guess it's okay.
-Somewhat harsh, right?
What's in everyone's fridge?
I wonder what's in Downtown's refrigerator
I want to know
-Why?
Just ordinary
Probably a lot of takoyaki or something in the refrigerator
Osaka people eat takoyaki!
They'll never eat it frozen!
Absolutely not?
-Absolutely not
Frozen is also very good
-No, no, no
It has to be done in the machine
I feel like you have all kinds of takoyaki in your house.
-Don't be stupid!
You're underestimating Kansai people, aren't you?
Blitz! Neighborhood Refrigerator
Refrigerator?
-Yes
Not "dinner"?
-Indeed
This time the challenge was carried out by these three groups
They'll raid ordinary homes without prior appointments
And then eat all the things in the refrigerator
First, multi-family housing
Then a single-family home
Finally, you'll ask passersby
Wait a minute... in that order?
3 families?
-Going to 3 families?
3 refrigerators?
Eaten in one day?
Eat through 3 refrigerators in one day
The first team to finish eating wins
What is this? This is...
We are the team that is good at cooking
Is it an advantage to like cooking?
I'm actually not that much of a big eater
What should we do now?
We're at a disadvantage already
-That's true
Can it all be finished?
First is going to multi-family housing
Each team will visit a street with many residents
The first place the big appetite comedians came to was
A street with many college students: Takadanobaba
There is a place called "Maa-chan" there...
Hey, where's "Maa-chan"?
Canteen "Maa-chan"
-It's really "Maa-chan"
Maa-chan, sorry
There are apartments
Like a house built with Lego
An apartment with a rich color scheme
Go ask around
It is not too late to make a surprise attack
Hello, we've never met before
Sorry, we're a funny group of comedians called Onigoe Tomahawk
Can we talk to you now...
-Is that okay?
Sorry its not convenient
No good?
Sorry to bother you then
So, they fail at the first hurdle
On the other hand, the team of the professional eaters are looking for people in Shimokitazawa
Hello
I am Angela Sato
Sorry to interrupt, I'm Giant Shirata
The most scary...
Sorry, we are looking to shoot at someone's home
And eat all the things in the refrigerator of someone's home
I'm going to work now
Ah really
Simply put, those of us who
Suddenly ring the doorbell to go to someone else's house
Also with a large rice spoon, is very scary, right?
Standing in the right place.
-Yes?
Not at home?
Because it's a workday
There is no one in the house
Most of the teams can't even get into people's homes
Sorry for the surprise visit
We're shooting to eat the contents of someone's fridge
It's okay... but there's just nothing in the fridge
Oh okay
No problem at all.
-It's totally fine
There's nothing to eat in the fridge.
-That's perfectly fine. Is it OK to come in?
OK.
-That's very helpful. Thank you
Lucky
So happy!
The first step for the big professional eater's team
Successfully obtained permission
Asking is difficult
Wow, this is great!
A very fashionable place
Are you a college student?
Yes I am
By the way, may I ask what your name is?
Tomii
By the way, which university are you from?
Tokyo University
Really?
It's not that great.
-So impressive
I'm nothing impressive
What is in the refrigerator of a Tokyo University student?
It must be small
What's in there?
That's about it, right?
This is a great fridge
Let's look below too
There should be a lot of frozen stuff, right?
Quite a lot of things, what is that big one?
This is pork
This is chicken, right?
-Yes
Pork and chicken
Eggs×3
bread
cheese
sweet cooking seaweed
potatoes×2
carrots
clear soup
ketchup
takoyaki sauce
drinking water
Eel
corn
frozen rice×2
pork
chicken
radish stew
ice cubes
ice cream
Because it is a college student living alone
Gotta eat all of that?
-All of it
Not many ingredients either
In addition, aside from alcohol
Liquid condiments such as soy sauce
Are also counted
It'll be a breeze, right?
Come on
Shirata, who is also the owner of a kebab store
Starts cooking
On the other hand, in Nakano's comedian team
We're doing a location shoot about people's refrigerators
I'm actually in the comedy world
-Eh?
Wait, what do you mean by that?
I am a professional
Ah, rakugo
Can you wait for 30 minutes?
No problem at all.
-Is it okay?
Thank you so much!
Coincidentally, they found the home of a peer
A successful negotiation
And later they meet the family
Musashi
Living together with his new wife
What will their refrigerator be like?
Suddenly appeared
Wow, what a big fridge!
After all, its for a couple
Then we'll just open it without further ado
-Please
Excuse me
Refrigerator open!
That's a lot of stuff
That's a lot
As expected
Check this out too
Loaded with stuff
And
The freezer
Wait a minute.
-Isn't it too much?
There's even eel
Having us eat it is just a waste
Three eels in total
There are three eels
And more!
There are six eels.
-Do you like eels?
It was given to us by my disciple's parents
I see
It's from your disciple's parents
The situation is this
A box of eggs
tofu×2
meatballs×2
sausages×2
burgers with steak sauce
boneless ham×2
mackerel stewed in miso
salted cooking seafood
fukushin pickles
pickled cucumbers×4
kimchi×2
tea pickles
natto×2
canned mixed fruits
onions
enoki mushrooms
shredded cabbage
eggplant×4
bean sprouts×2
Garlic
onion
pear×2
sheep soup×6
konjac jelly
cheese
butter×2
mayonnaise
ginger
mustard
mustard×2
spicy oil
drinking water
wheat tea
soy milk
yogurt×8
apple juice×8
pineapple juice
lemon juice×2
Eel×6
salmon
beef×6
pork
ham
soy sauce pickled ginger
Tuna sashimi
frozen rice × 3
ice cubes
ramen noodles
ice cream × 5
Although it is a refrigerator for two people
The ingredients inside are of a very high quality
That's a lot.
-A lot of meat!
How much mayonnaise is left?
Ah this is full
We've gotta eat it all...
No way, right?
Let's make a kimchi mayonnaise stir-fry with pork since we have kimchi
Add some bean sprouts to soften the taste
The three people who are confident in cooking
Prepare to combine unpalatable food into a delicious meal all together
Okay, sorry
The 32nd house
Got scolded...
What did they say?
They said "What are you doing?" And then I explained the content of the project
They replied "Get out!"
So scary
-That was scary
That...
"What?"
The speed from conversation to quarrel was so quick
"Get out!"
12:00 noon
Waited for a long time
Shirata's first course is
Vegetables and cheese with chopped meat
Stir-fried with tomato sauce and takoyaki sauce
Doesn't look too good
Here I go
Shirata, this is delicious
Is it good?
-The takoyaki sauce goes well with this dish
Round carrots, not cut into sharp pieces
Takoyaki sauce does not have a strong presence, right?
-Can't really tell its there
On the other side, Shirosaki is in charge of the cooking team
Here we go. This is a burger with meatballs
Eh?
Meat plus meat
A large quantity
This is roasted aubergine
Wow, it's great to have roasted aubergine
With grapefruit vinegar
They'll be out in the first place, surely
This is braised eel
Eh?
How many bags of eel is this?
Used three eels. Three left
Three more? Eels?
Guimisuke is amazing
-Too strong
※The presenter of the original show
The 57th family
Doing this kind of shoot all the time
I can't do it anymore, my knees are at their limit...
This won't work
This is not the climbing exercise that 180kg people can do
What is Sakai doing? I don't understand
Weak knees
Wow!
So fierce
With pork, sausage, and tuna.
-Used sausage and tuna
And two bags of bean sprouts
Although it looks fine it seems tough to eat so much
And cabbage, enoki mushrooms
And garlic
Let's finish this dish with ramen
How many bags of ramen?
-One bag
What is this system?
I really want to find a nice family
We're doing a project to eat everything in other people's refrigerators
-Eat?
Yes
If it is convenient
Can we come to your home to shoot?
Yes, you can. There's not much in the fridge.
-It's totally fine
So you agree?
OK, they agreed!
Thank you so much!
It took two hours to start shooting
Must be hungry.
-Super hungry
The team of big appetite comedians finally get permission
And were hosted by
Living alone?
Suzuki, a programmer on vacation today
Isn't this refrigerator a little big for one person?
-It's not bad, right?
I'm opening it!
Please
Please, please, please, please
Opening!
Now we've hit the jackpot.
-Great
Can this green onion be eaten?
-The color of this onion...
Onion hell
It's folded in half
Opening!
Do single people eat so much?
With mixed seafood
And beans
Wait a minute. Eh? Eh?
A salmon sent by someone else?
Wait a minute
This is heavy
This looks so disgusting ... awful
Do you have to eat it all?
-Stop it!
Don't say disgusting
Chicken breast
pork
beef
minced meat
mixed seafood
salmon pieces×11
frozen broccoli
Sweet noodle sauce
XO sauce
kimchi sauce
garlic paste
ginger paste
wasabi×2
mustard seeds
miso powder
drinking water
apple juice
Eggs×3
tofu×2
bonito plums
western-style kimchi
cabbage
scallions×2
margarine
mayonnaise
ketchup
miso
bean paste
Frozen lentils
frozen spinach
spring roll skin
dumpling filling
ice cubes
ice cream in a box
Although not much at first glance
But the freezer is full of salmon chunks and chicken
Let's get started quickly
Get cooking
Every second counts. Can you do it?
I'll do the cooking
Just Himan cooks
And mostly with frozen ingredients
Then
It's kind of...
What is this, dried sour plums?
It's a bit much
Onigoe eat the ingredients that do not need to be made into dishes directly
Just when the big appetite comedian team had only started eating
The professional eaters move toward finishing the first stage
Shirata's not eating anything
The first fridge is done
Yes!
Successfully completed the first stop of multi-family housing
Eating isn't really the issue
It's hard to find people who will let us into our homes
Tomii is a nice kid
Why're you smoking an e-cig?
You're still being filmed!
He had such vitality
He's smoking despite not having eaten anything
On the other side is the team of cooking comedians who drew the most abundant ingredients
We can't finish without drinking all the yogurt, right?
Eating and eating and eating
Still no end in sight
But
This is eel fried rice.
-Thanks
It looks pretty tasty but...
Delicious
It tastes great!
-I can keep stuffing myself
No problem? That's good
Although all are full, thanks to the high level of cooking
They can still continue to eat
Done
This is a stir-fry.
-Wow, it's done
Otsuru stir fry?
You can also say Fatty stir-fry
Yummy
-Yummy
You come and eat too.
-I'll eat right away
Is this with spinach?
-No, it's broccoli
Didn't get any broccoli?
That's it!
The next dish is prepared with spinach and seafood stir-fried with margarine
And salmon.
-Then make salmon and pork
Then cook it with some miso
Now at 3pm
The progress of each team is shown in the chart
Salt is according to personal preference, add it yourself
Looks delicious
This dish is salmon with seafood
Let's eat this much first
The next course is directly out of the pot
The smell is so strong
The taste of margarine is really...
Also
It's been a long time.
-Looks good too
It's a stew smorgasbord
-Looks good
They stewed all the remaining ingredients in one pot
This chowder one pot stew is their last dish
Yummy
-Delicious
Super delicious
On this side, they spent 3 hours eating
What is this...
Can't eat anymore
Probably don't actually eat much in the first place
This is what despair looks like, right?
-It's true
Is this what it feels like to be in despair...
The chopsticks are now stationary
As a halftime break occurs
Yeah, it's still hot
This is the last of the dried plums. I'm on it
Last one
So sour
Now all the dried plums are gone
Next
Finished eating
-Finished
Yes!
Finished eating
The big eater comedian teams completes this stage after 2 hours and 30 minutes
The first refrigerator has been fully raided
By this time, the professional eaters are seeking a refrigerator of the single-family house
I guess it's hard to find a single-family house
Let me change my clothes first
So we can shoot at your home, right?
-Yes, you can
Thank you, that's great
Success on the 4th house
Uehara, a family of four, agreed
Isn't it great?
-This is so stylish
So fashionable
Really great!
What is a refrigerator of fashionable people like?
Let's take a look together
Look!
Less food than expected
-Isn't it?
But
Down below?
What happens now?
What should we do now that this has happened?
Unexpectedly, there's 2kg of rice in the refrigerator
2.5kg, right?
Also
It's a two-parter, right?
It's really...
This is... what?
Looks like a whole chicken
That's for Christmas
Ready this early?
It was last Christmas...
Roasted chicken
But it's still edible
-Can still eat it?
They take all the ingredients out of the fridge
Shirata continues cooking
Shirata should also eat some
This one really does not eat
The big eater comedian team has entered its single-family home stage
Really?
-Really?
We need to pick up the energy
We need to show off our skills
-True
But
Absolutely unsuccessful negotiation, right?
I'm sorry.
-We can't?
Sorry, thank you
Who told you to look so scary!?
The dog's not happy
We're doing a shoot called "Blitz! Neighbor's Refrigerator"
Sorry
Okay, okay, it's okay
Negotiation is still an issue
How about changing our target range to older couples?
Even if it's a show, you shouldn't say "let's target old couples"
They just seem like criminals
It sounds a bit bad
The suggestion is that the elderly eat less
What if a passerby hears you?
Hello
Are you a fan?
-Yes
Really? Thank you for your support
I listen to you on GERA
A hardcore comedy fan!
You listen to GERA radio?
Always listening
This lady, although we can't say much
Can we come to your house?
-No, no, no
No?
The cooking comedians are still in a state of desperation
It's been 6 hours already
Just gotta eat this part
Then we can escape from here finally
You said "escape"!
-You're being too honest
It's been 6 hours
What is it like to spend 6 hours in a stranger's house?
Washing it all down
Yeah, I'm done
So, the first house is complete
At this moment it is already 6:30 p.m
So, let's get started
This is all ingredients in the fridge
With about 2.88kg of rice
The all-carb dinner is complete
The professional eaters goes for it
Such a small damn bite!
What are you doing!?
Also, the big eater comedians
It' ok, right?
-Seems fun
The 26th family finally accepts
Her daughter was a big help
-Really helped a lot
Wait a minute.
-It's huge!
What a stylish home!
It's a far cry from Suzuki's house.
-Stop it!
So, they begin shooting here
What will be inside the refrigerator?
Isn't this too little for a whole family?
Although there are natto and kimchi
What's below is the important part
The rest is some water... and wine
Is this another part?
There aren't many vegetables here either
Peaches and other fruits
Thank you, Madam
There are peaches
-I want to eat peaches
Now I want to eat peaches
So now the biggest problem is the freezer
Open!
Not good, the inside of our freezer...
Wait, wait, wait, wait
Wait, wait, wait.
-Excuse me
Korean pancake, octopus teriyaki, dumplings
On the other side, the team of cooking comedians also successfully negotiated with the single family
These guys can't eat anymore, right?
So fashionable!
Even got a hammock
Even a hammock
This is the home of successful people
Then, I'll open it.
-Please
This part is crucial
This is so critical, please!
Please
There's quite a lot
Here too
A lot of ingredients
The key is the bottom
Filled up!
We can make so many dishes
Below is also...
Wow, no way!
Pizza... even pizza
Isn't pizza a bit much?
Now all three teams are at the same stage again
By now it was 9:00 p.m
Thank you
It looks so delicious!
-It's delicious
Ah, incredible
So... incredible....
Nishimura, I'm done
It's a pizza
The difficulty factor of this dish is so high
-This is great
The cheese is shredded
Incredible...
Don't forget the content of this project
You sound so cool
While two teams are desperately trying to eat everything
The professional eaters have finished
-EH!?
Really?
They're so fast
-So fast!
Yes, actually
The professional eater team finished within two hours
Finished!
The duo managed to consume everything
Then, asking passersby
Yes, you can.
-Thank you
They complete a smooth negotiation
Awesome
Awesome awesome
Your place is great!
What a lovely home.
-What's this?
Is this your occupation?
I just do this in my spare time
This is incredible, right?
All of these
-Are made by hand?
It's awesome. It's like being in a boutique
This DIY-loving owner
What's in his fridge?
Good luck!
Super good!
Due to being single, he doesn't have much
What is this?
Pickled cucumber
Even has this kind of stuff
Don't wanna eat this kind of stuff
Bitter gourd what?
-Bitter gourd stew
Did you make it yourself too?
-Yes
I don't wanna eat this stuff
This is ginger slices
Also pickled
-Wow
Why're you pickling stuff yourself?
This is rakkyo, which I also pickled myself
-Whoa
The refrigerator is also stuffed with the owner's DIY products
Then
Great!
No need to cook much
The third stage is finished!
It only took 40 minutes to finish it
Yes! Thank you!
Yeah! We won! Yeah!
That team is just too strong, right?
I shouldn't have bothered to eat so much
In summary
The professional eater team won!
As expected
The first step to find someone is very difficult
-Yes
Nothing's been booked so its really tough to find
Our program team also gave these people a thank-you gift, right?
-Yes
Of course, we converted the price according to the contents of the refrigerator
Converted to the corresponding amount for people
If we didn't reimburse them then that's just too...
Just theft
Straight up theft
Everyone who was willing to cooperate was very nice, right?
All super nice people
But when you are eating the people are just watching the whole time?
-Yes
Constantly watching you
One thing, though, although it might not be appropriate to say
As they were all very nice people who let us eat their food
Broad-minded
-True
But in fact, they were all
Super weird
Ouch! Hamada, you're hitting the wrong person!
You've made a mistake
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03