Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let's get on with our first presenter please
It's Chocolate Planet
It's Matsuo Underground
Yes, the name was changed ten years ago, so don't mention it
Oh really
-Only you would say this name
Don't say it
So, let's get started, who here is on youtube
I am
Do you collaborate with other channels?
With the seniors and of course with the juniors
I see
So this time we bring a theory related to youtube collaboration
Its this
It's hard to refuse troublesome seniors when asked to collaborate on youtube
Troublesome seniors?
Well, Hamada is the meaning of "troublesome senior"
Very true
For troublesome seniors there's no better choice
Really?
Does Planet Chocolate have such seniors too?
There have been, yes
Fujimoto, do you have such a senior?
-I haven't had such a wide range of activity, and my knowledge is limited
No? Really?
But, someone comes to mind at least?
Yes, I'd be reluctant if it was that person
Yes, there is.
I haven't said who
So this time involves people involved in youtube
The most reluctant will be forced to upload a video
Its typical Wednesday Downtown
The "real prank" style of verification
-Seriously
Who is the person who set the trap?
-Yes
I most want to know this
It's time to witness another battle without a winner
It's all losers, this time
It's hard to refuse difficult seniors when asked to collaborate on youtube
Therefore, this time, the former artist who is difficult and wants to work together is
Why are we doing this?
42 years of experience Kuniko Yamada
Does this person understand the meaning of the program?
Hello, I'm Kuniko Yamada
Kuni Channel
She opened her own personal youtube channel two years ago
Kuni Channel, Kuniko Yamada
74,000 followers to date
Nevertheless, her latest videos have only received about 2,000 to 3,000 views
A channel that hardly brings even benefit for collaboration
Don't say it out loud!
So, the setting of the ambush is at a studio
Kuniko Yamada herself seeks co-production
Oh no
First
Good morning
Matenrou's Anthony
Anthony?
-Hello. First time we've met
I'm Anthony from Matenrou
I'm Kuniko Yamada.
-Of course
So happy!
-Thank you
Excuse me
You're from the north, right?
-Yes, I am
I am from Itabashi district
Really? I'm also from Icha
Yes, I wanted to meet you.
-Thank you
They begin by talking about their hometown, then...
I've been working my ass off on youtube for over 2 years.
-Yeah, sure, I've heard that
No way!
The dick one
I enjoyed it
I am telling the truth
The fan base is only 70,000
I want to be popular like you seriously.
-No, no, I don't have any fans at all
Can you shoot with me?
Dumbfounded
Ok... ok
Collaboration?
-Yes, yes, yes
It's impossible not to
It's impossible
Can you shoot with me?
Ok... ok
Although there was a strange pause
Really can't
Anthony agrees
Can you answer more appropriately?
Such a poor reply
What can we do together?
I'm getting excited.
-No, no
I'm so happy. Is it really possible?
-Thank you
Yes, yes.
-Does it bother you a bit?
No no no no no no such thing
Sorry for the suddenness
It's okay. It's okay. It's totally okay.
-I'm sorry to say this in the hallway
It's hard to say no in person
I'd appreciate it
Really?
-Yes.
If the itinerary fits.
-No problem, no problem
Yes, thank you
No matter what, there is no way to say no in front of people outright
What are his actual thoughts?
Who were you with just now?
Kuniko Yamada
The first time meeting her, I was scared to death!
I heard it so loud from here
-It really scared me
What'd you talk about?
Do something on Youtube together or something
But the viewers of her channel and mine...
It's really like the difference between a program about Go and Terrace House
That's too much
And Yamada Kuniko...
What to do? Shoot together?
It's not going to be filmed, is it?
-No?
No energy to get along
Ultimately, the most resistant artist was selected
They are subsequently forced to make a video together with Kuniko Yamada
As a punishment
How did you explain this to her?
Which will be uploaded to the channel
Collaboration trial
So, Anthony passed the first stage for now
We proceed to the next stage of the test
Next, the second person is
Nadal?
Korokoro Chikichiki Peppers Nadal
Seems like it'll be bad
I'm Kuniko Yamada. First time we met.
-Excuse me, I'm Nadal
Do not say anything bad!
It's the first time we met, right? I don't think we've met before
Yes, yes
I've been wanting to meet you. I'm so happy.
-Really? Thank you
I've started a youtube channel
The number of fans has not been able to go up
But it's still fun to shoot.
-That's for sure
If there's a chance, I've been talking to my agent about working together
No problem at all.
-Really?
Really really?
You're a big star. I'm honored.
-Really?
That's for sure
Now you are so popular
I'm so happy, my throat is a little dry
Why drink water at this time
Nadal, who is still rude as always even in front of big stars
What he really thinks is
Why drink water in front of seniors?
Did you just talk to someone?
-Oh, what?
This is really too much
Kuniko Yamada
Yamada Kuniko said she wanted to do a collaboration with me or something.
-Eh? Youtube?
Seems like she does a lot
More than 200 videos have been uploaded...
-More than 200 and still not going well?
After all, she's past her time
How outrageous!
Dress-up as the Beijing Olympic Games Dog only 816 views
Its a panda
Panda?
I see
What do we do? Accept it?
-Yes, no problem at all
Do it, then?
-Yes
She'll probably be in touch later.
-Okay, I got it
Although his attitude is very bad, he'll still go along with it
Despite the rude behavior, he agrees fast
So, at this stage, we tell Nadal the truth
I really had no clue
Although this is typical Wednesday
I don't get it
What?
It's a lie.
-A lie?
This time the theory is
It's hard to refuse troublesome seniors when asked to collaborate on youtube
Don't say it!
I didn't say anything about Yamada being troublesome
Only troublesome people can get ahead
I see
I don't think Yamada is troublesome
The only person that's really hard to get along with is Honkon
Although I'm not really sure
No, I'm not sure
The next target is...
Onigoe Tomahawk
I am Kuniko Yamada
It's tomahawk, isn't it?
I always said I wanted to work with you guys
Never met
Collab, right?
-It's a good match. On youtube, is that ok?
Definitely.
-I took the liberty of saying so
Really?
-Yes
What kind of... we both have no problem at all
I am almost as old as your mother, right?
But I was concerned when you and Hachi Hiro argued
{In 1987, when he appeared on a wrestling variety show hosted by Kuniko Yamada, he became furious over a rude question from Kuniko
That's too long ago
Kuniko Yamada, would someone say that as soon as they get out of the elevator?
Yamada Kuniko really exists!
Surprisingly quite beautiful
-Yes
I did not expect her to pay attention to newcomers
They have the look of being happy that the other party knows them
And then, for the matter of the collaboration
Then to adjust the itinerary
Want to do it, definitely
-Got it
Immediately decided
In addition
We'll dig into her past and try to inquire about it and so on
What's wrong with "ranking narrow-minded artists in important towns" or something like that?
The two people immediately started to consider the content of the joint project
So, these two are not in line with the theory
Thus, we immediately come to tell them both the truth
A strange phenomenon
This is Wednesday Downtown
Did I get pranked?
No, nothing happened, right?
Good Morning
-Good morning
We just met
You're out
-Out?
What's going on?
We explained the project to the two people who did not understand the situation
I really didn't think it was troublesome
We quite like Kuniko, probably since we were young
You're lying!
You weren't even tadpoles yet
-Tadpoles... what a dirty joke
Please don't say that, really. That's probably why
No, no, no
Isn't that very bad to get along with?
Now is the worst time to do this, right?
We do not know this, if we knew then...
Our contemporary Natsuko's style is very much like yours
She and I were born in the same hospital
Kazuko
Not the same day, of course
Are you up for working today?
No way no way
Is this the place?
-This is the place
The final target is...
I am Kuniko Yamada
Goodbye Light of Youth
Wow, awesome. Its really them
I'm sorry, are you here for a program?
-Yes
Oh, wow, I'm so happy.
-What's going on?
I was just about to leave
-Ah, so...
Can we stand and talk for a minute?
-Eh... you know us?
I do, Morita, right?
Ah... what're you called?
After a few moments of good banter...
I don't know if we can do it together, but I want to do it together
In other words I want to rub some heat in
"Rub some heat in?"
You'd say something so directly?
Don't, don't, don't come so close with your hands
What's that for?
-There are no seniors or juniors as good as you!
No no no no no no no
You guys are great!
No, no, no, nothing great
Really? Just this little request
I think you must be very busy
The reaction is very subtle
Can we shoot together?
A joint shoot? With us?
Collaboration?
Probably because of watching this movement of being pulled out
The two are ambiguous for a while without a clear statement
Wandering eyes
If we can do something together
No, no, what? Is there such a move to beg?
I don't know. I don't know either
So can I be optimistic...
Yes, no problem
-Really?
Yes
-Too happy!
We're honored that you would offer
-Yes
I've just been haunted by Kuniko Yamada
What's going on? Talked to Yamada?
As soon as she got out of the elevator, she stood there with a "wow its them" look
A bit like a bothersome fan
Saying something like "lets collaborate"
Youtube?
-Yeah
How about it, then?
Definitely wont do it!
Maybe she's still here
If you want to do it, do it
If you don't want to do it, you can refuse to do it
Refuse?
She's an important senior
A little scary
She's king of weird
-No, no, she's cheerful
But will it really happen?
Can't you get away with excuses like "the schedule is a bit busy"?
So, Morita seems to be the one most strongly trying to avoid it
So, if they contact us we'll refuse, right?
Yeah I guess
If I have to say, I'm positive
Anyway, two groups want to escape from Kuni Channel's troublesome nature
After a few days, a formal offer was sent through the agent
Moving to the next step
After 2 weeks
First, Anthony, who appeared in Talk Live on this day
Is informed of the invitation during a break
Do you remember when you met Kuniko Yamada at TMC?
Yeah
It's a real invitation.
Her agent said that the thing that we talked about before...
-You mean the collab thing?
Tissue touching
Yes, the other party is quite enthusiastic about the joint shoot
But its a little...
Anthony is shocked that it had happened
Although the situation is not clear, the other party seems to have sent a proposal or something
The plan is here, what do we do?
The program team has prepared a special plan
Joint Planning ①
Making Kuniko Yamada laugh 100 times on location! "The Wall of Kuniko"
Kuniko Yamada uses ○× to judge Anthony's pretending to be stupid in the outside scene
Kuniko Yamada laughs 100 times outside
Joint Planning②
A  segment in which Kuniko Yamada improvises and messes with a Matenrou skit
Yamada plays dumb on her own, can she develop a new type of routine?
Joint Planning ③
Kuniko Yamada and Anthony dressed up as the new character Yamada came up with
2 people alone burst of laughing conversation ensemble! What new characters will be born in the end?!
Laugh at Yamada! "The Wall of Yamada"
Kuniko Yamada improvised and messed up?
Kuniko Yamada's impromptu participation in the segments of comedians
The birth of a popular character? Cross-dressing conversation project
Wait. Oh, no. They're all super high calorie
Joint Planning ③
Kuniko Yamada and Anthony dressed up as the new character Yamada came up with
2 people alone burst of laughing conversation ensemble! What new characters will be born in the end?!
The birth of a popular character? Cross-dressing conversation project
This is super dangerous, okay? What is this?
Super embarrassing for me
Talking with Kuniko Yamada as a character I don't know
Others who see will think "what the hell?"
There's no explanation.
-That's right
Sure enough, Anthony was very reluctant to cooperate
On the other hand, in between the outside scenes
The other duo are informed of the invitation
They wrote a proposal?
-There's an email.
It says "Please, really"
Collaborative project①
Making Kuniko Yamada laugh 100 times on location! "The Wall of Kuniko"
Kuniko Yamada uses ○× to judge the pretence of foolishness of Goodbye Light of Youth in an outside scene
Kuniko Yamada laughs 100 times outside!
Make fun of Kuniko! "Kuniko's Wall"
Hey "Kuniko's Wall"...
Kuniko's wall?
I can't take it!
After all, it is a project
One doesn't work?
Neither do 2 or 3
But
But how to say, our taste is still too different
It's not the same thing as what our channel is doing
Does it have to be a collaboration?
What, like we're making an appearance on her side?
-Can't we just make an appearance?
First we shoot each other's
Then our planning side will decide separately whether to shoot or not
Are you really considering taking on this project? Seriously.
-Sort of
They are now at the point of compromising
Yamada Kuniko should be more, how to put it
A little higher level
Kamaitachi etc could do it, right?
Its weird
The Matenrou skit added in...
But I think she said she wanted to shoot with Anthony
-Seriously?
Although much appreciated
None of my channel's fans want to see her, right?
A very reluctant Anthony
So
A little...
I'm sorry, but it's too early for me
So, let's get right to the point, you don't want to do it, right?
You understand what I mean, you don't have to say it out loud
That guy is hinting.
-The agent is also at fault
I still haven't heard back from my side
If the schedule works out, we'll be on her side
If its just an appearance, it'll be fine
In this way, this time Anthony, who had been the most reluctant
Is confirmed for Kuni Channel's co-production
So that's how it is
So, the truth is revealed to the others
What is it?
Thank you for your hard work
What?
Its Wednesday Downtown
What is it? Wednesday?
Anything strange happened recently?
Recent strange events
What?
The drinking game?
-The drinking game?
I drank with a girl who said she was super into me
-No
No?
-That was extra information
"Super into me"
But I didn't bring her home...?
It has nothing to do with that
Completely unrelated
Not that...
-No one asked you about that
That wasn't a prank?
So, we tell them about the project
You decided she is troublesome
She's not troublesome
It wasn't a bother to us at all
She's super nice
Then why did you want to refuse when you were asked?
What?
You complained a lot.
-Yes, he did
We saw it all
Scary
Morita was super tempted to refuse
I don't think it matters
Morita's words
I didn't complain, did I?
-You did
Did I say that? I didn't say that
You said it
-Liar!
About this project
Two are already out
The one who absolutely didn't want to do it
A sigh of relief
They'll really shoot
There are more reluctant people out there, right?
Yes, Anthony was super reluctant
Anthony doesn't want to
By a narrow margin, Anthony won
Ah thank go- ok, yes
In short, a week after Anthony turned down the offer
He took the opportunity to visit the Tokyo studio again
Kuniko Yamada herself comes to deliver a fatal blow to him
Yes?
Troublesome knocking
Really troublesome knocking
Antony
Good morning
Your name's on the door
Did you reject the collab?
-No, no, no
It's a bit
Please.
-I didn't say no
Anthony, please
It's like a dream, really
What?
-It's like a dream
If it's a dream, it's a nightmare
The agent seems to have sent you something like a project book
Yes yes yes yes
You didn't even look at it?
Ah... yes yes
No no, I did a little
Please!
They didn't really explain it well to me
I know I didn't do it very well.
-I'm sorry
Blame it on Yoshimoto.
-It's the company's fault
Wait a second
Damn, they're all super high calorie
"Make Kuniko Yamada laugh 100 times on location?"
A project that makes me laugh 100 times or something like that
Laugh 100 times...
There is also a plan for two people to chat for a long time and so on
-Long time chat
There are various projects
Definitely No...definitely
It's super bad. What is this?
I am very eager to do it
I'm very grateful
Just schedule-wise
-Yeah
Yes, yes, that's the only thing.
-You're busy, right?
I'm not busy at all
You want to refuse again?
Just this little...
Do it!
I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it.
-Really?
Yes, really, absolutely
So, let's get right to the point, you don't want to do it, right?
You understand what I mean, you don't have to say it out loud
Absolutely?
-Absolutely
-Absolutely, sure
It's OK?
-Of course, of course
Really?
-Yes
Thank you
In a situation where there was no way to escape, the agreement of Anthony OK was obtained
Uhhhhh
Uhhhh
An unimaginable amount of reluctance
Looks so troubled
So, we reveal the truth
Is it that tiring?
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you for your hard work...
This is Wednesday Downtown
Did anything strange happen?
Strange things?
As far as what just happened
Oh wow, that's what happened!
Kuniko Yamada
Uhhh, what the hell is going on?
The forced collab thing?
-Yes
So why exactly
Wait, what the hell is that...
It's hard to refuse troublesome seniors when asked to collaborate on youtube
For me to refuse?
-Yes
Uh, so bad
It's too much. It's too much. So that's what happened
Weren't you sent the proposal some time ago?
That was filmed secretly
That's enough. Don't mess with me
It's too much, really
Uhhhh
It's too much
The next most important notice to Anthony
Anyway, Anthony-san, are you sure you want to work together?
Uhhhh
Uhhhh seriously
What to do
After this, we should probably start talking to her
-Wait a second
I really don't want to
I don't want to be like this but...
Wait a minute, you guys are the devil
The devil's work, really
Because of my reluctance, Yamada already knows about it, right?
-That's right
I've gotta work under those conditions
-Yes
Awful!
This really sucks
Give me a minute
How can I face seeing her after this?
I can't do it, so...
I can't take it!
Too bad...
So, Yamada is waiting for you in the other room, let's go
You guys are the worst
In a nutshell
It's too heavy
What expression should he use to face it
What are you muttering about there?
I saw it just it, just saw it
I'm really sorry
What are you doing?
I'm really, really sorry.
-What are you talking about? What are you talking about?
I'm really sorry.
-Why? Stop it. Really stop it
You are really quite reluctant
No, not reluctant
-Super troublesome senior and so on
No... no
No reluctance, it's a misunderstanding
After apologizing for a while on the floor
They immediately begin discussing the content of the joint video
Its good to converse, its a good contrast.
-Really?
It is indeed rare to have such a chance for two people to talk alone
-Very unique
It's true that we haven't had much chance to meet so far.
-I guess so
It is possible to put aside the content of those projects written before
Although there is something written "make me laugh 100 times"
Which one do you think is better?
Wait a minute, Yamada
You are inconsistent, you just said the conversation is good
Talking really is the best
But what characters should we play?
For example, grandpa and grandma and so on
You mean the tone of voice should always be like this?
Yes, Anthony
So troublesome
So, this time, the joint project will be a cross-dressing talk with Yamada's most recommended character
Hello, Kuni Channel
Thank you
How was it? The shoot is over
Didn't I already say that?
That... that...
Definitely not a good fit
Is that really going to be uploaded?
Yes it will...
In summary
The collab video will be released after the show, so be sure to check it out!
So, that's how it went
Anthony really was reluctant
His face was swollen
Looked like he'd just woken up and hadn't drunk any water
That's what happened. I think his face was swollen
By the way, Yamada likes young wrestlers very much
I met her at a wrestling match
She shouted at me
Next time let's talk about handsome young wrestlers
I was also cheeky and did not respond positively
It's the same thing
So we cant help but be more impervious to the troublesome
Yeah, it's scary when you can't see what's coming.
-Yes
Finally, regarding the collaboration
It will really be uploaded to Kuni Channel after the show
It should be viewed by many people
Thankfully it ended well
-People will surely be curious
If you are interested, please go and watch it!
On the contrary, is there anyone who Kuniko would be reluctant to be invited by?
The other way around
Probably Bando Eiji-level
I'm just giving you an example.
-Just an example
It's just a completely off-topic example
Not that off-topic
Let's welcome the next presenter
It's Koyabu
Hello
2m9
-Not 2m9, what are you talking about?
Giant Baba 2 meters 9
-Who's Giant Baba?
Please go and talk to Kuniko Yamada
Turning to the topic, I ask you all encountered whoopee cushions before?
1 or 2 times
-Many people played with them as kids
Yeah, I did.
-The boys in my class took them to school
You have, then
Today I bring you a hypothesis related to whoopee cushions, take a look
Can farting at the right time make the other person think they're being pranked with a whoopee cushion
What does it mean?
Will it work?
-Can the timing be that accurate?
The setters wait in another room for their farts to brew before coming in
When they're ready
It's like a waiting room.
Indeed
Can farting at the right time make the other person think they're being pranked with a whoopee cushion
Who came up with that?
-Amazing!
This time the participants are these four
It's great
Nice lineup.
-Yes
Do you all fart?
Release, but 80% of them are silent farts.
-My God!
It has to be a loud fart, right?
How is your physical condition today?
All good
What is a good state?
I have a little... diarrhea
With diarrhea the sound is a bit muffled
The feeling
-Its not a fart sound anymore
Not the sound of a fart?
The target is...
Hello
He is called on the pretext of a prank special
We explain a fake plan to make numerous comedians come in and sit unknowingly on a whoopee cushion
So, 4 people are waiting in the other room
What's Tsuda doing?
-What are you doing?
The challenge will start with the first person to go to DJ KOO to fart
If he doesn't realise the farts are real, the theory will be validated
What'll happen?
So, I'm going to use the fart pad to prank people
Just the right amount
DJ KOO, who knows nothing, happily sets up the cushion
Then, the staff quietly replace it with a deflated farting pad
The challenge begins
Not at all.
-I can't. I can't get out at all
Whoever is good, go ahead.
-Yeah, go ahead
There's a lot of stuff. There's a lot of stuff
Food to fart
Soda, apples, bananas, hard-boiled eggs, baked sweet potatoes
Is that a soda?
-Soda is good
It feels like it's coming.
-Burp
Burp
It's a waste.
-How wasteful
Farting is burping through the bottom
Oh really
Is that the truth?
5 minutes have passed
Wait
What the hell?
I thought it would come out a little bit and it came out
No, you are too wasteful
Wait, I don't feel like it's coming out.
-What's coming out?
Really, I don't feel like it's coming out.
I didn't feel like its coming out but i'll try
What a sorry face
I didn't expect the test would work
It's a waste of time.
-I really thought it would not come out
Tsuda goes off the rails right at the beginning
Good sound
Wait a minute, I really didn't think it would come out
Don't push any harder.
-That was a good sound
Just go in
Hey, just now, that sound... its a little different than usual, i'm a little worried
My ass doesn't feel right
Like an old woman
However
Wait
I'm almost there.
-Are you ready?
Go
I'm almost there
How many times does he have to say it?
Wait a minute, I can actually do it.
Wow, awesome
When the other party realizes that it is not the sound of a whoopee cushion, the plan ends immediately
What is the result?
Hello
Long time no see
-Long time no see
How are you?
-Good
Hello hello
Wow, so happy!
Have a seat. - Have a seat
Sorry
So fast
Butt hasn't touched the chair yet
Hold back a little longer!
What does the other side think?
Successful?
With the sound released, what was the result?
It's hard
What? What?
Didn't realise?
Hey, what... What?
What's up with that?
-Hey, what...is...
Did you just...
You didn't expect it, right?
Eh?
A good person
What's going on?
As expected
Didn't realise at all
Great, not exposed at all
-Totally convinced
Well covered
Actually, it's a whoopee cushion. Sorry, sorry
As expected
But it's a small sound.
-You'd realise otherwise
It's so real
So real
-Make a bit more noise!
But I heard it very clearly.
-Really?
Great
-Great job!
I was shocked that I could make such a small sound
You did it before, right?
-Yes, yes, yes.
Did you hear that?
-Absolutely
Really?
-That's awesome
Yes, yes, yes.
-Great!
What does KOO think?
The timing was just right
Can we keep going?
-I think so
So innocent
So, the farting challenge continues
I'll do this a little.
-That's a good position
Let the air in
That's good.
-It is
Do apples also stimulate farts?
By this point, 15 minutes had passed
I think it's okay.
-Come on, come on, come on
Sort of
-You do?
Have you got it?
-Already... its already saying "hello"
OKOKOK
The 2nd place challenger is THE-MOMMY Sakai
Long time no see
It's been a long time since I saw KOO
How are you doing?
-Thank you
Not bad, not bad
Thank you for your help on Youtube
-My pleasure
Please sit. Please sit.
-I'll sit down then
Please, have a seat
So nervous
What is the result?
Find the right time
I always see you on TV lately.
-No not really
A big hit!
Not out
It didn't happen
Are you okay? You won't be found out?
Sakai has a painful realization
Come back! Come back!
-Oh my God, he's going to find out
It's revealed! It's revealed!
We haven't been there yet
Busy day, right? Are you shooting later?
-Yes
Doing a small bit today, yes
However, at this time
What a fart
Adjusting the sitting position, he finally squeezes out a small fart
So
Sakai
-Yes
In fact, this is a prank
KOO is very able
-Good choice
I thought I something just happened...
He's so excited, his face is so red
We put a whoopee cushion under you
Wow, really?
This?
-Sorry, sorry
Wow, I just heard a nice weak sound
Maybe I missed it.
-Yes, it's true
It's flattened.
-Yes
So, there are two more challengers
The situation is good now
The sound of whoopee cushions and real farts
Farts don't usually have that sound
PAH! That sound
That's true...
-Yes, yes
It's true!
At this point, the challenge has been going for 30 minutes
However, Ogata and Nishimura have yet to release
Can't you? Relax. Boom, boom, boom
Such a crips sound
Seriously
What the hell
What is there to envy about farting
How nice to give him this sound
-It's so crisp, it's intoxicating
Intoxicated my ass!
And at this point, one hour has passed since the challenge
I can't. People are waiting.
-No way
And DJ KOO himself is...
Gyaru!
Doesn't care about the unexplained waiting time
Let me think how to promote the fart for you
-Have a think
Maybe a good ass-knocking.
-Got it.
That's good, that's good
Jump
Under the guidance of Sakai, the senior farter, the two of them began to tap their bellies and hips
I've got it.
-Here we go
You need to be confident
I'll go to the door and check again
I'll come back if I can't.
-OK
Go
The sound is going into the room
KOO heard you.
-Don't blow it
KOO has a suspicious face
At this point
Hello
It's been a long time. How are you?
-Very good
Look a little tired, you okay?
What is this?
-Sorry
Quite realistic
Don't do it!
-Sorry!
The expression afterwards, so realistic
Can muddle through with acting skills
It's out. It's out.
-Sweating profusely
This is a prank
Stop screwing around
Is it that unpleasant?
Great!
Nice
-What a big sound!
Loud enough?
-Loud!
This is how it should be
Next is Nishimura-san.
-It's hard to top
It's up to you.
-I've gotta do it
I'll go and prepare on the way
I'm almost there
No problem
How long has it been?
It's not over.
-2 hours
It's amazing!
Nishimura also came to the room and waited before rushing in as soon as he felt it
At this time
Looks kind of cool, what the hell?
What is the result?
Dashing
Slipped back in
After hitting himself for 5 minutes
What happened?
What the hell
-What the hell is going on in Viking?
Weird!
It went back
After that, the tide of farts rises and falls
Two steps and everything falls apart
When I leave, it's gone. Can I just go in?
-Yes
I'm exhausted, just finished shooting
Ah, it's hard
My back hurts. My back hurts.
-Sit slowly
Too tired,I'm too stiff
It's hard work.
-The waiting time is also long
Take your time, take a breather
Just too hard, my back is so stiff
On one side is the eager DJ KOO, and on the other is the Nishimura who wont sit without the feeling
An interesting offensive and defensive battle
The waiting goes on for 5 minutes
Finally
You're more tired this way.
-No, not really
There you go
Nishimura released a beautiful 2-hit combo
Good volume
-Lots of sound
Good!
-So free!
That's a lot.
-There are so many
Sorry
What what what?
What's going on here?
-Great!
You all waited for so long!
Sorry, sorry to keep you waiting
In summary
It took 2 hours and 18 minutes to confirm the theory
Didn't realise
The choice of KOO is a good one
It's true, it's almost too obvious
He's very innocent
What does everyone think of this project
Want to try it?
That...
There should be a female edition
Women
-Female comedians
Who would want to do this?
Having so much fun
Don't say it like "want to dance together?"
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03