Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Anyone there?
-Hard to say
Anyone?
-Must be
It's New York!
On this program we regularly bring you this project
It involves having to find something or not being allowed to go home for a long time
-Indeed
This time we bring you a theory relating to comedians outside
Please take a look
So long!
Hamada, please read it!
What!? Why're you shouting at me?
New York can read it!
When looking for someone whose ends sentences with "gesu" and you think "there can't be such a person" after a long time on location and fake actors appear who say "gesu", will they believe it?
Can't figure it out
What is this?
Someone will be on location to find a person that says "gesu" at the end of their sentences
What is "gesu"?
Isn't it basically impossible to find such people?
-Yes
So, as they will naturally be out looking for so long, finally they will find one
But will they believe it?
I see
The first target is
Find someone detective group!
Yay!
Using a fake plan, Hatse is challenged to find a person whose ends sentences with "gesu"
There is no time limit
-Wait!
But this will be impossible
So what to do?
I'm going over there
Excuse me, can I interview you...
It won't take much time
Do you have any hobbies and interests?
I like photography
Photography
-Yes
No one will say "impossible"
I see
After this also
Do you have any hobbies?
Guitar
-Guitar?
Do you live in Tokyo?
-I live in Shizuoka
Originally from Shizuoka
-But i've lived in both places
The fruitless location shoot lasts for 4 hours
So desperate
At this point, actors whose words end in "gesu" will begin to appear
What kind of work do you do now?
I'm a civil servant-gesu
Civil servant? Eh...
But... but... can you say it again? Sorry
I said i'm a civil servant-gesu
Eh?
He's scared
A civil servant-gesu? Eh? Eh?
Today is my day off-gesu
"A day off-gesu"
This one is so real
Is that so?
Eh...
What's wrong with gesu?
No, no, no, no, no, no
I found someone, it's a miracle!
Saying "gesu" is very common in the civil service
No, no, no, no, no...
The miraculous meeting with the person who used "gesu" at the end of the sentence makes Hatse finally calm down
Then the truth is revealed
This is Wednesday Downtown
Oh...
Eh?
At this point he is told about the theory
I'm sure you'll believe it
I've been talking to passers-by for so long
I really thought it was a miracle
So there are no such people after all!
It's really impossible for such people to exist
Really cheated
The next target is
Good morning, i'm Abareru
The kind of people he's looking for is...
You will be looking for people who refer to themselves strangely
Impossible
Its bingo this time
It's impossible. There is no one who calls themselves this
He is tasked with looking for specific types of people
Those who refer to themselves oddly
It starts straight away
Good morning
Whose bike is this?
It belongs to me (jibun)
To you? (jibun) What a cool bike!
Straight away he gets "jibun"
The easiest one
Next up
Favorite food?
Anything with rice
-I like seafood rice
Who likes it? Who? Who likes seafood over rice?
I (washi) like seafood over rice
I (washi)? I (washi)?
Surprisingly he finds a wild "washi"
Suddenly, a chance appears to complete the game
This is the same as an unheard of word
But for two hours after that, no other words are found
I don't think i'll find anyone who uses that word
I think i'll just be interviewing people over and over for the next four hours
That's a scary thought
As Abareru's mood is low, at this point the actors begin to appear
Togetsu Ginza is a great place!
-It's true
I'm (shousei) here to buy something...
-Eh?
What an interesting reaction
What did you just say?
Buying something...
No, not that part
Eh... who is shopping here today?
I (shousei) came here
"Shousei", that's impressive
"Shousei"... incredible
"Shousei"...
One hour later
Good afternoon. Where are you going?
Shopping
Where are you from?
Kagoshima, Kagoshima, Kagoshima
Awesome, Kagoshima!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Do you have any favorite foods like udon or soba?
Compared to soba, i'd rather have udon
Who likes Udon?
I do (oidon)
-I (oidon)!
※おいどん (oidon) is Kagoshima dialect
Is that what you usually say?
What?
-When referring to yourself
Yes, me (oidon) me (oidon)
Really?
Awesome! Feels like meeting someone from TV
I waited so long
He has no suspicions at this point
And he is one person away in three lines
Next
Excuse me
Keep going!
-Thank you, I (seshita) will
Ah... eh?
What did you just say?
What?
You just said "seshita", didn't you?
-Yes, I (seshita) did
I happen to be looking for you
What's going on?
I'm looking for someone who refers to himself as "seshita"...
Wait!
Despite the unreal situation
He does not question it
So, we end with the least possible
For whom did you buy the stuff?
For my (shin) wife
Eh, wait a minute! Eh...
Eh
How is it possible to have such a self-proclaimed person
No, wait!
Wait a second, please
For whom did you buy the stuff?
For my (shin) wife
Do you call yourself "I" (shin)?
Never heard someone say this before
Sure enough, Abareru believed them all
The truth is revealed
Did he really believe it?
What? What?
We are Wednesday Downtown
I did think the timing of "shin" was a little too perfect
But I was more happy than suspicious
The feeling of "it's finally over"?
-Yes
Then the final target is Kishi Takano's Takano
For example, there's "hair buns" here
No one does this anymore, right?
The challenge includes having to find "hair buns" and "a reverse Mohican" and "a man walking backwards"
A basically impossible game of bingo
What kind of person wears iron clogs?
This time a new element is added
Sorry sorry
Can you be on TV?
No, sorry
Got it. Sorry. It's okay
This is the most unpleasant
Hard to find
Sorry
All people have to agree to be on TV
What is this situation? Seriously
Can't use this clip?
-No
Even the people I meet...
The unwilling ones can't be used either?
These people are not normal
People are so strange nowadays
After that, we also come across someone eating oden while walking
Awesome
Sorry, I shouldn't be on TV
Sorry
This one also naturally turned down an appearance
I don't think this project can be done
Everyone is smoking like crazy!
Smoking in the Toyota HIACE
Then there is the "Abe's mask"
Who also refuses to participate
Next to appear is
What's this guy doing?
The most unlikely "person walking backwards"
Excuse me
Is it OK?
What are you doing right now?
Be suspicious!
Sorry, I can't be on TV
Can't shoot
Why's he doing this sort of thing but doesn't want to be on TV?
He's angry
Even the guy refused
Nothing achieved today
After walking for 8 hours
With barely any usable footage, the shoot ended
Can you give me one more chance?
One more day of shooting...
-Is that okay? I'm sorry
We're the ones who are sorry.
-I'm really sorry
And so it came to a second day on location
That's nice
And he wandered the shopping streets for two hours looking for non-existent people
I don't think so.
-No?
A little...
Later we came to Shinjuku where people were prepared
Standing sleeper
Sorry, sorry
Sorry
What?
We're doing a TV show. Can I interview you?
I don't think so
-That...
Can we talk for a minute?
-No
That...
What is this location bullying
May I interrupt?
-No
I'm ashamed to be on TV
Just a moment, just a moment
No, no, no
Not today, i'm not cute today
Very cute. Very cute
Nah nah nah
Really, really, really, really
-Nah nah nah nah
Super ugly
What are you saying?
So irritating
He's the worst!
Eh, this...
Little brother
-What is it?
Can we talk?
Well...just a little chat
-I can't
Like a police interrogation
It's really nice to meet you...
I'm really sorry
Just a moment... just a moment
So much useful stuff not shot
Reverse Mohican Haircut
This is it, right?
Sorry to interrupt. Sorry
Can we have a chat?
Is your hair called reverse mohawk?
-Yes, it is
We are here to do a TV show, is it ok to shoot...
I'm busy right now. Sorry
Is it okay if we talk while we walk?
I'm in a hurry.
-Walking and talking
I'm in a hurry. Sorry
Let's talk as we go...
-You're so annoying!
Pain in the ass!
That shit is unforgivable
These kids piss me off so much
That gyaru was so damn annoying
Anger at not being allowed to interview takes over
And yet he has no suspicion at all that it is a set up
So, a third day of shooting
There there!
We have a situation
Look bread, bread!
Desperately catching up with a person holding the toast
He's like a policeman
Hey, brother!
Can we have a chat?
I'm in a hurry, I don't have time, sorry
Sorry, just for a moment
I don't have time... i'm in a rush
A guy running like this probably doesn't have time to be on TV...
It's a movie!
He's too anxious
I can't catch up with this one
Unbearable...
Later
This is the 70-year-old...
Hello, Grandpa
Can we take a moment of your time to film a TV program...
I'm working now
Now you should be suspicious!
Just a moment...
Can we talk for just a moment?
The noodles will be stuck together
I'm working now
And after work...can we talk after work?
-No
No?
Because i'm working
Can you put down the delivery? We want to talk to you
I already said no!
Stop filiming!
After this also
This one?
This is too suspicious
It is not convenient to go on TV and I cannot be interviewed
Of course, he was also rejected the next time
Does your hair get tangled?
So annoying
Can you take off your mask?
It's twins...
Double mask drop
We are filming a TV show can we talk?
No
Just a moment
Forget it, don't, don't, don't
It's embarrassing
I can't get fired up
It's usually so easy for me to get fired up
It's tough to be fired up, being rejected by everyone
After 3 days of shooting, he has not a single usable clip
His mental state has also reached its limit
So, we reveal the truth
This is Wednesday Downtown
What?
We explained the project
It was all planned!?
All planned
That too?
All of them
Did you guys make these passersby say all that?
Are you kidding me? Really?
Was it all a lie?
Only the one eating oden was real
Only the one with oden?
In summary
It is difficult to find people who say "gesu" and for people to see through the prank
That was hard on him.
-3 days of hard work
A 3-day location shoot
Sure enough, they didn't expect it was all a setup
They just went along with everything
So the theory was successfully verified
Thank you
Thank you. Thank you for your hard work.
-Thank you for your hard work
New York just walked off...
New York
-New York
Do you want us to say more...
-Hamada has something to say to you.
What is it?
-There are a lot of people who say too much at the end
But you guys are going the opposite way
This is a Hamada-ism
-No, no, no
We don't want to talk too long and bore people
Such a short summary
We still need a little more, right?
It is a bit too short
But most of all, I don't want to annoy Hamada
-No
I can listen for a bit longer
What we watched was very interesting
Everyone else probably has something to say
We'll do it differently next time then
Let's welcome the next presenter
Who is it?
It's probably that...
It's Fujiwara!
Although it's nothing to do with you, since you've come out it can only mean one thing
Its that one, right?
-That's it!
Everyone has been waiting!
MONSTER LOVE has appeared!
No, no, no
Its MONSTER LOVE
I work in the same office as Kurokawa-senpai
You care about your seniors' love, right?
The last thing I want to see is seniors in love, it's disgusting
It's weird.
-Yeah, because he's weird as hell
So here's a recap
9 women that claim to like Kuro-chan have appeared
But among them are some just pretending to like him
They started to live together in Okinawa from the last episode
One held Black's hand in the aquarium, and another went to his room to kiss him
Whereas another drank with him alone to gain his favor
But so far, his record is excellent, right?
He's only eliminated the pretenders
Kuro-chan can see through the lies
Good morning
Wow, impressive!
Who cooked this breakfast?
What kind of clothes are these?
I did!
Miku did, by yourself?
I did
Very impressive
That's awesome
Ah, this omelette is heart-shaped
Mine isn't
Ah, just mine?
Only Kurokawa's is heart-shaped?
Yes
So impressive, two hearts
Delicious!
Ah, great
It's really awesome
We're eating so happily and getting along so well
I can't believe there are still liars among you
He came out with it!
You'd surely be paranoid
Sorry sorry sorry
I should just be happy with the life I have right now
Eat, eat, eat
He looks cute
Not cute at all!
No need for a drone shot
The girls footage is pretty good
A good opening, right?
Especially nice
So cute
Very cute!
This is not needed
Smelling again
He really likes to smell
What is this!?
Look!
What happened to the typhoon yesterday?
It's clearing up
This conversation is so boring!
Do you want to go to the beach?
Let's go!
Then everyone put on a swimsuit, let's go!
It's Okinawa after all
He's loving it
Awesome
Looks so happy
What the hell?
They're laughing
Save him!
No one except Miku is helping me!
So annoying!
So happy, so happy
Are you okay, Miku?
Let me help you~ yo, let me help you~
A bit too close
The pretenders must be super scared, right?
I'm here to save you
I'm gonna grab you
I am the bald sea monster
Wow, so boring
"Bald sea monster" is so boring
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
So sudden? What?
Don't stick together
Ah, wait, is this jealousy?
You can be a bit more jealous!
So close together!
I can feel the body temperature
I always want to talk to you, but everyone is very active
Take a seat
Everyone please consider if they're sincere or not
Mami, looking closer at you
You have a super small face
No, it's not.
-It is!
And beautiful.
-Thank you
I'm wondering if you really see me as a member of the opposite sex
Aren't we holding hands right now?
Can't you feel my heart beating so hard?
So disgusting
Can I lean on your shoulder?
Of course
I want to be with you all the time
Ah, so disgusting
Me too
Risa, what's wrong?
I hurt myself a bit
Eh? No way!
So I came away for a bit
Your foot?
Don't force yourself!
Thank you. Sorry. We were all having fun together
But if Risa is injured
It might as well be me getting hurt
What? What? So kind!
I'm so happy to hear that
Is your foot okay?
-Yeah
The bleeding has stopped, but it still hurts a little
I got some ice cream.
-Thanks
Is it ok to eat it?
-Please
Here I go
This is a little too natural
-She may be faking
Delicious
Too natural.
-Hamada is a bit suspicious
Super delicious
So kind, thank you for caring so much about me
Because we
Hamada is super into this
Everyone has been playing without Risa
I saw it. I saw it
But last night
You picked me first
So i've been wondering is it possible? Will you choose me again?
I was surprised when I was called...
Not only surprised, but happy and surprised at the same time
She was chosen first
I am very happy
I've told you already
Yeah, we made a deal, so I think I can trust you
What kind of expression is this?
Risa, do you really like me?
-Yes
I really like you, that's why I signed up
Yesterday, you realized someone was lying to you
So its understandable you're still suspicious at this point
But I really did come here because I like you
But i'm not sure how I can make you believe me
No, because you are the first in my heart, I chose you first yesterday
What's this expression?
The expression is so angry
So, well, I believe you
Risa also believes in you, so I hope you can trust me
Yes, it'd be weird if I couldn't
Everyone is still waiting. Let's go back
Is your foot okay?
Yeah, and the ice cream is also very good
Thank you, really
What to think...
-Indeed
I don't get it
Eh? Is she, or isn't she?
Don't know, right?
Really can't tell the difference
After playing in the sea, I'm hungry
Yeah, I'm hungry
Yeah, since we couldn't do it yesterday because of the typhoon
BBQ?
I want to BBQ
Then let's barbecue. Let's eat!
Let's eat!
Well, it's important to buy ingredients
This Kuro-chan wants to go
Please do
Ri, want to go together?
Eh, is that okay?
Is just 2 people okay?
2 is fine
-2 is better
It's a big responsibility
Yeah
Great
Here here here
Wow, it's huge!
Really pretty good
-Yeah
I'm looking forward to the barbecue!
What should we buy?
You know what to buy for BBQ, right?
Is there anything you want to eat?
-I want to eat lamb
So annoying
Let's look for it then
Ah
What's that?
Goat?
Never eaten it
It should be similar to lamb
Isn't it a bit cold?
Feeling cold?
Here we go
This girl is very direct
We bought a lot but its a pity there was no lamb
I want to eat it!
Goats?
-Goats
We bought goat meat
Were you surprised yesterday?
He's taking the initiative!
That I was in 5th place?
I thought Kuro-chan would definitely rank me #1
At first, I pretended to be a little uneasy, but I thought I was going to be first
The expression is very obvious
But you didn't call my name
Honestly, it was tough
They've had a good relationship so far
Tough?
-Yeah
I don't want you to be with other people
This is my honest opinion
What a face!
I'll say it from the bottom of my heart
You said in the previous relationships you had
That you didn't mind your partner liking others, right?
It made me think you're a very casual person
Even with those that had other girlfriends
Saying it straight!
I thought "I like him so it's okay", so I kept going out with them
I think its a bit concerning
Do women like that really exist?
So i'm unsure whether you really like me or not
What kind of tone is that?
So scary
He's talking with his mouth closed!
What just happened?
It's like he's dubbed
No, he is talking
Before...
Like ventriloquism
Even if someone has a girlfriend, I'd still want to go out with them if I like them
She's crying!
So i've been in such relationships
-No way, Richi!
But now i'm only concerned about Kuro-chan
She's good!
I only like Kuro-chan
So I also hope that Kuro-chan only likes me
She's actually crying
So I don't want to fall in love like I did before
Can I change what I said?
-Yes
So cool
I hope you don't think I'm a casual woman
Don't think such a thing again
She's a nice girl
I'm sorry to say that you are a casual woman
Kurokawa too?
Kuro-chan's also crying
This is why I always fail in love
Whenever I like a girl
I obviously like them
But because I have no self-confidence
I have no confidence in myself
I act like i'm relaxed and everything is easy
Must be lacking confidence, right?
Because there is no self-confidence, i'm always just trying
Are there really tears?
-No
So it gets worse and worse
Fake crying?
I will also change, i'm sorry
I will also change
What is this agreement?
What kind of expression is this?
Sorry
It's ready to eat, right?
Eat it, eat it
Let's eat
Delicious!
On this day also, an elmination must occur
Who will be eliminated?
It's concerning
Up to this point, these three have been proactive in building a good relationship with Kuro-chan
And on this day, Mami was alone with Kuro-chan for the first time and expressed her feelings
Mami is good
But Mina has yet to express her feelings to Kuro-chan
Who will be eliminated tonight due to not being selected by Kuro-chan?
Wow, super nervous
Thank you for waiting!
He made them wait
The 2nd day of cohabitation is coming to an end
Don't make people wait!
The person whose name is not called at the end
Will go home today
1st place is
Who is it?
While crying and talking so much...
Miku
She's not first again!
Miku is first!
Next, 2nd place is
Mami
What about Richi?
Where's Richi?
Next 3rd place is
Mina
Not good not good
Richi's in a bad spot
It was clearly agreed
They said they would change!
The remaining two have been loved by Kuro-chan since the beginning of the project
I thought these two would be safe at least
Because Risa is No.1 in my heart
I like Ri
This expression
I am so happy
I can feel the tingling of fate
I'm sorry to say you are a casual woman
Who exactly will be eliminated?
In 4th place is
Which one is it?
Richi
Alas, Risa is eliminated
Eh, why?
Today we are saying goodbye to Risa
Hamada suspected Risa, right?
Beautiful. Glamorous
To be honest, I have never been liked by such a person
And never had a good relationship either
Although you said to me "I like you"
It's a little hard to believe
Honestly, you don't really like me, do you?
I thought so, so I didn't choose you this time
By the way, do you really like me?
Does she?
I do
Eh... eh?
I signed up because I really do like you
That sucks!
Eh? Deceitful, wait wait wait
Eh? Really?
Eh? Then why...
If it's too messy here, others will...
Eh? Why?
Eh? Wait, no, it doesn't count
Richi is also crying, what does it mean?
It doesn't count, it doesn't count
You can't go back!
So, you were sincere, huh?
Well, perhaps I failed to get it across to you
Poor Risa!
It's also my fault for not making you believe me
No, no
Why... why did I suspect you
Why did I suspect you!?
You really meant what you said
-Yeah
Dating older men
All of it was true
Not a single lie
Risa liked him from the beginning
I really thought you look like an actress
Yes
I do medical-related work
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute
What have I done?
Really...
I did not believe the girl that likes me
A famous quote
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry
Someone liked me, someone liked me
You expressed your feelings to me properly. I'm sorry
He's gotten super excited all of a sudden
I'm really sorry
A soon-to-be famous scene!
I'm really happy, either way
It's been fun to date
A bit sad, right?
I can't do this
Because maybe only Risa is sincere!
True
Indeed
I suspected you
Not sure about the mood of the other people there watching this
It's beyond saving
Yes, it's hopeless
Although I couldn't make Risa happy
I hope you'll be happy!
Okay, see you next time
She will
-Don't make it sound like you've been in a relationship
I don't want to part so soon
We probably can't see each other again soon
I'm really sorry
Really, thank you
Richi is crying!
Can I shake your hand?
Handshake
Thank you
I didn't expect to be able to meet you after I signed up, but I'm glad
So you really like him!?
Thank you
I am the one who should be thanking you
Once you let go, you're going home?
Aren't you the one sending her home?
It's his fault
I hope we can meet again
Really, thank you
I'm sorry. Thank you
Do you best
Goodbye
Thank you everyone
A big scene!
Really crying
Tears are flowing
-Snot is coming out
What is this?
Please consider the mood of the remaining people
What is this...
Why did I eliminate her?
Don't react too much here
What's going on here!
It's your own fault!
STAFF!
Is there anyone else besides Risa!?
Is there really a girl who likes me still left?
Yes
Great! Great!
The worst!
What?
Everyone is listening
A bad guy
-Changes so easily
It's like a bug
I was distraught, apologies
Psycho!
I'm sorry, I'm a disgraceful man
But now I've become stronger too
Let's continue happily
So annoying
Risa really liked him
I even suspected her.
-Hamada was suspicious
It was too smooth and natural so you though it was fake
What do you think now?
-I'm sorry
What are you sorry about, you weren't tricked
-Not tricked
I should say, you are super into watching this!
I'm not!
Probably the most into it out of everyone
At first he was watching like this, but later like this!
He's taking notes
It was really messy, especially with everyone watching
Yes, yes, everyone is watching
Even if they liked him to begin with they may hate him now
They might become disinterested
Miku ranked first again
Yeah
-He especially likes her, right?
Then shouldn't Miku be guaranteed last place?
-She's not a racehorse
It's not like betting on a horse
Miku's gate
Horserace woman
She's not a horserace woman
There's more to watch, so let's take a look
He eliminated her because he thought there's surely no way she actually likes him
-Yeah
Kurokawa's weakness is his lack of self-confidence
Where is this place?
Looks Frieza sitting in that chair
Kuro-chan, can we talk now?
-Ah, Ri
Are you free now?
-I'm free!
Can I sit down?
You can't sleep either?
Must have something to say!
Yeah
She's angry!
I'm very concerned about the results announced today
For sure!
Announced results?
I am 4th place...
Boss!
She wants to ask
Rather than the sadness of not being called
That Kuro-chan lied to me is the most shocking
So I came to ask
A low ranking
That... I'm sorry, Ri
I would have liked to put you at number 1 too
But
Intentionally...
On purpose?
I did it on purpose
What?
At the octopus party
When I blew, you said, "It stinks, it stinks"
It's here.
-Yes she did
When she closed her eyes
It stinks!
Feels so smelly, so smelly
What did you mean by that?
I originally thought you were saying that to just make things more lively
So I thought "Ri so interesting"
You've said it in private too, right?
Did you say it?
In private?
At the time I though it's okay because it was funny
But I heard that you also said my mouth stinks in private
What kind of conversation is this?
The other girls said that?
-Yes
Someone just now...
Talking about "if your mouth stinks, it's a bit..."
Richi?
If I say it, I will become a traitor, so I can not say
Eh~
It's a bit of a shock
But it's not really bad
So many different channels
When talking to others
I was referring to after you'd eaten wasabi
So it probably smelt a bit because of that
But usually when you talk, it doesn't stink at all
The BGM and the conversation doesn't match at all
This content should not be said in such an atmosphere
That's right, I don't stink, right?
Not smelly
Because you were saying this stuff about me
What a boring conversation.
-What the heck?
I've been very concerned
The theme has become bad breath
I'll say it straight, right?
For example, when we went shopping
I didn't know how to bring it up
This should be said while laughing
People would usually burst out laughing while talking about this
But I really don't think it stinks
I said "stink" just to make things more lively
They've talked about this topic for so long already
Actually, I don't think it stinks
So now I "ha", i'll blow on you
Again?
Can you smell it?
Ok
Ah, are you unsure?
No
It's fine
"Yes?" If you say "yes", then does that mean you didn't say anything bad?
No, I didn't
Really?
Hope she says it stinks
Then i'll blow
Say it!
Not smelly
It must stink!
It stinks, it sounds like it does
You're holding your breath, aren't you?
No
Really?
-Yeah
Then I'll do it again.
-Ok
You don't need to
-What is this!?
No need no need!
It must stink!
Her face is distorted
Not smelly
It must stink.
-Don't force yourself!
Really?
Not smelly
1 more time
The third time
Her expression!
-She stiffened up
Close your eyes
Whoa that's surprising!
Terrible, terrible.
-She did it!?
This is terrible!
Finally!
Proof that it doesn't stink
Don't say it like it's evidence of "I love you"
This expression
Great expression!
Sorry!
So fast! So fast!
Amnesia immediately after a kiss
To prove that it doesn't stink, you kissed me?
What kind of evidence is that?
Yes
Like "did you just kiss me?"
I'm sorry I suspected you
So, I hope you can trust me
Can this be true?
I really mean it
Did she overdo it?
Is it or not?
Ah, Richi
Not good not good
Don't touch her!
Sorry!
You said it already!
I won't do anything weird starting tomorrow
I believe in Kuro-chan
And I hope you can trust me
Look at Kurokawa's expression
A terrible face
I'm going back
An incredible scene!
It has been a long time since someone kissed me on the lips
Disgusting
Scared the hell out of me
So, that's it, what does everyone think?
So disgusting!
"Did you just kiss me?"
Nagashima's "Want to join my team?
※A line from Shigeo Nagashima's SECOM commercial
SECOM's "Want to join my baseball team?"
No intonation
Let's get a female perspective, what do you think?
Saying "doesn't stink" doesn't necessarily mean "love"
-That's right
For a woman to be able to say "it stinks" could also be a form of love
But Richi is a fake though, right?
Do you think so?
-I think so
But Hamada can also guess wrong
I didn't guess it at all!
Following Hamada's bets is a sure-fire way to lose
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03