Welcome to Wednesday Downtown
Let's get on with our first presenter please
Who is it?
It's Ozwald
It's a shame about M-1.
-Don't do that
How unlucky
The qualifiers have not yet competed
Think about your position before you speak
It will have an impact
Anyway, this is the second edition of a previously tested theory
It is this
The 2nd As long as you say something bad in a positive way, a person won't lose their temper
This is interesting
The last validation results were very successful
Very successful
None of them lost their temper
Kowagata was clearly on the verge of fury
How would everyone else react?
It also depends on who it is, right?
What is it like? Can you show us?
Me? Okay
Say something to Hamada
Hamada, you've become an old man, but in a good way
Its positive
That's too mild
It's not easy to get angry when you say it's positive
I admire him
It's a bit subtle
The first person to make bad comments is...
Minamikawa
Mr. Bad Words
His target is
Not good
-It's a little dangerous
Panzetta Girolamo
Girolamo
He'll be beaten up, right?
Didn't he come close... to straight up hitting someone on this show?
Already scared
Really super scary
A famous quote now
Why are you fighting?
Shut up!
Who, me?
You've ruined the image of Italians in the minds of Japanese people!
Do you wanna smack?
Super quick
"Do you wanna smack?"
This time, Girolamo is told to wait for a fake show
3 bad "positive" lines have been prepared in advance
The first is
Tawdry
He's not really tawdry
This is sure to piss him off
I don't know what the tipping point is, though
This would be... weird, right?
Can bad words be invalidated by saying them positively?
I really need to ask for more advice today
You wife is angry?
You know?
Everyone's talking about it
My wife? Please don't do that
No no
You are always very positive
Is there a time when you are not so energetic?
Down?
Is it possible for you to get depressed?
Not really
Everyone has their bad days
But I can get back to normal pretty quickly
Ah, a quick recovery
But overall your mood is very high
High but also calm
Ah, so a positive tawdriness
Tawdry?
Well, it's actually positive
Immediately caught on
Scary!
Especially positive
Me?
-I mean...
You get along well with everyone around you
You seem to get along well with everyone
But that's not the right word to use, is it? Tawdry?
No, no, that...
Don't they say that in Italy?
The popular type
Oh... right
-Yes, yes, yes.
I think being positively tawdry is good
I still think your Japanese is wrong
No, no, really
It's positive!
Tawdry in a positive sense...
Although being slightly concerned about the use of "tawdry"
He's not technically angry, so this is deemed a pass
The second is
Lame clothes
No, no, no, no
This is what he makes his living on, right?
This sentence is something that will hurt his pride the most, right?
And the words just now are still fresh in the mind
You have a lot of clothes, right?
I have a lot, but I also give a lot away
You often see this type of pattern right?
This style is quite common
I've always liked this type
Your clothes are really lame in a good way
Huh?
No one's perfect, right?
Every man will be teased at some point
Oh, maybe...
Not in a good mood anymore
Not good
Can't stop!
Finally quiet
Am I talking too much?
No, I love to talk too
Especially when waiting
It's easy to talk to friendly people
But its the first time we've met
So I don't have that much to say
It's quite rare
As he says "this is the first time we've met"
Girolamo's anger is beginning to seep out
In light of the dangerous atmosphere
Minamikawa retreats momentarily
So annoying
Holding back
He's already angry, right?
Angry
Just us two?
Yeah, you two
-Ah
He's a weird guy
Kind of want to punch him
There we go!
Straight to the point
Ultimately, he returns to Girolamo, who can't wait to get his hands on him
To deliver the final blow
Scary
I don't dare to watch
How often do you return to Italy?
Before covid I went back all the time
I haven't got back since it started
But I finally went back to Italy in July this year
Although still because of work
You have a lot of friends back in Italy, right?
Of course, but there is no way to see everyone
Are you waiting to hit someone?
Can't see them all
It's like I thought, Girolamo
Don't say it
You've not gone back at all
Me?
-Yeah
Because...
Italy is ashamed of you, in a good way
The news?
What?
-What do you mean, Italy what?
It's a good thing
Me?
-For Italy
They want me out?
But in a positive sense
That's why...
How to say
Your efforts in Japan have made you lose support
Why do you think so?
That is to say
This is simply getting angry
Your... persona and so on
This would make you angry
I haven't been banned from the country
I was actually awarded a medal by the government
As a compliment
-The president gave it to me
From the president? That's impressive
Have you ever been beaten up before?
Eh, what?
What a question to ask...
Before he strikes, the truth is revealed here
Can this be considered a success?
We are Wednesday Downtown
Ah...
Did you notice anything strange?
Him, right?
I may have reacted if he said anything more
Beat-beat-beat me up?
-I wouldn't beat you up
I might just kick off, though
What a joke!
The next challenger is
Onigoe Tomahawk's Sakai
His target is
Actress Tono Nagiko
Have you worked together?
-No
Recently, it seems that she is a regular commentator
So i'm a bit nervous
The first line is
Emotionally unstable
No one would say such a thing
Positive emotional instability?
It's terrible
What will happen?
In the car
It's even scarier in tight places
I watched "Suzuran" when I was in middle school
※A 1999 NHK progam in which Tono appeared
Oh really?
I was just 13 years old at the time
Really? I'm happy
I'm a bit nervous
I still have an impression of Tono-san from that time
I've changed a lot..
It'd be strange not to
You say you've changed...
But compared to the past, how to put it
There's positive emotional instability, right?
All the emotions are on display
I didn't have much opportunity to show that side before
Indeed, only through acting is it possible
Yeah, it's just an act
So nothing has changed in terms of the emotional instability
In regard to this, she understands herself well
The first level is passed easily
The 2nd line is
Can't have a normal conversation
This is no good
I still have to talk to her
Set up the conversation
Tono, you're not...
In a good way, you can't have a normal conversation
What?
-It's not...
A good conversation
In a good way...
-I don't know what we'll talk about
It's like playing catch
I threw the ball but I don't know if you'll throw it back to me, there's this sense of tension
As a comedian, I think its very interesting
How to say...
Well rounded
Does it confuse you?
-No
Not confused
It's more of an immersive contrast
So its good?
-Yeah, it's great
This has to be reexamined
Despite some sparks, the second level is also passed
The last line is...
Comedy and stuff...do you watch it?
-I love it
Disregarding people's feelings, who do you like best?
Recently the thing I have to watch before bed is...
Well, in terms of comedians
Isn't the senior and junior relationship important?
No no
How the relationship is, etc
Don't worry about it
But I want to hear people say they like an actress I really hate
My expression is obvious
You'll think, "Seriously!?"
Do you have an actress you hate?
-Loads!
Like who?
As soon as they appear, I change the channel immediately
Something is happening
Can you tell me?
A very big name
I won't talk about nobodies
Although you are a big name artist
Yes
As an actress, you don't act much in film and television anymore, in a good way
Not good
Me?
-Yes
I'm in a stage play though
Ah, you acted in a stage play?
Ah, that's...
I feel like your strengths lie more in morning variety
This... I don't think so
Comedians can sometimes be kind of dangerous
So sometimes I can act help but act like that
That's pretty impressive
Your eyes are too serious...
Scary...no it's not okay
-Scary?
Not at all. You are beautiful
What's wrong? What are you trying to say?
Nothing
Have you been to Musashi Koyama?
No, I'm looking forward to it
It's too raw
A reluctant diversion from the subject
And the truth is revealed
This location shoot is fake
The show is Wednesday Downtown
-I knew it
I lost a friend once to Wednesday Downtown
This time I gained a friend
How to say it
Let's call it even.
-Scary scary scary
The final challenger is
Unagi
The target is
Honkon
No one wants to do this
What are you talking about?
It's too dangerous.
-Dangerous?
He gets angry even if you don't say anything bad about him
With me
Getting by can be tough sometimes
I just eat bento at Lumine
He said, "Don't eat a bento!"
The first bad thing to say is...
Your appearance and heart are the same
Indeed
His appearance and heart are the same
Like... like a monster
We didn't ask you to say to this extent
-No, you didn't
This meeting seems fun
He has recently opened an SNS and been ranting continuously
An off-balance Honkon
What will happen?
Positive mood gloom and doom
You've been getting a lot of commentary work
Just one as a commentator
Really?
-And...
Listening to the experts talk
Then they said that Japan is now very strange, so I also started doing some research
Now I'm starting to think it is weird
This is what you've been interested in recently?
You could say its become an addiction, even though its part of the job
But you've become interested
-I've become serious about it
I want to be complimented
So i've been studying
The good thing about you is your appearance and heart are the same
What do you mean, appearance and heart?
Well... how do I put it?
Noone has ever said anything good about my appearance
They always say "looks dirty"
I'm dirty from inside out
You're too weird!
Most say my appearance and heart are the complete opposite!
Still consistent... but in a positive sense
No, no, no
Most say "you're manly on the inside"
You're too weird
Just... appearance
Even if the exterior is dirty
You know...
People always ask "do you know"? Of course I do!
He's so moody
It's positive
Right?
No, the younger generation certainly wouldn't say it
What're you talking about?
They surely wouldn't say it to your face
You just said it, you said it
I think this is positive
Regardless of the inner self, a clear sense of patience pervades in terms of the subject of ugly looks
Not much anger
Second is...
Honkon, you...
Aren't you pretty harsh about being late?
What happened with that one, Ito of Ozwald
Don't involve me!
Taking up other people's time
Indeed, they should be scolded
And then chattering incessantly, of course i'd be angry
Do you think it's okay for an attending physician to be late to the operating table?
Of course not
Bullet train operators, what if they're late?
You'd be angry
Impossible not to be
It's definitely a bad thing
That's for sure
Honkon is the one
That is positively hated by all young artists
That's bad!
Really? I don't really care
It sounds like Ito hates him
Hated by young artists
Don't mention me!
And is everyone serious?
Indeed... seriously
Please don't think it was me that said it
There are times when I hate you
Saying "I can be annoying at times"
I also have people I like and people I hate
Do you know what it is? The thing that everyone hates
Even if people hate me, I still have rice to eat, so it doesn't matter
Not everything is about making friends
Otherwise there's no sense of tension, it makes things boring
Really, a little more tension
What a big name artist!
As the conversation is heating up, its time for the final line
Political-related statements are irrelevant
This is too deadly
This is bad
What do you think?
I meant to...
I do think they're wrong
Here's also gonna see this bit
What will happen?
I feel that Honkon is a very hot-blooded person
And you're very concerned about politics, right?
You guys think too little, its not all just about comedy
You can do that because its peaceful
I always hear your political statements
I think, in a good way, your political statements are irrelevant
What do you mean by "in a good way"?
If you don't know what you're doing, you don't know what you're doing
No, that's positive too
It's not relevant but it does a good job of livening up the show
I'm out of touch? Have you watched me?
Yes, one time...
-For example?
I can't really given an example
Can't even give an example
And you say I'm out of touch, that's not good!
You're being so vague
After all, it is positive
What's positive...that's not how to use "positive"
It means that although it is not right to say
It still makes the show very lively
Is it your intention to go in that direction?
-Which one?
Politics?
-Yes
No, it's part of the job
But I'm worried about Japan
Is there anything you want to change?
-There are too many things
Honestly speaking
This country is really in trouble
Is that so?
-Of course
So, you'll change...?
Of course it is to do what you can, and you don't
That's when it's positive. Get involved in some political activities
Do you think that by talking more about politics you'll get less work?
Yeah, I guess...
-Right?
You say this... then don't pay taxes
But in a positive sense
What "positive", you're pissing me off!
Do you think you can be forgiven for saying anything by adding "positive" to it?
No, I really don't think so
Straight up said it
In light of Honkon's comment, the truth is revealed herre
What are you doing?
This is Wednesday Downtown
Honkon was smiling from the moment he came in
Did something good happening?
-Nothing good
Do you really have such a bad impression of me?
I don't usually lose my temper
You are not the same on the outside as you are on the inside
In summary
No one was too angry (in a good way)
I see
What do you think?
Ah, i'm tingling
Girolamo was really angry, right?
When the person came in
He may have hit him, but it was edited out
Must have beaten someone up
It's true though, Minamikawa is really annoying
His expressions and so on, and his glasses
-Yes, yes
Don't say "positive" after that
Change it to say "I don't think so though"
Pretty good
But then they'll ask "so who said it?"
It makes no difference
Let’s welcome our next presenter please
Anyone there?
There is, there is
It's Fujiwara!
So, this is not a theory
But the project everyone has been waiting for
Please take a look
MONSTER LOVE
It's here!
It's here
There are also many people who hate this project!
No, no, no, the streets are calling it "MONLOVE" "MONLOVE"
It's not that popular!
So, have you all watched it?
Yes
-It's disgusting
In a "People I don't want to be hugged by" ranking, Kuro-chan was 3rd and I was 4th
Just one place difference?
Super close!
He's actually doing things wrong
But i'm just one place away from him!
It's about the same level
I live my life so carefully
What a sad story
So, a brief review of what has happened so far
Kuro has been living in Okinawa with some women who like him and some pretending to like him
Last week, Mami, a pretender, was eliminated
And it was revealed in the post-interview that those pretending to like Kuro-chan are doing so in the hopes of debuting as idols
Aspiring idols
That's why they were crying!
Then the cookies baked by Miku were smashed to pieces
The "cookie incident"
It wasn't that big of an event
The culprit was Kuro-chan himself
He's the worst
Is it really possible to broadcast that part on TV?
People may think that being a psychopath is appealing
It's the first time i've seen such a disgusting psychopath
Purebred psycho
Its surprising he can still be on TV
Okay, now these three are left
Richi, Miku and Mina
Let me ask, who do you like, Tanaka?
Eh?
Of these people?
Which one is your type
Mina
Disgusting
You're the one who asked!
Amazing!
Super beautiful!
3 people
There are only 3 people
Where's the other one?
A nice location
It's so hot today!
I'm really sorry about the cookie incident yesterday
I am the one most likely to be suspected
Because i've always been jealous
Now i'll be suspected again
And Kuro-chan will protect Miku
What a face!
I also think it was Miku that broke them
He did it!
That's why I said Miku
It's okay
No matter who did it, and why
I don't care at all
Being suspicious of others
It makes you feel sad
I don't want that
That's all
So I don't care who broke it
Good girl
It feels like a long time has passed and there are so many less people now
Its coming to an end soon...
I have this feeling
3 people, so scary
But a 3-person idol group is quite rare, isn't it?
Very few indeed
The last selected, will they have a solo debut?
Oh, is it like that?
But there are also people that like Kuro-chan
Didn't Kuro-chan say he wouldn't go out with an idol?
He did say that
Still can't tell
What will happen in the end...
There should be no lies here, right?
The opening is important
Everyone looks like an idol
So disgusting
Disgusting
Super beautiful
Ah, i'm so happy
Wait a sec
Everyone wasn't here earlier, right?
We went to a private beach together
Eh, private... the beach?
The beach
Eh? So cunning!
Leaving me behind?
Its nice for it to be just 3 sometimes
Yeah, it was fun
Super fun
But with me it'd be way more fun, ah, so cunning~
He's so annoying
-Really disgusting
Such a shock
Feel so tanned
I wore sunscreen
Put it on twice
Did you get a tan?
Eh?
Eh? Why? Why? Watanabe? What...what's wrong?
Eh, why?
Eh, what?
Yes, only Kuro-chan doesn't know
Hello
Oh, hello
Please take a seat
No, wait a minute. Wait a minute. Why are you here?
Eh? Wait a minute, why?
You have nothing to do with this project, right?
This isn't MONSTER IDOL
Eh? Why are you in Okinawa?
I have an announcement to make
It's not a coincidence?
I know you're here filming
There is an announcement to make
Congratulations to you all
You three will debut as an idol group
Congratulations
Eh? What's going on? What the hell?
Everyone?
Eh? What's Watanabe talking about? Wait, what's this?
What? Aren't I looking for a girlfriend?
What? I don't get it
Panic attack
No, actually, its not about liking Kuro-chan
It's about wanting to become an idol
Eh...
Wait, I don't understand, ah, too sudden
There's nothing funny about it!
What is this?
They can be idols if they remain?
Yes, the only criterion is to capture the heart of Kuro-chan
Thus, these 3 people have qualified for the idol debut
Ah, it has been confirmed
Hey, what about the ones who really like Kuro-chan?
Hey, wait, so, hey?
Does that mean there is no girl who likes me among these 3 people?
There's one left
One more?
Hey, wait, that... wait!
If she's my girlfriend, why will she still be allowed to make her debut as an idol?
Eh?
What do you think you are saying?
No, not my girlfriend...
That, that...
No, I really don't get it!
What the hell is this?
Hey...
Hysterical Kuro-chan
So this is the motivation behind it all...
He's realized
That's why people were crying
I don't understand it
There is 1 person who really likes Kuro-chan
1 person left
It seems that after this cohabitation
She has also come to think it could be good to try to be an idol too
No. Don't decide for yourself
If you stay until the end, do you want debut as an idol?
I will consider it
Finally, they agreed to debut as an idol
So, despite the inclusion of a potential girlfriend for Kuro-chan
These 3 will tentatively debut as idols
So I would like to ask Kuro-chan
Please decide on the name of the idol group and write lyrics for their song
I got confused
Because I was very "angry"
Like a volcano or something
Although Kuro-chan is very angry, this is still a love project after all...
So it is still mainly about Kuro-chan's love
Please return to Tokyo for a date
Then you will decide to choose who to confess to
What an expression
Hey...wait, wait, wait a minute!
I'm looking for a girlfriend...
But they became an idol group
So I have to find the girl who really likes me to date?
So hard to understand
Eh...
That's lucky
Scary!
Even if you don't like me, it's nice to pretend to like me
Only 1 person? Only 1 person?
Is there really only 1 left?
Hey
Suddenly saying there's just one person, i'm a little surprised
Indeed
So that's it
There are 2 people who do not really like Kuro-chan
That sucks!
Although the idol debut is confirmed
So please hold on until the end
Please continue to cheat Kuro-Chan
Ok
Such a loud response
This isn't what being an idol's about!
So, the cohabitation life in Okinawa ended
And Kuro-chan returned to Tokyo
Coming
Good morning
Good morning. Eh, what is it?
I want to see if you are composing lyrics
The color of his vest is really nasty
I'm not slacking off!
Immediately began work as an idol producer
So messy!
A different feeling
I challenged myself to do something new
It's not a typical approach?
It's a little different
Although it's an idol, it's not the "cute" kind of "likable"
"Cool"
Cool?
Quite serious consideration
This kind of vibe could be cool
A feeling of distinct colors, right?
He is responsible for BiSH's clothing
This time they are different from the previous style, right?
How can I say it? If I don't flip 360 degrees and think
Then its tough to come up with anything
If you flip it 360 degrees, wouldn't it be back to the original place?
Well, let's listen to it first
Ok
That's right. This time, Black wrote the lyrics for their debut song
It is the opening song of MONSTER LOVE
It's good, it's connected
I have written a lot
I'll write it out first
Yes, please
Watanabe, do you have any thoughts?
"The bond that can't be returned, the bond that can't be broken"
This
Miku made cookies
Then I broke them
You broke the cookies she made for you?
At that time, it became a total battlefield
It's all your fault!
What is "old man got up and became an old woman"?
I was surprised to be cheated
Thought everyone liked me
It was as surprising as a sudden change of gender
Very profound
Yes, it's very profound
I think it is very good
Watanabe, it's done!
It's done!
Full marks
You put all those memories to use
This will make me be liked even more, right?
There is 1 person who will
Kuro-chan also had the important duty of deciding on the group's name
The name is very important
Wrote a lot
I have written a lot
Thinking about these
This is very different from "Mameshiba no Taigun"
Bearslayer
Yes, completely different
Leaning more towards the cool type
Electricity, gas and water
Oh you noticed that one?
Because it's a threesome
It is very straightforward, 3 essential things in life
"Escaped Pineapple"
Used the pineapple, which is trendy, and put a sad spin on it
"Full of Sorrow?"
"Escaped Spinach"
Bearslayer
This is Willie Williams
※Karate fighter born in the Jukushin Kaikan with the name "Bearslayer"
Eh?
Willie Williams
Who would know that?
Don't you know? "Bearslayer"?
Why do you want to give them this name?
Let People Drink Sardine Water
Give them a drink when they're dying and they'll be saved
Is "Strawberry Honeydew Daifuku" a honeydew melon Daifuku?
No, it's not
Although it is strawberry Daifuku
The taste of honeydew melon is unexpected
What does it mean?
I see
What is "Father's Return"
This is a telegram
So that's it...
It should be quite touching, right?
It has meaning
Not touched?
No...
How to put it? Choosing from these names...?
No, to be honest, although I thought of a lot
I'm trying to think of more
More?
Please do
Most aren't doable
Despite thinking so many
Oh, it's been a long time.
-Long time no see
How do you feel after reading the lyrics?
Feels very fashionable
Not really like Kuro-chan
Not alike at all
Let me be clear, I'm not in love mode right now
Fully in producer mode
You see me
There may be feelings such as "I like you," "I love you," and "I'm finally at ease"
No, it's not
But when recording songs, you need to be professional
Be sure to go for it!
Ok
First of all, please let me listen to the original and unprocessed song
I get it
Good
Thank you
And so, the trio's first recording session ended successfully
They have good personalities and different voices
I'm sorry... I'm really surprised
I thought it would be random trash, I didn't expect it to be anything like that
So rude!
Great singing!
What makes you qualified to say that?
In addition
Ok
You're done?
-Yes
Little embarrassing...
Their costumes!
So cute
Superb!
Feel stronger
Feel stronger?
-Yes
Do you know what the theme of the outfit is?
A hero?
-Like a hero
Feeling able to fight
This time when designing clothes I thought of a "mini 4WD"
Why?
Mini four-wheel drive?
Mini 4WD...
Wait wait wait
You don't like it much?
No, I like it
So, wear these outfits and go for it!
Ok
So, this is the group name
Here we go
What is it gonna be?
"Mameshiba" is the cute type
But for your three I chose a trendier name
Looking forward to it
So exciting. What is it?
The group name is...
Somewhere in the City
Really?
Wait wait wait, did I hear it properly? What does it mean?
What did you say?
-Please say it again
Eh, you didn't you hear me?
Somewhere in the city?
Heard it
Yes, the group name is "Somewhere in the City"
You thought about it seriously, right?
They hate it
Of course
Although I thought up many names with places in them
"Somewhere in the City" can appeal to people from everywhere
So that's the meaning of "Somewhere in the City"
But only within the area of Tokyo
Although you say that everywhere
Eh...
If you don't like it, do you want to change it?
I also hesitated whether or not I should choose another one
What is it?
The other one is
"Eating Too Much Osaka"
Why do they all have place names?
Based in Osaka?
No, it's not based in Osaka, but it's easy to pronounce
So Mina, you think "Somewhere in the City" is better?
It's better
Then it's "Somewhere in the City"
Its decided
Also had "Tokyo Incident"
So, the name has been decided, and the costume has been decided
Don't compare them!
Let's gather around!
Ok
Here we go
Where are you going?
Somewhere in the City
Where?
Decided!
Not very exciting
1 more time?
In this way, the second idol group "Somewhere in the City" is born with Kuro-chan as the advisor
So, now, Kuro-chan's search for love is coming to an end
Miku
Where will his romance go from here?
Although i'm humiliated
Here we go again
Please go out with me
Please
I see
The idol group "Somewhere in the City", with Kuro-chan as the advisor, is born
I thought I would see more disgusting antics, but suddenly he became a producer
I'm very angry, I don't want to see that side of him
Wanna see his disgusting side
Show me a guy who is more disgusting than me
Nausea is less, and the love is less
I shouldn't have come
But the final scene was quite shocking
A close hug!
The next episode preview
It's very shocking
Who is lying?
Richi has been aggressive
She must want to be an idol.
-Definitely an idol
Richi wants to be an idol
The recording also reveals a personality of a very skilled person
Mina is not very active
Not very aggressive
You see
He's really surprisingly into it
Despite all the complaints
-Watching super seriously
Watching super seriously
Did you hear that? Can't take his eyes off the video.
-No, no, no
If you like MONSTER LOVE so much, just say it!
What do you think the song title is?
Could it be...
Cookie Incident?
The title of the song is "Cookie"
Guessed it!
Somewhere in the City's Cookie
Yes, Somewhere in the City's Cookie
So, you're wondering what kind of song it is, right?
-Can we listen to it?
Please have a listen to "Cookie" by Somewhere in the City
The theme of this song is falling in love
The 3 of them, I don't think they are that typical cute idol type
So I chose a cool and fashionable style
Please show your personality
Peeking into the cave, there's treasure
Great voice
Don't want a love song that ends in tragedy
Cute
Spent sleepless nights
Good voice too
Bound by the halo of angels
Why did you like it?
So addictive!
Mina is the most innocent
Don't cry
Whenever
A broken bond that will not be restored
The intersection of possibility and I love you
Forget the CPAP
Lovesickness
This is the first piece of honesty
The inability to weigh the trafficked
Escape in the display
Whenever
Good song
Now lets listen
To two members of BiSH
They all sound very good
They have a very good sense of balance
And I don't want any of them to become Kuro-chan's girlfriend
Why do you say such things?
It's a waste
These three people came together by chance
But they are very well matched and are totally idols
They've become idols
The old man and the old woman, Watanabe praised that line, but I really hate it
Luckily, it wasn't put in
Maybe it's in the second verse
Yeah true, this is the first verse
Yes
Such a bad line
I hate that line!
So, the CD of this song will be available at CD stores nationwide tomorrow, December 15
So fast!
And it will be available on all major music streaming platforms from 12pm tonight
Please do go and listen to it!
Awesome
The music video will also be released 11pm tonight
Please go watch it.
-Somewhere in the City, so confusing
That's great. People don't know it's them, right?
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03