Welcome to Wednesday Downtown
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
It's Savannah's Takahashi!
Savannah!
-It's not Savannah's combo debut
Yagi's been completely abandoned
-No no no
It's just me this time
So, today is a special episode
Today is just one project
First of all, please read this
Have you heard of K. Kazumi...?
K. Kazumi…
A huge body that is even taller than a vending machine
That big?
Height at that time was 213.3cm
Compared to April of this year, I've grown 1cm taller.
Height 2m and 13cm
At the time?
Weight 222kg
Weight is increasing
Now wearing 33.5cm
The size of the foot is 33.5cm
These images were posted online by an unidentified woman who calls herself K. Kazumi
However, her physique is not the only surprising thing
She also has the ability to squeeze a frying pan flat
And the strength to rip a pack of playing cards
I eat nine meals a day
The size of her intake is also shocking
Compared to an appetite king artist, she achieved an overwhelming record with 3.5 times the amount of food
But this K. Kazumi has not yet appeared in media
And has been on just Yahoo for over a decade
At some point, she became known as an urban legend woman in a small area
In Musashi Kosugi, there is a woman who is about the same size as K. Kazumi
There is also eyewitness information
In the convenience store there was a woman about 2 meters tall and weighing about 160 kg
Could it be K. Kazumi?
Despite a lot of eyewitness information
Seems unlikely
Occasionally some people believe it
I think this monster is just made up
There is also the view that this might just be an urban legend
In recent years, there has been a heated debate between the "existence and non-existence" factions
But tonight, the controversy over this K. Kazumi will come to an end
Really?
Can the human body really eat that much in one meal? It's incredible
If its actually possible, I think they could win the Olympic gold medal in weightlifting
After half a year of investigation and tracking, we are finally able to reveal the true identity of the legendary K. Kazumi
K. Kazumi-san will be on set soon.
-Then let's shoot
K. Kazumi's real face is...?
Have you heard of such a person?
Nope
- Me neither
I've never heard of them at all
- I know a little bit about it
You've heard?
-It's a frequent topic of discussion on websites
So, tonight is the hour of K. Kazumi's reveal
You're gonna put an end to it, right?
This is it
Whether they exist or not
-Yes, this is the debate
First of all, please take a look at this VTR
The body type is rumored to be 2m 13cm
Super big
Weight 222kg
Who took this photo?
-Yeah
This is supposedly the only photo that exists of this person
Uploaded themselves?
To prevent other people of enormous size from being called K. Kazumi in the street
They shared this photo so there's a distinction
I see
Although uploaded
In order not to be recognized, they used a mosaic
Kaz knows this person, right? Heard anything about her?
It's quite famous on SNS and makes waves every once in a while
Questions will also sometimes be answered on Yahoo
So, do you think this K. Kazumi exists?
If you're doing this then... I guess so?
So, let's put this to rest today
First of all, let's go over K. Kazumi's huge size and strange power
Please take a look
The Legend of K. Kazumi
At this point, as all we have to go on
Is the Yahoo account
Introducing their amazing body
As the account claims she resembles Nankai Candy's Shizu-chan
We asked Shizu-chan to do the voiceover for K. Kazumi's speech
Voice: Shizuyo
K. Kazumi's three main characteristics are firstly, her huge size, which has been specified
In 2017, she commented about changes in her height
In senior year she was 184cm and increased in height every year after
So tall
Finally exceeded 2m at the age of 32
Pregnant with your second child?
- Pregnant?
Now, five years after the 2017 submission
The height of K. Kazumi, 38, is
Had my height measured at the hospital I always go to, and my height was 213.3cm
Still growing?
So, she grew by about 10cm
And according to the uploaded physical examination form, her weight was 222.6kg
The name is there, too
Yes, the name is listed
The weight exceeds that of this sumo wrestler
K. Kazumi, a woman with an unconventional body type
If this is true...
Therefore, there are many inconveniences in her daily life
There are occasionally such people overseas, right?
My waist and hips and thighs are too big
So I can't wear commercially-available products, I even have to order special underwear
Really big
I've cracked the toilet seat several times, and even the entire toilet bowl
Although its embarrassing, I had to get a toilet for sumo wrestlers installed
Most commercially available products are an unsuitable size, making for great inconvenience
The next are K. Kazumi's superhuman characteristics
Pulled the hoop off
K. Kazumi is not only large but also has strength far beyond that of ordinary people
Pulled it down...
Is this possible?
With a little effort, I can easily tear up a pile of 54 cards
Is this a manga?
Grip strength like a character in a manga
It's like Kaoru Hanayama
This frying pan was also flattened by me, I took a picture before and after
Scary
And then there is this pot lid
Scrunched up
It is no longer possible to see what it was before
We sought the advice from the person with the highest wrist strength in the country
Super heavyweight fitness competitor Taisan Shimizu
Have you heard of K. Kazumi?
I've seen a little picture on Twitter
I heard that there is such a person of huge size
About K. Kazumi, she seems to possess strange powers
Such as being able to flatten a wok
She's a monster!
That's impossible. And this is a woman, right?
Although I have seen some of the strongest women
Such people do not exist
If she exists, she's likely to be the world's strongest
Its impossible
The next VTR is
A recreation of K. Kazumi's strange powers as detailed on Yahoo
It was about 20 years ago
Student days
When K. Kazumi was a college student
I'm looking forward to the sleepover, Kazumi
I'm hungry.
-Didn't you just eat?
(Yoneda2000 Love)
Don't do that
On this day, Kazumi came to the guy for her club activity
After entering the sports warehouse of this arena, I found an old instrument for measuring back muscles
The female members half-jokingly measured their back muscle strength values
Impossible!
-It's only 50
This is not possible
-So annoying!
Kazumi is next.
-Forget it
Try it.
-Okay, I'll try
I tried my best to do it
It's a lie, right?
-This is too much
Damn it, it's broken, what should I do?
The part where the chain is connected to the device started to crack
The pointer also stopped working
This can't be real, right?
This is not something that humans can do, right?
The world record is about 500kg
If you pull off the chain, you probably already have 1t of power
Rather than an anomaly, this is more like a monster
Yes, I think so
The next VTR of Kazumi's strange power is
I'm going to the bathroom
When I used to travel overseas, after entering a public bathroom
No way!
I broke the handle and couldn't open the door
It's broken
Because of the force, the screw broke
The sound of the break echoed in the bathroom, which made me feel embarrassed
It's not embarrassing, right?
The last example of K. Kazumi's power is
When she was a middle school student
Hey Kazumi, come here for a second
What are you doing?
-Don't worry about it. Just come here
Three bad kids
When I was in high school, it was a bad high school
Called over
Hey Kazumi, let's fight each other!
Why?
There were many heartless boys who were clamoring to fight me
Giant! Giant! Giant! Giant! Giant!
This is unforgivable!
She's really angry.
-That's enough
I won't lose to someone like this
This bad kid, I knocked him out
This didn't happen again after high school
What the hell
So cool
What's more
Why didn't you contact me?
Boyfriend?
My ex-boyfriend did something that can never be forgiven
This is indeed unforgivable
What are you doing?
-Kazumi
Really had a boyfriend?
I found my ex-boyfriend with another girl
Girls too?
Also hit girls?
When I came back to my senses, I found that I had beaten both of them up
Beat both of them up?
Nonsense
These are the cases of K. Kazumi's strange power
Hmm
Next, the last of the three characteristics of K. Kazumi
An otherworldly level of appetite
That's right, since has such a huge body
My dinner is about 3 liters of white rice and about 30 plates of curry
21 servings of Udon
3 pots of salad
72 kebab skewers
12 oranges
One meal?
The amount of food is unbelievable, is this amount possible?
We invited big eaters to consider it
And asked them to confirm the amount of food
This time I want to ask you to confirm the amount of food someone eats at a meal
A meal's worth of food?
-Yes
It's like school dinners
This is one meal?
-Yes
Probably all three of us together would struggle to finish all of this
Really?
If someone can finish this, its not anyone I know
I can't imagine one person able to eat this much
Even when I was the reigning champion, I had to fight to adjust my stomach capacity
Only then could I eat over 10 kg at a time
But you're telling me there's someone that has this much just for dinner...
It makes me feel like my accomplishments are complete negated
Even these big appetite warriors can not handle this amount of food
The person who can finish this is called K. Kazumi
K. Kazumi? K. Kazumi? I see
I guess she probably can eat this
I see
It seems K. Kazumi is well-known in this field
Sugawara and Angela are both aware of this individual
How do you know about her?
I searched eating records
After looking at everyone's results, I found that one person's record is simply unbeatable
I found out in this way
At Wagyu Family Restaurant and the buffet soba at Wagyu Noodles Sagami
A famous big eater set a record of 24 dishes
K. Kazumi's record is 82, 3.5 times that amount
It's really a record
An official record
Sugawara knows this person too?
Although I know, but, how should I put it say, I don't take it seriously
When I was a child, the Loch Ness Monster and Bigfoot
These were popular for a while when I was a child
I also categorize K. Kazumi in the same way
Like those legends
Although I think it's good to dream, I still don't believe it
In addition, the most powerful food fighter, Kobayashi
In the past, K. Kazumi once talked about eating 66 servings of soba noodles
Regarding this 0.5kg record, Kobayashi commented
They said that after not eating during the day, they ate 66 servings
The weight of the soba alone is more than 10kg, its impossible
This shows a fundamental misunderstanding of food fighting, its a lie
I see
A complete denial of the record
But this picture is indeed published on the official website of SAGAMI
As a listed company with 255 stores in the group
It is hard to imagine that the company would engage in fabrication
K. Kazumi, the mysterious legend, does she exist or not?
What is the truth?
Matsumoto, what do you think?
Although there's so much info about this, i've never heard of it
So I wont say anything for the moment
We do not have the right to remain silent in this program!
No, no, no, I can only say that I don't know
Do you have any opinion about the strange powers
Matsumoto, you are into fitness
This part seems a bit fake
But the last part of the soba store
That record is not forged, right?
There are records on the official website
In the end, I feel I have to believe it!
What do you think?
Well, it all seems a little too cartoony
But I do hope they exist
Today will put an end to it
So i'll be a little upset if this person didn't really exist
Indeed
Its a romantic idea for such a person to exist
Yes, I still hope this person really exists
So, now begins the search for K. Kazumi
Does K. Kazumi exist or not?
The information so far has been released solely by K. Kazumi herself
Of all this information, this record is the only clue to her existence
Strong evidence
So we decided to visit the site of the record
The best way
SAGAMI in Higashimurayama, Wagyu Noodle Shop
This is also a great opportunity to challenge the legendary record
In the meantime, we will confirm K. Kazumi's records with the store staff behind the scenes
Delicious
I can eat a lot because i'm super hungry
Another, please
As expected of one of Japan's top food fights, they swallow soba noodles at high speed
How many grams are in this serving?
160g per serving
-It's a lot
If the record is true
The total weight would be more than 13kg
How much can you eat at most?
Depending on the food, people have different limits
I'm afraid I can't eat that much soba
It is more difficult for solids like this
Although I have eaten 8.6kg of soba noodles, but that was a small bowl of soba
That was easier to eat so i'm not sure with this one
If its just soba, I can probably eat about 8kg at most
This bowl has 160g, so 9kg is about 50 servings
Even if it's a lie, at least tell a lie that is more or less believable, right?
The authenticity of this record is currently being confirmed
So, alongside the challenge
We asked the store manager, Mr. Mishima, the following questions
Is this record of 82 servings true?
This record was before I came to this store
I can only check with the head office
Because there was no staff present at the time
We asked him to confirm with the head office where the records were left
Really? He really doesn't know?
A little break
At this point, the retired big eater feels he has eaten enough
What do you think of 82 servings?
This isn't a smoking break!
It must be fake
Definitely not gonna go back and eat more
One hour after the start
Sugawara and Angela also slow down
Sorry, about the inquiry with the head office just now
Sure enough, the head office also gave a definite reply that it is true
Eh, really?
-There's no doubt about this record
No doubt
-Jeez
I see
After confirming with SAGAMI head office
They confirmed that K. Kazumi's records are factual
They said K. Kazumi really ate 82 servings
It can't be. Really?
It's a shock!
I don't want to believe it!
The competitive eating world will be turned upside down
-For sure
Demotivation in the face of such astonishing facts
We've now heard their confirmation
Until now we just heard some rumors and saw some pictures
And yet, I still find it hard to believe
The big appetite warriors still cannot accept this unrealistic record
After that, Sugawara and Angela continued to eat soba
The meal ended with the following results
Not even half of the record
Despite being higher than other female competitors in the ranking
K. Kazumi's record is still out of reach
Only by combining each are they able to meet the same amount
The total amount of three people
Its really awful
After the location shoot, while greeting the store manager
At the Koganei branch of "Aji no Mingei", a subsidiary of our company group
K. Kazumi also has a record there
As a result, we received information that K. Kazumi's records were also left in the sister store
So, we rushed to the location to conduct an interview
It is true that there is a 50 udon noodles-serving record left under the name of "Kazu"
An oversized record with a total weight of 12kg
I didn't actually meet this diner
No one here saw her either
Why?
- No, this is too strange
So we sent a request for assistance to the SAGAMI head office, which keeps detailed records
In response, we received a reply from the head office
Need help finding it?
Saying they would help find employees who knew about K. Kazumi
So while we waited for a response
There must be some, right?
We enlisted the help of a detective agency
Who questioned passersby on streets where there were rumors of sightings
Have you heard of K. Kazumi?
Tall person, right? Like an urban legend
No results were yielded
Three weeks after sending an inquiry to SAGAMI head office
We received a reply saying that three employees knew about K. Kazumi
It would be strange if this were not the case
Finally
So we rushed to the SAGAMI head office in Nagoya
To meet with one of the individuals in question
I am the person
This is one of the employees who knows K. Kazumi
Mr. Imamura, General Manager of SAGAMI Corporation
We are hoping to conduct an interview with K. Kazumi
Is K. Kazumi a real person?
It's true. I've seen her before
She exists!
Is K. Kazumi a real person?
It's true. I've seen her before
I've met her before
Finally, an eyewitness is found
As expected, the legendary K. Kazumi is a real person
How were you able to meet K. Kazumi directly?
Our company has also opened several stores in Bangkok, Thailand
K. Kazumi, as the record holder in Japan
We invited her to the opening ceremony of one of our stores there
I see
Mr. Imamura, met her while in Bangkok
What was his impression of K. Kazumi?
What kind of person is she?
I was in charge of the kitchen at the time
So basically, I only remember that she was there
I don't know any more details about the situation
But for example, she was taller than 2m and so on
No, no, no, really is a super ordinary woman
Ordinary women?
-Yes
2m? Absolutely not, really is completely normal
So she's not fat either?
-No
A sudden shocking discovery
What's going on here?
K. Kazumi is not a woman with a huge body size of 2m in height and 200kg in weight
What the hell?
So, this remarkable witness finally confirms her existence
Although the amount of food is true, she's actually small?
This is what he says
In a sense it's even scarier
Is anything else a lie, like the frying pan and stuff?
Its like big Freiza suddenly becoming smaller
The final form is unexpectedly small
And with deformation, right?
Very romantic
I suspect that this is a multi-person group calling themselves K. Kazumi
Everyone is eating together and keeping up the pretense of this story
Not one person, that seems likely
If this is not the case then it really does not make sense
So, lets get started
Who is K. Kazumi?
Her face will finally be revealed
Really?
-Will we really find out?
Next we will visit the second person who knows about K. Kazumi
It's this person
At the Higashimurayama store where K. Kazumi left a record
Honda, who has been working part-time since the opening of the business
We are investigating K. Kazumi
Do you know K. Kazumi?
Although I am a part-time team leader of the night shift
Before I heard that during the day someone ate 35 portions of soba
35 servings?
-Yes, 35 initially
I also heard that there were people who could eat very well before
People in the restaurant were talking about 35 servings
Not quite sure if was due to work
But the person gradually started coming here at night too
I served her soba noodles once
The last time I saw her was about two years ago
She hasn't seen her since the last time she was served two years ago
Here we attempt to confirm about the 82 servings
Instead of saying she's a big eater
As far as I can remember, she was just enjoying the soba noodles
Is the record of 82 servings real?
-Yes, it's the soba I served
You served it?
-Yes
What was the situation then?
-That day she was particularly into it
At first she was ordering three servings at a time, then it became five
Then five at a time, one after another
I also remember telling the backroom staff, "I think she's especially into it today, please speed up."
Isn't the record of 82 servings very impressive?
Yes, at that time it was unparalleled
I have never seen 5 servings of noodles so quickly eaten at once
Did they have any leftovers?
-No
I was going back and forth between the back kitchen and the restaurant endlessly
So you've seen how she eats?
Yes, her eating and asking for more
I had to adjust my pace accordingly
This is how it went
Was it a trick or anything?
-Not at all
Honda witnessed the birth of the record
Sure enough, the 82 servings is an irrefutable fact
That's incredible
There is a rumor online that she is 2m tall
No, not at all
Really?
-Yes
What about 170cm?
-Hm, well, probably
This point about her huge physique being untrue is also confirmed
The legend of K. Kazumi's is even more mysterious in terms of authenticity
Only the big appetite is clear
The last one who knows K. Kazumi
The SAGAMI Tsurunoshima Branch Manager Miyazaki
Were you the manager of the Higashimurayama store, when the 82-serving record was set?
Yes, i've been there for almost 5 years
So, when the record was set at that time
-I was there, yes
Isn't 82 servings a very impressive record?
Wouldn't they get interviewed on TV or in magazines or anything like that?
There were interview requests
For K. Kazumi?
Yes, for K. Kazumi
How were they dealt with?
I contacted K. Kazumi personally
Told her someone wants to interview her
Did she reject you?
-Yes
So you know K. Kazumi's phone number, right?
Yes, I know it
Finally, we have found someone who can contact K. Kazumi directly
So
We really want to meet this person, can you please contact her on our behalf?
I'll try
Just say it's a TBS show. We'd really like to meet with her.
-Okay
That's right. Don't reveal the name of the show
Please have some confidence!
But it seems she doesn't like this type of thing...
Making appearances?
-Yes
So it might be a little difficult.
-I see
After waiting for a week, we received contact from Miyazaki
If the conditions for obscuring the face and sound can be met
K. Kazumi is willing to be interviewed
So far, she has never accepted a request to appear on TV
Why did she choose to accept it this time?
K. Kazumi will be on set soon
-Then let's shoot
And what about the false claims of being more than 2m in height with strange powers?
Why have fake daily routines been detailed online for 12 years?
Next, the truth will be revealed
The Confessions of K. Kazumi
Looks very ordinary
Please take a seat
Are you K. Kazumi?
-Yes
We've been searching for K. Kazumi
We are honored to meet you.
-Thank you
Although there are many questions I would like to ask you
Seeing you like this, you don't appear to be 2m tall
Did you make that up?
It's a lie. I was stunned when I first heard it myself
So it wasn't you who said it?
Not me
Who wrote it?
-I don't know. I'd like to know too
Shockingly, the account on Yahoo is not operated by the real K. Kazumi
What's going on here?
-It's complicated
Is all the information about K. Kazumi posted on the Internet false?
Yes, it's all fake
The information about K. Kazumi online is all false, except for SAGAMI's records
None of the information was released by K. Kazumi herself
And it is unknown who the perpetrator is
How did you see all the information on Yahoo?
Well, my daughter happened to search for "K. Kazumi" online
But it wasn't me that posted it, I didn't even know of the website itself
When I saw it, I didn't understand what kind of person was using the name K. Kazumi
How did you feel when you first learned that someone was spreading false information?
Shocked, the image didn't fit me at all
I just like soba, that's all
That's the most impressive thing
As K. Kazumi herself has no desire whatsoever to attract the attention of others
How did the account talking about her appetite and physique earlier
Know about the record that was made later?
The name seems to have been changed afterwards
I don't mean to offend you, but you are K. Kazumi, right?
Yes, it's me.
-Okay
When I was at SAGAMI, the clerk told me, "Please use your initials to come up with a name"
I casually said, "Let's use the name "K. Kazumi"
K. Kazumi is your name, right?
Your name is Kazumi, right?
-Yes, it is
At this point, we reconfirmed the details of the record
Is your record of 82 servings also true?
It's true.
-That's incredible
That's awesome
I just kept eating and ended up having at 82 servings
That's what happened?
Ate and ate until you ate 82?
When did you start these challenges?
About 3 or 4 years ago, only at SAGAMI
The more I ate, the more delicious it became, then it ended up as a challenge
Really likes soba
Its hard to believe this amount can be eaten just accidentally
Did you prepare in anyway?
I guess I didn't eat much the day before
But its true that eating at a buffet isn't great for your health
So because of this I don't really do it anymore
You mean
Because it affects your physical condition?
Pretty much, yeah
Now i usually only eat a normal bowl of rice
So you usually eat a small or just average amount of food?
Yes, if I go to a convenience store, I usually just have one or two rice balls
What about TV appearances for eating, have you ever received an invitation?
There were invitations through SAGAMI, but I turned them all down
No interest in doing it
What about invitations for TV interviews like ours?
-This is the first time
Why did you accept our invitation to be interviewed this time?
First of all, I didn't know that K. Kazumi existed before
You mean K. Kazumi on the Internet?
-Yes
So I didn't expect an interview about this specifically
After actually learning about the online situation, that its a fake account
Someone's pretending to be me, so I wanted to state its a fake
So, the K. Kazumi on the Internet is an impostor
To convey this reality
She made up her mind to make a one and only TV appearance
If you don't mind
Can you tell us your actual height and weight or foot size?
Height 167cm Weight about 59 to 60 kg
Normal
The shoe size is 24.5cm
It is indeed very ordinary
The height written on the Internet is 213cm and weight is 222kg
-Nonsense
That's too much.
-Why did you tell her that?
I would also like to ask you about your age range if that's ok
Between 55 and 60
You are also married, right? You have a daughter?
-Yes
There are rumors on the Internet that your husband is a lawyer.
-That's not true
K. Kazumi-san, you're not a housewife, but you have a job, right?
-Yes, I do
What do you do for a living?
-No comment
Apologies
Finally, after this program is broadcast, the real situation should be known to the public
Do you have any hopes for the future?
Hopes for the future. On the impostor
I hope that the person pretending to be me can bear the corresponding responsibility
Indeed
I hope they disappear
On the existence of K. Kazumi
You want it to be over
In short, I hope the impostor will disappear
That the truth comes to light
That's all for the interview, thank you.
-Thank you
Thank you so much for coming!
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
-Thank you
Which way is it?
K. Kazumi just wants a quiet life
She came from the right
Have you seen this?
Must've seen this
Can we take this as a souvenir?
No, I don't want to see that
I don't want to see this
So who is this?
-Yeah
In conclusion, K. Kazumi exists
However, the version online is not the actual person
So we don't know who that photo is, right?
It must be photoshopped
Maybe someone was mistaken for K. Kazumi
Randomly uploaded a picture and mistaken for K. Kazumi
There may be such a person
With this body and strange power
It's impressive. It's really impressive
Yeah, right.
-Just agreeing to be in the show is already a big deal
First of all, there really is a woman that can eat that much soba
Such a woman exists
This urban legend is incredible
Yes, especially considering the fact that the professional eaters said its impossible
And that she just likes it
-So she ate and ate and ate
Set a record in such a way
Its so weird
-It's awesome
That's great.
-After 82 servings, her health got worse
That's right.
-It's horrible, isn't it?
In short, we've just watched an hour-long episode about someone that simply loves soba
SAGAMI's soba buffet is available for only 1980 yen
Tempura is also available
Tempura is very important!
Only 1980 yen with tempura!
This was obviously requested
A requirement
Surely a condition for helping, right?
SAGAMI is not that type of place
You have to do what they say
Don't underestimate the magnitude of SAGAMI
There are no conditions attached
Our buffet comes with tempura!
This statement only represents my personal feelings
Well, then Takahashi, you've eaten it before, right?
Not as of yet, no
-You haven't!?
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03