This is the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Arerende.
Automo director, Bridal West!
When we first met, he was still an AD.
He was an AD, but he's now a director.
He has to get married as soon as possible.
Heipo is always like that.
Heipo is impossible.
Why?
It's like going to a gynecologist and getting electrocuted in the ass.
There's no way he'd get married.
He's the director!
The director is nothing.
Anyway, Automo.
We were supposed to go to a happy marriage, but there was a problem between us.
We got old.
Automo is dirty.
That's not the case with Toshi.
I want him to be a little more beautiful.
I want him to be beautiful.
That's what I'm going to do in the opening.
Let's go.
Automo director, please.
Let's give him a round of applause.
He's going to be happy.
How far have you come in terms of marriage?
I've finished my first year of high school.
That's great.
So today you're going to do it for free?
That's right.
It's going to cost you hundreds of thousands of yen.
There are three courses.
Beautiful boy course, plastic surgery course, and refresh course.
Beautiful boy course.
I knew it.
We're always doing this.
That's right.
I'm a talent.
This program is brought to you by the sponsor.
So, what did you choose?
Beautiful boy course?
Beautiful boy course.
First of all.
It's a wrinkle stretch.
That's right.
Compared to the beginning, there's a lot of wrinkles.
Wrinkle stretch.
It's like a wrinkle.
It's like a small sword.
Yes, please.
Wrinkle stretch.
It's a good stimulation.
I recommend you to throw it away.
Are you crying?
That's a little.
It's about 4.5 times more than the original plan.
Let's take a look.
You're dirty.
Don't show your ass.
I'd like to move on to the next course.
This time, by sweating.
It's a waste of fat.
It's like a full body pack.
That's right.
I'll prepare it for you.
Otomo-san.
Yes.
I'll be back in a minute.
Please take a seat over there.
It's even more wonderful if you look at the constellation.
Please.
Otomo-san.
It's getting bigger, but it's not that big.
It's a very simple thing to do.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's better to do it yourself.
It's hard for a newcomer to do it.
It's about yourself.
It's proof that I'm listening to you.
It's a mess.
That's enough.
Thank you very much.
Otomo-san's butt is sticking out.
That's enough.
Otomo-san.
Otomo-san, you have an interesting face.
It's changed a lot since the beginning.
It's changed a lot.
It's changed in appearance.
Next, let's look for it.
Do you want to die by gagging your blood?
It's okay.
It's like a Tachan in the jungle.
Really?
Tachan?
Hey Tachan, why did you call me Tachan once when I called you Tachan?
You're going back on your word.
Me too.
Tachan.
I wonder if Nomoha is coming.
This is bad.
Tachan.
This is good, Tachan.
First of all, say hello.
Like this.
From the chin.
You look like a weird living thing.
Please put it down.
Don't talk like that.
Our director looks like a sea fish.
Revolution of the world.
The original low beauty course goes to the sewer.
Good.
This is good.
What is this?
Come here.
Sit down.
Shake your body.
Look at me and smile.
Good.
Smile more.
Your mental age is about 2 years old.
Let's have the director look at you.
Excuse me, director.
Excuse me.
This way.
What do you think?
It's over.
Tachan.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
Good evening.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
Thank you very much.
I'm back from the commercial.
I'm in trouble.
I'm sorry.
Yesterday was Valentine's Day, right?
Yes.
It was the first time in my life.
Why?
I don't know.
Who do you think I am?
I think there are three.
I saw you when you were on Fuji TV.
You mean the fan?
Yes.
Cocoa, you bastard.
Why are you angry with Cocoa?
I was angry when I was a student.
Really?
You were not popular when you were a student.
Why?
You don't have to laugh.
You were dating when you were in elementary school.
That's all, right?
Yes.
I thought a lot.
No, no, no.
I was told many times that you are my sweet honey.
Who said that?
Many people.
I was depressed yesterday.
I didn't think about anything.
I have three things.
I have a cell phone, a phone message, and three eyebrows.
I didn't receive a message until yesterday.
No way.
It's Valentine's Day.
I don't eat it.
I used to dig a lot of chocolate at Minami's house.
I used to take a lot of cars.
I used to do it.
I got a punishment at that time.
I don't know.
I got a punishment at the office.
You got a punishment at the office.
I wasn't at the scene today.
Yes, yes, yes.
I wasn't at the scene.
I was at the scene.
I was at the post office.
I wasn't at the scene either.
What?
I don't know anymore.
Have you ever done this?
When I graduated, all the buttons disappeared.
Please, please.
Yes, yes, yes.
Please, please, please.
That's right.
I wrote it beautifully.
Right?
I really didn't have anything.
It was like a cape.
Why?
My eyes got dark because of the diamond.
It's annoying.
Here.
I didn't have it here either.
I had seven here.
Why?
I was doing it here.
Where?
It's all gone.
At that time.
If you become a talent, you will gradually become younger.
What is it?
But I'm not that old.
I'm not that old.
When I did Fuji TV yesterday, I did it with a guest.
That's right.
There were about 100 people.
When I was doing it, I was doing it like this.
If it comes out, it won't break.
This program is the same.
That's right.
It's okay to be late for a day.
Are you worried because you're late?
Yes.
But it's hard to say that you don't have one.
It's hard to say that you don't have one.
Just above the station.
Don't sing like you're surprised.
I'm sorry.
I don't know who it is.
Hey!
I suddenly remembered something blue.
When I was in the first or second grade of junior high school,
At that time, I couldn't get one.
I was old.
Do you cry?
That's right.
I couldn't get one.
I was depressed and went home.
Then my mother gave me only one.
It's okay.
Your mother gave you one.
That's right.
You don't have one.
There are many things.
Let's go home.
What?
Do you want to go to the post office?
Yes.
Why?
Why didn't you tell me?
What should I do?
What?
Call me.
There are many things.
I don't care.
You wear different earrings every week.
How many do you have?
This is...
I don't care.
That's not true.
What was your name?
Hamamoto.
Ham...
Hamada, right?
You and Hamada only talk about looks.
I have many different earrings.
But they are the earrings of my heart.
Kindness earrings. Courageous earrings.
Wait.
What is it?
He saw this program and wrote it down.
I saw it.
I saw it and said it.
When he saw this air, he said...
I'm wearing kindness earrings.
That's the meaning of earrings.
Do you understand?
I don't understand.
You may not see it.
But I wear earrings to people who understand.
I wear pendants.
You wear pendants?
Friendship pendants.
I have such a kind of kindness.
I have kindness in my heart.
Until now, I have worn earrings, rings, and bracelets.
For example, you think your child is cute, right?
Yes.
You just said yes.
At that point, you wear a child-like bracelet.
Bracelet?
You wear a child-like flower earring.
Flower earring?
Why is that a flower earring?
That's what it is.
I understand that.
You wear something meaningless.
What is meaningless?
Kindness earring.
What is kindness earring?
For example, when you are talking, you slip and fall off the stage.
You can reach out your hand when something happens.
Kindness earring.
It makes you shine.
It makes your eyes shine.
When Mr. Matsumoto calls you, you say I, I, or sometimes you say Washi.
Sometimes you say Oira.
It is not unified.
How do you use it?
How should I put it?
I am...
I am five-syllable.
Basically.
Wait a minute.
Basically, you are five-syllable.
I don't understand what you mean.
How should I put it?
There are two people above me.
What is inside of me?
What is it?
Inside of me?
Yes.
For example, when you are angry.
When you are angry.
When you are angry, the person above you, Soichiro, appears.
Do you understand?
Hold on a little longer.
Yes.
Do you understand?
And when you are moved by something and you start to cry,
Ryuji from Jinan appears.
Ryuji from Jinan.
And the neutral state is Mr. Matsumoto.
I see.
Why do you say it like that?
That's what it means.
Do you understand?
Everyone has it.
When you are angry or crying, it's not the same.
For example, you are walking on the street.
You are walking on the street.
When you hit your shoulder, Soichiro appears.
Ryuji blocks it.
Wait.
Don't come out.
If you are blocked, you can endure it.
Yes.
If you are not able to endure it, you become Soichiro.
You become slightly green.
I'm sorry.
You run fast.
Soichiro.
That's good.
You run fast.
Yes.
I see.
Ryuji is strong against water.
He is strong against water.
I think he is doing something.
Why do you bring bread to school when you have a day off?
Do you bring it to school?
Or do you bring it to school?
I think I bring it to school.
I see.
I think I bring it to school when I have a day off.
I don't like it.
Do you know that?
No.
Bread is made of yeast.
Yes.
Shut up and listen.
He is the right person for this program.
Let's talk about it here.
For example, Kimura-kun.
Kimura-kun has a day off.
Yes.
Kimura-kun.
Come tomorrow.
Yes.
Come tomorrow and have fun with your classmates.
Right?
Yes.
Why do you bring bread to school?
Kimura-kun.
Kimura-kun has a day off.
Yes.
Kimura-kun.
Come tomorrow and have fun with your classmates.
Come tomorrow.
That's what it means.
I had a toothache the other day.
It doesn't matter.
I went to the dentist and had a toothache.
I was a dentist.
Really?
I had a toothache.
I could see my gums.
Mr. Matsumoto.
Why do women who can see their gums feel bad?
Do they feel bad or smell bad?
Please tell me the good points of women who can see their gums.
I think women who can see their gums are cute.
When they smile.
What?
I feel like I'm going to jump.
I understand.
I think there are good points of women who can see their gums.
I have to tell you that.
Teacher.
Yes.
I've done a lot of research about that.
Really?
The library is a house.
It's an orphanage.
I've done a lot of research about that.
The probability of having a traffic accident is very low.
If your gums are big?
You all know that.
If your gums are big, they shine at night.
They shine at night?
I don't know.
You don't know?
So, when you take a picture, you smile when you see your gums.
But when you smile, the picture looks like this.
I like that.
You like it.
I like it.
But they all shine, right?
They all shine.
What's the point of having a lot of children?
That's why, when you're walking at night, you'll understand.
Even if they jump out.
This, you, this...
What is it?
This isn't funny.
It was written in some magazine.
They sent it to me.
Gaki no Tsukai. From July 1992 to May 1993.
It's 35 times.
So, what you did to me.
One neck tightening.
One pull of the cheek.
One punch with both hands.
One kick of the knee.
Two punches of the cheek.
Two pinches of the nose.
One kick of the butt.
Fourteen times of the elbow.
Thirty-nine times of the head.
Thirty-six times of the head.
Sixty pinches of the butt.
Ninety-three times of the butt.
Ninety-nine pinches of the butt.
Two pinches of the butt.
One hundred and fifty-nine pinches of the butt.
On the contrary, three pinches of the butt.
Where did you get that magazine?
I don't have a talk show.
I'm surprised.
Is that so?
I get up in the middle of the night.
Really?
That's amazing.
I didn't know that.
No, no.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.