Last year October
Fukuoka Gaien Hokusu Nippon Ichi, congratulations!
Nippon Ichi's beer party was held to celebrate the opening of the Fukuoka Gaien Hokusu Nippon series
While no one from their hometown was present, the venue was heated up for some reason
And this year, that season has come again
Tokyo Yamiuri Gaien Gun, Nippon Ichi, congratulations!
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
This is Yomiuri Jan Yats, Nippon Ichi's beer party
It's a huge party
Let's hear from Nippon Ichi
Thank you very much
I thought it was going to be like this
But I couldn't win
Thank you very much
Akiyama-san, are you watching? I did it!
Oh my god!
This is the last one
This year was a year full of private events
That's right
I did my best for this person
Thank you very much
Congratulations to Nippon Ichi for making it to the Fukuoka team