Okamoto On Parade
We didn't have much to talk about, so it was pretty easy.
Yeah, it was easy.
I'm sorry we had to show you that for 30 minutes.
Okamoto On Parade.
Don't worry about it. It's a 30 minute show.
I'm the manager.
I was doing other things as well.
We're not the main characters yet.
I was wondering if I should air this.
Well, it was a good opportunity.
It was a good opportunity.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
I'm going to Okinawa.
This program is brought to you by Okamoto On Parade.
Today is Yamazaki's birthday.
We wanted you to see the prank.
It's actually over now.
It was really fun.
It was the worst prank ever.
I'm going to sue you.
I really thought it was a prank.
I thought I should just shut up.
I thought I should just go to Okinawa.
This memory...
I'm going to say this.
The best prank ever.
Yamazaki's birthday.
After the shoot, they had a nice dinner.
But the plan had already started.
Yamazaki who has no work.
Yamazaki who has nothing to do.
It's fun.
We're going to eat.
Thank you.
After the dinner, the karaoke competition.
The scary prank is finally going to start.
Why?
I have no work.
I'm desperate.
There was a person who was looking at Yamazaki.
A prank.
Yamazaki Hosei.
He was attacked by a scary person in the toilet.
Yamazaki was attacked by a scary person in the toilet.
I'm getting excited.
I don't know what I'm waiting for.