In the 1st episode of Gaki no Tsukaiara, Chikkun's 1, 2 finish...
Chikkun's Dantan presents worth 100,000 yen!
It seems like everyone is in a bad mood today
I'm in a bad mood today
I'm really in a bad mood
Everyone, do you remember what you looked like just now?
It's a strange transformation
A strange transformation?
I don't want to do this anymore
Everyone looks like this right now
It's been a long time
It's been a year
Is that so?
I don't know why he doesn't like it
That's right
We're still friends
There's no such thing
What is this?
I'm the villain in this story
This program is brought to you by the sponsors you see
First, we're going to fight for the right to get 100,000 yen
It's just one person
The person with the least amount of money will get 100,000 yen
The person who gets 100,000 yen will be chosen by me or Matsumoto
Then I'll get 100,000 yen
I'll get 100,000 yen
I'll take care of that
It's a bit early
This is...
This is a bit early
This is not good
This is 5
Wait a minute
This is not good
I didn't say I didn't drop it
I saw it at once and it was 6
I thought it was a 5, but it's a 5.
I don't like that either.
Okay, then let's go with 6.
Don't say that.
This guy is really selfish.
2, 2, 2.
2.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I can't do this.
I'll do it.
5th place.
Okay.
9th place.
Please, please.
4th place.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
7th place.
Okay, okay, okay.
It's the last one, right?
It's the last one.
This is Sakamoto-chan.
Wow.
4th place.
Hey, wait a minute.
Okay, Sakamoto-chan.
From now on, we're going to do a free throw.
Okay.
Let's do it five times each.
Whichever way you want to do it.
Please decide whether you can do it or not.
Please, please, please.
I'll do it first.
It's just us.
Before we do it, we'll do it like this.
Okay, let's go.
That was close.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
It's in.
That was close.
Ah, it sank.
It sank.
If this goes in, I win.
That's right.
Oh, it went in.
I won!
I won with 2-0!
Please go to the Royal Box
The
Mimic of the Mimic
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10
Please go to the Mimic of the Mimic
Everyone, welcome to the second stage
Yes
I saw something amazing
Let's win another 100,000 yen
Why are you so happy?
Why are you so happy, Harutatsu?
This is strange
What is this?
Let's do it again
Yes!
What is this?
Wow
This is amazing
Be careful
Yes
I don't know yet
This is amazing
Let's go
I won
I won with 2-0
Let's make it with 2-0
I will throw this ball
Let's see who will die
I chose this
Please
This is Hamada's normal debut
This is definitely the choice of Matsumoto
That's right
I don't know if I'm wearing the opposite
I don't have a choice
I'll do anything you want me to do.
Let's do it.
Ready, go!
I did it!
Let's listen to it.
I can see a new world.
That's enough!
This is scary!
It's dirty!
Scary!
Let's do the last one with Russian roulette.
You have six shots.
You have six bullets and one gunpowder.
I'll do it.
I did it!
I'm sorry.
It looks like it's going to work.
It's going to work.
I'm counting on you.
The third round is the other way around.
Rock-paper-scissors!
The other way around!
I won the first round.
I don't know who will win.
The second round!
I won the first round.
The third round is the final round.
The final round.
Rock-paper-scissors!
Let's go!
The transformation of charm!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Yama-chan, go ahead.
Let's make it a final round of love!
Ladies and gentlemen.
It's good again.
What are you looking at?
It seems like there's something going on these days.
That used one.
The old one.
What is it?
Well, well, well, well.
Isn't that right?
He's the used one.
It's just, it's just, you know.
That's not it!
Hey!
The one who's in that costume is called Hamada.
That's a good one.
Hamada?
Nothing has changed.
It's the same, right?
It's the same, it's the same.
That's right.
That's strange.
It's Hamada!
Even in fashion, he's the leader.
That's good, right?
He's cool.
He has a lot of things that I don't have.
For example, what is it?
A big house, right?
There's nothing wrong with that.
And a loving wife, right?
Right?
In the past, when was it?
Was it when you made your debut or high school?
It wasn't like that.
In fashion, it was zero to zero.
It was terrible.
It was better than you.
No, no.
When you were in high school, you were still called by your number.
That's not it.
It was terrible.
You went to Japan and did whatever you wanted.
Whatever I wanted?
That's not it.
I didn't do whatever I wanted.
I was just walking around.
I didn't know what to do.
If you see a friend like that next to you, just hide it.
I don't know where it changed.
What's this?
Is this going to be popular?
It's not going to be popular.
If you say it's good, it will be popular.
Why?
I don't have any influence.
It's not going to be popular if someone like me does it.
But if you say it's good, it will be popular.
If I do it like this?
What?
If you say it's good, it will be popular.
Are you stupid?
I'm sorry.
It's not good.
I can't reach it.
Can you reach it?
Yes.
From Toshi.
I can't find Shakutani.
I've been looking for him everywhere.
Shakutani...
I hope Shakutani will come to the show.
That would be the best.
I have a question for Matsumoto-san, who recently went from D cup to E cup.
You've been making a fool of yourself with the concept of bringing your brother closer.
How is your brother going to evolve?
My brother has changed a lot.
His underwear has changed too.
It's like 643.
What's that number?
It's the number of his underwear.
It's not 643.
What was it?
64...
2?
7?
It's 647!
It's the bell button.
Yes, it's the bell button.
That's right.
It's too old to bring him closer.
It's too old?
Yes.
How is he going to evolve?
That's going to be a big deal.
Let me hear that.
You've also gone from D cup to E cup, right?
Yes, I have.
What is this?
I'm talking to you.
Did you wear it then?
Yes, I did.
You're not wearing it now, are you?
I'm not wearing it now.
Why?
That's because...
What is it?
Why?
Please tell me the next one.
That's because I'm talking while singing.
That's not it.
For now, let's listen to the song.
Why?
You're doing a radio show.
You're not doing it.
I want to say this.
I know Matsushi, of course.
Please say it.
But if I say it,
I'll get a lot of calls.
They'll say,
You can't do it, Matsushi.
Please give me a hint.
A hint?
I can't give you a straight answer.
I'll give you a light hint.
What's the next one?
When the moon is covered in clouds.
I don't get it.
How do you say it then?
When the moon is covered in clouds.
You'll fall.
What?
Don't touch me.
That's strange.
What?
That's impossible.
That's not it.
If you two go to the jungle,
and Hamada-san gets bitten by a poisonous shrimp,
what will you do?
I think it's a question.
Why?
That's why,
I only think about Hamada.
when a poisonous shrimp comes out,
I won't forgive that poisonous shrimp.
Why would it come out in front of my Hamada?
Moreover,
when I ask it, it has poison in it.
Who did you ask?
It has poison in its tongue.
What's its tongue?
I can't help but get angry.
It hurts.
That's why,
I won't go to the place where Hamada gets bitten.
When I do something,
for example,
when I take this eraser,
is it good or bad for Hamada?
What are you talking about?
What's wrong with Hamada?
Are you thinking about Hamada?
When I drink mugi tea in the morning,
is this mugi tea good for Hamada?
N.H.K正しい日本語講座
My first brother, Masumoto-san.
Is that so?
Yes, that's right.
Do you have a cool way to call a Chirigami exchange student?
What's that?
It's cool.
There are many cool ways, right?
That's right.
For example,
even if you fall down on the street,
you can still be cool.
You can still be cool even if you get hurt.
Please show me a cool way to call a Chirigami exchange student.
So,
what kind of way is that?
Well,
I don't know.
Idiot!
What's that?
I don't know.
Chirigami exchange student.
At that time,
you open it like this.
Wait a minute.
This is my car.
Yes, that's right.
Everyone,
every year,
Chirigami exchange student.
I'm not doing this as a small business,
so I'm going to stop.
What?
I'm going to stop.
I'm just fooling around.
Don't get so angry.
Every year,
every year...
You know,
Chirigami exchange student.
You can just tell your girlfriend that you like her.
That's right.
I'm going to stop.
I'm scared.
If you tell me the truth.
After all,
I'm cool.
If Otama-Jakushi grows up,
he will change.
And Otama-Jakushi is in front of the frog.
Otama-Jakushi between the frog and Otama-Jakushi.
When Otama-Jakushi is growing up.
What are you going to say?
What are you going to say at this time?
Well...
Simply put,
what am I going to say?
It's a number.
A number?
I'm serious.
Wait a minute.
It's not funny.
Why?
It's Otama-Jakushi, right?
Otama-Jakushi, right?
The final type is a frog.
It's a frog.
In the meantime,
his hands, tail, and legs are growing.
What is this?
At that time,
I'm serious.
For example,
you,
Hamada-san,
you have various faces.
What do you mean by various faces?
For example,
you have the face of Kataya H-Jungle.
Yes.
Let's say this is a frog.
H-Jungle is a frog.
At that time,
you have the face of a frog.
A frog is a frog.
I see.
When you were in H-Jungle,
you were like this.
And one more thing.
When you were in a drama,
you were Otama-Jakushi.
But when you were in a drama,
you were acting.
Otama-Jakushi is acting as Otama-Jakushi.
You were acting as Otama-Jakushi.
I'm not acting as Otama-Jakushi.
Yes, I was acting as Otama-Jakushi.
Okay, okay.
Right?
You were acting as a frog.
Geku, Geku, Geku, Geku.
In the meantime...
In the meantime,
it was normal.
It was the most ridiculous time.
I didn't know how to act.
You had your hands, legs, and tail,
but you were told that you weren't a frog.
I didn't know what to do.
So...
How do you call it?
It's Su.
Su.
Everyone has that part.
The Su part.
Well, yes.
I was like,
are you serious?
I know, I know.
I can't be that serious.
Why is Omaru shaped like a duck?
What do you think about this?
You see,
Omaru is only used by children.
Only children.
Children.
Yes.
So, if you don't make it fun,
it makes people happy
to have characters like this.
Isn't that right?
So, in that sense,
it's a cute character.
To comfort children.
Yes.
Isn't that what it means?
It doesn't mean it's not cute.
If that's the case,
it doesn't have to be a duck.
It could be Anpanman.
There's something like that.
Are you serious?
It's just a normal answer.
I don't know.
It's serious.
I'm telling you.
If it's an animal,
there are many other things.
An elephant,
a giraffe,
but it's an excuse.
But why is it a duck?
Well,
he's asking why it's a duck.
I see.
Why is it a duck?
Yes.
In the past,
people used to
poop on a duck.
Let's go home.
What's so sad about pooping on a duck?
Don't touch it!
What are you talking about?
Listen, listen.
That's better.
From now on,
listen to me.
If it was a place where there was nothing,
it would make a sound, right?
That's right.
That's why girls are embarrassed.
Let me hear it.
So, in the past,
people used to poop on a duck.
Poo...
A duck?
They used to poop on a duck.
Ah!
That's why they made a sound.
As an excuse for a jerk?
As an excuse for a jerk.
Is it bad?
No.
Let's do it again.
Thank you.