I don't know how to use the side of downtown.
Ganbatchan Gakurenbo!
So, Hamada-san.
Today, we're going to show you the mansion of Ohashi Kyosen.
This is Mr. Kyosen's mansion?
Actually, this is a model room.
And look at this, everyone.
We have a gorgeous guest today.
I'd like to introduce him to you later.
First of all, I'd like to introduce you to Mr. Namikoshi.
He's here again.
He was hiding in the car the other day.
And he's here again this week.
And this is my aunt Komori.
Hello.
This is your first time here.
Actually, it's my aunt's birthday today.
Oh, really?
No, no, no, no, aunt.
Congratulations.
He's got a big heart.
I'm going to help you.
I'm going to hide you.
Oh, really?
Hamada-san is going to find you.
So, please remember his face.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay?
For the time being, that's the way he is.
I did it.
Honestly, I don't know what this is.
Really?
I don't know.
Why is it in this house?
Well, even my family doesn't know what this is.
It's expensive.
Wow, amazing.
He's definitely licking it.
Excuse me.
He's standing up seriously.
He can't move.
If you don't touch it, you can't feel the skin.
It's a well-made picture.
Whose work is this?
This is Komori's aunt.
It's a self-portrait.
That's right.
She's 82 years old.
It's a well-made picture.
It has a three-dimensional effect.
It's amazing.
But he can't move at all.
He can't move at all?
Yes, even if you put your fingers in his nostrils.
Really?
This is amazing.
The second floor is amazing, too.
He can't move at all.
Who are you?
I've been following you for a while.
I've been here twice, so I've been following you.
Up to this point, it's easy.
But from here...
This is good.
What are you doing?
I'm just asking you to follow me here.
I can't believe we're sleeping together.
Which room is this?
It's a scary house.
I hear something.
What are you looking for?
He's laughing.
He can't hide, but he's laughing.
What are you looking for?
I hear something.
He's still laughing.
What are you doing?
I hear something.
The teacher is amazing.
He's waving his hand.
Wave your hand.
That's how it is.
It was hard.
It was a great success.
The old man and the old woman did it.
Thank you.
It was fun.
Thank goodness.
It's a big hall.
It looks like it's going to last a few months.
It's true.
I know you're cheating.
Don't come out and leave in three seconds.
He's here to see you.
Even though he's a fan,
he doesn't like it when you take a lot of tours.
Even though he likes you.
If it's a girl he likes, he'll eat her poop.
What should we do?
This is my first time.
It's Ginza.
There's a lot of girls here.
The girl from the club.
There is.
I've never been to a club in Ginza.
It's very expensive.
What do you think?
Nan-chan seems to be going there.
Have you been to Okamabaya?
Yes.
I've never been to Okamabaya.
What are you doing?
Wait a minute.
I've been to a lot of good places.
I thought you were coming.
I'm not coming.
You don't have to reply like that.
What do you think?
Is it fun?
That's what you know best.
I don't know.
I've never been to such a beautiful place.
It's an old place.
It's been in Osaka for decades.
It's an old Okamabaya bar that was made when it wasn't called New Home.
I've been there.
It's amazing.
It's an old man.
Come on.
I can't make a voice.
Welcome.
I've been there.
I've never been to an Okamabaya bar, but I know a place where Okamano Mama is.
Why do you keep saying Okamano Mama?
I like it.
I'll sing it like a river.
Like a river.
I can't make a voice.
I've been there.
I've been to Osaka.
I've been to the theater.
I'm 2 meters tall.
I'm a real Okamano.
I'm wearing a rubber mask.
I'm a Hamada fan.
I'm always told,
It was a year or two ago.
Give me your autograph.
Where's Hama-chan?
You're so cute, Hama-chan.
It's scary.
In the past, there was no Okamano on the street.
There are a lot of foreigners.
There are a lot of foreign roadside shops.
They sell a lot of things.
They sell unbelievable things.
When I came to Ginza,
I was wearing a penguin umbrella.
What's that?
It's a huge one.
It's a penguin face.
It has wings.
It looks like a hat.
Who would buy it?
I've never seen anyone walking with an umbrella.
I know they sell it.
It was raining heavily.
The yakuza didn't have an umbrella.
What should we do?
We had to use an umbrella.
That's all we had.
But we were yakuza.
That's not cool.
It's not cool.
Give me that.
I want to try it.
There's this thing.
I was shopping on the phone.
It's a Nico Nico Poon blanket.
You can't go inside.
It's a Nico Nico Poon.
I was wearing a yakuza umbrella.
I was shopping on the phone.
It's a Nico Nico Poon blanket.
You can't go inside.
I saw you wearing a blanket.
It's cold in the morning.
You should wear a blanket.
It's not that way.
There's a collar attached to the blanket.
And there's a cotton ball attached to the blanket.
It feels really good.
There's a blanket with a collar attached to it.
The man is like, this feels really good.
I can't believe it.
Yeah, I think about it a lot.
Right now,
something big is coming, right?
What?
Something big.
A huge mountain.
That mountain,
I don't know what it is,
it's coming towards us.
It's moving on its own?
It's moving on its own.
Right now,
I don't know if we should blow it up with a missile or not.
Right now, we can't do anything.
Why can't you do anything?
If you look at the situation, you won't understand.
Maybe the mountain is great,
but the sea around it is melting little by little.
When you look at it, it might look like this.
There's a big incident, right?
Incident?
There's also the destruction of the ozone layer.
This is difficult.
What does this mean?
Let's ask him.
The destruction of the ozone layer,
what is it?
What?
What is the ozone layer?
The ozone layer is in the atmosphere.
It's in the atmosphere.
It's something that has to be there.
If it's there,
if it's in a good condition,
It's in a good condition?
What do you mean by a good condition?
If it's there,
it's in a good condition.
I see.
The ozone layer is there when you do it.
When I can't do it, I can't do it.
Just leave it as it is.
The temperature rises.
What?
The temperature of the entire Earth rises.
Because of the destruction of the ozone layer.
That means, if you keep doing this, it will be over.
I can't do this anymore.
This is a big problem.
If the temperature rises,
a lot of people will come out, right?
Is that so?
That's right.
The electric products will probably stop selling.
Why?
The temperature is rising.
If it's like that, don't cool it down.
See?
I can't do such a thing.
Why are you suddenly weak?
Why? Don't you understand?
I'm asking because I don't understand.
Maria, please give me a good bouquet.
Give me a good bouquet.
Are you asking Maria for a bouquet?
There are many things.
When a person is born,
is it decided that he will die?
How old is he?
When I told you not to die,
you should have changed your underwear.
Why?
Your underwear is really dirty.
You shouldn't have done that.
You are a pervert.
That was until junior high school.
You were wearing an unbelievable underwear.
It's your fault!
When you were in junior high school,
you made a record of changing your underwear.
That's why I made a record with you.
We were close friends.
How many days did you not change your underwear?
Two weeks.
Two weeks?
We went to the bathhouse together.
At that time?
At that time.
I changed my shirt, but I didn't change my underwear.
I didn't change my underwear,
but when Hamada didn't change his underwear,
I couldn't lose to him.
So I washed my underwear cleanly,
and I still wear stinky underwear.
You see,
when I take my underwear off,
I can smell the smell of the underwear next to me.
It's true.
It's hard to wear underwear in winter.
I can't stand it if I wear a kotatsu in winter.
I can't stand it.
It's amazing.
I'm serious.
I had an unbelievable underwear.
I couldn't stand it anymore.
So we decided not to change our underwear,
and we threw it away.
We threw away our underwear.
I recently realized that
I think I'm faster than a child who was raised in a poor family.
What do you think?
There is something special about a poor child.
Poor people get married early.
They get married early like a Yankee.
Poor people get married early like a Yankee.
Really?
Don't you think so?
Poor people get married early like a Yankee.
And they are black.
Very black.
Even though they are men,
they wear red randosels.
It's terrible no matter how many times you look at them.
They look at trumpets in the window of a musical instrument store.
They look like William Thoreau.
And they are especially red randosels.
You are poor.
Do you get married early?
No, I don't.
Don't say that.
You are poor.
No, I'm not.
I'm better than you.
How many rooms do you have?
Two.
You have two rooms.
Even if you have a jeepney, you have three chairs.
I was in good shape until I got pregnant.
After I got pregnant.
Because you are a painter?
Because I'm a painter.
Did your father paint the Soviet Union?
Yes.
The Soviet Union was like this.
Yes, red and white.
Did he paint that?
Yes.
I don't know anything about that country.
Did he paint all of that?
Did he go crazy?
Yes, he did.
Sometimes I can tell that he went crazy.
Did he continue painting in the fridge?
He was angry.
If your father was angry, he would continue painting in the fridge.
Why?
He was hitting the window glass.
He was hitting it like this.
I don't like this.
My father was like that.
My father was like that, too.
I didn't ask my father.
My sister was on the phone for a while.
She told me to go and paint.
She brought a knife.
She was like this.
What is she doing?
She was sleeping.
When I woke up, she was getting better.
She looked like she was getting better at night.
My father is not cool, so I didn't ask him to get better.
The other day, I went to a drama location in Atami.
When I got on the bus to go back to the inn,
I got on the bus.
It was a fire.
When the wind blew,
I didn't know who was next to me in front of the wind,
but my cheeks were swollen.
That's a fire.
I said,
That's the wind in the middle.
I did it to Taishu.
Bang!
That's a fire.
Everyone was doing it from the window.
I don't know.
But there are many people doing it.
Why?
They asked me to touch my stomach.
I said,
There are six of them.
Can't you confirm it?
You have to confirm it.
You should be the only one who is cold.
I have three words that are annoying to me.
I am angry that I am sorry or sorry.
Why?
No matter how you look at it, you say,
I'm sorry.
That's a word to belittle someone, isn't it?
No, you're apologizing.
You say, I'm sorry.
The more you apologize, the more I like you.
Don't you think so?
No, you're apologizing for refusing, aren't you?
That's different, after all.
And one more thing.
You don't like being apologized?
Then?
At times like that,
you're being belittled.
Stop it.
Why?
And you say, I feel sorry for you.
You say, I feel sorry for you.
For example, an amateur comes to you and says,
Oh, hello.
Where are you from?
I'm from Hamada.
Right?
And the person in front of you says, I feel sorry for you.
I don't feel sorry for you because I didn't like you.
Well, well, well.
I understand that.
But you're not angry at this guy.
I feel sorry for you.
I feel sorry for your head.
Well, I understand that.
I don't understand that now.
No one is angry at you.
You say, I feel sorry for you.
I don't feel sorry for you.
You're a high school student,
and you don't have any social status.
You say, I feel sorry for you.
Your social status is much higher than yours.
I have money.
You say, I feel sorry for you.
I think that the number of people in Owaru is higher.
Is that so?
Yes.
Do you go to the best stores of the variety show?
That's right.
In this organization.
Is that so?
Yes.
But I haven't seen that kind of thing.
And the person who wants to see it.
Japanese writing.
Everything is the same.
And the venue.
Please use it.
What is it?
The person who says it's free.
All of them.
I'll go anywhere.
If you send it now, I'll pick it up right away.
Right?
I'm sorry.
I'm going to be caught.
I've been doing it for 10 years,
and I've made a stupid mistake.
Well, see you next week.
Thank you very much.