In the winter of 2004, another harsh punishment game was launched.
There was only one rule.
It was a one-night, two-day trip to a hot spring that you absolutely must not laugh at.
If you laugh at the emotions given to humanity among all living things on Earth, and if you are taken away from that laughter...
...you will be punished by the 2003 punishment game.
And the ones who fell into hell this time were these men.
Naoki Tanaka.
Hosei Yamasaki.
Masatoshi Hamada.
The one who controlled the fate of these three men was...
...Shouzo Endo.
And the man who was in charge of the punishment game was...
...Hitoshi Matsumoto.
The memories engraved in the minds of these three men...
...were a one-night, two-day trip to hell.
Just do it already!
It all started with this match.
The first time, near the Gaki no Tsukai.
Gaki Shijo's first genius boy, Yamasaki Hatsun.
I don't know how many people will be punished.
Wasabi Sushi Russian Roulette Match!
The genius boy, Yamasaki Hatsun's Wasabi Sushi Russian Roulette Match.
The punishment game is to eat four Wasabi Sushi out of 100 sushi.
I don't know how many people will be punished for eating Wasabi Sushi in downtown.
The first one to be punished is...
Come on!
Don't be a middle-aged man.
That's enough.
Tanaka, choose.
Safe?
I think it's safe.
It's safe.
What are you saying?
Don't be a middle-aged man.
Yamasaki Hatsun's punishment game!
The second one to be punished is...
Safe?
I think it's safe.
It's safe.
What? Tanaka?
Tanaka, you're out!
I thought it was safe.
And...
I'm safe.
End safe.
We did it!
Hamada's punishment game is over!
The men who are chosen by the laughing devil will open the curtain.
Thank you for watching the punishment game.
We won.
Yes, we won.
Shall we call the people to be punished?
Yes, please.
How do you feel?
I'm fine.
But I'm a little tired after the game.
What?
You must be tired.
I was so excited that I couldn't speak.
Why?
I lost.
This is a long punishment game.
There are many punishments.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I know what you're talking about.
You should say it.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I was so busy that I had a runny nose.
You're all enemies.
I can't help that.
You can't help that.
You're all enemies.
Who can be on your side?
I've never been so quiet.
I was surprised.
It was 2 p.m. on the day of the punishment game.
Three people got on the train and arrived at Yugahara Station.
This man was waiting for three people in this town.
Hey.
You're so excited.
I'm laughing now.
Hey.
You're so excited.
I'm laughing now.
Do you know where this is?
This is Yugahara.
You're wrong.
You're wrong as a comedian.
You can't be funny.
It's a punishment game today.
And it's a goal.
Where is your goal?
I'll explain the rules of the punishment game.
One.
Three people will go to a hot spring hotel for two days and one night.
You can't laugh no matter what happens.
One.
If you laugh, you'll get a hard punishment.
That's all.
Mr. Matsumoto gave me a simple rule for the stupid Hamada.
Good for you, Hamada.
We're about to start the punishment game.
Are you ready?
All right.
You can't be funny.
The punishment game will start when you laugh.
If I laugh, it's over.
Follow me.
You can't be funny.
Let's go.
Let's go together.
Is the hot spring close to the inn?
It's close to the inn, but it's close.
Is that so?
Yes.
Look to the left.
The green of Yugawara is beautiful.
Yugawara is beautiful.
The city is welcoming us.
Look.
This is amazing.
I'm really surprised.
Tanaka.
You can't be funny.
What?
It hurts.
If this city doesn't cooperate, there will be no hole.
This is amazing.
What?
We arrived in Yugawara.
Where?
What's wrong?
What is this?
Wait a minute.
Cool.
Eun-vi.
1, 2, 3.
Mister, Mister.
I knew it!
Hamada out!
Yamasaki out!
Ouch!
Why did you get hit twice?
Tanaka got hit so many times!
YWGP World Heavyweight Champion!
He is the number one star in the world heavyweight division!
What are you doing?
Thank you.
Mom! Mom! Mom!
He is funny.
He is amazing.
The kids in Yugawara are studying hard.
I don't know anymore.
Tanaka!
What are you doing?
Help me!
It's hard.
Hamada!
What are you doing?
I can't stand it.
Tanaka is amazing.
He is amazing.
I can't stand it.
Let's take a break.
It's a hot spring town in Yugawara.
We should go to a traditional confectionery shop.
Let's have some tea.
Sit down.
Thank you.
He is still laughing.
I'm from Yugawara.
You can see me from the left or from the back.
He is still laughing.
I want to introduce something delicious before I go to bed.
What is it?
Where is Mr. Okami?
Mr. Okami?
He is a good man.
What is it?
This is Amanogawa Manju.
Amanogawa?
It's a beautiful name.
Did you draw Amanogawa?
We are filming.
This is Amanogawa.
Why do you call it Amanogawa?
I did my best.
It's beautiful.
Don't say unnecessary things.
That's why he laughed.
It hurts.
Is it delicious?
It's delicious.
There are many other delicious foods.
Please look forward to it.
Yes.
OK.
He is so small.
It's hot.
It hurts.
The director is so small.
He looks like an old man.
Next.
Let's go over there.
Before we go to the inn,
let's go to the place we want to go.
Let's go to the inn.
Let's go.
Hey.
Is this the best place?
Please get in the car.
I'm going first.
You're going first.
Please get in the car.
Excuse me.
It's more powerful than the last time.
That's right.
It's amazing.
The promotion of DYNAMITE was amazing.
It was amazing.
I don't think so.
You guys are so small.
Are you doing a business service?
Where are they going?
What is waiting for them?
It's amazing.
There are so many things.
That sign is amazing.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's amazing.
Can I listen to the radio?
Yes.
The show will begin soon.
I was really surprised.
This year is the year of the monkey.
It's the year of the monkey meat.
That's why I was surprised.
When I think about it,
It feels like it's the year of the monkey.
It's the year of the monkey.
Please give me more time.
And
You're out.
I can't stop it here.
I want you to come to Yukawara.
I'm so tired.
I don't have time to rest.
I'm so hungry.
Ouch!
What kind of sound is this?
I heard a loud noise.
I'm so tired.
It's tough.
Can I listen to the radio?
I don't know what to do with this.
Why?
Yukawara on my mind.
Dynamite Shikoku is coming to Yukawara.
I'm so sorry.
Let's go to Yukawara.
I was surprised.
Dynamite Shikoku is weak.
I'm getting tired.
Good luck, Tanaka.
Can I listen to the radio?
Yes, you can.
I can't listen to the radio.
Why don't you listen to the radio?
I'm so sorry.
Ouch!
He is waiting for a chance to attack.
I'm so sorry.
Why did you go to LA in Yukawara?
He is coming.
Ouch!
He is still going to LA.
He is going to laugh.
He is coming.
I have a cramp.
I think I have a cramp.
I haven't arrived at the inn yet.
Is this dirty?
It's dirty.
I'm wearing glasses.
He is laughing.
Stop it!
Why are you sleeping?
Why?
I see.
It hurts.
That's amazing.
Ouch!
It hurts a lot.
It's funny.
I don't want to go to the inn at all.
I know.
I can't wait.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
Ikko finally arrives at his next destination.
However, where has he arrived?
Can you get off?
Let's go to the inn.
This is a temple.
You have a lot of desires.
I want you to practice here.
I see.
Follow me.
Is this a temple?
This is an old and righteous temple.
What kind of training will the three of them receive here?
Let's not talk about unnecessary things.
That's right.
Tanako is really going down.
It's strange.
I'm fighting.
It doesn't matter.
What do you hate?
What do you think I am?
I'm not good at using the steering wheel.
I've changed.
I'm using it properly.
I'm telling you because I'm not tired.
I'm not tired at all.
You're usually tired.
Then why did you invite me to Hokkaido?
I can't help it because you were the only one there.
What is it?
Yamasaki out.
You were born.
What is it?
Wait a minute.
Tanaka out.
Yamasaki out.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
What is it?
Why are you laughing?
I don't know.
It hurts.
What is it?
You hit your hip.
That's it.
Please say hello to the staff who will be taking care of you from now on.
Staff.
Yes.
Welcome to the staff's exhibition.
Please come in.
I'll show you around.
This way, please.
Thank you in advance.
Of course.
Can I come in?
Please come in.
This is the main hall.
Behind me is the head office of the history department.
The first right corner is the head office of the history department.
The head office of the history department.
I'm from Kyoto.
I'd like to meet you all.
I'm not rude.
Please come in.
It was hot, wasn't it?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
That's what summer is all about.
It was really hot this year, wasn't it?
Is that so?
It's hot.
How is it?
It's hot, isn't it?
It's still hot.
It's amazing.
There are times like this on this show.
That's right.
It was hot, wasn't it?
I am.
It's sudden, but.
Well then.
I am.
First.
It hurts.
It's starting to hurt.
Well then.
I'd like you all to do zazen.
It's okay to keep your eyes open, but please don't disturb your mind.
Well then, let's start zazen.
I'm pregnant.
You don't have enough training.
Hello.
It hurts.
You don't have enough training.
What the hell is that guy?
I don't like this.
It hurts a little.
Tanaka out.
You don't have enough training.
It hurts.
That's amazing.
Oh, Maito.
Don't call me Maito.
It's Dynamite Shokoku.
You're the only one who calls me Maito.
Can I talk to you for a second?
I was beaten.
Excuse me.
The strongest wrestler in the world.
I hope to beat Escargoman.
Tanaka out.
Don't call me Dynamite Shokoku.
It hurts.
Let's go.
Here?
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Tanaka out.
Stop it.
You need more training.
Thank you very much.
This is the end of the training.
You learned English, didn't you?
They haven't even arrived at the inn for three hours since the start, but they're already about to give up.
But after this, the penalty game will continue.
Are you still at the inn?
I'm still at the inn.
That's right.
It's true.
You two haven't met yet.
Tanaka is the funniest one so far.
Tanaka is so loose.
I went to the inn before, but that was the first time I met him.
I was wondering if I would meet him like this.
But Dynamite Shokoku is interesting.
Actually, it's been seven years since he came back.
He came out for the first time during the 7th Henge.
During the 7th Henge?
That's right.
It was seven or eight years ago.
It was the first time.
That's right.
Since the first time I met him, I've been a pot.
It's been seven years.
It's been more than seven years.
He came out.
I see.
Everyone has a pot.
I actually saw him at the end of the 14th.
He has a great impact.
He is tough.
You haven't seen him in person, right?
He's really a four-headed man.
He's a two-headed man.
He's a one-headed man.
A one-headed man?
He's not a one-headed man.
It's just his face.
He doesn't have any organs.
It's 6pm. The sun has set and the three of us are finally in the hotel.
This is the hotel where the three of us will be staying tonight. What kind of trick is waiting for us?
Good morning.
I bought it.
This is a nice team.
This is so bad.
I can't do it.
You have to do it.
It hurts.
Let's go to the room.
This is a good place.
This is a good room.
I haven't seen the room yet.
Do you remember the room in the script?
This is a good room.
I'm going to the room.
There is something here.
Hamada out.
No, I'm Yamada.
Stop it.
Why?
Hamada out.
What?
I don't do anything even if I laugh.
Did you laugh in the bathroom?
I laughed.
I feel like I only did Hokusai Enda.
I was also hit.
Hamada out.
He came out.
This is you.
I was surprised.
Why did you get hit?
I don't know.
Hamada out.
I was hit.
Stop it.
It was painful.
It was really painful.
There was a bat in the middle.
Yes.
This is also painful.
This is the pamphlet Yamazaki got.
This program is introduced with the characters that came to Yumamara.
This is painful.
Yamazaki.
Hamada out.
Stop it.
I was hit.
I don't think I should laugh when someone hits me.
This is really painful.
This is painful.
This is beautiful.
There are many.
This is also beautiful.
I want to enter the showroom.
This is good.
Hamada out.
I was hit.
I was surprised.
This is painful.
This is not funny.
I was surprised.
I can't find it.
There is a yukata here.
Yes.
The size is L and M.
Which one is good for Tanaka?
I want L.
I understand.
Yamazaki.
I want M.
I understand.
What about Kuchibirobake?
I want Kuchibirobake.
This is painful.
I forgot something important.
This is a video of the showroom.
Please see this.
Yes.
Excuse me.
This is really embarrassing.
This is the first time I've seen this.
This is embarrassing.
I didn't see it.
This is really embarrassing.
This is embarrassing.
Please end this.
I'm going.
Yamazaki.
Damn it.
This is painful.
He was coming.
Today, I will guide you.
This is a long video.
I took a lot of videos.
I will do this.
This is cheap.
I want to go to the beach.
I did my best.
I went to the beach.
Good morning.
Meanwhile, Matsumoto arrived at the inn.
This is amazing.
It's 7 o'clock in the afternoon.
Only 5 hours have passed since the start.
The three people who entered the room are in relaxed mode in their yukata.
This is Chachin.
This is a battle.
They are in a great mood.
I'm looking forward to it.
The store is crowded.
There are so many people here.
In the atmosphere of praise
Yanasaki, out of the bag
You're ouiht!!
It's different from when he was wearing jeans, right?
Hana-chan is laughing too!
He's laughing
It's funny
What time is it now?
It's probably around 7 o'clock
It's past 7
I don't know the time
I really don't know
This is hard
What is it?
I'm hungry
I've been eating a lot recently
Really?
I quit smoking
I see
Who?
I quit
I see
I eat a lot
How long has it been since you quit?
2 and a half months
I want to quit smoking
I don't think I should quit
That's right
It's good to smoke when you have it
It's getting stronger
What's getting stronger?
The amount of smoke
The amount of smoke?
Yamasaki, out
What do you mean by the amount of smoke?
Out
No way
What?
Ouch
You shouldn't smoke
Did you do it on purpose?
No
If you did it on purpose, you shouldn't smoke
I don't know
What?
The gorilla is weird
I'm going to die
Stop it
Tanaka
You don't have to talk
Ouch
I did it
You always try to talk
No
If you did it on purpose, you shouldn't smoke
I wanted to explain
You shouldn't smoke
It's weird
What are you doing?
It's not that time yet
Out
Yamada
Yamasaki
What?
Why are you doing this?
I thought you were going to be okay
Stop it
Why are you talking in a gentle voice?
Ouch
What is he doing?
He's wearing a uniform
He's amazing
It's not that time yet
Ouch
Yamada
Yamasaki
What are you doing?
Ouch
I don't like it
I thought you were going to be okay
Stop it
Out
Yamada
Yamasaki
Stop it
Ouch
It's cold
This is
Stop it
Yamada
Out
Stop it
He's wearing a uniform
Ouch
It's 9pm
7 hours have passed since the punishment game started
It's time for you to go to bed
Let's go to the hot spring
You want to go to the hot spring, don't you?
Yes
Let's go
Shall we go?
Yes
This hot spring is one of the few hot springs in Japan
Enjoy
Actually, what is Matsumoto doing in the shadow of the bath?
Yamada
Out
Ouch
I did it
I'm tired
Yamada
Yamasaki
Out
Yamada
Wait
Ouch
Wait a minute
What are you doing?
What are you doing on TV?
You can't be naked in the hot spring
I've prepared a hot spring
Hey, Tanaka
Yamasaki
Out
Who is it?
Please be kind to me
Please
Ouch
It hurts so much
Tanaka
Put this on
Next
Yamasaki
Is this ready?
I don't want to put this on
Next, Yamada
Yamada
Out
Ouch
Yamada
Out
Tanaka
Why are you doing this?
Ouch
It hurts so much
Why are you doing this?
Ouch
Out
Next
Yamada
Out
Why are you doing this?
Ouch
Hey, Fujiwara
Out
Hey
The ball flew
What is this?
Why?
Yamasaki
Why are you doing this?
Ouch
Tanaka has a great camera
I can't catch it at all
This is the story of a military critic
I can't catch it
It was big when I took it out of the basket
That's
It's so hot
What is this?
I'm so jealous
It's so hot
What is this?
Tanaka
Out
Please cut my eyes
Ouch
I don't like it
It's hot
You've been looking at me all the time, haven't you?
You've been looking at me, haven't you?
It's so hot
I know
Hamada, you're so persistent
How long are you going to be like this?
Die
Yamaguchi, why don't you try it on?
At 10 o'clock in the afternoon, a familiar figure comes to the three people in the room
Yes
Thank you for your hard work
There's a wedding coming up soon, so it's kind of like a follow-up. Is everyone okay?
It looks like you're tired
Is everyone okay?
Fukada
What?
Let me hear the speech again
The speech is supposed to be done at the ceremony
Fukada, let me hear the speech again
I'll do it at the ceremony
Let me hear it again
I'll go home when I hear it
Are you done?
There are three important bags for a couple to be happy
The first one is an egg bag
I got an egg
Fukada, let me hear it again
I'm sorry
That's enough
Fukada, let me hear it
Fukada, let me hear it again
I'll go home when I hear it
It doesn't matter if it's an ogiwara or a hagiwara
Ogifara and hagiwara
Are you done?
Fukada, let me hear it again
I'll go home when I hear it
That's enough
Kanaka
Yamasaki
No
Ouch
Once again, Matsumoto makes a plan to bring Hamada and the others down
Matsumoto
How is it?
You're doing pretty well in the punishment game
Do you want some water?
Yamasaki, out
What is that?
What is it?
Ouch
It's a human-beast
I don't know why you look so disgusted
I'll split you up
You're here to encourage me
Talk
I'm just talking
Why did you bring this?
What is it?
I want you to see it
Yamasaki
Kanaka
Out
It's a goal
Ouch
I'm sorry
I wanted to show you
Do you like this kind of game?
It's a goal
That was close
It's fun
It's a goal
It's normal
Why is it all gold?
I'm counting on you
It hurts
I want to stop when I'm done
I'm not going
Good luck
I haven't even folded it back yet
What are you doing?
Hamada
Out
What are you doing?
I'm counting on you
See you
Thank you
What?
Hamada
Out
What are you doing?
It hurts
I'm going in
Hey
Are you okay?
What is this?
Hamada
Out
Stop it
It hurts
It's 11 p.m.
The three of them haven't eaten anything since they arrived in Yugawara
They're hungry or full
It stinks
You guys stink
You guys keep saying you're hungry
I prepared food
Do you want to eat?
I don't want to eat
It can't be helped
Let's eat
Let's get back into it
Let's do that
You don't know what it is, do you?
I don't know either
It's different
What?
Yamasaki
Hamada
Out
Stop it
It hurts
What is this?
It's a snack
I'm going to eat it
Tanaka
Out
It hurts
What are you doing?
I don't want to eat
You don't have to laugh
What is this?
What is that?
It's underwear
I ate a lot
I'm in a bad mood
Excuse me
Actually, we have a Japan tour in the room next door
I'm going to make a little noise
I ate a lot
Thank you very much
Please come back with the best drink
I'm tired
Yamasaki
Out
What are you doing?
I ate a lot
It hurts
10 hours from the start of the punishment game
After a series of attacks, the three of them started to look tired
What are you going to do with Mr. Malik?
Talk
Do you have a name?
Was it a Japanese name?
Was it Matsuo Shoukyokusai?
Matsuo
Where did you bring it from?
Tanaka
Out
Do you have another name?
What kind of name is Matsuo Shoukyokusai?
It's a very important person
It hurts
But that's because you say you don't know Matsuo Shoukyokusai
Do you know Matsuo Shoukyokusai?
I don't know
Was it when you were dressed up as an old man?
That's right
I wonder if you were doing something
Let's go to the next design parma
What is a design parma?
This is my
Why
I only draw the top
I think you can do it
But it's a part parma, probably a design parma
It's not
Who is a design parma?
I don't know
Probably
Probably?
Tanaka
Out
I don't know Tanaka
I don't know
I know that, but probably?
It hurts
Actually today
Hollywood stars are staying here
I want to say hello to something like you
I'll be surprised
Please
You look like you're crying
Yamasaki
Out
I've seen it many times
Mr. Deniro
Good evening
Tanaka
Out
It hurts
how much money do you have?
I have 90 million
why!?
this is gross, please
man, you really are crazy
OUCH
why
I didn't mean to help you
Ah, wait!
Ah, that hurts!
Why are you pretending to sleep?
I'll never laugh!
This is Deniro throwing a hammer.
Deniro-san is busy too, so I'll give him a hammer.
I'm glad.
Ouch, that hurt.
You know what?
Yes?
I'm really sorry.
It was C-3PO, right?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
It's different from the hammer.
It comes out like this, right?
I wanted to open it and take out the in-ring.
The in-ring is like this, so I can't open it.
Nakamura went and tried to open it and put in the in-ring.
Just opening it makes me laugh.
Ah, is that so?
I wanted to open it and take out the in-ring.
But the in-ring is like this again.
I'll close it.
I'll close it again!
I'll take out the in-ring again!
Ah, is that so?
But the in-ring is like this again.
Ah, it hurts.
I'm sorry!
Go home!
One o'clock in the morning. 11 hours have passed since the start, and the three of them look pretty tired.
But don't worry about that.
With or without the hammer, they'll get a new license.
They'll get a new license.
He's really fast.
He's not a professional at all.
He's been doing it many times.
He's like a dog.
Hello?
Yeah.
Black glasses.
Yeah, I'm not going to say that right now.
What are you saying?
Yes.
Change.
I'm a contact lens guy.
Wait a minute.
You're going to be surprised.
I'm more surprised than laughing.
It hurts.
I've been to Paris about three times.
Really?
Yes.
You've been there that many times?
I've been there.
I've never been there.
He's doing his best.
I can't help but laugh.
He's laughing a lot.
Let's change the atmosphere here.
Let's do it.
Let's proceed to the next stage.
Let's move on to the first question.
Do an impersonation of KUWATA KEISUKE.
End please.
Let's move on to Fujiwara.
Do an impersonation of KUWATA KEISUKE.
No knife.
I can't help it.
Look, look at me.
That was safe, right?
That was strong, right?
That was strong.
That was strange.
Go Hiromi's Mano Manchi
and what is it?
Takoyaki.
What is it?
I can't do it, I can't do it.
It's okay, it's okay.
Okonomiyaki.
That was good, right?
That was cute.
That was good.
Okonomiyaki.
Yamazaki, what is it?
I've heard it so many times.
Okonomiyaki.
It hurts.
I came here to have fun.
I had fun.
If you have any hope, I'll listen to you.
Take off your glasses and talk.
I'm getting angry.
So, Hamada.
If it's a person,
look at the person who's talking and talk.
Hamada.
I don't want to do it anymore.
What?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't want to do it anymore.
Who are you taking with you?
Tell me clearly.
Look at the face.
Hamada.
I don't want to do it anymore.
Fujiwara.
Let's go home.
It's 2 a.m.
12 hours have passed since the start.
Here, three people go to the hall next to the inn.
Then.
I fell.
I'm scared.
I can't see anything.
Then they arrive at the temple.
Here, the priest will show us a horrible ghost photo.
Here we go.
First, look at this.
Boys are doing physical training.
Among the five.
It's unusual for two people to be together.
The parents of the temple are joking.
But look closely.
The temple's reverse.
Each one.
Most of them are Kirishima.
This is no exception.
In the stilted shrine,
There is no Kirishima.
This is a absolutely certain image.
This is a completely certain image.
In the future,
in the future,
be careful of Kirishima.
She's the danful  tHis iod ochre
It's enmity again
He's still running.
That was terrible!
You were aiming for it!
You're the one who got hit!
Hamada, Yamasaki, out!
It's Gold-san.
No, it's not Gold-san.
I'm scared.
Gold-san.
That's not it.
It's not Gold-san.
It's 3 o'clock in the morning, and the three of them go back to the hot spring.
But there's a strange trap there, too.
I wonder what it is.
It's 3 o'clock in the morning, and the three of them go back to the hot spring.
But there's a strange trap there, too.
I wonder what it is.
It's 3 o'clock in the morning, and the three of them go back to the hot spring.
But there's a strange trap there, too.
No!
What's going on?
You didn't see it, did you?
I didn't see it at all.
Watch out!
Are you okay?
It's hot.
It's from the forest.
It suddenly got hot.
That's right.
Tanaka, let's go.
Hamada, out.
It was scary.
I was scared too.
It's gold.
It was on the right side.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's really hot.
I like it.
It's hot.
Stop it.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
There is a specialty in this inn.
It's a party.
Let's go.
Is it a different room?
Of course not.
It's amazing.
It's a night show.
Hamada, please enjoy it.
Please enjoy it.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
It hurts.
What are you doing?
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
Let's go.
Hamada, you should come here.
The angle is bad.
What are you doing?
Let's go.
It hurts.
I understand.
Let's go.
Hamada, please wait.
It hurts.
Let's go.
After leaving the room, they go to the night show.
The punishment game escalates at the night show.
Who will be the winner?
Welcome.
We will give you a fun dinner show.
The superstar of the Showa era is here.
Please welcome him.
It's so cute.
I can see the end of my life.
It hurts.
Let's go to the night show.
Cool.
Hamada, Yamasaki, out.
It hurts.
Please come here.
Next is Yoshimoto.
Please welcome him.
Yamashita.
Yamashita, out.
Hikunenji.
Hikunenji, out.
Next is a fresh new wave.
I will do an impersonation.
Showa style radio.
Put your lips on a red apple.
Showa 20th Anniversary.
The Japanese army is defeated.
Next is
Katsura.
Please welcome him.
Please come here.
He came to see the show.
Yamasaki, Tanaka, out.
It was fun.
It was suitable for the night show.
It will be a good memory.
Next is a big veteran.
Please welcome them.
Please come here.
He looks like him.
Yamasaki, out.
I can't help it.
At 4 a.m., the night show is over.
It's time for the three of them to go to bed.
However...
I was sleepy.
I also want to sleep.
I woke up.
I can't help it.
I don't know what to do.
Hamada, Yamasaki, out.
I can't help it.
I don't know what to do.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to wash up.
I can't help it.
Hamada, out.
The three of them went to bed.
They woke up at 7 a.m.
Wake up, everyone.
Wake up.
The fun punishment game is still going on.
Yamasaki, wake up.
Hamada, out.
I forgot.
What is it?
It's like a house.
I'm going to wash up.
The three of them went to bed.
They woke up at 7 a.m.
Hamada, you're the director of the day.
Yes.
You're going to write a sports newspaper, right?
It's delicious.
You're not eating meat again.
He's weak.
It's really delicious.
I've been calling you for a long time.
You did a great job today.
It was fun.
He wrote down the details.
He wrote down the details of the game.
I've been drinking since morning.
I'm going to read the name of the newspaper.
Escargoman.
Is this an interview?
This newspaper was made just like a real sports newspaper.
There was a surprising match between Dynamite and Shikoku.
Shikoku challenged the champion Escargoman, but he was defeated in 58 seconds from the start of the game.
I lost in 58 seconds.
It hurts.
This is bad.
Ah, it hurts!
He's already passed the check-out.
Why?
The check-out time is approaching, so shall we go to the lobby?
It's Hanada.
It's close, it's close.
It's close!
Hanada, out!
What is this?
It's here.
Why did he pick up the money at the end?
Hanada, out!
The employees are here, so let's say hello to them.
Stand in a line.
Hanada, out.
Thank you for your hard work over the past two days.
Thank you for your hard work.
We have prepared a small gift from the employees.
Thank you for your hard work over the past two days.
Everyone, I ask for your cooperation.
One, two, three!
Chikaku! Chikaku!
Shinkaku! Shinkaku!
Hanada! Hanada!
Chikaku! Chikaku!
Shinkaku! Shinkaku!
I'm sorry.
Ouch!
The last one is the best.
What are you doing?
Don't sing like that.
It was funny.
You were the best.
Thank you.
I was the best when I was in Fukuyama.
I'm 52 years old.
The number is different.
I have been on the search more than 20 times.
I will sing the last song.
That song is very beautiful.
This song is very beautiful.
This song is very profound.
This is beautiful.
This is very beautiful.
This is amazing.
Baka, the last one.
That's it?
Don't sing like that!
There's no such thing.
But you're singing.
That's right.
You're singing the best beat.
Who cares about the world?
Is that all?
Yes, that's about it.
Thank you.
Let's go.