What do you mean by that?
We will now begin the trial.
Defendant, please enter.
What is this?
We will now begin the trial of the case against Hamada downtown.
The defendant will defend himself, so please take your seats.
You guys are so stupid.
Defendant, please enter.
What is this?
There is no doubt that it is Hamada Masato-san.
Shut up! You can tell by looking at him.
So it is Osaka dialect after all.
You always say that you haven't done plastic surgery.
I said I haven't done it!
So there is no doubt?
I haven't done it.
I haven't been asked anything.
I was brought here.
You are often on TV.
You too!
You have been on TV recently.
Do you know the famous actress Haruko Sagara?
I know her.
She has a kissing scene in the drama.
Haruko Sagara left a comment.
I don't think so.
I want you to see it.
Test the evidence.
Who the hell are you?
I have been working with Yama-chan in the drama.
We are still close friends.
There was a kissing scene in the drama.
When I touched her lips,
I could feel her lips.
It was like a resin.
I couldn't feel her body temperature.
It was like a fake.
You didn't tell me!
Hey, judge.
You didn't tell me.
You made me tell you.
No, I didn't.
As I have been told,
her lips are not real.
No, they are real.
I want to talk about her lips.
Judge, please look at this.
This is your recent photo.
You can't tell from this distance.
You zoom in and zoom out.
Wait!
You can't tell from this distance.
I can't tell.
We almost gave up.
Wait! Let's try one more time.
One more time.
What is this?
Let me count.
108 needles.
You can tell from this distance.
It's strange.
108 needles.
Why is it black?
You can't do this kind of bad surgery.
It's just the number of human instincts.
You can't tell from this distance.
I can tell from this distance.
We did a lot of research.
You can't live without being hospitalized.
You have been hospitalized for about a week.
There is a photo.
Really?
Please look at this.
There is no such thing.
What is this?
Wait!
You are scary.
Why are you laughing at me?
I was very happy that the surgery went well.
I was very happy.
Are you stupid?
You can't tell from this distance.
I understand.
Can I call the witness?
Witness.
Witness?
Yes.
Who is it?
I see.
What are you doing?
What is this?
Thank you.
I often work with Mr. Hamada.
We take the bus together.
When I saw Mr. Hamada sleeping, I thought he was tired.
Mr. Hamada was talking in his sleep.
He told me to fix my mouth again.
I wondered what kind of dream he was having.
I often go to drink with Mr. Hamada's apprentice.
Mr. Hamada tells his apprentice something.
He always tells me that I have to get a plastic surgery to make a living as an entertainer.
You said it clearly.
When did you hear that?
I don't have an apprentice.
That's a lie.
What kind of relationship do you have with him?
He told me that he was Mr. Hamada's apprentice.
Do you have any evidence?
Yes.
Excuse me.
What do you mean?
When Mr. Hamada left Tokyo and I met him in my dream, I went to see him.
He called me and I went to the bathroom.
He told me to keep this.
I kept this.
I'm sorry.
What is this? Is it a piece of paper?
Yes, it is.
What is this?
May I?
Yes.
What is this?
This is the front lip.
Is this a
Thank you very much.
Don't you usually say something like that?
There are many things like this.
What are you talking about?
When I had a meal with him at work, the waitress said,
I want you to change your mouth.
I showed a strange reaction to that change of mouth.
What is that?
I have another witness.
It's okay.
Who are you?
Don't you know me?
I'm a smoker in Shinjuku.
I think it was three or four years ago.
He came to my store and said,
Auntie, do you have a big mask?
I gave him a big mask and he came to buy it.
At that time, the mask I sold was this.
This is a big deal to deceive.
How many masks do you have?
Don't you know?
Thank you very much.
Is it just for that?
I'm still wearing white.
I haven't done it yet.
Then, I would like to pursue a more psychological part.
Is it okay?
Charter-based molding judgment vote.
Do you have such a thing?
You're just making it up.
First of all, let's see this.
If you go on a date.
Date?
What is a date?
I don't know that.
I can't answer.
If you go on a date, do you go to an amusement park?
I don't have much to ride.
Yes.
Was the first kiss your room?
No.
Do you like coffee?
Are you molding your lips?
It's like this.
You...
Show me other parts.
Is it okay if I go into a big mess?
Let's see this.
What is it?
This is Hamada Masato's skull.
I showed this to an expert.
I had him put meat on it.
Then you can see the real Hamada's face.
If the real Hamada's face is different from the one you see now,
it means it's molded.
So I asked an expert to make the real Hamada.
Hikobumi, come to the center.
If you go from here,
Hamada Masato's face looks like this.
This is the real Hamada Masato.
Why is it like this?
This is scary.
Is it okay?
What?
I will now give the verdict to the defendant, Hamada Masato.
The verdict is death sentence.
What?
What are you doing?
Stop it.
Thank you very much.
Ladies and gentlemen.
It's been two weeks.
What?
That's right.
What are you doing?
It's been two weeks.
Are you not used to the audience today?
It's been a long time.
Are you getting used to it?
It's not the first time I've seen it.
I'm not impressed.
Is that so?
You don't answer.
I'm not old enough to be impressed.
That's right.
I'll die in 50 years.
That's not true.
It's not important now.
It's hard.
What?
You're having a hard time.
I'm looking for it.
What's so hard about it?
I don't think about it in advance.
That's right.
It's hard.
What?
What's the atmosphere like?
I was in a taxi.
There was a truck coming next to me.
It was a woman.
It was a bad place.
It was shaking.
I drank a bottle of milk desperately.
I'll drink it after I go to Thailand.
It's powdery.
And it's a bottle of milk.
I laughed a little.
Is that so?
That's right.
You're not a student anymore, are you?
I'm not a student anymore.
All the customers here are working, right?
That's right.
I'm not a student anymore.
I want to work as a salaryman for about a year.
Can you go to work at the same time every day?
What time is the company now?
It's 9 o'clock.
Can you go to work at 9 o'clock?
I'm a celebrity.
I can't go to work at 9 o'clock tomorrow.
But I have to go to work at 9 o'clock.
Can you go to work at 9 o'clock?
I'm a student, so I can go to work at 9 o'clock.
If I get on the train, I can't go to work at 9 o'clock.
Is that true?
That's right.
It's hard.
I want to fall in love in the car.
I want to fall in love in the car at my age.
There is such a thing.
I can't go to work at 9 o'clock.
Is that true?
I don't say such a thing.
That's true.
That's a good thing.
Is that so?
If you work in the same workplace, do you go out?
Yes.
Do you make a phone call?
Do you call your mother?
I don't do such a thing.
It's fun.
I have only one paper, but I can copy many papers.
It's fun to laugh.
I have an accident once.
I have been driving a car for more than 10 years.
No.
I was spinning in the parking lot.
I was in a good mood.
I have an accident once.
What is it?
It's a car accident.
Why do I usually get a car accident?
I resist it.
I have been hit many times.
I have never been hit by a car accident.
That's not true.
I have been hit by a car accident once before.
When I got off the car, I was in a bad mood.
I was in a bad mood.
Why?
Why are you hitting me?
I don't know.
I was in a bad mood.
Go.
Why do you resist it?
It has nothing to do with me.
Go.
What are you doing?
This is my coat.
I will write.
I have a sister.
I get excited when I see my sister's pajamas.
Do you have a sister?
Did you do something?
I have a sister.
What are you doing?
Sexual harassment.
I don't do that.
Don't say that.
Did you do it?
I don't do that.
That's not true.
Really?
Did you do it?
When you are sleeping...
What?
I don't care if you are sleeping.
I don't care.
When you are sleeping...
You have a sister, right?
Just a little.
Really?
I don't have a sister.
I don't know if you are a man or not, but you have a sister.
Did you look at her?
I did.
I see.
What did you look at?
When you are changing clothes.
Why?
When you are changing clothes, you wear underwear.
No.
Is it because it's sour?
When you are changing your underwear...
What does that mean?
That's when you change.
That's not changing.
When you are changing your underwear...
Have you ever looked at your sister when you are changing your underwear?
You haven't?
Everyone does that.
I think I looked at my sister when I was changing my underwear.
You didn't look at her.
We know that.
We know that we are being bullied.
When I look at my sister, I can't help but look at her.
Why?
Why do you look at your sister?
I can't help but look at her.
Why do birds move their necks in an unnatural way?
Like this.
Actually...
Why do you know that?
Birds don't have necks.
What?
What do you mean?
They don't have necks.
They have necks.
They just sit on their bodies.
They are connected.
They don't do anything good.
They move like this.
Have you ever seen a bird walking like this?
If it falls, it's bad.
I know that.
It will die.
It will die in this group.
There is a theory.
A theory?
I see.
I don't know.
Who is the person at the emergency exit?
Who is it?
I don't know until I ask you.
Do you know?
Of course I know.
Is it a woman or a man?
It's a man.
There is a model.
There is a model?
Yes.
How many people are there?
I don't know.
Everyone knows.
What?
Really?
Yes.
Who is it?
Shinichi Chiba.
The official name of Nihon TV is Nihon TV Broadcasting Company.
Yes.
The official name of Yokohama Kinbai is The Crazy Rider Yokohama Kinbai Rolling Special.
Please tell me the official name of downtown.
Everyone says downtown.
It's different.
It's not easy to say that.
That's right.
Actually, there is more.
Yes.
You don't know.
It's always in me.
When I hear the name of downtown, I think it's different.
I think it's great.
Really?
Please tell me.
What?
The official name.
The official name?
What is it?
Professor.
What are you talking about?
I can't hear it and I don't know what it is.
Professor?
Professor.