THE NEXT DAY
He's up.
Good morning.
He's so chubby.
I'm so pissed.
Did you see the guy in the black suit?
I saw him a little.
I didn't see him at all.
Did he laugh at you?
Was it a joke?
No, they came out and did it.
Did they laugh at you?
No, they didn't.
Right?
Why didn't you tell them?
They didn't have to laugh.
No, they didn't.
They were rude.
Rude?
They didn't listen to you because your hair was long.
They said that to you, right?
They didn't listen to you, right?
They were comedians.
They weren't comedians.
Right?
They wouldn't be comedians if they were like that.
They were wearing dirty clothes.
I don't think so.
I don't know.
Bring me some paper.
Paper?
Write your name on this.
I'll give it to you.
I'll give it to you as soon as possible.
Did you know where they were?
What are you talking about?
Let's fly a helicopter.
What?
Why do you want to fly a helicopter?
Get a pigeon.
Give me a pigeon.
Why are you doing this?
I don't know.
Can you do it?
I think I can do it.
I'll get it ready.
Let's fly a helicopter.
Stop it.
Let's stop it.
Let's fly a helicopter.
Write your name on this.
I'll write it.
Stop saying, we are.
Let's fly a helicopter.
Let's go.
Everyone.
Yes.
Let's fly a helicopter.
What are you talking about?
Get on the bus.
I'm going to the hospital.
This program is provided by the sponsor.
Are you coming?
I don't think I'm coming.
You're not coming, are you?
You shouldn't say that.
I invited you.
Why didn't you come?
Who am I?
Everyone knows.
It's okay.
I went to your house.
We didn't do anything.
We just listened to the song.
What song?
I'm going to your house.
I don't think I'm coming.
I'm not coming.
Let's go home in 10 minutes.
Is that so?
What?
Let's go together.
It's okay.
She's coming back.
She's good.
We want to hear her sing.
Are you ready?
Is that so?
I don't know
He's doing it
I can't do it
Asuka got hit
Chagi
Let's ride together
This is long
You have to put your ears out
Put your ears out?
Did Nishikawa-san say that?
You have to put your ears out
I have to put my shoes on
It's easy to move
You can do it
It's strange
You have to put your shoes on
When they appear, put your hands together
Well done
I'm gonna do it
Hey
I'm not saying it because I don't like it
I'm saying it on behalf of you guys
I didn't know
Hey
I'm going to be a great cartoonist
I won't let that happen
I've done it before
How's it?
I guess this is my life
He came
He understood me
I said sorry and said it was just a joke
I told him I'd sell him
I said I'd pay him back
He said I was too fat
I look thin on TV
But I was fat
I said everything I wanted to say
I can't sell for them
It depends on my Chinese
I get it
I don't care who says it
Happy birthday
Ladies and gentlemen
It's Hamada's birthday
He drank two cups of champagne
He's in a bad mood
What do you want to do?
I want to watch the wide show
Speak faster
There was a big incident in Osaka
I didn't know
He went fishing on his day off
He said his back hurt
His back?
He looked at his back and said
You've been stabbed
Really?
You're lying
It was on the news
It's true that it happened
But you're wrong
My back hurts
Please watch it
It's on the news
My back hurts
Please watch it
I won't say it
He's an old man from Osaka
There was a big fire in NGK
There was a big fire
There was takoyaki
I asked for takoyaki
There was a big fire
I asked him to wait
There are many things
Have you calmed down?
I'm in a good mood
You're acting like a human
I'm fine
It's hot
What are you doing?
You're putting it in again
If you hadn't put the mic here
I would have shown it
You're putting it in again
You took it off
I didn't mean to make it popular
Don't cut it
I'm sorry
It's very popular
Who is it popular with?
Marunouchi
Young salaryman
It's very popular
I didn't mean it
I don't know if you like it
I always do it
I had a class called Fuji Sankei Classic
I was doing it in the rain
It's wet
I was doing it
Did someone say hello to you?
It's usual
Hi
I thought you were filming
You were recording?
It was
Actually, we're the same.
Oh, hello!
We're the same.
I was caught by the camera.
Also, the commercial...
What do you mean by that?
At first, I thought it was a bit of a joke, so I made it sound good.
You deceived me.
The commercial didn't cost any money.
There are a lot of commercials that are like the Sangaria of the Shimoda Kageki.
It's like...
I was just doing this in front of Kuromaki.
I'm in the middle!
That's terrible, isn't it?
It's like the Shimoda Kageki commercial is worth a lot of money.
It's worth a lot of money.
The commercial is true.
That's right. It's terrible.
You should have spent more money.
I don't have any money right now.
I don't think I'll be able to do one more commercial.
It's not broken at all.
I'm not selling it anymore.
I'm selling it!
Now?
That's right.
That's the rest of the city.
I'm going to the convenience store.
I'm going to put it in the back of the big refrigerator.
It's going to flow forward.
There are few products that are selling well, so I have to add them right away.
That's right.
Zura!
The popular one is a little lukewarm.
It's cold!
Why is there a shutter in the convenience store and family restaurant that is open 24 hours a day?
There are times when you can rest 24 hours a day.
I can't rest 24 hours a day.
I don't know how many days you can rest on New Year's Day.
No, it's not that. The convenience store is open even on New Year's Day.
I take a break when I have something to do.
You're wearing a shutter for that time.
That's right.
Just for that?
Yes.
See you again.
When you have to set up a shop in a building, you have to wear a shutter.
That's right!
In the end, you get to know me by asking me all the questions.
Every time, a lot of customers come.
When a really good customer comes,
when I think this is a good customer,
I don't let them go.
Don't be ridiculous.
Do you understand?
What?
Don't push yourself too hard.
Recently, a shocking thing has become the topic of our class.
Masatoshi-kun's...
Ah, me?
Masatoshi-kun's is called a side shoulder.
Why?
I want you to confirm that Masatoshi-kun's is different.
Wait a minute.
But if you look at me and say,
Ah!
I get it!
What are you talking about?
No, I don't say that.
Then look at me.
Wait a minute.
The PC is not working either.
Thank you for the food.
It's different.
Why are you crying?
No, no.
It's not a side shoulder at all.
What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
Hey!
Come on, get a hold of yourself.
No, but...
A side shoulder is a little smelly for everyone.
Ah...
You don't wear this kind of thing, do you?
I'll never wear it.
Why do you know that?
I'm sorry.
The smell...
It's different, you idiot.
I really don't like it.
My feet don't stink either.
It doesn't stink at all.
Even my toes stink, you idiot.
Hey, hey, are you serious?
My toes don't stink like my sister before.
Your sister stinks like that.
It stinks.
It definitely stinks.
My feet don't stink at all.
My breath doesn't stink either.
Your breath stinks.
You smell like a squid.
Why are you laughing?
Well, it's a tough joke.
What's that smell?
Have you ever smelled like poop?
No, no.
I think it was about 1,000, 1,000, 1,000 weeks ago.
Do you remember that?
Like the prince of the country of poop.
No, I'm serious.
I don't smell like poop.
I smell like poop sometimes.
It stinks.
You idiot.
No, it doesn't stink.
It doesn't stink?
Well, it stinks.
It doesn't stink.
I go to the movies a lot.
I like movies.
You go to the movies a lot?
But I can't go.
You can't go?
I can't go.
I like amusement parks.
You don't like amusement parks?
I don't like them.
Stop it.
Where did you have your first kiss?
You're so cool.
You're a chanson singer.
Why?
This is a chanson...
This is a chanson?
I can't sing.
Wait a minute.
You sing.
I went to the Shimming Land in Amagasaki.
Really?
Actually, I went to the Shimming Land in Amagasaki.
I said that on TV.
I don't know how he got it wrong.
Mr. Matsumoto and Ms. Amano kissed in the Shimming Land in Amagasaki.
Please tell me the moment when the newspaper turns into a newspaper.
It turns into something when you wrap it.
That's not it.
It's just now.
Where are you going?
The stage.
The sleeves.
Where is this?
I see.
That's what you're saying.
I got it.
I'll read the newspaper.
Read the newspaper.
I'll put the newspaper I've read in a rack.
I'll put it in the house I live in.
The moment you put it in, it's still a newspaper.
It's still a newspaper.
I have to make onigiri.
Make onigiri.
You're making onigiri?
I'm making onigiri.
Even then, it's still a newspaper?
It's still a newspaper.
It has nothing to do with it.
Onigiri, yes.
Mom, I'm done.
Hitoshi, please get the newspaper.
It's still a newspaper?
It's still a newspaper.
I'm nervous.
Hitoshi put his hand on it.
He took the newspaper.
At that time it's still a newspaper
It's still a newspaper
It's a newspaper
This is done
Wrap it
Put it here
At this time it's still a newspaper
What are you going to do with it?
Wrap it like this
No
The other way
Wrap it like this
Yes
I'm doing it while thinking
I don't know which is better
Like this
That's right
It's still a newspaper
Like this
Happy birthday to you
It's amazing
You are 31 years old
You are old
Hello
Open it
I want to be on TV
Happy birthday to you
Thank you
Are there any questions?
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.