Ladies and gentlemen.
Today, everyone is having fun.
Ah, everyone is having fun.
We didn't have an opening today.
Today, we played dodgeball.
You lost, didn't you?
Well, I still have a lot to say about that later.
Ah, is that so?
But, it's nothing.
Today, we'll have everyone watch the penalty game.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Here you go.
What's the time?
Eh, I can't see it.
I can't see it.
Wow!
It's a camera!
Ah, I don't like it.
Now, Mr. Matsumoto.
Yes.
Are you ready?
Well, the moment I went up and went down, it was a direct hit.
No, I really don't know.
Eh?
I can't broadcast it.
No, it's okay.
When I go out, I get hit a lot.
Really?
Why do you play dodgeball with your fans and get a penalty?
Now, is everyone ready?
We lost, so we don't have time.
Now, Mr. Matsumoto.
Good luck!
Wow!
I don't like it.
I don't like it anymore.
Wow, 40 meters.
My lips are dry.
I don't like it anymore.
Wow!
Welcome back!
I'm sorry.
I can't move.
This is the most scary song.
It's really scary.
I'm going to move.
Where are you going to move?
I was really scared.
My lips are dry.
What am I doing?
I'm going to move.
This is so scary.
I'm going to die.
This is a real punishment game.
I'm not afraid of Alta's Kikkou-shibari.
This is definitely scary.
What is this song?
Omo Ahoonumare
It's fun.
Yup.
You should raise your head.
It's like this all the time.
Everyone, try riding it.
Seriously.
It's really scary, that roller coaster.
That's true.
I knew it just by looking at it.
Actually, it's been out for a week or so.
Yes.
When Ama-chan decided to go to Parma No. 2,
I said, if I could go again,
if you give me a hint, I'll go again.
So I understood.
And when I came back,
when I saw that face,
I couldn't say no.
Seriously,
why isn't everyone scared of that?
I don't like it either.
I wasn't scared of the roller coaster either.
That's true.
I enjoyed it a lot.
I was the only one who crashed into it.
Why isn't everyone scared of that?
I couldn't get a good shot of it.
Well, a good shot...
Actually, that was my own head.
What?
You have such a beautiful head.
Well, I got hurt on both sides,
so I had to take it off.
Really?
But seriously,
everyone is so excited.
I don't know about that, but...
I don't like it either.
I moved around a little bit,
and then...
Don't be scared.
I'm definitely not scared,
but I was more scared than you.
Why?
It's terrible when you get on a roller coaster.
In a sense,
I don't want the staff to think that I got on it.
That's not true.
It's terrible.
It's really terrible.
That's not true.
In Osaka,
there's a place called Hanshin Park.
It's a small amusement park.
You can fly there.
There's a roller coaster there.
It's like a rabbit coaster.
Oh, a rabbit coaster.
It's a roller coaster.
I got on it,
called it,
and screamed.
And then,
I got hit on my back.
I got hit on my back
with a heavy hit.
And then,
I lost all my precious memories.
What memories?
The memories of you and the staff getting on it.
It's terrible.
It's really terrible.
But,
that was the last time
that you were on a roller coaster.
Why?
Because it was a long time ago.
If you were on a roller coaster in the middle.
If you pursue your fear,
you'll be able to ride more rides.
But, it's still too early.
It's not like that.
But,
the one that was spinning normally,
it developed a little,
and it started to spin once.
And then,
it went straight down.
there's no more rails.
Probably.
And from here,
there's something like a capsule.
And then,
boom!
It's using this kind of space.
It's like a coaster.
That will come.
It's developing little by little.
The one that comes after that,
this time,
it leaves the material as it is,
and goes into this capsule
with the yakuza.
No,
the meaning is different.
This is also scary.
The meaning is different.
That will be talked about a lot
during the ride.
Where did you come from?
That's right.
There's a yakuza from the other world.
When you enter,
you have a card.
If it's B, then B.
There's a B yakuza.
And then,
there's that yakuza.
I'm scared of that.
There's a long story until you fly.
I'm being asked a lot.
Sing a song.
After the ride,
boom!
Don't say anything.
I don't care about the story.
It's because you're going to lose.
Listen to me.
What?
It was in the postcard.
It was a loss for me.
Why?
I was wearing the postcard.
I was a wind god.
What?
A wind god.
The coat?
Yes.
That's why it's a loss.
What?
It's a loss if you're a wind god.
No, no, no.
It's a loss.
Don't say that.
I was a wind god.
So what?
What?
The wind is coming from you.
You know that, right?
Your fans.
Your fans were there.
And you.
The wind is coming from the other side.
And you guys stink.
You know what?
I was playing a game.
I couldn't play a game because you guys stink.
You should have told me earlier.
That's a lie.
The balls are different.
That's not true.
The balls were thrown like that.
The boys were like that.
The girls were like that.
And you guys were like grass.
The girls were like grass.
It was very difficult to move.
It was very difficult.
I just don't know.
It was really difficult to move.
You were running around.
You got hit and went out.
More than that, my health was really bad.
You don't know how bad my health was.
You got hit and went out.
It was really difficult at that time.
Why?
The night before.
I was staying at Yomiuriland Hotel.
You were staying at Yomiuriland Hotel?
Yes.
I was staying at Yomiuriland Hotel.
It was from 9 a.m.
The room next to me was shaking.
I couldn't sleep.
You couldn't sleep?
Yes.
Really?
What should I say?
You couldn't sleep.
There were many things.
What things?
You couldn't sleep.
You were an enemy of sports.
You were an enemy of sports?
The room next to you was shaking.
I got it.
You couldn't sleep.
What do you mean?
Do you think you mean look at that?
What?
Tell me.
If you say that.
Really?
You are not wrong about getting parched.
I'll kick you now.
If you hear what I said, you repent your sins.
I don't care.
I can do it.
With a beard, with a beard.
You've done something amazing.
So what is it?
Yomiuri Land Hotel.
I don't have shampoo.
I have soap in my head.
Can you break it?
But it's painful.
It's painful.
With soap like this?
I have soap in my head.
But it's a small one.
No, no.
The one in front of me is getting bigger.
It's getting bigger.
You have that much in the hotel?
Yes.
What does it have to do with which one I lost?
You didn't show up with shampoo in your head.
This mental damage.
That's amazing.
It's nothing.
You didn't show up at the store?
No.
The one with shampoo and conditioner?
I went to see it.
I went to the lobby to see if there was shampoo or conditioner.
I went to see it, but there wasn't.
There was a game at the game center.
I'll do it.
Why?
You went to buy shampoo and conditioner.
I'll do it.
When I see something like this, I don't feel good.
What game?
What do you call it?
Shooting game.
I'll do it.
You'll collapse.
What are you talking about?
You're going to collapse.
Let's settle this properly.
You're going to do it again?
I have to do it again.
What are you going to do this time?
It's a 100th anniversary.
This broadcast is 85th.
Let's do something on the 100th broadcast.
One idea is to play in Okinawa like last year.
That's one.
The rest is like this time.
I don't know which one, but let's gather the money.
I'm thinking about how many people will really gather this time.
I gathered 1000 people and found out.
500 of my fans and 500 of your fans.
After all, you have a lot of fans.
Did you look at my fans in such detail?
Did you look at my fans and other people's fans in such detail?
Your fans are a little strange.
Your fans are strange.
Your fans are...
What is this?
You have a lot of hair.
That's a man's hair.
Even a woman's hair is like that.
Even a woman's hair is tight.
What is tight?
It's pretty tight.
It's called a nose hair bun.
It's a nose hair bun.
How many times did you do that?
Why did you change the number of the nose hair bun?
I look at dirty things.
You look at the number again, make a phone call, make an appointment.
It's a nose hair bun.
What is your name?
My name is Yuki Oseki.
How old are you?
I'm 22 years old.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I don't have a boyfriend now.
What is it like?
What is it like to be a comedian?
I like comedians.
Yuki Oseki.
What is it?
Where is that nose hair bun?
What is that guy?
It's like a mini bomb.
It's like a nose hair bun.
Bang!
I have a lot of hair.
It's like a dream.
Bang!
Thank you very much.
It's me.
Before the postcard.
The week before.
I don't really care.
I don't care if I get bald.
Right?
Marukome's audition or something.
You did it, right?
If my staff calls Marukome headquarters,
Please come to the audition.
I don't know how many generations of Marukome are there now.
But if you go to the audition and get chosen,
With this body type.
With a bald head.
Marukome.
Please give me a break.
If you get chosen,
You can go to the audition.
What?
You don't have to do that.
Bring the camera.
I'll go with you.
On that day,
At Kin-chan's time.
There was an audition.
Let's make it like a making movie.
Right?
Let's go.
What are you talking about?
What?
I'm just going to the audition.
Then you should go too.
What kind of audition?
You can be bald.
Marukome.
Moon-chan or something.
What?
You can dye your hair.
That's really a bad idea.
If you do that, it will be funny.
Dye your hair and become Moon-chan.
Are you stupid?
Why?
That's not going to happen.
It's funny.
If you dye your hair and come out.
If you do something like an audition,
I understand.
Moon-chan.
You can be an assistant.
You should be Gen-san.
Gen-san has never appeared before.
I can't make it like Gen-san.
That's what you said.
Marukome.
This is a good match.
I'll talk to you.
I'll see if Gen-san can make it.
Gen-san and Marukome.
Let's do that.
OK?
Just in case.
OK.
Let me introduce the letter.
I'm a girl in the third year of junior high school.
Have you ever felt embarrassed?
Last summer, after the pool,
I forgot to tighten my skirt.
I was in front of my favorite person.
A man with a strange face told me,
You have a hole in your jacket.
As soon as I put my hand on my jacket,
Two bags of napkins fell from my skirt pocket.
I've ever had an ultra high-class feeling.
It's embarrassing.
That's not good.
That's embarrassing.
Do you ever feel embarrassed?
Embarrassing.
I don't think so.
Well, I still don't know.
My mother.
We went to Osaka Castle.
That was the most embarrassing.
In Osaka Castle,
It's like an old ruins.
There's something written on the ground like a stone.
It's like a good story.
My mother read it like this.
This is the person in my arms.
This is the history of the castle.
There was a school trip.
There were a lot of people around.
My mother read it.
Everyone was looking at it.
When my mother came to the middle,
Her teeth fell off.
Because it's an elephant.
Kill it.
Her teeth fell off.
I can't stand it anymore.
What did your mother do at that time?
Was she in a hurry?
No, no.
Her teeth fell off.
Because she doesn't have teeth.
She said,
Her pink teeth fell off.
It's like a sticky condom.
I watch it every week.
You watch it.
I have a question.
When Hama-chan is on TV,
She always raises her bangs.
Is it because Hama-chan likes it?
Or is it because of the stylist?
I think it's cuter with bangs.
What do you think, Mach-chan?
It doesn't matter.
Hello.
Yes.
So,
You're going to have an audition in July.
Are you going?
Why?
If I'm going to attend, I'm going.
The staff is going to attend.
Right?
Let's do that.
Yes.
I'm going.
So, you're going to attend.
Don't say that.
Wait.
The audition date is already set.
I don't know what day it is in July.
Is it 31?
It's already set.
What day is it?
Wednesday.
I don't know what day it is on Wednesday.
It's a holiday.
Wednesday is the most important day of the week.
You have to work for a day.
No, no, no.
I don't want to be on a shitty program at midnight.
It's already set.
You have to take a break from golf every other year.
Don't think about it.
We're going to have a celebration.
We're going to ask for ideas.
We'll ask for ideas for the celebration.
It's a holiday day.
See you next week.
Thank you for watching!