I'm not going to use my time. Don't look at the opening!
Hettori Yamazaki vs. Taiman Gohan!
This isn't your first time, right?
It's not my first time.
You've been doing this about four times?
That's right.
Ah, I see.
Until now, I've been doing it mentally.
But this time, it's different.
What?
What do you call it? A fight!
You're going to use your body?
I'm going to use my body, so I might get injured.
You can really tell, right?
I can really tell.
Yamazaki-kun, go ahead!
That was a good one.
You're really going to use your body, right?
Yes.
Are you really strong?
I understand.
Does the pain go away?
It's because of your defense.
If you can defend yourself, the pain won't go away.
I understand.
Yamazaki-kun, go ahead!
Who are you going to use your body for?
Everyone has a flag, right?
The white one is Yamazaki-kun.
And the red one is your opponent.
Then, let's get started.
The first one, go ahead!
This one is your opponent.
Then, let's go!
Ready!
It's not me!
It's you!
You're lying!
It's fun!
It's not me!
It's you!
That was a good one!
Okay!
I lost.
That was strong!
What's your name?
Soeda Daichi.
Daichi-kun?
Yes.
How old are you?
I'm 4 years old.
4 years old?
That was strong!
Daichi-kun, are you doing something?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Boxing.
I'm doing something with Ultraman.
Everyone, go ahead!
Thank you.
Okay, let's go!
The second round, ready!
Hey!
드려도 되지?
드려도 되어!
You have to do it more and more!
I'm going to beat the A.G. with my mouth!
Let's continue!
Three times!
Ready!
Hey!
What are you doing?
I'm waiting for you!
Let's go!
What are you doing?
Hey!
This is Yamada Shokuhachi!
It looks like the opponent was really scared.
It's 2-1 now, so we still have a long way to go.
Let's continue.
The next person, please!
Hey!
I'm sorry.
You'll understand when you see it.
Hey!
What are you doing?
I'm waiting for you.
You're waiting for me?
What?
Hey!
What are you doing?
I'm going to beat the A.G. with my mouth!
You have to do it more and more!
What are you doing?
I'm going to beat the A.G. with my mouth!
You've already lost!
Please give me a chance!
Please!
I understand.
If I win this time, I want to win.
Please!
I'll do my best!
The last person, please!
Ready!
Go!
What are you doing?
Hey!
Wait!
You can't beat me!
I'll beat you!
Okay!
What are you doing?
I'm waiting for you!
You've already lost!
What are you doing?
Oh!
I got kicked!
I'm going to beat you!
Oh!
I got kicked!
I'm going to beat you!
Oh!
You've already lost!
What are you doing?
If I win, I can't fight anymore.
I don't care if I'm not good enough.
Oh no!
Let's do it as a special match.
Yes, please.
Say thanks to your master.
Thank you very much.
Then, just one more match.
Just one more match?
Yes.
Then, please step back.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you very much.
Today, we have Mr. Yamazaki.
How do you say it?
Gatsunatsu Ike.
Well, that kind of song is good.
Yes.
Yesterday.
The night is over, isn't it?
The night is over.
Yes.
I went home.
Yes, yes, yes.
About 4 o'clock.
At about 3 o'clock in the morning.
I turned around.
My grandmother was standing there.
How old was your grandmother?
She was over 70 years old.
Oh.
I couldn't turn around.
Because my grandmother was standing there.
Oh.
I was trying to get involved with her.
It was dangerous, so I stopped for a moment.
I dodged her.
I went to her house.
I came to her house.
I opened the shutter.
I went out for a moment.
I thought she was in the back.
A car was coming out of the house.
Yes, yes, yes.
I got out of the house.
I went to the back of the car.
My grandmother was standing there.
I was scared at night.
I was scared.
I was very scared.
I thought I should get in the car,
but the car would break when I saw it quickly.
ир.
No, it wouldn't.
I couldn't break it because the car was broken.
It would break.
I wondered where she was going.
I got in the car.
I closed the door.
I went to my grandmother's house,
put it in the back and put the car there.
I saw her Frau.
A otrosong.
When I looked at her,
she was very scared and trying to break the window of the control station of a passenger seat.
I screamed again.
At 4 o'clock in the night, you screamed twice.
I was really scared.
That's scary.
But I opened the window and I was like,
What?
You succeeded in making contact for the first time.
I succeeded.
I screamed again.
Because you were scared.
Because I was a scared idiot.
I was like, What?
I thought you were calm.
What?
The children.
I was scared.
I was really scared.
I was faster than usual.
That's scary.
I was like, What should I do?
I thought you were calm.
That's why I thought you raised your children.
What?
That's what I thought.
I didn't think you were calm.
I thought you were scared of my children.
I was scared.
That's scary.
Don't say things like that.
That means you did something to that old lady.
There are many things like that.
The other day, I was in the car with my writer, Takasu.
There was an amazing person in the car.
He didn't do anything.
There was only one lane, but he went the opposite lane.
That's the speed of light.
The traffic light was red.
When the traffic light was red, he went like this.
That's not true.
I was really surprised.
I was surprised.
I thought you took a picture of Mario's star.
That's the truth.
Then he disappeared.
What?
That's not true.
There was a car in front of me.
He went like this.
When he turned around, he disappeared.
That's not true.
That's the truth.
Speaking of strange, soccer is strange, too.
I think so, too.
I've been saying that since the J-League started.
I didn't say that much about Japanese soccer before that.
No, it's okay.
It's okay if you like soccer, but...
What do you call it?
It's all about the Japanese style.
That's for sure.
You can't just say you like it.
That's not true.
That's definitely strange.
What should I say?
Everyone likes soccer, so it's okay to watch soccer.
It doesn't matter who wins or loses.
That's the important thing.
Why?
I like soccer.
And it's Japan.
I'm a representative of Japan.
I don't like it that much, either.
There are so many people watching J-League.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Why do you support either of them?
I like soccer.
Good luck with soccer.
No, no, no.
That's not true.
I'm doing my best with soccer.
That's okay.
Why do you say you win or lose?
There are so many people watching.
There's no one to cheer for the ball.
That's what I think.
You have a bad character.
You're like,
Cheer up.
Come on.
The ball is coming!
I'm cheering for the ball.
But the numbers don't matter.
I don't care how many people are watching.
I'm worried about the number of people watching.
The ball is coming!
I'm afraid of the number of people watching.
Ball is coming!
The ball is coming.
The ball is coming!
I'm cheering for the ball.
You're so naive.
Don't everyone turn down the game?
Women are very simple. They are easy to get into.
Even though I wasn't interested in soccer at all.
Well, that's me.
I'm a person who misunderstands.
Is that so?
I'm a person who misunderstands women.
How can you say such a thing?
Do you know?
Do you know about the Macchan Jamba incident?
Ah, when I was in Osaka.
Macchan Jamba incident when I was in Osaka.
That's just what you say.
No, that's not it.
There was such an incident.
Hamada and I were invited to some kind of fashion show.
And I got a Jumbo jacket or something.
I said, this is good.
Then he said, I'll send it to you.
And he sent it to me.
Hamada said, I don't need it, I don't need it.
I left it at the head office.
Don't say such a thing.
I thought it was the same color, but I thought it was the same Jamba function.
I took a step back.
That's good.
I came, but I left it at the head office.
I don't need it right away, so I left it at the head office.
I said, I'll go get it that day.
That stupid Hashimoto.
I don't know.
What is he doing now?
I quit.
Hashimoto, the woman's manager.
Until a while ago, she was with Shinsuke Shimada.
That stupid woman.
What woman?
There's another ugly woman under that stupid woman.
There is.
This woman.
I'm going to take the Jamba little by little.
Do you want to come?
I thought so.
The ugly woman under the woman called Hashimoto.
Is my Jamba on?
Good morning.
You're busy, aren't you?
What? No way.
That's my Jamba.
Is that my Jamba?
What?
That's right.
Did you spit it out?
No, no.
That's right.
I'm going to wear it next time.
You can't wear it.
What?
No, no.
Give it back to me.
That's my Jamba, so give it back to me.
What?
She started crying.
Don't cry.
I'm not that angry with this woman.
Why?
What are you doing?
Hashimoto.
Hashimoto came and hugged the crying woman.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to say that.
Say it.
Don't.
What?
Don't cry.
What is it?
Hashimoto came and said,
Hashimoto, this woman has a boyfriend.
Really?
Is that right?
That woman, her boyfriend,
he's wearing Hamada's Jamba.
What?
Is it right?
So what?
It's a pair look!
Why do you get hungry when you're hungry?
Why do I get hungry?
Why do you get hungry?
Do I get hungry?
The beef will come out later
Why? Do I get hungry when I sing?
No, why do you get hungry?
No, do I get hungry?
Do I get hungry when I don't eat snacks?
Then isn't that number 2?
I don't know, but why do I get hungry?
Number 2 is...
Even if you get along, you'll get hungry!
Number 1 will get hungry?
No!
Number 2 is...
Whose land is the green land?
You're lying!
Do you think that far?
Then why do I get hungry?
You'll get hungry!
Why do I get hungry?
Do I get hungry when I don't eat snacks?
I don't know that!
Do I get hungry when I fight?
Even if you get along, you'll get hungry!
No!
Why do I get hungry?
Do I get hungry when I fight?
Even if you get along, you'll get hungry!
Mother, mother...
Do I get hungry?
No!
Why do I get hungry?
It's a counting song! There's even number 10!
There's no way there is!
Why do I get hungry?
Don't say it!
I'm a third-year high school student.
Actually, it's about my school.
My school was robbed of money and my bicycle chain was cut off.
Even if I locked it in the locker,
even if I put my wallet in my bag, it would be stolen.
Is there a school like this?
Of course there is!
But the one who stole the school lunch money,
the teacher came in with a strange face,
and everyone was like, close your eyes!
There really is!
Has it ever been solved?
If you do something like that in school,
this pencil case,
I had a pencil case with a picture of Chaplin on it.
Oh!
It's a comedy king!
It's a comedy king.
I really liked that pencil case.
Chaplin's pencil case.
It was a pencil case that looked like it had a picture printed on it.
It's not a manga.
There's no line here.
Because it's from the nose.
Yes, yes, yes.
You get it, right?
I went to play during my break and came back.
There's a line!
It's quite annoying to say that.
Who is it!
It's quite annoying.
The criminal can't get up at all.
I went to a convenience store I know,
was it a convenience store or something?
There was a painting on the nose of your face.
Take it off!
There's nothing on my face.
There's a painting on your face.
While looking at it, I always think,
ah, I'll do my best today as well.
That's nice.
I don't know, but I think it's okay.
Let's go!
He lost, he lost again.
He lost again.
That's too bad, Yamazaki-san.
The opponent was too aggressive.
That's too bad.
Yamazaki-san, let's give him one more chance.
One more chance?
That's enough.
Let's give him one more chance.
Let's go!
Ready!
Yamazaki-san, calm down.
Let's give him one more chance.