Girls! Come in!
For the last episode of Downtown, Yamazaki was going to ask the yakuza to play with him
But the yakuza came out
The yakuza didn't like the way he looked, but Yamazaki prepared a new setup
Where are you going?
I'm really sorry about the other day
You didn't like it the other day
Where are you going?
Today we have young people
It's a disco
You're going to play disco?
Is it fun?
It's fun, come in
Really?
It's really fun
Downtown Senpai, Dancing with Disco Gals
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
There's no audience
It's okay
Do you want to play?
Show us
There's no audience
I don't like this
It's okay, we've called them
It's like this
You're lonely
I'm not lonely
You're an idiot
What are you talking about?
Are you thirsty?
I'm not thirsty, I'm fine
Hey! Nocchi!
Let me go, you idiot
You have a bad mouth
Don't call me an idiot
I'm sorry
I'm sorry too
Thank you
Let me go
He's definitely drunk
Let's toast
Cheers!
Let's have fun today
It's about time
Today too
This side
You called me an old lady the other day
I did
Today too
Come on
There are four girls
There are four girls?
Ikeike?
Ikeike has four girls
I'm looking forward to it
You can't say harsh things
More than 50 points
I only say 60 to 70 points
That's good
I'll dance
Please watch my reactions
Hey everyone!
Young girls, come on!
Come on, come on, come on, come on, kick it!
She's here
She's a witch
She's laughing
The glasses behind her are really ugly
Her glasses are really ugly
Okay
She's a ***
Hey!
What's this? 60 to 70 points?
Yes, 60 to 70 points
Her body is really big
You're a life-threatening woman
Today, since Dan-dan is here
Let's have fun!
What's your name?
Mitsuyo
What's this?
It's candy
This is bad
Candy is bad
This is...
What is it?
You dropped something weird
It's not weird
I'm Hiroko
Oh, you changed your hairstyle
I'm a player
It's your first time
You look like a housewife
Okay, let's start
The game is over
I can't say anything
It's okay
Okay, let's start with Hamada
Okay, Matsumoto
Who will be the king?
Everyone, pull
Who is the king?
Me!
The 8th gyaru and...
Matsumoto will kiss
Who is the 8th gyaru?
Please forgive me
This is hard
Go to the side
I'm going to take a bath
I'll just die
I'll take off my glasses
It's over
Really?
This is a game
I'm sorry
It's over
Go to the side
He dances really well
I think so
There are many other gyaru
He dances really well
I think so
I can't believe I was born
There are many other gyaru like that
Okay
Music, start
I'm sorry
Stop the music
What are you doing?
You can't do this
What?
What are you doing?
You can't do this
Don't fight
Wait
You can't do this
Someone is coming
Queen
He's laughing
I'm an idiot
What's going on?
Queen
Queen's voice is loud
I'm an insect
Is there anything more high?
What is it?
What is this?
Is this a queen's ball?
What?
It's higher than a queen.
It's not a big ball that's slow.
This is bad!
Hey!
Let's go home.
Let's go home!
I said let's go home!
What is this?
This is bad!
I made a lot of similar shows with those two people.
What should I do?
My head is in the direction of the gold.
I'm scared of that.
It's been a long time since you did a talk show.
It's been a long time.
If you think about it, it's been three weeks.
Will it be that long?
It won't be that long.
It's been two weeks.
That's right.
It's been a long time since you did a talk show.
Ah, you did it.
I don't think that's good.
It's been a long time since you did a talk show.
Why?
On Sunday, you did a talk show with Gotts for two hours.
And then you did a talk show with Gaki for two hours.
It's been four hours.
This is really bad.
It's not like that.
I'm doing it on the side.
No, it's not like that.
You don't know the general process.
For example, you're watching Gotts for two hours, right?
Then you have to put up with it and watch it.
It's over.
Then you go to the bathroom and watch it again.
What are you doing?
You keep saying, Dan-dan, Dan-dan.
You're always saying Dan-dan.
You keep telling me to show you what my mom does.
I can't help it.
I don't understand why you keep saying Gotts and Gaki.
It's the same.
Dan-dan, Dan-dan.
It's the same all the time.
That's right.
I think it's the same thing.
That's definitely a loss.
But the numbers are showing.
You're so mean.
You're becoming more and more like Suga-chan.
There's nothing to do with numbers.
You've really become a bad guy.
Why?
You made a downtown calendar while I didn't know.
You're going to sell that next time.
I can't help it.
Even if you don't say anything, money will come in.
You really like money.
Money, money, money, money.
That's not true.
Dance with money.
You're a guy who dances with money.
You're always talking about money.
That's not true.
I don't want to be fooled by you.
What are you talking about?
It's really good.
Seriously.
What are you?
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm scared.
Don't say that.
What?
You made a character.
Go away.
Is curry rice cracker selling?
It's selling.
I'm just kidding.
Oh, really?
It's only in Kansai area.
I can't give it to you.
There's a lot of questions.
Who are you?
You're stupid.
It's dirty.
I don't want to say it.
I want to ask you something.
What do you say in English?
Is there an English word for this?
Of course there is.
There's an English word for everything.
When you go to New York, for example,
when you go to America,
when you want to eat this,
what should you say?
That's right.
What should you say to communicate with foreigners?
But there's an English word.
There's nothing to communicate with foreigners.
Is there an English word for this?
There's an English word for this.
Basically.
You're a sticky Japanese.
Should I say something in reverse?
Basically.
What did you say?
I can communicate with foreigners.
You're annoying.
I was surprised.
Can you communicate with foreigners?
Of course I can communicate with them.
But I can't communicate with foreigners.
But you can't say you're a foreigner, right?
Of course I can't say that.
I've been in New York for a long time.
Please tell me that.
I'm a Russian.
What?
Please.
Please?
I'm a Russian.
I don't understand the first part.
What did you say?
I'm a Russian.
You're so stupid.
I'm really sorry.
You don't understand English at all.
I'm sorry.
That's why I can communicate with foreigners.
I can communicate with foreigners.
I know that.
But if you dare to say it...
I don't understand.
It's a small tone.
Why can't you say it in the first tone?
You said it.
Yes.
In that tone.
Don't say it.
I'm sorry.
In that tone.
I can communicate with foreigners.
But if you dare to say it...
I don't understand.
Thank you very much.
That was a commercial.
I was explaining why I said it in a small tone.
I'm sorry.
If you don't say it in a small tone, it won't work.
If you say it in a loud tone...
You're really...
Let me do it, you bastard!
The meaning changes completely.
In a small tone.
Say it in a loud tone.
If you say it in a loud tone, the foreigners will misunderstand.
What are you talking about?
I was really scared.
I was scared.
If you work hard, you'll be able to fit into an empty bottle like Matsumoto-san.
You'll be able to fit into an empty bottle.
Yes.
Umm...
I said yes.
Where did you fit in?
There are many kinds of bottles.
It's really hard.
What do you mean it's hard?
Are there bottles that are easy to fit in or ones that are hard to fit in?
There are.
What kind of bottles are easy to fit in?
Umm...
Bickle is the hardest to fit in right now.
You have a big mouth.
It's better to have a big mouth.
On days off, Bickle is the hardest to fit in.
On days when there's nothing in the morning.
Why?
On the next day, when you're at work, Bickle is the hardest to fit in.
That's true.
It's really small.
I think this kind of thing...
You think about it from a negative perspective, right?
I think it's okay to fit in.
It's okay to fit in.
Can I ask you something?
Yes, yes.
How do you fit in?
How do I fit in?
If you fit in your mouth, your Bickle will be full.
As long as it's normal.
What kind of state are you in when you're in Bickle?
I usually break my legs.
Like this?
It's not that bad.
At first, it was always like this.
Yes.
It was like that.
I broke my legs.
Who told you that?
Please explain.
At first, it was the person who was wearing the sandals.
Hey, bring me the Bickle!
Bring it here!
What are you talking about?
It's okay, it's okay.
I'll explain it to you.
I won't do anything.
It's okay.
What?
At first, it was like that.
I broke my legs.
If I do it like this.
At first, there was a person who was wearing the sandals.
Yes.
The person who was wearing the sandals was looking at you.
Yes, and I...
And I told him not to look at me forever.
Yes, yes, yes.
Hey, please give me the Bickle.
I don't know that person.
I can't go in with you, can I?
Well...
You can't bring me to that old man, can you?
I think I can.
I think I can, but if it's that person, who is it?
It's okay if you explain it to me.
I don't know if you think it's a good thing.
What?
I don't know if that old man is you.
No, that's why you should explain it to me.
I don't know if you think you're a celebrity.
I don't watch TV.
When do I go in?
I thought it would be okay to wear the Bickle for a while.
I'm going to try the Ramune.
Are you going to the bottom?
I wonder if I did this inside.
That's the bottle you just happened to get in.
No one has ever tried to drink it.
That's okay.
This is just the right place.
The Ramune.
I'm going to hold the Bickle like this.
Master Matsumoto.
Why do people laugh when they're tickled?
Well...
Don't laugh!
Listen.
I'll tell you this.
I don't laugh when I'm tickled.
You didn't laugh earlier.
Everyone has a mission when they're born.
It's a difficult story.
I have a mission to entertain people.
That's why I don't laugh.
No way.
I'm the one who makes people laugh.
While you were talking earlier, you were laughing like this.
I've seen it many times.
What?
It's just my imagination.
That's why...
I'm the one who...
Huh?
What?
I'm the one who makes people laugh.
Huh?
What?
You were angry earlier.
Shut up.
I'm the one who makes people laugh.
You can't stop laughing.
It's impossible for me to laugh.
Really?
Yes.
Shut up!
Seriously.
This is the most embarrassing thing I've seen today.
What?
Huh?
No!
Listen.
I'm the one who makes people laugh.
Oh my god!
I'm the one who provides.
Huh?
I'm the one who...
I'm the one who makes people laugh.
It's just like that.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I'm the one who makes people laugh.
Why are you making such a scary face?
It has a different meaning.
I'm the one who makes people laugh.
It can't be helped. It's your mission.
Why are you doing this?
It's already 4 o'clock.
Huh?
Why are you laughing?
You're making me cry.
Stop laughing.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.