Chikitsuki Manga Dojo!
Ah, get out of the way!
Thank you very much.
Once again, Chikitsuki Manga Dojo has come to an end.
Next is me, Hamada Masato.
Thank you very much.
Now, let's have a look at today's guests.
First of all, next to me is Ebisu Yoshikawa-san.
Hello, everyone.
Hello.
I didn't even know what time this show was going to start.
And next to me is Itou Miki-chan.
Thank you very much.
Have you ever been to the real Manga Dojo?
No, but I've been there before.
What did you think of the teacher's book?
Well, for the time being, I wrote what I was going to write.
Are you underestimating me?
Well, let's have a good time today.
Next to me is Matsumoto Hitoshi-san.
Thank you very much.
I'm not good at drawing.
Liar!
I'm pretty good at drawing, though.
I'm not very good at drawing.
Well, drawing is completely different from drawing.
I'd like to show you how to draw.
The first question is this.
Look at this.
It's in your hands, too.
It's a cross mark.
This flip.
Let's use this flip.
Let's draw a picture diary of summer.
Well, for example...
Don't get angry.
Like this.
This is a summer cocktail.
Oh, that's what it is.
It's something like Hawaii.
I'm angry.
I'm tired.
Well, then, please draw.
Here we go.
What is it?
Well, Miki-chan, if you were a man, you'd be hitting me.
I see.
Ebisu-san, if you were a man, you'd be hitting me.
Let's start with Ebisu-san.
Here you go, Ebisu-san.
It says, I went to the pool.
What kind of picture is it?
There are four pools.
I swam here.
There's a fish swimming next to it.
There's an octopus swimming next to it.
There's a person swimming here.
You're an idiot.
Well, let's go to Miki-chan.
Miki-chan.
What is it?
It's a beach ball.
You're wrong.
Well, then, Matsumoto-san.
It's summer, isn't it?
It's a picture diary of summer, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Well, I'll use the punishment.
It's hot.
It's a summer picture diary.
What is this?
I'll give one to Miki-chan.
Of course.
Thank you.
Well, let's go to the next one.
If I get all of these, what will it be?
It's a top prize.
That was a good question.
The person with the most number of 0s is the top prize.
The moment you say, it's a top prize,
everyone here will clap and say, congratulations.
And then, this segment will end.
Well, then.
You can get a bonus from the top prize.
What is this?
This.
It's in everyone's hands.
This hot spring mark.
Using this hot spring mark,
something that spins.
Right?
With something that spins,
let's draw something that sticks to your head.
For example.
It's like this.
It's like this, right?
It's like lightning.
That's right.
Miki-chan, you're like lightning.
Right?
Why does it spin?
What are you doing?
Spin, spin, spin, spin.
My eyes are spinning.
It's like this.
Now, flip.
Who thought of this?
Now, please flip.
Using this hot spring mark,
something that spins.
Let's draw something that sticks to your head.
Now, let's go.
First, let's start with Elis-san.
This is a kappa.
The sun is shining on my head.
I don't have any water.
I'm spinning because I'm in pain.
Kappa.
Elis-san, aren't you happy?
Yes, I am.
Aren't you a little scared?
Miki-chan.
It's a spinning sushi.
It's getting hot in the summer.
I drew a spinning sushi.
It's spinning.
But it's hot in the summer,
so the steam is coming out from the top of the sushi.
You idiot.
Miki, you didn't even touch the girl earlier.
Now, Masato-kun.
This is perfect for me.
Something that spins.
Yes, this.
A light girl.
No, something that spins.
I'm going to spin this in Harappa.
Idiot.
That's...
You're being spinned by a person.
It's something that spins.
I'm not going to say yes.
I'll give one to Elis-san.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
It's over.
Hello, everyone.
Hello.
You're noisy.
Last week, I told you that I was thinking about new shows.
I've been thinking about it since then,
but there are good ones.
For example, what kind of shows?
This will definitely get 60 or 70 views.
Are you serious?
That's too much.
Will you get it?
I'll definitely get it.
60 or 70?
What kind of show is it?
It's a crane.
It's a big costume.
I'll make it look cool.
For example, a big costume like a rock.
That's right.
There's a Nittere at the bottom.
It's like a Nittere on top.
That's right.
I'll drop the costume at 10 counts.
I'll drop it on top of the Nittere.
Zero.
Bang.
That's too much.
What?
Why don't you make a proper show?
Why?
What are you going to do?
I've been thinking about it.
I want to experiment with it.
A skit with a smell.
There's a big pipe on the side.
We're going to make a skit here.
There's a smell coming out from the side.
It's like, hey, it's going to rain.
If you go like this, the smell of the sun will come out.
This will definitely get 60 views.
It's going to be embarrassing.
Why do you have to go to the TV and smell it?
I want to go home with a smile on my face.
When I go out...
Why?
I'm thinking about the second part of the drama.
What do you think about this?
That's the end of the first episode.
It's the end of the first episode.
There's a man who's a salaryman.
He's an old man.
Everyone in the family is warm.
But he's sick.
There's a lot of crying and talking going on.
There's a lot of fighting going on in the family.
There's a lot of things going on.
It's been an hour.
I'm not saying I'm not going to die, but it's getting red.
It's getting red.
In the hospital.
It's dangerous.
There's a lot of family.
Dad, Dad, get a hold of yourself.
I'm standing in front of the door.
There's no laughing at all.
I'm serious.
It's a normal drama when it's over.
Dad's like,
I'm not going to die.
Dad, Dad.
Dad's like,
His eyes are like,
It's only the last few seconds.
The husband is like,
2 and a half hours after birth,
He's like,
Bam, bam, bam, bam.
The second time, this one,
I don't know if it's going to be spicy, but
There's a couple.
But my parents are against me getting married.
I just can't get married.
I'm going to die.
I stay Medicare for things like that.
It's going to rain.
When I get home,
Okay, it's written,
The second time,
But the Greenway Arisaka
I've talked a lot about it.
zero
He was,
I don't know if he's with the
Who's going to pay for the car?
That's the guy who was driving the car.
Are you going to pay for it?
You're a fool!
It's a long story!
You don't need to go that far.
I'm thinking about the third one.
It's about the police.
Let's make a good police force.
They've been coming here since I was a kid.
That's right.
I'm going to keep taking care of the sick.
I want you to become a police officer.
Poor guy.
I can't stand it without tears.
Finally, it's time to be a police officer.
That's great.
I had my first...
My first...
I became an officer,
I became an official
Surrender the enemy.
When I was視 Incorporated...
When I wasraft in a
Renovation
After all, I think the most pathetic thing is the goat.
It's the most pathetic thing in the world.
It can't be helped.
Both the dog and the cat are the same.
The dog and the cat are still the same, but the cat is terrible.
Even if you hit the goat's face, it's the same.
Even if you hit the dog, it's the same.
It's the same.
I'm the only one who doesn't like the goat.
The one who gave you a name is the one who was influenced by other people, right?
What?
Firefly squid.
I was influenced by other people.
There was a person who was shining.
You decided to name it Firefly, right?
Yes.
Then, excuse me, but this squid is shining.
It's a firefly squid.
The feeling of a firefly squid that has been decided like this is really painful.
Can you be quiet?
I want you to name it more seriously.
I don't care. Why do you want to name it?
Are you thinking about a child's name?
I'm not thinking about it.
Come on.
I'm always thinking about it.
I'm tired of thinking about it.
If you think about it, I'll hit you.
I can't think about it from here.
I used to think about it a lot in the past.
Are you stupid?
Don't laugh.
Don't think about it like that.
Are you thinking about a child's name?
I'm doing my best, but I'm not thinking about it.
Don't think about it like that.
You're really bad.
I'm the one who's thinking about it.
I'm the one who's paying for it.
I'm doing my best, but I'm not thinking about it.
Don't laugh.
I have to make you laugh.
That's why I can't think about it.
There are 15 minutes a month.
For example, if Hanshin Kyojin comes out, it's 15 minutes.
If Sakuroshiro comes out, it's 15 minutes.
If Nikuyo Kurou comes out, it's 15 minutes.
Everyone is 15 minutes.
I'm 15 minutes, too.
I have to do a manzai for 15 minutes, right?
I'm doing a manzai.
If I'm not in a position to listen, I can't go home.
I can't go to the dressing room.
I'm...
What does that mean?
I'm always very serious about my feelings for comedians.
If you're there, don't talk.
I'm always thinking about it on the stage.
I'm going to do it today, too.
When comedians are sleeping, they're either going to win or lose.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to do it today, too.
I've been waiting with my sleeves like this at least once.
I'm pushing it in my heart.
I'm going to win or lose.
I'm doing it.
I'm going to go out and say,
I lost.
I'm going home.
I'm not serious about that yet.
There's a time when I can't go home.
I have to go to the dressing room at 1.15.
I have to go to the dressing room 30 minutes before.
I can't go to the dressing room.
I have to go out alone.
I have to go out alone and do a comedy.
I have to go out and say,
Hey, hey!
Go to bed!
I don't know what to say.
Hey, you.
I'll tell you something.
I was wearing it.
What?
Why are you wearing your sleeves on the stage?
I'm going to watch your show in the audience.
You're crazy.
You're late.
Which one is more?
You're more.
It's you!
In Osaka, I was doing the show from 4 p.m. to 1 p.m.
Monday through Friday.
Live.
For an hour.
At 4 p.m., when the sound of the opening came out,
The band came out of the door and said,
Hello.
And the show always started.
That's it.
It's a live broadcast.
I called the live opening.
If you're awake, come on.
Hey, you.
You woke up at 4 o'clock.
You were watching the opening at home.
It's a show called 4 o'clock.
I went to the 4 o'clock before.
In the morning.
It's 4 o'clock.
I was waiting.
You're tired.
It's open.
That's what it is.
Come on on time.
I often say that I'm sorry that you're late.
I'm not late.
There's a guy called Rollers.
He plays music.
He called me.
Why aren't you late?
I'm sorry.
It's important to be late.
Come on.
Even if you say so.
You're here.
I can't help it if I'm angry with you.
I'll do this much.
I'm sorry.
The next day, I'm late.
That's right.
He called me.
Hey.
Why are you late?
It's important to be late.
You're here.
I can't help it if I'm angry with you.
It's important to be late.
I'm angry.
Hello.
Don't you have a class today?
Really?
Are you a general?
What's your name?
I'm Matsumoto.
Matsumoto?
How old are you?
I'm a student.
What are you doing now?
Why are you here?
I see.
I understand.
Idiot.
Let's do it again.
What are you doing?
Thank you very much.
This person is asking Hama-chan a question.
Can you speak without using Osaka dialect?
Please speak with Matsumoto-chan.
You should speak in Osaka dialect.
I can speak Osaka dialect well.
I can use standard Japanese.
Please speak in Osaka dialect.
What?
Is it okay?
It's very hot these days.
I see.
What time did you get on the train today?
I got on the train at 12.48.
What time did you get on the train?
I got on the train after 3 hours.
It's been 4 months.
I'm not used to it.
I can't speak fast.
But I can speak fast.
You can't speak fast.
I can.
Really?
Yes.
What did you do last night?
I was on the radio yesterday.
I was with you.
You are an old man.
You are old.
It's impossible to be born as a man.
It's difficult.
It's impossible.
But it's okay.
It's been a year.
You are right.
I'm getting used to it.
You have to get used to it soon.
That's right.
Let's talk in standard Japanese until the end.
Okay.
Say, let's talk.
Let's talk.
Even a normal person says, let's talk.
Say it.
Really?
It's cold.
Is that all?
Do you want me to say more?
That's all.
That's all?
I've been talking too much lately.
That's right.
That's not true.
Half of what I heard today is not true.
It's simple.
I'm tired.
I don't understand.
It's embarrassing to bite.
What?
I don't understand what you mean by biting.
But you can't deceive me with that tone.
That's right.
Let's watch the encore video of the Tokyo Dome concert.
It's fun.
The encore is really cool.
It's really exciting.
He changed his costume and came out.
He sang like this.
He wore a white suit.
You can watch the video.
It's really cool.
He wore a white suit.
He came out like this.
He sang like this.
What kind of scene is that?
That's not true.
He came out and sang like this.
Is that true?
That's true.
You can watch the video.
The audience doesn't understand.
They're excited.
That's not true.
He's laughing.
I made a mistake.
They don't understand when I'm excited.
You're a mother.
Please write questions.
I know everything.
Bye!