Hello, everyone.
Actually, today, Yamazaki Hosei will be graduating with this room.
That's right. In the past, I was able to make a fool of myself.
I really feel that such a time has come.
Well, for the time being, let's ask him to appear.
This is Yamazaki Hosei. Please come in.
Please come in.
Well, I think that people who are watching TV are wondering what it is about.
Let's stop feeling dark.
I got married and had a child.
My wife is Aya.
Well, Aya gives me advice as a comedian.
Do you know how to use this child?
My daughter, Momo, doesn't wake up at that time.
That's why she's sleeping and she can't see.
Do you want to do that for the sake of your child?
Do you think it's better to have a time when your child is awake?
After all, if there is a Golden, I can see it honestly.
With the whole family.
From about 7 o'clock.
Yes, I have a lot of time, and that's one of the big reasons.
Well, I've been doing a lot of things for 14 years.
Well, I think it was hard, but I think there were a lot of things to gain.
Well, even if you look back on 14 years, it's hard to say that it's this high.
Well, let's take a look at the famous scene that Yama-chan himself chose.
Then VTR, please.
This broadcast is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
Yamasaki Hosei, 35 years old.
When I met you, you were full of youth and hope.
It's been 14 years since we've been through the same season.
I can't believe I'm going to have a time to say goodbye to you.
Let's look back on your great miracle once again.
What are you doing?
5th place, Yamasaki Image Up Oogiri.
You care about your image more than anyone else.
We were followed by the script you wrote, and you made us do Oogiri in front of a guest who only laughed at what you said.
It's not working.
You can't say this.
What is the last word of the person who fell into the bathhouse?
Matsumoto-san, the last word of the person who fell into the bathhouse is, help me.
This is the last one.
Melting!
And then, bang!
What is the last word of the person who fell into the bathhouse?
Matsumoto-kun, the last word of the person who fell into the bathhouse is, help me.
Why?
Next!
Yamasaki-san.
What is the last word of the person who fell into the bathhouse?
Melting!
I wish you were my partner.
I'll go with a letter.
The love letter is torn!
Yay!
Thank you!
The 4th battle between Yamasaki and Jimmy.
A fight between two people who couldn't stand the fight.
We've witnessed your miracle many times.
What are you doing in front of a car like this?
What are you doing?
Why did you kick it?
You know, Yamagaki, you...
You can't...
It's hot!
Yuta is an old man.
It's like a runny nose.
Let's go, Jimmy!
It's hot!
3rd place, Goodbye, Yamasaki Hosei.
A year ago, you said you were going to quit the show.
You surprised the whole nation.
At that time, I didn't think a day like today would really come.
Yama-chan!
Stop using kids!
Stop it!
Stop it, girls!
Stop it, stop it, Yama-chan!
2nd place, Yamasaki Hosei's moving wedding ceremony.
You were always everyone's idol, but you're finally getting married.
We all saw a part of that moving moment, didn't we?
This is amazing.
What is this?
It's like a wedding how-to video.
It's a beautiful video.
What?
No way!
What is this?
1st place, after the rain, everyone gathers.
Stop! Stop!
During the recording, Hamada suddenly gets mad at Tanaka.
What is this?
It's a lie!
Hamada, who is overpowering his juniors, admires his wildness.
I want to erase it after the rain.
After the rain?
Yes.
Wait, I'm going to cry.
Why?
I'm going to hold it in with my strength.
Kodon Tozai!
Names of flowers!
Okay!
Rose!
Okay, rose, okay!
Tulip!
Oh, I got it!
Yuriko, Yuriko, Yuriko!
Yuriko!
I got it!
Chibino wins!
Yutaka, you just barely made it.
Your turn to lose.
You're not going to make it.
I'm not going to make it.
It's not written in here.
You're not frustrated, are you?
You're going to say it out loud?
Ichiwa asked me to say it out loud.
What did you say the atmosphere was?
What did he say?
He said it in his own words.
He said it in his own words!
What are you doing?
Hey!
Where are you going?
I'm sorry.
It hurts!
It's raining!
You're kidding me!
Don't cry!
You're acting!
I'm going to hold you down and drop kick you.
Are you okay?
It's been 14 years since you were a kid.
It's been a long time.
How many times did you get dirty for the show and cry?
You, who devoted everything to laughter, will never disappear from our minds forever.
I wish time would stop.
The more I think about it, the bigger your presence was.
But it's goodbye.
Goodbye, and thank you for the memories.
How do you feel, Yama-chan?
You have special memories.
That's right.
That's why my image-up strategy...
Oh, the ogiri.
Yes, that's right.
I'm sorry. I just remembered.
I told you that I would never cry.
I feel like it's a waste to cry.
I'd like to say goodbye to the producer, Suwa-san.
Thank you for your hard work, Yama-chan.
I'm really sorry for all the bad jokes I've said so far.
I thought I wouldn't quit until last year.
I'm really sorry to hear that.
Thank you very much.
Let's go here.
Let's start with here.
Thank you for 14 years.
Thank you.
This may be a personal story, but...
I've been in Tokyo for 10 years.
Personally, you've been really nice to me.
I think you've given me a lot of love.
I'm sorry I couldn't answer you well.
I've been using the instrument since the second time.
At first, I was watching you on TV.
Then I joined you.
I've always been chasing after you.
At one point, I lost you.
Thank you for chasing after me at that time.
Thank you very much.
I only had the opportunity to work with Yama-chan.
I don't think I'll be able to work with Yama-chan anymore.
I can only say goodbye and do my best.
The staff of this program are also my family.
I want to work with my real family.
Thank you very much.
Finally, Yama-chan.
Please say goodbye to everyone.
Do you think I can get a bouquet of flowers like this?
For 14 years, I've been an instrument user for 14 years.
It's important to have friends.
I can't say anything anymore.
Thank you very much.
At the end of the program, I couldn't say anything.
We became four people.
It's easier to divide the program into four people.
Yama-chan won't stop being an instrument user.
Are you surprised?
This is the third time.
Yama-chan won't stop being an instrument user.
Thank you very much.
Everyone gather!
Think carefully.
Yama-chan is important.
Stop!