It's amazing.
You're looking for a house in Yamanaki, aren't you?
You want to live in a house that's one rank higher than yours, right?
Yes, I do. I live right next to it.
But if you guys decide, I'll live there.
Really?
Really.
Is it okay for me to live in a house that's one rank higher than yours?
It's totally fine.
It's totally fine?
I might get pranked.
You might get pranked.
I won't come to your house anymore.
I don't think it's a big deal.
I know you're an amateur.
If you get caught, you'll be in trouble.
An amateur doesn't have to be in trouble.
It's cold, isn't it?
The camera isn't rolling.
Wait a minute!
I wonder if I can live in a house like that.
I'm sorry.
I thought you were looking for a house.
But you're a talent.
You have to live in a house that's one rank higher than yours.
Thank you.
Stop it.
I won't do anything.
That's a weird way to get involved.
What?
It's hard.
What's wrong?
I feel sorry for my partner.
Wait a minute.
You can't leave so soon.
I was about to get excited.
I thought I had to leave soon.
What are you talking about?
This is hard, too.
It's not hard.
It's okay.
Let's talk a little more.
I'm scared.
What are you scared of?
I thought I had to leave soon.
Please look for a house.
I found two or three houses.
Thank you.
It's pretty cheap around here.
Really?
There's a cheap place like a lie.
I think I'll push this place for now.
Really?
It's really big.
It says to lower the price.
That's right.
Let's go.
This place?
Yes.
Let's go here first.
It's 135,000 yen.
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
It's around here.
It's nice, isn't it?
That's right.
But it looks noisy.
No, no.
It's noisy.
It's not running anymore.
What?
It's running.
Bus.
What's wrong with him?
He's crazy.
Well, this is it.
It's nice, isn't it?
M house.
It's an auto lock.
Really?
Yes.
You don't have to push the button.
You can go up the stairs.
What?
No, no.
You can't go up the stairs.
You don't need an auto lock.
It's okay.
I've been looking for it for a long time.
I can go either way.
You mean I can go from here?
Yes.
This way, this way.
Okay, come on.
Please come in.
It's not like you're in a restaurant.
It's like you're at a hotel.
It's nice isn't it?
It's nice.
This.
I like the interior.
I like this white one.
Yes.
It's spacious.
The kitchen is good too.
It's nice.
There's a kitchen too.
Yes.
What does it do?
Is it 1DK?
It's 1DK, right?
No, it's not.
It's over here.
Really?
It's 2DK.
It's 135,000 yen.
Will it catch fire?
The building before this will be gone.
Really?
There's a waterfall here.
It's noisy.
The scenery is nice, but it's noisy.
It's okay.
It's a mountain, isn't it?
Let's put it here.
We can finish shooting.
What do you think?
I like it.
It's enough to be this big.
Yes.
I'll decide.
Ouch!
What happened?
Someone broke it.
It's here.
I just broke it.
I heard it again.
What are you talking about?
It's here.
I can't break it.
I was strangled.
It's here.
What are you talking about?
What did you do?
It's here.
It hurts.
What are you doing?
I get it.
What is it?
I'm in the room.
Why are you crying?
I don't want to.
It hurts.
You scared me.
I get it.
Let's go.
It hurts.
Let's go to the next one.
Ouch!
Is there a way to say no?
That's mean.
It's a ghost.
What is it?
It's a bad guy.
It's the same as the one who lived before.
It's true.
The same as the one who lived before.
That's why it hurts.
It's a bad guy.
Let's go to the next one.
It's here.
106,000 yen.
106,000 yen?
It's here.
It's a bit old.
You're a fool.
It's heavy.
The inside is the problem.
It was crying.
It's unnatural.
The door is open.
It's here.
It came out from there.
It came out while crying.
Do you understand?
I came here to see the room.
It's too high.
It's sad.
It's an amateur's room.
It's beautiful.
It's real.
There's a room.
Can I take a look?
It's 106,000 yen.
It's cheaper than before.
This is the entrance to the other room.
There should be a big TV here.
It's popular now.
It's like a TV.
I see.
Young people don't like to show off.
It's better to show off at the entertainment world.
This is the toilet.
It's a marble.
It's real.
The toilet is a little plain.
It's a little plain.
There's a stone here.
What is this?
Hey!
I see it.
I saw a flower.
It's not a
What is it?
What are you doing?
Ladies and gentlemen
Ah, that's right
I wanted to see the provocation
It's amazing
The person next to me is like a predator
But Ryoma
Come here
No, really
What should I do?
It's been a long time
This program is really
There are some
It's not decided yet
I'm sorry
I want to do it
There are times like that
I was in a music fair
I was wearing it
I don't know
It's getting cold
It's cold
Ah, I
I don't know if you noticed
It's been a long time
This guy
It's personal
You probably
You probably didn't notice
You were watching TV
You know?
Please tell me
It really has been a long time
Seriously, I was angry
I couldn't do anything
I'm working hard
He's not a guest or anything.
I don't know if he came from the next studio or something,
but he's waving his hand between the camera and the camera.
Because you're working hard here.
It has nothing to do with you.
You can go to the studio and wave your hand from behind.
I don't know who you're waving it to, but it's a problem if you get waved.
Yeah.
You can't wave your hand during the show.
That's right.
You can't wave your hand.
You have to wave your hand for about 5 minutes.
I can't do that.
You can't do that.
I was doing this on the way.
How many times? Wait a minute.
Go somewhere.
No, I said it first because I said it came out.
It's just that the pig is big, isn't it?
That's right. That's what I'm saying.
That's weird.
No, it's not.
It's not.
It's not?
It's big. It's big.
It's pretty fat.
If it's a pig, it's big.
Don't say that.
How many times have you said that pigs are big?
You're really good at saying that.
If you die, you're definitely going to know that at the end.
Well, let's say goodbye to Hama-chan's VTR at the end.
If it's a pig, it's big.
The roll is flowing.
That's really funny.
I want you to do that.
They have a different sense of value.
When I look at something, I look at it with a sense of beauty.
They're different.
I can't hold it in.
This is going to hurt.
This is pretty good.
It's been a long time since I've been angry.
Recently, I haven't been angry with a pig like this.
Really.
In that sense, it's a waste of material.
That's right.
Now.
There's a thread on it.
I see.
I sometimes go to the video store.
Do you want me to verify it?
I don't know if I can call it a verification.
In the video store's adult section.
Who's going to borrow it?
There's an AV.
Can you take a look at this?
I'm surprised.
No.
Usually, the AV has a beautiful package.
If you actually look at it, you'll be surprised.
In that sense, I won't leave it to you.
Wait a minute.
You're looking at it, aren't you?
I'm not looking at the inside.
You're saying you're not going to leave it to me.
It's like you're actually looking at it.
No.
It's a little unsatisfactory.
There's mosaic in it, right?
It's not good if there's no mosaic in it.
You can't put mosaic on everything.
You can't put mosaic on everything until the end.
What about here?
Put it here.
I looked at the counter.
Really.
The tea fell down.
It's my house.
It's a video house.
What is this?
Really.
I went to the video house once.
I went back again.
You wanted to see it again.
I went to the video house again.
No.
I want to see it again.
This is...
Let's go.
Itao was there, too.
Itao said, there's no way it's like this.
He said, this is the director.
Why did the director put it in the package?
It has nothing to do with it.
It's a series.
Two out of the six series.
I can't even guess.
There's a montage.
There's a four-part montage.
There's obviously a lot of it.
There's a lot of it.
There's an eye.
There's a head.
There's a tooth.
There's a mouth.
This is a montage.
There's a head.
There's an eye.
There's a tooth.
There's something.
And then there's the mouth.
There's something skin-colored.
There's something like that.
And then there's the mouth.
No one's going to borrow that.
It's not even in their hands.
You've seen it, haven't you?
I was really surprised.
I don't know how to look at it.
How do you do that?
You can't tell which is the front.
That's too much.
Let's take a look at that.
No, I can't.
Let's borrow that and look at it.
All of us?
Yeah.
Maybe I'll just look at it and it'll be on TV.
But if you do something like that, this program is stupid, so I'll call you.
Someday I'll take you to the dentist.
I don't know what to do with that.
If the two people I'm talking about come at once...
It's going to be like this.
No, I mean, I can't put those two together.
Well, it's the same thing here and here.
I think the neck is more valuable.
It's too far.
Let's take a look at it.
I want to see it.
I'm really surprised.
What kind of nonsense is that?
For example, for example...
It's like he's eating insects.
Hey, don't you have any insects?
It's a woman who seems to say that.
I see.
Do you understand?
If you look at it, it's like a kingdom.
I have a question for Mr. Matsumoto, who has been training for a thousand days at that koa store.
There are various difficulties for humans to live, but what is the most painful thing in this world?
What do you think it is?
It's hard.
Well, there's a lot of hard things.
There's a lot.
It's not a light theme that can be explained.
I agree.
Why are you laughing now?
I don't think it's hard, but if you go through it, it's hard.
If you make various choices...
It's a small-scale law.
I wonder what it is.
It's surprisingly attached to life.
For example, when I'm really hungry and I have a lot of time today, I don't have a bridge.
That's too small.
What are you going to do today? I'm really hungry. It looks really good.
Run to the convenience store.
You're really...
I'm going to get angry.
You're the one who's getting angry.
If you say that, it's all the same.
For the time being, it's hard not to run when there's no bridge.
It was like a manga.
100,000 yen, 50,000 yen, I can't see it.
This is the hardest.
What's 100,000 yen, 50,000 yen?
That's not it?
Everyone doesn't pay attention to that.
Even if you say it's the hardest, what are you going to do because there's no bridge?
The poop is hard.
It's hard, but I'm going to be lazy.
I can't do anything about it today.
That's how hard it is.
When I was in elementary school, I was in pain.
When I took a break from school, I couldn't stand it when the dog ran away.
It hurts so much.
Mr. Matsumoto, the dog is running away.
It hurts so much that I don't have the ability to think.
I was looking for it on the back of my hand.
I found it, but I don't have any blood.
You don't have a collar?
I don't have a collar, so I did it like this.
When I laugh and get angry, I'm a god.
When I drive, I have a stomachache.
It's hard.
I was really angry before.
I was really mad when I was in the car.
I was suffering because of a traffic jam.
I thought there might be a toilet somewhere.
I thought, but I can't stay put in public toilet, so I stayed in the bathroom.
I finally arrived at the public bathroom.
I opened the door and squat down.
I'm angry.
What are you doing?
What? Air?
Like this?
Huh?
Nothing's coming out?
You did it with air, huh?
Inside my stomach?
What is this for?
It's to stop it.
It's to stop it. I did my best.
I didn't come to the public toilet to carry air.
When you get your graduation certificate, do you have any cool lines?
There's a lot of that.
The last line?
I often say, don't mess up the rest of the lines.
But isn't that something you get for graduation?
Do you have any cool lines?
No, but you know how students usually say it?
And the principal says it, right?
And you get it like this, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
And when you go like this, you get it right here.
Normally you go like this.
That's what normal students do.
But that's the last of the three years.
When you go like this...
That was a great graduation ceremony!