This is the last round.
Today, Makoto looks normal.
He looks like a convenience store brother.
This time, it is a competition between the Matsumoto team and the Hamada team.
The team that makes the opponent laugh and gains many points wins.
And the team is decided.
Rock, paper, scissors.
I won.
I'm sure.
My body is facing that direction.
If you take that direction, you win.
Why are you doing that?
I won.
What is the prize?
The prize...
I will go to the medical school.
I have a prize here.
I really want to go to this campus.
Next, Makoto is the spring of water.
Hama chose the Oishigoro of the dark horse.
I have a high eye.
And Hama chose the Tama of running.
The loser, Makoto, got the Otsuki Oji.
The remaining two are the winner.
Rock, paper, scissors.
I'm a Toraoda martial artist.
I'm sure.
I'm the last one.
This is difficult.
This campus is difficult.
I will do my best.
I won't do anything bad.
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
I think this is good.
I'm scared.
And a careful strategy meeting was held with each team.
It's dirty.
It's dirty data.
This is normal data.
There is such a difference in everyday life.
This is ugly.
And Hama's team is.
This is a decision.
I don't know who it is.
I will start with the team.
I will introduce you.
I will start with Oda Mudo.
I understand.
Thank you.
I am confident.
Where did that confidence come from?
Oda Mudo is full of confidence.
How many points will he get?
Let's go.
The first round.
Start.
The second round.
The third round.
The fourth round.
The fifth round.
The sixth round.
The seventh round.
The eighth round.
The ninth round.
I didn't do my best.
You got one point.
One point.
What is the first team?
Who?
Let's go to the professor.
I understand.
Let's go to Professor Otsuki.
Let's go to the professor.
Machan is doing his best to regain his own defeat.
Can Professor Otsuki respond to that?
Let's go to Professor Otsuki.
Let's do our best.
Don't look away.
If you look away, you will get one point.
Let's go.
So far, Oishi Goro was laughing.
I think it's okay to judge that I was laughing.
Yamaguchi-san, what do you think?
I wasn't laughing.
No one?
Zero points?
No way.
If you think I was laughing,
Haruro sensei was laughing.
Read it properly.
Let's go to the second round.
I would like to send Goro Oishi here.
Thank you.
Let's go.
The professor was laughing.
What is the first episode that Oishi Goro shows?
This is the second round.
Our team is Oishi Goro.
I don't know how it will be.
Good luck.
Look at the center.
Don't look away.
Let's go.
It's me.
Why?
It's Goro Oishi.
Stop explaining the Odamu-do.
It's Odamu-do.
Yamazaki sensei.
Why do you keep saying that?
He knows it.
There is a child who is in a difficult age.
I feel sorry for him.
Who is the second team?
Let's go to Yoshie.
Don't laugh.
He wants to reduce the distance.
He is looking forward to Yoshie.
There are many things.
Next is a strong opponent.
I have a bad feeling.
That woman is a pot.
Next is a strong opponent.
Don't drink.
Let's go to Yoshie.
This is bad.
Everyone sujet.
Everyoneற except Mr. Oda.
Everyone except Mr. Oda.
The crushed team owns 4 points.
Don't you know?
I don't know the reason this battery is掉.
There are three singles over.
What is Reiwa written on people's drug?
It's ridiculous.
It has been reversed.
Let us fight with guts!
Guts Ishimatsu
If it's like this, it's Guts
Guts Ishimatsu from the Hama-chan team
He's here
I'm Guts Ishimatsu
It's funny just by the name
It's funny just by the way he's sitting
I'll do my best
Let's go
Everyone, look at the center
Guts Ishimatsu
Yama-san, look
This is bad
Shion, you're amazing
Amazing
It's not funny
3 points
It's good
4 points
Good good good
Shion, you're amazing
You showed us that
You did well
The original one was better
The 3rd round
I'll go with Makoto
Get ready
Makoto is thinking
Does Makoto have a plan?
It's a good scenario
I don't know what will happen to Makoto
Really?
Let's do it
Let's go
Makoto is thinking
It's good
1 point
It's a tie
That was close
You're so beautiful
You're so beautiful that I fell for you
You're so good
You opened your eyes
I didn't
I was looking at the bird
You're so good
Makoto
You're in the way
You're beautiful
The Tama-chan team is good at looking
They're laughing at the setting
Tama's running
Everyone, look at the center
Let's go
1 point
It's a tie
That was close
You're so beautiful
You're beautiful
You opened your eyes
I didn't
I was looking at the bird
You're so good
You opened your eyes
I didn't
I was looking at the bird
You're beautiful
You opened your eyes
I didn't
I was looking at the bird
You're beautiful
You opened your eyes
I didn't
Why did you ask the question?
Why?
I didn't notice you were holding it.
I thought you were holding it.
It was almost like this.
Ah, ah, ah, hat.
I thought you were okay.
There is a story.
It was exactly like that.
It's a great costume.
Why? It's not funny.
What do you think?
I said I shouldn't have said it, but I said it to the tank.
There are many things like that.
I was surprised.
What kind of face will that Mizu Haruo make carefully?
This is the last one.
This is the last one, right?
Yes.
This is also good.
Maybe I will get full marks.
I'm not confident about that.
Let's go.
This is the last one.
This is Mizu Haruo.
I'm sorry.
There is a story.
It's not funny.
You look like a delayed alien.
The camera is broken.
It's hot.
I didn't see it.
How many points did you get?
Hamada and Gatsu got 3 points.
Did you get 100 points?
I got 100 points.
I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
I was surprised.
There is one more round.
Let's play one more round.
I wanted to make Hamada laugh.
Hamada's face was amazing.
His face was funny.
I will play the last round.
I will play Gatsu.
I can't help it.
The Hamachan team is aiming for a comeback.
They play Gatsu.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I don't want to fight.
Why?
I want to laugh.
Let's go.
Look at the center.
The Hamachan team is aiming for a comeback.
Don't make a funny face.
Yamazaki's score is 3 points.
I'm sorry.
Don't make a funny face.
The Hamachan team is 0 points.
I understand.
Who will you send to the final round?
I have to decide at the end.
I will send Yoshihiro Yoshida.
I will send Yoshihiro Yoshida to the final round.
The Hamachan team is Yoshihiro Yoshida.
Who will be the winner?
The staff are very good.
I heard that.
I can't use my weapon.
This is the final round.
I will send Yoshihiro Yoshida.
I will send Yoshihiro Yoshida to the final round.
Who will be the winner?
I won.
I protected you.
Everyone was angry.
I laughed at Yoshihiro Yoshida.
I protected you.
I was patient.
I was about to cry.
It was a great battle.
The Hamachan team won by 10 to 9.
It was very interesting.
Let's do it again.
I won't laugh no matter how many times I do it.
This is a great battle.
I won't laugh.
Did you see yourself in the mirror?
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.