Are you wearing a jacket again?
Yes.
What is this?
You bought a jacket and a jean.
I'm wearing a jacket now.
I heard that this is a suit.
You only wore it once.
It was a while ago.
Wait! Wait!
I was surprised.
I said that I was surprised.
It's okay.
Don't say that you won.
Good morning.
You should go.
Yes.
We're all here for a meeting.
Yes, I know.
That's why I came today.
It's a new format for the show.
You should have done it behind the scenes with only Suga.
But I can't ignore you guys.
Why do you come with your family?
Because we're family.
The girl is also not growing up at all.
She's gotten smaller.
She's still cute.
She's cute.
They're making love.
She's cute. She's cute.
She's really cute.
Who are you?
Today, we thought about the format of the show.
Today, everyone is not moving around much.
Last time was tough.
I feel sorry for that.
Oh!
The whistle has been blown.
Oh! It seems that Yamazaki-san has got a red card.
Why?
I think that was not aggressive enough.
What?
You are fired from the game.
You were dancing.
When did you learn to dance?
This time I did it with a talk-based feeling.
It's really easy.
This is revolutionary.
I think that Hamada-san can do this.
Really?
Hamada can do it?
He can do it.
He is already done.
Ah, he is already done.
Because the package is already messed up.
If you sit down, you'll get used to it.
I can't do that.
You can.
If I just sit down, I'll get used to it.
Well, that's not a problem.
Is it okay?
But it'll take a while.
It won't take that long?
Yes.
I'm going to do the 500th episode of Sugakendji.
No, no, no.
I don't want to know.
Please buy it.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Life is like a race, no matter how you look at it.
It's a music video.
It's true.
Oh, that's...
This program is a program that shows the life of various people.
I would like to introduce the first final guest.
It's Itao's wife.
What?
It's a wife.
She's a great woman.
She's the best partner for Shimo Furino.
She's a good partner.
It's Itao's wife.
Welcome to our show today.
It's too close.
Now, let's look back on the life of Itao's wife.
What do you mean?
I don't really know.
That's just a VHS video deck.
Today we will be looking back at this tape.
There is even a 7th note?
Let's first look at the video of the life of a basic person.
This time lag is amazing.
Now, please watch the video.
In the 1970s, a woman born in the northwest of India was raised with a strict father and a kind mother.
The woman was 9 or 10 years old.
You have seen the whole world, but you can not see it.
You can not see it.
Why not?
Because it's the first time.
Who is who?
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
What's going on?
So, this is how the show starts.
What do you think, Endo?
To be honest, I didn't know who was who,
and they didn't translate it into Japanese, so I didn't understand the meaning.
Well, it's a realistic reproduction.
You should have done it more carefully.
Today, we prepared a snack that everyone ate on their wives' birthdays.
Oh, that was on the screen.
It was in the hand.
We prepared a snack for you.
I'll give it to everyone.
...
It's the real one.
Isn't there something more to it?
Something like that.
Like the paper.
It's wrapped.
It's unhygienic.
This is actually the same as the naan we ate in the video.
I'm looking at you with a lot of thought.
The member of the club is crying.
What are you looking at?
He was crying when he was a member of the club.
What is that face?
Originally, one ticket costs 1500 yen, but today it costs 1300 yen.
That's expensive.
One ticket costs 1300 yen.
You don't need that, right?
I don't need that.
But I touched it, so I can't help it.
You touched it and then gave it to him.
If you do that, you'll get in trouble.
We'll move on to the next video.
After this, something terrible will happen to Yome.
When the time comes, the girl who is interested in him appears.
Which one should I read?
You read this one.
Please forgive me.
No problem.
Actually, the classes are going on for so long.
I have to wait for you to go.
No problem. Please sit.
I want to tell you something.
Yes.
I like you very much.
Oh, really?
And...
Is this for me?
This is for you.
Oh, really?
Please take it.
Okay, there is one thing. I will tell you too.
Really?
The first love was confessed to by the bride, and they decided to date.
I'm so excited.
It was a big deal.
What do you think, Endo?
Looking at the situation...
I don't know why it turned out like that.
The comments...
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know either.
He confessed his love for the first time and got accepted.
That's right.
I don't know why it turned out like that.
Today...
Today, we have a batting match.
He brought a bat.
I know, I know.
I know this.
This is the bat.
This is the normal color bat.
Endo, what do you think?
What do I think?
You can tell the feeling.
How about hitting it on your body?
Do you hit it?
Like this, don don don don
I'm hitting it
Well, it's not extravagant
This time, we asked the bat maker to prepare a bat with your names on it
This is the bat with your names on it
Each of them has a name
The colors are chosen by us.
We can't write it with magic.
We can't write it with special kanji.
Endo is that color.
But this is not Endo.
It's the real one.
We have named it specially for the production.
It's 5 books, so it's 15,000 yen.
No, I don't need it.
I don't need it.
Well, I've already given you a name, so it's not a problem.
Yes, thank you.
Now, after this, there will be many different weather in the life of a bride.
Please watch this video.
So, before I say it...
What is this?
It's good to be in this video.
It's already short.
She has a skill to summarize many stories of the Gappe.
She was hired as a first-class winner.
It's like a movie.
Suddenly?
There are two of them, right?
There are two of them?
There are two of them.
Why are there two?
I'm not crying. I'm flying.
It's over.
Now, we've been through a tough trial. How was it, Endo?
I don't know at all.
It was a tough trial.
Especially now.
I think it was a time when they had to stop working at the company.
It was in Tokyo.
In Tokyo?
In Tokyo, the employees were in Japan.
I didn't know that.
When they were working at the company,
two documents came to the company,
and the trial was held.
However, there were no such sad events.
Please look at this.
I'm saying that but...
If you could watch a single video, it would be that short.
It would be 60 minutes long.
That's all.
After this, the weather will change for the bride who has tasted the bottom of life.
I saw this earlier.
You saw it?
Can I make another plate..?
Lets try with this one we made before..
No no.
Just like that we have continued to compete..
That was..
I really Are happy with this
so what is your reply Endo
No way I am totally sailed
How about Chiaki?
What would be a potential attitude in Chiaki
aso who'd it be? delivered by Chiaki?
Why are you looking at the tapes?
What kind of material do you compare Akira with?
What kind of material do you think he wears?
I don't know.
That's how extraordinary his life is.
Now, finally, the cruel fate awaits his wife.
Not yet?
The story of the first love
In the late 1990s, a cruel fate awaits for the bride.
I'm sure you've heard it before.
This is like a scene from a movie.
I don't like it.
It's a scene from a movie.
This is...
It's a play.
There is no substitute for that.
I'm not going to do it at all.
I'm still not ready.
I'm not ready for the end.
You're angry.
She's gone.
It's over.
How about this mischief of a wife's favorite fate?
First of all, may I ask a question?
Did you go to war?
Yes, I went to war as a Japanese soldier.
As a Japanese soldier? You're an Indian, right?
Well, in those days, I was in a mess in the war.
Everyone was excited about the bubble.
I don't know whose post it is or whose paper it is.
It's better to be bold.
That's why I said it honestly.
Now, it's the shopping corner of the bride that everyone has been waiting for.
Please bring it.
What is the shopping corner now?
Yes, it is.
Yes, this time it is here.
Yes, it is the color gunte of the bride.
I've never seen one before.
In the middle of the night.
There was a war, so you couldn't miss the military service.
It's just the military, but I didn't do the military service in the war.
This is the color of the cell phone that Yome chose.
If you like it, you can order it.
I'll give you a discount later.
No, I'm sorry.
Please take your order.
This year is especially hard.
Yes, it is.
Everyone, there is one sheet each.
Please draw a line where you like the color.
A number of sheets?
Please change it.
No, it's okay.
Then I'll do it.
Let's do it.
I'll find it.
Yes, I understand.
I really don't understand.
The quality of the military service.
Please put it on.
No, no, no. I've never said the quality of the military service.
Why do I have to buy a military service here?
I don't understand at all.
Now, I'd like to go back to the program.
After this, the bride will finally arrive.
What?
Please see the bride after the movie.
I didn't know that.
This time, I couldn't make it in time for editing, so I'll be the narrator.
Excuse me.
Go ahead.
Why didn't you make it in time?
The wife who gained various experiences after that has finally come to Japan.
She has been doing many different jobs.
Among them, the first job she got was the second one in the TV station.
No, no, no. The way you say second is strange.
I think it's a given.
Furthermore, from the second day, she was able to get a beautiful transformation.
After that, the woman who was praised for her excellent technique as a makeup artist, suddenly became a trendier drama director.
After I achieved a great success, I met Itao by chance.
And finally...
This is Itao.
He suddenly appeared in the middle of the production.
Wow, wow, wow!
Amazing!
Huh?
Yes.
Did you take it from above?
I took it from above.
I'm sorry.
I changed my life after the next day.
Endo, how was it?
You came to Japan, right?
Yes, I came to Japan and got a second job.
What is a second job?
It's okay to be a cameraman, right?
Well, I was doing my second job professionally.
And it was very popular, so I was given a big discount on my makeup.
That's strange.
That's the fate of Itao's wife.
How about starting from day 2 and doing makeup?
You've been doing makeup until today, but starting tomorrow you'll do makeup.
If it were me, I'd be like...
What would you do the day before?
You've been doing makeup since day 2, but starting tomorrow you'll do makeup.
What would you do the night before?
Is it your turn?
What should I do?
You'll be surprised, right?
You'll be surprised again?
I'll be surprised.
I'll be surprised again.
Now, let's have the beautiful
Nikabe Saba-ki
to show us.
And then we'll say goodbye to the show.
Beautiful
I'm Sadaqui.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
That's all.
The program.
Is Mr. Tsutsuga here?
It's like this.
Yes.
There is such a program?
There is.
Yes.
Mr. Tomi is doing it in the morning.
That's right.
Well then, about 1 million yen.
Eh? How much?
About 1 million yen.
Yes.
Well, of course, the Bunta, the Karabata, the Nan, all of them are included.
Including all of them.
I think 1 million yen is too cheap.
Yes.
It's fine if you use it as it is.
This is also made properly, so I think it's very easy for Hamada-san.
Yes.
It's not a hammer.
Well, well, then, for the time being,
the board, really,
let's consider it.
Well, then, for the time being, for the time being,
in the first place,
please keep it.
Please keep the money.
Mr. Tsuda, too.
I have to pay for the technical expenses.
If there is any left over, I will bring it.
Then, please,
I'll do that.
Let's go.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
This is terrible.
We have to change the recording date.
This one?
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.