DTW Jiu-Jitsu Grand Prix, catch the order with the old-fashioned body!
Now, we are going to have the DTW Jiu-Jitsu Grand Prix!
First, the blue corner player enters!
Today is the day to commemorate, the first DTW Jiu-Jitsu Grand Prix!
Catch the order with the old-fashioned body!
The blue corner player enters!
Now, the wrestlers are entering the ring step by step, which is the dream of the national silver age.
Now, the blue corner player enters the Korakuen Hall with a beautiful atmosphere.
The opponent, the red corner player enters!
It's the red corner players who are facing the blue corner players in the ring.
They are coming to the close ring in a row.
The players are inside the ring, and there are many people who are angry.
All the players have gathered in the red corner.
This is the blue promoter.
His name is Mel Yamasaki-son.
Mel Yamasaki-son.
Please introduce the members of the Otaku team.
Hello, I'm Don Matsumoto.
I'm Don Matsumoto.
Is that so?
Let me introduce you.
Antonio Iino.
Tiger Jet.
Ueda Umanosuke.
Kenryuu Genichiro.
Maki Ueda.
孩子が wishing.
姉妹が
Now, it's an unlimited game.
Mel Yamasaki-son's team.
always cheering for me.
Nino
Ueda Umanosuke.
Kenryuu Genichiro.
Nino
Ueda Umanosuke.
Kintouma Shir bike.
Kintouma Shir FINAL9
It's the 18th and 16th kick.
Antonio Inoki takes it down.
Antonio Inoki runs to the touch without stopping.
Tiger Z is coming in from the red corner.
Indian Martial Art Tiger Z.
Butcher.
What does Butcher think?
It's hell.
No. 18.
He's here too.
Tiger Z.
He takes out the saber.
He hits Butcher's forehead.
Butcher blocks his head.
And the touch.
Once he goes inside the red corner.
Brody goes inside too.
He gets it out!
Brody.
And Ueda Umanosuke.
Brody gets a become.
Ueda Umanosuke gets out.
He drops the weapon.
just like Ueda.
They come and fight.
Brody throw Ueda Umanosuke into a rope.
Brody ends up at the edge.
Oh!
He zwischened it!
Hey
Oh
That get John
Yeah
yeah yeah yes
I'm sorry
sea
Thank you
police
A 1-10
The Merchis saw the padять and just fought
It is a mind that clashes with those who remain
Netachi Japanese
It seems that Dan Matsumoto will be嗯
And, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and ok
I'm going to buy it and food
Ahhhh
dozens.
Can also be 1986
I will ask for a fight
Butcher came back Butcher came back Butcher red corner
In the red corner, Tenryu Genichiro and the blue corner will be a half line
Uiii
I was caught by Hansen at the end of the day
I'm going to do it
Jacky is high
gefallen
Thank you
car
Natsuki
Yeah yeah
yeah
and
The
me
First time MTW
I can't
Ah ah ah
Real
I am
Hello!
It's hot.
It's really hot.
There was a bug.
I touched it.
It was hot.
It was really hot.
There was poop.
I touched it.
It was hot.
It was really hot.
I don't want to cry anymore.
I thought I had to change.
What do you mean?
I don't have enough exercise.
I've been saying this for a while.
My body is aching.
I'm going to change.
I'm just going to get my old self back.
I don't understand what you're saying.
I've changed.
What do you mean?
The room in the middle is amazing.
What is?
It's a little sports club.
What is that?
You're talking about money.
I don't have money.
It's a loan.
I did 100 push-ups the other day.
No, not 100 push-ups.
I did 100 push-ups.
If it was a long time ago, I would have done this.
I can do a lot of things.
You can do a lot of things.
I'm going to get my old self back.
No, no, no.
You weren't like that back then.
I was.
You always did push-ups.
That's why I said I was going to get my old self back.
You're so mean.
I've been doing this for a long time.
Are you drunk?
I'm talking to you.
No, no, no.
I'm not drunk.
I can't do that.
You can't do that?
I'm a cow.
What?
I'm a cow that's coming to me.
Where are you?
I'm like a buffalo.
Which one?
I'm a cow.
No, no, no.
I'm a buffalo.
Make it clear.
Where are you?
I'm a buffalo.
What's a buffalo?
Are you a horse or a buffalo?
They say I'm a buffalo.
I don't understand.
I don't care.
What?
I'm a man who was told that.
I'll get my old self back.
Please do it.
I think it would be nice if you did it like my body.
No, no, no.
Try touching it.
What?
It's moving.
You're the one who's been doing this all your life.
I don't have any chest muscles.
Touch your chest muscles and you'll have chest muscles.
I'll do my best.
You have to do your best.
How is it?
How is your work?
You're moving with me every day.
How is it?
I'm so angry.
I don't understand.
You're lying.
What are you talking about?
I'm a comedian and a comedian.
You're the first one.
I'm the first one.
I don't understand.
I'm not in the top ranks.
You're lying.
I should be in the second place.
Your nose is growing.
You're a man.
I'm sorry.
You call me an amateur.
You think I'm stingy.
I don't think so.
I don't want you to believe me.
I'm not stingy.
Your nose is growing again.
You're lying.
You have a mole here.
No.
My nose and my mole are different.
My nose and my mole are the same.
I can do it if I do something.
I can't take it off.
You can take it off.
I can take it off.
Is that so?
I can't take it off.
I can't do that.
Who are you talking to?
Why?
I don't care if I'm on TV.
I don't care if you're on TV.
It's like I'm sticking out my nose.
That's enough.
Is that so?
It's rude to talk.
What are you doing?
I'm doing it, but I'm being beaten up.
I thought, ah.
Don't do it.
I won't buy it.
I'm doing it because it's sticking out.
Do it nicely.
Don't put it in.
Don't put it out.
It's sticking out.
I'm getting a runny nose.
I don't like it.
What is it?
I'm getting a runny nose.
It's sticking out.
It's shining.
The audience who comes to see the use of the children here.
What do you usually do?
I'm working.
You're a bit of a strange person
What do you mean?
You just like to use the kid
Ah, I see
Even if you say you like the downtown, it's a bit different
Ah, but you're looking at me with those sparkling eyes
Then when that's over, you'll be like
Ah, this guy is like that!
That's right!
This guy is like that!
He won't break!
He won't even let me get in his car
I used to be like that when I was in Osaka
I can't even get in a car
You're not that old
That's true
It's hot
It's really hot
I'm going to start
Hello, Hamada Nii-san and Hitoshi-kun
Hello
I was thinking about this the other day
I want to see your manzai
But I want to see you two being the opposite
Hamada Nii-san being a joke
And Hitoshi-kun being a tsukkomi
Ah, I see
If you think about it like that, it'll be even more interesting
You see
Hamada-chan's tsukkomi is
Eh? What is it?
Don't say anything
Hamada-chan's tsukkomi is
Amazing!
I'll say that
I don't do tsukkomi
But if I do tsukkomi, it's amazing
Are you pretending to be sleeping?
No, no, no
No, no, really, really
Let's do it
Can you be a joke?
No, it's okay if it's a yukai joke
I remember everything
It's not funny at all
It's just that if there's no mic here, it'll be hard to do it
Give me the mic
Is there really one?
It's obvious that you're going to do it from the start
I left this for the last episode
Then you come over here
Go on
That's right
It's yukai
It's hard to do it if you don't come out
Shut up
It's not like that
Ah, I see
It's a rough comedy
What are you talking about?
You've been busy recently, haven't you?
Ah, that's right
Even when you're walking down the street, there are scary things
When I'm walking down the street, I take my child with me
It's scary, isn't it?
I can't stand my parents
What are you talking about?
Why are you so nervous?
You're talking very fluently
Really?
Ah, is that so?
When I'm walking down the street, I take my child with me
I take my child with me to a stranger
I'll call him later
Hello?
Are you kidding me?
Where are you?
Yes
Do you have a 3rd grader son?
Yes, I do
I have a 6th grader son
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I'm counting on you
What is it?
Why are you so desperate?
Why is it like this?
Hello?
How many do you want?
Let's see
5 million
5 million?
Is it expensive?
No, is it 5 million?
That's enough
What is that?
What are you?
What's with that attitude?
Am I slow?
You're slow
Listen
I'll tell you now, so bring it to me
Yes
I'll tell you
I'll put 500 million in a green bag and write it in a black bag with yellow paper
If you leave it in a red bag, I'll go get it in a white bag
You're slow
How many times do I have to tell you?
No, no, no
It's hard to kidnap people
Which one is better?
If it's like that, it's easier for the doctor to do it
Doctor
Let's remember it here
I completely remembered
I see
You're a doctor, you're a doctor
Doctor
I'm Masao's father
That's right
You came the other day
Yes
I took a photo of the Lendogen
That's right
I received it
What kind of comment is this?
It's been a long time
It's not the first time
I see
Masao's father
That's right
You came the other day
I took a photo of the Lendogen
That's right
I received a photo of it
I took about 200,000 photos
I sold the number and put it up in the hallway
If you have a number you want, you can tell me
I'll show you one
This
This is Masao's because he's a soldier
From far away
There are too many clouds, I don't know what's going on
I'll explain
The lungs are like this
From here, it's like this
I thought it would be like this
It was more like this than I thought
I thought I'd say it quickly
Everyone said it
Thank you very much
You're annoying
That's all
There's only one line
What were you doing in the car?
There's a baseball story
Director
I'm going to quit baseball
Okay, quit it
I'm the director
You can't
Why?
You have to stop me
Stop me?
If you don't stop me
In my dad's pajamas
Who are you talking about?
I'm not asking you to stop me
Why are you wearing your dad's pajamas?
If you don't stop me
That's right
Director
I'm going to quit baseball
Okay, quit it
What is that?
You can't
You have to stop me
In my dad's pajamas
Why are you wearing your dad's pajamas?
I wonder if I can get in the car
Please show me
Camera
There are so many people waiting
Have you been waiting this long?
You should have told me
This program was brought to you by these sponsors