The 13th Gaki no Tsukai Arai Exhibition, Chiki Chiki Oogiri Dai Gassen!
This is the 13th episode of the Gaki no Tsukai Arai Exhibition.
I'm Hamada Masatoshi. Thank you for coming.
Now, everyone, please welcome Mr. Hanashika to the stage.
Now, please introduce yourself in order from my side.
First of all, please introduce yourself.
Today, I'm the representative of the yellow team.
I'm the comedian, Kamon Yoko, Yamasaki Hosei.
Nice to meet you.
Please take a seat.
I'm sorry to interrupt your work.
In May this year, I gave birth to my eldest daughter.
Thank you very much.
Children grow up really fast.
Today, I'm going on a trip with my friend to Karuizawa.
It's not that fast, is it?
I'm Endo Shodo.
Nice to meet you.
Please take a seat.
The other day, when I woke up and sighed,
I didn't eat anything the night before, but I smelled like poop.
I'm the comedian, Mini Chua Humpty Dumpty, Miyasako.
Nice to meet you.
Next, please.
When I went to look for a new house,
I found Tanaka-san in the middle of the 4th floor.
He was born in the 3rd of the 4th floor.
I'm the comedian, Neri Goma Choco, Kokoriko Tanaka.
Nice to meet you.
Next, please.
Anyway, that was a great show.
I'd like to join in the fun.
I'm the comedian, Poten Hit.
Nice to meet you.
Next, please.
I'm the comedian, Poten Hit.
I'm not wearing any underwear.
I'm the comedian, Zaimichi Chamonoji.
Nice to meet you.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
I'm sure you're all used to this program.
Yes, we are.
I'm going to ask you to do a strange program.
First of all,
What is the name of the most effective nutrition drink?
I'm sure you've heard of it.
This will make you feel better.
That's the name of the nutrition drink.
Okay?
Yes.
Yama-chan.
It's not luck.
I'm sorry.
Yukeru...
Next.
Kokkirin-D.
It doesn't work at all.
Kokkirin-D is good.
Miyasako.
Double Gorilla.
It works.
Kitamex Junior.
It's good for children.
Okay, Oto-chan.
Power Giant Pentagon.
It's a good name.
Makka-Mamushi.
Makka-Mamushi Eijo.
Is it a grain?
It's not a nutrition drink.
Are you kidding me?
Oh, I see.
I'm not kidding.
I'm sorry.
To-Ijo.
It's not a nutrition drink.
Next.
Tsuyoshi Nagamachi's hit-and-run.
It's a good name.
Let's go with this.
Nagamachi's hit-and-run.
Kama-chan.
Kamakiri.
It's a good name.
Why are you so relaxed?
Next.
You can take care of me on a sunny day.
I know, but it's not good if you say it.
It's an album.
I know.
It's not a single cut.
It's not a super single.
It's an album.
Tsutomu.
It's a good name.
Ryuji.
There's Ryuji, too.
Next.
A man with a pure fist.
Why are you talking in one voice?
Next.
A stage where I say goodbye.
It's a lie.
I'll definitely sing it.
You're lying.
You can't make a song like that.
Nagabuchi will make it.
I'll definitely make it.
I'm Nagabuchi.
I know.
Why are you laughing?
Drowning, connecting, dancing.
Do you remember this?
Yes.
You make a dance according to the music in two bars.
Then you add it and make it yourself.
That's it.
For those of you who got stuck, I prepared this as a punishment game.
What is this?
It's a machine.
For those of you who got stuck, you have to go around like this.
Like this.
You have to switch.
First, Yamachan.
Ready.
You guys.
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
This isn't punishment anymore.
You have to do it like this.
I don't know.
Don't lie.
Just one more time.
It's easy.
Everyone is noisy.
Let's go.
Ready.
Don't do that.
Let's do the right and left together.
Why are you doing this?
I'm sorry. I'll do it again.
Don't say you don't know.
Remember it.
Let's go, Yamachan.
It's easy.
What kind of rhythm is that?
Let's continue.
I don't like this.
Let's do it again.
Ready.
Do what you feel like.
Let's go.
Ready.
What are you doing?
Hodo.
It's really long.
Do your best.
It's good.
I can't do it anymore.
No.6 is definitely a loss.
It's hard.
Ready.
It's definitely a loss.
Let's go, Matsumoto.
It's scary.
It's really scary.
It's a big mistake.
Who would do something like this?
I'm scared.
Here we go.
3, 2, 1, go!
It's done!
This is bad.
It's still in.
Here we go.
I like this.
You're going too far.
Just once.
The last one.
Let's spin it.
Hoto-chan.
It's good, right?
It's good.
The last one.
Yama-chan.
What are you doing?
No one does this.
You're doing something you're not supposed to do.
What are you doing?
I don't remember anything.
It was really easy.
It's scary.
What happened?
No!
I don't remember anything.
I totally misunderstood.
The blade...
I don't remember anything.
This is Sharni.
There's no way.
I thought it was Sharni.
No, no.
No.
3, 2, 1.
Domo!
IT'S DOMON!
That was good.
That's how you do it.
Amazing.
Okay, one more time!
I'll do the same song as before.
What about you, Junma?
I'm sorry, I'll go first.
That's not good.
What kind of woman is that?
She's got a strong back.
You're the one who did the double action.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Okay!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Let's start.
Let's start with Matsumoto-san.
Hey!
Why?
Because I want to end this.
I'll do it properly.
I'll do it like this.
Let's do it again.
You know how to do it, right?
Okay!
I'll do it like this.
Okay.
The pot is...
Ready!
It's hot.
I'll eat the pot ramen.
The pot ramen?
I thought it was a bath.
Yamachan!
It's a complete failure.
Are you okay?
I didn't know it was like this until last year.
There's nothing like this yet.
It's okay.
Ready!
It's hot.
I'll do it like this.
I did it!
It's more like a story than a dance.
Did you call someone?
I did.
I called someone.
Your father is here.
Next is Matsumoto.
It's already me?
It's been a while.
It's finally been a while.
Let's see how many laps you can do.
1, 2, 3.
Why did you take off your pants?
Why?
I don't know.
There must have been something.
This is a kitchen, right?
Why did you take it off?
It's a kitchen.
Thank goodness.
This is bad.
Even though he took off his pants, he said sorry and took it off again.
He took it off again.
The end.
Thank goodness.
It was dangerous.
Did you take it off?
I took it off and stood up.
I took it off and came out and said sorry and went in.
Everyone, let's go.
I can't count anymore.
1, 2, 3.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
He's safe.
Is he safe?
No, no.
It should be me who counts.
I don't know what's going on because he took off his clothes.
Who took it off?
Who is it?
Who took that out?
Who took it out?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
What?
Who took it out?
But it's that kind of corner, right?
No, that's not it.
It's the dance corner!
That's strange now.
Isn't it okay for everyone to do it?
No, no, no. I don't know if I made a mistake.
I don't feel like I made a mistake.
What do you think, everyone?
It's Komiya-san, right?
No, it's not.
It's Komiya-san.
Excuse me for a moment.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
3, 2, 1, go!
This kind of set is no good.
It's really stuck.
All the staff are going to hit me.
It's full of blood.
3, 2, 1, go!
1, go!
Next week's broadcast is the second part of the Oogiri大合戦.
In the new project, Let's go as far as we can go,
the questions from the entertainers are pushing the members mentally.
And in the last episode of Amidabe Zone,
the members are attacked by a new punishment game that has crossed the Oogiri line.
Who will be the winner?
Let's find out!
This program was provided by the following sponsors.