The holy land of bus fishing, Kawaguchiko, which wishes for a spiritual
prosperity.
The Tsuji baka who are more familiar with the entertainment world have created various dramas in the history of the past 10 times.
Pride and will that falls between glory and praise.
This year, the curtain of the hot battle will be cut off on the dream stage.
This year too, the hot battle will be cut off in the dream stage
11th Gaki no Tsukaiyaraen's Chiki Chiki Gainojin Tsuri Contest
Thank you
We've come
It's only once a year that we can host Gaki
Thank you
Let's do our best
It was June last year, but this time it's October.
So there are more fish than us.
That's right.
There are many of them.
I won't let you say anything.
I'll do my best.
Let's go!
Without getting married, I'm going to eat food.
The most unpopular guy in the entertainment world, Matsumoto Oshito.
Matsumoto-san, I love you!
I love you too!
Hello.
My wife said thank you very much.
Today, I'll catch one when Tanaka sinks into the lake.
I see.
It's difficult.
I'll catch it at 3.45.
I see.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you.
Let's go.
The world's best of the best.
The father is a comedian, Kaido Mashigura.
Itoi Shigesato.
There's nothing to say
All four of us
How was it?
It was like chewing gum during the show
It was a good feeling
Shall we start now?
Yes, please
Please
Let's go
Following Pabii, this time it's Kaera de Boromo-ke
Let's eat here
Who wants to see?
It says Kaera de Boromo-ke
Please tell us your enthusiasm for this time
This time?
It's no good, right?
Let's try our best.
I don't even feel like trying.
Please do your best.
Thank you.
Let's go.
The one who wears the mask and is cold inside.
Go for it, Uenzu!
Overcome, Uenzu!
It's Kato Haruhiko!
It's the first time I've been called that.
Thank you.
It's really shocking.
This is the first time I've heard that.
The character is the most popular in the industry.
Really?
If it's really bad this time, I want to hear a real story from you.
Next year.
I'll tell you a story instead.
If you bring a story, we don't know what to do.
Thank you.
Regular Gekigen.
The money is going up!
I don't think he's wearing anything right now!
No, no, no!
Good, good, good!
Zero-zero!
I have a regular.
You do?
I don't use the internet.
I use the internet.
That's the second one?
I shouldn't be underestimating, but
I'm going to use this bus to get a lot of people to come
and then I'll go to the entertainment world and
Thank you very much!
The first guest is...
The real Koizumi Child Train!
Koizumi Kozawa!
What is your father doing now?
What is that?
Did your father do anything?
He did when he was little.
Did he say he wanted to win?
I thought you were local.
I thought you were local too.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
I'll do my best to win.
Thank you.
He's a master of self-proclaimed fishing, Mr. Aikawa, who changed the
fish to a rod and hit the big brother with a forehand.
It's a victory.
But everyone is saying that this is not a winning method.
I've never caught a fish in front of people.
I want to catch one.
I want you to win.
I want to catch a fish of more than 35 cm.
I will do my best.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Now, the last one.
The real-life dress-lip gorilla.
The defending champion, Hamada Masakazu!
Congratulations!
Hello!
I don't remember at all!
You're like a memory!
You can't catch everyone just by looking at their faces.
I'm looking forward to seeing how Aikawa Shou can't catch anything today.
He's going to be in trouble.
He can't catch anything by himself.
I'm looking forward to seeing how he can cut the line.
Thank you for coming.
I'd like to introduce the person who comes here every time.
He's not here, right?
He's Yosuke Eguchi.
I heard about him.
He came here because of his schedule.
And it's a spare engine!
It's a spare engine!
I see.
I'm getting comments from Im-san.
Oh, really? That's great.
What?
It's a shame that it's fading out.
That's up to you!
The show will continue next year.
Please come back next year.
This time, we have another interview for the fishing championship.
We will start the interview.
Since it's the Senna-san corner, we will be broadcasting to the world.
It's been a while.
I'm not here.
Ah, here he comes.
The director is here!
The director is still...
He's back.
The director has gone abroad.
He's here.
Ah, Mr. Tamura is here.
How do you feel?
Stretch it out, stretch it out.
The weather is not good, but it's autumn, so it's the season of autumn leaves.
Is that all?
I'll do my best today, so I'll do this big black bass.
I'm so angry.
How many times did you say that?
I was told to run away.
I'm so angry.
Why did I say that?
What?
Why did you say that?
What are you talking about?
It's not related!
You're rude!
I'm going every time!
Listen to what the man in front of you says!
Look!
It's not your goal!
You can do it!
To Aiga-san too!
To Sho-san too!
You can do it!
You're wearing sunglasses!
Glasses are glasses!
It's the first appearance of the
Oh, you're giving it to Aika-san too?
To Sho-san?
What are you doing?
You're wearing sunglasses.
I'm wearing glasses.
Wow, amazing!
This is the first time I've seen this.
Like this.
I'll do my best.
It's like I'm going to be a star.
Go home.
You're a good guy.
I'm going to break this huge block.
It's so small!
It's a mistake.
I'll do it!
What is that?
Thank you.
When?
I heard it for the first time.
It's the last.
It's from Tanaka.
It's an announcement.
I see.
It's too much.
I'm the one who arranged the tickets.
Attention!
This year, again,
those who came to fish without eating,
those who cling to this entertainment world,
the rich people of money,
Oh?
It's not a joke.
B-class comedian, B-class actor, B-class musician, C-class comedy writer.
Unfortunately, this year is also C-class comedy writer.
Hey, C-class comedy writer!
You are also B-class comedian.
You are getting more and more C-class comedy writer.
From now on, if I say something grateful to you,
I'll say it with all my heart!
Please do.
We are...
The water bugs of the entertainment world!
The water bugs of the entertainment world.
We don't have any hard-to-treat aura.
Chiyaki, we love you!
Sh tu ja ki is is weak?
I said seriously I'm weak
As a position, I don't think it's a dirty, unpopular thing!
It's not a dirty thing!
You're a trashy, trashy human being!
Please, Mr. Nittere!
Let us fish like this!
Amen!
Anyway, aim for the championship and do your best!
Dismissed!
I haven't fished much, but I want to be a good angler
I found out that I can fish other than fish last year
I want to fish in various ways
I'm going to go!
Kojiko-kun, you've been away from that for a while
Last time, I finished 4th place, so this time I want to get 1st place no matter what
It's my first time at a bus ride, but I heard that it's a way to catch fish
I want to catch one
Everyone, please support me
I want to catch one.
I don't like zero.
You said you want to catch one.
Yes.
I've only done it in the sea, but I want to catch one.
Bang!
I'll blow up the whole nature today!
Now, the three-man match, start!
I'm going to catch a fish!
I caught a fish!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
The fishing competition rules are very simple.
The one who catches the biggest black bass within the time limit wins.
The one who started fishing earlier than any other boat is Tamada, Aikawa and Okuda.
Oh, there's a fish.
He's been fishing for 40 years, but this is his first time fishing for a bus.
How good is he?
Shou, you can't fish because you've been watching videos.
I can't.
That's a great way to learn.
I was eating the moment I turned on the video.
On the other hand, in this boat, there is a man who has forgotten the basics of bus fishing.
It's about 10 o'clock now, so please sink it.
Oh, it's about 10 o'clock.
Asano, who has participated in the first time in three years, is a little anxious.
And, in the morning, it's a painful fight.
Is it the first hit?
Did you get it?
Wow, amazing.
Bluegill.
Ah...
Gill.
No.
He thought it was a bus, but it was Bluegill.
It's Bluegill that's floating.
He's frustrated. He can't get it first.
On the other hand, this is Wakate Boat.
It's the first time Koizumi has been in the real mode,
compared to the Okiraku Combi of Yamasaki Kato.
Kotaro-kun, if you get the first place in the first round, you'll be cool.
Oh, this is...
It's a obstacle.
It's definitely Bluegill and Mizukusato.
Why is Black Master outside?
That's good.
That's good, right?
With fish.
What?
Is it coming?
Wow, that was a little bit of a moment.
It came out.
Really?
Every year, this...
No, it's not.
The number of times it shows is different.
Every year?
It's the usual thing to do in the new year.
And then at the end, the teacher scolds him.
Meanwhile, Itoi's face is again in a bad mood.
Agil.
I don't want to show it.
I'm not good at fishing.
I only know the cool ones.
Itoi is again a bitter bug.
From the start, 30 minutes. He's still not alone. He's going at a very slow pace.
Just like last year, he's also going through a lot of trials this year.
This is strange. I can't get used to this.
It's already happened.
What? No! How many years has it been?
It's trash.
You ask me the same question every year.
I'm coming!
Suddenly Okuda's face changes.
He feels the weight and lifts his heels.
What is this?
Okuda's first win in the competition.
I'm going.
What is this?
Put it in your pocket.
Put it in your pocket!
I want you to listen to me.
If you can catch one.
It's better if you can catch one.
That's right.
If no one can catch one, it's a victory.
I'll do my best.
Don't say that.
Usually, the one who caught one says that.
I see.
On the other hand, the unbelievable development in the boat of three young men with no pieces of the hit.
Oh, what is it?
You just went to the fish farm, right?
Hey, look! It's a Tachiro!
Oh, you surprised me. It's already my fish.
I thought it was a Tachiro.
Tachiro?
Why is it a Tachiro?
You're so mean!
I thought it was a small fish.
Mr. Yamasaki, this is a lake.
Meanwhile, Asano is struggling here.
And then, next to him...
Here it comes!
Matsumoto is hit!
Oh!
That's pretty good!
It's here!
Sorry!
The first one Matsumoto got is a big size fish!
It's here!
But it's not that small!
It's got a big nose and a big nose.
As expected of a veteran.
I'm not going to be able to do it.
I'm going to do it at 11.
Excuse me, I'm not only taking this boat.
You bastard!
Kotaro!
I'm asking you to be the leader.
You guys are useless.
I want to take it!
Hey!
Shut up!
Isn't it good?
I'm going to make him suffer.
The big guests gather once a year for the fishing competition.
But only two of them are fishing at this time of the year.
The members are looking a little worried.
Will they be okay?
It's not good at all. They're not fishing.
They're not fishing.
Only Okuda and Matsumoto.
Hmm...
But it's a paper boat, so it's like a coin coin.
It's a coin coin.
Does this have anything to do with the location over there?
Can't you change the boat?
It doesn't matter to me.
The bad thing about the pull is bad.
I'll catch one somehow.
Kotaro-kun, is your pull okay?
Don't worry about it.
I'm getting nervous.
The bad guy is you, Yama-chan.
At that time, Aikawa, who was just playing the reel silently, was already in a frustrated mode.
Please turn around.
I just ran the line.
I was watching it. I should have lost at that time.
He missed the chance
He's manly
That is suspicious
It's suspicious
Do you see it?
Somehow
Can you put it a little flat?
parallel to him
Small
Koguta gets the second fish
Oh, it's coming!
What is this?
It's a dangerous bird.
In addition, Hamada also got the first one in this tournament.
It's small!
It's so small.
It's a dead fish.
Don't lose to this!
Hamada-san, is it small?
Hamada-san's is really small.
I also got a small one.
This is a bit funny.
Right?
This is funny.
You can't say that.
I thought I could get one for my big brother.
But I was wrong.
I'm sure it was a big one.
It's bigger than the one before.
It's a good one.
Okuda perfectly got the big size he was looking for.
Why is it so hard to cut?
That's strange.
You should believe in yourself.
Thank you.
It's fast to cut here.
It's fast.
By the way, Itoi is being completely separated from the bus he was looking for.
Please.
You, you.
Please, please.
Sorry.
How about this?
This one!
A big shock!
Itoi's favorite bus is not found.
I'm not patient enough.
It's sad.
It's sad, isn't it?
Well, really.
If everyone had caught one fish each...
What?
This bastard.
Somehow...
If you think it's suspicious, you should wait.
Wait?
Wait for it.
Ah, it's coming!
I caught it!
That was close!
You did it, big brother!
Aikawa's first fish caught!
Hooray!
I'm sorry.
Please show us the fish.
It's a little bit of a fish.
Wow.
This is a good boat.
Thank you.
Can you go on this boat?
That's good.
If you think about it, you can definitely use the fish as a boat.
It's scary.
The whole boat was in a warm atmosphere.
That's good.
It was really good.
Thank you boss
Good bye
We are ended
Arukata
This is the army!
Cool!
Attention everyone to the left hand!
The Japanese army is here!
Hey, come on!
Thank you for your hard work!
Hey, Captain!
Next time, on the next episode of the Tri-Ten-Shen!
It's about time for the final round.
Ishikawa's army suddenly appears and faces a dangerous situation.
The five of them are still aiming for a slight reversal.
And the hero dives into the water.
In the middle of the battle...
Isn't this the last three?
The big brother is in a rage.
Who will be the one to grab the captain?
This episode was brought to you by Drangostanza.