It's been a long time since I've seen this.
This is a very interesting pair of gloves.
This is a very energetic guest.
What is this?
It looks like a civilian's helmet.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Do you remember me?
What do you mean?
I'm sorry, but...
What are you talking about?
The Japanese series, right?
Yes.
Hageoka.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
It was last week or the day before last week.
Yes.
I was with the Titans.
And you were with the West.
You said something like that, didn't you?
No, I didn't say anything like that.
You said something like the Nihon Seiyon.
I'm sorry, but I've won four times in a row.
You've won four times in a row, right?
I even drank beer.
Oh, you did.
I was in a commercial, and I didn't know who was going to win.
You didn't know.
I didn't know.
You said you were going to the West.
I did say that, but in the end...
It wasn't in the end.
In the end, I said, let's go the other way.
In the end, I won.
No, no, no.
That's what happened, right?
Yes, that's what happened.
Well, that's obvious.
No, no, no.
Something like a punishment?
No.
Are you misunderstanding something?
No, no, no.
I don't care if I'm not a West player.
I don't care if the West loses.
No, no, no.
There's still a video left.
Well, next week.
A punishment game that you can do at the opening.
Um, that one?
Are you going to cut it?
That was when I lost.
You said you were going to cut it, right?
That was about a few days ago.
It's rare, but I've lived 39 years.
I've been there about three or four times.
I had a pimple, and the moment I stood up, I stepped on it.
It hurts a lot, doesn't it?
No, no, no.
Shut up!
It hurts a lot, and it's embarrassing.
Well, it doesn't matter if you step on it.
It's a punishment game. Next week.
From now on, we're going to talk about the pay-off.
Why pay-off?
Where are you going to connect it?
This is the fun part of the talk.
Next week, we're going to have a punishment game.
Are you thinking about it?
Well, if you do this...
Who is that?
If the giant loses, it's like there was nothing like that.
Is that possible?
If I lost, I would have lost.
It's like there was nothing like that.
You should have been talking normally.
100,000 yen, 50,000 yen, I don't know what fate is.
I knew it for sure.
It's the same as my father's divorce.
I'm going to talk like there was nothing.
Oh, you're going to talk like Joichi.
No, no, I'll do it.
I'll keep that in mind.
What?
No way!
Then tell me how it feels.
What?
I don't care if you get beat up or not.
What does that mean?
You didn't tell me to wear it or anything.
I'm going to be very violent.
I'm going to talk a lot.
It's because I'm a kid.
Then tell me how it feels.
What does it feel like?
I'm going to be very scary.
I'll just tell you how it feels.
That's what the punishment game is.
If you go into a shop and ask if you want to eat curry, they'll give you curry.
This is the first time I'm eating curry at this shop.
I can't eat it because there's a curry menu.
I don't know what it is, but if it gets in my mouth, it's scary!
Say it!
There's no point in saying it, it's a punishment game.
You can't make me do anything.
I know.
I know, but I don't want to say it.
I don't want to say it's a punishment game.
It's just like that.
But it's the atmosphere.
It's really scary.
What is it?
I can't spend that much money on the opening.
It's really scary.
If you make one mistake, I'll tell you what it's like.
What is it?
If you make one mistake...
If you're strong, your bones won't break.
That's nice.
You can't do anything physical.
I know.
You can only do things that suit your style.
If that's the case, I can do a lot of things.
Are you stupid?
I'm not stupid.
What?
I can tell that you're stupid.
I'm not stupid.
Why?
You're more stupid.
I'm not stupid.
I'm really not stupid.
It's okay. Just enjoy it.
I can't enjoy it.
It's okay.
You can't get hurt.
Don't show up with someone you miss.
I hate it.
I hate it a lot.
And don't do things like lying down.
I don't do things like lying down.
It's really scary.
When you got hit by Jimmy, you were like a fool.
I didn't get hit.
I don't do things like lying down.
I'll tell you this.
When you're on a variety show like this,
there are a lot of complaints.
That's bullying.
That's not good for education.
A little thing like that can cause complaints.
I don't think it's that kind of thing.
I don't think it's bullying.
But lying down is bullying.
Why is that?
When you wake up, you're like a Tohyo person that everyone knows.
It's really scary.
Everyone is laughing at me.
They know me. They know me.
Why am I here?
It's really strange.
It's fine.
I don't do things like that in the Japanese series.
You're the one who said it.
Right?
Why did you say it twice?
I didn't say it.
If I had lost, I would have been in trouble.
Did I say that I was a seibu?
Please take a look.
Which do you think it is?
I think it's a giant.
Really?
I'm a giant fan, so I have to support a giant.
But I really think it's a seibu.
Shall we bet?
It's a giant seibu.
Really?
Yes.
It's been a while.
It's fine.
It's a giant seibu.
I didn't say it.
You didn't say it.
You just took a giant seibu.
Don't say that.
You should have taken it.
You should have told me to be a giant.
You were confident in seibu, right?
Next week?
I don't think I can win next week.
Last week, I bet on beer.
I bet on beer.
It's like a punishment game.
I want to kiss a grandma of a punch bag.
I want to kiss her.
You're desperate.
You're hungry.
I like kiss.
I know.
I've never done it before.
I can't believe it.
Let's move on.
Okay.
Go ahead.
It's a big boy.
This is a question for Matsumoto-san, who has been taken to the 18th space station.
You said that the 13th time was the most memorable.
Why is that?
Ah, yes, yes, yes.
I was taken away so many times.
Almost continuously.
18 times?
Yes.
Continuously? What do you mean?
There were times when I was only free for 3 hours.
Can you come back once?
It was over when I watched a video.
Why were you taken away?
When I watched a video of Godfather, it was over when I finished watching it.
Please show it to me.
Then why did you return it?
It was about 3 hours.
Please show me Godfather in UFO.
No, no.
I was taken away so many times.
What?
There are many reasons for that.
There are many patterns.
The picture is like this.
How is it?
Well, the most orthodox one that everyone knows is when UFO comes.
Yes.
And it is exposed to light.
Ah, yes, yes.
And it is gently sucked up.
There was a pattern like that.
While walking somewhere?
Yes.
If you look at it, it looks like everyone is taken away to paradise.
What?
It is quite difficult.
What is that?
It is going up smoothly.
No, it hurts a lot here.
No, you are using your teeth.
No, no, no.
Are you stupid?
You are like the light.
Do you really think that it will go up?
If it is a movie, it will be like that.
You can make it like this.
Like this.
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
You can put a sponge here and a sponge here.
Really?
No, it is not.
It is going up.
What is the inside like?
The inside is, how to say, it is like a square.
Are you stupid?
It is wide.
There are many things like that.
Oh, yes.
Where are you going to take it first?
If it goes up, where are you going to take it?
The Japanese room.
I am sorry.
What?
What is it like to be an alien?
It is like a work uniform.
Yes, yes, yes.
What is it like around here?
It is bumpy.
Bumpy?
Bumpy.
Is it a pig?
No, it is bumpy.
It is bumpy.
What color is it?
What?
It is a love color.
It is a complicated color.
It is more popular than you.
I think so.
It is a lot.
So?
When you go home, there are a lot of bumpy things.
There are a lot of bumpy things.
So?
You do not understand the word.
It is said that you can laugh when you are bumpy.
First, it comes to your brain.
I see.
Yes, yes, yes.
It is said that you should listen to what it says when you are bumpy.
Oh, we are?
Yes, yes, yes.
When you become Kachikata...
Eh? Kachikata?
When you become Kachikata, you do not understand the word.
It is a bit of a threat.
This is a threat.
I see.
You should listen to what it says.
You should take off your clothes.
First of all.
Yes.
Then?
I was given something like a garbage can.
Yes.
It is surprisingly small.
A garbage can.
Yes.
I wondered if I could fit in.
I was quite depressed.
I said, can I fit in?
I was about to become Kachikata.
You should not get angry at such a thing.
You will soon be Kachikata.
They are.
I see.
I am scared.
Yes.
When you take off your clothes, it means you are barefoot.
I became barefoot.
Yes, yes, yes.
Then?
I was given a lot of embarrassing things.
I see.
Yes.
What is that?
Is it that you are examining your body?
Yes, it is.
Yes.
I was given painful things.
I was given a lot of painful things.
What kind of things?
Why do you do that?
It seemed like I was joking.
You should not be so stupid.
It was an examination.
I was given a lot of painful things.
I looked like an adult when I was given a painful thing.
I said, hey!
And I was told, hey!
Hey!
You just said it!
I don't know! I don't know!
You're an idiot.
They were children.
I don't know which one is a child and which one is an adult.
It's not that they're big, so they're adults, and small, so they're not children.
Their body sizes are the same.
Oh, is that so?
That's right.
Yeah.
It's been this long.
What are you going to do in the end?
What do you mean?
If you investigate everything, they'll return it to you.
So I got a stamp card like this.
And then I went,
It's the first time, so can you give me two?
There are 24, so don't take it!
You're going to get hurt.
I'm going to go.
I'm going to go, but I'm still going.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
I'm going to go like a sponge.
I'm still going.
Oh, like a sponge.
I'm going to go like a sponge.
That's right, that's right.
And then it's red here.
And then when I got hurt,
Why is this so red?
You!
I've been saying this all the time.
18 times.
It's always this.
But all 24 stamps are not full.
It's only 18 times.
That's right.
So I got a handbook.
Not a handbook, but a college notebook.
What is it?
Why a college notebook?
I got a pencil and a notebook.
That's because it's been over 10 times.
It's been over 10 times.
Aoyama-san.
Oh, is that so?
If you go 20 times, it's a CD Walkman.
Right now.
Why is it right now?
No.
It's not even called the worst.
Okonomiyaki has Hiroshima-yaki, Osaka-yaki, etc.
I heard that Matsumoto has original Matsumoto-yaki.
What kind of yaki is it?
If possible, I'd like to make it for you.
Matsumoto-yaki?
Yes.
Is that so?
It's not sudden, is it?
Then tell me the ingredients.
The ingredients are basically the same.
Okonomiyaki and Matsumoto.
What's the difference?
What's the difference between Okonomiyaki and Matsumoto?
You're probably wondering what's being added.
That's right.
It's different.
What do you mean?
Matsumoto-yaki's main goal is to make something delicious without using anything that was never used.
I see.
So there's nothing to add?
To be clear, there's no cassette stove.
I put the iron plate directly on the tatami.
But there's a gun.
There's a gun.
Why is there a gun?
And then I turn it over.
Don't turn it over!
The whole family is going to be in trouble.
It's going to be a mess.
And then...
It's not hot.
Next...
It's going to be like that.
I'm going to eat it raw.
This is Matsumoto-yaki's main goal.
It's funny.
Once a week...
It's funny, isn't it?
The pen name is Begirama-san.
Shut up!
Once a week, Mr. Matsumoto says that he always checks new products in the home appliances section of Don Quixote.
Yes, yes.
That's part of it.
What happens when you play a CD in a DVD player?
I've never done that before.
You've never done it before?
Yes.
Electrical products are very...
You think they're smart, don't you?
Oh, electronic products.
You think electronic products are smart.
You're the only one who thinks that.
I think electronic products are smart, but they're actually not that different from electronic products.
That's right.
It's more like a joke.
You can only apply things that have been decided.
I see.
That's why DVD players always decide when they put in DVD software.
This is stupid.
If you put in a CD...
Yes, yes.
If you put in a CD, they don't notice.
They don't know what they're putting in.
If you look at it for about 10 minutes, it goes into the TV screen.
It goes like this.
And then it goes red.
They're stupid.
Wait, wait.
What?
Shut up.
Turn on the button, turn on the button.
Hama-chan, a super-duper, is often told that he has never done anything good for anyone except for the rich.
Is that true?
I'm sure that Mr. Matsumoto, who has been in Konpyo for many years, knows what good things Mr. Hamada has done for others.
I see.
Please tell me.
Yes, yes.
Can I think about it for a moment?
Why?
I was wondering what it was like.
Don't think about it. Just remember it.
Oh, I see.
I think there are a few.
I don't think there are.
Please tell me.
It looks good.
Please wait a little longer.
Matsun.
What's this, Matsun?
Wait a minute.
Matsun, please tell me what came over you.
I think.
Matsu! I don't get it! Ask Taka-chan!
No, no, I was just about to go out, in the park or something
Matsu!
Yes, yes
Say it!
I was just about to go out, in the park or something
Wait a minute
If you're late, you're late!
Okay, okay, okay
If you go out, you're just like poop
If you go out, you're just like drool
If you think about it, it's hard to imagine
Something happened, right?
I don't get it
Can't Taka-san teach me?
Hey, Taka-chan
Taka-chan
Matsu is in trouble!
Hurry up and say it!
I was just about to go out
Say it!
If you say one more, I'll go home!
That, that, that, that, that, that, that
What is it?
That's a one-time thing
In the end, that's a one-time thing
Hey, Matsu
I don't get it
You said it's a one-time thing
Say it! Just one more, you idiot
That's a one-time thing
It doesn't matter
That's rude
Hey, you
You took 18 aliens with you
How can you say that so casually?
It's been 21 years since we met
I've seen a lot of things
Say it! You did something good once
That's a one-time thing
If you say it so suddenly, I don't get it
Please
Why are you so irritated?
I'm thinking
You're thinking?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
You can't lie
I've never seen anything like this