Chuki Chuki Grandfather and Grandmother Zesture Battle!
This game is between Grandmother Matsumoto and Grandfather Hamada...
Grandfather Hamada?
No, Grandfather Hamada.
Hamada and Grandfather Hamada?
Hamada will be divided into two teams.
They will compete for points with Zesture.
It's a game just like the title.
I see, I understand.
The first question will be asked by Hamada-san.
Let's start the Zesture game!
It's a gorilla!
Don't look at it!
Stop it!
This is bad!
What are you doing?
Don't make a voice!
What?
What are you doing?
You can't do it anymore.
No, don't make a voice!
Don't make a voice!
Let me put in only Ehehe.
Only Ehehe?
If you put in only Ehehe, I won't be able to get into the mood.
Stop it!
Don't make a voice!
Only Ehehe!
Stop it!
What are you doing?
Don't make a voice!
It's a bear!
What are you doing?
Don't think about it!
The correct answer is a bear.
A bear?
Yes.
Oh my!
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Let's start!
Don't make a voice!
What are you doing?
No!
Stop it!
There is a bear inside!
It's a bear!
No!
Don't make a voice!
It's hot!
It's a crab.
The next question is a VTR.
The Hamada team, the old man is going to be on the show.
I want you to guess the song.
There is a song playing on the screen.
I want you to guess the lyrics.
Hamada, can you put on your headphones?
You have one minute.
It's easy.
Hamada, can you answer the question?
It's a dance song.
That's too bad.
The answer is Paradise Galaxy.
VTR, start!
I have no idea.
It's a dance song.
It's a foreign person.
The old lady gave me a hint.
Foreign person?
It's a super 4-piece.
We have a new set for today.
Look at this.
We did a good job.
It's exactly what Hibino wrote.
If you look at the new set,
it would be better if there was more reaction.
But you guys are more like animals.
We are like wild boars.
Even if you say to a dog,
this reaction is new,
it would be like that.
You guys are crazy.
Do something more.
You are more like wild boars.
We have a new set for today.
Thank you.
It's a lot of money.
It's our show.
Why don't we have money for our show?
We have a lot of money for 30 minutes.
Why?
We have sponsors.
What is the sponsor?
Pizza.
Pizza?
After you become a pizza,
you can't bring pizza to a restaurant.
You are crazy.
Pizza?
Bring it in 30 minutes.
In the middle of the night.
What else do we have?
FANKEIRO cosmetics.
No.
FANKEIRO cosmetics is the first thing I brought.
What did you bring?
I don't know.
It's like a set.
It's like a face wash.
I brought it.
What is that?
It's a FANKEIRO cosmetics that tells me to wash my face and come back.
If you wash your face and come back,
bring more.
The sponsor has changed.
Mobile gasoline.
We bring it.
Gasoline?
No.
While you are doing it,
if you say,
I didn't put gasoline today.
If you go out and turn on the gas,
and it's full,
it feels good.
Don't do that.
Bring more.
And GEOS.
It's an English language school.
English language?
Come and teach me English.
I don't want to teach you.
Don't say that.
What?
Oh, I see.
It's been changed since April.
Yes.
It's a big deal.
Well,
I have to do my best.
recently,
everyone doesn't say much.
What is it?
The weather in the Kanto region.
What?
It's really cold today, isn't it?
It's not really cold today.
Is it that cold?
It's cold.
Oh,
this year,
Uesugi was walking until he answered.
But it's really cold, isn't it?
That's why the news doesn't go around.
What are you talking about?
Well,
I have plenty of time,
so I'll talk slowly.
No,
I'm talking slowly.
I'm not in a hurry.
The news doesn't go around.
What are you talking about?
You guys!
If you think all the news is true,
it's a big mistake.
I'll tell you this.
You believe it, don't you?
The news is all true.
It's all made up.
For example,
I had a hijack.
No Japanese passengers were on board.
It has nothing to do with that!
What?
Whether Japanese people are on board or not.
Why does it have nothing to do with that?
Hijacking is not a big deal,
so do it more seriously.
But,
there's no one to worry about.
That's a different way of saying it.
What?
I had a hijack.
But,
there's no Japanese people on board.
That's a different way of saying it.
That's fine.
What are you laughing at?
I'm not laughing.
I'm not laughing,
but why are you so relieved?
I'm relieved.
Because there's no Japanese people on board.
What?
What if a foreigner gets on board and gets hurt?
I don't know.
If it's a foreigner,
it must be connected to somewhere.
There's no such thing.
I don't even know that.
Mr. Chadda from Yugoslavia.
What?
No, no.
It's just an example.
For example,
when you were about to get on the elevator,
right?
When you were about to close the door,
there was a person who opened the door for you.
That person is from Yugoslavia.
I've never been in that situation before.
The person who opened the door.
The person who opened the door is a Japanese person.
A Japanese person, Mr. Suzuki, opened the door for you.
Actually,
Mr. Austin from Yugoslavia
is a friend of Mr. Suzuki.
The person who saved Mr. Austin's life
is Mr. Chadda.
There's no such thing.
That's why you and Mr. Chadda were connected somewhere.
The reason is that if Mr. Chadda didn't save Mr. Austin,
the elevator of Mr. Austin's friend wouldn't have opened.
Do you understand?
If you think like that,
you don't care about foreigners.
There's no such thing.
That's what I think as a Filipino.
I'm so cool.
My partner is Filipino.
There are many lies in the weekly magazine.
What are you doing?
Shut up.
There's a CM model.
She's very popular now.
When she appeared in the CM,
I asked her who she was.
She said it was a lie.
It was a lie.
When she appeared in the CM,
I asked her who she was.
She said it was a lie.
Today, you and the audience
are against me.
What are you talking about?
That's enough.
What's enough?
If you behave like that,
I have an idea.
What is it?
What are you going to do?
What am I going to do?
You're scared if you make me angry.
What are you going to do?
If you make me angry,
I'll really be angry.
If I bend my back a little,
I'll be angry.
I'm angry.
If I bend my back a little,
the show will be messed up.
it will be messed up.
That's amazing.
If I bend my back a little,
it will be messed up.
What?
If I bend my back a little,
the show will be messed up.
I don't care.
I'll do it.
I'm really scared.
Shut up.
If I bend my back a little,
the show will be messed up.
Please.
You're...
Well, I won't bend my back today.
Is this a new Yoshimoto drama?
I'll bend my back next week.
Next week is fine.
Why next week?
When you talk to people,
it's hard for me to talk with my arms crossed.
When I'm scared,
I say something like this.
I don't know if I've said this before.
People are talking.
I'm listening to them.
Why don't you listen to me like this?
It's fine.
I'm talking and I can hear you.
If you can hear me,
you don't have to do anything.
I'm listening to you.
Talk to me.
What are you going to do?
Are you going home tomorrow?
What?
That's what I'm saying.
No.
That's not it.
I'm not angry.
You don't have to do anything.
Just answer me.
That's right.
If I say something like this,
people will answer me.
What should I do?
If you're angry,
I'm angry.
If you say something like this,
I'll go home tomorrow.
I'm not angry either.
Really?
Really.
I'm not angry at all.
I'm not angry.
You'll go home tomorrow.
You're going home tomorrow.
You have to keep working.
That's right.
It's you.
You're the one being angry.
That's annoying.
What?
Not being angry at the office.
I don't want to go home,
I'm fine with whatever I'm doing.
You,
What the hell is this?
So...
What do you call it?
What kind of practice?
Golf.
That's your hobby.
And this area is your workplace.
You bring your hobby to your workplace.
That's what I like about you.
No, no.
I'm not being serious.
I'm talking to you.
You...
Stop it!
Hello.
Please introduce yourself.
My name is Kiriko Kobayashi.
Kiriko?
Kiriko.
My real name.
I wanted to be on this show as a talent.
When I was dying.
In April.
I was told that I was going to do a lot of work.
As a first attempt.
I thought I could be an assistant.
That's why I came here.
I see.
For example, you want to be in a drama.
Yes, I want to be in a drama.
You want to be a comedian?
I want to be a comedian.
But it's harder than it looks.
You're facing the camera and doing this.
It takes six years to do this.
It takes eight years.
This is my first job.
This is the pose of a cartoonist.
It takes eight years.
When we take pictures, we usually do this.
This is the pose of a cartoonist.
It takes eight years.
This is hard.
Thank you very much.
You want to do something with 1,000 people.
Yes.
You want to clean the toilet in Yamase-Sennai station.
If we all do it together, it will be clean.
Why do you do that?
Here we go.
Seriously, why do you do that?
On a show.
You.
What?
You're a sheep.
You're a fool.
You haven't cleaned the toilet, have you?
I have.
I cleaned it with my hands.
You were able to do that.
That's right.
When I was in high school, I was cleaning the toilet with my hands.
Only in the first year.
That's a dirty story.
You have poop on your toilet.
What are you going to do with that?
With my nails.
Seriously?
You're a monster.
You're a fool.
I'm always having fun.
I don't know how to use the toilet.
By the way, Machan said that he is good at fighting.
How many people can you defeat if you are a primary school student?
If you are a primary school student, it's unlimited.
I don't know if there will be such a person.
I've been fighting a lot lately.
I'm going to tell you how to fight.
Hurry up and tell me.
There is a leader in every group.
That's right.
Finding that leader is the best way to fight.
Even if there are 200 or 300 elementary school students, there is one person who has a bad personality.
That's the leader.
Right?
That's why the leader is like this.
See?
That means what I'm talking about right now is useless.
There is a leader in every group.
Let me explain the situation so far.
That's right.
That's how you find it.
There is a leader in every group.
That's wrong.
That's not the leader.
Even though everyone is the leader, it's the leader in everyone's bath.
You should do as much as you can.
It's better to do as much as you can.
Everyone's here.
That's the leader.
Koko!
I'm here!
The leader falls down.
What a fool.
Why don't you appear in movies and dramas like Hama-chan?
I'm a fan of you.
What?
You're a fan?
When I asked my friend what he thought of me, he said, look at his face. He has a stupid face.
And he's a super ultra-handsome and homo-like person.
He can't remember lines and his acting is like Horichemi.
I was a super ultra-special mammoth shock.
Are you doing a radio shock?
Hama-chan, do you know how good Mach-chan's acting is? If you know, please tell me.
P.S. Hama-chan's acting is better than the famous short story.
This is...
I hate it.
And I'm a big fan of you.
Your acting is totally different from the acting in the story.
Totally different.
That's true.
Once I become an actor, I'll be scared even if I play Moriishi.
Why are you saying that all of a sudden?
Say something more serious.
I don't want to make Japanese actors and actresses my enemies.
But everyone's acting is a little stinky.
Who's stinky?
Everyone.
I don't want to make you look sad.
You can't make a sad face when you're really sad.
What kind of face do I make when I'm really sad?
When you're really sad, you can't make a face like this.
You can't make a face like this.
Say it quickly.
You can't say anything because you don't say what you want to say.
I can't say anything.
You can't say it quickly.
1,000,000 yen.
That's too much.
You can't make a face like this.
That's not true.
What kind of face do I make when I'm sad?
There are different ways to make a sad face.
For example, when my parents died.
Oh, your parents died. How did they die?
From the outside, the cell changes into one.
I was sick and just slept all the time.
I was doing my job.
Then I got the news that it was dangerous.
I ran back to the hospital in a hurry.
I opened the door, but I was already dead.
That's the setting.
Then there's a door, right?
There are five of us.
That's when the camera...
The sad feeling at that time.
Unfortunately, there are five of us.
Hello.
This is the ending.
It looks like you were talking today.
I talked for a long time, so I ended up like this.
The set has changed.
This is the set I've been wearing so far.
This neon can.
I'll give it to you as a gift.
For those of you who watch TV.
If you want it, write it down.
I'll give you all the details.
But it's noisy.
I'll give it to those who can come to get it.
This neon can.
For those who can come to get it.
I'll give it to you as a gift.
I'll give you a lottery from there.
At worst, if you take this off, you'll get a grilled meat party.
Barbecue.
This is iron plate.
This can't be iron plate.
It's a net.
Please come over here.
And the baby and the assistant.
The baby and the assistant are also here.
And the assistant.
Please come over here.
That's all.
I don't like crying.
Thank you for your viewing.