Chikichiki Quiz! Find the Zura! Grand Prix!
This time, it's called the Find the Zura! Grand Prix.
Which one of us is wearing the zura?
Simply put, who is the real one?
Let's do it!
First, we'll introduce the answer.
From here, it's Mr. Fuyuki Motoh!
Mr. Fuyuki, don't you usually do anything?
I usually wear a mesh wig.
I don't usually do that.
Next, we have Strong Kongo!
Kongo, you don't usually wear the zura, right?
I've been doing it for 8 years, but I've never worn a wig.
Are you wearing it?
Yes, I'm wearing it.
Kongo, you have one, right?
Yes, I've been wearing it for 3 years.
Today, I've prepared something like this.
Kongo, you're wearing it.
Oh my!
What a big head!
You look like Koike-san.
Lastly, we have Mr. Matsumoto, the Find the Zura!
Hello, good evening.
You're the one who's wearing the zura, right?
I've been looking through a lot of people.
You're the one who's wearing the zura?
There are people who can't see through it.
You know that, but you can't say it out loud.
There are people in the entertainment industry who can't say it out loud.
Oh, is that so?
There are a lot of people in the entertainment industry who can't say it out loud.
I've been checking it out.
What do you have?
How to sweat.
Oh, if you're wearing it, how do you sweat?
Why are you sweating from here?
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Let's go to the first question!
The first question is a question about VTR.
Everyone, please look at the monitor.
Go ahead!
VTR, VTR.
Let's go!
Let's go to the first question!
Let's go! The first question is a VTR question.
Everyone, please look at the monitor.
Well, I went out to Shinjuku, Tokyo.
Is this person a zura?
This is not a zura.
Well, there are four people walking around the city of Shinjuku.
I brought a little.
Well, let's go.
Is it number one, number two, number three, number four?
First of all, it's a light question.
How many of these four people are wearing a wig?
Number four is too wig-like.
This is a lie.
I see, I see.
Well, everyone, number one, number two, number three, number four, please.
Number one.
Is that a zura?
The most difficult to understand.
Well, well.
I understand.
Now, Mr. Hongo.
Yes, I am.
You've got a big hole.
This is.
Depending on the type of maker, there are various types of wigs.
Yes, yes, yes.
I feel like it's the most wig-like wig.
That can't be helped.
Now, Zura Miyaburiman.
Number two.
Partially, he's wearing a thin one.
I think that's the most natural way to deceive.
He's wearing a thin one.
Well, number one, number four, number two.
Now, let's see the correct answer.
This person.
Well, for the time being, I'll send you the wind.
Zura.
That's not it.
It doesn't fly.
This?
That's not it.
It's a wig.
That's why the correct answer is number four, Mr. Hongo.
Correct.
Well, then.
The second question!
The second question will actually be lined up here.
Let's get started.
Now, we have 5 people lined up.
You don't have to do the mantle.
The problem is the head, but you can do the mantle.
If you have any questions.
The first person.
Yes, the first person.
Is that a mantle?
No!
Who is it?
I don't know.
Yes.
Mr. Kongo.
Wake up in the morning.
Yes.
Tell me the time until the time is up.
From the first person.
I see, the time to prepare.
Are you wearing a mantle?
Can you wear it off in about 30 seconds?
Wear it off?
Is it a technical term?
Normally, you don't wear it off, do you?
Is that so?
What about the second person?
Wear it off for about a minute.
About a minute.
What about the third person?
About 10 seconds.
10 seconds?
What about the fourth person?
About 10 minutes.
10 minutes?
What about the fifth person?
About 30 minutes.
It takes 30 minutes?
It seems to take 30 minutes.
You have a good face, so you should wear makeup.
What are you talking about?
The first 5 people lined up like this.
I was holding it like this.
Please take a good look at me.
Here comes Mr. Kongo.
I'll show you how to do it with a big mouth.
With a big mouth like this.
Like this.
From the first to the fifth person.
How many people are wearing a katsura?
Please take a good look at me.
Everyone is here.
Let's start with Mr. Fuyuki.
Number 5.
I don't think the first person is the same.
What about you?
I don't think the second person is the same.
I don't know.
Number 5 for now.
Mr. Kongo.
Number 3.
Why?
It looks like a thick and small hair.
It feels like a mixture of a beard and a katsura.
I see.
Number 3 in that sense.
Zura Miyaburiman.
Number 5.
The same as Mr. Fuyuki.
Yes.
Why?
I don't think he has hair all over his body.
Don't say stupid things.
Let's see the correct answer.
Number 3.
Amazing.
Mr. Kongo is correct.
I thought he didn't have a hard hair.
I see.
It's true.
Other people have natural hair, but he has a little bit of hair.
So I think he has a lot of hair.
His face changes when he takes it off.
His face changes.
He has about 20 hairs.
Mr. Kongo, please take it off.
The shape is different.
What if I break it?
It won't grow back.
What?
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello, hello.
This hall is too close.
I don't like it.
It's always too high.
Punishment.
It's not funny.
It's always like this.
What you said, what I said, and what you sent me.
I put them all together.
But let's make a net.
I think so.
Yes.
Please take it out.
We'll talk about it later.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Let's start with this side.
I drew it.
It's pretty rough, isn't it?
What does it say?
Kangaroo?
Kangaroo and boxing.
It's scary to lose.
It's like a comedy that killed a kangaroo.
It's going to be hard in the future, isn't it?
I killed it.
Even if you scream like this,
that person killed a kangaroo.
That's right.
It's going to be hard, isn't it?
This is what I want to avoid the most.
What is this?
Bunchin?
This is Katsura Bunchin.
San?
Yes.
I'm going to use it a lot and play with it.
I came up with this.
What are you going to do?
For example?
I think the New Year's Day is coming soon.
We're shooting a New Year's show now.
Yes.
There's a happy New Year's Day.
With a big brush.
You have to shoot from above.
If the paper moves, I'll have you sit down.
Bone Bunchin?
Yes.
It's the same.
Semi-nude?
Semi-nude.
This is interesting.
If you lose...
Goroh.
Playboy.
Scora.
Semi-nude.
I asked a famous photographer to take a picture of me.
How much of a semi-nude are you?
I hide my front.
I don't show my butt.
Semi-nude.
How about this?
It's good.
Chimpanzee chop.
This is stupid.
If you lose, I'll chop you into a chimpanzee.
I don't know what this is.
What is this?
This?
This is difficult.
What?
Kiyoshi.
Sanshi.
Sanshi-san.
Sanshi or Kiyoshi?
Kiyoshi-san or Sanshi-san.
This is...
Stop it!
It's obvious.
This!
Sorry, I don't know what this is.
What is it?
What is this?
Katsura Sanshi Shisho.
Katsura Sanshi Shisho's...
Who are you?
This is just a simple chimpanzee chop.
I don't know what this is.
Kiyoshi Sanshi.
What is this?
Kiyoshi Shisho, Sanshi Shisho.
Either one or the other.
Let's play a prank.
I see.
This is fun.
In Sanshi Shisho's case, he goes into Sanshi Shisho's dressing room.
He goes in before Shisho comes?
Yes.
He is waiting in Katsura Sanshi's dressing room.
When Katsura Sanshi comes in, he says,
Welcome.
This is good.
In Kiyoshi's case...
He goes to his house.
In Yasu-san's dressing room, he says,
Let's get back together.
This is fun.
This is either one or the other.
But it's really scary.
That's right.
Bungee jumping.
This is just like that.
If you lose, you do it.
Yes.
Silicone.
You don't put silicone in your chest.
If you lose.
You become a very good father.
It's okay to have a comedian like this.
What is it like to fight in Spain?
It's not that simple. It's the sense of fear.
What?
It's not that simple.
You know what I mean.
Yes.
It's not like a fun fight.
Can you do it like Yuki-chan?
That would be nice.
If you come.
Like Albus.
I know.
Isn't that a goat?
It's Tōgyū!
You know, those guys...
They can't just pop out like that!
You have to lift them up, right?
They have to do it like this!
I know that!
It's like before their debut.
Even if it's a penalty game, it's a bit cruel.
If it wasn't for scary guys, I'd be doing bungee jumping.
You're doing it like this!
As expected...
It's you!
It's me, huh?
What's wrong with you?
It's like that.
It's Tōgyū from Spain.
Are you scared of the chimpanzee top?
I'm not scared!
It's just a monkey.
Are you stupid?
The monkey's claws are amazing.
It's like this.
They can't just do it like this.
You have to lift them up.
I'm the monkey!
I don't know what you're thinking.
It's okay!
I'm...
Oh, what an creepy...
It can be anywhere!
It's...
It's maybe inside this box?
You should do it around that effect!
ases!
You must be so stupid!
In the morning, you should've written down your bites.
There's no time!
Don't make fun of me!
It's okay!
It was really funny!
I know, so I'll choose one
Anywhere?
Let's start from here
Please choose one
Where should I choose?
Anywhere?
Really?
Then...
Stop it, you idiot!
I feel like you're going to do that too
But wait, why am I doing this?
So I'm the one who should do it?
I feel like I'm the one who should do it
If I lose, I'll do it too
But I'll leave it to you
Here
What?
Ah, I see
What is this?
I thought I'd leave it to you
What do you mean?
This or that
You can't do that
What?
Here
There's only one mark
Mark?
What are you talking about?
Are you kidding me?
So here
Here
Can I draw a line?
Sure
Then
Here
I drew a line
But it went back
It's meaningless
Right?
Here
Let's start
Dandara dandara dandara dandara dandara
You can take it
I have to take it
What should I do from here?
Are you going to put your arm in here?
I was looking forward to it
So I thought I'd draw a small line
from here
Take it
Okay
Alright
Dandara dandara dandara dandara dandara
Don't be a fool
Dandara dandara dandara dandara
So that's it
I'll play that penalty game
I think so. Next week, next week, I think I'll get a clear shot on the back of the net.
Let's do our best.
By the way, that's a big difference.
It's a golf rule.
Can you tell me about it?
Can you lower it a little bit?
The golf rule, right?
Yes.
I'll do five holes.
I'll do five holes,
and the one before that, three holes.
I'll win.
And then?
Yes.
I've prepared a professional for you.
I'll do it.
Is that okay?
Yes.
A professional.
A famous professional that anyone can see.
Professional.
Something like that.
Even if it's a professional, it's really a golf professional.
Of course.
What's the point of calling a professional?
Even if it's a professional, it's like Ajacomb.
Who would call you?
No one would call me.
That's no good.
Why?
It's like I did something dirty.
I don't like that.
What would you call me?
Ojiya.
Oh, okay.
There are people who are good at calling themselves Ojiya.
There are people who are good at calling themselves Ojiya,
but there are people who have never called themselves Ojiya.
That's not enough.
Why?
I've never done it before, so I don't know if I'm an old man or an old woman.
I'll write it down.
Seriously?
Okay, I'm sorry.
I'll write it down.
I'll put my finger in here.
This person is good at music and sports.
He likes watching videos.
What kind of videos do you watch?
I didn't say anything bad.
I didn't attack you.
What did you do?
What kind of videos do you watch?
The ones that make you cry.
Oh, the ones that make you cry.
I don't think it's that bad.
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
That's right.
Why are you bringing this home?
I'll introduce the postcards.
This person,
Hamada-san, Matsumoto-san, good evening.
This person is a female singer.
I always enjoy watching her.
I've thought about the fourth punishment game, so please listen to it.
In the previous punishment game, Hamada-san used her body.
Matsumoto-san was very embarrassed.
So this time, using your brain,
how about taking a college entrance exam?
This is going to be hard.
I thought about it for a moment.
College entrance exam,
it depends on which university.
I'm pretty good at it.
No, I'm serious.
I went to a high school.
I only got bad grades.
That's not true.
Hyogo is a prefecture.
Prefecture is just a name.
I only got bad grades.
That's not true.
I went to an elite high school.
I was smoking in class.
That's not true.
The teacher was smoking in class.
I thought I shouldn't smoke in a place like this.
It's like a school's military district identification card.
At this point,
it's finally time to play golf.
The punishment game has already been decided.
That's right.
If you lose, go to your boyfriend's place.
That's the rule, isn't it?
What?
The rule is...
The staff said I should wear a umekichi.
Who is that umekichi?
It's an old lady I brought home from the billiards.
Where is the umekichi?
What?
Umekichi is at my house.
Is it at your house?
Yes.
In Tokyo?
Really?
It's in the parking lot.
Why is it in the parking lot?
Also,
anyone who watches this program,
anyone is fine.
Anyone who is a fan of this program.
A celebrity?
A celebrity has a wide range.
There are AV actresses.
Also,
anyone who watches this program,
anyone who is a fan of this program,
please write to me.
Anyone who has been on a TV program.
No way.
That's a celebrity.
That's right.
That's what I'm saying.
A TV program.
Please write to me.
I don't know what to do.
Investigate?
Investigate.
Maybe you can help me with something.
So,
see you next week.
Goodbye.
It's finally time to write.