After this, I'll go to downtown to buy a kid's toy.
I spent a lot of money.
I've been waiting for a long time.
From now on, we will open the downtown dinner show.
Please enjoy the wonderful dinner.
Welcome.
It's been a long time since we had a dinner show.
I'm very nervous now.
I wonder if I can sing well.
Hama came from Hiroshima 10 years ago.
He came here somehow.
I did it.
I think it's because Hama was there.
What are you talking about, Machan?
Let's listen to the first song.
Please listen to the rain from Aki Yashiro's number.
The person who forgot Corona remembers the weight of his knees.
The long moon-lit lap of his knees was smoking.
I hate you. I miss you. I hate you. I miss you.
The person who forgot Corona remembers the weight of his knees.
Thank you very much.
I really like Aki Yashiro's song.
I sing it every time.
I talked too much.
Let's move on to the next song.
Please listen to the rain from Mori Masako's number.
Don't waste your daughter.
The person who turns his back on Shigure at the inn.
Thank you very much.
We sing this song every time.
Let's move on to the next song.
Please listen to the rain from Mori Masako's number.
The person who turns his back on Shigure at the inn.
Thank you very much.
We look forward to seeing you again next year.
The person who turns his back on Shigure at the inn.