From now on, we will begin the 4th trial of Heipou Fusuppera.
All members of the court, please enter the courtroom.
You don't have to be so angry.
You're in a neutral position.
The next defendant, Heipou, please enter the courtroom.
The defendant, Heipou.
Although he is a child abuser, he was accused of lying, being irresponsible, and cheating.
He was accused of many crimes, and he was sentenced to 3 years in prison.
He was sentenced to 3 years in prison.
However, he is still accused of lying, and he is causing a lot of trouble to the people.
Therefore, the 4th trial of Heipou Fusuppera is about to begin.
I'm Ryo.
To be honest, I'm surprised to hear this.
Prosecutor Hamada, please present the evidence.
Just like the other trials, we have a list of Heipou's crimes.
Everyone, please take a look at this.
This is when he went golfing as a child abuser.
Heipou men!
Nice shot!
Nice shot, Heipou! You're doing great today!
Right?
Fresh Heipou!
Hey, hey, hey, Heipou!
Golfing is fun, isn't it?
Heipou was in a great mood, and he finished the half.
I'm hungry.
Let's eat.
But I'm going to the bathroom, so please go ahead.
A few minutes later, Heipou comes back from the bathroom.
I feel so much better. Did you all order?
Yeah, only Heipou left.
What did you all order?
I ordered curry rice.
I ordered tonkatsu.
I ordered a sandwich.
And then...
You guys are so stupid!
Look at that!
It's Tororo soba!
Tororo soba!
That's right. This place is famous for Tororo soba.
You guys are so stupid not to eat Tororo soba here.
If you want to be the best man, you have to eat the best food.
Excuse me!
Can I have a Tororo soba, please?
A few minutes later...
Let's eat!
Oh, but this curry is really good.
No, no. My Tororo soba is the best. It's really good.
After a satisfying meal...
Thank you for the meal.
Oh, I ate. I ate.
Now the second half is perfect.
Then let's go to the second half.
And then...
Hey, Heipou, what's this?
You left something.
Oh, yes, yes.
This is Tororo soba.
Oh, I forgot to put Tororo soba in it.
What?
Heipou didn't put Tororo soba in Tororo soba.
He ate normal soba.
Heipou's second half was a mess.
Here's your obi.
That soba is dangerous.
Judge, I'd like you to testify in this case.
Everyone, of course you know.
Yes, I've seen it.
I'm Prosecutor Suga.
Yes, I know.
I'm a witness.
That's already a fact?
Yes.
You know, you can easily eat curry.
And I wasn't that hungry.
So the moment I ate curry, I was really hungry.
So I was told, you shouldn't have done that as a director.
That's what I was told.
You can't even eat one thing.
You have to eat the best of the best.
That's what being a director is all about.
I see.
So that's what happened.
So he ordered Tororo soba?
Yes.
So Tororo is the best?
That's right.
What does Tororo mean?
But you can eat the best of the best, right?
You have to eat the best of the best.
I know you can eat the best of the best.
Can I eat it?
The soba was really good.
I heard it was the best.
If it was good, that's enough.
So you put the soba in the soup and ate it?
Yes.
Was there Tororo next to it?
There was.
I forgot.
You didn't forget, did you?
Which way do you want to go?
Your character setting is wrong.
This is one of the many taxi accidents that happened to Heipo.
Taxi! Taxi!
Here we go!
Go ahead!
Hi, I'm Heipo from the world.
Driver, can you take me to Heipo?
I'm sorry, but I'm a newbie and I don't know much about roads.
It doesn't matter.
I know all the roads in Tokyo.
And then the taxi left in that car.
Listen to me.
What's wrong?
The other day, I got hit by a car.
That was amazing.
Excuse me, can I go straight on this road?
Yes, go straight.
Okay.
What's wrong, Saito?
I got in the way, so I'll tell you from the beginning.
The other day, I got hit by a car.
That was amazing.
Excuse me, can I go straight on this road?
Yes, go straight.
Okay.
What happened, Saito?
I'm really sorry.
I'll say it again.
The other day, I got hit by a car.
After that...
I'm sorry, sir.
Hey, you're so noisy.
Are you really a pro?
I've asked you so many times.
How can you eat like that?
It doesn't matter.
You can go on your own.
I'm a newbie driver.
A newbie driver who's completely lost it.
In the end, he was forced to pay for it.
Saito, help me!
I'll tell you the truth about this incident.
I know you.
I'm Nakamura.
This is the VTR.
When you enter a road that's different from usual,
you'll be like,
I don't want to pay for it.
If you're a pro, you have to work as a pro.
I have to pay at least once every three times.
That much?
That's amazing.
And...
Isn't that a little help?
No, no, no.
I've already paid for it.
No, it's hard.
Can I go to the bathroom right now?
There's still more.
You're just getting in the way of the conversation.
Why are you so angry?
I'm just talking to you.
How much of the conversation is true?
Of course it's true.
When I was drinking,
a woman suddenly appeared.
She asked me if I wanted to drink with her.
There's a lot.
There's a lot?
How often do you drink a year?
At least once a month.
It's true.
It's a lie.
He's telling the truth.
Don't lie to me.
You can't lie like that.
The woman called me later.
To be honest,
I've had a good relationship with her.
Every now and then.
Don't lie to me.
When the director gets angry,
I'm living in a hotel right now.
You're living in a hotel?
That's right.
Why?
That's why I'm living there.
That's right.
Why?
When the director gets angry,
I'm living in a hotel right now.
It's a lie.
I live in a hotel.
That's why I'm living in a hotel.
Who is it?
This is the story of the old time.
Nice to meet you.
Excuse me.
There's one more person, Heipou-san, the kid's servant, who's late.
Apparently, he's on his way here now, but he'll be here in a little while.
Eh? Could it be that Heipou-san?
That's right.
Amazing! Heipou-san's here!
Ah! I'm late again!
Heipou appears late.
Sorry for the wait.
He's really good at this kind of program.
That's for sure.
It's Heipou!
Yes, yes, yes. Everyone, isn't she really cute?
She's the perfect woman for me.
Well, for now, cheers!
Cheers!
Heipou-san is really busy with work, isn't he?
Yes, yes. That's right.
I'm really busy.
Thanks to you, I have a lot of money.
Wow, amazing! How wonderful!
What are you riding in your car?
Yes, yes. Of course, it's a red Porsche.
Yah! I want to ride it!
It's okay.
Apparently, she's a stewardess who's known for her money, and she's the perfect woman for Heipou.
Well, she's popular today, too.
Heipou is so into her sexy attacks.
Heipou-san is so cool. I want a Vuitton bag.
It's cheap. I can buy one or two Vuitton bags at any price.
Heipou-san, I love you!
Wow!
Heipou, who's so popular that he's become the center of attention, later made a date with her.
And a few days later, Heipou called to confirm the date.
Hello? Hello, this is Heipou from the world.
Oh, hello, Heipou-san. I've been waiting for you.
Tomorrow, let's meet at 6 o'clock and go buy a Vuitton bag.
Of course, after that, please keep it open.
Huh? Yes?
Tomorrow, I'm staying at the usual public hotel.
What? I'm sorry.
Tomorrow, my parents are coming and I'm going to stay at home, so I only have two hours to shop.
What are you talking about? Are you lying to me?
I promised to buy a Vuitton bag, but don't you know that it's an adult promise?
I'm going to buy something worth it, so I can't do it without merit.
I'll make it clear, but I won't buy it unless it's a bet.
Don't make it clear.
After that, he never met her again.
The bet is already decided, right?
I see.
Now, let's confirm this.
I know.
You know, right?
Now, Suimoto.
Yes.
By the way, why are you guys making such a concoction?
First of all, let me hear that.
Are you making a concoction?
I will make a concoction.
I will definitely make a concoction.
That means you didn't do it?
I didn't do it.
I'm going to buy it for you anyway, so it's the same if it's a bet, right?
You can go buy it after you do it.
Why are there so many?
I'm going to buy it for you.
I'm going to give you a present and put it in the bed.
Don't say that.
Thank you.
Other than this, is there anything else?
I used to lie a lot when I was in a motel.
Like a Porsche?
Yes.
I used to lie a lot when I was in a motel.
Why are you making a concoction?
I have enough money to buy it, so it's the same if it's a bet, right?
No, it's not.
It's a concoction.
It's the same.
I have enough money to buy it, so it's the same if it's a bet, right?
I used to go to a musical party.
At that time, a thief came into my house.
A thief came into your house?
Yes.
A thief came into my house.
There's a VTR.
If you watch it, you'll understand.
Let's watch it.
I really want to go to a wedding.
Recently, it's a personal matter.
What are you talking about?
There's something unhappy going on.
What is it?
Actually, I haven't told anyone recently.
Two or three days ago, I was in my apartment.
Really?
Yes.
Luckily, I put my passbook in the back.
But I couldn't get it.
It was okay, but the glass was broken.
I'll tell you what I found out later.
Actually, there was no thief in the police officer's room.
What?
What do you mean?
You said that just now.
That's right.
He said it was in his room.
He said it was broken.
That's right.
So, both of them entered my next room.
But it's natural that they entered it mentally.
It's natural that they entered it mentally.
What's the meaning of this?
This is the incident that happened at the end of last year when Heipo was in charge of the general production.
On that day, an emergency meeting was held, and the staff suddenly called Heipo.
Mr. Saito, actually, I have an emergency meeting tonight.
What?
Good evening.
Actually, I'm going to give a speech at the debate show today.
Mr. Saito, please.
The staff asked him to attend the meeting.
But Heipo...
I only have one body.
Please hold the meeting first.
When the meeting is over, I'll go check it out.
Heipo refused to attend the meeting and hung up on the phone.
And that night...
It's hot pot.
Heipo was in a good mood before his favorite hot pot.
Mr. Atsushi and Mr. Ryo, please.
Mr. Heipo, thank you for the past year.
What are you talking about?
Aren't you in a debate show with me?
Let's have fun today.
On the other hand, the meeting was full of ideas.
And two hours later...
The staff still had no idea.
It's almost time for Mr. Saito's speech.
Yeah, let's call him.
The staff contacted an acquaintance to catch Heipo.
Hello?
I'm looking for Mr. Saito right now.
Mr. Saito? He went to a mahjong match with Ryo.
Mahjong?
After the party, Heipo went to a mahjong match with Ryo.
Ryo!
I'm Ryo from London Bulls.
To be honest, I'm surprised to hear that.
I didn't know it was going to be like that.
I'm sorry.
Ryo didn't know.
But I remember it clearly.
I want to tell you the truth.
There was a year-end party.
At the end, Heipo invited me to a mahjong match.
The party ended early.
So I asked him if he had work to do.
He said he was fine.
I really remember that.
So I went to a mahjong match.
I won by myself.
It rained a few times on the way.
I asked him if he had work to do.
He said he was fine.
Please take care of him.
The party ended early.
Why don't you go to the meeting?
I wanted to play mahjong.
What?
His face when he said it was true made me angry.
It made me angry.
We will announce the verdict.
It is hard to believe that Heipo is a liar.
He has caused a lot of trouble to many people.
There is no room for excuses.
The verdict will be the punishment of a horror movie.
He will never appear in front of us again.
I don't want to do it anymore.
Why are you so cool?
I'm scared.
This is scary.
It's scary.
There are a lot of scary scenes.
Is this a shooting room?
Alone.
It's scary.
I'm scared.
I don't want to do it anymore.
The child doesn't understand this.
Please let me go.
I don't want to do it anymore.
What is it?
I'm scared.
I don't want to take it out!
I'm surprised!
I'm scared!
Please do it!
I don't want to take it out!
He's 5 years old.
Everyone else is going to see it.
What is it?
I can't stand it.
I don't want to take it out!
I'm scared!
It's over.
Turn on the lights.
I don't want to take it out!
Please do it!
What do you think, Yamaguchi-san?
I don't know how to say it.
I think it's a punishment.
I think it's the same as the viewers.
When I see that punishment, I get angry.
You want to do it more, right?
More!
Please do it!