In the fall of 1995, Gaki no Tsukai was broadcasted 299 times from the start.
Therefore, this week is the 300th anniversary of Gaki no Tsukai.
1990, the start of the program.
Many opening programs have been deepened by inviting various famous entertainers.
The appearance of Kin-chan's virtual grand prize, the punishment game, and many other memories have been engraved.
In 1991, the program received a huge response and broadcasted day and night from late at night.
In 1992, the famous So-chan-ka Grand Prix was born this year and became a hot topic.
In 1993, the program reached a viewing rate of 20%.
In 1993, the program reached a viewing rate of 20% and had a fun time with many people.
And from 1994, let's start today's Kouyuu-roku.
The fourth episode of Gaki no Tsukai, Tsuki-tsuki, Guts-tataiten, how many points will it get?
The entertainer who was invited as a talk show, how many points will it get?
They were two people who were very nervous about the former world champion, Guts Ishimatsu-san.
What are you doing?
We've met quite a long time ago.
Do you remember, Gaku-san?
Yes, I do.
Why?
What kind of arm is that?
I think it was about 10 years ago.
We had an interview once.
Arm wrestling.
Arm wrestling?
That's good.
You have a big arm.
Excuse me.
It was Guts Ishimatsu-san. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
The eighth episode of Gaki no Tsukai, Tsuki-tsuki, entertainer, Omae So-chan or Grand Prix?
In the popular show, Omae So-chan or Grand Prix, we have invited such a rare guest.
Come on out! Ota-san! Ota-san!
Come on out, Marina Watanabe-san!
Have you ever been caught at a traffic inspection?
Ah, it's a girl? So it's only for girls?
Eh, that's right!
What do you mean I'm Tama's running guy?
I get it
Next is this!
You're a minor!
You're only in elementary school!
Next is this!
You eat 8 meals a day!
You're only in elementary school!
Don't say it like that!
When I write it, it seems like I'm writing something bad
What's wrong? What's wrong?
You're Tama's running guy?
Tama's running guy is really bad!
Next is Mako-chan!
Surprisingly, there are a lot of people like this
What's good about it?
You're a minor!
Ah, I don't know about that
Marina!
No, I really, as an image...
As an image, I say, I'll go to your place
You can't say that!
Now, Matsumoto-san
I don't know your name, but
Yes
You're the weirdo of the Comedian Club
Hikari Ijuin from Wato
Matsumura Kunihiro
Yamata Kuniko
Matsumura
Matsumura Kunihiro
Yamata Kuniko-san
Ah, wait a minute!
You're pretty good at English
I'm sorry to bother you today
No problem
Today, Tama's running...
I heard that you've been studying for a long time
I've already studied
I came here on purpose
And we co-starred with Tama's running
You've seen a lot of things
He's a rare creature
That's right
Oops, I took the book
He's moving fast from here
First of all, the internal organs
The internal organs are all out
What are you looking at?
Are you looking at Gaten?
Gaten?
Huh?
It's Gaten
What kind of magazine is Gaten?
Gaten is a work magazine
It's a work magazine
That's bad
He's trying to get rid of Tama
Regarding this magazine
I don't show the erotic part at all
That's scary
I'll show you the erotic part
Excuse me
Thank you for waiting
It's unnatural for a woman to be angry
It's amazing
He's laughing
And with the world's Ryuichi Sakamoto
This kind of project
I'm the world's Sakamoto
I'm sorry
Who are you?
Why are you here?
I'm the world's Sakamoto
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry
I'm a man without a reason
But
Even if it's hot in summer
I can't lose to summer
This is a great opponent
To prevent summer
I have to say something useful
Say something useful?
Matsumoto-kun, do you have something useful?
Leave it to me
Something useful?
Yes
You have a serogun, don't you?
I have a medical license
Shut up
You've been doing this for 1000 years
But
I think it's good to have a serogun
You have to move your body in summer
Even if I move my body, I can't lose to summer
Matsumoto-kun, what kind of sports do you do in summer?
I've been thinking about this
What have you been doing?
I've been talking
Skiing
Skiing?
Skiing is good
Let's dive together
Let's dive
Let's go
One, two
Feels good
What do you do when you talk?
You can't talk
You can't talk?
You can't talk in the water
Ah, I see
In that case
You have to give a signal like this
You have to go up and talk
That's annoying
It can't be helped
Ah, I see
Let's go again
What happened?
The video I took a long time ago looked good
You're annoying
And he also got to know a lot of youkai living in the entertainment world
First of all, you can't see youkai
Today, youkai
It's said that there are a lot of youkai that have disappeared
The youkai that live in Japan now
Youkai
There are 5.6 million
That's a lot
Are you everywhere?
I'm walking around
That's not funny
What is that?
Look at that
What is that in the middle?
Hey, come on
Come on
What is that?
Is this youkai?
This is youkai
Don't come too close
What is that?
Youkai cat girl
This is funny
It's funny
Try to hit it
What is this?
I'm scared
There's something
What is this?
What is that?
It's my bag
What is this?
Youkai cat girl
Get the water from the other side
This is not good
Come here
What is this?
It's not sliding
This is not good
What is this?
Hey
Yes
Sing a song
Please
It's youkai
Yes
Youkai
What youkai
What's wrong?
What?
It's youkai
Why are you so nervous?
I'm not nervous
You're nervous because you're shining
You bastard
If you hug me, it's over
If you hug me, you won't say anything interesting
Clear
I'm a little fatter
You're noisy
He's familiar with Chi-Chi
He has a deep relationship with her in private
Good evening
Oh
What?
Chi-Chi
What is it?
It's Chi-Chi's otaku
You're so cheeky
It's a great house
It's not
Hello
Are you his wife?
What are you doing?
Thank you
Ma'am, this is a little boring
What are you doing?
I'm sorry
Please sit down
Excuse me
I'd like to have a special sushi
Please sit down
Do you really do that?
Thank you
You don't have to do anything
What is it?
Since you're here
I'd like to help you
That's right
Plus
We can only think about others
I've helped you a lot
Yes
What are you doing?
Today
I'd like you to lend me some money
Since it's a new house
I'd like to check the power
Why do you want to check the power?
Downtown means checking the power
Originally
I see
When you use a vacuum cleaner
You use a lot of electricity
I'm tired
You're tired
I'll give you a massage
Why do you look so sad?
Chiichi
What is it?
I'm doing nothing
I'm checking the power
I'm doing it for you
I'll put on a dryer
Let's put on a dryer
The power is okay
Let's go to the microwave
Switch on
This is pretty
I've been waiting for you
Thank you
Today
I'd like you to help me
I'd like you to see a lot of things
For his friends
He will cook for them
It's a warm-hearted project
Hey
Stop
What kind of mind play is this?
It's boiling
This is good
The fish is melting
Wait a minute
How is it?
It's crispy
It tastes like Koya
Okay
This is good
This is expensive
I'll put this
Stop
Okay
Wait a minute
What is this?
It's like an art
It's like a teacher's self-made dish
Are you going to eat this?
Please eat it
I'm doing something useless
After the commercial
Wada Akiko and Ume Miya Tatsuo have a good time
And the host of the entertainment world
Wada Akiko and Ume Miya Tatsuo
To clear up the suspicion
This kind of project
Wada Akiko and Ume Miya Tatsuo
The defendant, please come in
Wada Akiko has started the trial of a man
After the trial
I'd like to ask Professor Matsumoto to come in
And I'd like to verify a lot of things
Professor, please come in
Nice to meet you
I'd like to take a picture of evidence
Wada, look at this
I'm going to take off your monster face today
Let's take a look
This is the picture of the pilot Wada
If you look at it like this
It's not much different from the picture we usually see
That's right
And using a computer
I tried to get closer
You were closer
Yes, I was
Then I found out a terrible truth
You bastard
I knew it
I got a great video
Is that so?
If you look at this
It's going to be a big decision
Understood
I think it was last year when I was crying
I was a little drunk
My wife took me to the hospital
I was also diagnosed three or four times
But the real Wada was more manly than I saw on TV
I can go home at least three times
It's already decided
It's decided
Excuse me
Is that a woman?
That's a woman
It's a woman again, you bastard
First of all, I would like you to see the proof photo
Please take it out
This is funny
Yes
Is this before the show?
I'm wearing this
You're still wearing it
Next
We have a video
This is
Umeda station
This is the doll in front of us
This is the 10th floor
Is that a doll?
Next
This is a doll
This is a doll that looks exactly like Tatsu Umemiya
That's right
That means
This is a replica
We saw that this is a doll
Please bring the proof photo
Is that so?
This is it
Everyone, if you pass by a Harajuku store, please take a picture
Like this
D Haisho
Masabuchi
Also today
From Robin Hood
The famous Thai actor
This is a story
So today we're going to test it out.
Professor, Sumi is here!
Sit down, Sumi!
Professor, is this the machine?
This is the machine. Let's take a look.
Baseball is a pitcher, but at night it's a batter.
It's out!
It's already out?
Professor, what's going on here?
What's this?
This is my meal today.
Who's your meal?
You're making me sick!
Sit down!
The results are out!
The results are out?
Okay!
The results are out!
But the meter is moving!
What is that thing in the east?
It's huge!
It's nice!
It's creepy!
Isn't this Nausicaa in the wind valley?
It's coming out!
What kind of show is this?
What's going on here?
It's white!
What are you guys doing?
The first episode of the Gaki no Tsukai Arahenji, Chikitsuki!
Sokessan in 1994, the natural botanist grand prize!
In 1994, there were people like this who can't be missed in variety shows.
This is the judge, Mr. Matsumoto.
I'm the judge.
That's right.
What is it today?
Well, I don't know.
I'm sorry, I don't really know.
I'm the judge.
For the time being, it's a very easy-to-understand project that we're going to decide on the best natural botanist of the year.
I see.
Let's introduce the three nominees.
Yamasaki Hosei.
And next to him is Kouda Shin.
Nice to meet you.
And last but not least, Tetsu-chan from Dega.
Nice to meet you, Dega.
Sokkyo Utagassen!
Japan Passing.
Come on!
Dega-san!
You're fast, Dega!
Go ahead!
Ah, Japan Passing!
You're Japan Passing!
How are you going to live in this cramped city?
What do you want to do?
Are you okay?
When I was in 3rd grade, you were in 1st grade.
That was in 11th grade.