In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai, Chikichiki!
Suga Presents!
Buy it, buy it, win it all!
Arashi's Over the Top!
The four of us will form a team.
We'll face the general public.
Let's fight with our bare hands!
And then!
Within one hour of the time limit,
we'll win 10 games in a row!
If the five of us win two games in a row,
the prize money from Producer Suga will be...
100 million yen!
Amazing!
Thank you very much.
Who do you think will be the strongest out of the five?
This is out of the question.
I don't think so.
But we don't know who will win.
Maybe it'll be a girl or a boy, right?
If it's a girl or a boy, I'll go all out!
What is this?
All out?
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Let's decide the order!
The order decided by rock-paper-scissors is this!
Matsumoto vs. Hamada vs. Endo vs. Tanaka vs. Yamasaki!
Thank you very much!
It won't continue, right?
Not at all.
Now, we have a Japanese TV announcer,
announcer Terashima.
Hello!
Hello, I'm Terashima.
I'm in a neighborhood near your house.
I'm in a alley that's one step away from the main street.
From here, you have to find the target you've chosen.
The next person to enter the alley is Matsumoto.
The next person to enter the alley is me.
The first person to enter the alley is...
Is this the alley?
I'll be waiting for you.
The alley is out.
This is the mother who went out.
The first person to enter the alley is...
Is Moka here?
Moka is here.
This is bad!
This is a Japanese TV announcer.
This is a little...
I'm playing a game on a TV program.
I have a little time left.
I'd like to ask for your cooperation.
I'll be done in about five minutes.
Is that okay?
This person is okay, right?
Let's go!
The first person to enter the alley is Matsumoto's employee, Akira Kuwata.
Which one do you want?
I'm right-handed.
I don't care.
Let's go!
I'm right-handed.
Hold this here.
I can win with this feeling.
I don't know.
Ready...
Go!
Okay!
I won!
I still have one more win.
You did it!
You have to win at least one round.
Yes.
What?
I can't do the second round.
It hurts so much.
I can't do three or four rounds like this.
I can't do it.
You're going to lose.
I'm next, right?
Yes.
Let's go.
The next person to enter the alley is a girl.
The second person to enter the alley is Nakayami Hota.
Yamazaki is dangerous.
I'm not dangerous.
I'm a man.
Yamazaki looks dangerous.
I'm not dangerous.
I can't do it anymore.
Yamazaki, do you want to enter the alley?
Do you want to enter the alley?
Let's do that.
Let's choose between Yamazaki and Hamada.
Which one do you think you can win?
Me or Yamazaki?
I won!
Yamazaki suddenly changes from Hamada to Hamada.
One, two, three, go!
What?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
His legs are floating!
Damn it.
Hey!
Damn it!
What's with you?
Why are you doing that?
You're not a king at all.
I'm not a king.
This is bad.
Did you win?
I won, but...
Alright!
Two wins!
Well, well...
Hey, are you serious?
Terashima!
Yes.
Bring the next one in.
The next one in, right?
The opponent of the three consecutive wins is Toshio Yaragiya, a company employee.
This is interesting.
Well, well, well.
But, you know...
I didn't have that much of a heartache.
Don't say that!
Just shut up!
I'll give you some advice!
Ready...
Go!
I'm counting on you!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Damn it!
That was...
That was crazy!
Damn it!
You only have 36 minutes left.
36 minutes?
Oh, really?
You can't lose anymore.
Alright, alright.
I won't let you win.
Alright.
The first round begins with a losing streak.
Okado Yujiyo is 60 years old.
Ready...
Go!
I'm counting on you!
Damn it!
You're a 60-year-old dad!
I can't lose!
Alright.
Then let's do two rounds with your dad.
Next up is the high school girl, Fukushima Marisa.
Ready...
Go!
Oh!
Kenta, you're strong!
That was close!
Damn it!
You were trying to do it like Hamada-san.
He was pushing you a lot.
Yeah, he was pushing me a lot.
Seriously.
That was close.
The opponent of Yamasaki after the third round is the young student, Nakahara Takeo-san.
Ready...
Go!
Stop it!
It floated again!
Damn it!
Alright!
But from here on, Endo wins the match.
And Kanaka wins the match.
And Hamada wins the match.
That was the third round.
Next, Matsumoto challenges for the fourth round.
Let's do our best next time.
It's my first time.
It's my first time winning the fourth round.
That's true.
The opponent of Matsumoto is the Karate student, Sato Tanahashi-san.
I used to do Karate when I was in 11th grade.
Seriously?
Yeah.
That's not even close.
But it's 8-9.
8-9?
You don't know how dark it is.
It's cute.
It's 8-9.
What is this?
I failed.
I got it right when you
tried fired me.
It's alright.
The fifth win, fifth win.
He managed to get the victory!
The second birdie, Endo vs. Kodama!
The next birdie, Tanaka vs. Takuha Ikuzaya!
Tanaka won with his guts!
And Hamada won against a 70-year-old old man!
This is a great victory!
Now, the prize of 300,000 yen is in the hands of Matsumoto!
Let's just say this is it!
It's the last one!
Let's win!
It's the challenger who spent the last 300,000 yen!
Don't do that! Don't do that!
Don't do that!
He said it's okay!
He won!
The final birdie, Matsumoto vs. Roger Smith!
What is this?
Who wrote this?
The person who wrote it.
What is this?
Do your best!
Think about it!
Ready, go!
He's laughing!
That's not cool!
What is this?
Defeat him already!
This is a living hell!
Think about it!
If you can't do it, do it quickly!
You're embarrassing me!
The final birdie, Matsumoto vs. Roger Smith!
This is...
This is strange!
Everyone is useless!
Thank you!
This kind of mission is useless!
The final birdie, Matsumoto vs. Roger Smith!
I don't know if you're doing well today.
I'm doing well!
Really?
I was listening behind your back.
What's wrong?
You were doing it with a blue face.
I'm not looking at your face.
It's okay to smile, but a smiley face is ugly.
Everyone is like that.
A smiley face?
It's ugly, right?
It's not ugly.
You're dirty!
Are you stupid?
Turn off the camera.
It's not good at all.
I don't know about today.
I'm starting to hate it.
Why?
I happened to watch the on-air last week.
I talked to Yoko-san yesterday.
Last week too.
We talked for almost an hour.
There's no on-air for 10 minutes.
It's okay today.
Today's opening is not that long, right?
That's right.
In terms of time.
It's just right.
I see.
But I'm not in the mood to talk.
I don't know if this was on-air.
I haven't checked the on-air.
I don't know.
There's a cockroach in my house.
You knew, didn't you?
Since then, I've been in perfect shape.
I can go anytime.
I've never seen a cockroach since then.
I don't know why.
I dreamt...
A big cockroach appeared.
It was about two meters long.
He said, you said that to me on TV, didn't you?
I see.
I was really scared.
That's scary.
It's really scary, isn't it?
When I said yes, I thought I might get hit, so I said no.
He said, don't say it too much.
I forgot how many times I said it.
I said, don't say it too much.
After that, he stopped breathing.
I see.
What is this?
If there was one, there should be a lot, right?
There should be a lot, but I think that's what happened that night.
That's what happened?
No, no, no.
That's why I said, it's okay.
Matsumoto, it's okay.
Matsumoto, you can play in the kitchen.
What is this?
Why do you want it?
No, it doesn't make sense.
I think that's what happened.
Stop it!
No, it's not like that.
If it's funny, I'll laugh, but I don't know what you're talking about.
I see.
Wait a minute.
What?
It's not funny?
It's okay.
Even so, you shouldn't play it like that.
One button, one story, two buttons.
Don't underestimate me.
Well, there are a lot of things today.
What do you have now?
Is it soccer?
Soccer?
But I'm sorry, but I haven't watched the other day's show.
I don't really care about soccer.
I'm not really interested in it.
Besides, I don't like talented people who show off.
Talented people who show off.
I've been rooting for someone like that for a long time.
Have you ever said that you're a soccer player?
I've been saying it for a long time.
I've liked soccer for a long time, so I don't really care about people who say it.
Isn't it just people like that?
It's not just people like that.
Then who is it?
It's someone like that.
Is that so?
Wait, wait, wait.
It's hard to understand.
What is it?
It's someone like that.
Wait, wait, wait.
I don't really understand.
What is it?
It's someone like that.
Why do you have to say it out loud?
Don't say it out loud.
What is it?
It's someone like that.
But that's true.
There was a match on Sports Newspaper the other day.
It was a color match.
But that was an interview, right?
The press was watching it.
No, I don't think that's true.
It's because they were doing this with a megaphone.
They were looking at the TV.
Where did they take that photo?
That was an interview.
That's a lie.
They weren't doing it while watching soccer.
They were shooting it a few days ago.
So it was an interview.
It was an interview.
But it had nothing to do with soccer.
They were shooting it the day before the match.
But it was on the screen.
It wasn't on the TV.
It was only on the back of the TV.
Is that so?
Yes, it was definitely a magic trick.
I don't like that.
I don't like songs.
Everyone says they like soccer, right?
I've never seen an announcer say, I'm not interested.
But I'm sure there are announcers.
Even though there are announcers, everyone doesn't like soccer.
That's true.
Why do you say it like that?
It's like a hot meal.
Why is it so perfect for a hot meal?
That's good.
It's good if it's perfect.
That's right.
No one can be a keeper.
It's not a special skill or anything.
A special skill?
You can do it like this.
But if it comes...
If it comes straight, it's like this.
If it comes like this, it's like this.
It's like this.
I see.
Why is it like that?
What is that?
You can't take that.
Really?
If it's practice, people will understand.
How do you practice as a keeper?
You have to kick and take it.
If you don't, you can't practice.
But no matter how many steps you take, you can take what you can take.
You can't reach what you can't reach.
It can't be helped.
If there is a way to practice that you can do it easily, you can do it.
You can take what you can take, but you can't take what you can't take.
That's true.
You don't have to practice.
You can't do it even if you're an old man.
That's impossible.
Why?
Old men do it like this.
They have a lot of defense.
But old men have a lot of defense, but they're slow.
No, no.
They're fast.
If you say they're fast, they're slow.
If they're big, they'll be okay.
If they're big, they're slow.
What are you talking about?
They're big enough to reach the goal.
That's not true.
Are you serious?
I can't say that.
If you say they're big, they're big.
That's stupid.
You!
Osmo-san says that if you hold a baby, it will grow healthily.
If you hold a baby, how does it grow?
I say that a lot.
I say, hold me, hold me.
It's like the escape scene of Osmo-tori.
I see.
There's something like that.
Yes, yes.
I don't think this is a lie.
Is that so?
I've been drawn to Osmo-tori.
That's a different meaning.
Damn it!
I couldn't resist it.
I'll play with you.
Yes, yes.
Crying and laughing, crying and laughing.
I can't think of anything.
I can't laugh.
Yes.
I still have the answer to the question about holding a baby.
Stop it!
It was a normal answer.
The question is, Osmo-san, if you hold a baby, how does it grow?
It will get sick.
Why?
The other day, at Itao's wedding party, you beat up Hong Kong's son.
That's not true.
How many months has it been? Hong Kong's son.
He said, hey!
Hey!
Bang!
How many times do I have to do it?
When a man approaches, he immediately cries.
That's not true.
What's not true?
I heard a voice saying, poor thing.
That's not true.
What is it?
It's the same for everything.
Don't look at my part.
I want to say this.
What do you mean?
Certainly, in front of you, I hit Hong Kong's son's head.
But in front of you, I was doing the same thing to Hong Kong's son.
That's not true.
I can't go anywhere without being hugged.
Did he start to move?
That's not true.
He's not cute at all.
Even though he can't talk, he's not cute at all.
If he talks, he's even cuter.
That's not true.
At that age, he can't do anything.
Hey! Hey!
Even though he can't talk, he's not cute at all.
That's not true.
That's why I hit his shoulder.
Hey!
I'm scared of his face.
Bang!
That's why everyone is happy.
In the old days, there were three-step jumping and seven-step jumping.
I heard there were four more after hop, step, and jump.
Mr. Matsumoto, please tell us the remaining four steps.
Yes.
In the old days, the food was getting better and better, and the training was more expensive.
That's right.
Compared to the old days, I gained a lot of muscle strength.
When that happened, I had to do hop, step, and jump.
If I didn't do that, I would go too far.
So I decided to go to a meeting.
You went too far?
I decided to go to a public meeting.
A public meeting?
Well, I decided to go to a public meeting.
You went too far?
Yes.
I went to China and France.
I didn't go to China, but I decided to go to France.
You didn't say anything about Japan?
I didn't say anything about Japan.
It seems that I was brainwashed.
I didn't know about the seven-step jumping.
It's called Taisho-democracy.
The remaining four...
Where is my Taisho-democracy going?
What?
My Taisho-democracy...
I just said it, right?
Yes, yes.
You heard it, right?
Yes, I heard it.
Taisho-democracy, right?
Yes, yes.
I said it, right?
You should write something about it.
Something like a blanket.
Otherwise, it will be too soft.
You'll catch a cold.
No, it's okay.
I've already made a decision.
Well, you also mentioned that you had a headache before that.
Yes, I did.
That girl is also wearing a blanket.
It's very soft.
The next Taisho-democracy is also very soft.
Write something about it.
Yes, yes, I see.
Please.
Because my gags are catching a cold.
It means that it's cold.
It doesn't mean that it's cold.
It doesn't mean that it's cold!
Please.
It's okay.
Please tell me the remaining four.
I'll tell you the remaining four.
Okay, let's do it.
What? You're not going to do it?
Hop, step, jump.
Please.
Hop!
Step!
Jump!
Oh, it's, it's, it's.
Okay, let's do it.
Hop, step, jump.