Good evening
It's so cold
It's downtown's special
Thank you for coming
Can you see the view?
Where are we?
I'm in front of JR Amagasaki station
It's open
Yes it is
We are in New York
We are here to do something
They are going to give us a delicious tonkatsu
Let's go
Sakamoto Ryuichi is going to write a song for us
We are going to do a live
It's our debut
It's not downtown
Geisha girls
I'm Ken from Geisha girls
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
New York recording and live
Sakamoto Ryuichi is a huge fan of Gaki no Tsukai
And Matsumoto
He is going to write a song for Sakamoto
He is aiming for a big hit in America
Sakamoto Ryuichi Produce
Geisha girls
We went to the office where Sakamoto lives
We received a fax
Sakamoto is currently working on an album
But if they are going to come to New York, it's OK
Sakamoto has a lot of work to do
Will he have time to write a song?
Are you really going?
Is the song ready?
I don't know
I don't know if I'm a producer
This is the last
Matsumoto who hates overseas gave up
By the way, the office in New York
Sakamoto is working hard on his album
Is he thinking about downtown?
And finally they go to New York
12 hours to New York
Are they tired?
And downtown is in New York
Are you waiting for Ryuichi?
I'm going to the studio
They are going to the studio
It's still midnight in Tokyo
We are going to the studio
Let's check in, eat and sleep
No no
This is Broadway, the city where Sakamoto lives
You are cute
I don't know how to continue
I'm scared
What is this?
Everyone is unhappy
I'm not happy
I'm in the middle
There are so many people
Are they lined up?
Are they lined up to buy tickets?
The first time in New York
They look fresh
This is the studio where Sakamoto lives
Will they be able to meet for the first time in 4 months?
Are they really here?
They are dressed up as ballerinas
Is the song finished?
Hello
I'm here
Are you tired?
I'm a little tired
The world's Sakamoto Ryuichi was there
He opened the door of the techno pop era
He was a world star
He is also active in film music
He won the Academy Award in 1988
The world praised his talent
He appeared in Madonna's promotion video
He is a world-famous genius artist
Can I do it here?
Do you always do this?
It's a famous studio used by Whitney Houston and Madonna
I'm a disciple of Sakamoto
The staff that Sakamoto collected
He is the member of D-LITE
I will make it with these members
I'm making it
Shall we listen to it?
The song he was worried about was already finished
The song was almost finished
The song showed a perfect finish
I understand the high school students
You are lying
You were lying on your neck
It would be better to release this song
What should I say?
It was 4 seconds
What should I do with this?
Let's talk about it
One more song
He really made it
Sakamoto made another song for Downtown
Downtown
Downtown's high quality and serious expression
It's like a word
I came here to see you
You came to see me
You said you would make a song
I said it easily
Finally, the recording meeting will be held
It's like a comedy
It's a comedy
The idea of Sakamoto is to put a comedy in the intro
Downtown will be a comedy for the first time in a few years
I see
There are a lot of scary things these days
What are you talking about?
There are a lot of scary things in the news
It's not a comedy
It's a comedy
It's not funny
If you put 5 million yen in a green bag and put it in a yellow bag and put it in a red bag, I'll put it in a black bag
Do you understand?
Forever
It's really hard
It's the first time I've done it with this kind of tension
I worked as a professional
It's really hard
It's the first time I've talked with this kind of tension
Take me with you
Finally, check the recorded sound
I don't care
Hello
It has nothing to do with the music of this band
Cool
It was good at the end
I was waiting
Cool
I want to be more emotional
I'll be more emotional
I think it's a story where two people go up and down and two people go up and down
No way
I'll be more emotional
Two people go up and down
One time to cooperate with the best of the first song
I can't even dream of doing a normal comedy in a place like this
Come to New York
And then a short break
Hamada is tired after a long journey.
On the other hand, Matsumoto is...
In the meantime, Sakamoto is having a second meeting.
Downtown is...
I wish I could say something more.
I'm back.
It's okay.
Well, there was something.
I'm completely scared.
Is that so?
I can do it right away.
My legs...
I stepped on my legs.
I'm so sorry.
That's all I wanted to say.
The second recording begins.
First of all, the chorus of the chorus.
I got it.
Let's listen to it.
And this person also came to the studio.
What are you talking about?
It's true.
It's hard now.
We're talking to each other.
I came to see you.
The lyrics were written by Sakamoto.
It took them two hours to write it.
Osaka style rap.
You're talented, aren't you?
It's perfect.
I want to do more.
The lyrics were written by Sakamoto.
It took them two hours to write it.
Osaka style rap.
Tomorrow is the day of the debut live.
You did a great job.
Osaka style rap.
I have to do it again tomorrow.
The lyrics are too weak.
It took them two hours to write it.
Sakamoto is divided into two.
Please take a rest.
The recording is over in 12 hours.
The moment of the debut live is approaching.
The last night of singing and talking.
Downtown Binassho.
This project is very popular with the use of children.
Various activities are held to attract the audience.
This is a special event.
We invite famous entertainers who are active.
The top batter is Yoshichi Shimada.
The leader is Miyawasu.
Akechi's Matsuo and Rusher.
Haruichi and Tetsurou.
The most famous Japanese player is Kiyoshi.
Morikawa Shota.
Todoroki Ichiro.
Okure and Shoji.
And last but not least, Sakata.
They are entering the venue.
They are entering the venue with high expectations.
Everyone is a little nervous.
Cheers!
Downtown Binassho is about to begin.
Thank you for waiting for a long time.
The last night of singing and talking.
Downtown Special Binassho 94 is about to begin.
Everyone, please enjoy the wonderful dinner.
Thank you for waiting for a long time.
Good evening, everyone.
Downtown has been active for 13 years since its founding.
Today, we will enjoy singing and talking with them.
I'm Masumi Okada, the host.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'd like to present the great Japanese entertainers that they are.
Downtown on stage!
Hello, everyone.
Welcome.
Thank you very much for coming today.
Downtown Special Binassho is a dinner show.
Today, we will entertain the audience by laughing and acting.
It's a little different from usual, so I'm sure everyone is surprised.
Please listen to the first song.
Shama Kenjiro's No. 3, Streper!
Thank you very much.
I'm really happy to see everyone standing up.
It feels good.
But let's look back 13 years ago.
That's right.
About 13 years ago, we entered Yoshimoto in April 1957.
There were many songs.
I understand.
I'm going to eat a lot, so I'm going to eat a lot.
Everyone is saying this, so let's go to the second song.
That's right.
Please listen to the miso soup song.
Shama Kenjiro's No. 3, Streper!
Thank you very much.
There's steam coming out of the fish.
Today, we have a special guest for the 30th time.
We're the only ones who don't have a heart.
Today is a special guest.
Let's have this person appear.
It's Hino Mikasa.
Please let me go home a little more.
I won't go home tonight.
I don't want to go home.
Who's waiting in that room?
That's right.
No one's here right now.
It's winter rain outside.
It's a night to wet my heart.
I won't go home tonight.
I don't want to go home.
Yoshi!
Don'tоб
Don'tPlay
Don't Play
Shut up!
It's hot.
Take it easy.
It should be from now on.
Take a look at the window.
What is it?
Listen," I am a talk show.
I want to talk.
Take a good look.
My throat hurts.
I didn't expect everyone to be so happy.
Thank you very much.
It's like a zoo.
Our special guest is Ms. Hinomika.
I have a new song called Onna Nihonkai.
I'd like to promote it.
I really wanted to sing it, but I ended up like this.
Thank you very much.
When you're having fun, the next song is the last one.
I want to hear more.
I'll sing it with my fans.
Please come to the stage.
I was impressed.
The lyrics are very convincing.
Please come to the center.
It's a sad song.
Time has passed in an instant.
Thank you very much.
The last song is Inazuma.
Let's hear it.
You are the joy of the lightning.
You broke my heart.
It's too late.
You are the joy of the lightning.
I'll never forget the day we parted.
Fire!
Thank you very much.
Please come again.
I was deceived.
I was deceived by this program.
I heard it on a talk show.
I got on the Shinkansen at 7 o'clock in the morning.
I was deceived by this show.
I heard it on a talk show.
It's time to take a break.
Chikichiki Oogiri Daigassen is famous for its use of children.
This program has created many legends.
This program is a special program.
Chikichiki Oogiri Daigassen.
Good evening.
This program is a special program for children.
Please welcome Mr. Hanashika.
I wrote an interesting book.
Please buy it.
It's getting warmer these days.
How are you doing?
I'm doing well.
What are you talking about?
I'm Kanda Toshinori.
This is the last one.
The back of today's program is Die Hard 2.
That's right.
It's Die Hard 2.
Die Hard 2 is interesting.
Hey!
I'll come here again.
That's mine.
Nice to meet you.
The first topic is this.
Read the Atakamo.
Are you ready?
This is a book.
I didn't write something like that.
I don't know what it is.
I want you to read the book as if you were writing the Atakamo.
That's it.
The first one is this.
Ta-da!
Mo-Takuto and the Cultural Revolution.
Are you ready?
Let's start with Kagi-chan.
On April 6, 1994, Mo-Takuto was smoking in Tiananmen Square in Beijing.
A guard came and said,
You must have come from there.
The guard pointed at his finger.
Mo-Takuto was surprised by the sound of his finger.
What are you talking about?
I don't know what it is.
Is that so?
Edison was on Mo-Takuto's knee.
Why are you talking about Edison?
I was talking about 2039.
It was a story that I couldn't see yet.
I understand that very well.
Mo-Takuto was a woman.
What?
I'll explain it in a way that's easy to understand.
There are 108 spellings to start a great revolution.
I see.
That is...
Yes.
What is a spell?
That's a great thing.
That's right.
What is it?
What are the 108 spellings?
Shut up.
You don't have to ask questions.
What are you going to do?
I'm sorry.
What is going to happen with the 108 spellings?
That's right.
What is it?
What are you going to do?
Let's play the headphones.
I'm going to play the headphones.
There's a lot of music playing.
I don't know what you're saying.
Let's go.
Here.
That's good.
I'll say it.
California dance.
I'm scared.
Let's love each other seriously.
Do you understand?
Let's go over here.
Take this.
There was a hair on the sushi, right?
Did the sushi have hair?
Please give me the correct answer.
Housuki.
The next question is...
I'm going to be a man.
I'll explain the rules.
If you don't answer correctly, the man who is holding the macho man will come closer.
Shimada.
Yes.
Come here.
What?
Please answer correctly.
It's been a long time since I've been in the gym.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
This is hard.
Don't laugh.
The gentle spring breeze gently envelops us.
Today is a picnic with handmade bento.
I have a feeling something good is going to happen.
Matsumoto.
Let's go on a picnic with everyone.
I'm fine.
It's fun to go with these members.
It's a fun picnic with bento.
Saito.
Yes.
Sato.
Sankon.
Yes.
Hideo.
Takeo.
Yes.
Saori.
Hiromi.
Yes.
Kenji.
Matsuno.
Arimi.
Marianne.
Yes.
He's laughing.
Watanabe.
Yes.
Michael Tomioka.
Michael.
He's not here yet.
Michael is late.
What are you doing?
Michael is going to gather at the site.
Michael is staying for a while.
If he comes to the site.
We are going to get on the bus with Michael who is late.
There must be a child who is late.
It's going to be fun.
Shiori, who was given by Hama-chan, is excited.
Finally, the bus departs from Nihon TV.
I think Shiori is on the bus.
Yes.
Please move over there.
I'm going to sing a picnic song.
Yes.
Let's sing together.
One, two.
Let's go over the hill.
Let's blow a whistle.
Cheer up.
Look at the blue sky in the corner.
Let's stick our fangs out.
Hurry up.
Yes.
Let's sing together.
Let's dance together.
La la la la la la la.
Mr. Yagi.
Idiot.
La la la la la la.
Mr. Yagi.
Idiot.
La la la la la la.
While singing a refreshing picnic song,
we will pass through Koharu Biyori's Jingu and Shibuya.
Mr. Ben, who is always cheerful,
seems to want to leave today's wonderful moment in the video.
I'm done.
What are you doing?
What am I supposed to do?
Hello.
And finally, the bus arrives at Kinuta Park.
My heart is beating fast.
Oh.
That bastard just came.
What are you doing?
Stop saying that.
I was thinking about what to catch last night.
This is the result.
There's nothing here.
We're all heading to the park.
Everyone seems to be having fun.
This is our destination,
Kinuta Park Family Park.
It feels good to be surrounded by greenery.
We've just arrived.
Yes.
Let's take a picture of our free time.
We're going to enjoy this park.
Please enjoy it.
Let's have fun under the blue sky.
Who are you?
Oh, it's you.
And now, it's lunch time.
How will it turn out?
I'll take a picture and open it,
but I won't say it's mine.
I'll open it and see what's inside.
And I'll tell you who it is.
Wait a minute.
It's good.
It's cute.
It's well-made.
It's well-made?
Whose lunch is this?
It's a girl's lunch.
Yes.
What?
Hiromi's handmade bento with a cooking license is colorful and skillful.
It's cute.
It's you.
Is this different from mushroom rice?
That's right.
Speaking of mushroom rice, it's Chi-chi.
It's so cute.
It's cute.
I like this kind of lunch.
Do you like it?
This is mine.
What?
No way.
We don't like your bento.
This is good.
Why?
You just need to warm it up, right?
It's definitely a girl's hand.
It's not.
I'll warm it up.
This is what I cooked.
It's not a big deal.
That's right.
Haba-chan's bento that Mach-chan said he liked unexpectedly.
It's a good combination.
It's amazing.
I ate it.
Is this Kenji?
Yes.
I woke up at 6 o'clock in the morning and made it by looking at the book.
I made it by looking at the book.
This is amazing.
I made it by myself.
Kenji's bento was worth waking up early.
It's a luxurious lunch box.
What is this?
Who is this?
This is a lunch box with pickled plums, bonito flakes, and takuan.
This is what I saw.
Do you know this?
Who is this?
This is me.
Ben's lunch box is the same as his head.
I feel lonely.
This is a small lunch box.
This is a dessert.
Is this a dessert?
It's not.
This is a girl's lunch box, isn't it?
Who is this?
This is me.
The contents of this lunch box are all super.
This is a super lunch box.
Takamatsu's lunch box is like a girl's lunch box.
Hoshi and Tetsu are crying.
Makiko's natto lunch box is like a girl's lunch box.
Yacchan and Sato's lunch box is like a girl's lunch box.
Saori's lunch box is like a sweet potato sandwich.
Michael's lunch box is like a French bread sandwich.
Marianne's lunch box is like a curry lunch box.
Sankon's lunch box is like a Japanese lunch box.
What is this lunch box?
Who is this?
This is a lunch box that I used to eat when I was in elementary school.
What is this?
Wait a minute.
Why is there so much rice in this lunch box?
The last lunch box is a handmade lunch box of a cute girl.
Everyone, let's eat.
Let's eat.
This is a picnic that I was invited to in the spring.
The blue sky, green, and fresh air make me feel good.
I will engrave your smile and today as a memorable page in my heart.
Let's meet again.
HITOSHI MATSUMOTO continues to challenge various dangers. He has been in this world for 30 years and has always loved danger.
He is said to have heard the sound of the explosion when he was born.
He lives on the edge of death.
I can do it.
His challenge increases the intensity of the voltage day by day.
No one can stop him anymore.
No!
I'm glad I did it.
I'm impressed.
He survived again.
And tonight, the greatest danger is coming.
A total of 50 staff are preparing.
This may be the last time to see his face.
HITOSHI MATSUMOTO, the man of the sword, the greatest danger.
He challenges the intensity of the voltage.
Do you know that electricity passes through the human body?
This woman passed 10,000 volts of electricity through her body and operated a 20th generation fan.
However, this time, MATSUMOTO will challenge 20,000 volts twice as much.
Are you okay?
Do I just turn on the power?
Yes.
I see.
Good morning.
20,000 volts?
That's amazing.
To put it simply, electricity passes through the body and passes on to others.
I did it once when I was in junior high school.
That's 10,000 volts, isn't it?
That's right.
10,000 volts?
Take a look at this.
Are you serious?
What should I do?
Before we started shooting, you were one of us.
But after we started shooting, we became stars.
I don't think we should do this anymore.
But let me do this.
Actually,
I wrote a letter to ITSU.
It was a letter from my mother.
She told me that my son didn't study at all.
She sent me a letter about two months ago.
I thought I'd give it a try.
Let's do it.
I'll hold the cord at both ends.
You have to plug in the outlet.
I want my partner to do this.
Let's do it.
TO BE CONTINUED...
Are you ready?
I'll plug it in.
It's spinning.
Is it on?
It's on TV.
It's spinning.
TO BE CONTINUED...
I did it, didn't I?
Look at this.
TO BE CONTINUED...
What should I do?
The adventurer, Hitoshi Matsumoto.
Thank you for your inspiration.
What kind of challenge will he show us next?
A hot battle between a man and a woman.
A battle between Akko vs. Ume Miya vs. Jin Ginaki vs. Badminton.
This season has come again.
That's right.
I'm glad you two are in the mood today.
Today, we're going to have a battle with Badminton.
I feel like we've done this before, but we haven't.
We've done table tennis before.
We haven't done Orthodox.
We haven't.
I wonder what kind of match it will be.
Let's call them in.
First, we have Ume Miya and Tatsuo.
They're in the mood today.
They're in the mood.
It's already 3-1.
Even if you lose today, it'll be easy.
If you win, it'll be great.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Really?
But Tatsuo has a lot of muscles today.
Muscles?
Why?
I wonder why he's so small.
This is...
The man!
Why?
I don't like men.
Why not?
The first man is Akko, right?
That's right.
The first man is Akko.
The first man is Ume Miya.
The blue man is Akko.
What do you think of my muscles?
You're so mean!
Why?
I'm worried about my muscles.
I'm going to lift you up.
Today, Badminton has 3 sets.
If you win 2 sets earlier, you win.
This time, you're not going to do it, are you?
I'll go to the judge.
Why do you have to go to the judge?
Akko has a lot of muscles.
Let's see who wins.
Who do you think will win?
What do you think?
Me and Akko.
It doesn't matter.
Let's see who wins.
It's an out.
It's under the net.
This is an out.
Please hit it.
I know it's an out.
This is easy.
It's an out.
You don't even know it's an out.
This is easy.
It's an out.
It's strong.
It's like a fairy tale.
He's laughing.
I don't know.
Akko wins the first set.
I'm a fool.
I can't see it.
Akko is good.
He didn't touch it.
Which side are you on?
You're on the same side.
Go away.
He hit it.
He's serious.
It's in.
Akko wins.
It's over.
Why?
He's like a high school student and a donkey.
It's impossible.
I don't know.
He hit it before the punishment game.
He's serious.
You're on the same side.
Which side are you on?
We're on the same side.
You're a judge.
You're like a child.
He's on the same side.
He's like a producer.
He always does this.
Why does he always do this?
I want to hit him more.
What's wrong?
Idiot.
You don't know the rules.
What's wrong?
He hit too hard.
It's fair.
What's wrong?
What didn't you like?
I'm upset that I lost.
Idiot.
I'm sorry.
His way of doing it...
It's crazy.
I'm sorry.
I didn't do it well.
You didn't do it well?
Or was he angry?
Why were you angry?
He's being fooled.
He's using his power.
You know that kind of guy, right?
I'm sorry.
It's not like that.
He was bad at the beginning.
I wanted to hit him more.
Sometimes he gets angry because of acting.
I thought he was acting at first.
He was laughing when I hit him.
When I hit him, his face was like this.
I hit him too.
Sato.
Yes.
I was surprised.
This is funny.
You're a professional.
Why were you angry?
I was scared.
I knew it.
That's why I was surprised.
You're the only one I don't know.
What?
I was in a bad mood.
That's good.
It was a great success.
Thank you very much.
First topic.
The name of the hero.
Gatchaman.
Kamen Rider Amazon.
Kamen Rider V3.
No. 2 Rider.
No. 1 Hiroshi Fujioka.
No. 1 Jinny.
The name of the instrument.
Trumpet.
Flute.
It's dangerous!
Let's go to the next one.
J.League's team name.
Beldy Kawasaki.
Kawasaki.
Shimizu Hata.
Kai-chan.
I can still do it.
You're not doing it right.
The name of Enkakashi.
Dan Da Dan.
Nobuo Matsubara.
Eisa Okawa.
Kobayaki-ro.
What are you looking at?
You're not doing it right!
Time's up!
It stinks!
You're not doing it right!
What are you doing?
Let's go to the next one.
A song that starts with A.
Akashiyano.
It starts with A.
Aburamushi.
Sushi.
Sushi-neta.
Koada.
Akanai.
Kanohonaya-maki.
Ebi-maki.
Arureke.
Let's go to the next one.
The name of the solar system.
Kasei.
Mokusei.
Kinsei.
Dosei.
Chikyuu.
Nichisei.
Time's up!
It stinks!
This really stinks.
Let's go to the last one.
The third round.
Please sit down.
Soya, you do it.
This is normal.
It's not normal.
You're laughing at me.
The name of the seki-tori.
From here.
Kyokudo-san.
Konishi-ki.
Oni-chan.
No.
Why?
If you say Oni-chan, you'll know.
Whose Oni-chan?
If you say Oni-chan in seki-tori, you'll know.
Foreign movie star.
From here.
Shiwa-chan.
No.
Please sit down.
Shiwa-chan.
Time's up.
This distance is the most disgusting.
The name of an old story.
Momotaro.
He's dirty.
Grandpa Hanasaka.
Grandma becomes a wolf.
I know.
Wait.
Everyone knows.
That one.
The one with gold and silver.
Old Asked-for Uncle Kobutori.
How is it old Asked for Uncle Kobutori?
I know.
I will be beaten if I say that.
You knew the title.
You remembered now?
You are slightly safe, right?
Yes, Kanda-kun.
Aite, it's about growing up.
It was a long time ago.
That one.
Is that a story from last month?
No, it isn't.
If you do it like that, you'll be in trouble.
Don't lie to me.
That's what he said.
It's true.
Why did I give him a gift?
It's the name of a pink lady.
2.
K.
Yes.
Wait a minute.
Hurry up and get out of here.
This guy is very soft.
The day of the debut live after a stormy recording.
If you run away with a ball, I'll chase you.
Are you on it?
It is said that the live ad is on that village voice.
It's hard.
Ryuichi Sakamoto.
The photo of Ryuichi Sakamoto is smaller.
Gen-sha Girls.
Why is that?
I'm a man.
What is the reaction of the rappers?
Shut up.
Why are you laughing?
At that time, preparations were made at the venue.
This is a famous store at the forefront of the New York scene.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm a man.
I'm a man, but I don't care about the couple there.
Three hours before the show, the line up had already begun.
I've never seen it before.
I will go with this.
At the venue, Sakamoto prepared the Royal Remission.
Really?
I don't know what's going to happen.
It's not something that can be done with effort.
I'm nervous.
The two are nervous about their first overseas live.
They finally arrive at the venue.
This way.
You've got a boy with a UPS.
The debut live stage performance was produced by Sakamoto Ryuichi.
The U.S. hitmaker, Tomie, also participated in the live performance.
The dance demonstration was held to refer to the two's stage performances.
I think he's got an A.
One hour before the show, the final rehearsal.
Sakamoto's strict instructions also fly.
Finally, there are 400 people in the audience.
How will the two's stages be received in New York, the first city of all cultures?
The audience is cheering.
But there's a lot of scary things in the world.
There are a lot of scary things in the world.
Tell me what's scary.
I'm not afraid of anything, especially the kidnappers.
Hello.
Bring me 5 million.
5 million?
Is it expensive?
No, it's 5 million.
It's 5 million.
Are you going to lose?
I'm not afraid of anything.
Bring me 5 million.
Okay.
White hair on the back side, yellow hair on the green side.
I'll play it one more time.
White hair on the back side, yellow hair on the red side.
I'm going to jump.
White hair on the back side, yellow hair on the green side.
The black one is coming!
Nice!
The old lady is going!
Not yet!
Nice!
The old lady is going!
Good evening!
Let me introduce the members.
This is Koume!
Yeah! Koume from Geisha Girls!
And Shungiku!
Shungiku! Yeah!
And the drummer is Katsuno!
Katsuno! Yeah!
Yeah!
These members are still going!
They are still going!
And now...
Let's go!
The old lady is going!
Tokyo Dome Geisha Girls!
Geisha Girls is the strongest rap group in Japan.
Geisha Girls will be released in the US in the summer of 1994.