It's hard to get out. This is a new one. It's hard to get out, isn't it?
This usually comes out while it's on, right? That's right. I don't know when it will come out.
It's easier to get out once you've done it. It's easier to get out once you've done it.
It's easier to get out once you've done it.
This is how it looks.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
I will never tell a lie.
What?
If people think it's true, I don't like it.
What do you want to say?
I'm going to tell you a story.
I went to a sushi restaurant.
It's a place I've never been to.
It was open until 5 in the morning.
It wasn't a good sushi restaurant.
It wasn't open.
I happened to go in.
There were five men.
There was a counter and a seat over here.
There were only men sitting on the counter.
They were wearing thick tank tops.
Everyone was wearing tank tops.
It was strange.
What was it?
It was like a hard gay.
It was strange.
They were clinging on to each other.
They were like a couple.
I thought it was because it was a sushi restaurant.
They were all wearing tank tops.
I thought it was crazy.
But that's okay.
You can't put your hands out.
I didn't put my hands out.
I was surprised.
I thought I should eat quickly and leave.
There was a customer who asked me to hold it.
I used a lot of electricity.
I didn't like it.
I really didn't like it.
I arrived at the counter.
I said hello.
I suddenly felt the skinhead's neck.
I was surprised.
There was a customer who was in the 14th grade.
It was a hard gay.
I thought it wasn't Japanese.
I thought it was a poor guy.
I asked him where he was from.
He said he was from China.
I asked him what his name was.
He said his name was Kyo.
He said he was Kyo.
I told him to do his best.
He kept looking at me.
I was surprised.
I didn't think it was strange.
I thought it was Machan.
I'm interested in the new half these days.
What are you talking about?
I was surprised.
I didn't think it was strange.
He was a junior.
He was the younger brother of the Chihara brothers.
He couldn't get better.
He had an accident.
I see.
He had a trauma.
He couldn't get better.
He remembered it.
He didn't make a sound.
He said, I'm fine.
I was riding next to him.
I had a problem with my phone.
He was angry with Yamashita.
He was like a guardrail.
I was like, it's not that bad, it's not that bad!
I was like, I'll put it forward.
I realized later that I was a little bit on the guardrail.
I put it forward and it went like,
BAM! BAM! BAM! BAM!
And all the bumpers came off.
AAAAAAAA!
I couldn't help myself.
When I said BAM! BAM! BAM!
You should have said AAAAAAAA!
And then I went down and saw it again.
AAAAAAAA!
I was like, it's okay, it's okay!
It wasn't completely off.
I was like, who did this?
BAM!
And then it went in.
It went in, so it was okay.
I said, don't worry, Junior.
And then an old lady came up to me.
She said, these parts are falling off.
AAAAAAAA!
Who did that?
Junior.
AAAAAAAA!
With those parts.
Come on.
You were doing something.
It's weird.
I was saying AAAAAAAA one by one.
Then it's you.
I know what kind of AAAAAAAA is.
You were just saying AAAAAAAA.
I was surprised at the old lady's AAAAAAAA.
I was saying, these parts are falling off.
AAAAAAAA!
She said that.
That's not true.
It's true.
It's scary, isn't it?
Even when I was walking on the street,
I was saying AAAAAAAA.
Why?
I was saying, I can't think of a painful angle.
I don't know much about it.
I don't know about that.
I don't know about that painful angle.
I don't know how many times.
I see.
That's how it is.
Really.
I want to poop.
This is different.
This is a question for Mr. Matsumoto, who eats seven eel pies a day.
Yes.
How erotic is the Ero Gappa?
Well, eroticism doesn't exist.
It doesn't exist.
There's no such thing as an erotic dog.
It's just a nickname given to the Kappa.
That's right.
It's the Ero Gappa.
The entire Kappa is extremely erotic.
Is that so?
Yes.
There's a person called Kappa Kishitsu, isn't there?
Who is it?
It's you.
What?
You're the king of the Tsumoneda Kingdom, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
Why are you laughing?
It's amazing, isn't it?
You like the Tsumoneda Kingdom, don't you?
No, I don't like it.
There are a lot of people who misunderstand this, so I really want to say it.
The image of the Tsumoneda Kingdom is a little strong.
But this is a big mistake.
What?
A big mistake?
It's a big mistake.
I don't like the Tsumoneda Kingdom at all.
It's not just me.
All men like the Tsumoneda Kingdom.
This is a serious injury.
What do you mean?
What do you mean by a serious injury?
Everyone around you is talking about the Tsumoneda Kingdom with care.
Why?
Because they like you.
Because you're so excited about the Tsumoneda Kingdom.
So I told you that you should talk about the Tsumoneda Kingdom today.
I told you three things today.
I'm tired.
I'm not happy if I don't say it.
Are you so excited about the Tsumoneda Kingdom?
I really like the Tsumoneda Kingdom.
That's why the blood of the kappa is flowing.
That's what I mean.
Even a normal kappa is erotic.
How far has the erotic kappa gone?
That's amazing.
The erotic kappa.
What's amazing?
What?
Anyway, I'll say anything.
What's wrong with him?
You're really...
How far has the erotic kappa gone?
I'm going to put coins in the vending machine.
I'm worried about the erotic kappa when it comes out on the ground.
Now?
I'm going to put it in the card in the parking lot.
That's difficult.
Like this.
I can't get used to it.
I can get used to it if I put it in at the beginning.
The erotic kappa.
It's the worst.
There's no kappa anymore.
There used to be.
The kappa was able to have sex.
There's a kappa's age.
I think you're a fourth generation kappa.
I think you're a quarter.
Really?
That's why it's erotic.
It's amazing, isn't it?
What's so amazing about it?
It's amazing.
No matter what you look at it, you're trying to make it feel like you're biting or biting a mask, aren't you?
It's funny.
The way it is now.
When you become nude, the angel's wings tend to show.
I have a question for Matsumoto-san.
Seriously?
Please tell me how to distinguish devil, demon and satan.
I'd like to know that too.
Right?
Yes.
There are many ways to distinguish them.
If you tell me the difference, I'll know how to distinguish them.
The easiest way to distinguish them is...
It's written here on the jacket.
What kind of jacket is that?
It's a jacket.
It's not a jacket.
Are you wearing a jacket?
You're wearing a jacket, aren't you?
I'm not wearing a jacket.
Why is that?
Then what kind of jacket are you wearing?
What kind of devil, satan are you wearing?
I'm wearing tights.
What?
Am I wrong?
I'm wearing tights all over my body.
That's really stupid.
That's the devil, satan and demon in your imagination.
Really?
That's really stupid.
I usually wear tights like a salaryman.
Really?
That's right.
And here's the devil.
I don't get it.
There are too many devils.
What do you mean?
I'm pretending to be a fake.
I see.
That's right.
But it's hard to distinguish.
You can't do that.
That's right.
Especially if the other person is a devil.
That's why you're telling me to make it easy to distinguish.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
Right?
Yes.
The devil is...
For example, let's say it's a war.
It's not good if it breaks during the war.
Everyone, please make it easy to distinguish.
Listen.
For example, even during a war, the devil goes like this.
But satan goes like this.
That's because it's impossible.
That's why it goes like this.
Please make it easy to distinguish by appearance.
By appearance?
That's right.
Well...
Usually, when you wear tights, you wear something like this.
Right?
What's wrong with you?
When you wear tights, you wear something like this.
That's why you can distinguish.
You...
You're mistaken for Musimakin.
If you say something like that,
is it true that it's Musimakin?
Well, that's right.
Usually...
What are you saying?
Your imagination and my imagination are different.
That's Musiba's thing.
It's something to scare children.
But it's easy to understand.
It's like a traditional costume.
Is that so?
That's why Japanese people don't wear Japanese costumes now.
That's right.
They wear it naturally.
It's not like that now.
It's a business suit.
That's right.
That's why it's hard to distinguish.
Please tell me that.
Well...
Usually satan is ***.
But that's also a problem.
That's difficult.
Why ***?
I don't like that.
I want to have a number.
I see.
You don't want to wear a good costume.
You don't know what to wear.
That's right.
I don't like ***.
But I want to have two costumes.
That's my way of thinking.
I don't like this.
It's difficult.
This is difficult.
But...
You can see it if you put three people together.
It's like rock-paper-scissors.
What do you mean?
Satan is like a demon.
Satan is like, you know...
The demon is like...
Stop it.
But the demon is like a devil.
Satan is like, you know...
But the demon is...
I don't understand the picture.
I heard that the lyrics of the song are up to the 10th.
Please tell me the lyrics of the 7th song.
Do you know the 1st and the 2nd?
Everyone knows the 1st.
But I don't know the 2nd.
I don't understand it at all.
Where are your eyeballs?
Put out your horns.
Put out your eyeballs.
Put out your head.
The 2nd is...
I don't know the 2nd.
You don't know the 2nd?
If you listen to it, you might think, oh, really?
Oh, really?
Please tell me the 2nd.
In the end, it's a song about solving the mystery of the snail.
Where are your eyeballs?
The 2nd is...
Your...
Don't think about it.
Where are your hands?
Seriously, where are your hands?
There are a lot of songs that are up to the 10th.
I see.
What is the 7th song?
The 7th is...
I don't know the 8th and the 6th.
I'm sorry about that.
The 7th is...
Where are the mansions?
The body part is already over.
It's already over.
I see.
Where do you live?
Where is it?
In the previous episode, you said you were the chief.
You said you were going to change.
I was like, have you changed?
Oh, really?
You said you were going to come to my side.
I see.
Are you calling me?
I'm calling you.
What?
I see.
It's not just the 7th.
What about the 10th?
That's right.
Right?
Even if you listen to the 7th...
Yes, yes, yes.
There are songs up to the 10th.
That's right.
What about the 10th?
What?
What is the 10th?
Let's go with the 10th.
Are you going to tell me?
I'll tell you.
That's the easiest to understand.
That's right.
Right?
Then tell me.
Where are your eyeballs?
First of all, the first one.
Put your head out.
Which one?
The head.
Where are your hands?
My hands?
That's fine.
It's the 3rd.
The 3rd is a little different.
It's not different anymore!
It's a little different.
I wanted to change it around here.
I see.
The 3rd.
What time will you come?
It's not yours.
It's not yours anymore.
That's fine.
What?
What time will you come?
Put your horns out.
Put your head out.
That's fine.
The 4th.
The 4th?
This will surprise you.
The 4th will surprise you?
Yes.
The 4th.
Where are your eyeballs?
I'll ask you again.
Why?
I haven't asked you yet.
Why haven't you asked me?
That's really disgusting.
Ask me yourself.
Right?
Ask me.
I was surprised.
I was surprised too.
When I saw the 4th, I was like, what? Again?
Think about it.
What?
The 5th will change again.
From here again.
Yes.
Until you go to the apartment.
You're lying, right?
Yes.
The 7th apartment.
The 7th.
The 5th and 6th.
Yes.
The 5th.
Tell me about the 5th.
This is bad.
What's bad?
Don't come back.
You're so stubborn.
Where are your eyeballs?
What are you trying to do?
Are you Mitsui Mitsubishi Sakura?
You're completely...
You're trying to do something.
You're trying to do something, right?
The 6th.
What?
When I heard that, I was like, ah!
I thought I was done for.
Yes.
Are you drunk?
I was surprised.
You're completely drunk.
Your...
Where are they?
It's all over the place.
Really?
When I heard that, I was like, where are your eyeballs?
You're going.
This is terrible.
I'm scared.
You can't put it on.
The elementary school...
Where are your eyeballs?
Mama! Mama!
The education committee is asking for your horns.
You're so stubborn.
They're asking for your horns.
Where is the 7th apartment?
8, 9, 10. The last three.
That's right.
I'll make it look good.
Really?
Your...
Where is your love?
What is this?
It's like a heart.
You're asking for the course, the school, the apartment, and love?
Where is your love?
Where is it now?
I see.
I'll make it look good.
Are youング?
Do you think you're pregnant?
No.
No, no.
No children!
No, no!
You should have gotten a child.
No!
That's true, that's true.
I should have gotten a child, right?
Yes.
Next, I've got the rod 해줌 Saturday crank.
No.
I've got a lot of the rod ajou mother and I look like yesterday.
I've got a lot of the rod ajou mom and I look like yesterday.
Ok.
Don't say any more.
OMG.
Iím confused.
The last one is number 10.
If you don't end it here, it won't end.
Right?
Tell me number 10.
What?
May I?
Yes.
Tell me.
May I really?
Go ahead.
It's time to draw.
Yes.
Denden mushimushi.
Right?
Yes.
Katatsumuri.
Yes, yes.
Up to here, it's the same as before.
No, it's all the same.
It's all the same as before.
I'm surprised.
Denden mushimushi katatsumuri.
Yes.
Fly away.
What is this?
It's in English.
Didn't you make it?