From now on, I won't use your money!
Hooray!
Everyone, listen to me.
What is it?
I'm sorry, but I came in two hours earlier than usual.
This is my selfishness, but...
Yamazaki isn't here today, is he?
No, he isn't.
Actually, only I knew about it.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
To put it simply...
I don't know if you'll believe me, but...
He's not human.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm sure you're the first one to find out.
When I went to the apartment, that's what happened.
What is this?
What are you doing?
Yamazaki, hey!
I looked up the dictionary.
When you say a cold, it's supposed to hit a baraka.
A baraka?
A baraka is a far away baraka.
If you don't return it to Yamazaki, it won't work.
Yamazaki?
I can't buy it like this.
No, you can't.
No, I can't.
I wanted to buy it, but I can't in the winter.
It's hard.
I have to buy it every night.
I have to buy jelly every night, so I have to buy it quickly.
No, you can't.
I'll put it in the basket and return it.
You can take it, but if you leave it there, what will happen?
Should I take it out from here?
It's in, so you can take it out.
Miyo!
It's hard for me too.
I'll put it in the basket and take it.
I'm feeling good, so I'm sleeping.
You've been lying to us.
You're surprised.
I'm hungry.
Let's do something.
Let's do it.
What are you doing?
It's dangerous.
What's that?
Is that you?
Father and mother.
Where are you going?
Amazake!
Let's go home.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Let's go home.
Is it around here?
It's around here.
I wonder if it's alive.
Can you take care of it in the forest?
Amazake!
Come here!
It's not here.
This is fine.
It's a small animal, so it's okay.
Amazake is a heavy animal.
Is it okay?
It's cute.
I bought it for fun.
It's just a small animal, so it's okay.
It's cute.
It's cute, but it's better to be careful.
I wonder what it is.
It's chasing me.
The way it moves is strange.
It's you.
It's moving.
I can't hear the sound.
Come here!
Amazake!
Let's go home.
Ladies and gentlemen.
I can't speak because I ate too much.
I found it.
What are you going to do?
What is it?
I'm going to play a game.
A game?
Yes.
I'll ask the staff to play a game.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to play a game?
If you don't play a game, you can say it.
Let's do it.
What are you going to do?
I can't beat Takadobi.
I lost and went to the shrimp shop.
What are you going to do?
I don't care what you do this time.
Really?
Yes.
What is it?
Shall we do a marathon?
I don't care about that.
Can I decide?
No.
You're going to beat Takadobi.
I'm going to decide this time.
Tetris.
I'm really good at Tetris.
I can't do it.
I was called Tetris.
I don't know about that.
I don't play Tetris.
You don't play Tetris.
Let's do it.
Let's do a marathon.
I don't want to see a marathon.
Why?
I'm sorry to the people who do it.
I'm an idol.
I don't like it.
My father is shaking.
You're fat.
If you're fat, your father will shake.
I'm not good at shaking on TV.
What are you talking about?
You're talking about Katsuki.
You did it last time.
I'm not good at shaking.
Let's do a marathon.
I'm going to take a break from the marathon.
Why?
I'm going to take a break today.
I have a promise.
This is a promise.
I'll make a promise before that.
Not before that.
I'm making a promise now.
Let's stop the marathon.
Why?
No.
You're going to lose.
Let me challenge you.
You know you're going to lose, so you're going to challenge me.
That's right.
If you win, I'll say, you're pretty good.
Is that the end?
Why do I have to do it?
You can't do a marathon.
How many times do I have to do it?
I won't forgive you for being so selfish.
I drank last time.
Let's do a marathon.
No.
Why?
It's better to run a long distance.
You've been running for three years.
Why?
Wait.
You have the confidence to jump high.
You're going to challenge me.
I don't know why you're doing this.
You're the one who doesn't know why.
This time, I'll take my opinion.
I'll say it's a marathon.
It's not decided yet.
It's a marathon as a plan.
Let's take a break.
I'm 100 meters away.
Well, a marathon is fine.
You're 10 kilometers away.
Let's take a break.
I'll take it by hand.
I'm not going to do it now.
Let's do it for the first time.
Let's not do a marathon.
Let's do it.
It's not a big deal.
Where are you going?
Marathon.
Then you should stop the marathon.
Stop my opinion.
It's not a big deal.
Marathon is no good.
No, no, no, no.
That's not the case.
So now my opinion is a marathon.
So I'm not saying I'm going to decide here.
I'll talk to you again when I'm shooting the next one.
I'm just saying it now.
It's a marathon.
If you don't do it, it won't make any sense.
You were so confident at that time.
It's a marathon.
Let's decide the penalty.
Penalty.
Let's decide the penalty first.
What is it?
Let's do something dangerous.
I'm going to do something life-threatening.
You're not doing anything.
You've done a lot of things like riding a motorcycle.
You.
Tell me if you really did it.
Did you do it?
I didn't do it.
You don't know anything.
How many things have I done so far?
Think about it.
12 years of entertainment life.
Fight with bears.
Tell me if you really did it.
You went up the stairs on a motorcycle.
That's obvious.
You have to do something.
It's okay.
If you lose, do it.
That's.
That.
It's hard to go abroad for a week.
So.
I'm going to make a runaway group with one person.
That.
The name of the group.
I'm going to blow it up naked.
I'm going to catch it.
But you have to think about it little by little.
It's already the end of November.
It's already the end of December.
I can't decide next week.
I can't decide.
So.
You should practice now.
I can't do it.
But that's your...
I'm not going to do it.
Don't say that.
I'm not saying anything good right now.
Who's saying anything good?
So what are you going to do about the punishment game?
Punishment game?
So that's it.
It's dangerous.
It's more dangerous than skydiving.
What?
Tiger and skydiving.
How do you live with a tiger?
So there's a parachute attached to the tiger.
There's nothing to judge him.
So you're going to drop it.
With your body.
If you attach a parachute to the tiger, it will fall.
If you want to be saved, you have to be bitten by the tiger.
If you get bitten.
Don't say anything good right now.
Skydiving is okay.
Don't do it again.
It's as scary as skydiving.
Then do bungee jumping.
You say things like that, but...
I want to see your partner taking a dump.
I don't know if I'm going to take a dump or not.
I know myself best.
I'm definitely a man who takes a dump.
If you're going to take a dump, I'll do it.
I'll do it.
I can't take a dump.
I know I'm going to take a dump.
It's sad.
I took a dump.
It's okay.
When you were on top of the skydiving,
I was shaking my butt.
You were shaking your butt.
I don't know if I'm going to take a dump or not.
No, no.
I've been there a lot.
One.
Zero.
Oh, it's in seconds.
Five.
I was talking to a foreigner by ear.
What are you doing on Christmas?
What?
Why?
Why are you asking me while you're embarrassed?
I don't feel like I'm embarrassed.
I think about it every year.
Everyone is excited about Christmas.
Tell me what you're doing on Christmas.
I'm doing something because it's Christmas.
There's nothing to do.
If that's the case, I'll know what to do on New Year's Eve.
It's decided.
There's something I have to do.
On Christmas, my girlfriend said,
Are you free on New Year's Eve?
I said, Yes, I'm free.
I know what you're going to say.
I have to do it on New Year's Eve.
But on Christmas, she said she was free.
I said, Yes, I'm free.
What am I supposed to do with her?
I light a fire with a cake.
You're too particular about that cake.
That's right.
All couples do that with their lovers.
They all break their bones like this.
They hand a cake to the person holding it.
And keep going.
And then they hand it to her.
Everyone can take it.
Just let them take it.
What, you're going to say thank you?
No, you're going to leave it alone.
It's about 2 minutes.
If you include the whole thing, it's 5 minutes.
If you say that Christmas is open,
what do you say?
It's over, isn't it?
Even so, it's over, isn't it?
No, so Christmas...
For example, I want you to be with me all day long.
I want you to be with me.
What is it?
I don't want to tell you that I'm a manly student.
If you say something interesting, I won't tell you that I'm an amateur.
You're like an amateur.
But this day is Christmas.
It's cute.
This day is Christmas.
So it's a little different, isn't it?
It's a little different from normal sex.
If you're taking a picture,
you'll be stuck in the window where you can see the night view.
It's already 10 o'clock.
It's a candle.
Candle.
Who is the person who is secretly hiding in the corner of the sewing box?
I don't know at all.
Does this have a face?
Do you know?
No, I know that.
Please tell me.
This is a strange way of asking questions.
Why?
Who is the person who is secretly hiding in the corner of the sewing box?
I'm not secretly hiding.
It's not a person, is it?
It's like this.
It's a pink lady.
It's Mii-chan and Kei-chan.
It's a person like this.
Who is the richest person in the entertainment world?
It's Sabu-chan.
Sabu-chan is really rich.
Sabu-chan's house is huge.
It's not just one, is it?
Probably.
There are many places.
But the main house is amazing.
The main house stands up.
And there are many hot springs.
Is it scattered?
It's scattered.
It's amazing.
Please say something to us.
The main house is bad.
Where did you come from?
It stinks.
It's cold.
It's okay.