What are you doing?
I quit.
You didn't?
No, I didn't.
You didn't smoke?
No, I didn't smoke at all.
Can you stop smoking?
Do you have a cigarette?
I don't know.
You didn't smoke at all?
I didn't smoke at all.
Thank you.
That was fast.
That was pretty fast.
You don't trust me.
What happened?
Yamazaki-san asked me to bring everyone here.
Everyone's been calling you out lately.
That's a lot.
It's not like you're that popular.
Where are you going?
It's close by.
I'm sorry.
Please start.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
I'll hold it here.
Are you feeling down?
Here it comes.
Here's the first shot.
I'm feeling down.
Are you angry?
What are you talking about?
I'm feeling down.
Good morning.
What's wrong?
I'm Yosei Yamazaki.
Nice to meet you.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry for calling you out.
That was funny.
What was funny?
I called you out.
That was funny.
It wasn't funny at all.
Yamazaki-san, you're feeling down.
I'm feeling down.
Why?
As a comedian, I don't think I can do it.
It's too late.
What do you mean it's too late?
I'm sorry.
Did you know about the NS broadcast?
Yes, I did.
It was seven days ago.
At that time, at the library...
What?
At the library...
At the library?
Yes.
You called it a library, and I called it Choco Choco.
I can't believe it.
At the library.
At the library, there was a broadcast, and you all played a penalty game, right?
Yes, we did.
I didn't get a single point.
I didn't get a single point either.
Hamada-san is good.
Why?
Hamada-san is the best, so he can't get a single point.
Is that so?
I can't get a single point.
I see.
I didn't get a single point.
In a sense, I didn't get a single point.
It's true. It's true.
A comedian can only experience it as an event.
There is a moment when God descends.
However, Yamasaki has recently been blessed by the God of laughter.
Last week, a silent library was held at the Ernest Host.
The penalty game is decided by drawing a card and who hits the skull.
It's a game that depends on luck.
As you can see, the number of people who hit the skull is the same.
Hamada and Yamasaki didn't get a single point.
Everyone, please think about it.
Yamasaki, whose reactions are life, doesn't get a penalty.
This means the end of his life as a comedian.
To be honest, I think the TV director who uses me now is incompetent.
That's too much.
I don't have anything.
Don't say that.
I wasn't that funny in school.
Is that so?
That's right.
It's okay.
I haven't done it for years.
Bring it to me.
I'll show you how much God has blessed me.
I've seen it.
There's a lot of wasabi in there.
It's the most obvious.
It's the easiest to understand.
I'll do it.
Here I go.
It's good.
Really?
Well, well.
It's good.
That's right.
It's difficult.
You're making fun of me, aren't you?
Me?
I'm not making fun of you.
You're ruining it.
What a fool!
This is a giant balloon.
I see.
It's made of hose.
It's ruined.
It's split in half.
No.1
You don't need a hat
He doesn't know that
He doesn't have a delicacy
This has nothing to do with talent and staff
Are you ready?
Let's go
Come on
It's leaking
What?
Amazing
It was 1 in 2
It was funny
Let's see the host
It's like this
It's scary
It's terrible
It's dangerous
What is this?
It's the best in the world
There are darts
My parents throw darts like this
If there is a god, it will leak
This is good
This is the best
What?
You are the best
I'm not
Are you laughing?
I'm not laughing
Let's do it
This is my house
Where is it?
This is Tonga Shoto
Tonga Shoto
It's not funny
Tonga Shoto is funny
It's a good place
It's not
It's Tonga Shoto
Tonga Shoto
You are the best
Let's do it
My house is here
Where is it?
The name is weird
It's the Earth
I think so
Yamazaki
Zaki
It's funny
It's okay
I don't go to places like this
Come on
What is this?
There is helium gas in Japan
If you drink helium gas, your voice changes
It's a funny voice
Let's introduce ourselves
This way
Left
Let's go
Let's end this
Hello
I was expecting this
You are right
Let's go
Hurry up
Let's do it
What is this?
There are 10 T-shirts
There are many interesting things
Which one do you want?
This one
Number 2
Let's do it
I'm looking forward to it
Let's go
Look
What is this?
It's weird
Japan TV
It's amazing
Try it
You can see how much I'm doing
Tanaka is doing it
You are like a character
Look to the right
It's funny
What is this?
It's a coincidence
It's not a coincidence
It's a terrorist
It's funny
It's not a coincidence
I know it
I don't know if this will be popular
It's not a problem
Kamu
What is this?
It's a talent maker
The person I hate is this person
There are many people
It's amazing
The person I hate is this person
Yamato Yoshitake
I don't know him
He is from Kumamoto
I feel sorry for him
The person I hate is this person
Who is it?
It was close
It's amazing
It's amazing that you opened this page
It's a love between the police and the police
It's Heshiki Keigo
It's funny
It's like this
It's not like it's not funny
I got it
You didn't get it
It's not like that
Kamu
It's terrible today
It's all behind the scenes
What is this?
It's a polaroid
There is only one film
There is a funny face in front of it
When the paper comes down, it comes out
I got it
Let's go
Start
12 seconds
What is it?
I got it
It was a funny face
It depends on how you see it
It depends on the angle
There is a funny face
It's not bad
It's like an old comedian
It's like watching from the stage
It's funny
Is it good?
Let's play badminton
Kamu
What is it?
There is a scene
I got it
It's a scene
It depends on how you see it
Which one?
This one
Let's go
Get the sushi
Get the T-shirt
Let's go
Get the sushi
It hurts
Let's go
Let's do it
Good luck
5 seconds
4, 3, 2, 1
I've never seen this before
It's a machine
I'm scared
It's a scene
Get out
Let's go
It's a scene
Yama-chan, I've prepared the sushi
I'm in a hurry
It was fun
Let's do badminton
I don't do badminton
I'm in a hurry
This is a half
What are you going to do?
This is a normal woman
I'm going to dance tango
Let's go
It's a long one
You can see the tango
Bring the sushi
It's a long one
Take off your T-shirt
The T-shirt was too much
I'm hungry
Let's go
What is this?
It's a bomb
Let's go
Number 3
Can you do it?
It's a long one
Take off your T-shirt
I was born
What is this?
It's a long one
Hello
It's coming
Let's go
Isn't it enough?
Let's go outside
It's easy for Kami to be there
Yamasaki is going to go outside and call Kami
What are you going to do?
Please let me have the last game
What is it?
I asked the staff to make a hole here
There is only one hole here
I'm going to drop it in a minute
That's funny
Let's go
It's a long one
20 seconds
We don't have time
The dog ran away
Where is the other one?
We have to go to the other side
It's hot
It's over
Zaki
It's cold
What is it?
It didn't hit
It didn't hit at all
It fell where it was supposed to
You are completely tired
Thank you for watching