Let's do it.
What do you think about this?
Gakuyo Ballet.
It's good.
That's right.
Do you play G.O. in Gakuyo?
Yes, I do.
You play soccer.
It's too simple.
We can spend some money.
We can go to a foreign location.
Let's go.
Let's do it.
It's money.
It's good.
I like spending money.
I spend it a lot.
It's fun.
But it's a personal matter.
I spend a lot of money.
I've never seen G.O. in Gakuyo.
I've heard of it.
The punishment game I played with my mother.
How much did it cost?
7 million yen.
Let's do it.
Shall we buy it?
I have money.
You look alike.
You should buy it.
Shall we buy it?
You have a meeting, don't you?
I'm listening.
We've already decided.
We can go to the meeting.
I'm fine.
Let's just buy the money.
I'm just kidding.
It's fun, right?
That's right.
Sorry.
It's fun.
What is it?
I'm not sure.
I...
I want to fight with Moriman.
I want to fight with him at the Las Vegas.
That's good.
Are you a foreigner?
Yes, of course.
A Japanese mizet wrestler.
A tour guide.
I can't find a better place to say that.
That's cool.
A foreigner who's here to have fun.
But...
I'm sorry.
I want to do my best at Korakuen Hall.
I'm Japanese after all.
I can't spend that much money.
I don't know if I can do it.
What do you mean, you can't?
No, I can't.
What?
Hey.
You're not good at cutting.
You're too round.
Hey.
What are you doing?
No.
The plan is loose.
No, no, no.
I'm doing it now.
It's okay.
Wait a minute.
You can't spend money.
I don't care about the money.
I don't care if it's 50,000 or 60,000 yen.
No, no, no.
When you said it was about 10 million, you didn't say anything.
I don't think I said that.
No, no, no.
You said it here.
No, no.
When I'm here, everyone's worried about the money.
I'll be careful.
I told them to be honest.
There's something like that.
Everyone's fine with the money.
Everyone's saying yes.
Really.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Everyone's saying yes to the money.
I said yes to the money.
You did, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Everyone's eating.
If it's 10 million, we can eat a lot.
What do you want to eat?
I want to eat the best food in China.
What kind of food?
That's a good idea.
I want to eat a lot.
That's what I want to do.
Switzerland.
Can you eat the best food in Tokyo?
Yes, there is.
But it's expensive.
It's expensive.
You can go to China.
I think that's a good idea.
But I want to eat the best food in a restaurant.
These guys are getting angry.
They don't listen to me.
Why are you doing this?
Can I talk to you?
What?
Again?
Hey.
What are you doing?
What?
Are you going to buy something?
I'm worried about the time.
It's okay.
Let's go somewhere else.
Let's go to a crab restaurant.
That's a good idea.
Let's buy the price.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Let's go to a crab restaurant.
Let's.
It's hot.
Take a look.
Do you play this game every time?
It was a project where we ate crabs during the meeting.
That's a good idea.
I didn't want it to be a side dish.
Just the crab.
It wasn't like that.
Mr. Yoh, look at this crab.
It's so stupid.
Mr. Crab Yoh, this is really good.
It keeps coming up.
It's good.
It's hot.
It's not worth 10 million yen to go to the south.
That's tough.
But it's worth 10 million yen.
I'll add more.
Right.
It's spicy.
Is it okay?
It's hot.
What is it?
Be careful.
What's wrong?
It's good.
I want to eat some mozuku.
Why are you eating mozuku?
There's a lot of it.
What?
Hey.
This is good.
What's wrong?
He's taking the boiled one.
Hey, Sugahara.
What are you doing?
I was wondering if this was a good idea.
What do you mean?
You're eating mozuku and you're deciding.
No, come home.
When you see Sugahara, everyone is concerned.
Is it money?
Money is fine.
I've never complained about money.
Really?
You sound like a drunkard.
Go away.
I'm serious.
Good morning.
What's he doing?
He's gone.
Eat all of that.
Thank you.
Let's get the injured one.
What's wrong?
I don't want the injured one.
Go home.
Thank you for your hard work.
I don't know.
I didn't know you were like that.
I took him out of the house.
It's okay.
Eat.
This is grilled cod.
Is this grilled cod?
Yes.
It's good.
I'll leave it to you.
All right.
The crab...
What?
What's wrong?
Let's have a big crab fight.
But it's not a big crab fight.
What?
Pickles.
Pickles?
Why don't you eat pickles in a crab fight?
I don't know.
I'll have this cucumber.
Why are you eating so much?
I'll have a cucumber.
I don't want the injured one.
Cucumber is good.
Bring the menu.
Menu?
I don't need the menu.
I'm full.
You're full, right?
I'm not full.
There's this much left.
But I can't say it anymore.
I can't say it.
I don't care about that.
Hey.
What are you eating?
It's a fish, isn't it?
You're still eating?
Why?
You're doing this on purpose.
Who is this guy?
This is...
You know it.
That's right.
I know.
What is it?
Why are you eating so much?
You're full.
Did you eat it all by yourself?
Hey.
Let's take a look at each one.
There's a lot.
You can't do this.
Right?
If you have an interesting idea,
it's better to double it or triple it.
I've never said anything about money.
Right?
I'm sorry, but the two of you
will have to do it with your emotions.
I'm sorry.
Next week, let's use all the money
and do it comfortably.
Excuse me.
It's hard to eat.
Hey, Mr. Hamaya.
Yes?
Mr. Hamaya.
What is it?
In the opening song,
if it's this exciting,
it's good enough.
Is this the end?
It's already very exciting.
If we stand like this,
everyone will jump around.
Isn't this good enough?
It's good if we stand like this.
That's right.
I have to say this before I forget.
You're trying to run away, aren't you?
There's a punishment game.
But, Mr. Hamaya,
it's already very exciting.
If you keep doing this,
you'll be like this.
You'll eat mochi and be like this.
You can't do that.
There's a punishment game.
I wonder if it'll be difficult.
Is that so?
But I'm starting to move.
In the real sense,
in the real sense,
from morning to night,
everyone will be on TV.
Don't overdo it.
From morning to night.
I've already decided what to do.
Downtown, 8th anniversary.
Everyone will be on TV.
From morning to night.
Let's start with the first one.
It's getting cold.
It's okay if it's cold.
Downtown, 8th anniversary.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to make you forget that.
I didn't mean to make you forget that.
I just didn't like the feeling of being tied up like this.
But, it's not like that.
You can't do that.
What the hell is this?
Who did this?
Who did you do this with?
That's a high-profile attitude.
You're an idiot.
Is there anything else?
You have too many things you don't like.
But, if you don't do things you don't like,
you can't become a punishment game.
I said this in English.
If you do things you don't like,
you become a punishment game.
That's why you want to be happy.
No, no, no.
I don't want to be a punishment game.
You might get sick.
What?
Me?
You might get a chance to play with a dangerous woman.
You don't want that, do you?
I don't want to be punished.
Well, you'll be punished.
I don't want to be punished either way.
The three principles of comparison in Japan are
not to be made, not to be held, not to be brought in.
But, did you know?
Matsumoto-san's...
Non-commentator.
Good evening.
Matsumoto-san, what are the three principles of dandyism?
Yes.
I want to be a dandy, so please tell me.
You want to be a dandy, don't you, Sora?
Everyone wants to be a dandy.
You want to be a dandy, don't you?
No.
Do you have dandyism in your mind?
I want to be a dandy,
but how can I be a dandy?
I don't know.
I see.
But for me,
the three principles of dandyism are always there.
Do you have dandyism in your mind?
No, no.
I don't know.
More than I have dandyism in my mind,
dandy is calling me a dandy.
I didn't ask for dandyism,
but dandy came to me.
Isn't that completely different?
Hmm...
Do you understand?
So dandy came to you.
Yes, dandy came to me.
So you don't have your own three principles.
I don't have them,
but I want to tell the children of the future,
this is what dandyism is.
What is dandyism?
I want to tell them not to leave it.
I see.
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
It will enter the 21st century.
If I die like this,
dandyism in the 20th century will be over,
but dandyism in the 21st century will be gone.
I see.
I was very sad about that.
So I cried in the kitchen.
You should have cried in a bigger place.
You should have told us at the end.
These three principles and dandyism are very similar.
They are similar.
I can say that they are almost the same.
I see.
But on top of that,
there is a word called poop.
What is dandyism?
You can say it.
First, it means not to make.
This is dandyism.
You can't take poop with you.
You have to take it out more and more.
What is dandyism?
You can't say it.
You understand this, right?
Yes.
Not to make.
Not to take.
You can't take poop with you.
What is dandyism?
You can't take poop with you and say,
Good morning.
That's dandyism.
Who would say that?
No one would.
That's what it means, right?
Think about that a little more.
And then...
What?
What is the last one?
Not to take.
For example, when you're at home,
I'm a dandy.
A friend comes and says,
Oh, Masumoto!
And he takes poop with him.
And he says,
Oh, come in!
Who would say that?
I have poop with me!
I'll say it at the station show in town.
You have poop with you, don't you?
What does your house look like?
I don't like it.
First of all,
First of all, you don't open the door.
You don't press the open button.
That's...
It's not just you, it's everyone.
So I think the person who protects these three is a dandy.
Everyone?
I'm protecting you.
You're not protecting me.
When did you take it?
I've never taken it.
You're saying weird things.
Then the guest is good.
You can be a dandy.
Wait a minute.
Why?
I'll press the dandy button.
Press me, too.
To Yoyogi Park.
That's fine.
Why did you have to go to Yoyogi Park?
It's Yoyogi Park.
You have to press it one by one.
Oh, you're a dandy.
What's this?
Wait a minute.
If you don't have poop with you, don't you?
What are you talking about?
Oh, you're a dandy.
But I can't press it for you.
Why?
I've never had poop with me.
Press the dandy button.
I have it.
You have it.
I don't have it.
You just don't have it now.
You used to have poop with you, too.
Think about it.
You don't have poop with you.
You've never been to the scene, have you?
I've never been to the scene.
That's because I'm getting used to it.
But I always have it on my day off.
I've never seen you.
Yes, I've been to your house.
I've been to your kitchen.
I've got all the families.
In America, each typhoon has a name like Mitchie, Johnny.
If the typhoon in Japan had a name like Nino Matsumoto, what would the first one be?
I see.
Japan is lame.
They really don't have a sense of humor.
Ah, is that so?
After all, Americans think that they can play with a typhoon, right?
They think that they can get caught in it, right?
If it's that kind of name...
As expected, Americans think like that, right?
Japanese people are scared of typhoons, so they say,
Tojimari, be careful!
Listen to the typhoon information well!
Are you serious?
No, I'm serious!
That's really good!
It's big, it's small, it's a little small...
What kind of way of saying that is?
Eh, isn't there a name for Japan?
If it's number 16...
Ah, what number?
What number is it?
Before number 16,
What kind of typhoon came out?
Number 15!
It's just like that!
What is that?
If it comes next time, it's number 17!
If it comes next time, it's number 18!
No, it's number 18!
What do you mean, no?
Well, it can't be left out.
It can't be left out?
It can't be left out!
I'm angry about that.
What about the name?
Put it in front of me!
You really shouldn't have said that.
You're angry, but you don't know?
I don't know!
You put in a name!
Well, eh...
Mr. President!
This year's typhoon, Mr. President!
Can't you say it like that, Mr. President?
A big one, a really big one...
Mr. President!
The typhoon of the wave...
Can't you say it like that?
Even if it comes up to number 17,
how are you going to put it on?
Even if you say it, there's nothing left.
There's a lot, right?
Mr. President, Mr. President, Mr. President...
But it's not like that anymore!
Mr. President!
I can't say it.
Why can't you say it?
Why can't you say it now?
Mr. President...
In Okinawa, in the southwest,
Mr. President is coming now.
This year's President is scary, so please be careful.
Mr. President has finally turned into a typhoon.
The secretary has turned into a woman.
Mr. President has turned into a typhoon.
That's the answer to the actual question!
I know!