In the first episode of Gakyu no Tsukai, we're going to celebrate our 10th anniversary!
Mokutte Mokutte Scuba Diving!
Hey, Gakyu no Tsukai!
Hey, hey, hey!
Say something!
We're doing something rude!
It's just a bad thing.
Say something!
What are you doing?!
Is this okay?!
You're doing it the wrong way.
It's our 10th anniversary!
I see.
We're going to have a scuba diving experience!
What?
Challenge!
Do it!
Let's take a commemorative photo underwater.
I see.
I've never done it before.
That's why we're doing it!
You're bad at it, so we're doing it!
The engine's running.
You're bad at it, so you've never done it before, right?
So take off your hat!
Wait a minute!
That's why we're doing the scuba diving!
Yes, yes!
Yes!
I'd like everyone to see my scuba diving.
This is...
Why are you doing it?
This is my second time.
I've done it twice.
Do you have a license?
I don't need a license for scuba diving.
You do!
I don't need it.
How about you, Tanaka?
I've done it three times.
You've done it three times?
Really?
Where did you do it?
I went to Ishigaki Island.
That's not true. I went to Australia.
Australia!
Really?
Australia is a mountain.
Australia, right?
Australia.
Australia!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
This time, the scuba diving will take place in the OK Marine Pro 5m deep pool.
As you can see, this is the first time Hamada and Endo have dived only twice.
Will they be able to take photos underwater?
Yamachan's scuba diving!
Thank you.
This is the first time I've taught you.
If you teach me something strange here, I'll kill you.
That's right.
If you do it half-heartedly...
I'll never do it half-heartedly.
First of all...
It's normal, right?
It's really half-heartedly.
First of all, you can't lick the sea.
It's written in red.
You can't lick the sea.
Yes.
It's normal.
Why?
You can't lick the sea.
That's all I'm going to say.
Hey!
Don't laugh!
I'm just saying the same thing over and over again.
Is that okay?
Yes.
Please put this in the corner of your head.
In the corner?
Isn't it the most important thing to write in red?
Just put it in the corner.
You can't lick the sea.
Next!
Next is the name of the scuba equipment.
First of all, the mask.
The underwater mask.
I'm definitely going to use the underwater mask.
And the regulator.
The regulator is the tail of the mouth.
The tail of the mouth?
What is the tail of the mouth?
That's where you breathe.
And the auxiliary air source.
This is written as the source of the air.
It's called the air source.
No, it's not.
It's not that.
Tell me what it is.
It's a special case.
What kind of thing is this?
This is the pressure gauge of the air pressure.
This is how much air is left.
Next is the basic knowledge of diving.
First of all, the knowledge to average the pressure.
If you remember discomfort when you dive.
What kind of thing is discomfort?
You have discomfort, right?
What do you mean?
I feel a little uncomfortable now.
Ear removal.
Please remove your ear.
If you can't remove your ear properly.
The eardrum in the back.
You'll break it.
I can't do it.
I won't explain it in English anymore.
Please tell me how to remove your ear.
Please close your nose.
It's your first time, right?
It's my first time, too.
You have to do it.
You're going to break your eardrum.
Close your mouth.
Don't you put this in when you dive?
I put it in.
I put it in, but my ears...
Do you put your nose like this?
Yes, please put your nose in.
But your nose is like this.
It's like a mask.
But the mask has a hole so that the nose can be pinched.
Is that so?
Did you have a hole?
Don't you have a hole?
You're all starting.
It's from above, right?
If you have a hole, you'll have a hole.
There's a hole.
The mask has a dent to make it easier to pinch the nose, not a hole.
How do you do it?
I breathe in like this, and then I breathe out like this.
It's hard to understand.
Breathe in, and then breathe out like this.
When you take out your ears, you have to look down, pinch your nose, and when you bite your nose, you have to push the air out.
You can do it when you're on a plane and your ears hurt.
You have to feel the air coming out of your ears.
No, I can't do this.
You can't do this.
If you can't do this, you'll never be able to dive.
I don't think I can dive.
Please do it, Mr. Amada.
This is also important.
Next is the lungs.
You go down like this, right?
There's a bubble that comes up, right?
If you go further than that, your lungs will burst, and you'll get sick.
Really?
If that's the case, I'll quit.
There's a lot of diseases.
Are you okay?
If you go further than that, you'll get sick.
You'll get sick.
Are you okay?
It's like an illness.
It's called a diving disease.
Really?
Isn't that a disease?
It's like this.
I don't know what's going to happen next.
What?
What's going to happen next?
If you go up suddenly, your lungs won't be able to withstand the change in air pressure.
Don't panic.
Slowly continue to go up while breathing.
Next is a hand signal that is important to protect yourself in the water.
It's a trouble signal.
This is it.
Matsumoto-san, this is it.
It was really like this in Buramo.
Lastly, it's time for Yamazaki-sensei's question corner.
Okay, then.
Okay, end.
Today is a poll, so it's like this.
If sharks come out, what should we do?
When sharks come out, I'll definitely meet them.
What?
That's right.
If they come out, I'll meet them.
If you encounter sharks, don't panic.
Wait for them to pass by the rocks nearby.
What if you catch a shark's leg?
When I catch a shark's leg, I'll definitely meet them.
What?
What if I catch a shark's leg?
What if you catch a shark's leg?
I'll remove the regulator and the fins.
I'll remove everything.
I'll be naked.
It's a festival.
It's a diving festival.
I'll be naked.
You're wearing a suit and practicing in the pool.
You're the opposite.
Zaki-san.
Are you okay?
First, get used to the water.
It's something that can be removed neatly.
It's amazing.
Okay.
Let's go.
Why do you keep looking at me?
You're always looking at me.
What are you doing?
You can't turn around at all.
It's amazing.
You're always looking at us.
I'll show you how to swim.
What?
You did it, didn't you?
Contact.
This is so much fun.
This is so cool.
This is amazing.
I'm already floating.
I can do it with this.
It feels good.
This is amazing.
This is so much fun.
I can do it with this.
This is an important ear removal exercise.
Let's go.
Please come out.
You can do it, right?
Yes.
You can do it.
You're fast.
I did it, but I don't know what happened.
It doesn't hurt yet, does it?
I can't do it.
I want to put it in.
But it's too deep.
It's too deep.
I'm scared.
I'm going to do it here.
You're lying.
This is so sad.
And he's wearing a scuba suit.
I'm going to break my ankle.
He's going to break his ankle.
Pink.
Pink?
I've been very happy up to here.
Let's go.
I'm going to dive if I have time.
OK.
Hamada is showing a high tension.
Will he be able to make it to the commemorative photo?
Why are you laughing?
You should be a professional.
What are you doing?
It's a butterfly knot.
No!
It's a shoulder knot.
Next is breathing training underwater.
From the top of the hose.
From where?
From the bottom.
From the top of the hose.
This is Hamada's first challenge.
I can't do it.
You can do it, right?
If you can't do it here, you can't do it here.
Hamada is getting used to the water while practicing several times.
The other members are breathing in the water.
So far, everyone is doing well in scuba diving.
I'm the only one who's breathing in the water.
It's too much water.
Too much water?
I think I'll be fine today.
I'll show you how to swim.
Is this okay?
It's okay.
Hamada, are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'd like to learn how to deal with the water in the mask.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Listen carefully.
Are you listening?
Yes, I'm listening.
You're not listening.
I'm listening.
There are times when water comes into the mask.
When the water comes in, push it up and take it out.
Do it.
I'm just making a sound.
It's coming out.
Put the squid in.
It's in.
It's scary, isn't it?
It's coming out.
There are other ways to deal with water problems.
Next, I'll teach you how to remove the regulator.
What do you mean?
Maybe you can remove the regulator.
No, it's not like that.
Do it properly.
Why do I have to remove it?
Remove it once.
If you bump into it.
And then the other regulator.
There's another one.
Give it to the person next to you.
If you remove it in here, the water will come in together.
There's this button, right?
Yeah.
Push it hard.
Push it once.
And then the air won't go in.
What?
The water won't go in.
What are you talking about?
You're going to kill me.
I'm about to die.
I won't kill you.
The water won't go in.
Oh, that's what it is.
I see.
It's so big.
Let's try it.
I'll do it first.
Really?
Everyone is passing the regulator to the person next to them in the water.
Will they succeed?
Don't make me laugh.
Please remove it.
How is it?
Listen to me.
You're not letting me do it.
I'm doing it, but you're not letting me do it.
It's not going well at all.
He's being taught by everyone and he's doing it alone.
Put it in like this.
Put it in?
Yes.
And then add this.
If you do it like this, it'll be fine.
Ready, start.
You're weak.
You changed your character.
Is it okay?
Ready, start.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
I did it.
Let's go to the last gate.
Let's take a commemorative photo at the pool.
It doesn't have to be there.
No, no, no, let's take it there.
This is my ideal.
That's right.
I understand your ideal.
This is impossible.
There's a bench down there.
That might be true, but I can't go that far.
Dan-dan-san.
I'm in the middle.
Put it here.
Is this called a goggles?
Yes.
Do I take this off with my tongue?
Yes, take it off.
What?
This is the ideal.
I want you to take it off.
It's okay.
With Mr. Waraka.
If it ends with a tongue, it'll be like this.
That's dangerous.
Then I'd like to do it now.
Yes.
First of all, for example, if something happens.
When you get sick or get hurt.
I'll make sure that this person is responsible.
It's my own responsibility.
I'll take it off.
Say it to the camera.
It's crazy.
It means you're the one who's bad.
Right?
It's my fault.
It doesn't matter to me.
You did it, right?
Okay, I'm done.
Okay.
So, 5 meters.
If you go 5 meters, your head will explode.
Dan-dan, let's have two people take it off.
Just the two of us?
When?
After everyone takes it off.
The two of us who remain.
Only Dan-dan.
This is the pose.
A funny pose.
This is a 5-meter-long shooting set.
One by one, they go down to this place.
First of all, Yamazaki.
Good luck.
It hurts.
Let's do it one by one.
It went.
5 meters.
It's amazing.
He's crazy.
He's an idiot.
I'm going.
Why can you stand on the ground?
If I go down, I'll break.
Really?
Hurry up.
I'm a gay.
I don't get it.
I'm getting more confident.
This is impossible.
My head will explode.
It's a shocking video.
I don't care if my head explodes on a TV program.
Can I put this on?
Sure.
That's it.
Yes.
I can't use this.
I've been doing this for 10 years.
You did a good job.
It was fun today.
I've been doing this for 10 years.
It was really fun today.
Thank you very much.
I'll prepare a meal for you later.
Can they take a 5-meter-long commemorative photo?
There are only two people left in downtown.
If Hamada can't go, I can't go.
Let's go.
It's okay.
Hamada failed to take a picture.
I think I can do it.
It's hard.
Hamada failed.
Put the pen down.
It's hard.
This is easy.
Let's go.
I feel like I can hear it.
There it is.
It's going.
It's going up.
My ears hurt.
I can't do it.
My head is about to explode.
They failed again.
I'll try it.
My head and ears hurt.
Take a deep breath.
My ears hurt.
Matsumoto also failed.
It's hard to go down to the bottom.
Matsumoto will do a side challenge.
Matsumoto did his best.
Hamada is the only one left.
And the last challenge.
Hamada is doing his best to take a picture.
The photo was taken after this.
Is it taken?
Can't you see it?
There is a hose on the neck.
I can't move.
It looks like it's done.
It's the 10th anniversary.
It's a beautiful photo.
I'm sure it's good.
I'll take a picture.
I was looking at everyone from above.
I'm counting on you.
It's a photo for the viewer as a gift, right?
Of course.
I've been pinching my nose all the time.
This challenge was done by Downtown, which is always said to be cowardly.
Their courage impressed us.
Thank you, Downtown.
This is a memorable photo.
And a wonderful downtown two-shot.