Chikizuki's new year special episode
Masato vs Amada 3 rounds
I'm not going to lose
It's new year
The first round is flying box
Amada vs Masato
I'm going to let you two fly
Are you ready?
Let's do it
First, Hamada will fly this box
I got it
It's about 5 rounds
Next is Hitoshi Matsumoto's challenge
Hitoshi Matsumoto's challenge
Why did you blow up the box?
It's burning
What's going on?
You just blew up the box
Why?
The neck too
It's okay if you get hurt
Put your head down
Are you okay?
What are we going to do?
If you blow up the box
Why did you blow up the box?
Is something wrong?
It's cold
I've never blown up the box
What's that?
What's going on?
Wait a minute
I got it
Should I think about it?
I'm not feeling well
You don't have to blow up the box
My body hurts
It's burning
My stomach hurts
There's a lot left
This is like my adventure
What are we going to do?
There's no opening in the new year
But I think the same thing happened to the box
It's different
I prepared a throw
You just have to throw it
You don't have to run
Can you do it?
Don't use that
It's not fashionable
I'm worried about my parents
Should we start from the head?
The hair is not connected
Can you hide it with lighting?
We can edit it
The first special program
Matsumoto vs Hamada
I'm going to win
It's the new year
I'm going to start from Hamada
It's going to fall
I won
14m
Thank you
I can't lose
Hitoshi Matsumoto is going to start
Hitoshi Matsumoto's hammer throw
Start
Smoke is coming out
It's coming out
It's scary
Again?
It's a big fish
You should have told me
It's fine
Why is it exploding?
We can't pay for the fish
It's only for Hamada
He's in the hospital
He's going to Yoshimoto
You should have told me
I'm going to fight
It's not like that
I'm going to the hospital
Sorry
It tastes bad
Are you okay?
I don't know
Why is it exploding?
I can't stand it
Why are you laughing?
I'm not laughing
I'm scared
I can't recommend it
What should I do?
I can't use this
How about water?
How many times can you do it?
Is that okay?
It's okay
You should have told me
Why are you wearing the other side?
What are you doing?
You can't talk with that head
It's only 30 seconds
Let's take a picture
The hair doesn't fit
It's useless
Are you worried about your hair?
Don't kick it
Cut it
Let's do it
I can't do it
Ladies and gentlemen
Please change your mind
This year
It's the first time
I'm getting older
I went somewhere
Where?
Vancouver
It was hard
What do you mean?
I was surprised
I was watching it at home
I didn't expect it
I didn't imagine it
It was different
I was surprised
Really?
I thought you were going to cut the wire
It was like this
Why didn't you cut it?
I was surprised
What did you wear?
It was amazing
You looked like you were growing up
I was surprised
It was hard
I went to Hong Kong for the end of the year
It was good
But I woke up
I was really scared
I was sleeping like I was going to die
You were tired
I was really tired
There was a bed
I was sleeping like this
I went in
I was lying down
I was sleeping like this
I told him to lie down
I looked at him
I didn't know he was Jimmy
I thought he was a crazy guy from Hong Kong
I was surprised
I looked at him
What?
Everyone was looking at me
The staff
The staff was looking at me
I didn't know
What?
I didn't know what was going on
There were many people looking at me
I was really scared
You too
I didn't know what was going on
But I still didn't understand
I was surprised
I looked at him
My body
I was surprised
I didn't know what was going on
Why are you sleeping like this?
What?
He's an old man
He's just an old man
Why are you sleeping like this?
What is this?
This is really funny
After breakfast, everyone went out
I didn't know what was going on
I still didn't understand
I felt like I was being bullied
I felt like I was being made a fool
Everyone was surrounding you
I felt like I was being rude
I was really upset
Why?
I felt like I was being really treated well
I wanted to throw up
You can throw up
It felt so refreshing
You're lying
Don't do that
It was like he went down refreshingly.
Stop it.
I don't want to wake up.
Well, this year too,
the musical instrument will continue like this.
That's right.
Ah, that's right.
I still don't know what happened to Kouhaku.
If Hamada loses, the punishment for this year won't be funny.
That's right.
It's a nose-shaped punishment.
Eh, wait a minute.
Eh, are you peeling off the skin?
It's a skin.
The nose?
Yes, the nose.
Right?
That's no good.
Yes, yes.
That's why I'm going to cut this part.
It's going to be a crooked red tail.
That's good though.
What should I do?
I see.
It's going to be a big deal.
Are you going to write a letter?
Yes, I'm going to.
That's good.
The other day,
when I was in the car,
there was a guy who forced himself into a narrow alley.
There's a lot of people.
I don't know why he was in such a hurry,
but I thought he was going to come out like this,
so he came out like this.
If he had waited for me here,
I wouldn't have been able to get out like this.
Because it's narrow.
Yes, yes, yes.
He's coming.
He's really coming.
It's like this.
I can't help it.
Really?
Yes.
I can't help it.
I was just about to fall.
The driver's seat and I were here, right?
This is the driver's seat, right?
Yes.
I've been holding out so far,
but I'm getting more and more angry.
When the last body came here,
I stopped it.
Open it like this.
Open it.
The body.
I went out.
It's a narrow alleyway.
He said he was going to make a U-turn and come right away.
Oh, I see.
You didn't know your face,
so you just made a U-turn.
Touch it, touch it.
What is it?
It's a car.
Really.
I've said it many times.
Shinjuku.
In front of Lumine.
The road is wide, isn't it?
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm going to the tunnel over there.
Yes, I'm going.
At that time, everyone tried to turn to Shinjuku.
Isetan, Hokon.
Yes, yes, yes.
At that time, most of them turned left.
But everyone stopped turning left.
What do you mean, everyone turned left?
It's a reverse triangle in front of Lumine.
I want to go right away.
Come a little closer and go in.
What is it?
Is it like that every time?
It's like that every time.
I can't go straight at all.
Then you should turn too.
Why am I going to Isetan's pet shop?
Why is it a pet shop?
I went to Isetan's pet shop.
I don't know.
Then you should go.
Stop it.
If it's like that every time, you should change the road.
I can only use this on Sunday.
Because it's all that.
Because it's a pet shop.
That's right.
Let's go.
By the way.
Let me tell you the best comic book.
Stop the pet shop.
What is it?
Who would be happy with that?
I was walking while eating cup noodles.
In the 1950s.
From Shinjuku.
From Harajuku.
What is it?
Right?
I did everything.
I don't know.
Who is that?
What?
Pet shop?
Who is the pet shop?
Right?
I have to go to the TV show on Sunday.
You don't say I.
A year ago, you predicted the lack of glasses.
How was the result?
What will happen this year?
If you predict like that, the whole country will panic.
But you said the lack of glasses last year.
What will happen this year?
At the end of January, there will be a drop hole boom.
Boom?
I want to tell you one thing.
When you are walking on the street,
like pineapple,
or when you see a banana, don't get close to it.
Don't get close to the leaves.
I know.
It's unnatural.
I can't help it if you say it in January.
I have to tell you one thing.
I got it.
A bus gas explosion.
That's not it.
A new beast.
It is said to be the biggest enemy for humans.
A wild dog.
If you leave it alone, it will die on its own.
You don't have to deal with it.
At first, it's scary.
It will bite you.
But it will die on its own.
And it will bite you.
That's scary.
If it bites you, it's scary.
It's scary.
That's scary.
It's like a disaster.
You know that, right?
Yes, I know.
On the Earth,
there is a huge planet.
It's a huge planet.
It will bite you.
What kind of planet is on the Earth?
Hey!
It's much bigger than the Earth.
It will bite you.
It's scary.
And it will bite you.
What?
What's that?
And it will rub you.
It will rub you.
It's a planet, isn't it?
Shut up.
The trip to Australia on the Earth,
어요
This is interesting.
Mr. Matsumoto was kidnapped by an alien
because he found out the secret of NASA.
Please tell me about that incident.
I was surprised. I was driving by myself.
I don't know how to say it.
Light!
Simply put, it's a disc.
You can't say it's a disc!
I don't know how to say it!
You said it's light!
It's a disc type.
What type?
There's a lot.
But it's a disc type.
It's a disc type.
No!
It comes out like this.
There's a reason for it.
It's like a movie.
I don't think there's a reason for it.
It comes out like this.
An old man was sucked up.
Did you see the bottom?
An old man came out again.
It seems to have been a mistake.
I raised it once and said it was wrong.
It's a mistake with me.
I was sucked up.
What is it?
It's a one-room.
It's not that big.
The floor is floor.
How many people were there?
47 or 48?
It's a one-room.
Don't raise it.
Raise it when you can afford it.
I was surprised.
An old man came out.
Wait a minute.
Open it.
I met him.
I was told not to say it.
I suddenly got into it.
Don't say it.
I'm scared.
I was told not to say it.
How many people were there in the one-room?
I can't say it.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.