The 1st Gaki no Tsukai Arrangement 100th Anniversary Live Broadcast Special!
And, Suga-chan!
And thank you, Suga-chan, and goodbye!
The 1st Gaki no Tsukai Arrangement 100th Anniversary Live Broadcast Special!
Now, Masato-kun.
Yes.
Let's go.
What the hell!
So, that's what it is.
Yes, yes, yes.
100th Anniversary.
That's right.
Well, to commemorate, today is a live broadcast.
Yes.
Starting at 1.40.
Yes, yes, yes.
We're doing it.
Will you ask me what the meaning of this is?
Oh, what is this painting?
Well, our artist thought of this.
Well, look.
Kan'ichi Omiya.
Say it backwards.
Yes.
It's a 1-million-yen-diamond Megakurami, so it's worth 1-hundred-yen.
Don't say such nonsense!
Who thought of this? Who thought of this?
Kid?
No, it's not me.
Eh, Takasu?
It's not me.
Who?
Motoichi?
No, no, no.
Who thought of this?
Suzuki?
No, it's not me.
What do you mean, who? It's you!
No, I didn't think of this. Who?
No, I don't know who.
It's definitely Kid.
Cover, cover.
And then?
Kid is still on tour, isn't he?
That's right.
And in commemoration of the 100th anniversary,
the staff said,
Congratulations on the 100th anniversary.
What is this?
Today is such a big day.
Your birthday cake was big, too.
Yes.
This is the 100th anniversary.
Well, there's only one.
Ah, I see.
Well, it's a simple feeling.
I borrowed it.
Stop it.
Something like this.
What do you call it?
It's cold.
Right?
It's handwritten again.
Well, that's it.
Today is a live broadcast.
Of course, there's only 30 minutes left.
If we don't go on and on, we won't have time.
That's true.
Today is also a live broadcast.
It's a dream live broadcast.
I see.
This is also a dressing room.
This is the venue where everyone is coming.
And Team Zero.
It's raining in the Kanto region today.
They're not from the Kanto region.
Is that so?
Let's call them.
Team Zero.
Yes.
What are they doing?
It's 1 o'clock and 40 minutes.
What?
Team Zero.
Yes.
You can't hear the audience's laughter.
I can't hear it at all.
It's slippery.
It's beautiful.
The slippery entertainer is beautiful.
This program is brought to you by the sponsor you are watching.
Hello, hello, hello.
No, no, no, no.
Mr. Kyo.
No.
Now, please.
Mr. Kyo.
Yes, yes.
Yes.
Today.
Yes, yes.
100 times.
It's noisy.
I'll show it to you later, so wait.
Yes.
In this program, we don't show the audience.
We don't show it at all.
Today, we want to show it to everyone.
It's special.
Yes.
Hey, sister.
Put your underwear on.
Oh, really?
I'll show it to you later.
So, yes, yes.
I'll go on and on.
Yes.
Today is the 100th anniversary.
100th anniversary.
And the time has changed again.
Yes.
This 1 o'clock and 40 minutes will start.
Today is the last episode.
That's right.
Yes.
I'll show it to Golden.
To Golden.
I'll show it at 11 o'clock.
Yes.
Everyone is here.
Yes, yes.
I'm getting my shoes wet.
Are you okay?
I'll be okay this time.
Really?
Yes.
Okay, so let's do it, okay?
Let's do it together.
One, two.
3, 4, 5, 6.
Now.
That was different.
What?
I guess the 2nd Par Man won't come here.
The 2nd Par Man is desperate today.
Is he desperate?
Today, Team Zero is doing the clock with flowers.
Yes, they're doing it.
Really, that single part should be the 2nd Par Man.
It should be, shouldn't it?
What's he good at?
That man is good at drawing.
He's got a long nose.
That's right.
He has a long nose.
Let's do it.
What is he drawing?
It's too short.
That's too short.
That's right. What's that guy doing?
That guy is showing off his balls like he's so proud of himself.
Today, we'll be working hard on that.
So today, everyone at the venue came to celebrate our 100th episode.
100 people.
And then again,
100 people, with the same look.
And then, we have a bunch of idiots here.
Alright, camera-san, this is the first time in this program that we've received 100 seats!
This is the first time we've received 100 seats!
Well, by having these guys here, we've come one step closer to Kin-chan.
Today, we're really like a virtual grand prize, aren't we?
We're like a virtual grand prize, aren't we?
We've all come here wearing the same outfit as the 100th episode.
Just by looking at them, it's almost impossible to tell which one is which.
That's right.
So we have to look at that side as well.
Let's look at what we're interested in.
What are you?
What am I?
That's right, the 100th episode.
We are Shin-donburi.
I see.
There's one that's wearing the same outfit, right?
The lion, right?
The lion of the 100th episode.
That's right.
This kid is amazing.
I think this kid is working really hard.
You're wearing the 100th episode outfit.
I'm wearing the 100th episode outfit all over my body.
Are you stupid?
I think I'm a little stupid.
I'm sorry.
I've come all the way here.
What about you three?
What's that?
Say something!
Who told you to keep doing that?
Speak!
Have a talk!
It's a yaku-don.
A yaku-don?
I see.
I don't understand what you're saying.
You saw it, right?
The 100th episode, right?
I see.
And...
And you, your girlfriend?
What?
The 100th episode outfit.
What are you talking about?
Are you sleepy?
I think I'm a little ugly.
What?
I can't think of a face when you say that.
And...
She doesn't sit down.
She doesn't sit down properly.
Look at her.
She's a peach.
I can tell.
What are you?
You.
What's the number?
10-19.
What?
I don't know.
I think she's having a head crash.
You've seen it a lot, right?
What's the number she gave you?
You're Hyakumoto.
Wow.
That's a school uniform.
You're Hyakumoto?
You're writing things that are not Hyakumoto.
I see.
That's a rare name.
Is that so?
That's right.
What's behind you?
These guys are scary.
Hey!
Don't poke me.
What's that?
That thing that looks like Frankenstein.
What?
What's that?
Is that Boo-chan?
I don't think so.
What's after that?
That hand.
What's that?
One hundred.
Go home!
Your hand is red.
One hundred.
I see.
What's with you guys?
I'm sorry.
Please go home.
I don't want to see you anymore.
He's crying.
One hundred percent juice.
What's that?
Hyakuyobaka.
I see.
The school's...
Salusberry.
Hyakunichiko.
Hyakujite.
I see.
There are dangerous guys.
I'd like to show you how to do it.
Really?
Yes.
What's that?
It's a cake.
What are you doing?
Who are you?
Say sorry.
This is an experiment.
We've done this show a hundred times.
I thought it would be best for everyone to put out the fire.
I see.
But the stage is not a comedian, so I can't lift it.
The stage is not a comedian, so you can't lift it?
I can't lift it.
So please blow out a hundred people from that place.
If we all work together, we can do it.
It's also an experiment.
That's right.
Now, everyone.
Come on.
Do it.
One, two.
Blow out.
You guys stink.
Don't blow out.
Do your best.
Blow out.
One, two.
It was delicious.
If you blow out, it will be exciting again.
Okay, let's go.
One, two.
A little more.
There's a lot of wind.
He did it.
I wanted to show the viewers that moment.
But it disappeared.
Now, blow out.
That's all.
Today, we have a lot of food from the viewers.
Food?
We'll eat it.
Please bring it.
Here you go.
What are you doing?
It was delicious.
I didn't expect you to prepare this.
I ran away from the parking lot this morning.
You were still like this.
I was still like this.
Hello.
Long time no see.
Thank you for inviting me.
What are you doing at home?
You're late.
I'm sorry.
You're always sleeping, right?
Yes.
What have you been doing since you were carried away by a rope?
Since then?
Say it quickly.
What have you been doing since then?
Since then?
I've been doing something at home.
You're noisy.
You.
You're so noisy.
I'm glad you're wearing glasses.
What are you doing?
Thank you very much.
We're doing this together, but Yuya is the only one.
He's a regular.
Yes.
I've received a lot.
I have to introduce this.
Is that so?
I've heard about it, but you don't know it, right?
I've received a message.
Congratulations on the 100th anniversary.
As a comedian and as a friend, I sincerely support Hama's activities.
Come to my house next time.
The head of the village isn't angry anymore.
Hayashiya Kobuhei.
Really?
I really came.
Kobu-chan.
Is that so?
We're best friends.
That's strange.
Yes.
We're very close.
I heard that you were digging and being dug.
Are you stupid?
Thank you very much.
I've received a lot of messages.
That's how it is.
It's finally time for the main subject.
I've said it before, right?
Everyone watching TV, too.
Today, for those who came to the venue, I have a wonderful present.
But, I can't give it to everyone.
Only one of these 100 people.
Go home.
It's a 1 in 100 chance.
That's the only wonderful thing.
This is really amazing.
That's right.
If I had it, I wouldn't be able to say it.
It's an expression that can't be broadcasted.
Sharara used to drink tea in the old VTR.
That's not true.
It's a wonderful thing.
Everyone said that.
What?
Ah, I see.
Let's take a look at the clock.
Is that so?
Yes.
Here it comes.
It's raining.
Everyone, please go to bed.
It's almost 2 o'clock.
What time is it?
Not yet?
One more minute.
It's raining a lot.
Yes.
It was raining during the rehearsal.
It was raining a lot during the rehearsal.
They were soaked during the rehearsal.
When I came back to the dressing room...
Hey!
When I came back to the dressing room, I took off my raincoat.
I didn't walk like that.
What are you doing?
Are you all right?
Yes.
I have an injury.
I have water in my legs.
What?
Don't point at me.
I have to lower my back.
Is that so?
Let's go a little further.
Yes.
It's already 2 o'clock.
Today is really amazing.
How many seconds do we have left?
Two seconds.
Let's go a little further after 2 o'clock.
Let's go a little further.
The time is 1.59.30.
It's a long time.
The time is 1.59.
It's a waste of time.
I can't help it.
It's 2 o'clock.
It's not the time to fall.
The time is 1.59.50.
I'm counting on you.
The time is 2 o'clock.
Hurry up.
It's over.
It's 2 o'clock.
The water was coming out, but I couldn't tell because of my back voice.
It's okay.
Now, I have a wonderful present for you.
This is...
Are you really going to do it?
I'm a little nervous.
Everyone, please listen quietly.
Okay?
Don't move.
Until I say yes.
Okay?
Actually...
Today...
What are you laughing at?
How should I say it?
Right?
Actually...
I have a wonderful present for one person.
That's right.
Don't move. Don't move.
Even if you say that, I won't take it.
The chair...
The chair you're sitting on.
Don't move.
Down...
It's not down. It's around here.
I said don't move!
But that's the person who's sitting on that chair.
Do you understand?
Don't take it.
It's that chair.
If you don't have it, it's over.
Don't move!
To celebrate the 100th anniversary...
Yes.
The only person you're sitting on...
Under the chair...
Yes.
There's 1 million yen attached to it!
Look!
It's his money!
Find it! Find it!
Look at the back and the sides.
There it is!
Find it!
It's not a lie. It's true.
Yes.
Congratulations.
Show it to me.
Look!
This is yours.
It's true!
Wait a minute.
10,000 yen each!
What do you mean, 10,000 yen each?
It's no good.
We've thought of a lot of presents.
I think this will make them the happiest.
What's your name?
I'm Sekiguchi.
Sekiguchi-san?
How old are you?
I'm 21.
Do you work?
Yes.
It's 1 million yen.
What should I do?
I don't want to!
I invited them.
You invited them?
Why? Why?
I invited them.
What?
You invited them?
Yes. They called me in the middle of the night.
They said, let's go to the police station together.
What?
So?
They came out fighting with their parents.
That's 1 million yen.
What should I do?
It's no good. It's no good.
But why did you invite them when I invited them?
It's no good.
Why did you invite them when I invited them?
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
That's good.
What are you going to do with 1 million yen?
Really?
Of course.
You can't lie.
Actually, there is one more thing. We will sign it. If you can change it, we will give you 1 million yen back.
Can you ask your girlfriend to sign it?
Pass.
We will do it in front of you.
We will give you 1 million yen back.
What?
It's a good idea.
Why did you invite them?
It can't be helped.
That's why.
Don't say anything. It doesn't matter.
But I can't help it.
You can't help it.
This is the luck of the moon.
It's the luck of the moon.
Be careful when you go home.
Be careful.
Really.
What are you going to do if you get caught and get hit by a bag?
I don't know.
Maybe my staff is waiting for you inside.
Be careful when you go home.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
That's it.
Today is the 100th anniversary.
In that sense, he wasn't a normal kid.
As I said before, it was a wonderful present.
Actually, it was 1 million yen.
That's right.
I'm sorry to the people who came here.
It can't be helped.
Your face and body...
What are you going to do when you go home?
What am I going to do when I go home?
Are you going to go home like that?
With a lion's face?
But the train isn't running, is it?
I'm going to walk home.
But today, there are people who can go home.
Is that so?
I'm going to walk home.
I'm going to walk home in a taxi.
This is terrible.
Ignore him.
I don't know what's going on.
That's why we've been doing this for a long time.
Starting next week.
Starting next week?
Not starting next week.
Starting from October 20th.
It will be broadcast at 11 o'clock.
Sunday.
Yes, it will be broadcast at 11 o'clock.
I hope you will watch it.
Everyone's eyes are getting empty.
I've been standing for a while.
You can't sit there.
You can't get a million yen.
But you guys,
ever since I thought of that outfit,
I didn't have any rights.
When I was thinking of doing this at home,
I couldn't give you a million yen.
Right?
No matter what I do,
I can't get a million yen.
I hope you will watch it.
What is this theme?
It's different from usual, isn't it?
It's different from usual.
It's the theme of Gin-chan's imagination.
Gin-chan's imagination.
Everyone, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Let's meet again at 11 o'clock on Sunday.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.
Oh, it's already over.
That's fast, isn't it?
Goodbye.
Thank you very much.