Next time, at Gaki no Tsukai, Chikizuki! Ice Opittashi!
Omatanimonmari Grand Prix!
This Omatanimonmari...
We've done it several times in the O-League.
It's caused a social upheaval.
Really?
This time, we're going to use Omatanimonmari as a pair match.
For example, if it's something red...
Answer at the same time.
If the two people's phrases match, it's a correct answer.
If you answer 17 out of 10 questions correctly, you'll get 100,000 yen.
That's good.
But if you don't get the answer right, your partner's heart will get closer and closer.
That's how it is. If you get 4 questions right, your heart will get closer and closer.
It'll cause a social upheaval too.
It will.
The first pair is these people!
Can I call this a pair?
Is this a pair?
Of course it's a pair.
Your voices are too loud!
Please show us your pair match.
That's good.
The Monmari Machine is here!
Are you ready?
On the theme of the Monmari Machine...
Is that the theme?
Of course it is.
Ryuichi Sakamoto...
Tetsu-chan, you go first.
Tetsu-chan?
This is tough!
Yama-san, you go first.
When you take off your shoes, they're bare, right?
I'm sorry.
That's...
That's a pity!
You should've done something about it!
They were too bare.
You should've taken them off!
Why are you taking them off?
You should've just sat down!
Why did you take them off?
There's no need to take them off!
They're partners.
Let's go, Yama-chan!
This is a bad color!
It's hard to see this coming!
Tetsu-chan, get ready.
Yama-san, sit down.
It's a shame that they're bare.
They're so thin!
I'm so sorry!
Please take them off.
I can't do this to my mother either!
Let's go!
Speaking of the Japanese Prime Minister...
Let's go.
Ready, set...
Open!
Idiot!
Are you serious?
He's the real deal!
But the current Prime Minister isn't the only one.
The current Prime Minister isn't saying anything.
That's true.
Let's move on to the next one.
It's so long!
Speaking of the ice cream...
Speaking of dirty talent...
Let's go.
Ready, set...
Idiot!
Why?
I don't know.
How about you?
I'm Hamada-san.
Why are you calling me an idiot?
It's so hard!
I'm still here!
Are you sure about the previous question?
Speaking of the Japanese Prime Minister...
I got it!
Let's move on to the next one!
What if I get it wrong?
What if you get it wrong?
Let's move on to the next question.
Speaking of the SFO goods...
This is a matter of chance.
Ready, set...
Idiot!
You got it right!
That's the spirit!
Let's move on to the next question.
Speaking of the kind people in downtown...
Speaking of the kind people you think they are...
Let's go.
Ready, set...
Hamada Masatoshi!
Hamada Masumoto.
That's not what I always say!
Let's move on to the next question!
This is bad!
You're making me cry!
What are you talking about?
Let's move on!
Is this the last question?
Speaking of the kind people you think they are...
Ready, set...
Let's go!
Strong Congo!
There's no strong Congo.
This is the last question!
Speaking of the kind people you think they are...
This is bad!
That's not what I always say!
I'm shaking from the shivers!
The next pair is these two!
Good evening!
This is the Nagae Kenji pair!
They're both very refreshing.
And they're wearing Okamoto underwear.
That's good.
Speaking of the kind people you think they are...
I'm nervous.
I think they're both very refreshing.
The Nagae Kenji pair.
Shingo-chan, please sit here.
This is embarrassing.
You don't have to dress like this!
What are you talking about?
You look like a snowman.
What is this?
Let's go!
Speaking of the kind people you think they are...
Ready, set...
A plane!
The next question is...
Speaking of the kind people you don't like in the Kin-chan family...
This is easy.
I don't know if it's easy or not.
Let's go!
Ready, set...
Miehari!
Amazing!
Is that so?
This is wonderful.
These two will say it, so I'm sure of it.
I'm sure they'll say the same thing when they ask Kin-chan.
The next question is...
Speaking of the kind people you don't like in Gun-Town...
Let's go.
Ready, set...
Matcha!
This is too much of a service question.
Why? Why is it a service question?
Why is it the right answer?
There's no right or wrong answer.
The next question is...
Amazing.
Let's go.
Speaking of the kind people you don't like...
This is the most difficult one.
Let's go.
Ready, set...
Kin-chan!
That's right.
That's what you said, so that's why you said it.
Kin-chan.
That's right.
That's too much of a service question.
Let's move on to the next question.
There are three more questions left.
Amazing.
I feel like I've gained weight.
I guess you've gained weight.
The next question is...
Speaking of the kind people you don't like...
Let's go.
Ready, set...
Amazing.
That's the right answer.
Let's move on to the next question.
Speaking of Christmas...
Let's go.
Ready, set...
Yamashita Katsuro!
Let's move on to the next question.
There are two more questions left.
Speaking of the kind people you don't like...
Let's move on to the next question.
Ready, set...
Yakiniku!
Yakiniku Steak!
That was close.
It's the same meat.
Let's move on to the next question.
I've always been interested in this.
Let's touch it.
It's too strange.
Here you go.
You should have touched it a little more.
So far, there were three wrong answers.
In the next round, O-Mata will go first.
Kazami and Nanae pair.
They got the right answer twice in a row.
And they're left with nothing.
It's the second question.
Is it 100,000 yen or a crotch?
That's a big difference.
The last question.
Speaking of the king of vegetables...
The king...
Here we go.
Ready, set...
Katsudon!
That's wrong.
That's definitely wrong.
So, in the next round...
I'm watching you.
Who is it?
The last pair is these two.
Unlike everyone else, they're the only couple.
So, without further ado...
Let's call it a day.
Not at all!
As expected, Parko-san didn't laugh either.
What the heck is going on here?
I thought he was going to get his hair done, but...
It's a mess.
Did someone call me?
I was laughing, but my ears hurt.
I couldn't hear very well.
That's not good.
Are you okay?
I'm worried.
I'm okay.
I feel like I'm in a family show.
Here's the first question.
What is the best couple in the entertainment industry?
This is a service question.
One, two...
Takashima-san and Otsumi Hanae.
Correct!
I don't think it's Junran.
Those two are the ideal couple.
That's not funny at all.
What is the taste of a first kiss?
One, two...
Lemon!
Lemon and honey.
That's close.
The first kiss is moving!
No!
That's all for the first kiss.
But Pei-san is more beautiful than the other two.
Pei-san is beautiful.
Pei-san is not using his face.
Next question.
What is the manliness of downtown?
This is easy.
One, two...
Matsumoto-san!
Correct!
Next question.
What is the word for proposing?
That's a good one.
Let's go!
One, two...
Marry!
I have to see this.
Let's go!
Marry!
Next question.
What is the pun for banana?
There are about eight.
One, two...
Banana!
That's right.
If you get it right, you'll get 100,000 yen.
Next question.
What is the name of the king of Chinese cuisine?
That's a good one.
If you get it right, you'll get 100,000 yen.
Next question.
What is the name of the king of Chinese cuisine?
That's a good one.
Are you ready?
One, two...
Ramen!
That's right.
One step before.
I don't like this.
The char siu is expensive.
Yes.
Next question.
If you get it right, you'll get 100,000 yen.
What is the name of the insect?
This is...
Last question.
What is the name of the insect?
One, two...
Antenna!
Correct!
What is that?
Please get it right.
That's the correct answer.
Congratulations!
It's amazing!
There are some people who are not rich.
Can you do it by yourself?
No, I...
That's right!
I...
Wait a minute.
That's right.
I don't want to do it.
Wait a minute.
Masumoto-san.
Yes.
Let's do it together.
Of course.
I'm the one who doesn't want to do it.
The first one.
Why are you giving me problems?
I don't want to do it.
It's a simple problem.
Wait a minute.
Speaking of the teacher...
I don't want to do it anymore.
I got it.
Speaking of the teacher...
One, two...
Sandro-san.
The second one.
Speaking of the Komuro Family...
What does that mean?
There are a lot of Komuro Family members.
In this Komuro Family.
One, two...
Amuro-san.
Amuro.
What did he say?
Tomo-chan.
But it's the Komuro Family.
The first one starts.
Tomo-chan.
Matsumoto-san, your skin is slippery.
Well, that's why I've come this far.
The third one.
Speaking of the female voice of love...
There are a lot of them.
One, two...
Matsumoto-san.
Well, that's...
Amazing.
Speaking of the female voice of love...
How should I read it?
One, two...
Matsumoto-san.
You just said Hamamatsumoto.
I didn't say it.
Matsumoto-san.
You read it too much.
You said Hama first.
Go home!
Why are you still here?
Speaking of the female voice of love...
The female voice of love.
One, two...
Hyakuboji!
Why?
Hyakuboji.
You don't know that?
Go ahead.
What kind of third one is that?
This is...
Speaking of the female voice of love...
This is easy.
One, two...
That was good!
Speaking of the king of electronic products...
What is this?
The king of electronic products?
The king of electronic products.
I can't do this anymore. I'm going to get a torture.
I'm definitely going to get a torture.
This is wrong.
One, two...
The king of electronic products!
Wait!
Why?
Why is the king of electronic products in the fridge?
This is the fridge.
What are you guys doing?
Wait a minute!
You have to chew properly.
I want to chew.
What are you doing?
Why?
Why is it so smelly?
What are you doing?
This is the same everywhere, right?
Yes, that's right.
This is the same everywhere.
We use this when we go camping.
Toyota-san.
Toyota-san is here.
Really?
This is the same everywhere!
Thank you.
This is Matsumoto-san.
This is Toyota.
I bought it at Toyota.
Thank you.
This is Windham.
That's a good one.
It's a different sense of security.
Please give me one too.
You're the only one who can do this.
I came here a week ago.
This is good.
This is really good.
This is the same everywhere.
Thank you for watching.