What should we do?
Endo vs. Kato vs. Taka.
I want to watch this too. Moriman vs. Heipo.
With Heipo?
Yes.
I want to watch it.
I don't think I'll be able to do it.
What do you mean?
The main character is...
The famous one.
Yes.
Should we give the name of Yama-chan's child?
Seriously.
Seriously?
For example?
Desperado.
That's good.
I think it's decided.
Yama-san.
Yama-san?
Desperado.
I think it's really good.
Desperado is Des-chan.
Desu-chan is Desu-chan.
Here you go.
Hello.
You laughed.
The last line was a bit off.
You didn't talk at all.
Here you go.
You said, here you go.
I want to go to Hawaii.
Hawaii.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
Why didn't you tell me?
That your family was coming.
It was only for a day.
I thought it would be okay if I didn't tell you.
You're like a fool.
I'm going home tonight.
It's okay.
Shake your hand where you are with your family on the pool side.
If you shake your hand, you won't be shaken.
I'm not a fool.
It's okay.
Let's go.
Tomorrow.
Let's go to the pool again tomorrow.
He's a fool.
He's shaving his bones.
He has a beard.
I don't know what to comment on.
I saw that video.
Thank you.
You said you were 85 years old the other day.
You are single.
Please take me to the pool again.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
You are a fool.
Did you do that?
No.
I'm having fun today.
What's wrong?
Put it in your mouth.
You are a fool.
What's wrong?
You are hiding your face.
You are a fool.
I can't hear you at all.
Are you a pervert?
Yes, I am.
You are a pervert.
Red Light.
You threw that away.
How dare you?
I thought it was a lounger's guitar.
You did not organize my face at a Odaku later.
I don't like prophesying.
I didn't intend to do it so much when I wrote the book.
But Takasu Ishii, you did it without a Mission.
He let me keep imitating him.
Takasu's lie.
Endo was fooled too.
I was fooled.
Endo...
Endo and Dynamite Shikoku.
Yes, this is Uchida Yume.
What, you're not in Rikiya?
You can't go tomorrow? Why?
It can't be helped then. Got it.
Hello, this is Uchida who is making a reservation for tomorrow.
I can't go alone, so please take care of the three of us.
This is Uchida Yume.
What, you're not in Rikiya?
You can't go after all?
I've already made a phone call.
It can't be helped then.
Let's go.
He's kind.
Hello, this is Uchida.
I'm going with the four of us after all.
You're making a reservation yourself?
That was funny.
What's wrong?
Thank goodness.
It's 6 o'clock.
I should go home.
I can go home.
What's this?
It's 5 o'clock.
This is the worst.
I should go home.
Yamasaki.
It's over.
It's 27,000 yen.
That's amazing.
27,000 yen means that he's in third place.
He's in fourth place.
Fourth place.
Miyasakuri, 1,000 yen up.