Chiki-chiki! Newlyweds, hoya-hoya!
Kotori Director, Sakamoto Prefecture!
Otaku Homo!
Sakamoto-san!
He's right behind me.
Yes, yes.
He tricked me and told me he finished work early today.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Chiki-chiki! Newlyweds, hoya-hoya!
I'm a newlyweds, hoya-hoya.
You're probably eating, aren't you?
I see.
What would you do if you were?
That would be interesting.
Shall we bring the presents?
Yes, yes, yes.
If you speak too loud...
It's there, isn't it?
It's there.
Shall we go?
Let's go!
Newlyweds, hoya-hoya!
Yes?
Excuse me, my name is Hamada.
Yes.
Do you have a husband?
Yes, I do.
Thank you for waiting.
Yes, thank you.
Good evening.
I'm eating.
Please come quickly.
Good evening.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Zakao is eating in his dirty jersey.
He's tidying up nicely.
It's a nice room.
He's in a good mood.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
Nawa and Eriko...
What?
Kitsuta!
Nawa and Eriko's home.
What is that?
First of all, they say they love each other.
That's terrible.
They eat together.
You can't cheat on them.
Kitsuta!
It stinks.
You're starting to stink.
Did you know?
What?
A little.
She knew a little.
It's rude not to know.
Sano, what's this?
Sano likes birds.
It's cute.
Buy it for her.
A little more.
Wait a minute.
Nawa and Eriko's home.
What is this?
I don't like it either.
Fly.
It's here, isn't it?
That's great.
It's already stuck.
I'm going to clean up the penguins.
I hate it.
In this room.
I've had enough.
It stinks.
Not only the penguins.
We have a special guest today.
Please welcome today's special guest.
It's Mr. Kaoru Sugita.
Nice to meet you.
Please sing a bird song.
It hurts.
I wanted to laugh.
Sing together.
Everyone looked happy.
I'm sorry.
Don't mess with me.
If my heart is the sky.
I'm sure it's a pure white bird.
Birds, birds, birds.
Please sing this song.
A bird song.
Thank you very much.
You don't have to do that.
Thank you very much for coming to sing this song.
It's not a big deal to hear it live.
Birds, birds, birds.
It's over.
It was hard.
What was that?
Do you have a nickname?
A loser.
For example, how much money did you lose and how much money did you get back?
How much money did you get back?
What?
You're really dirty.
Why?
I'm desperate.
Listen to me.
Do you think money is dirty?
Of course.
In the end, I put my wallet in here and put money in here.
That's why I lost it.
If I don't lose it, I'll put it in here.
That's disgusting.
No, no, no.
It's a mystery.
I don't carry a wallet.
I've never seen you carry a bag.
I don't carry it at the end.
That's great.
I'll leave it to you.
Who do you leave it to?
I don't have any more fruits.
I'll eat an apple.
It's after the war.
I don't carry it.
How can you live without money?
What are you going to do when you want to buy gasoline?
That's why...
I heard something good.
What's that?
Close it.
I think about it in my heart.
I think about my body.
When you become a talent, you don't spend much money.
I don't spend much money.
I don't know how many celebrities are there.
What are you doing?
You!
Don't make a fuss.
Say it.
You!
What do you want to say?
You are the most common talent in Japan.
Don't make a fuss.
You haven't changed.
You don't drive a car.
I don't drive a car.
Everyone says my car is good.
Take a used car.
It costs about 500,000 yen.
That's not true.
Think about the time you earned money.
I didn't do much in Osaka.
I didn't sell it, so I had money.
I didn't sell it.
400 million?
Give me this.
Don!
I hate money.
This is true.
Why is there money?
I'm from Kurizakaya, so I don't need it.
What I want to say is that I dropped my wallet again a little while ago.
That's your fault. Because you're a doji.
I dropped a lot of money on the Shinkansen.
It's a license, right?
There's about 200,000 yen in my wallet.
Please!
200,000 yen?
What's that?
There's 200,000 yen in it?
There's about 200,000 yen in it.
You're a king of money.
Well, 200,000 yen is fine, but...
200,000 yen is fine?
Well, well, well...
Well, it's not that big of a deal.
You didn't change your license, did you?
No, I asked him what he dropped on the Shinkansen.
This time, I found it at Hakata.
There was no money in it?
No, there was money in it.
There was money in it?
There was money in it.
There's no such thing.
I dropped 200,000 yen on the Shinkansen.
I don't know if I'll ever find it again.
I was so depressed.
I said, it's not a big deal.
I felt like I was going to lose my head.
I see.
I finished my work in Osaka.
I realized I didn't have a wallet.
I was going to get a fan letter from a fan.
I looked at it.
There's 10,000 yen in it.
Yeah.
There's no such thing.
What is that?
I thought there was a fan who dropped 10,000 yen when I dropped the money.
That's amazing.
Isn't it?
I thought it was a good deal.
I don't have any money right now.
I see.
I thought that 10,000 yen was valuable.
I opened it and looked at it.
There was a 1 yen coin on the cello table and 10,000 yen on the side.
Damn it!
It's not a damn thing.
I didn't do anything.
I couldn't laugh at this customer.
I've been robbed of tens of thousands of yen in the dressing room.
There are many people in the dressing room.
Let's stop doing that.
But...
I went to the scene and found a bag.
I saw the wallet.
I didn't think, huh?
No, no, no.
I'll never do that.
I'm sure I have that sense of justice.
I'll be a politician.
I'll bring in a lot of money.
I can't do that.
My opinion will never change.
I'm a man like that.
I'll believe it.
Are you kidding me?
What is that?
I don't understand how a man like that can do that.
But I thought everyone felt that way.
You're a great man.
Can't everyone change their opinion?
Can't you?
It's easy for me.
You can do it right away.
I don't usually do that.
That's how I feel.
Why?
I don't like that kind of example.
Can you eat it if it's Nanbo?
What is that?
I'm a human being.
I don't understand who you are.
I'd like a bowl of tea for kids.
A bowl of tea for Sailor Moon.
Do you have a hot spring?
Yes, I have a hot spring.
How many do you want?
I know you're curious about it.
You're talking about what I said.
Can you do it with 100 million yen?
That's behind the man
Behind the man?
Can you do it with 100 million yen?
100 million yen right?
Behind the man right?
Behind the man is mine
It's a little lucky
I'll eat it
You'll eat it? I won't eat it
You'll know if you have 100 million yen
Everyone will eat it right?
It'll come
I'll eat it
If you have 100 million yen it'll definitely come
There's no harm to the body right?
There's no harm to the body
Is that so?
I ate it and it came out of my butt
I thought it was just you eating it
Just eating it?
It's not that simple
It came out like this and it came out like this
It's Alpha
There's this thing in America
It's like a shocking movie
It's interesting when you get hit
It's not interesting
But if you get hit like in the movies
You can't do it like this
Is that so?
The moment you get hit
It's like
Really?
That doesn't hit
You'll get hit in the stomach
What are you doing?
Did you just add that?
It's true
No no
That smell
Wait a minute
That movement is a little different
Please hit me a little
Stop it
It's a little different
You get hit once but you don't stand up
And then you go like this
You're lying
It's not like that
What is this?
I got hit
If it's a joke, it hurts
That doesn't hit
There's a lot of blood
Are you serious?
This is a lie
It's not like that
It's going up
I don't know
What are you reading?
I'm going to write a letter
Please write a letter
I was reading at the convenience store
It suddenly got dark
It's scary
I screamed
After a while
I said, excuse me
I turned on the light
There was a show in the back
Everyone who was walking outside came together
That's right
I was standing in front of the book
Before that
You have money, right?
Buy it
It's hundreds of yen
Don't say that
Buy it
You have hundreds and thousands of yen a month
What were you looking at?
You
Were you looking at an aerotopia again?
I'm very curious about something
What is it?
Your lips look thinner than they used to be
No way
From your eyes to your lips
That's not true
What do you think of looking at Mr. Hamada in front of you?
How do you do that?
Your lips
What are these seams?
Why?
I'm scared
Where are the seams?
I can't tell from the camera
There are no seams
It's like a Matsuri
That's not how you do it
Did you hear that?
Do you know how to do that?
Are you doing it?
No
Are you not doing it?
We are always together
Have I ever said that to you?
No
I remember
If you do that, you have to wear a bandage for a while
What are you talking about?
You have to wear a bandage for a while
That's when you push your teeth
That's how you do it
I'm scared
That's when you push your front teeth
When you were wearing a bandage
Your front teeth were broken
I broke my front teeth
I broke them
When did you change them?
That's not true
Stop it
You've always had this kind of mouth
I used to have a thicker mouth
This is true
I used to have a bluer face
My mouth was always open
If you look at me from the side
What are you talking about?
All my family members
What?
You're rude
I'm just saying that the air is thin
My mouth is always open
My wife and three children take a bath together
I have a question
Why is there a hole in the middle of the bath chair?
Isn't that for hot water?
What are you looking at?
You're trying to get hot water through
That's why there's a hole in the middle
You can sit and take a bath
But the water will fill up
Hello?
The water is flowing
You can sit normally
I'm telling you that the water is flowing
I'll tell you
It's dangerous for a child to take a bath alone
So by making a hole in the chair
What do you call it?
With that chair
With the hole
Let's try not to fall and get in
If we get bigger than this hole
Shou-chan, let's get in
Is that what you mean?
It's a hole