Good morning!
Ah, good morning!
Today is going to be tough!
What do you mean?
No, really, today is going to be tough.
Yes!
Today is going to be a little different than usual.
That's right.
We're going to have everyone watch a lot of VTRs.
The other day, you know, you dressed up like a blonde,
and came to the riverbed of Arakawa.
Yes.
Did anyone of you come here?
Yes!
That's all?
What about the others?
I've said this before on the show,
most of them raised their hands, right?
But when I opened the lid, it was like this.
It's like this.
They're really cold, aren't they?
That's all?
What were the others doing?
They were taking a break.
They were playing somewhere.
Ah, good morning!
And the weather was nice that day.
The weather was nice!
If you go to a place like that,
it's not the time for blondes to be doing this.
But it's fine!
Let's all have fun!
Why aren't you coming?
Blondes...
No one's dressed up like a blonde.
Well, well, how do you say this?
The non-citizens are the non-citizens.
This...
All of a sudden?
What is it?
There were a lot of non-citizens.
There were a lot on that day!
Today, we'll show you a lot of that.
We'll show you a part of it.
Let's eat.
Here you go.
Non-citizens!
Let's all give them a round of applause!
Hello!
Well, let's take a look.
I'll say one thing.
You, red wig, go home.
You're not allowed.
Okay?
I'm aiming at the camera from above.
If you look at the air, you can see everyone.
I don't know if you can see it, though.
Are you ready?
Ready, start!
I'll say it.
After that, Masato-kun.
2 years and 4 groups?
2 years and 4 groups.
3 years and 4 groups.
4 years and 4 groups.
I don't know where you're going.
Behind you!
Wait a minute.
I'm waiting for the train.
4 years and 4 groups.
3 years and 4 groups.
Okay!
Okay, but wait a minute.
I'll check.
Okay, okay, okay.
Let's go!
3 years and 4 groups.
This is funny.
Now I'm going to do a one-word practice.
Are you ready?
I'm going to do a one-word practice as a kid.
First of all, I'm going to give you a white towel.
And then I'm going to take off my jacket.
I didn't say I'd be naked.
I'm going to take off my jacket.
What do you call it?
A rectangle.
At the end, we'll go down.
I'd like you to give me some space.
Something's shaking.
It's shaking, isn't it?
I'm scared.
We're going to combine the back and front.
I don't need it.
Everyone, hold the camera tight.
One, two, three.
It's okay.
Let's do it one more time.
Let's do it a little longer.
One, two, three.
Okay.
Please take a picture of me.
I won't do it many times.
I'm going to do a manzai pose.
I'm going to do it.
One, two.
I'm going to do a manzai pose.
Are you shooting?
I'm going to do it.
1, 2, 3, 4!
I never thought that we would gather this many people in this costume.
I'm surprised.
Thank you very much everyone.
I think that we will be able to gather this many people when we do something.
We are also feeling less confident.
So, let's go!
Let's go!
Louder!
This is the last one!
What?
Do you want to do the third person?
Yes!
Everyone, move your body.
I will say the last one.
Coming, right?
Everyone, do you want to do the third person?
I don't know.
Mr. Matsumoto, please sing the lyrics.
Yes.
Please sing it as it is.
Move your body to the right and left.
Let's go!
The one who takes away the green earth.
But there is no one who can take away the green earth as much as I do.
Everyone, thank you very much!
Mr. Matsumoto, I was impressed this time too.
I made it like that at the end.
It was wonderful.
If you gather this much.
If you gather this much, I can't make a house.
We have to make a new development from next month.
We don't have a break.
What is waiting for us next?
We have to play a game of golf.
We talked about playing a game of golf.
Do you want to play it?
No, I'm fine.
I have one thing to say.
We played it as a punishment game.
Can you change your mind this time?
You're saying something nice.
You can make the winner's wish come true.
I don't understand what you're saying.
I heard it once.
How about this?
There is a pressure that you can't lose because you have this.
But you want to win because you have this.
That kind of...
Wait, wait.
What is it?
No matter what the winner says, you have to do it.
That's right.
No matter what he says.
You can't do that.
When you lose, you can't say this or that.
We played the punishment game three times and went skydiving.
I thought there was nothing more.
I thought so, too.
That's why I quit the punishment game.
There was one.
Something similar to that.
What is it?
Bungee jump.
Bungee jump...
It's like a chimpanzee chop.
Chimpanzee...
Sorry.
I was looking at you chopping a chimpanzee from the side.
What makes me happy?
What?
You should have just chopped it.
If I win...
I want you to skydive as a couple.
Wait a minute.
Wait.
Hey, wait.
What are you thinking?
It's high.
I can't do it today.
Or you can ride a bike and go around Suzuka together.
When you turn, it's like this.
How about this?
It's easy to ride on the other side.
If you fall, your bones will be broken.
How about this?
You...
Wait a minute.
You should have done something more exciting.
Like kangaroo boxing.
You can laugh.
You can't laugh.
I thought you were chopping a monkey.
I can't do it.
It's a punishment game.
You should have done something more exciting.
Let's get back to the topic.
What do you mean?
Let's start with golf.
Otherwise, you'll lose.
I'm not confident.
Give me a handicap.
I'm thinking about it.
I didn't want to win.
I'm thinking about a chance card.
If I don't win, I'll get a chance card.
I'm thinking about a good person.
Who is a good person?
A professional.
I don't want to be a professional.
I'm going to give up my head.
If I give up my head, I can't communicate.
Please.
I don't want to be a professional.
You're just talking to people.
Please say it.
I'll listen to you.
What is it?
I'll lose.
You'll do anything.
It's a penalty game.
What is it?
An air swing.
It's okay.
What?
I'll do anything.
If I lose?
I'll do an air swing, too.
If we both lose, we'll do an air swing.
Why did you do an air swing?
There's a net underneath.
I couldn't shape it for a week.
It's a net.
If you walk on the street like that, there's no difference from a mackerel.
What?
I'll do it again.
I can't do that.
Do you want a penalty game?
Rather than a penalty game, I'd like to think about golf again.
Let's think about it.
I don't have time to think about it.
Do you have music to go home?
If you have music, we'll be sorry.
Please come to play again.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'm tired.
Seriously.
The penalty game hasn't been decided yet.
The content of the game hasn't been decided yet.
Let's play a game of shooting.
What?
Let's be friends.
I don't like shooting.
What is it?
Let's play a game of shooting.
You don't have to worry about it.
I don't like it.
How about a game of golf?
I can't allow it.
I was surprised.
Let's play a game of shooting.
Thank you very much.