The beginning of the story was once again far away.
I was a delivery man at the house's ginkgo garden.
When he came, he would definitely come with a really loud voice, singing enka.
That old man was really fast.
He came in about 10 minutes.
A man's voice.
Huh?
That old man?
Yeah.
Kato 52.
Why is your man's voice Kato 52?
He came with a really loud voice, singing enka.
You can tell that he came, right?
Huh? He didn't sing until the entrance?
He was like this all the time.
He didn't stop there?
He didn't stop until the other person came?
No, no.
That's the end of it.
When I open the chorus, he'll sing the chorus.
There are so many mysteries hidden in modern society.
With his sharp sense of observation and deep insight, he will unravel them.
Hitoshi Matsumoto.
These are the four points of this test.
Will the truth really be there?
Hitoshi Matsumoto.
The old man who cuts off modern society.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
This is Tsutsuimoto's house.
It's our staff's house.
It's just inside the prefecture.
Inside the prefecture.
Yamasaki!
Yes.
Call me.
This is ***.
Oh, hello.
Yes.
Hello.
Well, I'm sorry, but I'd like to make an order.
Yes.
Where are you?
I'm Yamasaki.
Yes.
Honcho.
Honcho, yes.
Roku no ***.
Yes.
One tanuki soba.
One zaru soba.
Yes.
Thank you.
Start.
Yes.
First of all, whether the verification of coming within 10 minutes will be correct or not.
That's right.
Well, this is already a flow.
If you come within 10 minutes, is it similar to Kato?
Yes.
Are you singing a song while you're coming?
Even if you open the door, are you still singing?
Yes.
Well, singing a song.
This and this may be possible.
Yes.
Even if you open the door, are you still singing?
Well, if you say so, it's okay.
Is that so?
Yes.
Now, Mr. Matsumoto.
Five minutes have passed.
Oh, it's coming.
Five minutes left.
I said within 10 minutes, but it won't take 10 minutes.
Oh, is that so?
Yes.
After all, tanuki soba is.
Why?
It's soba.
It's the best if it's a party.
It's something to simmer.
Why?
It's not simmering.
What?
It's terrible.
It's still the first verification.
It seems to be lost.
It's already.
No, no, no.
I'm trying to stand for seven minutes.
Seven minutes?
No way.
It's terrible.
Seven minutes?
Oh, really, seven minutes.
It's three minutes.
Three minutes.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
It's strange.
I thought I could go to one and three, but this is one.
Oh, it's coming.
Look at it.
Seven minutes and twenty-eight seconds.
First, ten minutes.
I'm going to take it off now.
I got the first verification.
Did you get it?
Yes.
This is zero.
Well, the next verification.
A man who looks like Kato Go.
Yes.
I'll show you Kato Go.
It doesn't make any sound at all.
Yes, excuse me.
May I?
Yes.
Excuse me.
What is this?
Yes, don't do it.
Yes.
Oh.
I didn't know Kato Go.
I'm sorry.
Well, eight hundred and ninety-one.
Yes.
Oh, excuse me.
I'll give you a hundred yen.
I've never seen it before.
Oh, it's back.
Please give me a hundred yen.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's messed up.
It's just the delivery time.
What is it?
It's over here.
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm not lying.
Not at all.
Well, even if you open the door,
I'm singing.
Well, it doesn't make any sound.
It doesn't make any sound at all.
It's a lie.
It doesn't make any sound if you sing your nose.
Right, Yamasaki?
I didn't sing at all.
Right?
Yes.
Did it look like Kato Go?
Not at all.
It doesn't look like Kato Go at all.
It doesn't look like a man at all.
Hey, I had my face puffy today.
No, that's not the problem.
Why are you puffy only when I'm singing?
I took the delivery ten times,
and I've been puffy ten times.
No, but...
That's enough.
Only that man can shoot a singing show.
One hour.
I didn't sing at all.
You're a champ.
What are you going to do if you sing like that?
No, no.
I don't want that man to be a champ.
What are you going to do if you sing like that?
If I ask him to deliver one more song, will he come?
I think he'll come.
I know Yamasaki.
I'll do it again.
He'll come for sure this time.
This time...
I don't think he'll come.
He's not used to it.
That's why he's a little depressed.
He's like a regular customer now.
I know Yamasaki.
So I can think of a way to make him come while singing.
I'll ask him to bring me a big ball.
Okay.
It's going to take some time.
The first shot is 7 minutes and 28 seconds.
This is a test.
I'm Yamasaki.
Yes.
I'd like to order another Kitsune Udon.
One Kitsune Udon.
Okay.
I hung up the phone.
I'll call you later.
Okay.
What did he say?
He ordered it right away.
It's a Kitsune Udon.
Kitsune Udon?
Yes.
Udon is...
I don't think he'll come until I've ordered it.
At the entrance?
I don't think he'll come.
It's a stubborn store.
It's very...
It's very friendly.
I'd like to see Kato again.
I couldn't see him properly.
It's already been 7 minutes.
It's slower than before.
At that time, the old man was already running through the shopping street.
Will Matsumoto's words really come true?
He's here.
It's faster than before.
It's 7 minutes and 24 seconds.
It's so fast.
Good morning.
Why isn't he here yet?
Come on in.
It's a matter of time.
It's very early.
I'll wash the dishes.
Do you need a towel?
He's making a joke.
It's the worst.
You can't hear the singing voice, can you?
I can't hear it at all.
What is it?
It's that guy.
What?
Ladies and gentlemen.
Good morning.
Once again, Mr. Matsumoto has lied to us.
Well...
Today, Mr. Demaeno went to see a doctor, didn't he?
Yes, of course he did.
Yes.
Mr. Kato 52 is a man.
That's why.
There is a difference in personal taste.
You look like a pot.
Do you think Mr. Kato 52 is a man?
Of course I do.
Even if you look like this?
That's because I think you're a man.
If there are people who think you're cool, I think you're cool.
This is a personal taste.
I think you're 15 points.
Is that so?
Why are you making a serious face?
That's fine.
On the way here, he was singing a song.
It was very quiet.
That's the worst.
That's why...
I'm sorry, but you're sorry, too.
Why am I sorry?
I don't lie.
No, but everything was a lie.
If you don't say that, everything I've said so far will be a lie.
It's a lie.
Kappa hikari.
Kappa is that kind of thing.
I've been told this since elementary school.
There's a kappa in the bathroom.
When I came home, I told you about the time.
There was a monster of the
And then he said, shpo shpo shpo, shpo shpo shpo, and then he said, akka!
And then he said he wouldn't come out and ran away.
Hey, that's a lie!
It's a lie!
You're living on lies!
What kind of crying dog does he have?
I'll ask you this.
What kind of crying?
He says, nyan!
No, this is real. This is real.
No, but I've seen a dog do this.
This is real.
No, this is real.
I don't say that much.
This is real.
He does this.
That's impossible.
No, he really does this.
Definitely.
No, that's impossible.
What does he do?
What?
Nyan?
There's a dog that says, nyan!
It's a little strange.
It's a little strange from the beginning.
Geez.
Otama.
Otama family.
Stopping the car.
The delivery man.
The delivery man is here.
It's all crumbling.
It's not crumbling.
If there's anything, please tell me.
Shall we?
There's Chirimen Jako, right?
Yes, yes.
Chirimen Jako.
Do you know Chirimen Jako?
I know it.
There was a little crab in there.
Can I say that?
Yes.
There is.
Everyone says there is.
Do you know udon?
I know it.
Udon.
Do you know udon?
There's only one soba in the udon.
There is.
I don't have it.
What is that?
What are you talking about?
It's not a verification or anything.
In the udon restaurant, there is a shop that shows you kneading it through the glass.
Yes, there is.
There is, right?
There is.
There is a shop that shows you naked in the water.
I don't have it.
Old man, come here.
First of all, make soba.
Why are you doing this?
There is no way.
Mr. Matsumoto.
Yes.
What is it?
This is for you.
They made it by hand.
They delivered it to the site today.
Hitoshi Love.
They gave me a letter.
Dear Matsumoto Hitoshi.
I always meet you at work or in private,
but this is the first time I'm sending you a letter.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Do you know what day it is today?
Well, I'm giving you the chocolate, so I'm sure you know.
But today is a special day for Akko.
Today is a special day to confess your love.
Everyone in the entertainment world thinks of me as a little scary lady.
That's not true.
It's not a little scary.
You know the real me, don't you?
I don't know what you're writing anymore.
I'll confess my love to you.
I love you.
Please answer me soon.
I'm serious.
I'll call you again.
Akiko Wada.
Wow.
What is this?
Hitoshi Love.
I haven't been in touch with you lately.
I'm glad.
This is bad.
If you receive this, you'll definitely write to me.
I thought you were a person I'd be happy with.
What do you mean?
Well...
You're really young.
That's right.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Do you like her?
That's right.
I see.
Send her to me.
I'm scared.
You scared me.
What is this?
She brought it to me.
This is bad.
Please answer me.
You're busy, aren't you?
Is it okay for you to die like this?
My hair is shaking.
Why are you sweating so much?
I was really surprised.
I was surprised when you hit me.
I feel like I'm in the Yakuza.
Thank you very much.
Why didn't you answer me?
He found out.
Why are you sweating so much?
Because you're saying the opposite of what you think.
Don't you remember when you came to my house the other day?
You really liked me.
I'm sorry you're married.
You should have known each other sooner.
He's a Neuro.
That's weird.
What's wrong with you?
I'm scared.
Have you calmed down?
I haven't calmed down yet.
I want to go to the post office and forget about it.
Let's go to the post office.
Can I?
What do you think when you say the word, Matsumoto Hitoshi?
Have you ever said the word?
No.
You haven't.
You never say the word Matsumoto.
No, I haven't.
But when you say it in a brave way...
He's a moron.
When you say it in a brave way, it comes out.
Like this?
Courage? The energy to go towards something?
Stamina? Effort?
And then, you pull a thing like this and write,
Like Hitoshi Matsumoto,
It's written, Koto.
Ah, it's Koto.
There's a point here?
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Even if you open up Yuuki's part?
And if there's a point where you go backwards,
Bring it over here.
Matsumoto Hitoshi is the opposite of Dame Ningen.
Eh? Dame Ningen is the opposite of Matsumoto Hitoshi?
What's that?
Ah, there's no time.
Ah, wait.
There's only two lines left.
Ah, I can't do this anymore.
The break has started.
Okay, let's watch it.
Ah, I can't do this anymore.
The break has started.
Okay, let's watch it.
What's going on?
The break has started?
Kanpei-san, you're here!
You're here!
You made it in time!
It's only 24 hours.
What? You're looking at Yuuki's part?
Yes.
You're slow.
Yuukan.
Yuuki, Yuukan.
Kaki.
Yuuki.
Which Yuuki?
You're Yuuki Kagobutsu's Yuuki, aren't you?
You're the only one left, so I don't know!
Who's Yuuki Kagobutsu?
Which Yuuki?
This Yuuki?
That's right.
Isn't it this Isamuuki?
You're not afraid of anything.
You have a strong feeling.
That's right.
That's why this is strange.
What year is this?
This kind of thing changes a lot.
It changes, but the basics don't change.
Even if it increases, it doesn't decrease.
No, it's on the old one.
I wonder if you hit it.
Ah, this isn't good.
What's not good?
It's 2060 yen.
Isn't it more of an Aizou version?
Whose Aizou version is it?
I can tell if it's a record or something.
Okay, another lie.
I've been pooping since I've pooped.
And there's poop on my pants.
What should I do?
I'm 19 years old.
First of all, there's poop on my pants.
You're an experienced person.
Of course.
Because I'm the main one.
What?
There's poop on my pants.
Everyone get together and do something.
He's the sub.
I'm the main one.
You're the main one.
I'm sorry.
First of all, throw away all the pants you have.
Why?
Because all the pants you have now have poop on them.
But if I wash them...
You can't get rid of the poop even if you wash them.
Don't lick the poop.
I didn't lick it.
I shouldn't have licked it.
To be clear, there's no way you can't get rid of the poop.
Everyone has it.
I'm sorry.
You?
No, no, no.
Everyone...
All mankind...
Say it again.
I apologized as a representative of all mankind.
I'm sorry.
If you don't apologize...
That's why there's poop on your pants.
There's no poop on it.
No, no, no.
That's enough.
You don't have to pay attention to it.
I didn't pay attention to it.
It's natural.
There's poop on it.
When you have a stomachache, when you fart, there's poop on it, right?
There's no poop on it.
You're a fool.
I've never done it that way.
I've done it the right way.
What do you mean the right way?
That's why there's poop on it.
But you haven't taken it all out.
What do you mean the right way?
You left a little bit.
You blew it once and it came out.
It's not a residue, but...
You were walking around like Zanbaba.
Your butt came out, didn't it?
Hey, hey, hey.
Okamoto, call a lawyer.
If you sue me, you can win.
Let's fight in court.
Call a lawyer.
I had a date the other day.
I'm a man.
I had a date the other day and got along well with that woman.
We're starting to talk about marriage.
But before that, there's one thing I have to confess.
I'm Katsura.
That's good.
How can I confess without hurting her?
That's a good thing.
How can I make her accept me without hurting her?
I think it's best to make it look like an accident.
Even if it's an accident?
Yes.
So, for example, the low part of the ceiling...
That's it, that's it, that's it, that's it.
That's not funny.
It's too beautiful.
That's nothing.
That's no good.
That's difficult.
If you're going to get married, you'll have to stop at some point.
Yes, yes, yes.
Where should I leave you in the morning?
That's obvious.
That's shocking.
When I saw it.
I wonder.
What kind of reaction should I make pretending to sleep?
No, no, that's you.
Because you don't know which one is your girlfriend.
What?
It's going to be as if you're putting a lid on it again.
Is there such a thing as a lid?
It's just one side.
There's no gap between me and her.
What would you do if you were naked?
What if you were wearing a veil?
After all, there's nothing you can do about it.
What is it?
Put animals on it.
As it is.
You can't put animals on it.
You have a lot of things to do.
You have to cover it up.
Even if you don't cover it up, there are animals that do it properly.
Put it on the head.
That's.
What?
What is it?
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.