In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai, we will investigate the popularity of talent in all of Japan in 1996!
Let's introduce the talents who will be participating.
First, next to them is Pierre Kaki!
Next to him is Ana Iroko!
Next to him is Matsumoto Kancho!
Hello, nice to meet you.
From now on, we will drop the talents' belongings on the street.
We will give you the time until they are picked up.
The last person with the highest points will receive 100,000 yen as a prize.
I can go home and sell it.
The person with the highest points will receive 100,000 yen as a prize.
The first talent is...
This!
Date Kimiko's tennis racket.
Everyone, please look at this.
Kimiko Date?
It's written here.
There's no way it's written here.
I don't get it.
The average person would think it's Kimiko Date.
First is Date Kimiko's tennis racket.
Pierre has 25 seconds, Ana has 60 seconds, and Matsumoto has 4 minutes and 15 seconds.
Let's go!
25 seconds, 60 seconds, 4 minutes and 15 seconds.
Ready, start!
What?
Wait a minute.
It's already 8.9 seconds.
It's already 11 seconds.
These two will pick it up.
What is that?
There's a racket.
What?
The foreigner picked it up.
Two minutes?
Well, I picked it up anyway.
It's just a matter of manners.
It can't be helped.
It's 4 minutes, but...
It's 3 minutes.
Here's the next question.
The next question is...
Kimutaku's script for the long-haired ghost.
Is this for real?
Kimutaku?
That's...
I'll get in trouble.
Kimutaku's script for the long-haired ghost.
1 minute for the long-haired ghost, 46 seconds for the short-haired ghost, and 18 seconds for the long-haired ghost.
Ready, start!
I'll get in trouble.
Should I drop it?
This is fast.
9, 10, 11, 18 seconds.
14 seconds.
I can pick it up standing up, right?
I didn't expect it to be a human.
I dropped it.
It's in front of you.
It's laughing.
1 minute has passed.
Really?
Time out!
Unexpectedly, it's not popular.
That's true.
It's not popular.
The next question is...
The legendary record of the boy band Degameron.
What?
I thought so.
I'm curious if I can listen to it because I opened it.
It's a record.
I see.
If you think about the possibility of winning.
The next question is...
The legendary record of the boy band Degameron.
1 minute and 50 seconds.
3 minutes and 15 seconds.
The legendary record of the boy band Degameron.
Ready, go!
Start!
I'll get in trouble.
It's like I'm fixing my shoes.
I see.
Where is it?
It hurts.
What is it?
I was sad.
It's fast.
I got it.
It's over.
It was fast.
29 seconds.
2 points.
I thought it would be easy.
Really?
Next is this.
The glasses of Shohei Shofutei.
What is this?
How?
This is like this.
Please use it freely.
Shohei.
He said it.
That's strong.
These glasses.
Please think about it.
I don't know.
It's like a TV.
Next is the glasses of Shohei Shofutei.
22 seconds.
2 minutes.
If you get it right.
2 points.
Don't step on it.
Don't pick it up.
I kicked it.
You kicked it.
It's bad.
It's broken.
It doesn't look like Shohei.
It's sad.
It's no good.
2 minutes.
5 seconds.
7 seconds.
I picked it up in 1 minute and 7 seconds.
It's Shohei's glasses.
Put it on.
It's broken.
You can put it on.
You did it.
You're the best.
The last question is here.
Curry rice cracker.
It's no good.
It's spicy.
It's not bad.
It's food.
It's good.
Is it good?
It's not good.
I told Pierre.
I want to see the sticker.
Is there anyone who wants a sticker?
Yes.
This is a propaganda.
I'm a little lucky.
I got a good one.
Next is the curry rice cracker in downtown.
Pierre 1 minute and 55 seconds.
Anai 2 minutes and 30 seconds.
Matcha 4 minutes.
I got a sticker.
Look, look, look.
He's not even looking at me.
I kicked it.
I kicked it, so I saw it.
I kicked it myself.
I'll kick it again.
I didn't notice it.
You guys have a sticker.
What are you going to do if there's a stupid man in there?
What are you going to do?
I want to think.
5 seconds left.
Yeah, yeah.
It's over.
Time over.
And here's another reverse quiz.
Now, everyone.
Pierre, who was the lowest in the game,
I got you in a cardboard box.
I'll put a sticker like this.
Pierre is tired and sleeping.
Don't open it.
I'm having fun.
I'm scared.
How many minutes and seconds do you have to go?
How many seconds do you have to go?
I'll open the box.
What do you think about this?
If you like Pierre so much,
I won't open it.
Pierre is tired.
A cardboard box where Pierre sleeps.
Pierre is 4 minutes and 20 seconds.
Anai is 4 minutes and 38 seconds.
Matcha is 2 minutes and 50 seconds.
Pierre, who can get out of the cardboard box right away.
Will the time come when the lid can be opened?
The time has come.
Taki is being carried.
Pierre is being carried now.
I'll put it in the middle.
Ready, start.
Don't stand out.
I opened it.
The lid is blocked.
I'm scared.
Taki is over.
I'm over.
I'm very interested.
Please.
I opened it.
I opened it in 36 seconds.
I won.
Welcome home.
Pierre opened it in 4 minutes and 38 seconds.
Are you scared?
I'm scared.
I'm serious.
Pierre opened it in 4 minutes and 36 seconds.
I'll ask Matsumoto to open it.
I'll ask Matsumoto to open it in 10 seconds.
The cardboard box is thin.
I'm scared.
I'm very scared.
Please set it up.
The paper is separated.
I didn't know it was like this.
Ready, start.
What is this?
It's creepy.
There was a big cardboard box.
that's my favorite one.
That's my favorite one.
It's not pretty.
Is it a young man?
Take a look.
I wonder if it's true.
It's like a kid.
He's a junior high school student.
He's laughing.
I said, that's not true.
What should I do?
I'm scared now.
I stopped next to it.
I went.
No way.
I opened it.
4 minutes.
I wonder if it's true.
I'm so scared.
What was that?
He's scared.
I was so scared.
It's funny.
I'm scared.
Please sit down.
I'll give this to the viewers.
If you want it,
I'll give it to you.
Please write a letter.
Do you use the steering wheel I made?
I think so.
Don't lie.