In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai, we are going to have a baseball tournament!
Now that the pro baseball tournament has started, the baseball team is going to have a baseball season.
We are going to defend the baseball team.
You are the ace of Gaki Tsukai.
Sorry, I should have said it more interesting. I lost to a helicopter.
I thought it was a helicopter.
Did you lose?
I lost, I lost.
Idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot.
I'm sorry. I'm the ace of Gaki Tsukai.
I think you can tell by looking at this outfit.
I'll take it.
What about the others?
Just like that?
I think you can tell by looking at this outfit.
Where are you going to defend?
I just wanted to be funny.
Where are you going to defend when you are looking at this outfit?
I don't know where to defend.
It's an ugly outfit.
Let's go.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
The game is about to begin.
Let's get started.
As expected from producer Gordon.
The Gaki Tsukai team vs. the Haruno baseball team has finally begun.
Let's look forward to what kind of talent will appear.
Number one, second, electric groove, Pierre Taki.
Number two, Nana.
Number one is Pierre Taki.
Yamazaki is glaring at him.
Pierre, Pierre, shoot, shoot.
The game is about to begin.
Iyagao is also getting nervous.
He looks at the sign and nods.
He throws a big ball.
This is a sudden bing ball.
Yamazaki is not sure where to put his hand.
Pierre is also looking at him.
Let's get closer.
Yamazaki is challenging.
He regains his composure.
Number two.
lado bedQuery.
Stop this.
Pierre.
Don't be greedy, Pierre.
Don't shoot me.
You hit me.
He hit you.
Stop this.
ã£Go home!
What the hell are you doing?
Hey, Yamazaki
Don't get excited
Let's have fun
Finally, the two were separated
Pierre is the first
No.2
First
Nakano Hideo
Familiar with Choro
No.10
No.2 is Nakano Hideo
Yamazaki jumps
Nakano also jumps
Again
Stop it
Let's play baseball
No.1
Yamazaki jumps
He throws
The ball hits Nakano
Nakano goes to Yamazaki
Stop it
Both teams are excited
What the hell are you doing?
The controller is bad
If you use your strength, you can catch the ball
Let's have fun
Team Sky
No.1
No.3
The butterfly club
Ryuhei Ueshiba
No.7
No.11
The batter is Ueshiba
I'm watching
In the middle
I can't hit it
Yamazaki's pitching
This is a dead ball
This is Ueshiba
Sorry
Stop it
Go home
Yamazaki
You should apologize
Sorry
You messed up my field
Don't get angry
Yamazaki's strike
No.4
Center
Miyaji
No.1
Yamazaki
What kind of pitching will he show?
He is in the set position
He threw the ball
Where did you throw it?
Yamazaki
He threw the ball
I don't remember
Yamazaki
He threw a bow
When you apologize, this has to be so
Yamazaki
You made a mistake
What are you talking about?
I don't care anymore.
It's a dead ball.
You have to pass it.
Pierre.
It's a push-off.
It's a push-off with four consecutive dead balls.
The Gerojin team is one point behind.
Number 5.
Catcher.
Kenji Takano, who is familiar with Pizzeria.
Kenji Takano.
Number 17.
Now, the scary batter has come out.
He is the current pro-wrestler, Kenji Takano.
He is a power hitter with a height of 2m.
Time.
What?
Time?
Wait a minute.
I'm...
What's wrong, Yamazaki?
He calls everyone to the mound.
It's dangerous.
You said it.
Is that so?
That's right.
He said it himself.
That's not true.
He said it was funny recently.
Takano.
It's not funny.
The game resumed.
What kind of ball will Yamazaki, Kyosha, and Takano hit?
Oops.
It's a dead ball again.
I'm cool.
Really.
Takano, really.
I'm cool.
Takano.
I'm cool beauty.
I'm cool.
Takano.
Hey, he hit it lightly.
He hits it lightly.
I dont't know what happened.
No, it's fine.
It's fine.
It's OK, it's OK.
It's OK.
That's fine.
This is fine.
Indeed, Yamazaki.
That's not true!
It's your fault!
My fault?
Why?
Who told you to open the door?
It's my fault.
Then I'll do it.
Stop it!
Yamazaki!
Let's run!
Stop it!
Come on!
Ladies and gentlemen...
You know...
You know the buzzword, right?
The buzzword.
That's a simple story.
It's just a story about how many times you have to repeat it.
It's a complicated story.
I've said it before, but it's painful.
It's painful.
You don't think about it at all, do you?
You don't think about it at all.
I know.
I don't think about it at all.
But I've been saying it for about two months.
It's painful.
They've made it a buzzword.
I don't think about it at all.
Well, it's okay.
I don't know if it will become a buzzword.
How many years has it been?
I don't know.
It's stupid to think about it.
I used to say that I haven't heard of it for a long time.
Come to think of it, I'm the only one who has a buzzword.
For example?
For example, there are a lot of people who haven't noticed it.
Well...
No, really...
Say it!
You can't say, for example.
You're laughing, aren't you?
That's not what I'm laughing at right now.
What are you angry about?
That's right.
The buzzword is...
The real buzzword is...
Say it!
It's painful.
Well, it's okay.
It's never going to be a buzzword.
The buzzword that made me popular is...
It's a buzzword that's too deep to be a buzzword.
For example, what is it?
Recently, many people say,
You seem to be a little blue today.
I'm the one who said that!
Right?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I didn't say that.
I know you're going to ask me why.
If you can't say it, it's okay.
If you dare to say it, let me say it.
Until I said it, everyone didn't say it was blue.
I don't know about that.
Like it's heavy.
You can't say that.
Ah, it's heavy today.
That's what I said before I said it.
But it's become so popular that it's not even a buzzword.
I have a lot of buzzwords like this.
What else is there?
Other than that...
That's right.
It's tight.
Everyone didn't say it was tight either.
What?
In the past, everyone didn't use the word tight like that.
Eh?
What is it?
What is it with you guys?
Do you know what it means when you say, go go?
No, no, no, no, no.
These guys are no good.
I think it's better not to say things like that.
But it's starting to get weird.
I know, I know.
You're starting to get weird.
Well, it's fine.
If it's starting to get weird naturally, then in your mind...
I said that.
Well, it's fine.
With a big heart.
I said it.
It's starting to get weird.
I said it, so it's not cool.
It doesn't sound like me at all.
But...
I'm imitating you.
I'm saying the way you say it.
Why are you imitating me and you?
I often see you imitating me.
Who?
Me.
No, no, no.
I've never seen you imitating me.
I've seen it.
Really?
I've never seen it.
Does it look like you?
People around me...
They say I look like a rotten talent.
Who is a rotten talent?
I don't know.
I mean,
I'm a customer who wants to see it.
Don't buy it.
I'm saying it's a rotten talent.
I'm not saying it.
There are people who look like you.
I look like a person who looks like you.
I have a lot of them.
Don't say that.
No, no, no.
I have them.
What?
I said you look like him all the time.
Even when you're wearing clothes.
What kind of face is that?
No, no, sometimes I look like Nobu at the door
But there's no one who looks like me
There was a time when I was in Downtown Jill
When you were on the phone?
Yes, yes, yes, I was tricked by someone who looked like me
We're really similar, we're in the same car
The way we stand is exactly the same
I definitely thought it was you
I want to see that
It was you, wasn't it?
I'm going to tell you now
That woman was totally into you
She was totally into you
She was into me
What?
That's enough
I'm going to tell you now
You know, you know
First of all, I don't know what kind of image you have of women
But I've never been able to trick a woman
That's amazing
It's like a gold-plated front door
Do you remember it clearly?
But I was in Osaka
I was wearing the same clothes as you
I told her to show me this
She tried it on
It's different
You look exactly like me
I can tell by the way you talk
I don't know because I'm an amateur
But I know
Why do you know?
Even if you look exactly like me
I can tell that it's not you
Of course
But
I can tell by the position of your mole
I can tell just by looking at you
But I've never seen you up close
So I don't know
That's not true
There are people who saw you on TV for the first time
It's completely different from watching it on TV
It's completely different
I can tell why you're popular on TV
Because I saw you in person
What do you want to say?
You're talking nonsense
My legs are longer than they were on TV
It's not long
It's normal
Let's talk about that again
It's here again
It's not long
You're really
I told you not to believe everything you see
It's not what I saw
I saw it with my own eyes
What?
It's long, isn't it?
What's long?
My legs
You said it's not long
There's nothing here
It says to go deeper
There's no place to go deeper
No, no
It's not like that
It's deeper
It's here
What is it?
It's a roll
I was looking for that
What's written on it?
And then
What?
How long are you going to do this?
It's not over yet
I can't help it
When I'm working
Are you going to cut it?
Of course
If you cut it, you can use it
What do you mean?
Do you want to do it to someone?
To a bald person
Who do you want to do it to?
I said to a bald person
Give me the writing
The other day I was doing the internet
And I got a secret information from a medical person
Matsumoto-san, every month
Why are you doing a blood test to the limit of your body?
Have you ever done a blood test?
I've done it before
You can't do something like that for someone
Why?
That's a lie
It's true
How many times do I have to tell you?
Why?
How many times have you done it?
I've done it almost every day
Are you stupid?
You've done it twice to the same person
You've done it so many times
There's no way
Why?
Why do you do it to the limit of your body every month?
Do you know the limit of a human's mouth?
I don't know
How many cc did you take?
I don't remember
I was trying to cover it with mine
It's not like that
Usually you take 200 cc
Is that so?
Right?
Really?
I think you took 200 too
What?
You said 400
A little
A little bit
What do you mean by a little bit?
A tough person
A tough person?
I was amazing
A normal person took 400?
Yes
I also took a hectare
Because the people who are a tough person
call it a hectare
Because it has a name
It's called a hectare in the north again
It's a stupid name
It's called a hectare
This is stupid
A hectare?
So tell me why you're doing it
Do you want Yakult?
I'll give you a quarter
Don't be so stingy
Don't go that far
Don't think that it's the same as the Yakult you gave to your partner
and the Yakult you gave to a stingy person
The weight is different between the money you worked hard for and the money you got
I'm going to tell you about that
I'm sorry
Tell me about the weight
I'm embarrassed
The weight
What?
Mr. Matsumoto is famous for being fast
Please show us your skills
Have you ever done a fast shot?
I haven't done a fast shot
I've done a shotgun
Why?
Because you're from Tokyo?
A shotgun?
What are you going to do when you go to practice?
It's a foreign country
Are you sure it's a foreign country?
Please
A fast shot?
I haven't done a fast shot
Try it
Isn't it easy?
I'm going to do it
It's really slow
Why?
What's wrong with it?
I made a mistake from the place I went on my school trip
It's impossible
I see
I made a mistake when I went to Kutami-gaura
You too
It's too slow
Too slow
I went to the second floor
What's slow?
The posture is wrong
It's like this
If it's a shotgun, say it's a shotgun
What's wrong with it?
It's strange
Normally it's like this
No, it's like this
I feel bad
You feel bad
You look like you're going to throw up
I feel bad
Please do it
Are you sure?
Do you know what a fast shot is?
A fast shot
It means to shoot fast
I know
You can't even lift this hand
I can't say it
You can't do a fast shot
You can't even lift this hand
Hey, hey, hey
Let's do it
Let's do a fast shot
Please do it
Let's do it
Hey
What is it?
Put it in front of you
Why are you doing that?
There's no point in shooting this
It means to shoot fast
There's usually people on the other side
I don't know about that
If you shoot fast, you win
You can shoot as fast as you want
It's dangerous if you shoot here
Why is it dangerous?
I don't know if you'll hit your foot
It's a bit dangerous
I just did that
This program was brought to you by the sponsor