The 4th Gaki no Tsukai, Tsukitsuki, Ogiri, Daigatsu!
Good evening, everyone. I'm Masatoshi Hamada, the 4th Gaki no Tsukai.
Now, let's have Hanashika-san come on stage. Hanashika-san, please!
Hanashika-san, please introduce yourself one by one.
Thank you very much. The other day, I received a letter from a fan, and there was a hiragana on every kanji.
I'm not an idiot! Look at me! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
The other day, Mr. Hamada appeared on the main character's drama, and when I acted, he said,
Yes, okay! What do you mean by that? I'll do my best!
Thank you very much!
The other day, I co-starred with Yumero Oyako. I'm the manager, Okamoto. Nice to meet you.
I'm Matsuro Toshitoshi, 29 years old. My favorite show is Tsukitsuki!
Now, let's have Hanashika-san come on stage.
Excuse me, Mr. Hamada. May I introduce myself?
Excuse me.
I'm your assistant, and I'm the director...
What are you talking about?
I'm Tokusho Atakamo!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
That's enough!
I'm going to use this book, and I'm going to read a book as if it were written by Atakamo.
First of all, this is Michael Jackson's story.
Start!
Hello!
The title of the book is Hello!
I was born in Ohio.
Is that so?
I was born at the age of 18, and I had a plastic surgery.
You had a plastic surgery at the age of 18, didn't you?
Yes.
Until I had a plastic surgery, I had nicknames such as Jacky, Silica, Jack-yan, and Mai-san.
That's enough!
Don't give me nicknames!
When I was on my first date, Mai-san touched my nose.
Don't touch me!
I was angry.
At that time, she said...
I did it!
She did it.
She did it at that time.
I wonder if I should have done more.
But Mai-san said this.
Mai-san said,
If you like me, catch me.
What are you talking about?
No, no, no, no, no.
What, is it Hamabe?
It's Hamabe.
Hamabe.
And Mai-san's nose was removed.
Don't take it, don't take it.
I closed my eyes slowly.
I'm in the present.
Next is here.
Headphone full-on game.
The music is playing from the headphones.
I'm going to tell you what I'm saying in order.
The first topic is here.
The winner is...
Dave Spector.
What?
Is there such a word?
Why?
Taylor Senpuda.
What is that?
I don't know either.
Okamoto-san.
The answer is Dave Spector.
Don't clap.
What was your name?
Dave Spector.
I'm Dave Spector too.
Dave Senpuda.
Dave Spector.
The answer is...
The winner is Dave Spector.
The last topic is here.
The music is playing from the headphones.
Today...
Why do you say today twice?
I'm emphasizing today.
Yay, yay, yay.
Today...
That's enough.
I have something at home.
That's good.
Let's go.
Get ready.
Go ahead.
You are a funky monkey baby.
I'm going crazy.
But I'm in love.
My girlfriend...
Ok, guitar.
That's too much.
What about the solo guitar?
I said ok.
You said it.
I said it.
Yamazaki.
Yes.
Which one?
This one.
The toilet.
Yay, yay, yay.
Is it convenient for you?
Yes.
I can't get out.
Next.
And me.
Chin chin.
V V.
Ie-chan.
Shawa-chan.
Next.
Yes.
I'm a monster human who lives in the dark.
I'm a monster human who can't show himself to others.
I want to be a human soon.
I'll shoot away the dark fate.
It's a black bat.
It's a monster shark.
And gentlemen.
Good morning.
It's been a long time since I started.
It's the same as usual.
Yes, yes, yes.
It can't be helped.
After all, it's all up to the audience to get on the stage.
That's right.
The audience is bad.
If the audience is bad, I won't get on the stage.
I see.
I don't think it's a good audience today.
Is that so?
You know, before Team Zero goes on stage, a girl goes on stage, right?
Yes.
Not a single girl laughs.
It's like being in a team.
It's quiet.
Why do you think Team Zero is doing this?
There's still a long way to go.
It's no good.
Well, I don't have any comedians to be acknowledged.
What?
Don't bite me again.
Don't you have any comedians to be acknowledged?
I didn't say I didn't have any comedians.
I don't have any.
I understand.
Let's give them a name.
What are you doing?
I don't have any comedians to be acknowledged.
If you say that, then...
Enoken.
That's old-fashioned.
I thought that was true.
If I don't say why I don't have comedians to be acknowledged,
they'll think I'm rude.
Let me explain this.
What is it?
It's natural not to be acknowledged.
Why?
Because today is more interesting than yesterday, and tomorrow is more interesting than today.
I'm next to you.
There's no reason why the comedy in the past is more interesting than the comedy in the present.
I understand.
Then, I can't be acknowledged in the present.
For example...
Don't say it.
For example, I did this.
I got this much.
This is the present.
But the next one is in the past.
I can't be acknowledged in the present.
That's already in the past.
I don't think about the present.
Why are you being so honest?
You're so mean, Maria.
Why?
Who is acknowledged?
That's better, isn't it?
I'm acknowledged.
That's right.
I can't be acknowledged in the present.
But to be honest, I'm the most interesting one.
That's good.
I know that.
Who is not acknowledged?
That's great.
There's a scream machine in this hall.
There is a scream machine.
There's a scream machine in your hall.
I've heard that you complain to people in your life.
I didn't hear that.
I'm going to have a bad talk again this week.
I'm going to do this 30 minutes.
You're the one who's talking.
Get back the human mind.
There was a magazine written by Mie Nakawa.
He said something like this recently.
He said, I only say bad things.
I've been watching you since you started laughing.
You can laugh even if you don't say bad things.
Why do you only say bad things?
Disappointment.
This is a really good word.
This is a good word.
I'm not good at saying such things.
After all, when I'm told, I can't accept it honestly.
What's right is right.
No matter how many bad words you say.
Is that so?
Let's admit that.
So it's okay.
I just wanted to ask you a little bit at first.
Because you say that.
Let's stop doing that.
That's right.
Saying that kind of thing.
It's a sense of resentment.
What is it?
But I can't see Nagao saying that.
I can't see Nagao saying that.
I can't help it.
This is a pattern.
I want to laugh.
Recently, I've been having bad luck.
I've been having bad luck.
There was a time when it was popular.
Is there such a thing?
I don't know if the fortune teller is right.
There's definitely a Biorhythm of fortune.
Why? Did something happen?
No, it's not bad.
What is it?
I'm scared.
If you say that kind of thing.
It's a sense of resentment.
I can't help it.
It's a gang.
Why?
No, it's not good.
It's too bad.
Why don't you have a better woman?
It's a woman with a more
I'm a fan.
Why don't you send me a picture?
Why do you say that?
It's true that this Hitoshi Matsumoto is.
It's a pretty good rank.
But Hitoshi Matsumoto.
Who are you?
I'm right next to you.
I don't have a woman.
Do you have that?
No, I used to have a little more.
That's forcibly, isn't it?
It's like a rape killer.
No, it's not forcibly.
Even if you don't have a lover.
If you persuade me with this,
First of all,
I don't have a woman to marry.
Women are basically stupid creatures.
Is that so?
Women are stupid creatures.
What do you mean?
You say men and women are equal, right?
That's absolutely impossible.
Why?
For example,
I'm doing men and women are equal.
What do you mean?
For example, there are ugly boys.
You say you want to look ugly.
Even if the girl is ugly,
I say I'm ugly.
That's called men and women are equal.
It's men and women are equal.
I say I'm a pig.
To a woman who is fat.
When I say that,
It's horrible for a girl.
I say it with a ugly face.
I'm doing men and women are equal.
A woman who says it's bad for me.
I don't have the right to say it's men and women are equal.
Is that so?
Men and women are equal, right?
Yes.
There are times when you hit a man like this, and sometimes you hit a woman like this.
You hit a woman by force?
No, I was pissed off.
This is a good thing you're saying now, Hama-chan.
Why?
Yamashiro, stop it.
This is a good thing you're saying now, Hama-chan.
Today I will introduce the story of Totteki.
Totteki?
Yes, Totteki.
That's a big one.
That's Mutsugoro.
The other day, I found him at a famous hotel in Tokyo.
I approached him and asked,
Are you Mutsugoro?
He said,
Yes, I am.
What kind of attitude is that?
He said,
Yes, I am.
What kind of disease is this?
I asked him,
I don't understand why an amateur like you would say something like this.
I didn't write it.
You're dead.
Chatoran.
I didn't write it.
But if it's true, it's amazing.
I don't know if he's an animal lover.
He likes all animals, right?
That's right.
But animals are very discriminated against, right?
If someone calls him a dog or a wolf or a baby,
He's loved a lot.
Like a kid.
If you say you're going to kill a kid,
Everyone says, I feel sorry for you.
What about sharks?
I don't know why sharks are killed so easily.
Is that so?
Everyone here is a shark, so it doesn't matter how peaceful it is.
So if I love all animals,
I'll admit it.
Even in the sea,
If you say you're going to kill a shark,
People will think you really love animals.
If Matsumoto is a TV producer and makes a trendy detective drama,
What kind of title would you like?
But I think we need to think a little more.
What kind of title do you have now?
What are you?
Dekakizoku.
What is Dekakizoku?
What are you talking about?
That's right.
Dekakizoku.
It's an interesting show for those who are doing it.
That's right.
What kind of title do you have now?
What are you talking about?
What is Dekakizoku?
You're a TV producer, aren't you?
Idiot!
People who are on TV are really nice,
What are you talking about?
Dekakizoku.
It sounds good, doesn't it?
What else do you have?
What is Dekakizoku?
That's right.
Dangerous.
Dangerous Dekakizoku.
What are you talking about?
Where did you do that?
Did you do it?
I think the title should be played more.
I think it will change more and more from now on.
I see.
Dekakizoku had seven dekakizoku, didn't it?
In the past.
Even so, five or six dekakizoku.
How do you do that?
It's already spring.
You said five or six dekakizoku.
What are you going to do with the opening?
Normally, you come out with a detective or something.
What are you going to do with five or six dekakizoku?
That's why it starts with walking on the airfield.
I know.
Five or six dekakizoku.
It's like G-men 75.
What are you going to walk?
There's a guy like this who's a little out of the blank.
There's something.
Half out.
Can you do it properly?
What?
In the drama.