Next, we have downtown's Gaki-no-Tsukai-ya-ara-hende.
Please watch!
Gaki-no-Tsukai-ya-ara-hende!
What's the matter with you all?
Are you ready?
I'd like to have fun with everyone!
Let's have them on stage right away!
Today, we've prepared a lot of things for you.
It's a simple story about why you got hit from behind.
That's right.
This...
What is this?
It says it's a good eye.
Hey!
Your head is messed up.
You can set it up later.
I can't see at all.
Which one is cooler?
It matches this jumper.
No, I don't need that eye.
I don't need that eye.
Here I go!
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?
It's so tight!
Who the hell is this guy?
What's the correct answer?
Number 5.
Number 2!
Mr. Ami.
Yes.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
Let's go.
What are you holding?
You tell me.
Why did you get hit?
Here, here, here, here.
Let's do it again.
You know what I mean, right?
You tell me right away.
Here we go.
I'm the manager of Yoshimoto factory.
Oh, this chair.
You're wrong.
What's your answer, Hamada?
Here we go.
Why do you look so happy?
Let's go.
Don't move.
Let's do it again.
What?
You're a bad guy.
What's your answer, Otomo?
I don't think so.
I don't know either.
You're a bad guy.
Your answer is this.
Let's do it again.
Here we go.
Here comes number four.
And...
Oh, no.
No, Otomo, no.
No, no.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
I'm sorry.
What are you sorry about?
What's your answer?
I'm sorry.
Wow.
You're a bad guy.
Are you ready?
Yes.
What?
You're a bad guy.
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
Don't move.
Don't raise your hand.
Wait a minute.
Are you okay?
What?
What are you doing?
You're a bad guy.
Here we go.
Hey.
You.
You're a bad guy.
Yamanashi.
Let's go, Yamanashi.
Where are you going?
You are the one who is scared.
This is scary.
Now, what is this?
Is it over?
Yes.
I will kick you.
Just like that.
What will happen if I do this?
It's scary.
I can do it if I do this.
No, it's slippery now.
I can do it if I wear it.
No, no, no.
I can do it if I do this.
Sit down.
I will do this.
No, no, no.
You guys can't do it.
I can't do it.
Last year, we had a bet.
Who will win?
After 5 and a half hours, one of us will be naked.
After that, we will be naked for hours.
We will be naked.
We will be naked from 4 to 5 in the morning.
Please watch it.
Yes.
We will show you the making next week.
After 5 and a half hours, one of us will be naked.
After that, we will be naked.
Are you ready?
Yes, I am.
I am looking forward to the ratings.
Yes, yes.
You can't be on the show.
How long will you be on the show?
I have been on the show for 5 hours.
You can sleep once.
You can live in the morning.
I don't know when the next episode will come out.
As of now, we have been on the show for 5 hours.
The show has been finished.
The next episode will start in the morning.
It will start at 5 and a half hours.
Yes, yes.
The real caravan has been running for a long time.
We have been on the show for 5 hours.
So I'll be like this for about 5 minutes, and if it's 5 minutes, I'll immediately change to the weather forecast for the morning.
I feel like I'm going to lose.
I don't care if I do carabao.
It's early in the morning.
Instead, if I do carabao, you do garrison.
What is that?
Say Hayami.
Why are you doing that?
Why?
I don't care.
If you call me at home, I'll be like you.
I'll do it.
I don't care.
Even though I'm sleeping.
I'll watch it.
That's the first thing I'll do.
That's the only thing I'll say as an announcement.
If this program ends, I'll be on the show in 5 and a half hours.
It's a busy season right now.
My apartment in Osaka is a one-room apartment.
I'm sorry to say this, but I don't have a lot of money.
I've been living next door for about a week.
What is it?
I'm asking for my money back.
That's scary.
Really?
I've never heard that before.
It's a live voice.
It's about 1 and a half in the middle of the night.
I thought I'd take a nap while watching a video.
I'm doing this.
I don't know if you're hiding.
Come out.
It's hard.
I thought you were with your girlfriend.
That's not good.
You're the one who's going to pay back what you borrowed.
That's right.
It's hard.
Is this it?
I think so.
About two.
Two of you?
The guy next door.
I know he was washing his clothes a few hours ago.
I know he was doing it.
It's been about two hours.
Turn off the lights.
He's doing it.
Poor guy.
Is he a young guy?
I've never seen him.
Poor guy.
It can't be helped.
It's 1 and a half in the middle of the night.
I thought it was rude to take a nap.
At that time.
I thought I'd take a nap while watching a video.
There are two of you, right?
There are two of you.
But I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do.
Open the door.
Get out of here.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
Are you going to live like this?
Don't do that.
What are you doing?
Don't open the door.
Stop it.
Stop.
I can't stop two people.
I can beat them to dance to the rhythm.
You two are going to be beaten.
I'm totally fine.
I can't do this.
I can't avoid it.
I'm just shaking.
I'm really alright.
I'm scared of those kinds of things.
Well, it's their job.
You've been there too, haven't you?
I've been there a long time ago.
What was it?
Hand-shaped.
My father fell on the back of the hand-shaped one.
He fell, didn't he?
And he was taken away like an alien that my father captured.
He was taken away!
My father was taken away somewhere.
He was imprisoned.
He said, I'll be back in a few days.
He was taken away from a small window like a prison.
Are you kidding me?
It's true.
See?
This is Nakata Botan.
So, when he was in a terrible situation,
he would do a manzai like this, right?
His sleeves would be like this.
A debt-trigger.
When he said, I'm back!
He would run away from here.
He was a bad guy.
He would run from the entrance like this.
He was taken away, like you said.
He was taken away from a small window like this.
He ran to the rice field.
He was runny.
He came to the theater the next morning.
He was like a baby.
Bad guy!
If he went that far.
It's amazing.
Recycling is really scary, isn't it?
It's scary, isn't it?
You see, in the past, I didn't do that kind of recycling, but...
There's this thing called Ojiyanoma Shopping, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
There's a guy who bought that.
Ah, it's a prank, right?
It's a prank.
Then, he comes, right?
Pay up, pay up.
I came.
That...
It's called the Youth Set.
Ah, yes, yes, yes.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
It's called the Nigiri Gekitaisuru.
Something like that.
There's a guy called Spon, Spon.
I came.
That's the Youth Set, right?
It's the Youth Set.
I was leaving it there.
I can't send it to you.
I think it's because of the fans.
You're a fan, but you're leaving it there?
I've done a lot of things like that before.
I see.
It's one of those things.
The Youth Set.
I was leaving it there thinking that I was doing it.
I kept saying, pay up, pay up, pay up, pay up.
Ah, pay up.
Pay up, pay up, pay up.
I left it there.
The fourth time, the fifth time.
When it's about the fifth time, that's the kind of attitude you have.
That's the kind of attitude you have.
So you can't pay up?
If you're like that, you can't even take legal action.
I see.
I came, paid up, made a big call.
Made a big call.
I'm waiting.
I'm saying, hey!
I suddenly got sad.
I didn't even tell the person in charge.
I said, I'm going to go out.
Hey, you!
You can go out, but what's the Youth Set?
Did you mess up your youth?
Hey!
Help me, Popeye!
The other day, my mother told me to do whatever I want.
I did whatever I wanted, but she scolded me again.
Then what should I do?
I have a dad who says things like this.
He says things like this to his girlfriend.
But there are a lot of places like that.
When I was told to make tea,
my face changed.
I said, I'm going to make it!
I said, I'm going to go to the kitchen.
I really don't know what to do.
If I point there, I'll be in trouble.
I said, I got it, I'll make it.
What are you going to do?
You'll end up putting the tea in.
In the end, I'll be in trouble if I drink it.
Then drink it.
Why won't you let me drink it?
It's really annoying.
I drink it once.
That's why, when I open the door,
the glass door opens like this.
It's broken here.
It's bleeding.
I said, I'm going to drink it.
I said, bring me a handkerchief.
That's right.
It's bleeding here.
I thought you were playing a water game.
Why do I have to do it with you?
Hello, Osai-san.
It's often said that men complain.
What kind of state is that?
Complain?
Ah, I'm sorry.
You complain, right?
You want to do it, right?
You complain.
You complain, right?
Yes.
When do you complain?
When I'm tired.
It happens.
Right?
When you're on the Shinkansen,
you wake up early in the morning,
you get on the Shinkansen and go to bed, right?
No.
Never.
It's going to explode.
It's going to explode, right?
It's harder than iron.
You can't even do a reclining.
It's going to explode, right?
Good evening.
I have a question.
A lot of people are running at night, right?
Yes.
Why do those people often write kanji?
It's often written on the wall with a spray.
And they often use calligraphy.
Where do you think that came from?
Dan-dan, please tell me.
There are a lot of them these days.
I wonder why.
These days, those people are ugly.
They used to be beautiful.
There were a lot of beautiful women in the past.
These days, those people are ugly.
They're fat and ugly.
They're annoying.
They're crazy.
Don't show off.
In movies,
in TV shows,
they're cool because they're actors.
They say,
I'm the president.
But in real life,
in the movies,
in the movie theaters,
they say,
I'm the president.
I'll do it anytime.
You're a little high.
You look like you can win.
I look like I can win.
An amateur can't speak.
It's hard.
You're a little stupid.
Nice to meet you.
You're not speaking.
You're a little nervous.
Everyone will say,
What are you?
That's no good.
Let's go home.
Let's talk about the theme.
The theme?
When I was a kid,
when I was in elementary school,
I was bullied again.
After lunch,
we ate as soon as we could.
It was a race to go to the gym.
One day,
I ate the first one and ran.
The next guy was coming.
I had to go to the gym as soon as possible.
When I came,
I was grabbed from behind.
My arm was beaten.
I fell down.
I was taken to the health center.
Everyone was like this.
It's hard.
It's a counterattack.
I don't have the guts.
I'm a little weak.
You're already in the blue.
I'm already in the blue.
That's what they say.
Everyone was alone.
I drank milk.
I was like this.
I drank milk on my head.
On your head?
Yes, yes, yes.
I knew it smelled,
so I went to the hospital.
I was like this.
I was kicked out.
My mother sometimes wore red pants.
When I was in elementary school,
I didn't know that.
You can't stand out.
That's right.
When I went to the party,
I was like this.
It's a man.
It's just a man.
Matsumoto pants are red.
It's a man.
I was surprised.
Hey! Stop!
That's Tomiko.
We played together on New Year's Eve.
What did you do?
I went to the movies.
What did you go to?
The Truck Man.
I was watching the Truck Man together.
There was a man next to me.
He was in the military.
Do you know?
I don't know.
You don't know?
I was looking at the screen and the old man next to me was standing and doing a handstand.
It was a very good scene.
Oh, I remember.
You don't?
I don't remember.
Then, the movie theater was all like, zawazawazawa.
Ba-n, pa-pa-pa, pambarapam.
What are you doing?
I was turning around.
I was looking at the screen and the old man next to me was standing and doing a handstand.
I think the old man was a bit more dominant.
No, I think the young man was more dominant this time.
You were able to distinguish them well.
There was no problem at all.
Yes, yes, yes.
Thank you very much.