Yoh-kan-kan-no
Yoh-kan-kusai wa nakayoshi da
Itsumo futari de nitsu yoh-kan
Yoh-kan-no danna
Yoh-kan-no yome
Yoru wa kuri yoh-kan
No, no, no
I'm sorry, I really didn't mean it from the beginning
Don't say that, Matsumoto!
I don't know if you'll say that
Today...
I'm really sleepy
Matsumoto, don't say that!
I'm sorry, really
I slept too much the day before
I couldn't sleep at all yesterday
I couldn't sleep until around noon
I was like, I'm done!
You were awake?
I woke up, and then I woke up
I have lotion left on my body
I'm sorry, but I'm really sleepy
I'm really, really, really, really sleepy
I'm really sorry
I was passing by Harajuku Station
There was a pharmacy in front of Harajuku Station
And there was a tea-salon called Tea-Salon Kaze
I know that place
It's really really really really
I was driving my car, and I heard the name Tea-Salon Foo
You're saying that too much
It's true!
In this world, Foo?
I thought it was Nami Nami Foo
I'm really sorry
Do you know what a brain is?
What?
Hiragana's brain
Do you know Hiragana's brain?
What?
Hiragana's brain
I've been researching a lot about the brain
The brain is an interesting thing
It's proof that the brain is being licked
I don't know what you're talking about
Then tell us
What does it mean?
For example
It's called Kabutomushi
It's not called Kabutomushi, right?
No, it's not
Right? It's called Kabutomushi
It's the first time you've been able to get your brain
You've gained citizenship
You haven't been licked
What is he talking about?
No, no, no
Karate chop is strange, right?
It's strange
It's Karate chop, right?
It's strange that you're saying Karate chop
But you used to say it
Really?
Maybe when Karate didn't gain citizenship
There was Karate
This is chop, right?
You used to say that this is Karate chop
I didn't say Karate chop
No, no, no
That's not what I'm trying to say
Golf club
Right?
Golf has penetrated into everyone, so it's called a golf club
In the past, when golf wasn't that popular
They used to call it a golf club
A golf club
So when you have a brain, it's proof that you've been licked
It means that you haven't been recognized as a person yet
What's there to be licked?
For example, let's talk about the easiest one
Downtown Matsumoto
This is because you're loved
It's established
Downtown Matsumoto
You've already gained citizenship
But you're a sad downtown Hamada
You're being licked
That's your way of saying it
No, no, no
You can say downtown Matsumoto
You can say downtown Hamada
The level is low
Why do you say that?
I'm asking if there's anything else that's licked
Hamada's nipples
That's right, Hamada's nipples
You haven't gained citizenship
Are you referring to Matsumoto's nipples?
Matsumoto's nipples
That's your way of saying it
Is that so?
When people hear it, they think it's licked
If you don't say it
You know
Matsumoto's
You can't say that
I want to say this
It's easier to understand
Let me say this
Matsumoto's nipples
This is a no
Because Matsumoto doesn't have nipples
Hamada's nipples
This is because you've gained citizenship
No, I haven't
It's because you're all smelly
It's because you know you're all smelly
That's why you've gained citizenship
Why can't you just say no?
It's strange
You should say something that everyone can understand
It's because you're alone
I'm not alone
No is
Say something that's easy to understand
You know this right?
It's because you're alone
This song
That's impossible
I heard it on Japanese TV
No it's not like that
Japanese TV is probably the fastest
It's because you're alone
Let's watch Japanese TV
No it's not like that
The reason why you lost your brain
Is because Japanese TV has accepted you
So if I want to say something
It doesn't matter
Just do your best so you can gain your brain
That's a joke
You can't just close it like that
I can't understand
If you do that
It's always going to be 7-3
What?
It's because you're alone
Matsumoto-san said that you spent your youth in a monkey mountain
Yes in a monkey mountain
It seems that the more your butt is red the more popular you are
Why is that?
Please teach me how to break my hair so that even a monkey can understand
I know a lot about animals
I understand
What do you think?
I don't know
Even if you say red
It's because you're fat
I'm fat?
What?
I don't know that word
Do you know?
I'm fat
The intonation is weird
What do you mean by fat?
It's because you're sticking out
You don't use it?
I don't use it
I'm sticking out
What?
What's wrong with a black guy?
There are black guys too
They stick out like a rose
There are
It's because they're popular with monkeys
Why?
If you think with the same values as humans
There's no answer
You can't think of it as a monkey
Please teach me
For a monkey
What do you think a butt is for humans?
Other than a butt
For example
You do this
Yes
What's that for humans?
Propose
Propose?
It's like a negligee
It's pretty
That's why
In that way
Animals have things that humans can compare to
I see
What's a monkey for a butt?
I thought a lot about what it is
If I put it in front of humans
I don't know this anymore
When I threw a stick
This is it
If I put it in front of humans
A monkey's butt is like a sports car
Ouch
A bright red sports car
A red sports car
You want to ride it
You say that
That's terrible
Don't ever say that in front of me
I'm sorry
I don't understand
Why are you so stubborn?
What?
What I said is wrong, right?
What's wrong?
A sports car
You said it
Please tell me the answer
This is negligee
That's why it's wrong
Are you okay?
This is negligee
Are there any other animals?
A deer
A deer has a horn
It says I'm a man
If you put that in front of humans
It's a hair liquid
That's what you say
A lion's male
Can't he be bald?
If he can be bald
What's the cause?
He can be bald
He can be bald?
Please tell me the cause
I haven't seen a lion that's bald
That's because humans don't know how to make a lion bald
How to make a lion bald?
It's easy to make a lion bald
Let's think about the mechanism
Stress
If you get stressed, you can make a lion bald
Without a doubt
For example, a lion
It doesn't matter if it's a zoo
Let's go in front of a lion
A lion will pretend to be a house
I think I'm strong
If you come
It's like this
A lion is powerful
Then
It's like this
This is the annoying part of them
Don't let it happen
Say wow
Wow
I'm interested
I'll tell you
That's funny
Then the lion
What is it?
I'll say
After returning home at night
I was told something strange
I'm worried
I'm in a bad mood
Today's guest was strange
Tomorrow, as usual
I'll be strong
The next day
Wow
It's cold
Kiss
Thank you for watching