Suddenly, a visitor appears at Ichido's place, relaxed and ready for the show.
Damn it.
Good morning.
We're here to get a gala.
What is it?
24 hours.
24 hours?
Yes, the punishment game.
The one before?
Yes.
What did you do?
I've been doing it all along.
What?
I'm here.
You were doing the Thai kick?
Yes, I was.
Itao has appeared again.
This time, he's doing the Thai kick himself,
after the 24 hour punishment game.
Is it really Itao who made everyone fall into a
And his real purpose is...
That's a lie, it's not like that
The costume is different
The material is different
It's shiny
The tension is different from the actual performance
The way it looks is different
It's not that safe
I'll show you the kick.
I'm sorry for the kick.
I kicked about 7 times.
I've been doing this all the time.
You're going to pop now.
But...
The gyal is...
It's okay to pay for it.
Pay for it?
Yes.
This time...
I'm just saying it.
Let's do it for 10,000 yen.
Then, 10,000 yen.
10,000 yen...
I'll pay 10,000 yen.
And then, three of us.
30,000 yen for three people.
What do you mean by three people?
My wife and children...
Hey! Hey! Come in!
You're kidding me!
It's definitely not true!
It's not true!
Hey, wait a minute!
It's so small!
Did you do it?
I did it, right?
You're not involved, right?
Yes.
I'm not involved.
You're not involved, right?
But actually, I did it.
Let's show the evidence.
There is.
There is evidence.
What is this?
Look at this.
This is the game of life.
You did play with this, right?
I did, but...
This is the one.
You prepared this for me?
No matter what he says, he doesn't back down.
It can't be helped, the producer, Sugai, has to pay for the character he has been asking for.
I don't have to say it, but I think it's a bit too much.
This is really...
It's not normal.
But...
Normally, this kind of thing will never be able to be passed.
If this kind of thing were to be passed, I wouldn't be able to stay silent.
You're looking at it with a big smile.
You do a lot of things.
I don't think I can do it like this.
And also, that thing...
You did something with the Kiki.
Yes, yes.
Kiki tobacco, Kiki coffee.
This is curry.
I did that too.
Your wife.
Kiki coffee.
I brought the video so can you see it?
The prize money is 200,000 yen. Itaoka Kiki Coffee Competition.
Can my wife guess correctly?
The coffee she will guess is this one.
Let's try it.
Let's start.
Please, the fourth one.
I'm going to take a picture.
Please remember the taste.
Did you remember?
Now, can you guess the fourth one?
Please take a picture.
Now, let's start the coffee machine.
I'm not sure.
I drank milk and coffee.
Congratulations on the correct answer!
You have won 200,000 yen!
Yay!
Yes.
It's a fun show.
So, you've come to get the prize money.
Huh?
I think it's that one.
First, there are many things I have to say.
That's right.
Umm...
What should we start with?
Kiki Coffee isn't a successful company.
It's more successful than that.
Why?
Because it's Brazilian.
I can't accept that my wife is Brazilian.
To be honest, what is your purpose?
You're making a connection with our company.
There are many other things too.
There are.
If you go to such a place, you'll be treated like a ***.
It's a strange place.
Moreover, Itao started to do the trial of the show, Itao's Wife, with a sexy excuse.
Sexy!
Itao can't control his excitement.
That night, the Itao couple were either in love or not in love.
How was it?
It was fun, right?
And, since she's such an interesting woman,
I thought she'd become a regular.
That's how far I've come.
What's a regular?
No, the kid's wife.
The wife?
Yes.
Even though she can't show her face?
That's right.
Even though she can't show her face.
Well, you see,
this Kokoriko Yamazaki...
What?
Yamazaki has been on TV for the second time.
He's been on TV for the second time.
It's about time.
You mean you're going to change your wife and Yamazaki?
I think so.
That's not true.
Well, Yamazaki's potential is pretty low.
It's low but...
Please stop.
Please say it properly.
But I think that opinion is...
What is it?
That's not good.
I was doing something.
What?
Something with dolls.
Dolls?
Chucky?
I think it's fun. But it's more fun to do it with my wife.
That's not good.
Then, Yamagaki, you're a comedian with a long life.
So, even if it's just for fun, I can do it.
It's okay.
I'll show you a little bit of Yamagaki.
Yes, yes.
I'm told that I'm losing to the newbie.
I'll show you a little bit.
Please watch it from now on.
Okay.
I'll do it. I'm very motivated.
Are you motivated?
I'm motivated.
What?
What is this?
I just realized that he's forcing his teeth.
That's not true.
Using the regular way of using the toilet, Yamazaki and the wife of the chef are experiencing a close-up experience.
Happy birthday to you!
This program is brought to you by the sponsors you see.
Wadou-san, are you ready for Yamazaki?
Yes, I am.
This is a long time ago.
He tried to make another boom in the world.
To be honest, that was a failure.
It was a failure, but it was more fun than a wife.
Let's go.
Please, Yamazaki's Chucky.
I'm ready!
Wow!
I'm coming!
That's good.
She's ready.
I'm ready!
I am a sadistic person!
Make captain!
Help me!
Give you!
I did it.
Hey, you...
What's with that face?
What?
Can you be quiet?
I can't do it, but it was good, right?
It was good.
I was shaking my hand before opening the curtains.
That was funny.
You can't do it, can you?
Yamazaki is not funny at all.
My face is funny.
Really?
It's the first time I've seen it.
I've seen it.
You haven't seen it.
Let's see it.
My wife's.
Yamazaki is not funny at all.
I heard that earlier.
Next is Itao's wife Chucky.
So, Itao's wife...
Leave it to me.
Leave it to me, I know Itao.
I did it right away.
At home?
I said it was more fun, and I did it right away.
Itao's wife Chucky, go ahead!
I don't hide anymore
you must crazy
This is amazing!
What should I do?
Wait a minute!
It's a regular.
But, Yamazaki has been...
Since the second time...
That's the only thing I can say.
Yamazaki, leave it to me.
That's right. It's long.
It's long, so the reason is...
That's a great reason, but...
It's not that I don't think it's funny.
Well, I'm fine with it, right?
Well, it's not really good.
Itao gave up his regular replacement with Yamazaki.
But his intention was directed towards Endo.
Endo?
Yes.
Yes, me too.
What were you doing?
If I had to say it on this show, I was doing high tension.
Ah, I see.
This is...
I did this.
That was a bit strong.
My wife is probably more interesting.
As far as I can see, I think she's interesting.
Right? You want to see her, right?
Can you do high tension?
Of course.
Really?
If you can do it, I'm totally fine with it.
There are things that only men can do.
That's right.
Are you okay?
Shirakobeku.
What are you talking about?
Shirakobeku?
What?
What's wrong with Shirakobeku?
I think you got the wrong input.
That's right.
After the regular day of the kids, Endo and Itao's wives are having a competition.
Endo, I want you to do your best.
I'm getting a little crazy.
It's okay.
You're the one who's going to be told off.
No, no, no. It's fine.
It wasn't fine.
Now, show us your smile!
Look at that body.
That body is just right.
That movement is just right.
You've gotten a little better.
This is it.
I know the rhythm of Samba.
I want to go to Ghost Town.
That's right.
What are you doing?
That was good.
You're not laughing at all.
What?
Endo is not funny at all.
Endo is disgusting.
You're not laughing at all.
Endo is not funny at all.
Endo is disgusting.
Well, it's just a trick.
If you're not happy, just say it.
Ahhhhhhhhhh!
Is that okay?
It's not okay!
It's really okay!
There's no way I'm going to lose!
No, you should just sit down.
You're the senior.
What's with that?
Next up is the wife's high tension.
Can the amateur's girlfriend do it?
Please give me the high tension of your wife!
Can you do the samba rhythm?
I want to go to the booth
I'm back
But this is...
You've already got it
What should I do?
What do you think, Endo?
Honestly, I lost to him in 6-4.
I understand.
Then, as promised, let's change it.
Endo-san.
Wait a minute.
I can do many things.
If I just follow the current method, 6-4...
Honestly, it's 8-2.
It's 8-2, honestly.
You can ignore it.
Really?
There will be a time when Senpai will do strange things.
Wait a minute.
It's good, right?
There are many other things.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's not just that.
It's just that.
It's good.
Sorry, but there is a high tension next time.
The company is being included in the schedule.
If you can go to the end now.
That's right.
Then, well, the partner of Endo, Tanaka, you did something, right?
Tanaka?
Well, recently, I've been doing a mixed-sacrifice with Hoero.
This is...
A mixed-sacrifice.
You can do a mixed-sacrifice with that.
I see. Then, well, it's a combination of the two.
Then, Tanaka and my wife will fight.
Why are you fighting with an amateur's wife?
That's right!
I don't understand why you're fighting.
Why are you losing so easily?
With the help of the regular of Gakinosuke,
Tanaka and Itao's wives are going to fight with Matsuda Yusaku's G-PAN.
Let's go!
Tanaka's G-PAN, please!
Go ahead!
Who's there again?
Nice.
How are you?
I'm good.
Good.
Ready!
Thank you!
Now, from here.
It's a little hot.
What the hell is this?
Nice.
I told you.
I'm not saying that.
Arrangement.
It's really similar.
That's the name.
I don't want to die.
Amazing.
It's good.
I don't want to die.
Arrangement.
This is the best.
Yes!
This is definitely a good one.
I think it's a perfect one.
I don't know why, but I'm already surprised.
It's okay, right?
I was a little surprised.
This is amazing.
This is impossible.
I see.
Tanaka is totally funny.
Tanaka is young and hairy.
What does that have to do with anything?
My video is completely funny.
What?
What do you mean by that?
Tanaka is not funny at all.
I said I understand.
Young and hairy.
I can't say that I don't understand.
Will he be able to overcome Tanaka?
Please give me the G-PAN.
Then, give me the G.
Give me the G.
It's important. Give me the G.
What is this?
I don't want to die.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
That was amazing.
How was it?
It was very similar.
It was similar.
But it was heavy.
Well, that's right.
The use of the makiwaki is interesting.
It's interesting or not, it's similar.
If you say it's interesting...
It's not like you're imitating.
That's right.
It's interesting.
You're funny.
Hey.
Hey!
Wait a minute.
Isn't that a true story?
What?
Hey, are you okay?
I'm not okay.
Hey, someone, an ambulance!
It's not an ambulance.
That's right.
Hey, Mr. Itagawa.
Why are you a foreigner?
Are you okay?
I'm a
It's not the time to be laughing.
Are you okay?
The breath of the cow.
Hey!
Are you okay?
You're so messy.
No, it's not like that.
This is a big problem.
No, no, no.
This is it.
Three shots in the chest.
It was pierced.
Oh, it's a bra.
There's no way that's real.
But it's actually like this.
Is it going to die?
It's already in a coma.
Is it a shrink?
The owner is Yamada.
What?
What a perfect timing!
I'm in a pack of popcorn!
Is that the guy?
Hey...
Hey, wake up!
You're not going to help me, are you?
What?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Is that all you can say?
What?
It's not shaking.
It's not dead.
It's gone in a flash.
It's not dead, but it's a little strange.
Oh, something amazing is coming up.
Hey, are you okay?
Hey!
Teacher, are you okay?
Tonight is Yamada.
I understand.
Hey!
Yamada!
Shikase!
What?
Of course, it's late.
Oh no, Yamada!
He's dead!
He's dead, right?
He's dead.
I can't read!
I can't read.
I don't like when you say that.
I'm sorry.
Please leave.
What?
Please leave your family alone.
I don't have any other family.
I'm sorry.
Is he dead?
Today is Yamada's...
He's not dead yet.
I'm fine!
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.