Happy birthday to you, happy birthday dear Hamachan
Happy birthday to you
How many times have I done this?
6 times
32 times
Let's have a toast
Thank you for coming
Cheers
Happy birthday
We are going to have a sale to celebrate the release of the book
It's rare to come to such a beautiful place
And this book is very popular
If it's popular, I'll sell it more
I didn't write anything
What are you talking about?
It's the second time
Since we are here today, we will give a gift to the person who bought it
You have to put a price on it
Please pull it
Let's go
You have to buy it or it won't start
It's 900 yen
This program is brought to you by the sponsor
Do you need a book?
Your girlfriend
It's 900 yen
Sorry, I have to get money
Thank you
Here you go
I don't have much money
You got it
This is your prize
Thank you
Are you going to do it?
Let's do it
This prize
This is the prize
This is good
Thank you
Do I have to wear it?
Yes
You can wear it
Thank you
Are you going to give it to me like this?
It's 900 yen
Thank you
Here you go
Will she get it?
She got it
Are you ready?
This is good
Let's see
She got it
This is for you
This is the prize
You can wear it
What should I do?
This is good
Thank you
I don't need the book
Here you go
You have to buy it
This is the prize
She got it
Please look at this
She is the first one
She got it
The one that Mr.Suga is riding
Please look at this
This is live
He is riding for you
Mr.Suga is riding for you
Let's see how much she will cry
Is this the prize?
It's the prize
She got it
This is good
It's 900 yen
She got it
Please look at his Mickey Mouse
I'm good at drawing
I'll show you my pose
I can only draw the face
I'll show you
When did he become like this?
This is my drawing
Thank you
This is my father
This is my daughter
Please call your father
She got it
This is my father's prize
Congratulations
Please look at my joke
Please close your eyes
Congratulations
This is not a joke
This is Mos Burger's employee
She got it
Thank you
Have you ever had a match?
This is the first time
What is this?
I don't know
This is the product
Heipo used this
You hold this
Please use it
You'll be surprised
I'll give you this bikini
Thank you
He got it
Stop it
You look like a mouse
Let's see his joke
Yamasaki
Congratulations
This is the finished product
You can't see this
What are you looking at?
He's holding this
I'm angry
I thought you were great
What?
I like my character
I'm normal
I'm the same as always
I don't want to say this
You didn't say it
My ribs are broken
I didn't go to the hospital
I was told by the doctor
My ribs are broken
Stop it
Your ribs are broken
I told you
I'm wearing a corset
I just put it on
It's broken
Who told you?
I know
I told you it's broken
When I touch it, the sound is different
There's a low sound
I don't care
It's really broken
I know
That's why
Let's explain why your ribs are broken
Let's explain
If you don't hear this, you won't know what's broken
Don't touch it
Let's explain why it's broken
It's a low sound
There was a short film
I was looking at the table
I was looking at the monitor
It was hard to see
There was a chair
I was looking at the monitor
The chair goes like this
You put your weight on the back
I was standing on the chair
There was an iron stick behind me
Really?
An iron stick?
It's stuck
There was an iron plate
I hit it
If it was a drama, everyone would have stopped
Everyone would have stopped
Why?
It's broken
Stop it
I can't do it
They can't do it
I couldn't breathe for a moment
I couldn't breathe for a while
But the camera was rolling and I was laughing
That's variety
I can't help it
I'm fine
I'm not broken
It's really hard
It's broken
I don't think it's broken
Why?
I can't sleep
It hurts
That's why it's broken
It's broken
It's broken?
Don't lie
It's broken
That's a big deal
It's not broken, but it's broken
It's broken
It's definitely broken
From now on
I thought it was amazing
The moment you fall
How many seconds is 0?
It's fast
It's not fast at all
When I fell, I thought it was over
I didn't think about anything
I thought I was going to fall, hit my head, and go to the hospital
You thought that?
I thought
It was fun
That's a lie
You lied, didn't you?
It's a lie, isn't it?
Hey
It's a lie
It's true
You did chop
I did chop, but it's a lie
You did
I've been looking at the battery for a month
It doesn't take that long
It took
You've been wearing it since yesterday
I'm wearing a corset right now
You should
You should go to the doctor and get a corset
Why don't you wear something like this?
You should go to the doctor
Why did I get a corset?
It was easy
Let's go to the post office
It's hot
Hello, Mr. Cha
It's a lie
It's Mr. Cha
I heard that Mr. Cha did it by himself
Matsui is so famous
Who said that?
It's been a long time
It's a twin deed
Is this the picture?
Of course
It's not Tsumagoi
It's Fujitera
That's right
What's Fujitera?
The opening was the best
Mr. Cha was dancing
He was doing something like this
It's been a long time since I played the guitar
That's right
Mr. Matsumoto
Is it okay?
It's totally fine
I didn't think I could play in a place like this
In front of the audience
Is it okay?
It's totally fine
Really?
How many people should I play?
I want to play something that I'm good at
Something you're good at?
Yes
Are you holding it here?
Wait, I'm matching it
Matching
My ribs hurt
Wait
Wait a minute
I'll show you Mr. Cha
That's right
I'll show you the same thing
I'll show you the action that Mr. Matsumoto taught me
Is that right?
Of course
Mr. Cha, you're still good
Hey
You're still doing it while the sound is left
Mr. Cha, you're still doing it while the sound is left
Did you get caught?
Hasn't it changed?
That's right
Basically
It's round
You were always like this
We did it together
That's enough
Mr. Cha, you're going to get a stomachache
I'll hold it
You're all dirty
Thank you
You're so dirty
You didn't teach me at all
That's true
We're old friends
You will be surprised
You'll be surprised when your relatives come
That's true
It's the same
This is just right for your situation
What do you do when you're having a hard time?
It's sad when I'm having a hard time
It's hard because it hurts
What do you do when you're having a hard time?
I'm more of a bridal man
Bridal?
You know what I mean
You're a bridal man
So at home...
Of course I haven't used it yet
But I have a wedding dress
You haven't used it once, when are you going to use it?
I'll take it out like this
You're still going to use it?
Right?
I'll turn around
And then I'll say, ah, hurry
So cool
I feel like you're going to do something
It's really...
I feel like you're going to think I'm crazy
I feel like you're going to think I'm going to do something weird
It's normal for me to get mad
It starts and ends with a bow
It's weird that I keep my socks on
Why?
I'm barefoot but I keep my socks on
I'm serious
You can take them off
I don't want to wait for the four of you
Ah, Aoyama
The four of you
Aoyama
I've been waiting for the same amount of time
It's in me
I didn't give everything to you
What?
Mysterious
No, no, no
I'm just wearing my socks
It doesn't have a deep meaning
I think I keep my socks on
Ah, of course you do
Of course you do, Chirorin
Who's Chirorin?
Nomi's life is...
Why are you pulling my leg?
Why are you pulling my leg when I'm talking?
I don't get it
Why are you so angry?
How long is Nomi's life?
I don't know
Nomi's life is really fast
It flies
It's dead in the air
It's flying
Why does it have to fly and die?
When it's flying, it's going to land
Of course, Nomi
I want to go that far
Nomi's like, okay, let's go
Nomi's like, let's go that far
Yay!
I don't feel good
In the air, I don't feel good
I'm sleepy
I don't feel good
It's cold
Do you have a theme for Downtown?
What kind of song is it?
I don't have a theme for Downtown
I have one, you idiot
Who wrote it?
Me
Can I teach you?
No, no
You can't do that
And then?
Idiot?
I'll start with Okinawa Minions
Why?
It has nothing to do with Okinawa Minions
No, no
You can't do that
It's like, click, click
Why don't you do it in Debayashi?
What Debayashi?
Stop this music
Oh, Gaki no Ka?
There's always an opening
Ladies and gentlemen
Stop that
Stop that?
No, no
You can't do that
What?
Let me hear it properly
You can't do that
This program was brought to you by these sponsors