It's been an hour since the show started.
It's not a showdown, but it's an opening show.
There are a lot of things to do.
I have a special guest today.
I was surprised when I came out for the first time.
Two people over here, two people over here.
At first I thought it was a speaker.
Why are there two people over here?
I've been chasing you for about a week now.
Liar!
This program is brought to you by the sponsor you are watching.
You like Sumo-tori, don't you?
Sumo-tori, Sumo-tori.
Why Sumo-tori?
Tobacco, bath, Sumo-tori.
I don't know if it's tobacco or bath.
Sumo-tori.
I don't know his face.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
By the way, I was surprised to see it on TV.
There's a lot of import of boxers now.
The one I was doing last night was a Japanese title.
Japanese champion, Japanese, of course.
No matter how you look at it, the Japanese ranked second is a black person.
It's not a black person, but it's a Japanese nationality.
That's why it's imported.
Is the nationality in Japan?
That's why you're a black person, so you're really strong.
The Japanese champion was KOed in the second round.
What are you going to do from here?
I brought an American flag and shook it.
The champion became a Japanese champion.
Even if you're interviewed by a ship, you say thank you.
It's a strange story.
It's strange.
If that's the case, even in the world of sumo.
I don't know. I can't bite a pig.
I don't think that's strange.
Why?
It's a nationality. Sumo is a Japanese nationality.
I don't think so.
I'm saying it's different from when foreigners are doing sumo.
Oh.
What's the difference?
It's different from the moment you say thank you.
It's different.
That's fast.
I don't know exactly, but there's a school for sumo.
It's different from the moment you say thank you.
That's where you're wrong.
It's different. You're a black person.
It's a nationality. It's a Japanese nationality.
What are you doing with your head?
It's strange.
But if you can speak Japanese, I think it's okay to forgive each other.
But I don't understand.
That's because he's important, so I don't understand.
I don't know what the whole sumo world is talking about.
That's not it.
I'm not going to do a horror movie.
It's hard to speak.
Speak more naturally.
That's not it.
I'm sweating all over.
I'm using a lot of strength.
I'm finally back.
I'm glad you told me.
I'm in the room for a while today.
The pot looks delicious.
How is it?
I can't stand it.
You're hot.
If you're hot, I'm hotter.
What happened to the garbage problem?
It's being said in foreign countries.
Japan's privacy.
That's right.
For example, you live in an apartment, right?
There's a pretty good woman next door.
I don't know.
Let's say you have a girlfriend.
You have a girlfriend, don't you?
Her name is Tanaka.
When I go to the garbage store,
If I see Tanaka,
It's not written as San.
If there's a trash bag called Tanaka,
I want you to see it.
I'll open it for you.
I don't have Tanaka's privacy.
You open it.
I'll leave Tanaka alone.
It's okay if you pass by.
Why?
It's Tanaka's.
But Tanaka is a good woman.
It doesn't matter if it's a good woman.
It doesn't matter if Tanaka is a good woman.
When you leave the house,
If you say,
It's Tanaka's,
I'll do it.
I'll definitely do it.
You'll do it, too.
Tanaka is a very good woman.
I've been walking around like this.
It's disgusting if you walk around like this.
Tanaka is as beautiful as a eel.
It's Tanaka's trash bag.
I'll see it.
If you say that, I'll see it.
That's right.
It's disgusting.
It's definitely disgusting.
There are only 23 of them now.
I was doing it on the news.
If you go to Sendai,
It's all over there.
There's a guy who throws away a black plastic bag.
There's a sticker on it.
It's a warning.
What happens when you put a sticker on it?
I leave it alone.
What's going to happen?
A monster headland.
I have a parent.
Is that so?
That's how it is.
You're walking around like this.
If you write Peter,
What kind of trash do you throw away?
You'll open it, right?
I can't write Peter.
If you really write Peter,
I think it's a little weird.
Cool Five.
Everyone's alive.
Miyamoto-san and Uchiyama-san are alive.
There are a lot of entertainers living in Tokyo.
There's a problem with entertainers.
There are a lot of entertainers.
If you say that Matsumoto lives in a mansion,
The people in the mansion already know.
They'll find out.
They'll see it.
There's a lot of stuff coming out.
My face is going to turn red.
You don't have to do that.
Put it in your pocket, get in the car,
I'd like you to throw it away on your way to work.
You're not going to get electrocuted from the car window.
Why?
You don't have to do that.
Take it.
Give me a pen.
But
It's getting on my nerves.
Who?
Me?
Who's getting on your nerves?
Why are you getting on my nerves on stage?
I'll tell you in the dressing room.
I'll call you at night.
Why are you using the industrial year-end?
You're getting on my nerves.
There are times when you have to pick up trash.
You have to stop somewhere.
This is the last time.
I'm not saying I agree.
Let's all do a demonstration.
It's not cool.
I don't want anyone to do it.
Then I'll lead the way.
Really?
Really.
I'll do it.
I'll watch the news.
What are you talking about?
If you agree with that, I'll give you a black rubber band.
Let's do a demonstration.
Let's do it.
Where should we go?
We should go to the city hall.
Okay, let's go.
Leader.
No matter how many times you tell me to go to the city hall, I can't do it.
Let's go.
I can't do it.
If it's 3 o'clock, you have to come at 3 o'clock.
You're always an hour late.
I can't do it.
What are you going to say when you get off the city hall?
When I get off the city hall, if you ask me what I'm doing,
I'll go round and round.
For the time being.
If you're going to do that, I'll give you a black rubber band.
Let's go to the city hall.
For the time being, let's do a demonstration.
Let's do a demonstration.
I'll talk to you from there.
No, no, I'm sorry I'm going round and round.
That's okay.
I don't need that kind of apology.
I'm going round and round because I have a bad intention.
I don't need that.
You can't do that.
I can't do that.
Let's do it.
You're being treated like a fool.
I don't talk much.
You can't talk.
You're the leader.
Why am I the leader?
Let's do that.
Let's get a talent.
Let's talk to more talent.
What do you have in your mind right now?
Like Heisuke Sugi.
Why?
Even if you put Heisuke Sugi in the anti-transparency.
You know it's Heisuke Sugi, don't you?
That's why you can't do it.
I don't know why.
I'll get a handkerchief.
So.
I'll go with a talent.
Who is it?
Take Wada Akiko.
That's nice.
Is this the guy?
It would be nice if a Chinese person came.
It's called anti-transparency.
I'm not going to use a child.
Chikitsuki entertainer.
Are you so-chan? Grand Prix.
I'm the same.
I came out to the street corner.
I'm taking a survey of the people on the road.
The person who was brilliantly shining in the Grand Prix.
Let's start with the theme of the Grand Prix.
Today's participants, please.
Please take a seat.
The next is Mr. Otake Yamamoto.
I'm used to it.
I told you not to call me.
The next is Mr. Ibasuke.
Do you know this guy?
I saw him in the special edition.
But it's not like that.
It's not like that.
Haven't you seen it?
I don't know what you're doing on TV.
I'm doing it just for you.
The next is Mr. Rasa.
I'm Rasa.
Of course you know Rasa.
I already know.
I'm a fan of Downtown.
The last is Mr. Matsumoto.
He seems to have a lot of problems.
A little more than usual.
That means you're going to increase the number of enemies.
I'm not doing it with that in mind.
Do you have that many enemies?
Don't you know?
If you do it in the hallway, no one will listen to you.
That's just the way it is.
The first question is this.
You're definitely going to the SM club, aren't you?
You've been on TV for a long time.
When you're done with work, you're going to the SM club, aren't you?
I don't think so.
Is that so?
That's right.
But after that, you're definitely going to the SM club, aren't you?
Let's start with Mr. Otake.
Is that so?
Who is it?
I don't know.
Is that so?
Mr. Iemoto's answer is...
I'm looking forward to it.
It's Masoyoi.
That's what they say.
It's not my opinion, so I'll take your opinion.
This guy is a little bit of a ***.
What do you mean?
What about Raka-chan?
Mr. Iwai.
That's right.
Mr. Iwai is ***.
I heard that.
The last one.
Who is it?
Nagashima Jr.
Who do you think it is?
Let's start the VTR.
I'm sure it's Sanoshiro.
Yamashiro Shingo.
Junji Takada.
Kaneki Shimoda.
Yamamori.
I think I can see those tight pants.
Beat Takeshi.
Ryu Oshiba.
Katsura Sanshi.
He's got a pretty high voice.
Tanaka Yasuo.
Takeshi.
Downtown Matsumoto.
Shibarai.
Sanoshiro.
Ryu Oshiba.
Katsura Sanshi.
Beat Takeshi.
Junji Takada.
Ryu Oshiba.
Sanoshiro.
Junji Takada.
Ryu Oshiba.
Mr. Oshiba.
You're all wrong.
Let's move on.
So the people don't know the truth, right?
Don't say nonsense.
Let's move on.
The next question.
The next question is...
This one.
You're the son of your parents, Hanahadashi.
What the...
Well...
Please write it down.
Please.
I've already written it down.
Please think about it again.
Please think about it.
Please write it down.
Otake.
You can't do that.
I can't do that.
No, no, no.
I ran safely because of this man.
Why do I have to respond to everyone's request?
That's good.
Let's start with Otake.
Well...
A member of the parliament who looks like B-saku.
I made a mistake and said B-saku.
Ivo-san.
I'm going to add my brother to that.
Brother.
Who?
Me.
Yes.
Kaneda.
I ran safely because of that.
That's right.
I don't know the other one.
Ivo-san.
Well...
I was Kanji.
Hiragana.
Ogata Naoto.
Takashima brothers.
Kitashima Mai.
Nakashima Kazushige.
If Shigeo wasn't there...
Shigeo.
I don't think I'd be in the game.
Hayashiya Kokuge.
Otsuru Gitan.
Ishida Issen.
I can feel it right away.
Nakashima Kazushige-san.
Takashima brothers.
Hayashiya Kokuge.
It's not funny at all.
Otsuru Gitan-san.
Nakashima Kazushige.
Ogata Naoto.
Takashima brothers.
Ishida Issen.
Ishida Aise.
Takashima brothers.
Now, all of the Takashima brothers in the Grand Prix are out.
Thank you.
I think that's how popular it is, isn't it?
It reminds me of everyone.
You're following me.
Let's move on to the next question.
This one.
You guys should disband your group.
How long have you guys been doing this?
It's like a draw.
You guys are different from the entertainment world.
Stop it.
You guys should disband your group.
Now, Iguchi-san.
I don't want to.
I don't want to. Everyone is laughing.
This is what the public thinks.
Now, Raka-chan.
Raka-chan.
Is it that bad?
I don't know.
Raka-chan.
You guys are not funny.
You guys are not funny no matter how long you've been doing this.
We're not funny no matter how long we've been doing this.
Shut up.
If you don't shut up, we're going to broadcast this.
This is a bit...
I don't know.
Kadao-san.
You guys should draw.
Who do you want me to draw?
What do you want?
I drew this.
Forever.
Say it again.
You guys are not funny.
You guys are not funny no matter how long we've been doing this.
We're not funny no matter how long we've been doing this.
Who do you want?
I'm being scolded.
I think this is the same for the red traffic light.
Boys.
I'm not a boy anymore.
Dachau Club.
Hikaru Genji.
Downtown.
Tunnels.
Aozora Kyuujikouji.
Dachau Club.
Tsunan.
Hikaru Genji.
Roller skates are coming off.
Drifters.
Boys.
Ucchan Nanchan.
B21.
Hikaru Genji.
Boys.
Ucchan Nanchan.
Hikaru Genji.
Dachau Club.
Roller skates are coming off.
The red traffic light is still on.
The world doesn't know the existence of the red traffic light.
I know.
Of course.
I can't think of anyone.
Here.
You're like GonCold.
Ucchan.
Let it go.
I'll answer it.
I'll put a transition on this question.
I can't put it on just this one.
Let it go.
I got it.
You're like GonCold.
What kind of Ucchan?
GonCold.
I'm scared.
Okay, go ahead.
I didn't see it.
I thought I saw it.
It doesn't matter if you saw it.
Let's start with Otaru.
Ready?
Sakuma.
I'm going to win, so don't tell anyone.
I didn't see it.
I'm really a man.
I don't think I'm a man.
I'm not going to see it.
Sakamoto Issei.
Yabasa-chan.
That's right. I've never heard of it.
Ready, go!
I don't get it!
I just remembered!
Ready, go!
It's 90%!
I don't get it!
Otake Makoto.
Mokku.
Takashima Onii-chan.
Something like that.
Tano Shiro-san.
Mokku-kun.
His face is sharp, right?
That's why.
Downtown's Matsu-chan.
Kejirabi-kun.
Mokku-kun.
Minamoto-san.
Takada Junji-san.
I don't know about Tamu-san.
Ruu Oshiba.
Tano Shiro.
Tano Shiro?
Because he looks like a pervert.
Downtown's Matsu-chan.
Mokku-kun.
Matsu-chan.
Matsumoto Hitoshi.
Mokku-kun.
The winner of the Grand Prix is Motoki Masahiro-san!
You're all out!
Otake-san, did you get 2 points?
I got 2 points.
You're underestimating me.
You're popular because you're famous.
Enough!
The last question.
Ah, really?
The last one?
The last question is...
here!
You're a *** with a metal in your ***.
No, I'm not.
I can't think of anything.
You're the only one I can think of.
What?
What the f**k are you talking about?
Not this one.
Why don't you make a mosaic for one person?
I'll accept only the person who says,
please erase that part.
One?
Yes.
The part that comes out.
Thank you for waiting for a long time.
From now on, we will hold the downtown autumn dinner show,
which is famous for singing and talking.
Everyone, please enjoy the wonderful dinner.
Hello.
This is the second time for our dinner show.
Yes.
Thank you for coming to Sagamiko Hyatt.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Don't worry about the food.
The food is also made by a wonderful cook.
Yes.
He cooks with his own hands.
The cook...
The chef...
Hama-chan, you are so mean.
I'm sorry.
I'm already crying.
It's embarrassing.
I'm really sorry.
So, let's listen to the first song.
Yes.
From Sagamiko Hyatt's number,
please listen to the song,
Blue Rain.
OK.
Ah, the blue rain.
It embraces my shoulder and disappears.
Thank you very much.
Hama-chan, you are so mean.
I'm sorry.
I'm already crying.
You are so mean.
So, let's listen to the next song.
Let's listen to the next song.
From Venus's number,
please listen to Kiss on Many.
Yes.
Please.
It's a song.
Yes.
I can do it!
OK!
One up! One up!
Falling into a trap
A seducing voice invites me
Kiss me in the eyes and laugh
Thank you!
Today, we invited top dancers from New York.
Yes.
I think it was very exciting.
After all, there was a lot of fun from New York.
There was.
After all, the real thing is different.
It's different.
Well, that's it.
Let's go to the next one before we get excited.
Please listen to Never from Me.
OK!
Never from Me
We are cooperating with dancers from New York.
When you're hurt and broken
It's a chance to get stronger
Never from Me
Thank you very much!
Thanks for your support!
Never ever never never speaks
Thank you very much!!
Thank you very much.
Actually, this album was recorded in London.
I wonder why.
When I go to a place called London, I feel very free.
That's right.
I was told that I made a very confident album.
Then, it's a very difficult thing to say.
What?
It's the last song.
Is it over already?
Wait a minute.
What?
I have to wait a little longer.
The audience seems to be mentally prepared.
Is that so?
Yes.
Be careful, audience.
Please sing with the audience.
Yes.
Then, the last song.
Let's burn.
Thank you.
Roll up your midsemintheme and make it a inability.
Let's burn.
Shake the red.
Let's burn the place where we can't see the light of the new year
Let's burn, burn more, burn more
Thank you very much!
See you next month!
What kind of action does the actor do when the scene of the drama is cut?
I did it once.
Don't do that.
In front of people.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What are you talking about?
I'm lying, so I'm talking about it.
I did it once, but I was doing it all the time.
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's not cool.
I'm talking about it.
I don't like it when you say cut and leave.
I don't like it.
I'm talking about it.
I was pushing you down and saying,
I'm still doing it.
On the day I was told that it was a love scene.
Bed scene.
That's a little tough.
I'm saying,
I'm talking about it.
I'm scared.
I can't do it at all.
Really? Why?
I don't know what to do after that.
That's why I just did it at the time of production.
It's not cool.
I did it from the rehearsal.
I'm talking about it.
I'm talking about it at the time of production.
That's not it.
I'm talking about it.
You may be a teapot.
But your tongue is like a devil.
If you show your tongue, it's like this.
Well,
I can't do it.
I don't know.
Well, I can't do it for the rest of my life, so it's okay.
I always think this is love when I'm with someone else.
Please tell me the difference.
Well, isn't it a relationship that doesn't go that far when you're in love?
No sex?
Yes.
Is it love that there is no sex?
Not yet.
Well, I'll say it.
Well, you say that.
The period of love is short.
It's about two hours.
Is there such a thing?
Love is about eating.
Idiot!
There is love, right?
It's love until you have sex.
It's love when you have sex.
Where does love come from?
It's difficult.
But I'm not wearing it until I take off my clothes.
It's still love.
This is love.
It's still love if it's a bra and panties.
I don't know if I can do that.
It's still love.
It's a bra and panties.
Right?
Yes.
Pring!
Bopopring!
It's still love.
Still love.
Oh.
Kyukyu kyukyu.
Still love.
Why?
Zaku!
Sawa!
You still love me?
Eh?
Why?
Why do you take out a sketchbook and draw this?
It's an art.
You still love me?
Sawa!
It doesn't matter if you stand upright or not.
You still love me.
You still have a pose.
Well, well, well.
You still love me?
What are you doing there?
I'm in love.
That's right.
Up to this point, it's love.
It's just...
It's just.
I've been in this situation all the time.
Pichan.
What if I'm in love?
What about this?
That's strange.
What if I'm in love?
Why? That's OK.
That's OK.
Why?
If I'm naked in front of someone who's not conscious of anything,
I won't be in love, right?
Well.
Everyone, come with me.
He's pulling something.
I see.
He's in a state of acceptance.
Well, I understand that it changes from sex to love.
Certainly.
Right?
If you have sex, it's love.
Pichan.
Please stop Pichan.
Who is it?
You can stop him.
Let's go stop him together.
Who is it?
Who is Pichan?
Please stop him.
This is what it means.
I see.
Right?
It means to stop at home.
No, no.
You don't want to stop Pichan at home, do you?
No.
I don't know what kind of person he is.
He's called Pichan.
Right?
I'm nervous when Pichan comes.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to prepare.
Should I use a toothbrush?
Can I wear my pajamas?
I don't know.
I'm nervous when Pichan comes.
I enjoy watching the show every week.
By the way, why are there so many P's in the show?
What are you talking about?
Do you get scared in the show?
If you're frustrated, tell me.
There are a lot of P's in the show.
So, today...
I'll show you.
I'll give you an hour.
I'll show you without you knowing.
Well...
If I do this...
Of course, I'll air this.
I might turn Japanese celebrities into enemies.
What?
Who are you?
I want to do it.
First of all, PR.
PR.
Please take a look.
If you're frustrated, tell me.
I'll show you.
This is the material that was broadcasted.
The guy who married Nishiki.
He's a bad guy.
But,
He's the most difficult guy to deal with.
This is...
You're the gorilla man, right?
The dirty thing is that the producer who joined your team...
It was dirty.
The other day, I was going to tackle.
No, no.
I was going to tackle.
It was a great show.
The writer of my team, Takasu.
Kouhaku, which one will win?
I'll be the white one.
If there's a happening,
I'll be the one.
This is a serious story.
I think it's getting more and more exposed.
Even in a five-man group,
Wow!
A comedian marries an amateur woman, right?
It's like...
If you show this without a P,
I can't do it.
You guys are with us today.
By the way,
You can watch this broadcast without a P.
Of course.
You guys are so fast.
This is a key point.
I've been hiding it with a P.
A broadcast without a P.
Let's watch it.
That guy who got married to Konishi-Ki,
He's got a bad head.
But the hardest thing in a married couple is...
It's a good match.
That was nice.
If you use the same material as me,
The string is cut.
You guys are so good.
However, there are times when you can say that it's okay, right?
For example, it's okay for us to say that our fiance was rude, right?
That's not enough!
That's not it!
Instead of that, we can say, ****** fiance, ****** fiance is not okay!
That was awful, too!
That was awful, too! ****** fiance, ******
Yes! I'm not like that, but if you say that I'm more ugly than ****** fiance, that's really bad!
Really ugly!
How can you have such a bad personality?
Well, that's just a matter of nature.
The player's wife is pretty beautiful, isn't she?
Oh, really?
Yeah.
The f***ing fiance...
Well, well...
It's so ugly that I can't even explain it in words.
It's a big deal.