Since the last time I was on a TV show, my life has changed a lot.
But recently I've been receiving a lot of information.
There was a man who was more stingy than I was.
That man's name is...
Masumoto Hitoshi.
What the hell, you idiot!
Masumoto Hitoshi will be the judge of the Seco Seco trial.
Wait a minute.
Why am I so stingy?
Is Masumoto really stingy?
Tonight, the truth will be revealed.
You're going to die!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
We will now begin the Seco Seco trial of Masumoto Hitoshi.
Prosecutor and the plaintiff, please enter the court.
Next, the defendant, Masumoto Hitoshi, please enter the court.
The defendant, please take a seat over there.
Prosecutor, please read out the verdict.
Masumoto Hitoshi is a very popular comedian.
He is a very popular comedian.
But he is a very stingy man.
The size of his bowl is exactly like a choco.
I don't understand the meaning of a choco.
No, the size of his bowl is exactly like a choco.
He is causing a lot of trouble to the people around him.
We will now begin the Seco Seco trial of Masumoto Hitoshi.
Understood.
Prosecutor Hamada, please present the evidence.
We have received a lot of complaints from different sides.
First, please watch this video clip.
This is when Matsumoto went on a trial trip with the three of them.
The incident happened on the last day.
Matsumoto-san, we still have three hours before the flight. What should we do?
I wonder what we should do.
Oh, that's right.
There is a very luxurious pool near this hotel. Do you want to swim there?
Oh, that's a good idea.
Alright, let's swim.
The three people who moved to the nearby hotel immediately went to the pool.
No, no, no. Stop, guys.
What?
The three people who were called by the hotel's security guard.
In fact, in this pool, you have to pay $20 for admission, except for the guests.
Yamasaki, who found out about this, said...
That's right. Well, $20 is fine.
However, Matsumoto said...
That won't be paid.
What? $20 is fine, isn't it? You can't swim in the pool.
Then who will pay?
And since we swam a lot yesterday, the water will be gone.
As soon as Matsumoto realized that he had to pay $20, his attitude changed.
However, the hotel's security guard who saw this said...
If you promise me not to go into the water, you can stay by the poolside.
That's what he said.
That's fine. Then let's go home.
Yamasaki, who tried to go home because he thought it would be meaningless if he didn't go to the pool.
However, the moment Matsumoto found out about this...
All right.
He started swimming in the poolside.
It feels so good.
In the end, Yamasaki spent three hours with Matsumoto in the poolside.
Who are you?
Hello.
I'm calling the witness.
Please come to the witness stand.
Yes, please.
Of course, we're on VTR now.
Does that mean we're on VTR Street?
That's right.
It's been a while since we went on a trip.
At the end of the trip, we had to pay for the pool.
I thought I could just go in.
Hey, don't let him catch you.
That's right.
My job is over there.
If you mess with me there, I won't be able to stand up.
I know that.
Why don't you just go in?
What do you mean by just going in?
I got it.
If you just go in, you can't go in.
That's what I just saw.
I just want to ask you something.
You have to pay 20 dollars.
That's about 2,000 yen.
What about you?
I thought 2,000 yen would be fine.
You have 3 hours.
If you can go in, let's go in.
I went in.
He should have more money than you.
I don't know why.
That's right.
It's here.
Now, the defendant.
I want to make this clear.
I'm going to go back in time to what happened the day before.
He really likes Bakuchi.
Yamada-kun, the hammer.
Who?
Yamada-kun.
Who the hell are you?
What do you mean by Yamada-kun, the hammer?
He hasn't been hit at all.
He hasn't been hit?
I just hit him.
It was close.
I completely avoided it.
You like Bakuchi.
I like Bakuchi.
Since the day before, this idiot has been playing Bakuchi like an idiot.
This time, I'm not going to do that.
We came up with the theme of going straight to Nikko.
I see.
He's been playing Bakuchi all the time.
In the end, he lost 400,000 yen.
No, 800,000 yen.
It's 800,000 yen.
I lost 800,000 yen there.
Think about it here.
I can't spend any more money on Yamazaki.
If that's the case, why don't you pay him?
About 20 dollars.
That's a separate payment.
What do you mean by separate payment?
I don't want to spend any more money on Yamazaki.
I get it.
The three of us can just say yes.
I wonder what it is.
What is it?
Why don't you pay him?
Isn't that strange?
If the guy who spent that much is willing to pay 20 dollars, that's fine, isn't it?
That's not it.
I wanted to say that to the guard at the hotel.
Who do you think you are?
I caught Yamazaki, who lost 800,000 yen.
I don't know what he's talking about with 20 dollars on top of that.
But...
Let me drink the water of the pool.
I lost 800,000 yen.
I lost 200,000 yen.
That's right.
I wanted to enjoy those three hours with you.
Then I'll ask you a question.
What do you know?
What?
What's wrong with you?
You mean I couldn't get in?
You don't know because you didn't pay 20 dollars?
What do you know about that?
It's 6,000 yen.
Don't be ridiculous.
Stop it.
Stop whining.
Idiot.
What do you know about 6,000 yen?
What's wrong with you?
When was the last time you had fun with someone?
You!
Die!
You die!
I'll kill you!
When was the last time you had fun with someone?
I didn't have fun!
I had lots of fun!
You didn't even notice you were dead!
You're crazy!
You're the boss!
Boss?
It's okay.
You're the boss on the weekend.
I'll stop on the weekend.
No. It's okay.
It was a few years ago, when Miyasako was invited to Matsumoto's house for the first time after the rain.
Well, whatever.
I'm coming in!
Wow, amazing!
There's a piano and a piano stand!
That's Matsumoto-san for you!
Alright, let's go!
He got excited at the billiards and forgot that time was passing and went to play.
And after a while, Matsumoto said...
I'm hungry. Should I get some rice?
Oh, that's great!
Matsumoto-san is coming! I'm sure he'll treat us to a high-class meal!
By the way...
Miyasako, can you go to the convenience store for a bit?
Go buy whatever you like.
Oh, and don't forget the donbei!
I really like that!
Miyasako's expectations were crushed and he ended up going to the convenience store.
And when he came back from shopping...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
See you later. Here's 1,000 yen.
No, um...
When he saw the shopping bag Miyasako was holding in his hands, it was obvious that 1,000 yen wasn't enough.
However, he couldn't say that Matsumoto didn't have enough money.
Miyasako paid for the rest with her own money.
And Matsumoto said...
Donbei is the best! The best in the world!
He kept saying that and kept cutting down on donbei.
That was a terrifying incident.
Please take the money.
Are you okay?
Good luck!
Please be honest with us.
I'm sorry.
We won't hurt you.
To be honest, I came into this world with a dream.
I thought that if I worked hard in this world, I could become rich and eat a lot of delicious food.
But I didn't understand why a rich man would want to eat donbei all over the world.
To be honest, I didn't have any money back then.
But my wife is also very poor.
Good luck!
What?
The problem is...
Are you okay, Hikoku?
He didn't order delivery food or go out to eat.
I think that's okay.
It's okay to have such a situation.
Right?
Don't you blame him for that?
When you saw the amount of money he bought, you thought that 1000 yen wasn't enough.
Did you think about that?
First of all, what I want to say is...
Don't think that Matsumoto in downtown is amazing.
I don't want to show the arrogance of a comedian.
That's why I want to be at the level of the general public.
So you don't want to show arrogance?
I understand that.
I don't want to show arrogance.
That's why I didn't order delivery food and went to the convenience store.
I understand that.
But I know that my junior is writing a letter.
I didn't tell him to give me money and go.
I told him to go.
When he came back, he had a lot of luggage.
1000 yen wasn't enough.
Didn't you understand that?
To put it simply, I understood.
I see.
When I think about it, 2000 or 3000 yen wasn't enough.
It costed 2000 or 3000 yen.
I understand that.
What about the money you gave?
The money I gave was about 1000 yen.
This is 2000 yen.
What are you going to do?
This is it.
During that time, I had a lot of conversations with Miyasako.
I gave Miyasako about tens of millions of money that she couldn't see.
I should have stolen a lot of things from her.
At this time, I did this.
At this time, I did that.
I should have given Miyasako a lot of funny things.
If you think about the amount of money, 1000 yen is easy to get.
Hey, Tsukushi.
Hey, Shonin.
Please choose a word.
I'm sorry.
To be honest, this is a long time ago.
Please give it back.
Why?
I want to make my wife eat something delicious.
I don't know if I can say this.
Your partner can't speak.
By the way, Hikobu.
Not Hikobu, Shonin.
Is he at the scene?
He was there.
Were you there?
I don't know.
I was there.
Everyone was there.
I was there, too.
I don't know.
You don't know?
Wasn't there such a thing?
I don't think so.
I'm sure there is.
Are you sure it's true?
It's true.
But Hikobu said it was the amount of money.
What do you think?
I've learned a lot from him.
I see.
What are you talking about?
When I'm eating, I can't pay.
When I go to the convenience store, I can't pay.
We'll talk about that later.
We met for the first time at that time.
I see.
I didn't pay for anything.
I paid you first.
From now on, my memories with Matsumoto will expand.
That's a concession.
How much do you owe me?
I'm sure you owe me.
I don't owe you at that time.
I don't owe you.
You can sue me for something else.
I don't want to sue you.
You're just saying it.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to sue you.
That's Matsumoto and now.
That's when Yamashita, the former Jyarizumu, went to a bar.
You're doing your best these days.
I'm doing a little more.
Yamashita, how about you?
I can't do it at all.
You have to do it better.
The three of them got excited and the meal was over.
It's time to pay.
Let's decide who pays with rock-paper-scissors.
That's fine.
Let's do it.
But Yamashita doesn't earn as much as the other two.
So...
Please give me a hand.
If I win, I win.
Mr. Imada wins twice.
If Matsumoto wins three times, he wins.
What do you think?
Then...
Why do you have to do it with a hand?
I just want you to do it with a hand.
Even though Yamashita's earnings were hundreds of times as much, Matsumoto didn't accept this offer at all.
In the end, he decided to play rock-paper-scissors.
All right, let's go.
It's a one-on-one game.
Rock-paper-scissors.
I lost.
All right.
In the end, Yamashita, who lost, had to pay the fee.
It's a one-on-one game.
Again, this kind of incident.
All right.
Chief.
The witness.
The witness, please come in.
Here you are.
Yamashita, who just appeared on the VTR.
Let me explain.
Are you all right?
I lost a hundred times.
Rock-paper-scissors was good.
Actually, I've done it before.
With Yamazaki and Miyasako.
Is that so?
Yamazaki said, I'll do it with a hand.
I see.
I enjoyed it as a game.
That's right.
Yamazaki felt that way, so I thought he'd do it for me.
Please give me a hand.
Then suddenly.
Why don't you give me a hand?
I don't know what I want to get.
That's right.
Why don't you give me a hand?
I'm not the one to give you a hand.
That's right.
First of all.
All right.
You're up.
I'm up.
That's good.
You're up.
I'm up.
I'm really fond of Matsumoto.
Yes.
I want to see something cool.
I see.
So I saw something cool.
What is it?
I went to a bar with Nakai of SMAP.
Yes.
I saw a naked Nakai.
I'm sorry.
That's not good.
You're my junior.
Matsumoto-san.
That's not good.
You can call him Gochisousama.
But you can't call Nakai-san Gochisousama.
Not only me.
You can't call Imaya-san Gochisousama.
That's a fact.
That's Matsumoto-san.
No.
That's not good.
I know that.
That's right.
That's a defendant.
You know.
This is.
It's not a personal problem.
It's not Nakai Masahiro vs. Matsumoto Hitoshi.
It's Yoshimoto Kogyo vs. Johnny's problem.
Which one of you is winning now?
No, no, no.
It has nothing to do with Nakai.
It does! It's between the agencies.
No, that's not it. You're older than Nakai.
Lion Heart sold a lot.
But they don't have much money.
That has nothing to do with me.
For the time being...
What the hell are you?
I'm just saying it's a personal problem.
Go home.
I was at the scene, too.
You were there.
When I was paying for the money,
Nakai asked me to pay for it.
Matsumoto-san refused at first.
I said, I'll pay for it.
We're always like this.
We're the old ladies in Osaka.
I said, I'll pay for it.
I thought the scene would begin.
He said, really?
He's really weak.
No, no, no.
You guys are stupid.
What are you thinking?
I'm asking why you don't pay for it.
I'll pay for it, you idiot!
I'll pay for it.
Do your best.
What are you talking about?
I'll pay for it.
You'll pay for it.
No, you guys don't know.
You guys don't know.
I'll pay for it.
I'll pay for it later.
When I pay for it abroad,
I'm paying for it.
With Matsumoto-san's wallet.
That's why I know everything.
You're not moving.
I know the places you pay for it.
That's not true!
That's why he's asking for it!
I'm not paying for the places Matsumoto-san asks for.
I don't care if you don't pay for it.
Do your best!
I don't care!
You're a talented comedian.
You are all the same!
All die!
You just go back to normal.
Why?
You should have told me.
Say that.
Say that, not that.
Here!
What?
What is that?
Please hold us.
Mr. Shuzaku.
Please be angry.
No way.
Gasoline.