Chikichiki Akitani Kakuzan Hayaguni Ooguitaitai!
Are you a monkey?
Akitani Kakuzan Hayaguni Ooguitaitai
Today we have prepared a box.
We have prepared from 1 to 8.
Please choose a number you like.
Let's start with what's in the box.
Let's say it's 1 minute.
The person who eats the fastest in 1 minute wins.
And the person who wins last will get a wonderful prize.
That's how it is.
What should we do?
There are two rounds.
There are two rounds?
Yes.
I want to choose number 1.
You choose number 1.
I choose number 5.
You choose number 5.
I choose number 8.
Let's start.
The person who eats the fastest in 1 minute wins.
This is tough.
This is really tough.
It's noisy.
Number 5.
Noriyasu, please choose number 8.
Wow!
What is that?
It's a jumbo rice ball.
The person who eats the fastest in 1 minute wins.
Please eat as much as you can.
Do you understand?
You have 30 seconds to answer.
Not 1 minute, but 30 seconds.
How do you calculate this?
If you drink 1 bottle cleanly, it's 1 bottle.
Oh, I see.
It's no use even if you drink slowly.
By the way, how do you win and lose?
I only drink milk.
Is this 1 bottle?
I don't know. I don't watch TV.
It's disgusting.
Noriyasu, it's disgusting.
I'm sorry.
Don't spit it out.
Don't spit it out, idiot.
It's over.
Yamazaki, 1, 2, 3.
Let's admit that it's 3.
Noriyasu, it's 4.
It's half and 1 squid.
Noriyasu wins.
I don't know how much Matsumoto ate.
The first round is over.
My staff wants to drink a lot of milk.
What do you mean?
You're going to be killed.
You said you couldn't stand it.
I remember.
You don't remember?
What's your name?
Moriyama.
Ready, start.
Is my salary low?
It's over.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
It's 5.
Idiot.
It's amazing.
My throat is dry.
Let's start the second round.
It's over.
Stop.
And then...
You did your best.
But it's not good.
Noriyasu wins.
Thank you.
Noriyasu has won twice.
It's amazing.
There's something amazing.
What do you think?
You can give him the rights.
I'm sorry.
I don't know anything about it.
But please forgive me if I get it right.
Okay.
If you get it right, I'll give it to you.
No.
Wait a minute.
It's a friendly product.
What's wrong with it?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Noriyasu.
The pig's face.
It's amazing.
Yamazaki has got the rights.
You didn't get it right.
It's you.
It can't be helped.
Come here.
Open it.
What is it?
It's alive.
It's Mutsugoro.
Mutsugoro's Sugatayaki.
This is the real thing.
I've cooked it.
Please try it.
It's good.
What's wrong with him?
Do you know that you're doing this in front of me?
Yes.
Can you do this?
I can.
I'm sure of it.
You should say that.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Don't you think it's a little strange?
Last week...
As promised.
Last week, I promised to change my clothes.
I always wear a hat, and Masamune-kun wears a suit.
It's not funny.
That's right.
I got a letter asking me to change my clothes.
Today I'm wearing his clothes.
He's wearing my clothes.
What do you think?
It's crumpled.
It's nice.
I'm wearing the same tie as usual.
It looks nice and long, doesn't it?
It's nice and long.
It's long, isn't it?
You're doing what you're supposed to do.
So I have to change my standing position, right?
Let's change your standing position.
I always change my standing position.
The person who turned on the TV just now might think it's strange.
Is it okay?
Can you show it to me when you forget?
That's right.
With a telop.
My costume is the opposite today.
It's the opposite.
If you don't show it to me, I'll think it's my hobby.
No, no, no.
When I do this, you should talk.
Before I talk...
No, no, no.
That's strange.
You don't have to imitate that.
I'm sorry, but I can't change my standing position.
No, no, no.
I can't talk if you touch me.
You're going to talk.
I'm doing it 100 times more than you.
You're doing it.
But I'm always wearing a hat like this.
Why?
I feel strange.
It's strange.
This is a mistake.
Then I'll wear it a little deeper.
Wait.
Why are you taking it off?
Why?
That's right.
You're doing it.
But this is hot.
You're doing this.
Well, that's fine.
Well, let's get started.
That's right.
It's hot.
It's hot in this hall today.
The summer vacation is finally over.
Yes.
Do you have any fun memories of the summer vacation?
No.
No?
There's no vacation.
Oh, really?
The only thing that's open is that I'm going to get my driver's license again.
Yes.
All the time.
Sayonara.
You're going to get your driver's license now.
I'm worried if you say something real when you get your driver's license.
Why?
You're going to get your license.
I don't care.
I'm not going to let you get your driver's license.
Don't say that.
If you don't have a driver's license, it's going to be hard.
That's fine.
If you suddenly ask me to get my driver's license.
I went to the public school for two days for that.
I treated you like a criminal.
I'm going to get my license.
You shouldn't be a police officer.
Why?
You probably can't broadcast this.
But it's funny, so I'll say it.
There's a firework show.
It's going to be on the media.
You shouldn't be a police officer.
It's not on the media.
If there's a main character, we'll never do it.
There's a firework show.
That was the first time.
There were a few of them.
The first one was on fire.
I thought it was beautiful.
I thought I'd do it next time.
I was preparing for the next one.
I looked at it.
It was burning.
I thought someone was burning it.
That's why you're aiming for it.
What?
I didn't know that.
Did you catch fire?
It's burning in the grass.
It's burning in the grass?
The grass is burning.
What should I do?
Should I put it out?
When we all went, it was burning like this.
One of us was naked.
I thought it wouldn't be funny.
I did it with my clothes on.
I couldn't cut it at all.
It's burning.
I noticed it.
It's burning in this hole.
Don't say anything.
In the grass?
In the grass.
What should I do?
It's like a lie.
Really?
It's amazing.
What should I do?
Five firefighters came.
It's dangerous if you run away.
Everyone, look away.
It's burning like this.
The firecrackers are coming.
Is there anyone who got hurt in this fire?
I'm asking you.
No one got hurt, right?
Or if there's a firework here, put a name right away.
Everyone, let's go.
Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang.
Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang.
I wanted to express the feeling of running away in a single car.
Everyone ran away.
Did you go after that?
No, I went to see the next morning.
What's going on?
The criminal returns to the scene.
Don't tell anyone.
It's my secret after you.
Oh, I'm going to the police station now.
When can I get it?
The next one is...
I think it's a verification.
Well, there's also a identification.
Be careful.
Why?
I was dropped once by that.
I can't forget.
If I get this last one, I'll pass.
I was running.
When I was running, a sparrow stopped in front of me.
What's going on?
I thought I shouldn't pull the sparrow, so I stepped on the brake.
Then the instructor said,
Why don't you stop meaninglessly?
Now the sparrow is...
Now the sparrow is gone.
That's right.
I'm in front of you.
You stepped on the brake meaninglessly.
You're not going to stop, are you?
That's what he wrote.
And then I was dropped.
One verification?
That's what happens, so be careful.
I see.
If I were a sparrow, I'd have a lot of guts.
That's right.
When can I get it?
If you pass the verification, you have 10 hours left on the street.
That's what happens.
I hope I can get it by September.
I don't have time to go.
How about this?
What?
I'm going to support your graduation with this viewer.
No way!
Don't get in my way!
Why?
No way!
Just do it quietly.
At the end of the street, when there are people on the crosswalk, the car won't stop.
They'll go all the way.
That's why all the people watching this show are on the crosswalk.
Welcome.
Hello.
You look like a professional today.
Yes.
You have glasses like Hiroshi.
What's your name?
I'm Michiru Tanioka.
Do you have a job?
Yes.
What is it?
I'm an assistant in a TV show.
What kind of TV show is it?
I don't watch it at all.
It's a TV show about the supermarket.
What?
That TV show?
What's that?
It's a TV show about the supermarket.
That's a TV show about the supermarket.
The producer is the same as the producer of this TV show.
The producer of this TV show and the producer of that TV show are the same?
They are the same.
What's your name?
I'm Suga.
Is Suga doing that?
He's doing it proudly.
What's the number of that TV show?
It's that one.
Thank you very much.
Is it okay like this?
It doesn't make sense to bring this and bring this home.
It doesn't make sense.
The other day, I opened a postcard.
I read it every week.
I'm looking forward to the 100th anniversary.
Today, I have a question for you.
Why do you call Kyoko Suizenji a cheater?
It's strange. I can't sleep at night. Please tell me.
I read the postcard the other day.
I don't know the answer.
Why do you call Kyoko Suizenji a cheater?
Let's see.
Happiness doesn't come by walking.
That's why we walk.
Hello.
I'm happy to be able to walk.
Thank you for your question.
It's written in this postcard that I'm quick-witted.
But it doesn't matter.
It's an old story.
He wasn't born yet.
Even if I make my debut,
It's a nickname I got when I couldn't make my debut.
My real name is Tamiko.
I'll never forget the feeling of being a little Tamiko.
That's why I'm a cheater.
That's the real meaning.
This is me.
It's not Seiko Matsuda.
This part is written in English.
Young man, I'm counting on you.
That's why I'm working hard.
If you have any questions,
I'll answer them right away.
It's really hot today.
This person's pen name is Hama-chan Saikou.
Thank you.
You're a little crazy, aren't you?
He's angry.
He's angry, Hama-chan.
Hama-chan Saikou.
What are you?
Are you that amazing?
If it's this girl,
How can you call such an amazing person Hama-chan?
Isn't it okay?
It's love.
What?
Are you still angry?
Don't read it.
Matsumoto Hama, how are you?
What?
I listen to Shizuka Kudo's radio every week.
On that radio, it was a downtown story.
Kudo-san said,
I like matcha.
Because it's interesting.
I'm going to wear a burma and play dodgeball.
It was a long time ago.
At that time, I thought I'd wear a purple burma and go.
I was going to go to the studio next time.
Please do an interesting project that will surprise Kudo-san, who is such a big fan.
I see.
If you wear it, I don't have money for this program.
A postcard carrier.
A postcard carrier?
That's right, but I don't have money.
I don't know.
Really?
If it's open, I'll wear it.
100th anniversary.
That's right.
I don't know if that's possible.
Live broadcast.
But the time is slow.
It's 740 minutes.
It's live.
100th anniversary.
I'll do it live.
The time is slow in the morning, so it may be impossible.
It's 1 hour 40 minutes.
Who else wants to go?
So let's ask.
Ken Takakura.
He won't come.
What if he comes?
If he comes, I'll ask him to carry me.
Ken Takakura.
I'm a martial arts master.
If he comes, I'll ask him to carry me.
Don't ask Ken Takakura.
I don't care.
I don't care if you ask him to carry you.
I went to Tetsuko's room today.
Tetsuko's room.
I saw Tetsuko.
I didn't see Tetsuko.
Let's go home.
Yes.
He said yes.
Why don't you two talk here?
I don't have anything.
I'm sorry.
I was a little excited.
What are you talking about?
Let's go home.
I haven't been here for a long time.
I don't know where to go.
It's already 9 o'clock.
I have to leave by 9 o'clock.
Say something.
Seriously.
Let's go home.
If you have time, hurry up.
It looks delicious.
Don't laugh.
Goodbye.
It's dark.
Really?
Hello.
I have an announcement to make.
On Tuesday, September 24th,
we will have a live broadcast to commemorate the 100th anniversary of Gaki no Tsukai.
we will have a live broadcast at 1.40 p.m.
The person who is doing this now is Honjamaka.
I like Honjamaka these days.
No, no, no.
It's true.
So it's either me or Honjamaka.
So I'll do it.
I'll do it.
If you want to watch it,
I want you to send me a letter.
However, the broadcast will be from 1.40 p.m. to 2.10 p.m.
I'll leave it to the person who can buy it.
Since it's a 100th anniversary, I want you to wear a 100-day outfit.
I see.
I want you to wear a 100-day outfit.
That's it.
I see.
Please send me a letter.
I'll do it.
After Honjamaka.
You're so persistent with Honjamaka.
Honjamaka is good.
Even if you don't call me Honjamaka, I'll call you Honjama.
That's it.