It's time for Guda Guda Gainin's Regular Kaktop show!
Today, I feel like I've been very calm since before the show.
I think I'm going to stay calm from now on.
The main character is Guda Guda Gainin.
To put it simply, the show has changed a lot at this time of the year.
A new show has started from spring.
From now on, the number of regular viewers will continue to decrease.
There will be fewer and fewer.
Today, the people in charge of each show have gathered.
This time, 18 people from Japan TV and the staff of the show will be in charge of the screening.
When all the Guda Guda Gainin's content is over, they will choose the person they like.
Who will get the regular viewers?
I wonder why the fun entertainment is coming.
You have a lot of fun entertainment.
This program is brought to you by the sponsor you are watching.
Let's get started.
The first person, please.
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
You're nervous, aren't you?
Of course.
What are the regular viewers?
There are two of them.
What are they?
In TV Saitama, there are four seniors, Gokuraku Tomo and Supadaka Bokujo.
Supadaka Bokujo!
Let's get a good job.
I'll do my best.
Are you ready?
Yes.
You don't have to be nervous anymore.
Thank you very much.
I'm already excited.
Are you ready?
I'm going to do a show where I eat takoyaki and milk.
What?
I'm going to do that.
Your pronunciation is bad.
What are you doing?
I'm going to beat you up.
I'm sorry.
What did you say?
I'm going to do a show where I eat takoyaki and milk.
Takoyaki and milk.
You do it.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to do a show where I eat takoyaki and milk.
The end.
This is Kumamoto TV.
Mr. Ogawa.
Yes.
What do you think?
Squid and octopus move a lot.
Octopus is more difficult.
Which one is more difficult?
Mr. Ogawa, you just saw it.
It's okay.
Everyone, please.
Mr. Ogawa.
12 years of career.
Thank you very much.
How old are you two?
I'm 37 this year.
I have a child in May.
He is the younger one of us.
I think so.
What are you going to do today?
This is thanks to our old age.
I think you're being too old.
What are you going to do today?
What are we doing today?
Today, we are going to drink a bucket of water.
A bucket of water?
Not a normal bucket of water.
Please look at the other side of the curtain.
Please open it.
How long is it going to take?
Hmm...
This is...
It's called the year of the monkey.
Everyone, please stand by.
Ah...
Mr. Hamada.
Yes.
It's hard to get involved.
Everyone, I'm going to drink a bucket of water.
I'll do my best.
He's drinking it now.
I want to see him drinking it.
Are you pulling it?
I'm not pulling it.
I'm watching you.
He's drinking a lot.
It's okay.
If you don't want to get involved, drink from that side.
What?
I don't feel good.
Okay, it's over.
Turn around.
Hello.
Thank you very much.
How was it for you guys?
Ah, is that so?
It's really hard.
Shizuoka Daichi TV, Mr. Yasuoka.
Can you do a lawn mower?
I have a lot of energy.
Will it be on camera?
Maybe.
I'll ask the viewers to help me.
Anything is fine.
TV, please.
That's good.
Anything is fine.
Is there anything you want to show?
This one.
Magical brain power.
Sorry, Magical.
Magical, how was it?
Thank you very much.
It's different from what the show wants.
It's a shame.
Why don't you do Magical Banana here?
How about doing it in the water tank?
Magical Banana.
That kind of talent show.
He's shaking his head all the time.
I'm in trouble.
If you haven't seen it, please watch it.
Magical Banana
What's your name?
I'm Oosei Yamazaki.
What's your regular job?
I have 9 jobs.
You have 9 jobs?
9 jobs?
What do you have?
I can't cut my hair.
Don't say that.
You said you have 9 jobs.
What do you mean you can't cut your hair?
It's fine.
But when I watched your previous shows, I got angry.
I see.
I'll show you the real talent.
You're pretending.
What are you trying to do?
I'll do it.
Did you just see my butt?
Don't pull it.
What?
What are you doing?
Hello.
Be quiet.
Are you ready?
Yes.
What are you doing?
I'm in a bad mood.
What are you doing with this atmosphere?
Zusho from Sapporo TV.
Can you play on a snowy day in a cold place?
Can I play on a snowy day?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Can I ask you a question?
What?
Are you sure?
Have you ever been on a show?
Yes.
Really?
But I didn't do any airing.
What?
You didn't do any airing?
I didn't check it.
No, I'll let you do it.
This is the last one.
Yes.
The last one.
I don't think there's anything.
Really?
Yes.
I don't think there's anyone who wants to do it.
I see.
I don't know what it is.
Let's go.
This is the last one.
It's a mistake.
What are you going to do?
You can do it, right?
I can do it.
I have a lot of books.
Books.
How many years have you been in this world?
25 years.
I have a lot of books.
All of them are empty.
I'm looking forward to it.
Really?
I don't know where the key is.
It's nothing, but let's show it a little.
Shall we?
Please show something today.
One or two.
It's a waste.
It's okay, isn't it?
Yes.
A face copy.
Welcome back, Onoda-san.
It's old.
I saw it many years ago.
Which program?
After that.
Where is the regular?
It hasn't been decided yet.
After this, you can't make a face like that.
Hey, mister.
What?
Is that all?
Can't you do anything else?
Shall I open another drawer?
I haven't opened it yet.
It's been a long time since I came here.
This is the super power of the boom.
Boom?
That's the idea of an old man.
It's a moment.
This finger.
I'll pierce through anything.
Here we go.
The muscle.
I'm laughing.
Don't laugh.
No.
Why can't you tell the difference?
I'll be busy with this.
After this, the results of the big wave.
It's far beyond my imagination.
The results are far beyond my imagination.
Thank you for your applause.
Thank you.
How are you doing recently?
I'm still good today.
What's good?
I don't know.
It's good.
This is good.
Thank you.
I can see this dirty mole from your sweater.
If you say that, your nose will be dry.
It's natural that my nose will be dry.
It's not dirty.
I don't feel good.
Why is your mole so three-dimensional?
I don't like it.
Okay.
I'll take it off.
I can't take it off next week.
I can't take it off.
I'll burn it with a laser or something.
If I have this, I'll get cancer.
This is not good.
I don't have a three-dimensional mole on my body.
Why is it three-dimensional?
I don't know why you asked me.
You can't see the skin on the neck by this three-dimensional mole.
It's such a small area.
I can't see it.
I want to see the other side.
I can't stand it.
I can't see it from the other side.
I heard that the taxi driver Matsumoto-san has a secret route to go to Tokyo and Osaka in 15 minutes.
Please tell me where that road is.
The story is originally a colorful one.
I see.
It's not 15 minutes, is it?
But it's an hour and 20 minutes.
Please tell me what kind of road it is.
It's Osaka, right?
Well, um...
Koshu Kaido.
Koshu Kaido?
You have to go to Osaka from O-gyo.
You have to go to Koshu Kaido.
You're annoying.
That's why no one notices.
The secret route.
Do you know that?
There's Kanpachi, right?
Yes.
Kanpachi.
After crossing Kanpachi,
there's a side road here.
Where is it?
There's a lot of things on the side road.
That's not true.
Where is it?
There are many things on Kanpachi.
Where are you talking about?
That's right.
There's Kanpachi, right?
There are many things on the side road.
That's not true.
Koshu Kaido.
You like that, don't you?
There are times when you have to go to Kanpachi on Koshu Kaido.
Right?
There are, but you can't go in from many places.
Koshu Kaido is that.
This is Shinjuku.
Yes.
Right?
You can go all the way to Koshu Kaido, right?
Are you listening?
Why is it like this?
You can go to Koshu Kaido, right?
Right?
There are a lot of things on the side road.
You can go like this, right?
On the side.
There are things on the side road, too.
Are there things on the side road, too?
There are Kanpachi, right?
There are Kanpachi, too.
Right, there are Kanpachi, too.
There are, but they're not vertical.
I know, I know.
There are Kanpachi, right?
Kanpachi.
There are Kanpachi.
If you go this way,
you can go to the Koshu Kaido.
I know, I know.
This is the Takai-do side, right?
This is the Takai-do side.
If you don't go either way, you'll go straight.
Straight?
Which way is straight?
I'm getting angry.
That's the side road, right?
Which way is straight?
Tell me!
If you go to the Koshu Kaido, it's the Koshu Kaido.
It's like this with Kanpachi.
Oh, that's right!
You're going to the Koshu.
Yeah.
Right?
You're going to the Koshu.
Oh, that's right.
I'm going to the Koshu.
There's Kanpachi, right?
There's the Koshu Kaido, right?
You're going to the Koshu.
If you cross Kanpachi, it's right here.
It goes diagonally.
What's that?
There's a road.
What?
The old Koshu Kaido.
Oh, the old Koshu Kaido.
That's right.
But you're going to the Koshu Kaido at the end.
You're going straight.
You're going this way.
That's what it's about.
You sounded like you were going to the Koshu.
I said the Koshu.
He wrote the graduation thesis on DNA and human anatomy.
There are many things that humans have. Some people get so excited when they are stepped on the face.
Is there anything else that gets you excited when you are stepped on?
M and S are interesting. I'm doing research on them.
When you go to a store, you go like this.
It's a B course.
A course you don't even know.
I'm still like that.
You're still stepped on?
I'm stepped on.
Who is he?
He's a high school S.
What do you mean by high school?
Middle school and high school.
You're so annoying.
This is the 4th time.
It's high. It's high.
It's high?
I feel like I'm different.
I'm not different at all.
You're the one who gets stepped on, right?
I'm the one who gets stepped on.
I'm not good with words.
I saw a kid using it.
It wasn't funny.
When he said that, I was like, wow, it's not funny.
B!
Someone come here!
That's a lie, but...
It's too late for that.
The most amazing thing I've ever experienced was...
when the queen came with 5 or 6 people.
Isn't that a special course?
She came out and said, who are you?
What are you doing here?
She said, where are you putting the kotatsu?
She took the kotatsu to the living room.
There's a kotatsu?
She took the kotatsu from the living room to the living room.
I was so excited.
Wait a minute.
Are you going home?
That's right.
You're not going to the store?
I'm going to go in like this.
What are you doing?
What are you doing here?
You took the kotatsu to the living room.
She changed the whole pattern of the room.
She denied my life.
The telephone line was cut off, and the water pipe was cut off, too.
My lifeline was cut off.
I was really excited.
My life was...
Thank you very much.
We don't have much time today.
That's right.
Thank you very much.
No, no, no.
We'll come back again later.
Next time.
Next time, we'll have another combination.
Next time, Yamasaki will come out.
Yamasaki will come out.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for today.
Look forward.
What are you doing?
Thank you very much.
You can't end it like that.
Now, let's introduce ourselves one more time in order.
We'll see if the cards go up or not.
It's like this.
Now, number one.
Yes.
Entry number one.
Let's go here.
I did my best.
Thank you very much.
Now, even if it's regular, it's a good card.
Here you go.
It's been a long time.
Thank you very much.
It's good.
The winter was cold.
That was a bit.
Still good.
It's still good.
Number two.
It's the summer ofgang.
Let's do things this year.
Thank you very much.
Everyone who wants me to hug Little Nanas head-on.
Everyone, please show us your placards!
No way!
Really?
There's a new one!
What are you going to use?
I'm going to use it for the reenactment of the video.
That's great!
My heart is beating so fast!
Let's do it!
No.3!
Yes!
Yamazaki Yose!
I did my best!
I said there were 9 rules, but 5 of them will be over by the end of spring!
That's too early!
Please take care of me!
Don't lie to me!
You're laughing all of a sudden!
Let's go! Yamazaki, you can use me as the reenactor.
Everyone, please show us your placards!
Oh, Shizuoka!
There were 3!
Yes!
Tamushi Yenge, what should I do?
What should I do?
The last one is Mister!
I'm not going to do this!
Really?
If I say I'm the star, it's going to be Momoe-chan!
This is Momoe-chan!
This is the last one!
Please take care of me!
Everyone, please show us your placards!
It's you!
Please give him a round of applause!
He's so busy!
He's holding his body!
Sekai Warumiya-san, you're going to do it too, right?
Yes, as a guest.
Sekai Warumiya?
Yes.
I'm not going to talk.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.