9th Gagi no Chikai Arai and Chiki Chiki's New Year's Celebration!
How many times do I have to do this?
I've been doing this for a long time and I've received a lot of positive feedback.
So I'd like to do it again this year.
I'm Yonazaki Honsai.
Thank you very much.
And now, we have a special guest.
Why?
It's just started.
The main producer, Mr. Kenji Sugawa.
I hope we can all get along this year and make a fun program.
Get along?
Let's start with a toast.
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
You guys aren't in a good mood.
You should say, Good evening.
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
You should say, Good evening.
There are a lot of people here, but I heard that you know us.
Raise your hand.
It's funny.
Raise your hand if you've never seen us before.
Which one?
Yonazaki-san, is this okay?
Oh, really?
I'm sorry.
Well, then.
Let's start.
I hope we can all get along this year and make a fun program.
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
Cheers.
We hope we can all get along this year.
Well, then.
Please take a look at our program.
The next program is sponsored by the following sponsors.
The 9th Gaki no Tsukai New Year's Party.
They are drinking alcohol in a calm atmosphere as usual.
And they continue to talk about the party.
Thank you.
Thank you, Jel, Hamada san.
Mr. Hamada give Mr. Hamada.
Thank you.
Well, really...
I can't.
We didn't get any drinks.
Really?
Mr. Hamada doesn't drink.
We already had our drinks.
You're right.
This is our drink.
You should drink it right now.
You've had enough, then?
We already drank enough.
Everything I've had will turn up.
Give it to me.
It's for this training day of last week.
It seems perfect.
He didn't say anything.
That's right.
That's the point.
Thank you very much.
He was cool.
I wonder why.
I admire him.
That's right.
He didn't even say anything.
He didn't say anything.
That's the point.
Say that two more times.
In the same way.
What are you doing?
Mom.
Mom, I'll pour you some tea.
I'll pour you some tea.
What are you doing?
I'll drink it.
Why did you put it in?
I put it in.
downtown.
Nakai.
Your face is so red.
In the next episode of downtown's Gaki no Tsukaiya,
Chigichigi.
Wake up the UZO of comedy.
Shinshu Oarai Nyuuen.
Manzai Taigasse.
From now on,
Hamada.
Please stop.
That was a joke.
Don't say it.
Let's go!
You still don't know?
Not yet.
You're not going to say it?
No, not yet.
I'm still going to say it!
You're going to kill me!
Stop it.
Don't say it.
If you say it like this, I'll be the one who gets hurt the most.
Hurry up and say it.
Don't say it!
So, out of the 20 members of the cast and crew,
5 teams will be chosen.
What kind of new unit will be born?
First, I'll say the first number.
Start!
It's hard to decide.
Number 3!
Who is it?
I don't want to say it!
Who is Nakamura-san's partner?
Nakamura-san, please tell us.
I don't want to say it.
Nakamura will go first.
Let's go first.
I don't want to say it.
Number 5!
Who?
I don't want to say it.
Let's go for the second number.
Number 2!
Who is it?
I don't want to say it.
Who is Oonuma-san's partner?
Number 4!
I don't want to say it.
This is good.
It's like an old comedy comedy.
Let's go for the third number.
The third number is...
Number 6!
It's the first number.
It's the second number.
I have a habit.
You have a habit.
Who is Komu's partner?
Who is it?
Number 16!
This is hard.
I haven't been with Komu since 1998.
I'll say it.
Please don't do it.
Number 17!
Matsumoto-san!
It's Suzuki!
It's Matsumoto-san!
It's Suzuki's first time in a long time.
I was so into it.
I thought I'd be in trouble.
Matsumoto-san, please choose your partner.
It's Suzuki.
Number 8!
Who is it?
It's Kiri-san!
It's Suzuki!
Let's go.
The last one is Komu.
Please!
Number 9!
Who is it?
It's Tsutsun!
Please don't do it.
Who is it?
It's Takahashi-san!
I'll decide the topic from the first group.
The topic decided by Yamazaki.
First, Nakamura and Yanaoka's long-distance relationship.
Hamada and Onuma's topic is a space trip to the future.
And Kobayashi and Komurasaki's topic is a challenge to a homosexual topic.
Matsumoto and Irie's topic is a birth drama.
And finally, Takasu and Tsutsumi's topic is a couple with a mask.
It's a birth drama.
But I don't know which one is a joke.
It's a joke.
The story of the combination that was chosen by the lottery has started.
It's a serious battle with a professional will.
What kind of comedy will it be?
First, the first group.
Hamada and Onuma's topic is a space trip to the future.
It's coming.
Let's go.
1998 is over.
It's over.
It's the 21st century.
Two more years.
In the 4th century, a lot of things were invented.
For example, the internet.
The internet is popular now, isn't it?
You can do anything while you're at home.
This is convenient.
What's the secret?
That's right.
For example, in the 21st century, you can use your computer at home.
You can use your computer to order food delivery.
You can do it with your phone.
Also, in the 21st century, space travel.
Space travel?
I see.
Space is getting closer and closer.
Anyone can do it.
Even if it's a little difficult, you can do it.
You don't have any knowledge.
That's right.
I already know everything.
You know everything about space?
I already have knowledge.
Really?
Yes.
Then, for the sake of the time when something happens, please tell me.
I'll tell you today.
I'll tell you specially.
Thank you very much.
Yes.
Well, space.
We've arrived.
You're fast.
We've arrived at space.
We've arrived.
This is space.
No, it's still inside the ship.
The destination is inside the ship.
The destination is space.
I see.
Up to here, it's still okay.
That's right.
From here, it's space.
And it's weightless.
I see.
Why?
I know, in spite of that, why?
I know.
What?
You know.
Let's do it properly.
We'll do it properly.
We'll do it for real.
It's weightless.
Yes, please.
From here, it's weightless.
Yes.
I see.
You know, it's not a place.
Oh, I see.
I don't care!
There's space, but we were wrong!
I know.
I'm counting on you.
From here, it's weightless.
I'm already here.
Do it properly!
I'm already here!
I'm here!
Where should I go?
Why did you do that?
I'm not a sea!
Everyone, did you see?
Do it properly!
I'm sorry!
Don't say the same thing!
That's amazing!
Take it off!
Thank you very much!
That was good, wasn't it?
Tomurasaki-kun and Kobayashi-san's
Homo-sexual-manzai.
I'm looking forward to what kind of manzai it is!
It's Seido-style!
It's Shinjuku, isn't it?
In short,
it's a city of homosexuals.
Oh?
Are you okay?
So,
today...
That's amazing!
I'd like to study about homosexuals.
Good evening, everyone.
Today, we have a homosexual course
for 1 million people.
I'd like to study about homosexuals
Let's start with the first skit.
The first skit is
the best welcome
to the audience.
Let's get started.
Sensei, go ahead.
Welcome!
Thank you very much!
He's shy!
The second skit is
the best welcome
to the audience.
Sensei, go ahead.
Thank you very much!
He's shy!
The last skit is
the best welcome
to the audience.
Sensei, go ahead.
Thank you very much!
He's shy!
Why is this funny?
Taka's wife,
Kamen couple.
Welcome!
We, Ganso,
Michinoku,
Eisho,
We're singing.
That's right.
We look normal,
but there are
a lot of families
who look like they don't care,
but when you look at them,
when you look at them,
there are a lot of families
who look like they don't care.
Kamen couple.
I'm sorry.
It's a skit.
Ganso, Michinoku,
Eisho,
Kamen couple,
part one.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
I'm tired.
Do you want to take a bath?
I want to eat.
What is this?
I didn't know that!
I'm sorry.
Ganso, Michinoku, Eisho,
Kamen couple, part two.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Do you want to take a bath?
I want to eat.
Let's get a divorce.
You look happy.
Push the button.
Why are you saying that?
You don't get it.
Is this a divorce?
I don't have the confidence.
It's hard.
Nakamura and Yano are
Yano is in a long distance relationship!
Hello!
I'm Nakamura from FACT!
I'm Yano from FACT!
So cute!
Let's eat together!
The FACT!
Recently...
Yes?
There are a lot of hot topics.
What are they?
Torimachi-kun and Izumi Iramori-san's love story.
I didn't think those two were dating.
Those two are...
What kind of drama is that?
Beach Boys!
What are you talking about?
That's Beach Boys!
There are many kinds of love stories.
But the most popular one is...
Long distance love story.
It's a movie called Tokyo Station.
It's called Cinderella Express.
I'm going to give him a good look.
Finally, we're in Osaka.
We're here.
Why are you here?
It's because we're far away.
Scary.
It's scary.
Do your best.
See you next week.
I'll be waiting for you.
Kiss.
Caramel for you.
Why are you on it?
You have to do this in the center.
What are you doing?
He was born in Matsumoto and Irie.
Hello.
I'm Machan.
I'm Irie.
Together, we're Hammers.
I'm going to hit you.
Thank you.
Last year, there was a lot of news.
What do you remember?
The bank went bankrupt.
What about me?
It's all about the bank.
That's not true.
There was news that left an impression.
There was.
Tell me about it.
Actually, I made a new hit.
It's private.
It's completely private.
That's not true.
It's expensive and cheap.
There was news that a big star got married.
There was.
Tell me about it.
Sam's marriage.
Sam looks lonely.
That's right.
He's lonely.
Amuro is lonely, too.
What surprised me was that he was pregnant.
That's right.
He was singing while dancing.
He was pregnant.
I wonder if he's okay.
That's right.
That's a lie.
I was learning how to dance.
What?
Who were you learning from?
Amuro.
That's a lie.
It's true.
That's impossible.
Listen to me.
It's true.
Try it.
I'll try.
Stop it if you don't like it.
I really don't like it.
You're making me do it.
I'm begging you.
I'm sorry.
But when it comes to pregnancy, you have to be careful.
When it comes to childbirth, you have to be careful.
What was it?
That's right.
You have to be careful.
Where's the string?
That's not it.
You can't point that out.
But there's that thing.
The Lamaze method.
That's called,
You have to breathe in and out.
Try it.
I'll try.
Breathe in and out.
That's right.
You're a weirdo.
You're a nerd.
Stop it!
I'm done!
That was fast.
I was really nervous.
But I didn't forget anything.
I did it as you said.
As you said.
I'm half-way through, right?
That's right.
This is all thanks to Onuma-san.
I don't remember anything.
It's all thanks to Onuma-san.
Thank you, Onuma-san.
I lowered my head.
I should be able to take a picture.
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.