Shiku Kekkon Kose-Sakka Ryusen Hichi Hengen!
Yes, yes, yes.
This is a very special time.
Yes, that's right.
After all, this Kotobuki...
It's a celebration, isn't it?
That's right.
This person must do it too.
That's what's going on.
Yes, yes, yes.
Last week, at the meeting, when that story came out,
I suddenly stopped talking.
It was a reaction that could only be called the first point.
I see.
Let's have him appear.
Good morning.
The results so far...
I see, I see.
Kogoriko's Tanaka is the best.
Thank you very much.
That's right.
That's amazing.
And Kose-Sakka.
You're Kose-Sakka this time, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
What's Takasu?
The person who does the best in the back is...
That's right.
That's the result.
I don't think you'll get this.
I won't get it.
That's right.
Right now, luck is coming.
That's right, that's right.
I'm really nervous.
I don't know what's funny.
Everyone's face is dark.
That's a strange thing.
Everyone's eyes are dark.
That's right.
Everyone's mouth is dark.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
What should we do?
Hmm...
Hey...
Tohba?
What's Tohba?
Fujiwara is amazing.
His swimming is really good.
That's right.
It's really funny.
His butterfly is really funny.
What do you think of the people's vote?
Yamasaki needs to be used as a kid.
That's right.
This is necessary.
If you do it yourself, you can do it.
That's right.
Why are you so angry?
I don't know why you're angry.
I don't like it when you don't like it.
To be honest, I've been bored of it for two years.
I want you to get married.
I'm not angry.
It's a daughter's vacation.
I'm having fun.
Come.
Good, good, good.
Nice and slow.
That's it.
Come on, let's go.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on.
There, there, there, there.
Come on, let's go.
I'm not going to take this home with me.
I'm going to use it for my training.
The first half is similar, but the second half is getting more and more similar.
The first half is going to be a little more interesting.
It's not going to be so very natural.
It's not something you see on TV.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
What should I do?
I wonder if I should put something on it.
It's cold.
I'm starting to feel cold.
I wonder if the fangs will come off.
Maybe I should stop using fangs.
I can draw eyes.
But I can't draw hands.
I always forget to draw an item.
It was a little funny.
You did a good job.
I did a good job.
I wonder if I should put something on it.
You did a good job.
What should I do?
I don't have a microphone.
I have three weeks.
What should I do?
I'm scared.
I have 282,000 yen.
I don't have money.
I'm going to draw a cross.
I wonder if I should put something on it.
I'm done.
I had a good look.
I should have something.
It doesn't matter who it is.
I'm the boss.
I'll have milk tea.
I'll have a drink.
I'm the boss.
What? What about gravure?
He's definitely doing it.
It's getting late.
Do you want to have dinner again?
I'm sorry.
Horime-chan, good work.
Thank you.
You did well today.
I was going to pay you back for today's gala.
Can I pay you back as a gamer?
That's right.
I was going to pay you back for today's gala.
I'm going to pay you back as a gamer.
I'll give you a job as soon as possible.
Takahashi.
Yes.
I'll give you a job as a gamer.
Don't do that.
But he's the director.
He doesn't follow the rules.
He's a villain.
He used to be an old entertainer.
I'll give you a job as a gamer.
I can't move my body.
I'm cold.
I want to do it again.
Let's do it again.
It's really long.
This is nice.
Good morning.
Hello.
Sorry, I'm late from Matsumoto.
I'll get in after 15 minutes.
Yes.
No.
I'll say it.
Yes.
What is it?
That is...
Yes.
What is it?
I think it will be done in 30 minutes.
No, I understand that.
What is it?
Yes.
If you can do it with Mr. Tsukasa.
I understand that.
No, I understand that.
No way.
It was the last 7th time, so I didn't think it would end like this.
It was amazing.
Now, we will do the final calculation.
He's saying it very well.
There were 2 dirty ones.
Dirty ones.
If I say it again, Tanaka Kogoriko is the champion with 40,000 yen.
The final calculation has been made.
Who will be the winner?
44,000 yen.
That's amazing.
Congratulations.
Whose power is this?
Who will be the winner?
Yōkan Kusai wa Nakayoshi da Itsumo Futari de Mitsuyōkan
Yōkan no Tanna Yōkan no Yome Yoru wa Kuriyōkan
Good evening.
It's a little late.
Yes.
I'm looking at you.
I can't help it. I'm not feeling well.
Why?
I thought about it last night.
If I say this, you might think I'm weird.
It's okay if you don't say that.
Don't you think I should quit smoking?
That's right.
It's annoying.
I'm not using any health equipment.
It's just stupid work.
You eat it, you light it, you inhale it, you exhale it, you erase it, you eat it, you light it, you inhale it, you exhale it, you shoot it.
I wonder what you're doing.
I don't like that work, so I should quit.
It's getting hard to inhale, and I'm getting angry, so I'm going to quit.
I'm going to quit, so you quit.
Wait a minute.
I'm getting angry.
What?
Why me?
You said something like you wanted to quit.
That's right. I don't like that kind of work.
How many packs do you smoke a day?
About two packs.
About two packs. I smoke about two packs at least.
There are times when I get angry.
I see.
Think about it.
I've smoked before.
Now I'm going to smoke.
On the contrary, I'm going to try to smoke.
I've been smoking for about five years.
My eyes are like this.
It's not a cigarette.
My eyes hurt.
I haven't been smoked.
It's okay. If you're going to quit, you have to say it out loud.
You can't quit.
I see.
Say it here.
It's not true.
I think ordinary people can quit.
But you might think I'm going to get angry again.
Don't pretend to be angry.
I have a lot of bad habits.
I'm sorry.
You can bring it to me.
You have a lot of bad habits.
You can say it here.
You have to say it out loud.
You can say, don't bring it to me.
Just say it.
If you quit.
Why?
Because you are the leader of downtown.
Who is the leader?
If you quit, I might quit too.
For the time being, you should quit.
This recording is the last cigarette.
I'm going to smoke.
Why me?
Please.
I'm not confident.
Why?
Because you are the leader.
No.
I'm not confident.
Because you are the leader.
I smoke at home.
I don't want to bother anyone.
If you smoke at home, children will smoke.
They will smoke next to you.
Think about the future of your children.
I will use it three times.
Don't do that.
You are a very good person.
Really.
Think about that.
I'm not a good person.
Don't smoke.
No.
Then.
From today, I smoke as long as I drink.
What are you talking about?
That's why you are a non-smoker.
I will never smoke again.
Please don't smoke again.
Don't do that.
I told you to do it.
I don't want to do it.
But as I said earlier,
We have been laughed at for 10 years.
But we are a non-smoker.
We have been laughed at.
But I have been laughed at.
I have a lot of hair.
I am not a non-smoker.
I smoke a lot.
That's why you smoke.
I am not a non-smoker.
Don't smoke again.
The end.
I have a question for the beautiful-looking Matsumoto-san.
Yes, yes.
What is the meaning of Cosmetics Salon's Cosmetics?
I have studied a lot of English.
It's called Profile, right?
It's like Japanese English.
Do you know what that means?
It means side face.
What is the meaning of Cosmetics Salon's Cosmetics?
Do you often hear Cosmetics Salon?
Yes, I do.
What is the meaning of Cosmetics Salon's Cosmetics?
Say it in your head.
You won't get it anyway.
Don't talk like a fool.
I want to hear your opinion.
Cosmetics Salon.
Do you know what it means?
It means beauty, right?
I don't know what it means.
Let me hear your opinion.
What is the meaning of Cosmetics Salon's Cosmetics?
Say it in your head.
It means side face.
Or it means beautiful face.
What is Cosmetics Salon?
It means the beauty of side face.
Are you kidding me?
That's good.
I was surprised.
Cosmetics.
What is the meaning of Cosmetics Salon's Cosmetics?
It means romantic.
Don't talk like a fool.
Say it in your head.
I have to think about the meaning of Cosmetics Salon's Cosmetics Salon.
Cosmetics Salon means like.
You know, I'm a bit like a Yakuza.
I'm a bit shiny.
I'm a bit like a Yankee.
Tic means like.
Like.
Like what?
Like a couple.
You can say that as Tic.
So if you know Cosmetics Salon,
Tic means like that.
So what is Cosmetics Salon?
It means like that.
Do you understand?
If you don't understand.
If you don't understand, tell me.
Cosmetics means...
Half-open.
Half-open?
It's like the door of Cosmetics Salon is open.
It's like half-open.
Half-open.
I don't understand this Salon at all.
Can you tell me about the Salon?
It doesn't matter if it's a store.
What?
Is that so?
Half-open.
I don't know what kind of store it is.
Cosmetics Salon.
I don't know the meaning of half-open.
What's inside?
Don't ask me that.
Why?
It doesn't matter if it's a curry shop or udon shop.
If it's half-open, it's Cosmetics Salon.
Matsumoto-san, you have successfully overcome your baldness.
Please tell us the real reason why people are bald.
You have successfully overcome your baldness.
Really.
You can't overcome your baldness?
I really did my best.
Everyone is trying hard to overcome their baldness.
There are many scholars who say that it's because of stress and lack of sleep.
But I know that the real reason is not because of that.
Really?
Some kind of stress is really stress.
But the meaning is different.
Let's be clear.
There is no such thing as baldness in this world.
There is no such thing.
There isn't.
There are a lot of bald people.
Do you think so?
For example, let's say you see someone and think that they are a little bald.
But in reality, there are no bald people.
It's the stress of seeing them.
What do you mean?
It's obvious that you are bald.
You don't have hair.
You look like that because you are tired.
That's not true.
No matter what anyone says, the original Fuyuki is bald.
When you see the original Fuyuki, you look like that because you are tired.
That's not true.
No one is bald.
This is a little thin.
Onuma!
Come here!
That's what I mean.
I want to say that it's the responsibility of the viewer.
That's not true.
No matter what anyone says, the original Fuyuki is bald.
Yokoyama Noc is bald, right?
No, that's not true.
If you look at the original Fuyuki, it's not bald at all.
That's not true.
Onuma, come here!
This is bald.
That's not true.
Onuma!
That's why you have a problem.
Really.
How about the one who is wearing a wig?
What?
There is no one who is wearing a wig.
You are wearing a wig!
Who is?
Who is wearing a wig?
For example, who is wearing a wig?
Did I misunderstand?
That's right.
There is a misunderstanding.
Donmai! Donmai!
This program was provided by the following sponsors.