Last year and this year are completely different.
I was a little bit disappointed.
Usually idols put out calendars, but they do it beautifully and beautifully.
But this time, it's the opposite.
It's a ugly calendar!
Let's try to do it for a year with an ugly face.
That's what we decided to do.
It's not enough to just do it like that.
No, no, that's not true.
All of our staff, including the talent, are really all male.
No, no, no, no, no.
The back is especially terrible.
It's a shame.
This is a great
I'm going to make a show with a group of men.
No no no no
Please watch from here.
These guys
It's not strange anywhere.
It looks like you're motivated.
When you wear a tuxedo
Especially here
My father is a comedian
You can't see it!
This program is brought to you by the sponsors.
In the last episode, the person who was born during that month will be decorating the page.
As Mr. Matsumoto said, it's a punishment game.
The moment you do something, the face of that moment,
I'll make it into a calendar.
I don't want to see the ugly face I made.
The ugly face when I forgive myself,
this will last for a month.
Are you ready?
The panel over there.
There are various things hidden there.
Please choose.
Do something that you can see through.
I want you to capture that moment.
It's a little cruel inside.
Really?
There are some painful things inside.
I don't want to be in the video.
That's right.
First, Yamazaki Hosei who was born in February.
What kind of martial arts will he show us?
Thank you for your hard work.
It's in order from A.
Then I'll go with D.
D?
Face-to-face tennis smash.
It's scary.
Amazing.
This is a little dangerous.
Please!
Please watch carefully.
Wait a moment.
How was it?
It's impossible.
Slowly, slowly.
I'll stop it with a nice shot.
Here too...
Hey!
How...
This! This! This!
Stop! Stop!
That! That! That!
Well, Yamaguchi-san.
Is it okay now?
You got a pretty good one.
Thank you very much!
But, how do you think?
This is really something!
This is amazing!
It's like a flower.
If you make it a flower,
the screen won't show, right?
The face.
But the moment you hit the target, the face after the hit is more interesting.
Wait a minute.
It really hurts.
Tears are coming out.
Do your best.
This is hard.
Wait a minute.
Please.
I'll make it fun.
It hurts.
Why are you sweating so much?
I'm sweating.
Let's see it again.
Wait a minute.
Ah, it's already been 2 people.
Look at this.
Ah, it's good.
This is the last one.
This is the face of February.
You don't like this, right?
As a talent, you don't like this.
I don't like this.
Yuuki Yakon!
Ton!
Arale Yakon!
Next up is the high school footballer who was born in August,
Adachi Motoichi's challenge!
C!
Giant Shin!
Okay, start!
That's it!
Look at that! Look at that! Look at that!
Look at it more! Look at it more!
You have to look at it more!
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, that's good.
By the way, the first one was amazing.
It's scary.
Look, look, look, look!
Look!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Go back a little! Go back!
Put it back!
This is amazing!
Okamoto Taro!
Next is Hiroi Naoki
The next one to be chosen is the famous downtown manager, Kuchigawa.
Please choose E.
E!
The first is the face cleaning.
Oh, that's good.
Start!
You should have done it earlier.
Hey, stop that!
What are you doing?
It's funny.
Stop it!
You're so funny.
I'm asking you to do something.
Try to put it back.
It's not a joke.
Put it back.
When you lose this one, try stopping it.
This is a good one.
At this time...
How should I say it?
This was interesting.
Let's have Fujiwara-kun try something different.
I see.
I haven't been able to film it yet.
Next, the director who was born in June, Komunazaki, will challenge the kickboxer with his fierce kick.
I don't like this.
It's too early.
Not yet.
I...
It's not yet.
So my ears are so pretty!
It's like that guy who's feigning in front of YoungTiThis quiet over there.
He's a really feisty boy.
You're like a move player.
Are you???
How about here?
Ah.. this will be so hard.
Ahh so YOUre saying that this is hard, too.
Do you wanna go a bit further over there?
Ahhhh!
It's already a pekebo.
Tell Tell Bozu Tell Bozu
Fujiwara-san, can you do the part you did before?
Do your best, Fujiwara-san!
Okay, then...
Please!
Ouch!
I'll do it here...
And here...
This is a serious matter!
I'm going to the toilet!
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
That's hard!
The end
Next, the first appearance of the show, until October, Producer Kisarusa, what kind of face will he show us?
Please!
Let's see!
It's a face!
It's a small face!
It's a big face!
It's usable, right?
It's usable around here.
This is the sound of a pig eating a pig in a port town.
Next is the 4th born, Kokoriko Tanaka.
She is a giant balloon that is fixed in a chair and blows up in the trainer.
The end.
Ready, start!
Wow, it's coming.
I like the part where the balloon is in the front.
Oh, this is...
What is this?
It's Nike!
Next, I'll go.
You'll go?
It'll be hard if I go after you.
I'll go.
I really don't like it.
K!
Face-to-face rap!
You're good at fighting.
You're close to the opponent.
That's good.
If you slip and your face goes in here...
You'll be able to get the momentum.
You'll be able to jump.
Who's going to listen to me?
Ready...
Go!
이라는 Mister
Wait.
The liero 2 is open.
He may not be opened, but it is ok.
Why don't you know?
I'm not sure.
I can't move.
You look like a grandpa.
You look like a Jigaraku Bicho.
I can't move.
Please open your eyes.
If you don't hit it, it's a hit.
Can I do it again?
You have to open your eyes.
I think it's wrong to open your eyes.
I don't want to open my eyes.
I'll start.
Ready, go!
You were more powerful than before.
I thought I was going to hit you.
I had more strength than before.
That's scary.
Koji-san, you're really doing your best.
I'm still fine.
You're still fine.
You're doing your best.
From here on, you have to be firm.
Ah, I see.
I'm the leader of the Fujiwara group.
This is it!
I don't like it!
Usagi, Usagi
Next is the famous director, Onuma.
He is a huge face with three guns, and he is a real face.
Let's go!
Ready, start!
Oh, this is good.
You should open it sideways.
It's just a spying.
What is that?
What are you doing?
What is this?
Open your eyes.
Open your eyes!
What are you doing?
It's funny, isn't it?
What's with this face?
It's funny.
Stop it!
A little bit forward.
Look at this!
What is this face?
The next one to be chosen is the director of January, Tsumimoto.
He will receive a
falling shell from above with his brain and make a ugly face.
Let's go!
Hey!
There it is!
There it is.
You didn't change your face.
My head is getting bigger.
That was funny.
Your face is not getting bigger.
I'm not a gold digger.
Next is Kokoriko Endo's neck washing brush.
The dog pulls off the brush that is between the neck of both.
I'm ready.
Ready.
Go!
Wait a minute.
Ouch!
It hurts!
Show me!
Wait a minute, Iwaruka!
What is it?
You're looking too high.
I can't do it at all.
It's not ugly at all.
Your face is like this.
How about something different?
I'll tell you why.
It's like blood is flowing from my neck.
Really?
And finally, the down town hamada appears.
In front of him, a magic fire is burning up.
It's a big fire.
I hate this the most.
I can't move.
I got bitten.
Ouch!
What are you doing?
Sorry.
Do it again.
Ouch!
You guys are so noisy.
You!
You are hitting my ears.
What is Magic Fire?
So, I'm going to do it here.
I see.
This is scary.
Is this distance okay?
Really?
Don't stop me!
Don't blow.
Is this live?
You should have said that earlier.
Okay.
There are many behind you.
What?
Please!
This is the scariest thing
Ah!
You might burn your hair if you have water
If you don't have anything, pour water on it
You shouldn't hesitate
Okay, let's go
Please!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Do you need water?
You were really angry, right?
No, no, no
Right?
I was surprised.
His lips were a little hot.
It's amazing.
It didn't break for a moment.
This is the part.
It's a mask.
What is this?
Who's going to hit the mother?
You can use a lot of it.
Ah, seriously...
Seriously, there's a lot of them!
What is this?
Ah, I'm about to cry.
I'm about to cry.
This is sad.
I'm going to be reborn.
There is something Atlanta shut off in fact...
Spitting out
The fire is also very strong!
Very strong!
What is this?
A fire with a firecracker!
Very strong!
Let's see.
The fire is stronger than mine.
It's a firecracker.
Yes.
This is a firecracker.
It's a little funny.
I'm death
Finally, fire..
What can I do about it..
It is so beautiful
N-Low can't even take picture that
аша looks only at one side of the world
to go for something else
I'm ready but when I'm in the corner, I'll go
The four cards were all in bad shape, but they were decided to be played by numbers
The last one is the world's best Heipou, Director Taipou
He will show his face with Marvado
Here I go!
What's going on with the K-POD end?
You scared me!
What's going on?
I'm sorry!
Next is the same producer who was born in November, Tsugaga Shosen.
His job is to be a carpenter. Will he be able to take good photos of his work?
Please!
It hurts!
What do you mean by it hurts?
You know, it's really...
It's really painful.
I'm sorry.
It's dangerous. It's dangerous.
I can't stand it anymore.
The 11th month is not going well, but Saito is challenging again.
What? He's running away?
Oh god...
What is this?
It's a ghost!
This is amazing!
It's a ghost.
It's a monster.
It was a hard month in November, but Saito's expression was the final one.
Just in case,
It's temporary.
It's finished.
It's a gorilla.
It's a gorilla's child.
What is this?
What?
He's saying it.
What is this?
It's a photo.
It's either art or skin.
It's a question.
I eat dog food at home.
I lick the back of my pants.
That kind of...
That kind of ghost.
The dog is running away!
Let's go for a walk.
This is a good present.
I've been with people like this for a year.
In November, everyone, really, don't do new challenges and overcome it.
It's already too late.
If you do things you don't really need to do, it's too early.
Don't do things like talking too much.
I don't feel anything.