Let's meet in the 4th episode of the 100-yen goods challenge, Kekeke no Youkai Gundan!
This time, we're going to become Youkai characters using 100-yen goods.
In the past, it was Showa no Star and Star Wars.
It was a huge success.
It wasn't a failure.
1000 yen budget, 100-yen goods challenge.
This time, this character is the theme from the popular Youkai you all know.
Please enjoy while comparing the real thing with your smartphone.
First of all, let's take a look at each of the characters.
Ready?
The main character.
As expected.
Amazing.
I see.
200 yen.
800 yen.
Each Youkai character is decided here.
KITARO, 1000 yen is not enough.
1000 yen is not enough.
Please.
The mouse sound is also surprisingly easy.
This is the most difficult.
This is very difficult.
How do you express this?
I will definitely give you 100 yen.
Why is that?
Because you are naked.
DOM ROCK will also be happy.
You cheated on me.
I'm sorry.
They went to the 100 yen shop.
They went back to the studio and finished their production.
Finally, the Youkai battle in the studio set will be shown.
This is an image.
This is in my head.
Do you have any particular points?
Basically, I'm barefoot.
I'm naked.
I will make this with felt.
This is perfect.
This is OK.
This is fast.
I will definitely use this.
I see.
This may be good.
I will do this.
I will make two of these.
This is perfect.
I will decorate this later.
I want a head.
This is strange.
I want a small head.
I want this.
Do you have an image?
I don't have an image.
Do you have hair?
I have no hair.
I have no choice but to shave this.
Everyone said that this can be made with 200 yen.
I have never seen a 100-yen shop that sells only white cloth.
This is a envelope.
ITAMONOEN has a unique corner.
This is not sold.
If I put a corner on this, it will be over.
This is solid.
This is good.
This is good for creating a corner.
Wait a minute.
This is a rice bag.
Is this a purchase item?
This is an ideal corner.
This is perfect.
How much is this?
This is 5 yen for this.
This is sold, so this is good.
This is a non-woven sheet.
This is a non-woven sheet for gardening.
This is 1.35 x 2 meters.
This can be made with 5 yen.
This can be made with 200 yen.
Do you have an image?
I don't have an image.
I only need this.
I don't need this.
This is 70 liters.
This is a rice bag.
This is an eye ball.
I don't know if it's okay to call it an eye ball.
I think the wire is better.
This is not good.
I think a ball is better.
This is good.
This is the most difficult.
There are many things to buy.
I definitely need this.
I wear clothes inside.
I have a beard.
I have hair.
I don't know if I can do this with a garbage bag.
What color is this?
This is black.
I see.
Is it okay to have a black garbage bag?
I don't think this is dirty.
I will cut this.
This is 300 yen.
I don't think this is dirty.
This is my beard.
I will paint this black.
For example.
This is a hair tie.
This is good.
I don't need to cut this.
I don't need this.
How many do you need?
I need three.
Really?
What kind of shirt is this?
This is blue.
This is like this.
I don't need this.
I have a beard.
What kind of face is this?
This is different.
I can draw a face from above.
What is this?
This is a cloth that can be pasted.
This is convenient.
This is this.
This is difficult to throw away.
This is too cute.
This is this.
I think hair is important.
What is this?
This is a little doping.
This is a very good head.
This is very good.
This is like this.
This is a good head.
This is a stainless ball.
I put sand in this.
I think cat eyes are important.
I put this in.
I think this can be used for cat eyes.
I cut this.
What is this?
This is a light.
This is a little doping.
This is 200 yen.
This is not 100 yen.
This is like this.
This is a little different.
This is this.
He checks other items that can be used for red clothes.
This is 200 yen.
This is a black gum.
I want to hang this up.
I want to make cat eyes.
I put this in.
I'm curious about the other products.
I think KITARO is a mouse man.
I think the mouse man is too strong.
I hate the mouse man.
I cut this.
I think this can be used for cat eyes.
MATSUMOTO eats a lot of mouse products.
This is too shiny.
This is quite expensive.
This is 100 yen.
This is small.
What is this?
This is more sticky than I thought.
This is a mouse.
I think this can be used for cat eyes.
I don't need this much.
This is a character production.
I want to use this.
This is easy.
This is enough.
MATSUMOTO is making a bunch of straws.
The color of the hair is different depending on the tree.
This is a purple kimono.
This is a white kimono.
What happened?
This is shorter than I thought.
What is this?
This is a obi.
HAMADA starts making CHANCHANKO.
This is a horizontal bar.
This is different in length.
This is shorter.
How can I cut this?
I can't cut this.
He arranges the items he bought at a 100-yen shop.
It's difficult to make a sphere.
He cuts the hair with scissors.
He makes a beard.
Please give me a long beard.
Why is this a safety pin?
This is a safety pin.
This is a very good thing.
I'm relieved.
Can I fix this?
If I fix this now, it will be like this.
What should I do?
He starts working for 30 minutes.
This is a lot of work.
After this, Ichido and KONAKU gather.
How did they get together?
Ichido, who made a yokai character using 100-yen goods, has gathered in the studio.
What will happen?
Murarihyon, the leader of the yokai, has a plan to defeat Kitaro.
Where is the mouse man?
His body is made of suit covers.
His face is made of a computer case.
His beard is made of a bandage.
His face is made of a bandage.
Will Kitaro really come here?
Of course.
I'm looking forward to it.
I will stop him today.
What is this?
This is a hairstyle reproduced with a garbage bag and a raincoat.
You are Murarihyon.
You deceived me.
Sorry.
This is your last day.
Take this.
Damn it.
I got a remote control.
What?
I want to see everything in your hands.
Damn it.
Wait a minute.
You are Murarihyon.
This is a hairstyle reproduced with a bandage and a raincoat.
You deceived me again.
Take this.
Sorry.
Wow.
Damn it.
This is the only way.
Are you running away?
Kitaro.
Defeat them quickly.
The lower half of the body is protected with duct tape.
The eyes of the eyeball are finished with red and black felt.
I brought my father.
Dad.
Damn it.
I can't do this.
What should I do?
Damn it.
You deceived me again.
This is a girl's style with vivid red.
The nails are made of duct tape.
The eyes of the cat are made of soap.
Take this.
Damn it.
Kitaro.
This is your chance.
Take this.
Youkai Chan Chan Ko.
Dad.
Are you okay?
Get ready.
Mom.
The eight parts of the head that he was most particular about.
It's a big problem that he boldly put two
balls on it.
Mom.
Hey.
Why?
Why is this guy on it?
No, it's getting heavier and heavier.
It's going back to the back of the head.
It's all gone.
It's going to be crushed by a friend.
I can't move it because it's heavy.
Eight points.
It's my turn.
It's a good place.
I'm going to kill them with my magic.
I know that.
He uses a non-eating sheet for entertainment.
The hand that uses the fork, the eye of the tape, and even the details are particular about it.
Ah, it's painful!
What? What's wrong with me?
Looks like you've regained your sanity.
I'm glad. Now all that's left is to punish him.
Hey, mouse man!
Where are you going?
Wait!
Mouse man!
My mother used a straw and put it in here so I wouldn't lose it.
What's wrong with you?
This is 700 yen.
You have 300 yen left?
I have 300 yen left.
And I have a lot of straws left.
I have a lot of this, too.
What's this?
This is something to stop.
Oh, but it's good.
Is this a computer case?
What's a computer? Well, something like that.
This is a straw.
I put it in here so I wouldn't lose it.
It's convenient.
Can you see it?
It's good, isn't it?
What is it?
What?
I have a cold.
You have a cold.
Are you okay?
A mouse man.
It's hard to see the food.
It's dirty, isn't it?
Shut up!
The mouse man is a little dirty.
It was a play, but it wasn't very good.
It wasn't good at all.
You were the worst.
It was very bad.
The tempo was also very good.
No, no, no.
I haven't changed my name at all.
Are you okay?
I can't do it anymore.