Part 5
OK, I'll show you.
OK, start.
All right.
Where is it?
Here?
Ouch!
Shhh!
Ah!
Negation
Let's see
One, two
Good
Shhhhhh
Tsk
Seriously?
Ah, here
Tsk tsk tsk
Wait, wait
Ouch
You just failed
Shhh
Be quiet
No
Ah, sorry
Sorry
Wait
Shhh
No, be quiet
No, no
No
Come on
Wow
Oh
none
n
me
Tak Seriously
No
w
a
I mean
I'm sure it's a big one.
Where is it?
It's a big one.
What is this?
Sit down.
The microphone is off.
I didn't know.
What is this?
It's the last one.
I didn't know.
Please.
It's the last one.
I didn't know.
I was nervous.
What is this?
It's a big one.
There are many legs.
I will open it.
Please open it.
I will put my tail on it.
Please move.
It hurts!
Shhh!
Wait a minute.
It hurts!
Your face is funny.
It's disgusting.
It hurts!
Your hands are full of religion.
My room...
Sorry.
We'll do it slowly.
I'll do it, so just célo.
Please wait.
Please wait...
Shhh!
It hurts!
I'm sorry.
Shhh!
I want to catch fish.
You caught a fish.
I failed, right?
You failed.
You moved a lot.
It was stiff.
It's okay.
You can't move.
Be careful, be careful.
I'm going to try it.
Ouch!
I'm going to continue.
It's fast.
This is a river because it hurts.
I won't do it again.
I'm going to continue.
It's so good.
That's an interesting face.
Don't shake it.
I'm sorry.
Up and down.
This is Hamada's first punishment.
And the third episode ended with Yamazaki being bad at it.
However, there was a story that was not broadcasted because of Yamazaki's mischievousness.
Please take a look at the unreleased story.
What is this?
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
He said wait a minute.
I told you to wait!
What do you mean, wait!
Wait a second.
Everyone's waiting for me.
I don't want to see it.
I told you to wait.
That's what I said in front of the car.
That's not good.
Everyone doesn't like it if it doesn't pass.
At least don't report it.
It was a safe place.
Don't do that.
It's a safe place.
What is it?
Change it.
Which one?
Ready, go.
It's a safe place.
It's the worst.
Sorry.
It's a safe place.
It's a big voice.
It's a library.
Are you okay?
It's a safe place.