The five men who aim for the top of the entertainment world.
Their name is...
Osu! Ikidome-Bun!
Masato-san, what are we doing today?
We are going to create a new club.
There are many clubs in this world.
The club that we are most good at is...
Ikidome.
Who is good at it?
The five men who represent Yoshimoto.
It's about us.
Were you sleeping?
I was sleeping.
Ikidome-Bun will be formed here today.
How many seconds can you hold your breath underwater?
This is the first time we are going to have a match like this.
The leader is Yamanaki Hosei-san.
Thank you very much.
I am the leader.
I am Yama-chan's leader.
No, it's simply long.
This is a secret weapon.
Really?
You have a lot of lung capacity.
Ikidome is about lung capacity.
You just said it.
I said it.
You said it.
That's why I have a lot of lung capacity.
I don't have to do anything.
What do you mean you don't have to do anything?
I don't have to say that.
I don't have to wait for my turn.
I will definitely win.
However, this is the first match of the staff, so I won't bring anything half-hearted.
I see.
Today's opponent is a strong opponent with 3G.
That's fast.
Then, let's have the memorable first opponent appear.
Here you go.
Come on.
It's amazing.
This is amazing.
This is completely stupid.
This is dangerous.
Are you all right?
This is completely stupid.
I'm a stupid boss.
Why are you hiding?
I was a little embarrassed.
This is a strong opponent.
I'm sorry, but you're wrong.
Why?
I think Mizumoto is the number one in the entertainment world.
That's right.
I just want you to lick my yamanaki.
I will do it.
I'm already a bug.
You can't do that.
I will definitely win.
I've had a near-death experience when Mr. Daruma fell in the water.
That's too much.
You're working too hard.
I will definitely win.
You guys, too.
You can't do that seriously.
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
This is a team match.
From the vanguard to the leader.
We will do it alternately.
We will eliminate the victory in the total time.
Please decide the order.
Let's start the game.
This is a vanguard match.
Who will be the team?
I'm not the strongest in the universe.
Is it me?
It's me.
The universe is...
The end.
Thank you.
I will do it seriously.
I will not lose.
I will definitely not lose.
I don't want to lose.
The team that came to the vanguard is JORDAN'S MIMATA.
Will the hungry stomach be able to survive?
The team that came to the vanguard is MIMATA.
Wait a minute.
Why did you decide to go first?
That's too serious.
I have a record.
I can't do that.
I will think about it from the middle to the end.
I understand.
Let's go to the second half.
By the way, the world record is 8 minutes and 6 seconds.
This is the world record.
Please do your best.
I don't think about it later, so I can do it.
I will measure the time when your face enters here.
I understand.
Are you ready?
Yes.
I will do my best.
Let's go.
Start.
I will do my best.
Why are you worried about his face?
You are still in the middle of the game.
What are you doing?
Can you hear me?
I can't see it.
This is not a gesture.
What are you talking about?
I don't know what you are talking about.
36 seconds.
What did you say?
How many seconds?
You can't hear me.
36 seconds is not bad.
I don't know.
I don't have everyone's record.
This is the first time.
The first team is Endo.
I'm nervous.
Relax.
I'm not used to it.
Let's go.
Endo, get ready.
Start.
He looks serious.
Good.
He is concentrated.
It's good that fine bubbles are coming.
Good.
Calm down.
It's a little dangerous.
Good.
It's not too far!
Oh!
Oh, no!
You got it!
No way!
Next, it's Taka-san and me.
Okay!
We're going to talk about it here.
We only have 11 seconds left.
That's right.
I'm sorry, but...
Yeah.
We're going to have to split it up.
I'm sorry, but...
The northern team, Jihou, is 45 years old.
He has a rich career and is in the top class in the entertainment world.
Oh, I'm so calm.
You're calm?
I feel like I'm back home.
I feel calm when I come to this water tank.
Okay, let's go!
Ready...
Go!
Why are you making a refreshing face?
It's refreshing.
Amazing.
Amazing, amazing.
It's refreshing, but it's a little oppressive.
I see.
It's time consuming.
But is it okay to open your mouth?
No, it's not.
Why do you have a advertising agency?
Advertising agency?
Wait a minute.
Oh, my God.
What are you doing?
It's not finished yet.
It's coming out of my mouth!
Are you kidding me?
More!
Hang in there!
It's coming out!
50 seconds!
One more!
Wow!
I wanted to get one more!
Something came out of my mouth!
Something came out of your mouth!
It's hard!
It's coming out of my mouth!
By the way, he's the worst in our team.
I think he's probably the worst.
Gaki team.
Jihong is Hamada.
How far can a weak guy survive in the water?
How many seconds?
I want you to say 45 seconds.
Hamada was 53 seconds.
I'm 42 seconds below.
If you say 45 seconds,
You can see it inside.
You can see it?
Not at all.
You can't see it?
You have to wear goggles.
Let me borrow your goggles.
I can't take my face off with goggles on.
We're the reaction of the face.
Hamada is a bodyguard.
Mr. Hamada.
Thank you in advance.
Ready, start!
I'm counting on you.
45 seconds.
Look around you.
What?
No way.
It's weird.
It's just a half cut.
My ears are tingling.
It's like a man's cotton swab.
I'm counting on you.
It's red in the water.
It's time.
I'm sorry, but we won.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was a good job.
It's like a child.
I can't see it.
I can't see it if it's that fast.
I was trying to see it desperately.
I'm sorry.
It's red.
I was trying to see it desperately.
Next, the junior high school students are from the Gaki team.
I want to make use of my scuba experience, but I'm worried about my weakness in the real game.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm not kidding.
I want to continue this down.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm concentrating on it alone.
Don't ask me anything.
OK.
Let's go.
Are you ready?
Sometimes I have an accident like this.
Don't worry.
OK.
I'm scared.
It's good.
I'm concentrating.
I'm focusing.
Not yet.
Don't do it.
No.
I can't concentrate.
Ok, go ahead.
31 seconds.
No way!
What the hell?
I drank water.
That's terrible.
Team Juken is in Jodanzui Yamazaki.
They are 180 cm tall and have a great body.
Can they keep the lead?
Are you ready? I'm going to do it seriously.
What did you say?
What?
I'm going to show you how I do it.
I'm sorry.
I don't care how you do it.
I just want to show you how I do it.
Just show me how you do it.
Ok, let's do it.
I'm going to show you how I do it.
Ready.
Go.
It's too big.
It's hard to see.
I don't know how far it is.
I'm so angry.
It's dangerous.
What?
Oh my god.
Hey!
Wait a minute!
Get out!
You still have it, right?
Do your best!
Hey!
You can win!
I'm sorry.
I hope you win.
You can go home.
You can win in 30 seconds.
If you have more than 30 seconds, you can win.
What should we do?
The order of our team.
If you have confidence, you can win.
You can win.
I'm serious.
If you really do it, you can win.
Let's leave it to the old man.
Really?
Excuse me.
Can I do it?
I'll change the order here.
What?
This is the order.
Wow.
It's more amazing than I thought.
I'll give you a pressure.
Boom!
The king of the school team, Yamazaki.
The father of Ichijino, who has absolute confidence in his son-in-law,
changes the image of a loser.
It's about time for my record.
Actually, the other day,
Yamazaki-san.
It was a washing machine.
Yes.
About 3 minutes.
What?
I think.
I went inside.
I was surprised by the difference in pressure between the washing machine and the water pressure.
That's.
If you put it out, it's like 9 seconds.
Please, Yamazaki.
Let's go.
Oh, I just read it.
The problem is that it sinks in such a picture.
It's like taking a bath.
It's a little dangerous, so 50 seconds.
Are you okay?
You're already in the water.
I'll be back in 50 seconds.
There's no choice but to betray.
This is serious.
It's not funny at all.
Betrayal.
Let's go, Yama-chan.
Ready.
Start.
Then it floated.
Yes.
It's more suspicious to breathe.
Oh, it's already stuck.
Look, look, look.
It's okay.
From here.
It's different from a sleeper.
It's better to raise your head, but it hurts.
That's right.
Oh, look, look.
I'm not going to be able to afford it.
It's okay.
This is bad.
Are you crying?
I'm crying in the water.
I'm crying.
It's already 50.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Look at my eye.
It's NYX!
It's here!
It's great!
One minute.
It's here.
It's our chance, our time.
That's great!
That's one minute.
It's great.
1 minute 10 seconds.
What?
Zaku-san, do your best!
Apologize!
All of a sudden?
You look like Kyogenji!
Amazing!
That was amazing!
You were amazing!
You were completely defeated.
You were one minute ahead.
1 minute and 4 seconds.
You have one minute.
You can win.
Yamazaki, you are amazing!
That was amazing!
Amazing!
The Gaki team has a good ace.
That was amazing!
You were suddenly defeated.
I was suddenly defeated.
I died once.
You were completely defeated.
You were amazing.
You were suddenly defeated.
You were completely defeated.
The Tsukishou from the northern team is the second best in bench press.
The well-trained body shows an evolution.
Are you ready?
Ready?
Go!
Here it comes.
What is this?
Look at this.
You're so fast.
But he's still doing it.
He's still doing it.
You can still do it.
You're getting close.
You're so fast.
This is bad.
You're getting close.
You're getting close to your father.
You're not good.
Hey!
You're getting close.
You're not good.
What is this?
Mark from Anies Bay.
Not yet.
A little more.
He's still doing it.
You can do it.
You're getting close.
Just a little bit more.
You're doing it.
You're getting close.
You've got one minute left.
He's doing it.
Just one more minute.
Just a little more!
Wow!
Oh my god!
Yes...
Класс, spiral!
Yay!
Good work, guys!
Finally, let's find the winner!!
Let's find the winner!!
That's how they are looking for members of Great Gida!
That's how they are looking of members of Great Gida!
Ready, start!!
ugs!
Please stop!
These pictures are not allowed!
Ahahaha…
I can't move at all.
This is not good.
He's coming back.
He did it!
He definitely got it.
That's the only thing you could do?
I'm really sorry.
I've been doing this for a long time.
That's right.
What should I do?
It's a subtle second.
You can do it.
46 seconds.
It's different.
That's right.
It's subtle.
Do you have any advice?
No, I don't.
Wait! Wait!
The target is Matsumoto.
Will he be able to reverse the difference of 14 seconds in the pressure?
He's really good.
But he couldn't swim 25 meters in the water.
He might have jumped out of the water with his eyes rather than wearing goggles.
It's hot.
It's okay. It's okay.
There are a lot of galleries.
I'm nervous.
Relax.
46 seconds.
46 seconds is a long time.
It's 30 seconds.
It's impossible.
I'll do it in 30 seconds.
You have great pressure.
That's right.
That's good.
What's with the rubber band?
Here we go.
I'm counting on you.
Ready.
Go.
He's being cornered.
Okay.
He can't do anything.
What kind of face is this?
It's like a wax doll.
It's okay.
It's really stable.
Why is it so stable?
It's 30 seconds.
It comes quickly.
It's really stable.
Why is it so stable?
It's 30 seconds.
It comes quickly.
Yama-chan, you're suddenly getting...
Hey, hey!
Hey, Kanasawa!
WHAAAAAAAAT?!
Wait, wait!
WHAAAAAAAAAT?!
WAIT!
OOOOOH!!!
That's close!
Close!!
OOOOOH!!!
That was close!
You had 4 seconds left!!
It's a tie!
Matsumoto-san, thank you!
I'm a bit frustrated!
3 minutes and 55 seconds vs 3 minutes and 51 seconds!
The one who drinks too much wins!
Let's do a rematch!
Of course, let's do it!
Can I accept this?
We were serious today, but I think they'll be serious next time.
Let's do a special training!
I'm glad it was 13 seconds.
To be honest, we were like that too.
Even if it was 15 seconds.
This program was provided by the following sponsors.