I'm hungry.
You know Tokyo Walker, right?
Yes, yes.
I'm looking for a restaurant there.
Oh, really?
Here.
Oh!
No one knows this place yet.
Is it good?
It's really good.
Really?
This is the only restaurant I know.
Oh, that's good.
It's really good.
Yes.
Hello.
It's nice here, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
The old man is nice, too.
The old man is a stubborn old man.
Yes.
What should I do?
I want a pork cutlet set menu.
And you?
I want a set menu.
Just fool around.
What?
I usually order a pork cutlet set menu.
I think it's better to fool around.
I was fooling around.
What?
You were fooling around just now?
Yes, I was.
It's a set menu.
I'm sorry.
It's hard to understand.
I want a pork cutlet set menu.
Yes.
I want to have a pork cutlet set menu.
Then I'll have a pork cutlet set menu.
Hum.
You laughed, didn't you?
I'll have pork cutlet set meal
I'll have the same
You're so annoying
Welcome
What are you doing here?
I was watching Tokyo Walker
You came here
I heard you were coming
Really?
What should I do?
Don't make fun of me
I'll learn
I can't make a set meal
I'll have pork cutlet set meal
This is golden 4
I see
I'll have tempura set meal
I'll have pork cutlet set meal
You're so slow
What?
I'll wait for you
You're so slow
I was coming
You're too slow
The entertainment industry is flourishing
Two wild beasts are trying to kill each other
Stop it
Jimmy Onishi is scared
Don't hit me
What are you doing?
Yamazaki Hosei is the fastest in the entertainment industry
A fight without justice
Do you like your seniors?
What are you doing?
Why did you come here?
Sit down
I want to see your seniors
Stop it
Do you want to destroy the restaurant?
Do whatever you want
You're too strong
Don't talk to me like that
You should ask Imada
Do you want to?
If you don't want to hit me, hit me somewhere else
I won because of my strength
This program is brought to you by the sponsor
Thank you for watching
Please subscribe to our channel
What are you doing?
Do you understand?
Let's eat together
Let's go
Do you understand?
There's no point in hitting each other
I'm angry at you
Eat
Why are you so quiet?
You're good at eating after a fight
What are you doing?
Stop it
Do you like your seniors?
What are you doing?
Stop it
They're tired
Give me some water
What are you doing?
No way
Stop it
Do it outside
You don't understand
Let's go
I'm angry at you
He's sensitive to smell
Hit me
He came out
He's sensitive to smell
I'll run away
Yamazaki, catch him
Do it inside
Why did you let him go?
You should flush the toilet
What?
You can't go to the toilet
Flush it
I can't flush the toilet?
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
You light a cigarette for me
You're the same
Wait
You light it
I don't light it
You don't flush the toilet
I'll tell you
No one will notice if I don't flush the toilet
No one will notice
I don't know
If I light a cigarette for you, you'll go
Why?
How many cigarettes did I light?
You're doing that at home
If you light it at home, you'll get a cramp
Don't say that like it's a joke
You should flush the toilet
There's a reason why I don't flush the toilet
What's the reason?
I'll go back there
Teritory
You can go back after you flush the toilet
I don't flush the toilet
You don't flush the toilet
I can't flush the toilet
That's not true
You pooped a lot
Did you see me pooping a lot?
That's too much
I thought it was a big dream
It doesn't matter
I don't care
Listen to me
I'm so angry
To whom?
You know
Hakone's sculpture
Listen to me
If you don't cut it, I'll flush it
I'll talk here
There was a story about me and two girls going to the museum
I said I don't know
I said I didn't go
I read the article
I didn't wear a hat or sunglasses
I just walked around
I'm a big star
I said I'm a big star
Can you do that?
I don't know what you're talking about
I don't know how you felt
I have many faces
I just happened to be in that situation
I'm angry
I've been in that situation many times
I don't have a photo
I'm nervous
You saw it, right?
I thought so
There are two Abecs in the forest
I saw it too
I was surprised
Why are you so excited?
I'm not excited
I was surprised
I don't care about the photo of Abec
I want to see it
I don't have such a photo
You don't have to say that
When did you take it?
I'm angry
I know that
You don't have to say that
I'm angry
I don't care about the photo
I don't have such a photo
I don't know about it
I don't care about it
I have a girlfriend next week
You don't have a girlfriend
If you say that, I can't be popular
You...
Stop it
I'm not good at eating
If there is a rumor, I will write it
Thank you
You are a small man
If I say I'm going to go out, you don't have to go out
That day, I was in front of the apartment
I was listening to a song
But that day
It was a Friday night
I didn't have an alibi
I was listening to a song
My girlfriend was working in Ginza until 7 o'clock
What?
She was working in Ginza until 7 o'clock
Don't try to hide it
Let's go
7 o'clock at night
That's too extreme
At 7 o'clock at night, I was with a person who was working in Ginza
We fell in love
When I went to Hakone, what time was it?
Picasso was sleeping
What?
Right?
That's right
There was an alibi
I had a lot of things to say
I thought that if I went to the apartment tomorrow, there would be a lot of people
I was going to say it
But when I went out, no one was there
I was in the army
I couldn't explain it
If you get married, you'll be sick
If you get married, you'll be friends
I'm glad I was in the army
You were just in the army
I was in the army
That's too bad
I didn't see it
I heard it from someone
There was a wide show
There was a reporter who told me that I was wrong
The reason why I was wrong was
Anuma-chan wouldn't go to such a romantic place
What's the reason?
You're talking
I'm very romantic
I'm romantic
What's the reason?
Do you want to get on the planet?
I want to die
I want you to die soon
That's a wide show
I lost weight
That's a story that ended
You can't change it
That's true
Is it over?
I don't know if it's over
But it ended before I got married
I'm not married
Why?
I don't have money
What?
I don't have money to get married
I don't have a partner
What?
When I talk like this
They talk quietly
I'm serious
I'm scared
What are you talking about?
Is there a bomb?
Maybe here
If I'm going to get married, can I say it as a kid?
It's up to you
I'll say it as a kid and leave the mic
Hello
By the way, are you afraid of being kissed by a woman?
Or are you afraid of showing off?
Do you wear a kiss mark recently?
Do I wear it?
It's not a long time ago
About 20 years ago
About 10 years ago
I didn't wear it
At that time, a kiss mark was an expression of love
I don't wear a kiss mark now
I just wear it
When?
A long time ago
I wore a kiss mark
I was told a lot
I don't know if it's a kiss mark
I don't know if I was bitten by a crab
It's cool
Why do you wear a helmet when you go to school by bicycle?
It's because I follow a rock
Are you stupid?
Why?
I'm the one who runs on the cliff
You know
There is a school road that follows a rock
Is it helpful to wear a helmet?
That's the truth
The answer is correct
It's because there are a lot of yakuza around here
It's a matter of mind
When I follow a rock, I wear a helmet
I can't do that
If I follow a rock, I'll die
But it's more important to wear a helmet
It's a matter of mind
Why don't you wear a helmet in the city?
I don't have to follow a rock
There are a lot of things in the city
Like under the construction site
I know that
I've been hit by a hammer
When I was in high school
You didn't die?
I didn't die
The hammer hit me
Really?
What happened?
I'm fine
That's not true
You fell down
I didn't fall down
That's not true
It's true
I was talking to him
We were talking about something
He said it's dangerous
The hammer hit me
I thought it was a hammer
You're lying
What are you talking about?
I was talking about something
You're lying
I thought it was a hammer
Really?
A rock followed me
A rock?
A beast came out
A beast came out and I was wearing a helmet
I thought it was a helmet
I was talking about something
Why would a beast look at a helmet and run away?
I don't think so
I don't think it's a weapon
I can make tempura with a helmet
It's not a weapon
It's a weapon
Why are you different?
It's okay
Don't say it
I really didn't hate it
Really?
Let's end it here
I really didn't hate it
One more
What are you doing?
Why are you wearing a helmet when you go to a country school?
That's because
There are times when a rock follows me
That's dangerous
You're a rock
Even if a rock follows you
If you wear a helmet
You can't wear a helmet
Even if a rock follows you
You won't be saved with a helmet
It's for carrying
There are a lot of yakuza around here
It's the same as wearing sunglasses
I don't know if a beast will come out
What is a beast?
It's for carrying
What?
One more
Why are you wearing a helmet when you go to a country school?