Next time, at Gaki no Tsukai Arahen, Chikitsuki Jitsukyan Baachan Jutsu Chou Taikai!
Good evening!
How are you all doing on your day off?
What?
How are you all doing today?
What are you talking about?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Tonight, we're going to have some fun with our grandfathers and grandmothers.
Let's start with the Matsumoto team.
Good evening!
We're going to give you a quiz using gestures, right?
What do you think of these shoes?
Aren't they easy to put on?
What kind of person are you?
I'm from London.
How long have you been wearing these shoes?
About 100 years.
Isn't it fun?
First, we have Komori's aunt.
Please give her a round of applause!
Recently, she's become the answer to a lot of our questions.
Her name is Amamoto.
Good evening!
How long have you been wearing these shoes?
I've been wearing these shoes since I was young.
I don't
There used to be a button like this.
I have moved half of it to the left....
We don't have to worry about this.
Next, welcome to chop
we have Namikoshi and Tokujiro.
And, the assistant is this person. Please welcome!
First, Hamada Team's Namikoshi-san, please come over here.
Hamada Team's Namikoshi-san, please come over here.
What is it?
Your teeth are so narrow!
Please make a gesture to your ally.
I guess I'll do that.
I'll do that.
And, Matsumoto Team...
Look!
The king's R3, D2.
Oh, I got it! I got it!
What? Is it a T-ball?
Can you see the Matsumoto team? This is the correct answer.
They're fighting, aren't they?
Yes.
Oh, pro-wrestling?
Pro-wrestling?
They're going for a good fight! They're going for a good fight, Captain!
What's that?
They're going for a good fight for pro-wrestling?
Yes!
They're going for a good fight!
They're going for a good fight, Captain!
What's that?
They're going for a good fight!
Oh!
Sorry.
What are you doing?
What? I don't get it!
That was a shame.
The correct answer was Giant Baba.
I did it like this.
What are you laughing at?
Let's go to the Matsumoto team.
Do you understand?
Yes, I do.
Yes, it looks like it's okay.
What's that?
I don't know.
What?
Oh, I got it.
Yes, Mr. Yamamoto.
Madonna.
That's wonderful!
Thank you.
Here it is.
Ready, start!
It's quite detailed.
Wow!
Oh!
The Olympics.
What's that?
You can say whatever you want.
I don't want to see it.
It looks like my face.
You're angry.
Okay.
Here you go.
Synchro.
That's correct.
The correct answer was 100 points.
The correct answer was synchro dance.
Now, the Matsumoto team.
Here is the question.
What's that?
Here it is.
Oh!
Demon.
That's correct.
That's strange.
There is no such thing.
Please look at the front.
What do you say when you see a demon?
I love you.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Please look at the front.
I wonder if there is something I can think of.
Here it is.
I don't know the name of the machine.
It's a good thing.
What do you say?
Z-Ghost?
Correct.
Wonderful.
That's correct.
Thank you.
Now, the captain.
Here you go.
Here it is.
Ready, start!
That's easy.
I have muscle pain.
Ah!
I don't know the name of the machine.
It's a devil.
That's correct.
I don't know the name of the machine.
Now, the captain.
Here you go.
Yes.
That's correct.
Ready, start!
I don't know the name of the machine.
I have muscle pain.
That's easy.
That's correct.
I don't know the name of the machine.
Yes.
Takasaki Yamanosawa.
That's not it.
It's like this.
It's Ryutaro.
Ryutaro?
That's right.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
Hello, hello, hello.
Well, you're dressed roughly again today.
The set has changed from today.
Oh, it's beautiful.
I don't know if it's good or bad.
The staff was complimenting each other.
Oh, it's beautiful.
Well, if it's beautiful, it's not a good thing.
Now, when I look at it, it's beautiful, it's beautiful.
Do you have any money left?
I'm told that I don't have any money left.
You've been doing this program since late at night, haven't you?
Yes.
At night, there was really no money.
That's right.
Seriously.
There was really no money.
Is there any money now?
Apparently there's no money at all.
Really?
Yes.
There's no way you're going to do anything.
You've read that old man and old woman today, haven't you?
I don't know anything about that kind of character.
For example, if you say TDS's bento, it's pretty amazing.
Oh.
It's all green.
There's a lot of side dishes.
There's a lot of shrimp.
It looks like a rice ball here.
It's a rice ball.
It's me.
Are you on a trip again?
I'm not on a trip.
Don't break the rice ball.
TDS is really persistent, but there's no shrimp.
The shrimp is like this.
It's like this.
But the shrimp isn't bad either.
What?
There's something under it.
It's like a cream croquette.
It's like this.
But it's bad.
TDS's bento is pretty good.
Yesterday, there was sukiyaki.
Sukiyaki.
In the morning.
Sukiyaki in the morning.
There's a chawanmushi.
There's a sukiyaki next to it.
It's a raw egg.
That's right.
It's a pooh.
There's about six onigiri in it.
It's in there.
What's that long brown thing?
It's like Tsukudani.
What do you think?
Did I go overboard?
Why onigiri?
Well, it's like that.
I don't know why I'm like this tonight.
There are a lot of things about movement, like politics.
I'll tell you everything.
What's going on with politics?
What's going on?
What do you mean by politics?
You used to say something about PKO.
What are you talking about now?
What kind of movement are you doing?
Now it's PKO.
Not yet?
I've been listening to that all the time.
I don't want to be considered smart on TV.
To tell you the truth, I'm a pretty knowledgeable person.
For example, if you're familiar with politics, you're smart.
If you're familiar with anime, you're an idiot.
It's not like that at all.
It's the same.
I don't think you're an idiot.
If you're familiar with politics, you don't even know the name of Peter's mother.
I don't know.
You knew that.
That's right.
I think you're smart because you know everything.
What's your field?
What's my field?
I'm being asked.
I don't know.
I don't know if this field is strong.
It's just a little bit.
What?
Golf?
I like golf, but that's all.
That's why I told you to say the name of a professional golfer to ten people.
That's it.
I hate golf, but I can say it.
Then say it.
Say it.
I can say it.
Ozaki Naomichi.
There's something.
Ozaki has three brothers.
So say it.
Don't be a coward. There are three brothers. Don't be a coward. There are three brothers.
Ozaki, Ozaki, Ozaki.
If you can't say it, you can say two more.
All of them are Ozaki.
I don't know what Ozaki is.
That's enough.
Wait a minute.
I thought it was thirteen people.
That's enough.
You can't count Ozaki.
I don't care if Ozaki is gone.
That's all.
I'll just say it.
Toua-gyoku.
I really like Toua-gyoku.
And then, monkey.
I'm a manga.
I'm a pro golfer.
That professional golfer monkey comes out.
What's his professional?
I'm a professional.
The sun is deep.
I'll be in the sky tomorrow.
I'm a little fat.
Reiko.
I'm a professional golfer Reiko.
I'm a professional golfer.
Why?
Why is it a manga?
I know a lot like this.
But if you say that, there are a lot of things that you can't say.
That's right.
So, when I'm on a quiz show, I always do a joke, but when I say the truth, it's amazing.
While I was shooting the comedy, I was doing a 6th grade drift.
I did it.
I got 80 points for a 6th grade drift in the national language.
I got 80 points for a 6th grade drift in the national language, so I can do a quiz.
You can't do a drift in elementary school, can you?
If you can do it, show me the answer of your kanji.
I'll leave it all.
What do you mean?
I'm already answering.
Who are you?
I'm the manager of Nishimoto Cooperative.
This is an announcement...
What club is it?
You tell me!
Isn't it an announcement?
It's a batman club run by young people in Nishimoto Co.
So who are you?
Who are you?
I'm Nishibori from Yoshimoto Kogyo
I'm his manager
How much do you weigh now?
It doesn't matter
If you're going to make an announcement, let go of your weight
I'm not going to let go of my weight
This is the Asahi Super Dry Hall
My body is so small
Team Zero is going to be on the stage
This is the guest, Jimmy Onishi, Shinodaki Michi
It's funny
The audience is going to love it
It's a twin
If it was just one person, it would be a pig
It's a twin, so it's this
If it was just one person, it would be amazing
Thank you
The other day, I got a signature from Hikaru Ippei
When I went home and looked at it, it didn't say Hikaru Ippei
Is the signature written properly?
Please write it
I'll think about the signature
Where are you going to write it?
It's down there
Really?
I prepared it
I'll tell you to give me a signature
But are you happy to have that?
I want to get a signature, but I can't
No one has ever had it
I can't do anything
What is this?
You can use your signature
I'm going to use my whole brain
I'm going to use my brain
I'm going to write it and put it on the pad
I can't laugh
I'm not going to do that
When should I write it?
I think it's better to write it after showing it
I wanted to write it now
I'm going to write it
My signature is like this
Write it
I'm going to write it
It's new
What is your signature?
My signature is like this
What is this?
Do you understand?
Please explain
My signature is like this
Why?
It's like this
Where should I write it?
On the back
Like this
I'm going to write it like this
This is a hammer
Why?
It's like this
This is a hammer
Even if you tell me to do it
It's a hammer
You guys
I don't know
It's a hammer
What?
It's like this
It's a hammer
I'm writing the year
What is this?
It's a hammer
I can't do it at all
In my case
It's perfect
This is Matsumoto's signature
For example, I think this is the easiest way to understand
When you do this
I don't like it
This is Matsumoto's year
This is my signature
Look
Where are you writing the year?
I can understand this
You can understand this
What is this?
It's a
It's a year
What is this?
It's a hammer
This is gone
What?
What is this?
When I wrote the year
I got an OK sign
You can't do it
I wrote everything
I can't do it
Write everything
Matsumoto's year
I can understand
What is this?
Where is the hammer?
The hammer is here
It's here
Even if I say this
I think I got an OK
You got an OK
I got an OK
I wrote everything
Thank you for watching