Hamada Masatoshi, 33 years old.
The man who has never been injured before is...
fractured.
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Arahen, we will continue with the project of emergency fractures.
Let's take a look at the audience of Hamada-chan.
Today, Hamada...
fractured his arm.
I think he didn't actually do it.
No, I didn't.
He did it because he wanted to get everyone's attention.
Ah, because he was lonely.
That's not true.
No, I didn't.
He was really fractured.
That's a big deal.
In downtown, one of the four legs is broken.
That's right.
One of the legs is gone.
If one of the legs was missing, he wouldn't be able to eat.
It's all broken.
For now, let's call him over.
Let's call him over.
The main character is Hamada-san.
Please come in.
Ah, it's good, it's good.
Ah, it's good.
Thank you.
It's good to be in a place like this.
Yes.
Well, that's how it is.
I don't know what the purpose of this trip is.
I'm a little annoyed.
What is it?
I don't know how many talents are in Japan right now.
There are a lot.
I don't know who is going to come to see me.
You're not coming?
I'm not coming.
You're not coming alone?
Look at these things.
Ah, it's the past.
Ah, with magic.
Look at this pure white dress.
I loosened it once.
I rewound it.
In the past.
At that time, I was wearing it.
Kimura Takuya was wearing it.
It's true, it's true.
You want to say something like that, right?
That's a lie.
It's a lie.
It's true, it's true.
It seems that my son is also playing.
My father.
This program is provided by the sponsor you are looking at.
This concept is to give a lucky bag prepared by the entertainer here.
It means that you will be given a lucky money for sure.
However, many entertainers are gathered at Ikuta Studio.
Ah, at Ikuta Studio.
I didn't think that they would come like this.
Today, Hamada-san, look at this.
There is a magical set, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
Today, we are shooting a magical set.
I see.
That's why there are various things.
Ah, it's Hideki-san.
Hideki-san.
What's wrong?
Ah, it's already...
Ah, something terrible has happened.
I fractured my bone.
Didn't you pierce it?
No, I didn't pierce it.
You didn't?
Didn't you know that?
I didn't know.
Ah, this is already bad.
Right?
Ah, you came to see me?
Yes, I came to see you.
Ah, I see, I see.
Good luck.
If you look at this, you will understand.
Because there is no one coming.
Since you came, you should write a sign.
Ah, that's right.
Please write here.
Good luck.
There are various things.
It doesn't matter.
Good luck.
It's the first time.
Ah, it's good.
Yes.
Ah, thank you very much.
It's wonderful.
I should write a sign.
No, it's good.
It's good.
It's hard to get something like this.
And, well...
There are various things.
When you get sick, it will take a long time.
It's a waste of money.
That's right.
Well, thank you for your hard work.
Well, I have prepared some things.
Ah, I see.
What is that?
I have prepared some things.
Since Hamada is like this, we have nothing to do with each other.
No.
Hideyoshi-san also has some relationship.
Well...
There is also a place that looks like a foreign car.
What?
It's a good memory.
But, it's scary.
I have been to a bad place.
This silhouette is good.
It's amazing.
What?
It hurts.
What is it?
Hong Kong.
It's moving.
Thank you.
Brother.
What is it?
I have received something.
Really?
Wait a minute.
Can I see it now?
Let's see it.
There is nothing to say.
It hurts, right?
It hurts.
You came all the way here.
Yes.
What is it?
I did it.
Moreover, Hideki is a close-up.
It's amazing.
Really?
It's good.
It's really cool.
Please take a commemorative photo with Hideki-san.
What are you talking about?
It's the first time in this world.
I'm so happy.
Let's go.
Cheese.
He received 50,000 yen from the downtown.
Good morning.
Shingo-chan is here.
Shingo-chan.
What happened?
I saw it in the newspaper.
Why didn't you come?
Where did you go?
I came to see you.
Shingo-chan signs while receiving unreasonable comments.
You are a great person.
It hurts, right?
It hurts.
Right?
Hang in there.
Don't do that.
Right?
It's terrible.
There is no end to it.
Don't do that from the stairs.
What is it?
It's in the middle of Kagai-sha.
In the middle of Kagai-sha.
I'll wrap it up.
Shingo-chan was taken by surprise.
Max is here.
Max.
Is he alone?
No.
I didn't know it would be like this.
This is a big deal.
Shingo-chan, write something here.
Can I write?
Yes.
Shingo-chan was caught after taking a dump.
It's not a dump.
What were you doing?
I was peeing.
Really?
Were you hiding and peeing?
Max is here.
This is an unexpected development.
I received a present from Iegaki Takahashi.
That's right.
It's a miracle.
What about Max?
Max is amazing now.
That's amazing.
Hair.
No.
I don't need that.
Everyone, write something.
A lot of people are here.
Really?
Yes.
I was worried.
Kato is here.
Everyone.
Of course.
Everyone, write something.
I'm sorry.
I've been watching you guys for a long time.
You've grown up.
Write something.
I'm just a socialite.
The four teams were not able to get any money.
Bando.
It's been a long time since I've seen Bando Eiji.
Good morning.
I've been waiting for you.
Really?
That's right.
Bando Eiji.
This is the staff of Magical.
Happy birthday.
Is it your 30th birthday?
Yes.
That's good.
It's just in time.
That's right.
Masao.
Yes.
Please give me a bag.
It's a big deal.
It's a gift.
Yes.
Then give it to me.
This is what I'm talking about.
Good.
They got 10,000 yen.
There are a total of seven stars in Ikuta Studio.
As a result of the situation, Downtown went to the next destination, Kinuta Studio.
The goal is 2,300,000 yen.
What?
2,300,000 yen.
2,300,000 yen is not enough.
Who will give me that?
I have to buy a bus with a lift.
I'm not that kind of guy.
We've arrived.
The more I thought about Ikuta, the worse the entrance was.
Are you a gold digger?
There are some other talents here.
There are.
Let's wait here.
Hello.
I'll take you home.
That's right.
I'll go to the place where I can relax on my way back.
Thank you.
Will Tamura Masakazu and other big talents get two gold diggers?
Here he comes.
Who?
Rasane.
Thank you.
Hello.
It's been a long time.
That's right.
Please sit down.
What?
I don't know.
This is what happened.
I see.
I didn't come to see you.
What?
We came to see you.
We have this.
I'll write to you.
I'll write to Mr. Ishida.
I'll write to Mr. Ban.
This is a max.
This is a big blue.
That's right.
Can I write here?
No, you can't.
That's not good.
I'll write to Mr. Takagi.
Can I write to you?
No, you can't.
It's hard.
Mr. Takagi and Kabukai.
Mr. Takagi wanted to write to you.
He was so desperate.
I won't miss you.
Where did you get the treatment?
This is what happened.
It doesn't have anything to do with you, does it?
Wait a minute.
What do you mean?
But you're not the victim, right?
I'm not the victim, but...
If you think about it that way, you're the victim of a distant place.
Why do you say that?
I've prepared something like that.
Of course, there's nothing inside.
It's a light-weighted power supply that uses electric waves.
It's not that.
Hey, Rasaka-san.
Huh?
That's...
It's not that.
Why are you making such a lame joke?
It's not like I'm making a joke.
Wait a minute. What's that?
I'll take a picture of you.
I'll use it when I need it.
That's bad.
What are you talking about?
This is going to be written all the time.
This is the only thing that's not over.
Four or five times a year.
What kind of life is this?
Ishii-san seems to be in a lot of pain this year.
Because of the lack of power, he decided to make a sudden phone call.
Hello?
Yes, hello.
I'm always in your care. I'm Matsumoto from downtown.
Good morning.
Are you Shohei-san?
Glasses!
Good morning.
I'm Mahito.
I'm with my partner.
Yes, yes.
It's like I want to see you.
It's like, don't you miss me?
What are you doing?
I'm practicing golf right now.
Are you playing golf?
I'll be right back.
Yes, yes.
Hello?
Yes, hello.
Are you in Uchipanashi?
Yes, I'm in Uchipanashi.
Is that so?
Yes.
I want to see your face, so can I go?
Ayaki-kun is playing.
Please practice.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Yes, yes.
I can't hear you anymore.
Didn't you feel suspicious?
Yes, I did.
Matsumoto-san.
Yes.
Nia is over there.
Yes, she is.
She's completely aware of the camera.
She's looking at us.
That's terrible.
Ah, Nia.
She's coming to my private room.
Why are you wearing black glasses at a time like this?
No, no, no.
What do you call it?
Yellow glasses.
Yes.
Is that something you wear at work?
When I was in the army, I wore yellow glasses.
Ah, yes, yes.
When I wore black glasses, I wore Kishi Hiroshi.
That's not it.
It's Hoshi Hiroshi.
I finally met you.
No, no, no.
There's nothing wrong with that.
It's a big deal.
Do you know what it is?
Ah, what is this?
What is this?
It must have hurt.
I've heard a lot about it.
You're going to do something like that.
I didn't do anything.
I couldn't sleep last night because I was hungry.
That's a big deal.
You're not responsible at all.
Well, that's true.
Well, this kind of thing.
Well, I don't know if I should put it in.
He won't do it, so I'm tired of it.
I'm tired of it.
Normally, well, what do you say?
I'm not going to bring this kind of thing.
And, um, what do you say?
I think it's better to think about it.
That's what the staff said.
We talked to each other.
Oh, that's right.
No, I don't want to talk about you anymore.
I'm sorry to cut it off.
It's funny.
Are you going to look at the rest of it?
Of course.
I know how to do it.
You know how to do it.
How do you do that on the show?
You're going to tear it up.
Why are you tearing it up?
Why are you doing this?
You're going to tear it up.
It's a place where you can edit.
Thank you very much.
Please be careful.
I'm sorry.
Let's take a look at it.
Are you going to do it all of a sudden?
We're having a hard time wrapping this up without making a fool of ourselves.
I think it would have been better to be a fool, right now.
No, no, no.
It's okay to be a fool.
I don't think it's okay to be a fool.
It's not like that.
It's not serious, is it?
You don't have to be a fool.
It's not a fool.
I think we should have been a fool.
Don't be silly.
You look like an old lady.
It's better now than being silly.
Why?
If there is a silly thing that goes beyond now, it's fine.
The director of the second film, Shohei, gave him 30,000 yen.
And the two of them decided to aim for something big at the end.
I'm with Hamada right now.
What about Hamada?
Hamada is very worried.
What?
He wants to meet Nagao.
Let's talk to him.
Hello?
Good evening.
Akira?
Where are you?
Can I talk to you?
I'm in Ginza right now.
What?
I'm in Ginza.
Are you going to Ginza?
I'm going to Ginza's bar.
Ginza's bar?
I'm going there.
What?
Yes.
I'm going there.
What?
I think that the director of the film, Tatekawa, and the director of the film, Katsura, might come.
I don't know if the director of the film will come.
Akira, wait a minute.
Do you want to talk to the director of the film, Tatekawa?
No.
What else?
In the film, Kamioka.
Kamioka.
He's a great actor.
I just talked to the director of the film, Kiyaru.
I don't know who he is.
I understand.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
I'm leaving.
Please understand that the director of the film is not a person who can be trusted.
This is a difficult place.
I'm going there.
You can't go there.
Is there a guy, a woman, or a Kamioka in Ginza at night?
The director of the film, Kiyaru, has no idea.
Mr. Kazunosu.
Yes, yes.
Could you please tell me where you're from?
Well, I'm not sure where I'm from.
I don't really know where I'm from.
Nia.
Go ahead.
Yes.
Were you there?
Yes, I was.
Who was there?
Mr. Nagao was there alone.
He was sitting in the back of my seat.
Alone?
Yes, he was.
He was sitting in the back of my seat.
Oh, I see.
Let's go now and go home quickly.
Yes.
Oh, there he is.
How are you?
Oh, hello, hello.
Oh, hello.
Good morning.
I'm glad Akira was alone.
What should I do if there's a member I was talking about earlier?
I'm glad you came today.
Oh, really?
You've been drinking a lot, haven't you?
Yes, I've been drinking a lot.
Oh, these two don't drink.
I don't drink.
If I could drink...
Aren't you going somewhere after this?
No, I'm not going.
You're not going?
No.
Why are you looking at me with such scary eyes?
Is that so?
I heard you were grumbling.
You can't drink, can you?
I can't drink.
But you're really okay, aren't you?
I'm okay.
Well, Mr. Taisa...
You knew, didn't you?
Mr. Nagao, right?
I knew.
Hama-chan asks for a chance to get a signature while taking a break.
For the rest of my life...
the pain...
will remain.
Hey, you!
In a sense, this is...
reverse love.
For the rest of my life, the pain will remain.
Thank you.
You should feel it as pain.
I see.
You've been working hard.
You've always been working hard.
That's right.
You've grown up, haven't you?
Thank you.
Well, today...
I'm sorry to bother you.
No, no.
Akira came here because he can't drink.
That's right.
If you knew, you would have come.
I wonder why he can't drink.
I won't go.
Why not?
I can't drink at all.
I see.
Why is that?
If I go, I'll die.
Really?
Yes.
Akira.
Yes?
I have a favor to ask you.
What is it?
Is that so?
Well, well.
It's about the sword.
Oh!
As expected.
Of course.
That's right.
I was going to bring this.
Oh, that's great.
When I met you the other day,
I was going to give you this.
But...
You were there.
So what if I was there?
You were next to me.
You were always looking at me.
You didn't know that I was there.
Wait a minute.
You were looking at me.
I was looking at you.
You were always looking at me.
Why did you look at me?
It's not something you can show in front of people.
That's right.
Go over there.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry, Naha-chan.
All the movements around here are the same, right?
It's the same for everyone.
It's not something you can do in front of people.
For him,
I don't want him to see my wallet.
Well, then.
It's been a long time.
You still want to see it?
Yes.
It's like this, right?
Thank you very much.
What is it?
You don't like it?
Thank you very much.
I like this.
I'm a painter.
Really?
Really.
I'm a painter.
This is amazing.
Right?
I'm a painter.
Well,
I'm a little more.
What?
I'm a pretty good painter, too.
Well, then.
What is it?
Why are you laughing?
Are you lonely?
Everyone will come one day.
That's right.
That's why I want you to buy it soon.
I'll send it to you.
No, it's okay.
It's okay.
I'll give you a piggyback ride.
All right.
I'm sorry.
It's light.
Thank you very much.
I want you to give me a piggyback ride.
That's funny.
Well, really.
Everyone is watching.
Isn't this a great picture?
It was a great picture.
Did you think about running for president?
I didn't think about it.
Did you aim for a promotion?
NAKO gave me a piggyback ride.
He gave me three pictures.
There are 10 victims of the opposite side.
Hama is also very happy.
I'll tell you.
If there are other people, I won't give you a piggyback ride.
It hurts.
We are very painful.
Why are you so painful?
We can't give you a piggyback ride.
I'm really sorry.
We are painful.
Thank you very much.