High Tension The Best Ten!
This week has started again.
High Tension The Best Ten.
Good evening.
This week, what kind of people are coming to the show?
To be honest, most of them are under 100 yen.
It's the best ten.
The best ten?
All of them are like gamers.
Let's get started.
Yes.
The 10th place of this week is...
52 points.
The song of the sheep world.
Kogoriko, Tanaga Naoki.
Good evening.
This is the best ten.
By the way, no one laughed when I put on this costume.
First of all, it's a slip.
It's a slip.
Don't say anything.
I know.
Then, let's go to the third place.
The 10th place of this week is Kogoriko, Tanaga Naoki.
The song of the sheep world.
Wait, sheep.
Listen to me, sheep.
Don't go that way.
Go that way.
Hey, Kogoriko.
Wait, sheep.
Don't go that way.
This and that.
Thank you very much.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
The 9th place of this week is...
85 points.
The song of the sheep world.
Degawa Tetsuro.
Good evening.
When we were divided into Hamada team and Matsumoto team, you did a terrible thing.
No, Matsumoto-san.
That's not true.
After that, I bled.
I got an explosion at Happening.
That's right.
I had a heart attack.
I saw the airing, but it was about 1 in 20.
Today, I did my best.
Then, the 3rd place, please.
Let's go.
The 9th place of this week is Degawa Tetsuro's high tension Michael Jackson.
Michael Jackson.
Thank you very much.
Degawa-san, please take a seat.
Degawa-san, if you can sit down, please sit down.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
I'll buy everything from now on.
What are you saying?
It's all right.
The 8th place of this week is...
Hotohara Toru, who wants to get rid of 151-year-old delusions.
Thank you very much.
Hotohara-san is the 8th place.
Thank you very much for coming back.
That's right.
This time, Hotohara-san is addicted to wine.
Is it wine?
I've prepared 3 kinds of wine for you today.
I'd like to know how this wine tastes.
This is good.
Is that so?
This is sold in Otaku.
This is a wine from 1998.
This is a wine with a monkey on it.
If you don't have it, don't have it.
I have a lot.
Are you all right?
Please tell me how it tastes.
This is the taste I wanted.
Is that so?
Is that all?
This is called Den Mille Anjou.
Den Mille Anjou?
Where is this from?
This is from France.
This is a wine that was made by following the French wine line.
This is a good wine.
I didn't drink it.
I know.
I just saw it.
I see.
Standby, please.
Mr. Yamaoka.
Yes.
You don't answer my questions.
Let's get started.
The 8th place this week is Hotohara-san who wants to get rid of the rain.
He is in a hurry because he is young.
He will Sophie.
He can't get rid of rain.
Strongly recommended.
Weak rain.
BAM! BAM! BAM!
Just One Kill!
WINS!
We have 19 and 8 here.
They're not in the top 10 yet.
But they'll be in the rankings soon.
Let's look forward to it.
Let's introduce two young comedians.
The first one ranked 17th this week.
It's Gori Ken.
Here he is.
Gori Ken
Hello.
This is my first time meeting you.
Me too.
I don't have any data.
Do you have any close comedians?
Degawa-san is my older brother.
My older brother passed away.
I hope you'll do your best.
I'll do my best.
I'd like to introduce myself.
Do it.
I'd like to introduce myself now.
Introduce yourself.
I see.
Please stand by.
I don't know what kind of person he is.
I don't know.
Let's take a look.
17th this week.
Gori Ken.
It's Gori Ken.
It's a little funny.
I don't like it.
The second one ranked 13th this week.
It's Mori Sanchu.
Here he is.
Mori Sanchu
This is dirty.
Are you Yoshimoto?
Yes.
What's your grade?
How old are you?
I'm 20 years old.
I'm 21 years old.
I don't know your age.
You're angry, aren't you?
This is funny.
She's definitely a Kirie.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I don't have a boyfriend.
How about you?
I'm a girl.
I have a boyfriend.
You're lying.
Are you serious?
What does your boyfriend do?
I go to a vocational school.
How did you know each other?
We're married.
Why do you have this hairstyle?
It's strange.
It's private.
What do you mean by private?
Can I say it?
Why do you have this hairstyle?
It's private.
Do you like it?
Stand by, please.
This is scary.
You're the one who lies the most.
Look at this.
This week's 13th place is Miyuki Oshima.
She changed into Yosoeki's shoes.
The first place is Miyuki Oshima.
The second place is Miyuki Oshima.
This is the worst.
What?
My leg...
This is the worst.
Thank you very much.
Let's go back to the first place.
This week's 7th place is...
189 points high tension student, Fukawa Ryo.
Fukawa-san.
Thank you very much.
Are you okay today?
I'm okay.
Last time you got a lot of punches.
I got a lot of punches.
Fukawa-san got a lot of punches today.
There's a phone call for Fukawa-san.
Really?
I'm glad to hear that.
Hello.
Ryo-chan.
Ryo-chan?
It's not Ryo-chan.
It's not Ryo-chan?
Who is it?
Mom, nice to meet you.
Hello, nice to meet you.
It's Dantan.
Ryo is taking care of me.
What are you talking about?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You don't have to say it.
Your son is not shining right now.
No, I don't know.
I don't know.
Please take care of him for a long time.
For a long time?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
This week's student is Fukawa Ryo.
Please go to your seat.
Are you okay?
I can't forgive you even if you're a downtown person.
No, no, no.
You should have cut it in reverse.
I thought I had saved you.
Let's go back to the 6th place this week.
277 points.
The man with the most beans.
Dachio Club, Ryuhei Ueshiba.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Ueshiba has no stars today because of his work.
The 5th place this week is...
298 points.
Please give me love.
I want to erase the rain.
Miyasako Hiroyuki.
Thank you very much.
This week is the 5th place.
It's going up.
Your partner has become like that.
I'm not sorry.
He's not a bad guy.
To be honest, I've only received 3 points so far.
Please go to the 3rd place.
I'll go.
The 5th place this week is Miyasako Hiroyuki.
Please give me love.
Nakamura Akira.
Yesterday, I looked at you very hard.
If you look back, your ass will be down.
You can not do this.
your ass will be down.
If your ass is not in good condition, you can not do this.
Weak, Weak, You can not do that.
Weak, Weak,
Unigachan, when I look at you, I can't help but salivate!
Unigachan, Unigachan, you're not going to die! You're not going to die! You're not going to die!
Everyone who moves hates you!
That's a lie!
Thank you very much.
Next week's 4th place is...
360 points, Kouda Shin from Izukoe!
Kouda Shin from Izukoe
Kouda-san.
It's not about Izukoe, it's about where you've come from.
That's what I want to say.
Please stand by.
This week's 4th place, Kouda Shin from Izukoe!
Kouda Shin from Izukoe
See you next week.
Sit down.
Kouda-san, isn't this just a campaign?
This week's SPOTLIGHT!
This week's SPOTLIGHT is Mr. Shigenori Yamashita.
Hello, nice to meet you.
Mr. Yamashita, this is SPOTLIGHT.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Yamashita, this beautiful flower has been selected as one of the 100 best flowers in Japan.
It's already been selected?
Yes.
It's been selected as one of the 100 best flowers in Japan.
Really?
Here's the answer.
Although it's a big flower, the hole is too small.
But it's not a bad flower.
That's good.
However, this type of flower is slow to bloom.
As a comedian, the flower blooms at the age of 60.
It's slow.
Please stand by.
This week's SPOTLIGHT is Mr. Shigenori Yamashita.
Yamashita.
Yamashita para para.
Yamashita para para pyon.
Yamashita.
Yamashita pa pa.
Yes, pyon pyon pyon pyon pyon pyon pyon pyon.
The 3rd place this week is...
454 points.
Hoi!
Banzai Cholesterol edition.
Let's end the show here.
This is what I expected.
You never got 1st place?
I got 1st place in the past, but this Banzai Cholesterol edition is my first time.
I got 3rd place.
I see.
You might get 1st place next year.
That's right.
I definitely want to get 1st place.
However, when it comes to this...
Why do you say it's too much?
There's room for improvement.
That's not really...
Stop it.
Please stand by.
Are you ready?
Why are you laughing while you're getting ready?
The 3rd place this week is...
Kokoriko Endo Shouzo.
Hoi!
Banzai Cholesterol edition.
It didn't matter.
C O L E.
This. C O L E.
This.
I love you.
That's why this is here.
Let's start.
It hasn't started yet.
Everyone, let's do our favorite Hohohoi.
Now, hold this with both hands.
Open your legs.
Let's go.
Hohohoi.
Breathe in.
I love you.
Thank you very much.
This week's 2nd place is...
483.1 song racing part 2.
Dondogodon Yamaguchi Tomomitsu.
Thank you.
Please.
It came to 2nd place.
Yes, 2nd place.
Yes.
I was very busy.
I was shooting a video of the next studio.
Yes.
It means AV.
Please.
Let's go.
This week's 2nd place.
Dondogodon Yamaguchi Tomomitsu's song racing part 2.
Hickson.
Hickson hickson.
I see.
As expected.
As expected of the 2nd place.
Now that I think about it, Fukawa must be really angry.
What kind of face is that?
Now, everyone.
The man who stands at the top of everyone this week.
Let's go.
This week's 1st place is...
526 points. In English, it's mermaid.
Yamasaki Hosei.
Stop it.
Hello, Yamasaki-san.
Yes.
I'm 1st place.
I'm really happy.
I've always been in the spotlight.
That's right.
This is the first time I've been in the spotlight.
I see.
I'm 1st place.
I'm really happy.
The character hasn't been decided yet.
Yamasaki-san, since you're 1st place.
I've prepared socks for you.
Here you go.
This is an interesting movie.
Can you see it?
I got it.
Congratulations.
Yamasaki Hosei is 1st place.
Good luck.
It took a while to get 3 points.
That's amazing.
This week's 1st place is...
Yamasaki Hosei.
In English, it's mermaid.
Yes, yes.
That was dangerous.
I did it.
That's terrible.
Am I 1st place?
Here we go.
Pose!