Next time on Gaki no Tsukai,
Tamage!
Chiki-chiki rugby match!
Batsuzen Menomichi!
Ah, the young men have gathered.
I said young men, but look at this.
It's full of garbage.
Can you stand up for a moment?
You are Peanuts-kun.
Let's play rugby.
Let's do it.
The members are like this.
After deciding the punishment game.
Ah, everyone is going to be trained?
It's not a selection, it's a draft.
I understand.
First of all, you will become a popular person in the aquarium.
Everyone, if you are watching the show, please gather around.
And you will do a show here.
That's a great person.
You have to do a show on this side of the glass bar.
That's the punishment.
What does it mean to spray water with a scrub?
Why are you throwing away rugby scrubs?
What are you talking about?
You are a no-use series.
Next, Garison-kun and Booby-chan are American kids.
What is this?
Tsukasa-chan is aiming for Hayami.
He is aiming for it.
He is really a no-use series.
If you use it.
Come on.
It's a no-use series.
Next, punch-bar with Daibutsumaide Zenza.
This may be interesting.
It's a no-use series.
If you use it.
This is a no-use series.
Explain it.
In this no-use series.
You can fly.
Well, I don't know.
Let's go with the elimination method.
I don't like this one.
It's not expensive.
Let's leave this one, too.
The American Kid.
I think we can leave this one.
For Suga-chan, too.
I don't like it.
This one or this one.
We can't leave this one.
That's right.
We might lose because of these guys.
You and I might do our best.
That's where it comes out.
This one.
This time, this punishment game is a double structure.
I see.
This is the captain.
You're the captain.
I'll tell you.
You can't have a perm with long hair.
What?
After you buy it?
After you buy it.
What are you talking about?
I'll make it 2 cm long.
And then I'll curl it.
You can't have a perm with weak hair.
That's why it's funny.
You got it, right?
You guys are trying to make the show more exciting.
Now we're going to divide into teams.
But we don't know what they're capable of.
So today, we have three teachers.
What do you do first?
I tackle.
You tackle, right?
Excuse me.
This camera guy is amazing.
He's my manager.
He's a camera guy.
You're holding him.
I'm going to take it.
No.
You're going to do it?
Yes.
You should have done it from the start.
I did it when I saw it.
It's totally different.
Kama-chan.
Now, let's go into the trout.
Yes.
Are you ready?
By the way, who wants to be on my team?
What?
Are you serious?
Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Yes.
You go first.
Is it okay?
Yes, I won.
If you do it from the start, it should be Okamoto.
I see.
Okamoto-kun.
I'll go first with my body.
Yes, Noriyasu.
I did it.
Takasu.
I got it.
You guys really don't want to be on my team.
Producer Sugai.
I got it.
Takasu.
I did it.
I got it.
You.
Hey.
Why are you looking at me with sad eyes?
Actually, I feel the same way as Akko.
Seriously.
I can't even speak.
Let me sleep.
Really?
Yamazaki and I are two girls.
No, the four of you are a couple.
That's right.
Shinohara-san.
Yamazaki.
Yamazaki wants to come here.
Yamazaki has been...
Hamada-san and I are different.
We are different.
What should I do? It's difficult.
What should I do?
I've been working out for 44 years.
Shinohara-san.
Why don't you wrap it up and go home?
You even have a tackle.
Ame-chan is naive.
I'm naive.
Ladies and gentlemen.
She's here today.
She's calling me Tama-chan.
She's so excited that she's calling me Tama-chan.
What's that?
Hama-chan is Tama-chan.
Hama-chan is in a class higher than Hama-chan.
Hama-chan is higher than Hama-chan.
She's becoming Tama-chan.
You're talking too much.
It's work.
I don't like it.
You're like a showman every day.
You're coming out.
It's work.
I don't like it because I don't have any makeup on.
I don't like it because my face is so pale.
Sometimes it hurts.
I'll hit you.
Even if you hit me, I can't change my opinion.
You're talking about your face in front of makeup.
Is it broken?
That's it.
I don't know.
What's the matter?
You shouldn't do this kind of work for a long time.
You should wear makeup every day for 10 or 20 years.
What?
You'll become a makeup artist.
That's a big deal.
I think so.
Let's stop it.
What?
I don't care.
Let's stop it.
It will continue tomorrow and the day after tomorrow.
That's right.
I want to go out to play.
What?
Just the two of us?
Really?
I don't like it.
Why do you go on a private trip?
I don't like people who watch TV.
I hate them.
I don't like them.
What?
Do you hate me?
I don't like it.
It's disgusting.
Don't say it's disgusting.
No, no.
I don't like it.
If you walk around like this,
there's no one who looks like Sakura.
It's disgusting.
Is it weird?
It's weird.
I feel like this.
You're the same.
I understand.
Why are you doing this?
I'm not doing anything bad.
Let's go somewhere.
What?
Just the two of us.
Why?
Why can't we go together?
What if it's just the two of us?
That would be dangerous.
It's not like that.
It's disgusting.
Is it?
Is it disgusting?
Isn't it disgusting?
If you take a private room on the Shinkansen,
people won't know.
I don't want to.
Why don't you go to a private room?
Why?
What are you talking about?
Don't say that.
We've been friends since elementary school.
What are you talking about?
I want to talk to you.
Right?
I don't want to talk to you anymore.
I want to talk to you here.
Why are you laughing?
How are you doing?
Are you eating?
Shut up!
We can talk about that.
It's fine.
But, you know,
I'm going to work.
I'm going to the same school.
Same school.
We're not going to be there.
We're going to the same school.
I'm going to be there.
I'm always going to pick you up.
I'm always going to be in this state.
You're not going to be there.
I'm not going to be there.
I don't know how to explain it to everyone.
Why can't we be together?
We're a team.
I think everyone is wondering what's going on.
But we're really close.
That's right.
We're really close.
I can't stand it if we're in the same room.
I can't stand it.
So we're together.
If someone is doing a show,
there's D,
D,
and the manager.
I don't bite at that time.
I talk a lot at that time.
Mr. Okamoto, you have a call.
Mr. Okamoto.
I don't know what to do when I'm alone.
Suddenly,
I'm alone on the other side of the road.
I don't know what to do.
That's right.
It's disgusting.
It's like that in the dressing room.
Why can't we be together?
I hope we can be together.
I'd like to go there once.
I have to work.
I'll make some time.
Okinawa is very crowded now.
Why?
I don't know.
It's all on the net.
In Okinawa.
Okinawa is popular.
It doesn't matter.
Okinawa people are black.
They have thick eyebrows.
That's right.
I went to Okinawa.
I want to do it.
I can't do it in Okinawa.
All the young people who have gathered in Okinawa
do it.
Last time,
you didn't write a letter to the governor of Okinawa.
I don't know the people in Okinawa.
I don't know.
I only know people from Osaka or Tokyo.
What?
Do you know a Thai person?
Wait a minute.
You too!
I don't know.
You...
Do something.
What are you talking about?
You're a Thai person.
While you're doing it,
why don't you sing a folk song?
Hamada Masatoshi.
Matsumoto Hitoshi's idol-like plan.
You're talking nonsense.
Let's not talk about making up stories.
What are you talking about?
You...
I'm not talking about making up stories.
I'm not talking about your stupid stories.
That's right.
I'm talking about the real story.
That's the real story.
I'm going to the lawyer's office.
What?
I don't want to see it anymore.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to the lawyer's office.
What?
I don't want to see it anymore.
You...
You're making up stories.
Wake up!
What are you talking about?
Do you do things like this?
I did.
I don't know.
We went together.
We went to a place like Hinadan.
You chose it earlier.
I chose it.
What?
I chose number 29.
That's because I wanted a badge for number 29.
You're funny.
I was just asked to tell me what to do.
What did you do?
What?
You're a strange person.
I don't understand.
What kind of story is this?
Are you suspecting me?
You don't have to say it.
You only know women in Tokyo and Osaka.
You only know women in Tai.
What do you know?
What?
What kind of woman do you know?
I don't know either.
You don't like foreign women?
I can't speak English.
Do you like American women?
I don't like them.
You don't like them?
No.
Do you like French women?
I don't like them at all.
Do you like British women?
I don't like them.
Do you like Thai women?
I don't like them at all.
I have a question.
When you get on and off the train,
do you always have the same attache case?
Why is that?
What is it?
Do you know?
It's not like that.
It's necessary.
It's necessary for all drivers.
You don't need this case, do you?
It's inside.
What's inside?
Something like this.
Something like this?
That's for yourself.
What?
That's for yourself?
Something like this?
Yes.
Something like this.
You don't have that.
Really?
I don't think that attache case is necessary.
Everyone has it.
Even pilots.
A pilot's attache case has no meaning.
It's just an attachment.
Why do you look so angry?
I don't think it's an attache case.
It's an attache case?
How did you see it?
It was just a black board.
With a handle.
I don't know if you see it, but it's a board.
It's a condom.
You're the one who made it with a handle.
You did it with a handle.
You're taking so much time.
It doesn't have to be, either.
I drove it and opened it.
What? I'm going to drive it now.
Do you want me to explain?
Is it that scary?
I'm not saying anything.
It's not. It's not.
That's a
It's not in there.
The one that's in the book.
That's the ticket.
Where did you get it?
Green.
And 5000 yen plus.
There's something like that.
I'm putting all that in there.
Is it like that?
Of course.
It's definitely not.
That's right.
I think it's cool.
A pilot.
A pilot wants to be popular with women.
I think it's like that.
There's no such thing as a young man.
Well, if you're young, you want to do it.
There's something like that.
But it's a movie.
My pen name is Machiko.
There are people who blow their breath on their hands when they work hard.
Why is that?
And when you have something heavy,
There are people who put their fangs on their hands.
Why is that?
It's as easy to understand as it is when you're excited.
I didn't understand it at all.
Are you still saying that?
Are you still saying that you're excited?
I don't want to talk about that anymore.
I'll tell you this.
When you blow your fangs on your hands, you do this.
This is because you're giving them moisture.
What do you call it?
Do you call it being excited?
What?
I'm giving them moisture here.
You're giving them moisture here.
Yes, that's right.
This is because you're excited.
Like this.
Hey!
And when you do that, the moisture goes down here.
You can make a veil of moisture like this.
A water cannon.
Where?
When you blow your fangs like this.
That's not true.
Where's the moisture?
You're not fooling me.
Everyone can do it.
You blow your fangs here, right?
The more you think about it, the better it feels.
That's what you're trying to say.
That's right.
It feels good now.
I just blew my fangs.
It doesn't feel good if you don't blow your fangs.
Try touching this.
Really? That's not true.
That's not true, right?
You blow your fangs here, right?
It feels warm.
That's not true.
You blow your fangs here, right?
Hey!
It hurts more if you blow your fangs here.
So you're saying this one doesn't hurt?
Everything that has love has the nature of blowing your fangs.
Only humans have that.
You're saying something I don't understand.
This is my precious jar.
You blow your fangs to something that's important to you.
Is that so?
Yes.
You blow your fangs to the feelings you have for the other person.
I'm going to kill this guy!
If you get any closer than that,
stop blowing your fangs!
No, no, no.
Are you trying to hit the criminal?
No!
I'm going to kill him, so stop blowing your fangs!
This one?
Yes.
I'm not going to kill him, so stop blowing your fangs.
You're saying this?
I'm saying this.
This is complicated.
Why?
Are you going to blow your fangs?
I'm going to.
It's like a sports club.
It's not just a sports club.
Everyone is like that.
I can't say it.
What can't you say?
No matter what I put on, I can't say it.
Say it.
I'm going to kill you.