Chikitsuki! Dantan Presents!
The 1,000,000 Yen Spring hide-and-seek tournament!
It's the 4th time.
We've never done it before, so let's do it today.
We always do it in the middle.
In the 1st hide-and-seek tournament held in December last year,
a mysterious UFO landed and captured an unknown alien.
The 1,000,000 Yen prize will be given to the winner.
In the 2nd hide-and-seek tournament held in February last year,
a mysterious man was caught in a time-slip.
He was asked to take care of him,
so the 1,000,000 Yen prize will be given to the winner.
3 months later,
in the 3rd hide-and-seek tournament held in February last year,
a cute baby was found to be sleeping.
The kind-hearted Dantan was caught by the baby in the hide-and-seek tournament.
The 1,000,000 Yen prize will be given to the winner.
Who will be the winner of the 1,000,000 Yen prize?
The producer, Mr. Suga, told me to stop raising 1,000,000 Yen.
I'll raise 1,000,000 Yen every time I walk.
That's great!
1,000,000 Yen!
What is it?
Is that a horse?
It's a horse.
This is terrible.
In this peaceful era without war,
that hero came.
What are you talking about?
Napoleon Bonaparte, the emperor of France,
came here in a time-slip.
That's terrible.
That's impossible.
The era is different.
That's terrible.
Let me do it. Hide-and-seek.
It's always raining when he does this.
He's the worst.
Come on.
I wanted to do it.
1,000,000 Yen for walking.
I'm getting 1,000,000 Yen.
Napoleon Bonaparte, the emperor of France,
Napoleon is his full name.
There are children.
What's going on?
Hey!
What?
Napoleon.
It's Napoleon Bonaparte.
Now.
He came like this.
He has the French flag.
Hello?
He has the small flag of France.
He has a dictionary.
It's a small dictionary.
It's impossible for him.
That's right.
Hello?
Let's follow him.
Shall we follow him?
That's terrible.
There's no time to hide.
That's right.
It's all my fault.
It's just an incident.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
I was in a time slip.
I was shocked.
You were shocked?
I see.
But it was amazing.
I looked like a person from the East.
Hello?
He didn't wake up at all.
He woke up.
Let's wake him up with this.
He woke up by mistake.
That's right.
He woke up like this.
He had no choice but to wake up like this.
This is the second one.
He definitely woke up.
He woke up.
This is Napoleon.
Where are we?
We are in Japan, in Heisei.
Is it Japan?
Yes, it's Japan.
This is the place where the hero Napoleon Bonaparte was born in France.
There are no impossible words in this dictionary.
This is a famous one.
I know it.
He is terrible.
There are no impossible words in this dictionary.
It says that there are no impossible words in it.
Is it true?
Let's try it.
This is a famous one.
If there are no impossible words...
There are no impossible words in it.
I don't know if there are no impossible words in it.
Why is he sighing?
What will happen to this if there are no impossible words in it?
It hurts!
What's going on?
Hang in there, Ramuneo!
What is this?
This is a good effort.
As expected of Napoleon.
This is his drink.
It's 40% alcohol.
It's alcohol.
Don't hold back.
It's okay, Mr. Napoleon.
Just drink this for now.
You can't break it with your fingers.
It's wonderful.
Is he really Napoleon?
I don't know.
I'm curious.
The last prince in the history of the world is Natsu.
That's amazing.
Help me.
I'm scared.
That's dangerous.
Watch out!
There are no words of appreciation in the revolution.
What is this?
Just a little more.
A little more.
He jumped.
It's dangerous.
It's like Hyeon-kichi didn't say anything.
What is this?
Here you are.
It's good.
I'll do it with a weapon.
It's fast.
It's different from Fujiwara.
I'll stop it first.
Mr. Napoleon jumped.
Why did you do that?
I made a mistake with the sound of the propeller.
What is it?
I want Napoleon.
Napoleon asks for a brandy.
He shows that he can't do it.
But he can't stop drinking.
After that, he puts on a bra.
He suddenly goes into the water.
Mr. Napoleon.
There is a game.
Let's enjoy the beauty and the game.
Let's do that.
This is good.
Look at this.
This is amazing.
It's yellow.
It's good.
It's getting good.
It's amazing.
What is this?
Napoleon.
Who is it?
I can't read it.
I can't read it at all.
I can't do this.
I want you to press the button.
Macchan.
Yes.
Macchan is so cute.
Why?
Macchan.
Macchan is a lady.
Hama-chan is a lady.
You know I'm motivated.
I'm running out.
I'm confident.
This is my first appearance.
What are you going to do tomorrow?
I'm going to throw a party.
I have a party tomorrow.
I want to attend my favorite party.
I talk about this.
The president of Yoshimoto will hold the party.
I want to attend the party.
If I don't attend, I'll be fired.
That's not good.
I can't go because of that.
We should go together.
I'm sorry.
Where are you from?
Eh? I'm from Nabe Pro.
Nabe Pro.
Ah, this is a rare combination, isn't it?
Yes.
It's a different product.
Really, Yoshimoto...
I've been saying this for a long time, but...
I'm in the middle of a car delivery.
Where does the gas bill come from?
That's the story.
Well, yeah.
Right?
Normally, the manager would come pick you up in the morning, right?
But that's not the case.
He'd be like, why did you wake me up?
He'd be on the phone.
He'd be calling.
He'd be on the phone, and I'd be on the phone.
Right?
And if there's something important, he'd be on the phone.
He'd be like, what's important to you? I'm on the phone.
Don't be on the phone.
It'd take him about 100 minutes to hear that.
It's funny, isn't it?
Well, yeah.
I've been saying this for a long time, but...
It's funny, really.
You shouldn't be saying that.
What is it?
To the president.
To the president?
Yeah.
Why is there no car?
That's what I really think.
Normally...
That's why...
Everyone in Yoshimoto
Be debug and whine?
That's what I think.
What do you mean?
Are you sure we're talking about me?
You should just tell him tomorrow.
You hate that, right?
My glasses?
His glasses?
I hate your glasses.
I'm sitting in a corner, so tell me.
No, no, no. I've never really talked to her that much.
And you've been friends with her for a while, right?
You've been friends with her for a long time.
I mean, we've been friends for a long time.
You should go and tell her that you're in a good mood tomorrow.
You should hit her head and say that you're in a good mood.
You're making me cry.
You're in a good mood. You're definitely in a good mood.
I've grown up, so I don't really...
If you don't say something like that, you're really a nuisance.
No, she's been like that for a long time.
She has a lot of strength.
That's right, that old man.
Shinsuke-san told me to go and hit her head and tell her that I'm in a good mood.
That's right. I don't want to do that.
I'll go and tell her.
My back hurts, too.
I have a question for Matsumoto-san, who always says that he doesn't have a castle.
Yes, yes.
When an old lady uses a toothpick, she hides her mouth with her hand.
I think there's a reason to hide it.
What's going on in your hidden hand?
I'm taking a toothpick.
If you're taking a toothpick, you don't have to hide it.
It's already a spoiler.
It's a spoiler, but you can't see it when you take it.
If that's the case, you can only do this when you get it.
You don't have to do that.
I don't care if you see it at this point.
When you think you've got it, you can do this.
Or you can do this.
The reason I'm doing this is because I'm doing more than I thought.
What's going on?
Well, that's it.
I'm going to tell you that now.
Oh, please.
There's no need to rush.
There's plenty of time.
But it's not just old ladies.
What?
There are men who do this.
Men do this, too.
I've never seen a man do this.
Do you do it?
I don't.
You don't, do you?
Then it's not right.
That's enough.
It's about time.
What?
Tell me what's going on.
Do you want to hear it?
That's right.
I'll tell you if I really want to hear it.
I really want to hear it.
What is it?
Why are you trying to go to the next page?
Do you think I don't have anything?
No, it's just a spare.
Are you stupid?
Don't try to go to the next page even though you know it.
That's right.
You shouldn't do that.
I'm going to tell you now.
Oh, really?
Of course.
Your acting is strange.
It's not strange at all.
I've been saying it all the time.
Why are you hiding it with your hands?
Look at this sweat.
You know I don't have anything yet, right?
No.
You should have noticed.
I thought so.
Is this the sweat of the next page?
What is it?
Cold sweat.
Say it with both hands.
I thought so.
That's why you tried to go to the next page, didn't you?
Oh, I see.
Right?
You went to the next page.
Oh, I see.
You went to the next page, didn't you?
And then...
Oh, that's right.
It's the same as before.
I understand that.
I understand your love.
But think about it.
There are only three people in Downtown.
You don't even know the next page.
I don't think about the next page.
If there's a story here, I'll think about the next page.
Don't say that.
I'll think about it all the time.
You're a fool.
If you say that, I won't be able to move on.
That's why I said I'd go first.
You're still going to come back.
I should come back, right?
No, I'm angry that I lost.
Come on, come on.
I'll definitely do it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Come back.
Mr. Matsumoto seems to know all the titles of the same word.
Oh, I know.
Please guess all the titles of the same word that I'm going to give you now.
Oh, it's easy.
Why are the crows crying?
The crows are in the mountains.
This is why.
If you say it in detail, why...
No, I don't need that.
If you say it like that.
Why?
It's a joke.
It's true.
No.
I asked you why.
To whom?
To the teacher, the kindergarten teacher.
Why?
I'll go forever.
Forever?
I'm a child of seven.
Oh, that's wrong.
Which one is right?
That's strange.
You should look it up.
If you're wrong, you can do anything.
Look it up.
You can't do anything.
Well, I can do a little bit.
Let's go to the next one.
The crows are in the mountains.
How do you say this?
My lover.
Forever.
In detail.
This is my hometown.
You're wrong.
Look it up.
You're a child of seven.
This is your hometown.
What do you know about the staff here?
Show me the evidence.
Line up all the writers here.
Did you look it up?
How is it?
What's going on there?
I didn't look it up.
What?
Who looked it up?
The director must have looked it up.
Get the director.
Line up all the writers here.
Is this okay?
I'm not like you guys.
You're wrong.
Why are the crows crying?
The crows are in the mountains.
You're a child of seven.
This is your hometown.
What are you wearing?
What do you want to eat?
What are you eating while you're working?
The crows are in the mountains.
This is your hometown.
Where is your hometown?
This is my hometown.
Why are you saying that?
Your head is getting thinner.
There is a song called Sumida River.
This is the last one.
Please tell us the title of this song.
It hasn't come out yet.
What will you do after this?
Climbing up and down.
The people of the sea.
The people of the sea?
The people of the village?
The people of the sea.
The people of the sea?
Which way?
There are a lot of adults here.
Sit down.
The autumn breeze.
It's true.
Climbing up and down.
It comes back again.
The people of the sea.
The people of the sea?
The title is the people of the sea.
What is the title of this song?
Flower.
Why are you saying that?
What is it?
At the beginning of the program, I gained a lot of weight.
Idiot.
At the end, look.
What's going on?
What's going on in your left hand?
Everyone, listen carefully.
You do that a lot at restaurants.
You think everyone does it in front of people, right?
That's not it.
How much did you eat today?
After this, you have to go to the toilet.
That's what you're calculating here.
I think I did a good job.
In this situation.
Yes, yes.
Don't make me hate the details.
The same thing will happen next week.
I'll bring the book.
That's right.
No, wait a minute. It doesn't matter who's right about that.
What?
You're the only one who's wrong.
If I'm wrong, it's a mistake.
So what?
You don't have to say anything.
Say sorry.
I was wrong.
You're so arrogant.
What?
What do you mean by sorry?
In fact, you're like a doctor to me.
To be honest.
I'm really stressed out.
I've been attacked by so many adults.
I don't remember exactly, but I think that's the title.
It's okay. You can tell me here.
Why did you think this would happen?
I'm sorry.
Right?
That's why you chose that title, right?
I'm sorry.
An emergency announcement!
In the party in Yoshimoto, downtown is having a gala negotiation!
Downtown Stemino gala negotiation is going on!
Give me this.
I'm going to go to the president right now.
Let's have a gala negotiation.
These are the two from downtown.
Where is the president?
The president is over there.
President! President!
Ah, president. Thank you.
You're making a difficult face.
This is the worst calendar I've ever seen.
No, it's not like that.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I want to say something.
Ah, ah, ah.
We're not going to talk about gala today.
If we don't talk about gala, I won't be able to talk at all.
But today, I was caught by the traffic light.
The fine is 9,000 yen.
I don't know who's going to pay for this.
The company will.
Really?
Really!
I feel like I've been bitten.
Really?
I said I'd pay 9,000 yen.
So I'm going to take the one that was cut off.
I'd like to hear the microphone of the two from downtown.
President, my brain injury was cut off.
Yes, I'm sorry about that, but please.
9,000 yen, please.
It's a promise.
Ah, thank you.
1000 yen.
1000 yen for fishing?
Are you fishing?
I can't help it.
Really?
9,000 yen.
Yes, 9,000 yen.
Thank you very much.
You kept your promise.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.