Today's guests are very energetic.
Very energetic.
Why are you so excited?
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Thank goodness.
Only the guests are energetic.
That's not true.
I'm not that energetic.
I'm a little tired.
That's why I'm going to talk for 4 hours today.
What does this say?
Sherry?
You're Sherry.
From today.
Nice to meet you, Sherry.
The other day, when I was walking around,
I saw a handwritten paper at a bar.
A set of horoyoi.
How much was it?
About 1200 yen.
A horoyoi set.
With one beer.
That's good.
And a set of oden.
I'll leave that to the store.
I see.
I saw that handwritten paper.
I was very depressed.
Why?
I don't know.
Isn't it blue?
That's not true.
That's very kind of you.
Really?
We're shooting a drama right now.
I don't really go to the restaurant.
It's not very good.
I like the restaurant.
It's the worst.
What's that?
Rice variety.
A rice variety.
There's no rice.
It's a yakisoba set.
Where's the rice variety?
I think the English is a little wrong.
It's wrong.
That's very kind of you.
It's not like that.
I'll be done soon.
That's enough.
It's very sad.
A hard-working salaryman.
A set like that.
It's very sad.
But it's okay.
It's a set of beer.
What set?
A horoyoi set.
It's okay.
It's sad.
You should have at least chosen four oden.
There's a lot.
And konnyaku.
There might be three konnyaku in it.
That's impossible.
You don't know, do you?
There might be konnyaku in it.
That's impossible.
But you have to leave it to the restaurant.
It's very non-calorie.
It's okay.
It was very blue.
I'm sorry.
I feel bad.
It sounded like you had money.
That's okay.
Is that so?
It's okay.
I didn't want to talk about this at all.
There was a writer, Kramos.
He was in a car.
A foreign couple was fighting over there.
A man and a woman.
They were amazing.
The man was like,
He was in a hurry.
He hit the hood of Kramos' car.
What should I do?
That's scary.
It's scary.
What?
You couldn't do anything.
That's right.
It can't be helped.
I was in a car once before.
The car in front of me was down.
I was like,
It's okay.
When I dashed to that car,
My mirror went like this.
You hit it.
I hit it.
It went like this.
Me?
That's not true.
They were very excited.
They were like,
I don't want that car to come this way.
They were very excited.
That's not true.
That's a bad thing.
To Mr. Katsumoto.
Yes.
How big is the door of Megane-saru's glasses?
I don't know.
I don't know where to put it.
I'm waiting for a place to put it.
Normally,
That's right.
It was just said that it was a animal doctor.
I don't think it was said.
It was said that it was a animal doctor.
Is that so?
Please answer this.
What?
How big is the door of Megane-saru's glasses?
Have you ever seen Megane-saru?
I have.
It's not like he has glasses on.
What do you mean?
Megane-saru doesn't have glasses on.
Then what do you think that is?
It looks like that.
It looks like he has glasses on.
Why?
Megane-saru doesn't have glasses on.
No, no, no.
I've never seen him like this.
You're a fool.
What?
Megane-saru at the beginning was like this.
What do you mean by that?
He was like this.
It's not like he had a long neck.
That's true.
It's the same as that.
Megane-saru was like this at the beginning.
It's gradually evolving.
It's becoming more and more annoying.
It's gradually becoming a sports type.
It's becoming natural.
Or it's like this now.
It's changing like that.
The one who does this now is a very old type.
Why do you call him Megane-saru?
What do you mean?
I don't know what you mean.
He doesn't have glasses on.
He's the old type.
The old one was like this.
The new one is like this.
He doesn't have glasses on.
Touch him.
Touch Megane-saru.
What an amazing lens.
You can tell if he's wearing a lens.
You can tell even if you don't touch him.
Megane-saru can't tell at night.
He can't see at night.
He can't see in the daytime.
Megane-saru can't see from the front.
Because it's a flat lens.
When he does this, he glows.
He's not wearing glasses.
He does.
It depends on the type of person.
That's true.
If he's wearing glasses.
I don't know.
He's not wearing glasses.
Where did you see Megane-saru?
There's a statue of Megane-saru.
I saw him at the zoo.
A statue is cool.
Why did you touch him?
I saw Megane-saru at the zoo.
Megane-saru at the zoo is a lie.
What do you mean by a lie?
Don't think the lion at the zoo is a lion.
He's a lion.
He's not going to be a prey anymore since he's been in the cage.
You don't need a cage.
The lion is a lion.
Megane-saru is at the zoo.
So he's not wearing glasses.
But he's wearing glasses in the jungle.
I don't understand why he's not wearing glasses.
Why?
He's not wearing glasses since he was born.
If he was wearing glasses, it would be a show.
Glasses are glasses.
Where did you get those glasses?
This is from my mother.
Your mother?
Your mother is also a monkey?
My mother is also a monkey.
Where did you get those glasses?
I took them from her.
You took them from her?
You took them from a human, didn't you?
You took them from a human?
You are a monkey.
I took them from a monkey.
You took them from a monkey, didn't you?
Your mother took them from you and put them on you.
At first, I didn't like it.
Glasses are glasses.
Glasses are all glasses.
Why? You just took them from her and put them on.
That's right.
At first, I didn't like it.
But gradually, I started to like it.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Matsumoto-san had a fight with a snowman in the middle of his trip to Everest.
How did you settle this?
This is a great story.
I want to hear it.
How much percent do you want to hear it?
Please express it in numbers.
How much percent did you want to hear the story about the glasses?
50 percent.
That's why it was like that.
How much percent this time?
100 percent.
On the contrary, I don't talk to people who want to hear it that much.
If you tell me, I'll be happy.
You're looking forward to it too much.
I see.
That was hard.
First of all, I didn't go to Everest on the way to Tokyo.
I don't care about that.
I'm glad I met you on the way to Everest.
Before the special meeting, I want to ask you first.
What kind of guy is the snowman?
I want you to tell me what he looks like.
Everyone misunderstands the snowman.
Actually, he's about this big.
In our imagination, it's like a big guy.
You think it's big, right?
But it's all snow around, so it looks big.
There's no object.
I've never seen a snowman with a cigarette.
If he had a cigarette, he'd be like this.
A cigarette.
A cigarette?
It's a pure white world, so it looks big.
How big are you?
I'm about this big.
What does he look like?
He's small.
I don't know what he looks like, but he has long hair.
He has a beard.
That's what he looks like.
He has the same eyes as you.
He has a clean face.
He's small, but he's cute.
Amazing.
I was climbing up Everest.
Elevator?
When I was climbing up Everest,
at the beginning,
at the bottom,
the climbers would say,
Hello.
That's not the Everest.
That's not the Mt. Fuji.
That's not it.
At Everest,
at the bottom,
there are hikers.
They say, Hello.
At that moment,
I was climbing to the top of Everest.
It was an elevator.
Right?
I thought a child was coming,
so I said, Hello.
Then, the climber came.
I said, Did you climb up?
It was a snowman.
Why did you do that?
I don't know.
Why do you think he's a snowman?
You thought he was just a child, didn't you?
What?
That's why the climber is a snowman.
Is that so?
He's amazing.
He's hairy?
He's really hairy.
This was scary.
I've never heard this story before.
But it's about this, right?
You can win even if you're a top climber.
Why?
You have a cute face.
Your face is ugly.
You're kicking the snowman.
You don't look at anything else.
You're only looking at the snowman.
You're like this.
If you're only kicking the snowman,
you can protect the snowman.
But he's just kicking the snowman.
I'm scared.
You're crazy.
I'm not crazy.
If you kick the snowman,
you can stop it with your hands or legs.
That's not true.
I'm used to kicking the snowman.
Even if I kick the snowman,
it comes off.
This is really scary.
You kicked the snowman, didn't you?
How did you deal with it?
You kicked the snowman many times.
That's right.
How did you deal with it?
I had a girlfriend.
Even though you didn't have a girlfriend?
I stopped it with my hands.
The judgment is amazing.
It's fast.
I know you kicked the snowman.
How did you deal with it?
That's the question.
It's a story of a showman.
That's right.
I've never heard of you kicking the snowman.
I want you to tell me how to deal with it.
I can't fight
against
the snowman
underwater.
I see.
You're used to it.
I'm used to it.
I'm controlling the snow.
I'm controlling the Everest.
That little thing.
I can't win if I fight there.
I can't bring it to my field.
I see.
Before I say anything,
I put it in my rucksack.
By the way,
I've already won.
I kicked the snowman until now.
I caught it and put it in my rucksack.
It's over.
I kicked it out of my rucksack pocket.
It's amazing.
You can kick it with that.
I don't understand why
you kick the snowman.
I can't do anything
if I take it to a warm place.
I'm sorry.
Apologize.
I'm sleepy.
I'm very sleepy.
I often see a child
on the rear glass of a car.
I often see a child on the rear glass of a car.
What does that mean?
I always look at it and think,
A child is riding.
So?
If a child is driving,
I understand.
What's the reason?
I don't think you should drive too fast.
So don't get on my back.
Don't get on my back.
I hate the idea that
I don't care about the child.
It doesn't matter.
I see.
You have to treat children like adults.
That might be the case, but it's just that...
There was a time when Miyasako gave birth to a child.
Yes, yes.
She gave birth to a child, right?
She said, please come see it.
It's only been a few months, so it's been like this the whole time.
Right?
Everyone, Yo-san's juniors also came and said,
Wow, it's so cute.
But it's not cute at all.
What the hell?
I asked her, what are you doing?
She said, please sit on the veranda.
She said, there's a bride.
What kind of image is that?
You didn't do anything like that, did you?
Why do I have to sit on the veranda for Miyasako's baby?
That's a stupid movie.
Well, I thought I'd watch it.
I watched it, but there's nothing to say.
Everyone says that the eyes are similar.
Isn't that all a lie?
It doesn't look like that.
I don't know if it's grown a little bit, but it doesn't look like it in two or three months.
Well, I don't know that.
Miyasako's baby doesn't look like it, so it doesn't really work.
I looked at it and I didn't have a place to praise it.
There's a chick app here.
It's more yellow than I thought.
It's got a cute face.
It's yellow.
Miyasako, that's a chick app.
Is that so?
I thought the bride must be laughing.
I looked at it and it was like this.
That's not true.
It's a bad image.
Where are you looking?
I don't know. Ask your wife.
Matsumoto and Hamada can't win over the history of the 12-year-old servant.
It's a battle and punishment game where Matsumoto and Hamada compete with each other.
And this year, the Matsumoto vs. Hamada team's 50-meter race to mark a new century has begun.
The Hamada team won this match.
Matsumoto lost to Muzan.
Therefore, the punishment game has been decided for the first time in seven years.
The other day, a talk was held between the Hamada team about the punishment game.
The last time we were here, it was so bad.
It was terrible.
It was beyond the punishment game.
That's right.
It was mentally and physically painful.
I can't work at 2 or 3 o'clock.
This is the worst punishment game ever.
It's a 24-hour long game of tag.
The four of them are trapped in a secret gym.
No!
The four of them have experienced the worst humiliation ever since they started their lives.
I want you to do the same thing as before.
I want you to play 24-hour tag.
Only if you get beaten.
I'll definitely get caught.
I wonder if the target is Matsumoto.
I can't escape.
Only if you get beaten.
But...
Skydiving...
Even if it's Fujiyama.
I'd like to take you there, but I can't.
That's 24-hour Fujiyama, isn't it?
But...
24-hour Fujiyama, or 24-hour skydiving.
If you get off, you still have to ride.
If we were to go, we'd have to ride for 24 hours.
That's very...
I think it's okay to go higher.
Really?
48 hours.
That was that hard.
I can say that.
Remember the bus game in Yamasaki?
It wasn't broken, was it?
It was abandoned.
We played it.
That was hard, wasn't it?
That was hard.
It was scary.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
If we were to go for 24 hours, we'd have to come in the afternoon.
Ah, I see.
It wasn't scary.
It was scary in the dark.
If you go up, you play Seeing buses.
You play Majesty buses.
That sounds good.
Why not two?
In hondake.
That sounds good.
At night, it's scary.
In the morning, you play seeing buses.
When it gets dark, you play seeing buses.
You play seeing buses.
That sounds good.
Let's leave it at that.
That's good.
Yeah, that sounds good.
For people watching TV.
Yes?
People seem to have high hopes.
We do.
We will play a punishment game to answer your questions.