Today is a special day.
I'll buy you something.
Mr. Suga will give you a big present.
Really?
It's perfect.
The prize is 3 million yen.
3 million yen?
Why?
It's a 600th anniversary.
Really?
It's a 3 million yen prize.
If it's 3 million yen,
it's a lot of money.
It's 1 million yen.
Is that so?
Everyone will do their best, right?
The prize is 100, 100,
40, 40.
Why?
It's the same if you put it here.
424.
That's right.
This program is
brought to you by the producer.
Don't say such a thing.
This person is
the mirror of the producer.
That's amazing.
What do you get for that?
That's right.
It's a really
simple game.
Is this okay?
Really?
I wanted to give it to you.
That's right.
I have something to do,
so I have to go.
Do you have money?
That's amazing.
Wait a minute.
I'll leave this to Kobayashi.
Kobayashi,
I'm doing this to give it to you.
I see.
I think you'll press the recording button,
so you can use this.
I can get a lot of money.
That's right.
We already have that much.
So,
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'll give it to you.
It's a prize.
Thank you.
That's amazing.
I don't know how many producers are in Japan.
It's okay.
I'm doing it now.
Then, do it.
I'll get it.
I'm so lucky.
The first time,
the prize is 3 million yen.
Last of Mumble
3rd match.
It's 3 million yen.
Thank you.
I'll do it.
I'll go to eat a puffer fish.
I'll tell you the rules again.
Let's do it together.
Let's clear the game.
You can get 1 million yen for each game.
That's amazing.
There are three in total.
If you succeed in three,
you'll get 3 million yen.
It's an easy game.
It's easy.
Let's start the game.
Here it is.
If you collect 50 videos in 3 minutes,
you'll get 1 million yen.
Is this the end?
If you collect 50 videos in 3 minutes,
you'll get 1 million yen.
It's easy.
You don't even need 3 minutes.
It's amazing how much Suga tried to give.
It's amazing.
If 5 people line up,
you'll get 1 million yen.
Thank you.
Let's do it.
Be careful.
Ready.
Go.
You don't have to be in a hurry.
Slowly.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
Let's do the end.
You can do it.
You can't run away.
I got this.
You're too close.
Wait a minute.
There's still time.
You're too close.
You can do it.
Wait a minute.
Hey, Aoka!
Don't lean against the wall.
Don't lean against it.
Hey,
you're not good at this.
You're not good at this.
You're not good at it.
Aoka!
It's okay.
This is the last one.
I'm sorry.
It's over.
Excuse me.
Hey.
You should have put the cable on.
Red one.
You should have put the camera on.
What is that?
There's no reason to say that.
There are three cameras.
He was doing like this.
That's not good.
Do it again.
Rules are rules.
What do you mean?
It's my fault.
Yes.
We did it.
But rules are rules.
You got in the way.
Who is that?
I don't care.
There are two more.
You can take two hundred.
Hey.
You shouldn't have put it in.
Right?
It's dirty.
You're not good at it.
I'm not good at it.
You're not good at anything.
You're right.
If you eat 100 bowls of bowl soba in 3 minutes, you'll get 1 million yen.
It's only 3 minutes.
I think it's more expensive than before.
If you eat 100 bowls of bowl soba in 5 minutes, you can eat 20 bowls of bowl soba.
It's only 3 minutes.
I can do it.
You can do it.
If I say yes, will you put it in?
Raise your hand.
Yes.
Okay.
Let's do it.
Let's do it quickly.
Let's get it.
It's about this amount.
It's a little less.
Are you ready?
Please put it in.
I'm ready.
Let's do it.
Ready.
It's hard.
Okay.
Auntie, hurry up.
Let's do it quickly.
Auntie.
Here's the bowl.
Hurry up.
Auntie.
Soba.
Come on, Grandma.
Come on.
Hurry up.
You shouldn't do that.
You're not using your hands properly.
Hurry up.
You did good.
You're doing great.
Grandma, hurry up.
Soba-chan, Soba-chan
Hey, what are you doing?
Put in the soba
This is impossible
Here you go, Soba-chan
Give me the soba
What is this?
Can't you eat this?
Give me the soba
Soba, soba, soba
What are you doing?
Time's up
Hey, hey
It's hard to get another 100,000
But I'll do my best
I'll reset it and do it again
Time's up
I'm hungry
You can't eat this
I don't want to do this
Thank you for your hard work
You can't eat this
You can't
You're the last one
It's been a while since I watched the first and the middle
Since you're back, let's go to the next game
It's for me
That's right
It's been a while since I said it
It's been 10 years since I said it
Okay, time's up
The last game is
If you can get 10 soba in 3 minutes, you win
I'm counting on you
It's been 3 minutes
Let's get this
Okay
Let's go
Ready
Put it in the basket
I caught it
What are you doing?
Put it in
Let's catch it
Put it out
I caught it
You're amazing
Time's up
Hey
Why?
I don't know
Why are you making so much noise?
Today
I'm fine
Why are you so fine?
I don't know
I don't know if you look like him
I don't think you know him yet
I don't feel good
The other day
I was so hungry
I was driving around Shibuya
There's a selfie video, right?
Yes
I'm not going
Really?
Let's go
No
I'm not interested
I was just going to take a picture of you
When I went in
There's a movie
I was just going to take a picture of you
I knew everything
When I went in
Everything was erotic
Right?
From the video
To the DVD
Everything was erotic
I thought it was amazing
You were happy
I was happy
Right?
I looked at it
I was surprised
My teacher
Black
I took a picture of his face
My lips were open
Maru
Also my recommendation
No
It's strange
En
Is there a video that we can feel satisfied with
I don't know what you want to feel satisfied with
Conf eigen or something
I was so happy
It's not like that
No
No, no, this is...
Take this!
It's the same!
So what did you do?
I said,
I can't do this, I can't do this.
But I said,
I'll say it, even if you say it on purpose,
I'll become a shop assistant again.
I'll say it,
I'll say it.
So I said,
I'm counting on you.
I said,
No, no, I did buy it in Japan.
I bought it without a doubt.
But that's not really a matcha corner.
That's a picture.
I was waiting for it to come.
I did buy it,
and I went to the store.
But the matcha corner is
a bit strange, right?
No, no, no,
because you say it like that,
people think you're a representative of eroticism.
It's like a sex symbol.
I don't know if it's a symbol or not.
It's just an image.
No, no, no, it's you!
It's you!
It feels like you're borrowing eroticism.
You!
Wait, wait, wait.
You haven't seen it, right?
You haven't seen the one I chose, right?
You're taking a picture, right?
No, no, no.
You're making me angry.
It's strange,
but I can't help it.
Why is it me?
Some people are saying
that I went to a magazine
and went to a club.
It's written all over the place.
By the way, here's a matcha from downtown.
I don't know.
Why?
Because you went.
Even if you didn't go there,
you went somewhere else, right?
I'm telling you,
I didn't go to a club
like the average Japanese guy.
No, no, no, no.
You didn't see it, right?
I'm telling you.
I have that image.
It's completely different.
You've never been
kicked in the butt with your fingers?
No, I've never been there.
You've been there, right?
No, I haven't.
That's not good.
You did it.
I'm not saying it's not good.
I'm telling you.
I have that image.
I've never been kicked in the butt in an AV
Why do you have that image?
You won't be in the movie
because you are the one that gets kicked in the butt.
Okay, so that's your thoughts.
I don't have any tits.
I'm always in the certain way.
Like a boiled egg.
K 20 THOUSAND
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Do you have money?
Of course I have money.
How much did I make this year?
What are you talking about?
It's a little bit of a competition.
I see.
That's what we're talking about.
I'm trying to figure it out somehow.
If you have something to say, say it.
I'm going to run and fly.
I see.
Fly.
Why are you going to fly again?
Because I'm confident.
I think I can fly 4-5 meters easily.
You can fly 5 meters?
I think I can fly.
5 meters?
I'm sorry, but...
I think I can fly 3-4 meters at most.
No, no, no.
If you're going to fly, you need one major.
That's what I thought.
It's a long story, though.
Don't say that.
So!
It's 4 against 1.
There's a reason why I can't continue.
But if I continue,
You guys are four, right?
I'm the only one, right?
You guys can fly four times, right?
I see.
To be honest, I can beat you guys just by flying three times.
Why?
Because I'm a spring man.
A spring man of fear.
That's not fear.
That's what I think.
That's what I think, but...
You seem confident.
I'm confident, but...
I'm a little scared.
Flying four times is...
The first and second times, I think I can easily fly over 4 meters.
But flying three times and four times...
Even if I say so, it's 42 meters.
Who said that?
38 meters.
With this 38-year-old body,
Can you fly four times?
I see.
I'm a little scared of that.
No, no, no.
It's okay to fly four times.
I have to fly only three times.
What?
Really?
Yes.
I'll definitely win.
But I don't know.
Really?
No, really.
Well, shall we call the three of them?
No, no, no.
I'm not surprised.
It's better to fly four times.
Well, but...
Well, that's it.
Well, I can fly four times.
I can fly four meters.
I can fly four times.
Listen!
What are you doing?
Is it a party?
Who do you think can fly?
What is it?
I'll definitely win.
No, if it's 44 meters, I'll definitely win.
44 meters?
Four times at a time, right?
How many meters can you fly?
Maybe 3 meters and 20 meters.
I think I can fly that much.
Right?
And 2 meters and 50 meters.
You can't fly at all.
You're kidding me, right?
I'm really good at jumping.
Really?
No, I was doing kendo.
What?
Kendo.
It doesn't really matter.
No, it doesn't matter.
Hey!
Come here!
This is...
What are you doing?
I can fly kendo.
I can fly a lot of things.
I want to fly more.
You want to fly more?
Well, 3 meters...
Let's say 3 meters and 50 meters.
3 meters and 50 meters.
How much is 3 meters and 50 times 4?
14 meters.
14 meters, right?
I'll definitely go over 4 meters.
4 meters is 16, so it's 16 meters.
That means I've already won.
And Tanaka...
This is a bit of a joke, right?
I think I can fly.
I think I can walk in the air.
Really?
If you do that, it'll be weird.
I think I can do it for a while.
Don't say that.
When you try to fly forward, you're an amateur, right?
That's not true.
It's the time you spend in the air.
You have speed, so even if you just fly up, you can move forward.
So the point is how much time you spend in the air.
Even in the previous match, I was so confident that I couldn't even swim 50 meters.
I couldn't even score a goal.
It's not that you couldn't swim, but your eyeballs were about to pop out.
Why did you do that?
I was suffering so much that my eyeballs were about to pop out.
But it was okay to do it.
But when I went up, the drone came out.
Can you do it?
No, I can't blur it.
Even if you can blur it, there's a drone around here.
There's a blind spot.
What did you think?
That's not good.
If you have a problem, you can fly over there.
But I can fly four times.
You can fly five times, and I can fly four times.
That's perfect.
I'm sorry, but I'll decide the other one.
For example?
For example, the one that's the most popular right now is Heipo.
That's definitely not good.
Heipo Uchiyama-kun.
Uchiyama-kun.
I'll leave it at that.
Then, Heipo-san, over there.
You mean you're going to fly four times?
Heipo will fly once every four times.
That's what it means.
I'll fly three times.
I'll fly four times.
I don't know.
I'll move a little bit, so maybe...
Don't you feel like you're going to fly sideways?
Scary!
What's scary?
You can't fly wide?
I'll just let it go and fly.
Then let's fly wide.
Are you sure?
I'll fly really far.
Then fly really far.
I think it's going to be amazing.
Even if you don't fly wide.
Everyone says that about eight times a month.
I'll say it a little more.
After I get home, I'll be saying it in a weird way.
Even if you don't fly wide.
That's going to be a trend this year.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.