Keiro no Hi special with Jin-chan Baachan and Kakurenbo!
Today we have 6 guests.
First, we have our guest, Mr. Amikoshi!
If you hold it down a bit more, your thumb will break.
It's not broken yet.
It's flat!
It's soft!
I haven't said anything strange yet.
Next, we have our guest, Mrs. Komori!
I'll have her hide.
Please don't call me Mrs. Komori when I'm hiding.
I'm still in love with you.
I'm in love with you one-sidedly.
What about Mr. Amikoshi?
Mr. Amikoshi doesn't call people who look like Mrs. Komori.
Mrs. Komori doesn't call people who look like Mrs. Komori either.
Let's be friends.
I saw Mrs. Amikoshi's sad face for the first time.
We have 4 more guests today.
Who is this person?
Umekichi.
She appeared on this show before.
We named her Umekichi.
Masumoto took her home on a rope.
Umekichi took her to Osaka and talked to her.
Now I'm here.
I blow my whistle and she comes back.
What?
She gets angry.
We have 2 more guests today.
It's been a long time since I played hide-and-seek.
I remember when I was little.
Really?
See you later.
I set everything up.
You don't know this.
Really?
I've been a veteran detective for 50 years.
I couldn't do this.
Really?
It took a long time to hide.
It's hard to move.
I'll kick you.
Let's go.
Say you know.
Are you kidding me?
I don't think she's found yet.
I think there's a strange light.
I'll kick you.
She's at the station sometimes.
There are 5 more guests.
5 more guests.
She doesn't want to do it.
She's hiding, so she's keeping her voice down.
She can't laugh.
Let's throw her out.
She's happy, so let's leave her alone.
Let's do it already.
I've been thinking.
If I gather the 7 grandpas and grandmas, I'll have a wish.
She's there.
She was there just now.
Grandma!
Now, let's have a look.
What are you doing?
Grandma, I'm sorry.
Please come out.
Grandma, please come out.
Are there three more people?
Hamada.
What?
You passed.
Really?
Hey.
Grandma, let's go to war.
I found you.
Hey, Utsuka.
What did you find?
Are you ready?
What?
You didn't turn off the microphone.
This is very funny.
I want to go to the children's meeting today.
Look at the air conditioner.
It's noisy.
Because the volume is high.
Because the microphone is noisy.
I can't hear myself.
One more person.
This is a grandma.
What?
Hamada, what do you do when you wake up in the morning?
What time is it?
It's really me.
I can't believe it's a male toilet.
What are you doing?
You look like a model.
Grandma.
Grandma is a model.
Hamada.
It stinks.
Thank you very much.
100 years old.
It was interesting that you were in an unexpected place.
I didn't expect you to be in a toilet.
But this is the first time I've been in a male toilet since I was born in 1981.
It was a little painful today.
Please tell me more better.
Thank you very much.
You'll be lucky.
I'm sorry.
I'm not good at it.
Hey, Matsumoto.
Come on.
Have you all read it?
I read it in downtown Kaishanbyo.
I'm sorry to say this at the beginning of the program.
I don't think you'll get away with it.
Hey.
We were supposed to have a party this year.
Matsumoto and Hamada are not friends.
They both said they didn't want to continue laughing.
If it's that good, I'll stop it.
Hey.
I'm really sorry.
Can't you close the last one properly?
Are you crying or laughing?
It hurts.
This was on the news in Osaka and Tokyo.
I don't know what you're talking about.
The front line of the masked reporter.
What are you talking about?
We were surprised.
If you had checked it, we would have disbanded.
It's true that they're not friends.
I haven't told him yet.
About six years ago, I was so angry that I still can't forget it.
What did I do?
I think it was when I was leaving the theater.
He stepped on my foot.
It hurt a lot.
I thought I'd stop it from that time.
What are you talking about?
The way he wrote it was so funny.
We both laughed.
He wrote that he didn't want to do comedy.
He said he wanted to be a producer.
Hamada didn't want to work at all.
I want to play.
Hamada wants to play, so he can't help it.
It's impossible to tell him to study and practice comedy.
I'm happy to come to Tokyo, so I can't help it.
If I go to Roppongi, I'll be teased.
I want to play.
Who are you?
Come out, the front line of the masked reporter.
I want to be a producer.
Hamada hasn't worked yet.
I want to play.
The big company employee told us to be serious.
Then we said,
We're selling.
That's what we said.
All the news is a lie.
Will your wife get pregnant?
Why don't you do it?
I don't think so.
Why did you hide the fact that you had a baby?
I didn't hide it.
I'm working anyway.
I can't help it.
I didn't hide it.
Your wife will get pregnant.
I'm playing with the audience.
That's why you have to be careful.
I saw it on the news yesterday.
My girlfriend found out.
I don't know who it is.
I don't want to bother her.
But I have to be honest on this show.
That's right.
I've been dating for about a year.
It's embarrassing to say it myself.
My car broke down.
I don't want to date.
It's a lie.
I was bullied in high school.
That's not true.
At that time, I knew the fear of writing
So, there was a quiet kid in the class
Everyone was kind of a bad guy, but
There were about 5 of us, and we were like,
Hey, what's up?
There was that kind of thing
Hey, you, come over here
That's what he said when he got home
I was like, oh, he bullied me
I wrote it down in my notebook
First, Daredare-kun kicked me in the face
Then, Matsumoto-kun kicked my wife a couple of times
I wrote it all down, and I went to the library
What do you call this over here?
Dekopin?
It's called Osaka Konpachi
Even if you do this, you can't write Dekopin when you become a Kijin
The face...
The face?
I'm so angry
If you become a Kijin, you can't write Dekaiji
No, no, no
Let's go to the field
Hello
Let me introduce you
Yamaoda Reiko-san
What do you like about her?
She's funny
She's cool
She's funny and cool
Does that mean you can do anything to us?
You like her a lot, don't you?
Even if you were to step on my father, would you be able to accept that?
I wouldn't be able to accept that
You don't like that?
You don't understand how a man feels about a woman, right?
For example, if you have a favorite actress or singer, you want to do it, right?
I want to do it
You want to do it, right?
You like Dandan, don't you?
You want to do it?
Why do you want to do it?
That's a strange story
It's strange
You like her, don't you?
Do it!
Hey!
I won't do it
I won't do it, but I'll do it even if I have to
Even if you have to bully me
I'm sorry
Let's go
It's hot
It's really hot here
I can't stand it
It's really hot
The other day, I was walking and I saw your face
The sky is hot
When I touched it
It's really hot
I can't stand it
It's hot
I know what you're talking about
The other day, I was walking and I saw your face
When I touched it
It's really hot
Now, the break is over
Let's introduce the post
This is from Tokumekibo
The other day, I went to see my favorite Matsumoto
I waited for about 30 minutes
Matsumoto came
I went to see Matsumoto
Matsumoto had a very angry face
I was a little scared
Is it always like that? Please tell me
I read it before
Please take care of your fans
It's always like that
I think he's going to clap
Usually?
Yes
He's walking like he's annoyed
But usually he doesn't walk with such a smile
Smile?
He doesn't walk with a smile
I can't say that he's smiling
If he says something, I can't say anything
What if he comes with a gift and asks you to take it?
What do I do?
That's all
That's all you have to say, right?
I can say thank you too
You can say it?
No, that's...
When you say thank you
What do you mean?
Everyone think about it
Thank you
Think about it when you say thank you
Thank you?
When you say thank you
When you do something unexpected
Unexpectedly
Thank you is when you say something unexpected
That's not it
Even if you do something unexpected
If you do something for yourself
Thank you
There are people who bring cigarettes, right?
Yes
What do you do with them?
It's all the same
Thank you
Why do you carry a cigarette in your hand?
You smoke
No, no
Rather, you smoke this and you...
No, I don't
You want to kill me
Are you out of your mind?
Did I say thank you?
You didn't
When I was doing radio in Osaka
Someone came and said
Downtown-san, Nainai-san, good evening
Everyone said good evening
Actually, I...
I can't even say good evening
You can't
Why?
Everyone is thinking about greetings
Greetings
Wait, you
You can't even say thank you
If you say this
Greetings
You say it while looking at people's eyes
This is a greeting
You
When you come to work
You say hello to everyone
You don't even try
When I say it, I say it properly
Liar
Thank you
Good evening
This is...
This is something I learned from my parents
You saw it
I don't understand how you can say good evening to such a stupid letter
No, that's something you say to this kid
You say thank you
What?
Are you listening to the radio?
I'll tell you a serious story
You get a cigarette
At that time, I couldn't say thank you
But I have to think about one thing
What did she want me to do?
What are you talking about?
I just did it
It's a serious story
I did it
Wait
What did she want me to do?
Why are you crying?
Do you want me to read this?
Sure
Yuki-chan
The other day you did a commercial for Alta, didn't you?
Yes
Right?
You did a commercial for Kikkoshibari
When you did that commercial
You said you'd do something if there were so many people
So I thought it would be nice if we all made a letter
I was looking for it on the internet
What do you think?
I think it would be nice if we could do it
It doesn't matter
We did it at the opening of a children's show
Like this show?
I don't know if that's right
I'm doing it near Tenjin
I'm doing it
You have to take a helicopter from above
At that time I went skydiving
Are you stupid?
I know the trick
I don't know
That's not good
Let's think about the opening of a children's show
Right?
That's all for today
That's right
I can't do it with you anymore
Really
Aikata
I can't do it anymore
It's hot
It's already 8 o'clock
I can't do it
It's not fashionable
When it's 8 o'clock, all the cars I got in are pumpkins
At this moment
Yes
What should we do?
In November
If that time comes, let's talk about it again
Yes
If you can make a sentence
Let's meet in front of Alta
No
I'll be scolded again
You'll be scolded again. You'll be taken away again.
I'll dress up as a cat.
That's enough.
Next week, on this show,
I'll be in Okinawa.
I'll go to Okinawa.
I'll dance while I'm in Okinawa.
That's all for now.
We'll see you next week.
Good bye!
They'll tell me to dance while I'm laughing.
I'll dance while I'm laughing.