Good evening, everyone.
Today, I have something to tell you.
As a regular of this program, Mr. Hosei Yamasaki, who has been working hard with us since the second time, will graduate from the program.
Well, in the past, I was doing something like saying goodbye to Mr. Yamasaki like this.
At that time, I felt like I was having fun with a prank.
Let's hear the truth from Mr. Hosei Yamasaki.
Well, it's a sudden story, so the staff here are surprised.
Well, let's start with Mr. Yamasaki's mouth.
Well, this is the last time, but I don't want to have such a dark atmosphere.
So what kind of life story is it?
I'm 36 years old and I'm an old man.
I bought a house and I have two children.
I feel like it's a big step.
Yes, yes, yes, I understand that.
I don't see much confidence.
My wife's name is Aya.
I know.
Well, as for me, it seems that the gala is going up a lot.
Yes, yes, yes.
So, when I look at the budget of the children, it seems that it is becoming very cramped.
This is also a real problem that it is very difficult to say.
Do you mean that there are places that you can't pay off?
Well, it's not that I can't pay it off, but it's very cramped.
It's cramped?
Yes.
It's cramped.
Also, Hamada-san, after all, he only plays the endo.
Isn't that a little too much to think about?
I read the endo in the dressing room and talked about it secretly.
I thought I would be called next time, but there was no drop at all.
I also talked to my wife about it, but she said that the relationship between people is getting worse.
How much did the people who are watching TV understand what Yama-chan said now?
That's right.
Actually, I think there is something more in the back that we can't measure.
Well then, let's take a look at the famous scenes of Yama-chan that he chose in order to look back on Yagashi-kun's memories.
Yamazaki Hosei, 36 years old.
He participated in the program from the second time he started as a child. He has been active for 15 years and has created many famous scenes.
He will graduate from the program with today's broadcast.
So I look back on the great miracles he left behind.
5th place Yoshimoto Combi vs. Synchro
Yamazaki-kun, who has been saying that he is also a field in the water since Kanete.
He should have participated in the combination, but for some reason he teamed up with the director of Komurasaki without a partner.
Yamazaki Hosei and Komurasaki Kozo
Komu, thank you.
Komu's smile is dirty.
What?
What is this?
4th place High Tension Famous Scenes
Please take a look at the acting of Yamazaki-kun, who was always full of life.
I made a mistake.
If I make a mistake, I can't do everything.
5th place Yamazaki Kozo
Yamazaki Kozo
3rd place Goodbye Yamazaki Hosei
Yamazaki-kun loves to tease people.
You've been telling me that you're going to graduate from this program at the same time as me for the past 3 years, and you've been lying to me.
But this time, it's really goodbye.
Yamazaki Kozo
2nd place A moving wedding
Yamazaki-kun, who was our idol, finally got married.
And we all saw that moving wedding ceremony.
Yamazaki Kozo
1st place Will the god of laughter come down to Yamazaki?
The god of laughter doesn't come down at all.
You've tried a lot of things to make the god of laughter come down, haven't you?
It's delicious.
It's funny.
There's a button connected here, and there's a firework coming out.
It's amazing that the god of laughter came down for the first time.
Yamazaki Kozo
How was it, Ayano?
I thought there were a lot of VTRs.
It's time to say goodbye.
Please say goodbye to the producer.
Thank you for your hard work, Yama-chan.
I was told that it was hard to be a gyaru.
Actually, I was thinking of uploading it again in April.
I'm really shocked and disappointed.
But regardless of the gyaru, I came to Japan TV this time.
Anyway, I was told to throw away everything I didn't need in Kojima.
I never thought I'd throw Yamazaki away in Kojima.
That's also an order from the company.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Let's talk to each other one by one.
Thank you for your hard work.
Yamazaki-san will be removed, but what he did as a kid will remain in everyone's hearts.
At first, I saw Ko-san on TV.
I wanted to be an artist with a flower like Ko-san as soon as possible.
I really don't have a flower.
Thank you for your hard work.
I've only met Yama-chan on the spot.
It was about three hours long.
I don't have any regrets about this.
Even if you graduate, please be healthy.
Thank you for your hard work.
There was a talent maker in the dressing room.
There were so many people that I thought there would be so many changes.
If we were a family...
I would hate a real family.
Thank you for your hard work.
Finally, let's say goodbye to everyone in front of the TV.
Who do you think will be surrounded by such a large bouquet of flowers?
I've been out since the second time I was a kid.
It's been 15 years since I've been out.
I'm sorry.
I said I didn't cry.
Goodbye, Yama-chan.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's not like he's going to quit.
If you search for Yamanaki on DVD recorders, they'll record it for you.
I'm sure the recorders will be in trouble if you put it in.
Who?
Let's do it again next week.
Let's go home.
Yama-chan is a kid's worker.
I can't do it.
Viewers, are you surprised?
I'm going to ask Kogoriko to do it again.
It's the first time I've seen it.
Yama-chan is a kid's worker.
I can't do it.
We'll be waiting for the day we can see you again.
I'll wave my hand and shout on the road of cherry blossoms.
I can't stop crying.
It's my fate to go down a sad road.
I'll wave my hand and shout on the road of cherry blossoms.
We're going to change our costumes again.
I hope it's the last one this year.
This is from Yamazaki-san.
It's a little low.
I only know for an hour.
It's terrible, isn't it?
Let's go!
I can't stop crying.
Hey! Don't wait!
Try it!
Downtown-san and Kokoriko-san!
We're going to change our costumes again.