Next time, we'll be back with a new episode of Gagi no Tsukai!
He's so kind!
What kind of story is this?
We've been doing this for a long time.
We've been doing this for over a month now.
We asked our staff to be honest with us.
This is serious.
We asked them to marry us if they could.
No, this is a serious story.
Let's go! The contestants are here!
Please take a seat.
Why don't you try this on?
Let's start with a self-introduction.
Let's go!
I'm Yoshimoto Kogyo Okamoto.
I'm 28 years old.
I'm here today to find my girlfriend.
That's a lame self-introduction.
I'm Takasu, the reporter.
I'm turning 30 this year.
People around me are getting married soon.
You guys are so hard!
What are you talking about?
Is this a documentary?
I'm here to find a woman who will go to the shrine with me.
That's a good idea!
You know what you're doing!
That's what I'm going to say.
That's what I'm going to say!
You little brat!
I'm Tsutsumimoto, the director.
I'm Kishin Kinomi.
I'm here to find my girlfriend.
I'll do my best as the representative of the staff.
Lastly, number 5.
You're so small!
I'm sitting down!
You're so big!
I'm Saito, the director.
I'm 41 years old.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Kumiko Takaoji.
Number 2.
I'm Nanase Mizuno.
I'm 24 years old.
I'm Harumi Nakane.
I'm 21 years old.
I'm...
Soap?
What kind of soap is that?
I have a lot of childlike parts.
I like people who are older than me.
Saito is putting on glasses right now.
There's only one person putting on glasses.
If you're told you're older than me, I'll give you a hug.
I'm Yoshie Maite.
I'm 22 years old.
I'm a fritter.
I'm Nanami.
Nanami?
What do you mean?
Everyone can hear you.
Why can't I hear you?
Are you a fritter?
I'm Harumi.
I'm a fritter.
What kind of fritter are you?
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Let's start with the usual.
Question time!
That's right.
Let's start with the usual.
Is this okay?
Let's go.
What kind of person do you like?
I like people who are funny.
I'm a broadcaster.
I like everyone.
I like funny people.
I like people who make me laugh.
Number two doesn't make sense.
I don't like that kind of person.
I like people who make me laugh.
It's very difficult.
Did I ask a question?
I didn't have a good answer.
I like people who are sincere.
I was waiting for an answer like you.
If you got an answer like you, you'd be in school.
I like Hamada.
I don't need that!
Don't say that!
It's fun to be together
Anything else?
Number 3 was quick
What do you need a woman for?
This is a difficult question
It's a severe question
When you want to feel good
Yes
What you don't have enough
That's mean!
You're a narcissist!
That's not true
Kazutaiji said it
Don't say Kazutaiji
I'll say it
I'll ask for something I don't have
What are you saying?
I'm not happy
I want to be happy
You're not happy?
A place to relax
I'll say it
I didn't hear you say it
Basically he's eating rocks
You can appear in that
What?
Never ending story
He's eating rocks
Really?
For my wife
Number 4
If you spend Christmas together
How would you like to be escorted?
Number 1
From Christmas Eve
At 12
We'll meet at my house
How do you show up?
By car?
No, by walking
By walking?
Yes
That's a normal Thursday
Why Thursday?
I'll drink champagne
And go to sleep
It's Junya's birthday
You're lying
I'm not
You're a bad character
So
You made a reservation
For money
That's true
Super
Super?
Why didn't you make a reservation?
Super
Bar
On your birthday
You'll go home
I'll go home
I have an iron plate
I don't know what you're talking about
You're so bad
I'll make takoyaki
You have an iron plate
Let's make takoyaki together
That's right
I have a restaurant
That I go to
You have a restaurant
That you go to?
I'll make a reservation
At the convenience store
You can take it home
You can do it yourself
Christmas party
I've never been to
Disneyland
You've never been there?
I've never been there
I want you to take me there
Christmas is
You take me there
It's like
Men's
Who are you?
I'm a talent
You're a kid
But
Men's
I can't see it
You can practice
I want you to look here
I'm a salaryman
As long as I don't get fired
I can live a normal life
You can say that
Yes
Worst
Even if I can't eat it
What?
I know I can't eat it
I don't know
What?
I'm a broadcast writer
I can eat it
I have a store
You have a store?
What are you riding now?
Itasha
What's Itasha?
Italian car
Italian car?
Fiat Panda
Small car
I have a strong will
If I like you
I'll do it
I'm old
I have money
He has money
He has a pearl
What do you think?
It's good
It's good?
Everyone, please press the number
Let's go
Switch on
No.1
Let's see who pressed
Let's see
No.2
No
This is tough
It can't be helped
Let's see the girl
No.5
Who did you choose?
Okamoto
What's the reaction?
It can't be helped
Let's see
No.6
No.2
Everyone, please press the number
I wanted them to be at least two
I wanted it
This is a ritual
Yes
Where?
Here
No, Takasu
You just lied
Shake
Yes
Ah
Did you get 8?
Ladies and
Gentlemen
Hello
Congratulations
What is this?
Let's shake hands
I'm pissed off
Kouhaku
Last year
When Kouhaku was on
He was on a TV show
I don't know why
Well
I asked you a question
Last year he was on a TV show
Next year he will be on a TV show
That's it
Next week
I will show you
The list
I don't know
Ryoko
Ryoko is not here
I don't know
Ishimine
There is a
I don't know
If you win the Grand Prix
You can be on Kouhaku
I want to be on Kouhaku
I am on
Ishimine
That's fine
That's a reward
Ishimine
What kind of panties are you wearing?
I can't see panties
That's a reward
That's fine
If I win
I am not doing my best this year
I want to be on Kouhaku
I say that
That's a reward
You guys
You guys are so annoying
I am
I am not doing my best
You are not doing your best
You are watching me being nervous at home
I am a geisha girl
Come out
I am not called a geisha girl
Geisha girls are red
Of course
I am a geisha girl
I look like a shimo
What?
You can't say that
Why do you look like a shimo?
You look like a shimo
The kid's book
Part 2 is out
Part 2
Pro-wrestling Jyuchin Matsumoto
The magic technique that is sealed in the world of pro-wrestling
Flying rolling sobat express
What kind of technique was it?
Pro-wrestling
Yes
Many pro-wrestling schools
What do you mean?
In the end
Everyone gets together once a month
There are parties
Do you belong to any group?
Yes, I do.
Which group?
Well...
I'm a masked wrestler.
Yuta Akagi?
That's right.
I'm almost blind.
Masked wrestler?
Can I ask your name?
No, that's...
If you say that, people will find out.
There's a gathering.
There is.
And then...
Last year?
Yes.
Sakaguchi Seiji said,
I won't quit.
He's the new president.
Who made this technique?
It was done by Grey and Kojikaga.
No one knows.
It became popular in the area.
Is that so?
Yes.
But it's a magical technique.
A sealed magical technique.
It's too dangerous.
I see.
Yes.
This is related to life and death.
I won't quit.
You won't quit?
Yes.
It's similar to eye-killing and kicking.
It's similar?
No, it's not like that.
What do you call it?
It turns blue.
No matter what kind of technique you use, it turns blue.
It hurts.
Even if I go home for a while, it turns blue.
I can't see my wife's eyes.
If you do that.
What?
I want to see it.
It's a technique that turns blue.
I won't quit.
Seiji Sakaguchi said it.
At first, it was called Sakaguchi-chan.
Sakaguchi-chan?
Sakaguchi-chan.
Tameuchi?
Yes, I did.
Let's get rid of it.
Everyone was against it.
Only Grey and Kojikaga were against it.
That's right.
You made it.
I said I wanted to do it, but I thought it was okay.
So this time, I quit.
Rolling Sobat Express.
Flying, right?
Flying.
I decided to quit.
What kind of technique do you use?
There are only two of us.
If I quit, you'll be the one who gets kicked.
It turns blue.
I can't see my wife's face when I go home.
My wife comes out to congratulate me.
At that time, I can't say anything.
I can't help it.
I want to see it.
What about the damage?
I'll explain the damage in 10 stages.
This is 9.5 damage.
What about the rest 5?
10 is death.
It came out.
What?
I touched it.
What is this?
I told you to set a trap.
What about now?
What?
That was the Sobat Express.
What about me now?
It's a joke.
I was surprised.
Let's fall forward.
Let's fall backward.
Which way?
Backward.
Let's go.
When it comes like this, it goes in like this.
This is the Flying Express Sobat.
That's why I said it.
What is the first thing to be careful about when you go to the bank?
Is there anything you have to be careful about?
Yes, of course.
First of all, you have to be careful when you go to the bank.
When you go to the bank?
You have to be careful when you go to the bank.
Avoid Sunday.
Do you mean that there are a lot of people?
It's not open.
You should go because it's not open.
No, no.
I'm talking about the so-called bank robbery.
Be quiet.
I'm talking to Ceron.
Who are you talking to?
I'm talking to a thief.
This is the first thing to do when you go to the bank.
I see.
What should I bring with me?
What?
When I go to the bank.
Basically, I don't need anything.
What? A wallet?
Are you kidding me?
What?
You have to be careful when you go to the bank.
First of all, you have to be careful about the time.
Avoid Sunday.
And then...
Don't make a note.
I can't make it there.
Don't wear sandals.
I can't run away.
Make it warm.
That's right.
Why?
You can't wear it if it's cold.
If it's cold, I'll catch a cold.
I don't understand.
What?
You can't wear it if it's cold.
See?
I'm telling you what you can't do.
Listen.
You can't wear it if it's cold.
You can't wear it if you're sleepy.
You can't use it on your dogs.
You can wear it on your feet.
You can't eat sweets.
People will think I'm an idiot.
A long time ago, a boy scout even worked as the branch manager of the Western Japan branch.
The genius of games, Mr. Matsumoto.
What kind of fun game can you do with a 10-yen coin?
Please give it a try.
I don't have a 10-yen coin.
Here you go.
How do you enjoy using this 10-yen coin?
That's right.
Like this, right?
I'll go first, right?
Go ahead.
I'll go first.
Here you go.
Three points.
Oh, you lost the reverse point.
You lost the big reverse point.
I won.
I lost the big reverse point.
Here you go.
66 points.
What?
I didn't get anything.
Okay, let's do it properly.
Let's do it properly.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Look over there.
The one holding this is the winner.
Let's use this to play.
Okay, let's play.
Okay?
Front or back?
Oh, okay.
Ready, set, go.
Front.
This is the same point.
Ready, set, go.
Back.
You're good.
Okay, let's go.
What's funny?
Let's go home.
Can you do it?
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.
The fishing boat sank in the Noto Peninsula and six crew members are missing.