Good evening!
What is today's topic?
Today, we are going to talk about the 7th part that many talents have challenged
This is the first part
I see
Please watch the masterpiece
We have to look back on this
There is a history
Don't wear it with your lungs
Why are you wearing it with your lungs?
In the past, these people have challenged
The one in red is a talent
The one in black is an amateur
Bob Sapp is...
The newest
53,000 yen
This is the first part
Please look at this
I see
There are many people who want to challenge
7th part?
Yes
Like Takeshi Kaneshiro
I want to see it
And Kimimaro
Koji Aoyama
I want to see it
He has already done the first part
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
The history of the 7th part that many talents have challenged
It started 8 years ago from Hitoshi Matsumoto
The rule is that the challenger appears in the middle of the meeting
If you laugh at his appearance, you will be fined and it will be very simple
That's why people ask for your sense of humor
Today we will reveal the masterpiece of the 7th part
The 10 masterpiece of the 7th part
First of all, the first challenger, Hosei Yamasaki
Yamasaki likes Suga-chan
I like Suga-chan and Yamasaki
Really?
I wonder what happened
I have no choice but to think about it
I don't know
I don't spend much money
It's cold when you come to the prefecture
I want to throw up
I don't know
I don't know what's going on
Next is the masterpiece of the masterpiece of the masterpiece
Next is the masterpiece of the masterpiece
The light went out and he asked me to do it again
Next is Tanaka Kokoriko who got 40,000 yen
I want to see the family fight
It's dirty
Next is Tanaka Kokoriko who got 40,000 yen
Next is Matsumoto producer Bob Sapp
Next is Matsumoto producer Hoshihori Oba-chan