Good evening!
Well, well, well...
I've been doing this for a long time.
I'm not sure if I'm clapping or not.
Well, well, well...
It's exactly like that.
Well, thank you very much.
There's nothing.
Normally, there's something like this, right?
There are times like this.
I've been doing this for a long time.
There are times like this, right?
What kind of public program is that?
There are times like this.
There are times like this, right?
Today, I'm out.
What do you mean, you're out?
It's all because of you!
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
I'm sorry, but this is only the first time.
It can't be helped.
Have you been somewhere?
I've been to Hawaii.
At this time of year...
What?
In Hawaii...
It's been four years since I've been to Hawaii.
Really?
I've been to Guam.
You haven't been there, have you?
No, that's not it.
I haven't been to Hawaii.
What?
What do you mean?
I had to take a day off.
Are you kidding me?
That's why it's so luxurious.
It's elegant.
That's what it is.
It's like that.
It's like a veranda.
It's wonderful.
What are you talking about?
It's hot in Guam.
Why is that?
It's cold in Hawaii.
It's warm during the day.
When the sun goes down a little.
I'd like to be able to say that.
Why don't you go?
The flight time is the limit in Guam.
Oh, really?
If it's longer than that, I'll be sick.
I feel like a little crab is coming out of my mouth.
It's like a little crab in miso soup.
I want to see it, so let's go together.
I haven't been to Los Angeles, so it'll take some time.
It's different from that.
I don't want to have a reporter.
I want to sell the feeling of being at home like you.
It's like waiting for a life insurance commercial.
It's just once a year.
Going out there.
That's right.
It's a little broken in the typhoon in Guam.
There were a lot of cancellations.
That's right.
How were the people?
There weren't many people.
It's empty.
I didn't have much stress this year.
How do you say it?
Signs, handshakes.
But if there aren't many people, I can't see you.
It's lonely at night, isn't it?
It's lonely at night.
It's not lonely at night.
It's the same in Tokyo.
That's right.
I understand that.
It's not like that every year.
It's not like that.
How is it?
There are people who make you angry.
That's right.
Why is that?
They come to you and say,
The children want your autograph.
They don't care about what the children say.
They say, I'm sorry.
What?
No, no, no, no, no.
That's impossible.
Even though the children are saying it.
I'm getting angry.
No, no, no, no.
It's very likely.
That's right.
At the airport, at the airport on the way home,
They came again.
The children.
It's their birthday.
That's not true.
They said, I'll take a picture.
I said, I'm sorry because it's my birthday, too.
It's September.
I was like, what?
Is that true?
It was over.
I was on the plane.
The plane was quite empty.
I was relaxed.
I said, it's okay.
I was playing with my headphones.
The sound of the headphones was cut out.
You think something happened, right?
It was so loud.
There was a birthday guest on board today.
Why?
Why is it someone else's birthday?
I don't know if I should wake them up.
I don't even know why they stopped the song.
Please look at the screen in front of you.
I said, happy birthday.
It's true.
I said, I'll give you this coffee cup.
The coffee cup went up.
I can't get it.
What's wrong with me?
The people around you are like this.
What's wrong with the people around me?
The people around me must have woken up.
That service is definitely wrong.
I don't know about that.
When I think about it, it's his birthday.
I said it earlier.
Think about it the other way around.
On your birthday, if you get on the plane, you'll get hit.
But you can't say, it's this person.
You can't say, it's this person.
But it's embarrassing.
When I was in a hurry, there was a birthday person on this plane.
His face was red.
I thought he didn't know.
He came to the party and gave me a coffee cup.
That's right.
It was good in Hawaii.
That's not true.
I want to go to Hawaii too.
You should go.
Where did everyone go?
Did you hear?
Heihei Shimizu came with me.
He said he was going to eat and the next day he went to play golf.
I said it was morning and he said he wouldn't come.
He came back only at night.
I asked him why he didn't come.
He said he was pulled by a black man.
He was not pulled by a black man.
He was pulled by a black man.
A black man?
I asked him if he wanted to go to the toilet.
He said he didn't want to go.
He went to the doctor because he was in pain.
He said he was broken.
What's wrong with you?
No, the black guy pulled my leg.
Don't say things like that.
The black guy...
The black guy pulled your leg.
The black guy's bike or car, right?
I don't like that.
Do you know Kim?
He's always traveling.
This year too, when we're going to Guam from tomorrow...
The water sign?
He said his hand was numb.
His hand was numb.
He's always traveling.
The day before, Miuchi would come.
He said he was going to Okinawa from tomorrow, but Miuchi was taking care of him.
In the end, he said it was okay.
He said he couldn't go to Guam.
He said he'd take him to the airport.
While he was driving to the airport, he would cry.
He was frustrated.
He didn't know.
I couldn't go.
He was frustrated.
He would cry.
Shut up.
I'm serious.
Ask him.
I'm going to cry.
You're making fun of him.
He's the one.
I'm serious.
In Guam, there was a water sign.
I had a cramp in my neck.
There were four of us.
The three of us didn't scream.
But basically, we kept going.
That's fun.
We were screaming.
I had a cramp in my neck.
What happened before that?
About two days before we went to Okinawa,
we failed the three times.
We failed the three times.
We all thought it was strange.
We went to a hot spring.
The next day, we went to Okinawa.
I was wondering if it was okay to go to a hot spring.
I had a cramp in my neck.
I thought it was strange.
The three juniors were all wet.
I said, let's do a skinhead.
He said, I don't want to.
I said, really?
We went to a hot spring.
We borrowed about 30 security cameras.
We did a skinhead.
I said, that's cool.
It was midsummer.
The next day, we went to Oiso Long Beach.
I was excited.
We went to Oiso Long Beach.
The sun was...
I was weak.
It was a skinhead.
My skin was getting used to it.
A person who didn't have anything suddenly had a skinhead.
It was midsummer.
I was in a good mood.
There was a cute girl.
The girl was cute.
The girl looked at me and laughed.
I was in a good mood.
I put on my goggles.
I couldn't get in.
I slipped and couldn't get in.
The girl laughed at me.
I was in a good mood.
When I got home, my head was shaking.
You were in a good mood.
I looked like a lychee.
I was translucent.
I was blue.
The car was about to leave.
We went to Oiso Long Beach.
I was driving.
My head was hot.
I turned the towel over.
From behind.
How much should I turn it over?
There were three signals.
I was caught in a traffic jam.
I couldn't turn it over at all.
If I had escaped, I would have been killed.
That's true.
I don't know the reason.
I don't know the situation.
I have a question for Matsumoto.
There is a place called Kawanabi.
If you go there, you will be attacked.
Where is it?
I have never heard of it.
I think it exists.
Tell me if you have experienced it.
I have.
Where is it?
There are many places.
There are many places?
Where?
Think that you are Kawanabi.
There are many things that happen.
Why?
For example.
If you are called youth, you will be in trouble.
This is serious.
Can I talk about serious things?
Please talk about this too.
I will talk about serious things.
Where do you use Kawanabi?
Panasonic.
If you use Kawanabi against Panasonic's rival company, you won't get out.
Rival company?
Yes, other than Kawanabi.
What do you mean by try?
If you want to go to Pioneer...
It's a lie that you won't get out.
What is this?
It doesn't mean that you won't get out.
I don't know.
I don't know that Kanabi is lying.
I don't lie.
I can't lie.
I don't know that nuance.
What is your type?
If you want to go to Pioneer, you can go like this.
If you play Sonic the Hedgehog as a pioneer, you'll be like...
Just kidding.
Just a little.
Just a little!
But you still have to say it.
Well, it's a little...
It's a little...
That's a little...
Just kidding!
No, no, no. Please tell me. I want to hear that.
I've been scolded so many times.
By the firecrackers.
Where? Where?
Hey.
Don't ask me those things.
Your firecrackers...
Firecrackers are mostly women, right?
Yes, yes. They come out first, right?
Women...
Standing there.
Standing there, right?
Yes, standing.
They'll turn into old men.
Hey.
No, no. It's not like that.
When the firecrackers come out,
At the beginning, there's a woman standing there.
That's long. That's annoying.
She's standing there.
Yes, she's standing.
What about that?
That woman will turn into an old man.
Yes, she'll turn into an old man.
No, I mean, she'll push that woman like this.
And the old man will say,
Hey!
If you do something like that.
But the firecrackers come out first, right?
Yes, yes.
After that, they'll turn into an old man.
After they turn into an old man, the old man will go like this.
Say something like that.
Where is it?
Tell me where it is.
I want to try it.
If I put it there, will the old man come out? Tell me.
Umm...
My dream, right?
What a fool.
It's okay. I'll tell you where it is.
Please.
If you tell me like this,
the whole of Japan will panic.
Who are you?
Are you okay with that?
What is that?
No.
If I put it there, will the old man come out?
You think you can do anything.
Let me do it on my way home.
You're so easy.
If I put it there, will the old man come out?
I can't put it there, so tell me where it is.
If all the people here do that,
you'll panic.
Everyone can't be sure that they're driving.
This is discrimination.
You're told that you can only ride a bus.
If you say that, you'll panic.
This is a question for Mr. Matsumoto, who is more familiar with baseball than the Americans.
I'm familiar with baseball.
Next season, please tell me the necessary rules for Matsui to play in the major leagues.
It's okay.
Really?
Tell me.
What is it?
Please tell me the necessary rules for Matsui to play in the major leagues.
This is really Matsui...
Matsui, are you watching?
I don't know if you're watching or not.
I don't know if your acquaintance is watching and teaching you.
Shut up!
Please tell me.
Go home!
What?
You can't go home.
Please tell me the necessary rules for Matsui to play in the major leagues.
What are you doing?
Tell me the necessary rules for Matsui to play in the major leagues.
I think Matsui is under great pressure.
That's right.
He is expected by the Japanese people.
I think Matsui is under great pressure.
That's right.
So...
Do your best!
Matsui, listen to me.
Stand up.
I'll send you an A.
It's a writing exercise.
There are five.
If you protect this...
It's okay when you protect this.
You can play.
I really want you to deliver this to Matsui.
I didn't see it and I didn't go.
Do you deliver it or not?
I won't do it if you don't deliver it.
I can deliver it.
Really?
I'll send you an A.
I'll send you a message.
Matsue...
Do your best, Akane!
Don't go so low!
Are you listening, Matsue?
Yes, I'm listening.
You...
It can't be helped, Matsue.
What's that sound?
Let's start with that part.
Let's drop it once.
Drop it once and then raise it.
Listen, Matsue!
How long are you going to do that?
What's wrong with you?
Your belt is here, isn't it?
It's strange, isn't it?
There's a fire in the center!
Listen, Matsue!
From now on, Matsue!
Matsue!
You just want to say, Matsue, don't you?
Say it, Kaki Kokeko!
From now on...
Say it, say it.
From now on, for you to do your best on this show...
Kaki Kokeko!
Say it!
Listen, Matsue!
Matsue!
I've already drawn it.
If you can't protect this...
I'll tell you to die.
You don't have enough words.
I don't have enough words.
I don't have that kind of stupidity, Matsue!
I'm sorry!
Matsue, I'm sorry.
Listen to me.
Let's go!
Matsue!
You don't have to say, Matsue.
It's true that I've been saying it for a while.
Matsue!
Let's go!
Matsue, listen to me.
Matsue, look at me!
Not you, look at me.
Matsue!
Matsue, are you crying?
This is a question for Matsumoto-san, who has been sleeping with Hamada-san's wife for 5 years.
It seems that you recently went on a trip to Guam with Hamada-san's wife.
Please tell us about that trip.
Well...
I was wondering when this letter would arrive.
Well, Shikari Shuganjosei.
Shikari Asahigeino.
I was wondering when I would get a scoop.
Were you nervous?
I was nervous.
I contacted three of them.
Hey, why is your voice so small?
Are you okay?
I'm okay!
So, in conclusion, I'm okay.
You were with your wife.
No, no, no.
That happened.
I see.
But it can't be helped.
This is the most interesting part.
I understand that.
In conclusion, I'm okay.
To be honest, there was a phone call when we were shooting the opening scene.
While I was worrying about you,
I said,
Hey, wife!
Are you okay?
I was doing it.
Did you go to Guam?
Well...
Well,
From the second day,
I went to Guam three times.
I pretended to go to Hawaii.
I see.
I came quickly.
It was amazing.
It was...
You know,
This kind of dangerous love,
or dangerous love,
makes people angry.
I see.
That's why I said,
Hold me.
I said almost nothing but,
You liar!
Shut up!
How many times do I have to tell you?
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.