Gaki no Tsukai's famous project, Hichihenge.
A bold idea, a secret acting, and the power to read the atmosphere.
The challenger will use all of these powers to transform into the 7 main characters.
It's a serious battle that will make the audience laugh.
The challenger this time is this man, director Otomo.
The first episode of Gaki no Tsukai, Chikizuki!
Director Otomo Yuji, Hichihenge!
To be honest, we always decide on the opening act after it's over.
The challenger was in a hurry because he had to go to the bathroom.
I'm about to cry.
Otomo, please.
Here you go, Otomo.
This is the record for money.
The winner is Isomata.
Isomata is the winner.
How confident are you?
Well, I've been laughing a lot.
Who's laughing?
Here's the opening act.
What's this?
Writer Takasuke Otako.
I've been here before, but he's moved.
This is easy to do.
There's about 30 stories, so I can't go crazy.
This is amazing.
How about Kokoriko?
Maybe Tanaka can use it.
There's a lot of reaction.
If you look at it like that, I'm done too.
All the staff are involved in this, right?
That's right.
I think it's better to hold back the loss here.
There was a scene in Isawa, right?
If you shake the camera at Yamazaki, it'll fall.
Really?
What should I do?
Yamazaki, right?
Not yet.
Not yet?
No, it's my turn.
No, I don't know.
It's okay.
Did you see my feet?
I saw it.
I was laughing at my feet.
Speed skating.
I was wondering what I was doing at first.
I was waiting for my turn.
You're moving to Yamazaki, right?
I want to move.
I heard you're looking for a house.
You're looking for a house, right?
I'm looking for a house, but I'm looking for a house.
I'm moved.
Thank you very much.
How many times have you seen it?
I'm moved.
Thank you very much.
That's what it is.
What should I say?
You can go to Kokoriko.
It's like you went to Yamazaki.
Next, I'm going to Shinohara.
You're going to Yamazaki, right?
I'm going to Kurukuru.
I'm going to Merhe.
I'm going to Shinohara.
You're fast.
But you're going to sleep in that.
I'm going to sleep in that.
What should I do?
What should I do if I get kicked out?
I have no choice but to get kicked out.
You're so persistent.
I didn't think you'd be so worried about it.
Why aren't you getting married?
I want to get married.
I'm getting older.
Kurukuru.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Where do you live?
You're too young!
Hey!
Why did you choose this?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know either.
How was it?
7, 8, 9, 29,000
You're the best!
You were dancing at the top.
I can say this now, but it was a little cold in Shinohara.
We're going to have another talk with the players.
It's the second time today.
It's been a while.
There's one more thing.
It's going up.
I don't know what you're talking about.
First of all,
What?
You said you were a crazy talent, right?
Yes.
When you said you wanted to use Toshio Matsumoto for a commercial,
You said you couldn't do it because of the schedule.
The next one to come is...
The last one is Katsura.
If I can't do it, I'll be the second one to come to the top.
Really?
You're not what I thought you were.
You know what I mean, right?
Who's the one who said B?
If I had to add one more thing to this,
I think I should add a similar animal.
I'm definitely a leopard.
It doesn't matter.
A leopard, right?
Isn't that right?
You're like...
You're like Ayu, right?
Are you really saying what you think?
Do I look like Ayu?
Ayu or something like that.
It's not like that.
The sport I can't go to is...
Basketball.
What's that?
If you're that tall, you'll win.
Little by little,
When basketball started,
Now everyone's in a different mood.
So if it's about five meters long,
Everyone has the same conditions.
You don't have the same conditions.
It's not like you can grab a bank and say,
You can't grab a bank and say,
At that point,
What's that?
There's a lot of such things, so it's fun.
Small games like that are fun.
Everyone shakes it like this.
It's fun.
It's fun because you're gonna jump in and kick it.
It's funny because you can't stop it.
Why? The little one is so desperate.
Don't be so f*****g stupid.
You're f*****g stupid.
Don't explain it.
You don't need to explain it.
You're f*****g stupid.
It's funny.
I just did it.
Then, I want to decide.
What?
I want to decide.
I thought it was here.
Then, please take it.
It's here.
You can't say that.
You're f*****g stupid.
How can I make you laugh?
I don't want to make you laugh here.
I want to see your f*****g face.
It's difficult to make you laugh here.
I'll make you laugh here.
This is difficult.
What is this?
Say something.
I can't do it.
What do you want to do now?
Battle Royale.
I've said it many times.
I'm getting anxious.
I wonder if there was such a thing.
Battle Royale.
It seems fun.
It's not fun.
But if it's 4 people, 4 people.
If it's 4 people, 5 people.
While one person is fighting,
the other person is like this.
There are other people who can talk.
I can't do it.
I feel like it's fun.
I feel like it's a party.
First of all, come and see.
I'll film the front.
It's more fun.
When is it? Battle Royale.
That's right.
This year.
There are 3 people.
Yes, I do.
Is someone coming?
I've already decided.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Well, I definitely want to do Sasuke.
I have Sasuke.
What about the others?
Well, I have a few others.
You don't have any?
Well, I'll hold down the seat.
Well, take my hand.
I'm begging you!
I'm really begging you!
Where are you holding down?
Matsumoto-san, you've been riding on the backs of many beasts since you were a child.
What is the animal that took the longest time to ride on your back?
Ah...
Wait, let me ask you first.
Yes.
What kind of animal have you ridden on?
Well, when I was a child, I rode on a rhino.
What did I ride on before that?
I don't have a picture of that time, so I don't know.
You don't remember anything other than a rhino, do you?
I remember. When I was a child, I rode on a rhino.
So you remember what happened after that?
I remember what happened after that.
What are you talking about? Are you angry?
Are you crying?
Who's crying?
I'm angry.
So you started riding on a rhino.
My life.
When I was a child, I rode on a rhino.
You rode on a rhino.
I don't remember that.
But I've been riding on a rhino since I was a child.
Oh, you've been riding on a rhino since you were a child?
Do you remember?
No, I don't.
I remember riding on a rhino.
You remember riding on a rhino.
That's what I'm saying.
Why are you so excited?
I remember riding on a rhino.
You said, let's go from there.
It's not riding on a rhino, it's riding on a rhino.
I don't understand that.
I don't like it.
It's over a rhino.
I'm a rhino.
I don't remember riding on a rhino at all.
You don't know the difference between a rhino and a rhino.
This is a baby.
Baby.
Baby rhino.
I said rhino.
Baby.
Baby rhino.
But this has a soul.
It's a rhino.
Tell me from here.
What did you ride on from here?
That's what I'm saying.
How many have a soul?
Well...
18.
18?
It's okay, it's 18.
Tell me after 18.
I rode on a rhino until I was 20 years old.
What did you change?
I don't know what to change.
I don't know how many years I've been riding on a rhino.
I'll tell you simply.
I've been riding on a rhino for two years, and I've been riding on a rhino for seven years.
What?
I don't have the feeling of being on a rhino.
At first, you were going wild.
I was riding on a rhino, and he was riding on a rhino, too.
There was a fight between me and the rhino.
There was.
He was doing this on purpose.
But you were falling.
Who's going to fall?
I see.
It was a great feeling.
Yes.
It was a great unit.
You're going to ride on a rhino anyway, aren't you?
I was waiting at the front door in the morning.
I really wanted to change that.
I didn't like it.
I understand that.
I had an affair.
Who?
You?
I had an affair with a rhino, too.
Both of you?
I said, let's stop.
When I asked the rhino, he said, I have someone else I want to ride on.
That's a good thing.
I understand that.
What did you ride on after that?
Then there was a new rhino.
A rhino?
It was a completely different rhino.
I rode on it for about half a year.
When it came to me, I was tired.
The previous one.
He was looking at me.
I thought it was a bad habit of the previous one.
Is it hard to ride on a tiger or a lion?
It's hard to ride on that.
But you rode on it, didn't you?
I rode on it.
That's amazing.
For example, how long did it take you to ride on a rhino?
Two months.
But it took two months.
It took half a year to ride on a lion.
That's a long time.
I think I'll get in trouble if I get a letter.
You'll get in trouble.
At that time, I thought I shouldn't get a letter.
It's hard to ride on a lion.
I was told that I shouldn't get a letter.
Is it okay?
It's a movie if you like it.
Are you angry?
I don't know how it is.
It's a movie.
It took half a year.
How long did it take you to ride on a lion?
It took more time than I thought when I rode on a lion.
I'll tell you the truth.
I rode on a lion smoothly.
I see.
But it's not impossible.
I'll tell you the story.
Amaryllis.
When I'm in the dressing room, I always...
When I'm in the dressing room, I always massage your tired body.
I have a question for Mr. Matsumoto.
Please tell me the true identity of cataclysm.
Do you know what cataclysm is?
Originally, it was called catacorins.
I'm saying it in a short way.
Catacorins are cataclysm.
Catacorins are catacorins.
What?
It's strange.
I don't know.
But you know the true identity of cataclysm, right?
Of course I know.
Please tell me.
In the end, cataclysm is not a good thing.
That's why it's called catacorins.
Everyone doesn't know.
I don't know.
Why?
It's not catacorins.
You're making a great discovery.
How to cure catacorins.
I'm going to tell you how to get rid of catacorins.
Who discovered it?
How much?
I'm saying that.
Really?
First of all, I have to think that I can't do it.
I see.
You can't do it.
That's why.
There's a difference between you and me.
I see.
You might get angry if I say this.
Well, you won't get angry.
But you might get angry.
What?
Everyone doesn't know.
Then let's say it.
Catacorins have a stupid face.
You have a stupid face.
You have a stupid face now.
You wake up early every morning and do a two-hour fitness on the balcony.
Mr. Matsumoto with a sexy body.
Yes.
I haven't pooped for two weeks.
It's a complete constipation.
What should I do?
Let's say it in English.
Say whatever you want.
Just say it.
Rilla.
Mr. Matsumoto is standing up.
I think he can still do it.
Trust me.
Are you okay?
If you think you can't do it, you'll fall down right away.
Human beings are always a little bit powerful.
At any time.
I see.
Even if you tell me to relax my body, I'm sure it's somewhere.
Yes.
By releasing that power,
I can poop as much as I want.
I see.
But the power of the body is opening pores.
It's opening all the pores.
It's getting a little bigger.
All the pores are getting bigger.
The body is getting a little bigger.
It's getting a little bigger.
All the pores are opening.
Then it's already dry.
My body and my eyes are all broken.
Well, you're right.
You should have stopped me.
You should have stopped me at that time.
What should I say?
I want you to stop me even if you hit me.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.
Thank you for your viewing.