This is Kawaguchiko, which is also known as the holy place for bus fishing.
It's been exactly a year since Downtown first challenged the black bass.
The match between Tsurishi and Itoi was a huge victory with Hamada hitting 47cm.
In the first round of the Tsuri Championship, Matsumoto defeated a strong opponent and won the championship.
And now, to aim for this trophy, the best anglers in the entertainment industry have gathered here in Kawaguchiko.
The second round of the Tsuri Championship, Tsurishi!
Mr. Tsurishi.
Yes, yes.
The second round.
That's right.
You're the champion of the first round.
Thank you very much.
By the way, when the champion won the first round, the black bass...
He won with 28cm.
Thank you very much.
And you won the trophy.
I brought it home today.
Oh, really?
Yes, yes.
So this is the second round.
Yes, it was a good experience.
We have a lot of fishing-loving entertainers here.
Yes, yes.
Let's start with Itoi Ishigesato!
Hello.
From the first round, it was Itoi Ishigesato who made this corner.
Originally, he dragged us into the corner and lost to me.
He gave me a humble personality.
Itoi-san, you have to stop that dad joke for the time being.
Thank you for your time today.
Thank you very much.
Next up is Okuda Tamiyo!
Tamiyo-chan, how are you doing?
How are you feeling?
Please take it home.
I'm fine.
This is a little dangerous, isn't it?
I bought something that was a little expensive.
It's your own suffering.
It's pretty good.
Next up is Eiji Yosuke!
From the first round...
The first round was a boy.
It was just a boy.
A boy is not angry.
I'm angry.
If you raise the ball, you can use a small one.
How many minutes do you have?
I want to fish today.
The staff is pretty good.
It's nothing.
It's just an image.
This time, the 8th place is...
Miyata Kazuya!
Are you fishing too?
Yes, I'm fishing.
Everyone is fishing.
You like Mifuji, don't you?
How are you feeling today?
This is my second time fishing in Kawaguchiko.
I've caught five fish in the past.
I call Kawaguchiko an easy lake.
If I can't catch anything today...
You have to think about it a little.
I'm going to cut off all my hair.
I'm not happy about anyone's trouble.
There's no loss or anything.
Everyone, the rule is...
I'll give you two hours.
If you catch a big fish in less than two hours, you win.
How long is it?
It's the same length as my dad.
Dad joke for two hours.
I'm going to shut up.
Let's go, everyone.
Departure!
The second fishing competition is about to begin!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
I've been fishing since this morning, so I'm sleepy.
That's the problem.
I'll win, right? I'm sure.
I'm here again.
I'm a sunburned old man.
I'm going to be in a bad mood today.
I'm a professional.
I've never lost. I'll do my best.
I don't think I'll be able to catch a big fish.
I've got a big hook.
I'll do my best.
I'm going to fish today.
I can't lose to Tamiya.
I'll do my best.
I'm the winner.
The weather is perfect for fishing.
Unfortunately, it's the hardest time to catch fish.
Can he catch a fish?
Itoi's main boat is Matsumoto.
Hamada and Miyata are on this boat.
In addition, Okuda and Eguchi get on the same boat.
Damn it.
You're all sensitive, aren't you?
He quickly caught a black bass.
It's big.
As expected of a bass pro.
Itoi and Miyata easily caught a black bass.
Okuda.
Yes.
Don't give it to Eguchi.
You can't say it's a manga.
I can't.
No one is talking to me.
Itoi and Miyata easily caught a black bass.
Don't give it to Eguchi.
Please take a picture of it.
I'll write your face on it.
It's Shinbo.
Is it Shinbo?
Is Shinbo your father's line?
A little.
It's not the other way around.
Hamada is lying down with a fishing rod.
Will he be able to catch a black bass?
Or has he already given up?
On the other hand, Matsumoto doesn't even have a fishing rod.
It's time to eat.
Is this the result of the earthquake that won the last time?
A black bass has fallen.
Please catch a black bass.
Matsumoto is a fisherman who loves nature.
He picks up a bag with a fishing rod.
This is a bad place.
No one is coming.
Hamada, Miyata, Eguchi, and Okuda are moving to find a fishing spot.
Will they find the best fishing spot?
Hamada, I caught a black bass.
I caught a black bass.
I want to help you when you don't have a fishing rod.
It's been an hour since they started fishing.
Eguchi's rod is broken.
It's big.
Are you serious?
Eguchi, who was a bad fisherman last time, is one step ahead.
If that's how it's going to be, I can't stand it anymore.
Eguchi caught a black bass.
Miyata caught a black bass.
Miyata also caught a black bass.
It's small.
It's better to catch a black bass in the front.
It's a shame.
It's better than a black bass.
Okuda also caught a black bass.
It's big.
This is a big fish.
This is big.
Hamada caught a black bass.
Really?
Are you serious?
Hamada can't hide his frustration.
On the other hand, Matsumoto is about to give up.
Can I go over there?
Let's go.
It's been half an hour.
Itoi Matsumoto is going to a new point.
And Hamada Miyata.
Shall we go?
At that time, he tried to change the point.
It's coming.
It's easy.
This is good.
It's big.
Wonderful.
This is a victory.
Look.
It's being swallowed.
Come on.
Let's stay here a little longer.
It's coming.
It's a big fish.
He caught a big fish.
It's coming.
It's a mini bass.
It's small.
It's a black bass that looks like an eel.
It's shallow.
He threw it without a hook.
Is it Okuda's pride?
He released it too small.
I have a fish of this size.
He caught two fish in a row.
I saw it in the picture.
On the other hand, they are fighting for a new point.
Matsumoto and Itoi.
I can't catch it.
I caught it.
Finally, Itoi caught a fish.
It's small, but I caught it.
It flew like a kite.
But I caught it.
I caught it again.
He caught a fish at once.
An hour and a half has passed.
Matsumoto and Hamada are the only ones who have not caught a fish.
I caught it.
Finally, Hamada caught a fish.
I caught a fish again.
Will the 47 cm fish be caught?
I caught a fish.
I caught a fish again.
Is this a black bass?
Stop it.
Rockfish.
This is a rockfish.
Who hasn't caught a fish yet?
Tama and Matsumoto.
Matsumoto.
If I can't catch a fish, I'll catch another fish.
I'll try to catch a fish.
I don't care if I think it's my imagination.
This fish is heavy.
But I can't catch a fish.
That's the only difference.
I can use both.
I don't know.
This is a rockfish.
Hamada changes his hat to change his mood.
I caught a fish.
Is this a black bass?
This is a big fish.
I caught a fish.
Is this because he changed his hat?
Hamada caught a big fish.
This is a big fish.
I'm under pressure.
At the same time, Matsumoto changed his fishing rod.
This is a big fish.
This is big.
I caught a fish.
This is a big fish.
He caught a large fish.
Only a few hours left.
All the boats have gathered to the point where they can fish for the last time.
It hurts.
I was surprised.
Hamada doesn't have a fishing rod and shows a relaxed expression.
Is he confident in his victory?
It's getting dark and the time limit is near.
Downtown is challenging with a serious expression for the last game.
It's coming!
At the end of the game, Miyata catches a big fish.
Will Miyata turn the tables?
It's coming!
It's like the last scene of Platone.
It's going well.
It's over.
It's big, isn't it?
It's not small, but it's not big.
It's big.
You should have been a cannon.
Everyone is tired.
I'm a winning candidate.
You said it was long.
My stomach is dented, but it's long.
Six warriors who have been playing fishing battles have returned.
Who will the goddess of victory smile at?
Everyone is fishing, so it's fun to fish.
It was fun.
It's perfect.
The results are out!
The long battle is over.
Everyone has caught a big fish.
It doesn't matter if it's a big fish or not.
It's Itoi's turn.
Excuse me.
Itoi has caught a lot of fish.
He said it was a big fish.
I caught four fish.
It's big.
Itoi's turn.
It's no good.
It's 36 cm.
I thought I could catch all four fish.
It's no good.
Thank you.
It's my turn.
It's a big fish.
It's 33 cm.
My goal was to beat Okuda.
It's about 33 cm.
It's a big fish.
It would be fun if I caught a big fish today.
It's at sea.
It's bent.
36 cm.
In addition to it, is it 7 cm?
I'm glad it was a 6 cm.
It's a big fish.
We can give you a towel if you weigh it.
I don't need it.
Maybe a big fish was boiled on the ship.
This is a big fish.
It's about the same for everyone, right?
If you add it up, it's 5, 5, 6, right?
It's about the same.
Then, it's my turn.
It's big, isn't it?
It's not big, it's my turn.
It's big.
What should I do?
Everyone's doing it.
Do it yourself.
I'm scared. I'm a fairy.
It's big.
It's a good bus.
It's heavy.
I don't understand the meaning of a good bus.
It's a good bus.
It's big.
I dropped it, too.
I'll do it.
Which one is solid?
It's me.
It's 5.
It's 7.
It's the top.
Now, Mr. Matsumoto.
If I don't go to 37,
I can't win.
If you go over 37,
I'll give you a double shot.
It's big.
Everyone, do it.
It's a double shot.
It's big.
It's light.
It doesn't matter how heavy it is.
Let's do it.
It's a double shot.
Look at the dents on the belly.
It's broken.
It's a double shot.
Let's take pictures with the fishes.
Put it in the middle.
It's big.
If you get it, it's 40.
Hang in there, you'll win.
I'll give you a trophy.
Thank you very much.
It's the first time I've won.
This is the second.
It's delicious.
The winner.
No.1 is Gaki and No.1 is Shibata.
Everyone's names are in there.
Look, it's kind of unique.
No.2 is me. I'm No.2.
No.3 is Ebushi.
No.4 is Hitori.
No.5 is Miyata.
No.5 is Tamino.
No.6 is Hiroshi.
No.7 is Tamiya.
No.8 is Nobe.
No.9 is Nobe.
No.10 is Nobe.
No.11 is Nobe.
No.12 is Nobe.
No.13 is Nobe.
No.14 is Nobe.
No.15 isTERRY.
No.16 is Hiroshi.
No.17 is Nobe.
No.18 is Nobe.
No.19 is Nobe.
Tamiya is Hiroshi.
No.22 is Nobe.
No.23 is Nobe.
No.24 is Hiroshi.
No.25 is Nobe.
No.26 is Hiroshi.
Who will be able to win the golden trophy?
Downtown Osorubeshi
This time I will definitely win
I say it every time
Thank you for your hard work
I understand that the downtown wall was unexpectedly hot
I will do my best next time
Goodbye
There are many lines that I want to catch
On the contrary, I feel that it was not good because it was read by the bus
Please invite me again
I didn't think it would be beautiful
Excuse me
I want to aim for the next big trophy
I will do my best
Thank you very much
I'm sorry
Goodbye