Today, our guest, Mr. Aigata, will be doing a punishment game.
I've already lost, so I can't help it.
By the way, if you saw the punishment game this morning, please raise your hand.
But most of the people were ignoring it.
It was about half of them.
They were like, oh, you're going to do it?
But you can see it today.
We went to the scene.
Was it a punishment game when we went?
Matsumoto-san was having fun.
Let's go to the main character of the day.
Please!
I don't want to leave without laughing.
Why?
Everyone hasn't seen it yet.
Why haven't you seen it yet?
I'll say this, but that was a punishment game.
Really?
You're having fun?
No, no, no, I'm not having fun at all.
To be honest, I haven't seen my dad in a while, and I thought,
I wonder if he's going to die.
Wow, that's true.
And then, I saw him in the middle of the night.
Seriously.
The next day, we were all going to Disneyland,
and my dad said he wasn't feeling well, and he was going home.
And when he went to Tokyo Station by himself,
he was in a daze and he fell down.
And the station staff said,
He was like an alien that was captured by the Japanese army.
He was like, Grandpa, you can't do this alone.
I said, sure.
I'm sure you can do it.
The Matsumoto vs. Hamada team has created a new chapter in the history of the children's use.
The regular running and jumping competition.
This fierce battle between the two teams was won by the Hamada team, who showed excellent teamwork.
The punishment game by Matsumoto Hitoshi has been decided.
The punishment game is...
Matsumoto Hitoshi!
The last one is...
You said it.
I said it.
What is it?
Why did you lose?
That's right.
Okay, okay.
The punishment is the punishment of the year of the horse.
You lost the other day.
Do you know what this is?
What is this?
It's like, sorry.
It's like the staff of the car wash.
I saw it. I saw it.
This is the jump of the problem that Heipon showed.
Now, I will announce the punishment of Mr. Matsumoto.
You are not alone.
Five people from the Matsumoto family will participate.
The five people are...
Who is it?
This person.
Mother.
Father.
Big brother.
Big sister.
Everyone.
First appearance, big sister!
Second appearance.
First appearance.
Is it okay?
In 5 minutes, Matsumotoge will do the Hero Award!
I'll do it.
This time, the punishment game is a Matsumoto-Renja-Ishou with 5 members from the Matsumoto family.
And we'll make a theme song, and the finished product will be broadcast live for 5 minutes.
Umm, overall, the age is already quite high.
The lowest is me, I'm 38 years old.
As long as there is a competition in this world, the winner and loser will be born.
Up until now, the people who have become losers in the use of children have been humiliated in many ways, which can be said to be the best of their lives.
Matsumoto Hitoshi's Punishment Game!
The President Matsumoto Renger Show!
I'm sorry!
What are you doing?
Wait!
I'm sorry!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
First, a live broadcast of the video.
Wow! Wow! This is fun! This is fun! Summer vacation!
It's not showing.
Where should we go for fun?
Wow! Wow! This is fun! This is fun! Summer vacation!
Do it!
What is this?
Help! Help! Somebody help me!
Help me!
Human
Why are you using the word toji?
The sound is so soft!
I'm a ninja!
For me, I'm a real ninja!
I'm a real ninja!
Oh, what is this?
I can't do this!
My shoulders are the only thing that hurts.
Oh my god!
Oh god, oh god, I can't do this anymore.
I'm going to the toilet.
I'm not good at this.
The grumpy face of Temiko.
What is this?
It's raw.
I can't do it.
It's so funny.
It's terrible.
They are!!
A wonderful!
hitaki!
All together!
Old man has already what it what it is!
I can it sounds almost collapse No?
The country is!
Six traveled sea
All together!
­ Yakuza Togoro!
­Togorr!
—Hey, [(Kabuyaake!)
—Do it!
—Hey, Zouk capacidad!!!
—We don't know that recipe but don't put soda,
​Mash relat És Baska?
The winner is...
...Yoshiyama!
Donmenger!
Don't say anything!
Win!
Naomi!
I know, I know!
Sakaari Donmenger!
I'm not going to let you sleep for three days!
Finally, I'm going to let you sleep for three days!
Who are you?
I'm a year old ranger, Okan.
I'm a child's pen.
It was hard, wasn't it?
Your face...
Please take care of me.
Thank you.
You're eating it!
Today too, tomorrow too, tomorrow too.
Charlie's jam is on the top of my head.
Please play it for me.
The sound is too heavy.
It's not heavy at all.
Today too, tomorrow too, tomorrow too.
It's okay to hit the wall.
Everyone, take care of your family.
I'm not going to cry!
It's been 6 and a half hours since the live broadcast.
What is it? Fujiwara No Matsu Japanese TV has arrived.
Don't get caught.
I'm sorry for the long wait.
Thank you for coming to our Japanese TV today.
I look forward to working with you.
Why is it my Japanese TV?
It's not Japanese TV at all.
Please say yes on Japanese TV.
Come on!
Yes, please.
Please.
What is this?
This is the room for the room service.
Why did you go to the room service?
I'm so happy to see you all relaxed.
Today, I'm going to be taking care of Mr. Matsumoto.
I'm Fujiwara.
Please take care of me.
10 minutes later, Matsumoto Family finally arrives at the Japanese TV.
He really is energetic.
She was fine at first.
She was fine.
Hello.
Please lead the staff.
Please come here.
Long time no see.
Hello.
I'm from the same school.
Thank you.
I wonder who will be the next one.
I don't know who will say it.
Who will say it and who will do it?
I don't know.
It's difficult.
What are you going to do?
Who will do it?
The flow is also difficult.
Like the flow of the river.
Hey!
It's a prison.
What are you doing?
I will explain the schedule.
First, I will make the cover of the Matsumoto Renjai.
This is the schedule of the Matsumoto family on this day.
From making the cover to the live show in Tokyo, they can do it without any time to rest.
Who is it?
It's me.
What is it?
Fujii Gaya.
Thank you.
First, we'll start with the action hero's soul.
It's been a while since I've seen you.
You're a white man, right?
Well, it's fine.
I'm 70.
I don't know.
I'm almost 40.
I'm 41.
I'm 35, so I'm 70.
I'm not 35, I'm 30.
Don't get angry.
What are you doing?
You're late.
I didn't take a picture.
You did.
It's the last one.
Why did you take a picture?
I took it.
What's wrong with this?
It's delicious.
Why did you take a picture of your old face?
Stop it.
There was also a moment when I were invited.
A handsome, fit man?
Stop always having the names.
I didn't think it was paraffin.
Yeah, but everyone around us was saying so.
Did I say so?
When I went camping with my family, I was like...
Will we all die?
I wonder if it's true.
It's more simple to watch.
But you said that you would definitely go home and do this.
I wonder if I will die in front of them.
I hope so.
What is that?
You don't know anything about it.
I don't know what to sing.
Let's sing.
It hasn't started yet.
We have to think about the lyrics.
Let's make a simple song first.
Oh, it's coming out.
It's coming out.
Protecting the peace of the universe.
My warriors are rising.
It's been about 10 years.
It's not that long.
I have to get this from the beginning.
Shioedo machinami ga
pisun disconnected
Hanako Malin
KarTarara ta yoru
The next line is....
I'm not sure.
What?
You're a child of the moon, aren't you?
To protect the peace of the universe,
the warriors of the universe stand up.
It's too much of a joke.
If you hit the pager, it won't work, right?
It won't work, right?
I don't know how to play the guitar.
Well, the bass is...
It's easy.
It's easy, isn't it?
It's a random C.
The rhythm is...
I can sing.
What is your family?
I have one family.
I have one cooler.
I, Mike has to do this way.
That's why he says I can't send anything on.
As we stand, we rise.
A festival ofThere is still tomorrow
The fate of Suminom allegory
Wait, wait.
Where is the Chosuke that my father named?
I remember.
He was a cat.
He brought the cat home.
That's it.
Chosuke.
I remember.
Why did you eat?
I don't remember, but I think I ate.
I said that it was a good place.
I was thinking.
I was thinking that I should drink a lot.
If I drink so much, it's definitely fun.
You're doing something you don't remember.
I'm sure.
Let's go with Ama.
I'm not going to drink Ama.
You are a Shioi, right?
Yes, I am.
I'm not sure about Shioi.
What do you think of Shioi?
Shioi's peace is Matsumoto's.
Yamada's peace is strange.
Hamada, Yamasaki and Kokoriko's four people came to monitor the team.
They are doing well.
Matsumoto family.
Hello.
It's been a while since I saw you, but you look just like your mother.
It's my first time seeing my sister.
It's my first time seeing my father.
Why are you laughing?
It looks like you're having fun.
I'm not laughing.
I'm a good guy, I'm a good guy, I'm a good guy
I'm doing it!
100 people
You're always singing when you're singing
I'm the brain of the Motoki family
I don't have to do anything
That's right.
You're really young if you're a child.
Hama-chan.
Yes?
You're not going to do it?
You're going to have a fluffy head soon.
I'm going to have a fluffy head.
Well, we can't watch the on-air, but...
What? You can watch it?
It's time to sleep.
I'm hungry.
You're hungry?
Yes.
I'm hungry.
Well, well, well.
You're hungry.
I'm hungry.
Ah, yes, yes.
It's hot.
I'm hungry.
Please wait.
Thank you.
It's 11.30 at night.
It's suddenly raining outside.
If you say Ottonranger, it's like a punch.
Don't say anything.
You can say sorry-smelling punch.
I'm sorry.
You always do that.
I'm sorry. I always do that.
Who is it?
You always do that.
It's Kai-chan.
He's really excited.
It's okay. I don't have to be 30 years old here.
How was it?
I'm a
Thank you.
B
After this, the king of anime song appears.
He pours his soul into the song.
This is my brother, Ichiro Mizuki.
This is totally different.
It's not different.
Y вообще...
Sem
Hello
I Han
It because
No
Nothing
Not
K
It
I'm sorry, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
We can't do this.
We will go to the hospital.
If you get better, we will come to you.
Thank you very much.
What are you talking about?
You can go.
Really?
You are so strong.
He is sitting.
He is the best.
Well, if you get better, you can go.
Ah, that's right.
At first, he was doing fine.
But in the middle, he suddenly turned down.
That's right.
He almost died.
What's wrong with that?
He was really shaking.
I was really surprised.
I'll come out later.
I said, I can't come out yet.
During the rehearsal, I said, I can't come out yet.
It wasn't my father's scene.
I was like, aaaaaah!
I was like, what the hell?
I grabbed his hand and went over here
I went over here and his hand went like, pa!
Aaaaaah!
That was scary
You didn't do anything during the actual scene, did you?
Well, during the actual scene, I was just staring at him
You were just staring at him
I was just staring at him
It was already half-transparent.
Even though everyone has two bells...
Even though everyone has two bells, one of them fell somewhere.
The bells are ringing for me.
Do you know what the bells mean?
The bells are also...
This will continue to be looked up on from time to time, then!