On the 11th of this month, Kokoriko Endo got married after 2 and a half years.
Endo was supposed to have a happy ending, but he had a problem.
I decided to get married on my own.
It's a good thing, but I thought it was hard.
Well, that's hard.
I thought there were a lot of people I had to break up with.
I don't know if I can do that.
If it's okay with you today, will you go out with me?
I want to end it today.
I'm married and I want you to break up with me.
It's personal.
But I don't know what to do by myself.
If possible, I want you to cooperate with me.
Just break up with me?
Can I go out with you today?
We can only see each other.
Before that, I'd like to ask you who you are.
Don't say that.
I don't want to hear it.
I want you to tell me something that's related to you.
Do you know me?
I know you.
Who?
It's Mr. Sugasu.
Mr. Sugasu?
Mr. Sugasu.
I don't believe it.
I'll give you some evidence.
You like bikes, don't you?
Yes.
Let's take a picture together.
You're really fat.
That was the peak.
Last year, we went to the Harleys.
It was hot, so we went to the Tohoku area.
There are a lot of things I have to return today.
First of all, wetty.
You use it a lot.
It's oily.
Don't look at my face.
I'm 97 years old, so I'm 100 years old.
You guys are funny.
I don't understand why you guys look like that.
This program is brought to you by the sponsor.
Ikko is taken to Sugamatsu TV.
It's close.
Let's go.
What do you want to do?
If there's something, let's stop it here.
Hey.
I'm going to get married.
I know.
We set up Yuino.
Congratulations.
Are you angry?
I'm looking at you.
Why are you looking at me?
I'm angry.
I'm married.
Congratulations.
I'm married, too.
It's a double disadvantage.
If you were dating.
I was dating.
But I can't do it anymore.
I want you to break up with me.
It's one-sided.
I want to make good memories.
Let's kiss.
I want you to kiss me.
What are you doing?
This is a company.
Let's stop this.
End.
What are you doing?
I want to make good memories about the past.
End.
What are you doing?
You should go.
I'm sorry.
If you want to get off, you can get off.
I don't do that.
I'm sorry.
End.
I broke up with KUSUGA.
What do you mean?
I'm still dating.
Still?
I'm GIDAYU.
What?
I'm GREAT GIDAYU.
What are you doing?
I have a picture.
I didn't want to show this.
End.
Please.
I can't do this.
I was surprised.
After I announced my marriage.
That's right.
The next day?
Yes.
This is just a guess.
I did it, so I'll do it, too.
I'm most afraid of this type.
After marriage.
I have to be clear about that.
End.
I'm fine.
I don't think so.
Everyone.
Good morning.
I think you know.
I'm married.
Congratulations.
Are you still waiting?
I was surprised.
GIDAYU.
What is this?
This?
This is a guess.
To whom?
To me.
To the portrait.
Wait a minute.
I don't think it's a guess.
I can finally get married.
Because it's the next day.
This is a little.
Wait a minute.
Don't look at me.
Why are you so friendly?
Don't you remember?
When did you make this?
You said you made it.
Until now.
Accept it as reality.
I want to make a wonderful memory.
What?
So.
Finally.
Give me a kiss.
I don't want a kiss.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
I want to forget about GIDAYU.
So I'll give you a kiss.
I'll give you a kiss.
Calm down.
You want to forget about GIDAYU.
No.
I'll say no.
I'm sorry.
It's not over yet.
Can I kiss you?
With whom?
Endo.
Let's kiss.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
I'll prepare.
Prepare?
Is there a girl?
It's hard to kiss.
I don't feel like it.
I'm sorry.
I'll kiss you.
It's weird.
You can't do that.
Thank you very much.
Let's wrap it up.
We're done with Gidai-U.
What? What do you mean?
But there's one more person I want to say goodbye to.
There's more?
Well...
The next person is...
Really?
I think you know him well.
Yes.
He was in the same drama as you.
His name is Kase.
Really?
Why are you naked in the middle of the show?
This is my birthday last year.
I'm 30 years old.
I was invited to a party in Shinjuku.
Kase invited me to his birthday party.
The two of us.
It was really delicious.
That's good.
I'll show you today.
What?
We played like this.
What's wrong with your body?
This was the peak.
You're taking too much.
There was a time like that.
This is shocking.
There was a photo.
There's something I have to give back to Kase.
This is what it looks like.
Taishu?
There's a Kase.
I used Kase a lot.
That's a long name.
Taishu is longer.
I bought it at the same time.
Kase.
Kase was on my side.
I don't think he's wearing it.
He's not a loser in time.
I think he's wearing it.
It's the one that comes five minutes before.
As expected.
There's a Kase.
He's a man.
I'm going.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I want to make it clear today.
With Taishu.
I want you to break up.
You're cool.
What is it?
Let's go with the usual Taishu.
Taishu.
Where is it?
Taishu doesn't have a scooter.
I think you'll understand if you see this.
Taishu.
Hard play.
Thank you.
Why did you write my name?
Taishu wrote it.
Taishu.
Kima was bullying me with this Kase.
I'm sorry.
I don't know this.
Yes.
Motosu.
Look at me like a bad guy.
I don't know.
I'm a man.
I don't have a girlfriend.
I understand.
Let's talk about the past.
I want to cherish the past.
I want to kiss on this place.
I want to end it.
Kiss?
Why do you have to do it?
I'll kiss you.
Don't say that.
What is it?
What are you saying?
I want to kiss and end it.
It hasn't started yet.
There's nothing, right?
There's nothing.
Why am I doing this?
Where is the place to make this?
Taisho, really, let's kiss and end it.
Let's end it.
Please do something.
I'll probably do it too.
No way.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to pat me.
You can pat me.
You don't have to grab me.
Taisho.
Why?
Endo's friend.
It doesn't matter.
Taisho.
Endo, hurry up.
Hurry up.
Why are you doing this to me?
Endo, I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I've already cut three.
There's only one left.
What?
Not yet?
There's one last person I really want to cut.
This is really the last one.
Please.
He's close.
He's still here?
What the hell are you talking about?
Endo wants to say goodbye with more sincerity than ever.
Who is the last person?
Everyone may already know.
It's my senior.
Yamamoto of Gokuraku Tongo.
To be honest.
I thought it was okay.
But I thought it wasn't a show.
So I couldn't say it.
There's something I have to give back to Yamamoto.
What's that?
It's homemade jam.
Jam?
We bought strawberries and made it together.
I don't need it.
It's okay to have it.
What are you doing?
It's good to dip it in bread.
I see.
To be honest.
I think it's okay to say this.
The first three people are clear.
To be honest.
This is the main.
I want to crush this.
They've been in more private relationships.
Today, Endo says goodbye to the person he loves.
Is it over?
Where's Ono?
He's gone.
It's true.
I'm going home.
I'm scared that he's coming.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's the best two so far.
I don't have much to say.
I'm married.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I've been dating Yama for 11 years.
It's longer than my wife.
I don't want you to get married.
Simply put.
I don't want you to break up with me.
I have a lot of memories.
I brought a lot of things I have to return today.
What are you talking about?
Who are you talking to?
Who made this?
It's Jam.
Thank you.
I've never given you anything like this.
What is this?
What kind of project is this?
What are you doing?
I've never given you anything like this.
Why do you have such memories?
I don't have such memories.
I know that you don't give me anything like this.
I'm not going to deal with you.
I'm just telling you.
I don't think so.
I think the three of us have different things.
I'm alone.
I can't do it alone.
I need everyone's cooperation.
Yamazaki is also a colleague.
Yamamoto.
I'm not going to date you.
I'd like you to stop it today.
I'm going to do it with my seniors and juniors.
It's you, isn't it?
Did you come up with a plan?
I don't know.
Please don't do it for fun.
Please do it for fun.
That's what you're doing.
If you do it lightly like that, you'll get hurt.
It's better to be funny.
What's the fun part?
Isn't what I'm doing funny?
Don't say that.
Can I do it?
Let's end it by kissing to clean up our relationship.
What do you mean by that?
If it's a kiss story and I'm here, I'll kiss you.
Then it's over.
What are you talking about?
If possible, Yamamoto.
That's right.
Think about the reality.
Endo is not married.
Give up.
Why can't you give up?
Please stop taking pictures of me next to Yamamoto.
I can't stop it.
It's a picture that can be misunderstood.
You're the coolest picture.
Let's meet.
You were cool.
You're the coolest picture.
I like you the most.
What do you mean to throw that picture away?
I understand.
But can you give me a kiss?
I'll never give you a kiss.
Wait a minute.
Stop it.
I can't stop it if I don't kiss you.
Why can't you stop it if you don't kiss me?
I want to end it.
You said you liked me.
I like you as my senior.
I don't like you so much.
I like you so much.
I'll be in your place a week from now.
Why?
Because you're a cool picture.
I'm going to be jealous.
Stop it.
I don't want to.
I'm going to be jealous.
Let's end it.
I'll never give you a kiss.
I'm going to be jealous.
I'll run away.
Let's end it.
You're a boar!
It's dangerous.
Catch me and give me a kiss.
Quick.
What is this?
Don't come close.
Catch me and kiss me.
This is the end.
Let's end it.
You want to end it.
That's enough.
Then which one?
What?
You answer the next question.
What is it?
Matsumoto Sanhaka or Hamada Sanhaka?
What are you talking about?
What is this?
Give me a kiss.
Why are you using lotion?
Wait.
It's a kiss.
Give me a kiss.
What are you guys doing?
Kei-chan.
What is it?
Give me a kiss.
What is this?
Yabayaki.
I thought you were my friend.
Kei-chan.
I don't know.
Kei-chan, I like you.
It has nothing to do with him.
He wants to go home.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.