In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukajiwara
It's cold and hot with Yamazaki Okamoto
These two are really cold
Really?
Yes
It's so hot
It's called Kokusho this year
I'm shaking all the time
Like a small dog
I want you to be warm
That's a good thing
Yamazaki always says he's cold even in the first episode
He's cold up to 102 degrees
Let's warm up
Yamazaki Okamoto
It's true
Are you cold?
A little
I think it's around 30 degrees
It's only 32 degrees
Let's do it
Which one is cold?
That's me
That's a good one
It's a unison
I'm not cold like you
Wait a minute
Stop fighting
He's crying
Yamazaki san is sweating
I'm sweating
You're sweating?
Because it's cold
Let's go
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
First of all
Spoonless
I think it's a little hot
Please bring it
It's really cold
Let's put it in
What?
Wait a minute
You can't put it in
Is it impossible?
It's impossible
Let's go
Spoonless
Ready
Don't drop it
If you drop it, people around you will get in trouble
It's hot
Dad
Wait
It's hot
I won
What is it?
It's a box
I don't think there's anything
Let's light it
This is good
It's better than anything
How do you light it?
With your foot
With my foot?
Okamoto san
Okamoto san was great
It's hot
Yamasaki san
He's not good at driving
Okamoto san got 1 point again
Thank you
This will burn in the bar
Please warm it up
You can use it as much as you want
That's right
If you can't clear it, you win
Yamasaki san
Let's go
It looks like a dragon
It's hot
Yamasaki san is good
Okamoto san
It's hot
Great
Are you going to the next race with a draw?
Or do you want to lead and go to the next race?
Let's let the loser choose
I lost and lost
I'm going to the next race with a draw
You lost and lost so you're going to the next race with a draw?
Can you explain the next race?
This is a bread eating competition
The string part is burning
You have to eat freshly made bread
Freshly baked
It looks good
The bread at the end is burning
It's true
Freshly baked
You have to line up in the morning
You can't eat freshly baked bread
I'm glad
Ready
It's good
It's a good drawing
Yamasaki san, are you kissing it?
It's hot
Yamasaki san, you dropped it
It was big
Let's replay
It's hot
If you bite this bread, you get 3 points
3 points?
Jump
It's hot
You don't have to replay
Okamoto san
He's licking it
It's hot
Okamoto san again
Time
Time is up
He ate it
It's a dry food
Ready
It's hot
It's clean
Let's do it again
It's hot
What a pity
Let's go Okamoto san
Ready
It's hot
You have to get more vegetables
We don't have enough vegetables
It's good for the last
Sun is cool
We are like lions
I'll do it
Okamoto san first
I'll show you
Yamasaki san, you look like Yota osu san
Let's do a mini-contest
Okami, are you ready?
Can I do this?
If you do this, you win
Mini-contest
Yota
I think he's going to stop
He's looking at the starry sky
Where did he go?
Are you looking for him?
Okami
It was fast
I wanted it to be faster
It's a punishment for the two who couldn't do it
You have to do it twice
You drank too much
Thank you
Okami
Ready
Why?
Yamasaki san, you were great
The winner is Yamasaki san
Congratulations
It was a good fight
Thank you
It's hot
What is it?
It's quite late
It's already 10 o'clock
I thought the audience was tired
I'm fine
Both of you are tired
But it was more interesting than Yamasaki's speech
Yamasaki san, how was your speech today?
It was great
There are many things
There's nothing
I'm really tired today
It was hot
Summer vacation feels really long this year
There's still more
I don't like summer vacation
I don't want to go home
It's really hot
There's a lot of space next to my house
It's the only place that's still cool
There's a lot of space
I can drink juice with one hand
It's amazing
I can laugh
It's magic
I can do this
I can look at the car like this
It's hard to come home
But I can come home and say I'm sorry
I can say it
There are people who can't make contact
Even though I come home, if I come out
What is this?
It's like a person sitting on the street
I can't say anything when they don't talk to me
I can just say I'm not home
It's really cool
What?
I just happened to be waiting for someone
What was that?
What?
That was a new one
I have a corner
I'm standing there
I can't come to my house
I'm standing in front of my house
I can't say anything
I'm sure you're at home
I know the story
I'm in love with your eyes
If you ask me
It's not just us
Most of the summer holidays
My parents call me
My daughter says she's going to stay at my house
That's not true
It's a problem for the company
I don't know if it's true inside
Why are you acting like an old lady?
It's true
But there are a lot of summer holidays
I want you to stop
To be honest
They really come
They ask me to stop
What?
They ask me to stop at home
Half of them ask me to stop
You're annoying
You're not doing anything
You're a non-stop person
I'm not a non-stop person
What do you mean?
You're always like that
I don't hate you
I think they're high school students
Or junior high school students
You can't let them stay at your house
This is a big fight
In my opinion
They come by themselves
They come by themselves?
You can't do that
No, really
Really
In the past
How long ago?
About half a year ago?
You're already downtown
What?
You're not downtown
I'm not downtown
You're almost there
I'm downtown
Who are you talking to?
I have nothing to do
I'm going to stay home
You?
I have a lot of work to do
I'm bored
I'm full of work
You're talking to yourself
That's not true
No, no
You're a student
I want you to come home
I want you to stop
I'll stay home
Don't come home
Do you want me to write?
Yes
Curry bread has curry
Jam bun has jam
Why does melon bun not have melon?
It's been 4 years since I started this show
I ignored it
You
Why does melon bun not have melon?
No, melon bun is
I named it by its appearance
Which part is melon?
The pattern
This is
The connection of the sky
If it's light blue
It's the sky
I want you to be clear
You're thinking melon bun has melon
But jam bun has jam
Cream bun has cream
Then what?
If you name it
It's all inside
But this
There's glasses inside
You're saying that
You're talking about bread
I'm talking about glasses
No, no, no
You're talking about bread
It doesn't hurt
Then let's talk about bread only
Glasses
It doesn't matter
You know glasses
Glasses
That's not true
If you say that, it's easy to understand
French bread
What is French bread?
That is
The first
French bread
Right?
It's not French at all
There's no French inside
Croissant
What's inside?
It's like this
Uguisu bread
It's not that
What kind of bread is uguisu bread?
I'm asking you
There's green filling inside
Really?
Yes
You said it like an artist
No, no
It's not uguisu at all
No matter how much you put it on your chest
Shut up
Uguisu is
It's similar to you
No one thinks it's uguisu
It's not appearance
Uguisu is green
It's not like that
Appearance and name
That's fine
It's not like that?
What do you do if you agree?
I always think about soccer
There must be a reason why a soccer player should be happy when he scores a goal
I'm trying to appeal
I put it in
Everyone is the same
Aren't you interested in soccer?
I play soccer
I play baseball
I see
You don't see it
Soccer
I don't see it
It's me
Good job
I have a bad luck
I always fail
How can I get rid of bad luck?
You just think it's bad luck
You're being kind
You're like an old comedian
This is his hand
If I'm troubled
Don't get too excited
That's his hand
What are you talking about?
I have a bad luck
For example, you say
If you use your luck on something like this
It's bad luck
It's strange
Why?
It's bad luck to use your luck on something like this
Don't stop
Who are you talking to?
I'm really about to get out
Where?
Teacher
Are you going to get out?
I'm really about to get out
I'll check
Last year
If you think you have bad luck
Your luck will get worse
You keep getting hurt
You keep dropping things
I was there
I don't remember
What?
English that you use
There are words that can't be translated
What should I say for Parma?
Parma?
It's English
Is that so?
Permanent
Teacher, teach me
What is permanent?
Parma
Parma means
To roll
Is that so?
Nento means
To do something
Roll
Let's roll
That's permanent
For example, you don't have sunglasses
What?
Japanese
Do you know what glass is?
Glass
Wait
Is it wrong?
I don't know
Then set