The day of the New Year's party has come!
The 12th Gaki no Tsukariya Line's Chiki Chiki Welcome New Year's Party!
This year too, without any evidence, has started!
The usual New Year's party!
I can't do it anymore.
This year too, I'm the host of the New Year's party!
Yoshimoto's Mikako Nii Hikobu vs. Yomazaki Hosei!
And today, we have invited a special guest.
First, we have Mr. Hotohara who wants to end the rainy season!
Mr. Hotohara!
Nice to meet you!
Mr. Hotohara, your partner, Mr. Miyasako, isn't here today.
Yes!
Mr. Miyasako...
He's at Charity Soccer, so I'm worried about his future.
What?
Excuse me!
Mr. Yamashita Shioda!
Mr. Yamashita!
Idiot!
Excuse me!
Mr. Yamashita Shioda!
Are you serious?
Grandma!
Mr. Yamashita Shioda!
And the first participant this year is...
Mr. Yamada!
That's not him.
That's definitely not him.
That's not Yamada.
Oh, he said it.
And the producer of the show, the master of young comedians.
Mr. Tsuga, please say a few words.
Thank you!
This year...
Unfortunately, it's not an unfavorable situation.
But I hope you enjoy it.
Thank you again this year.
Thank you!
Next, we have the two mascots of this show.
From Downtown.
No, no, no.
What?
You're just a mascot.
Thank you.
Please look at the mirror and say hello.
Do you have the last one today?
What's the last one?
What?
Do you have the last one?
Of course.
That's the main thing.
Even if you come out, there are people who say it's cold.
You can't stop that.
Yamazaki's manager is a girl, right?
I don't know what to say.
That's the main thing.
It's pretty tough.
Let's wrap it up.
Thank you.
Everyone, please say hello to the mirror.
What?
One, two.
Mirror.
What?
You're going to say hello to the mirror, right?
Please take care of us this year as well.
Thank you.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Everyone, please make a decision.
I'll still take it.
It's the annual Gaki no Tsukai new year party.
A delicious drink and a delicious meal.
Everyone takes a sip.
But in the midst of all this, a single man
sneaks into Matsumoto.
It's a bit strange.
I don't know what beer is.
What kind of mark is that?
The mark on your chest.
The mark of the maker.
That's normal.
Well, this year is your year, so do your best.
I'm really looking forward to it.
The 4th Yami Rotsukai.
Chikiduki.
The 21st Hakuwarai Manzai.
The 5th.
This time as well as this time.
Really?
I'm thinking about it.
And I...
What are you going to do?
Are you going to join?
I'm a mystery.
Why?
What's your skill?
I don't know!
The new year's fun project.
Manzai Dai Gassen.
Out of 25 talent staff members,
5 teams will be chosen by lottery.
Each team will perform an original manzai.
First, we will draw lots for the number.
The first round of the new year.
Thank you!
I don't like it anymore.
I don't like it at all.
Number 3!
Who is it?
The number 3.
It's been a while since I saw you.
You look cool today, Naguri-san.
Thank you.
Then, Naguri-san,
please choose the number.
That's right.
Please.
Who is it?
Number 12.
Thank you.
And the second round of the lottery.
Number 11.
Who is it?
Thank you.
The second round of the lottery.
Who is it?
The director, Otomo.
Then, I will choose the number 3.
Number 9.
Oh, Matsumoto.
Yes.
Number 11.
It's been a while since I saw you.
Amazing.
What do you think of this?
It's not like that.
It feels good.
The way you touch me, it's really soft.
The side of my belly is really soft.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Then, after this, we will be alone for about an hour.
We will be alone.
We have to have a discussion.
Yes.
It's really scary.
It's okay, right?
I will do my best.
What are you talking about?
I am the star of the 21st century.
The fourth group is Yamashita, a former Jeryzm.
This is Hamada.
And this is Kogoriko.
Good.
And this is a burnt tennis ball.
That's right.
Number 10.
Yes.
Tanaka will do it again.
If Tanaka does it...
I remembered.
I forgot.
Last year, Kogoriko did it.
That's right.
It was the most slippery.
Tanaka.
Number 14.
It's me.
You.
You're able to take it.
It's got to be a patriotic fight.
Yeah.
You need to raise one more person.
Yeah?
Raise the two of them.
We were standing like this.
You need to comb your face see it with three of them.
Yes.
Do it like this or two of them.
Like it, huh?
It's important.
Something is interesting.
Someone, Three-Four-Sports get it to me.
No. 7, Lucky Seven!
If that was the case...
Can Tanaka and Endo do it?
No!
Please don't do it!
To be honest, after that...
Amata Hamada wants to do it with me.
Okamaya!
I don't want Okamaya!
I don't want Okoge!
It's not Okoge. It's the opposite.
It's Okoge, right?
It's the opposite.
It's not Okoge.
It's Okoge becoming a man.
It's the same as Tsukagata.
It's completely different.
Please wait a moment.
What should we do?
It's already decided.
Me and Endo...
Please let me do it again.
This is fine.
Why?
If I had to decide,
I'd let one person do it.
But Amata's Tanaka-san...
No, you can't do P.
Really.
No P.
You can do it.
Tanaka is determined to do the nightmare P.
And Endo Hamada is determined to do the Tsukkomi-Konbi.
In addition, Matsumoto and Okamashi Shirono are full of expectations.
The combination of the director Otomo, Amiagari, and Hotohara.
Hanazeka Yamashita and the natural director, Sakamoto, are entering.
And the dangerous 120% staff combination.
For the sake of a peaceful fight, the third person is chosen.
Number 21.
Number 21 isn't here.
Please wait a moment.
You again.
Yamazaki-san.
The sixth group is decided by Yamazaki's entry into the trio.
The six groups that have been entered.
Let's start the meeting of the famous story.
It's a new year's party, but it's the first stage of the 21st century.
You can't slip.
Everyone is fighting against that pressure.
After all, it seems that there are various ideas depending on each group.
It's just squeezed.
I'm Hiroshi Fujiwara of Yoshimoto Industrial Co., Ltd.
I'm sorry.
Fujiwara, I can't stop you.
I'd like to start the first group.
Hamada-san and Endo-san.
The theme is snake year.
Please.
It's the 21st century.
I'm going to do my best in the 21st century.
Everyone is talking about 2001.
What are you talking about?
Do you know the theme of this year?
Of course I know.
This year is the year of the snake.
But if it's the year of the snake, it's the year of the mouth.
The mouth is a hot topic.
Really?
If you catch it, it will be money.
Who is dirty?
I don't know.
The prize money has changed.
Let's go catch it.
Okay.
Endo-kun.
Yes.
That hole is suspicious.
It's in that hole.
There are 600 coins in that hole.
Okay.
Let's go catch it.
Can you take a look?
This is...
There is a rock.
Hamaya-san.
Yes.
There seems to be a rock on the hole.
I see.
I'll hold this rock.
Please look at this hole.
I see.
There may be a rock.
Please.
Let's go.
How is it?
Endo-kun.
Yes.
It's hard to run.
Is that so?
That's strange.
The rock is perfect.
Endo-kun.
Yes.
Don't move too much.
I understand.
I'll push the rock.
Endo-kun, get up.
Yes.
It's better to go inside.
I don't know, Endo-kun.
It's strange.
What?
Endo-kun.
What is that hole on the top?
There must be a piece of dirt.
Is that so?
Endo-kun, please take a look.
Me?
I'm fine.
Wait a minute.
Endo-kun, please take a look.
Hamaya-san, please take a look.
No, I can't.
Endo-kun, please take a look.
Hamada-san, please take a look.
Hamada-san is good.
Endo-kun, I'll support you.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Please take a look.
I'm here.
Endo-kun.
Yes.
What's wrong?
Hamada-san, what's wrong?
Endo-kun.
Yes.
Endo-kun, I'm here.
I understand.
I'm not here anymore.
Let's go home.
Please take care of me.
I want to catch you somehow.
Yes.
If you could do a shoulder-wheel, I might be able to see you.
Shoulder-wheel?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Then, it's fine.
Then, just a little.
Yes.
Here we go.
Then, please.
Endo-kun.
Yes.
Behind you.
Behind.
The shoulder-wheel is behind.
Please.
Then, let's go.
Endo-kun.
Endo-kun, don't move too much.
Yes.
Endo-kun, don't move.
Endo-kun.
What's wrong?
There's a moon child.
Hamada-san.
This is ***.
Thank you very much.
Hotohara-san and Otomo-san.
The theme is Kimo-Taku and Kudo Shizuka.
It's a marriage.
Please.
Hello.
I'm Hotohara.
I'm Otomo.
Together with Spain.
Don Tacos.
Don't dance.
There were many stories of the 20th century.
But the most memorable one is...
What are you looking at?
Where are you looking?
What are you thinking?
Why do you talk?
Really?
What was the most memorable?
Kimutaku and Kudo Shizuka got married, right?
That's amazing
Right?
They got married
They got married, right?
That was the most memorable
That's right
What was the most memorable?
The press conference
That was great
Excuse me, do you have any comments?
What are you talking about?
It's not about who did it
No, it's about Kimutaku
Right?
Do you have any comments?
It was great
That's your personal opinion
Don't do that
Thank you
It took an hour
What was that?
You guys are not good
You should have said that
Let's move on to the third question
Yamashita and Sakamoto
The topic is Ichiro Major
Please
Hello
I'm Zomo
I'm Zomara
Two people plus alpha
We started
Last year, many people participated
But this year, in the 21st century
The person who will be active
It's Ichiro
It's tough
No, you are the one who is tough
You are Ichiro
Do you know Ichiro?
I know him
It's you
I lost to loneliness
No, I lost to the world
Don't do that
What are you doing?
Yamazaki, Irie and Heipo
The topic is the 21st century
Please
I'm Fukun
I'm Raku
Don't hit me
The 21st century
The zoo will change
The zoo will have more people and animals
Let's go to the zoo
It's a monkey mountain
I don't like monkeys
What?
That monkey
Is it active?
It's a female
I'm angry
Let's see more
Why did you do that?
It's a female monkey
What are you doing?
I'm sorry
I don't like monkeys
Let's go to another place
What is this?
Gorilla?
It's a male gorilla
What is the topic?
The 21st century
The zoo will have more people and animals
Let's go to the zoo
Matsumoto and Shiono
The topic is the Sydney Olympics
Please
Matsumoto
I'm Matsumoto
I'm Shiono
Let's see more
I don't like it
I don't want to turn off the lights
I don't want to wear gloves
I don't like this character
I'm sorry
What are you talking about?
You are so funny
Let's do our best
There were many things last year
I'm worried about the Olympics
It was amazing
It only opens once every four years
It only opens once every four years?
Compared to that
Every night
I don't care who it is
I don't care
I swatted
What?
You are talking too cute
That's not true
I don't say things like that
When you look at the Olympics
There are many people
in theamię
I remember that. Who else do you remember, Shiono-kun?
I remember the strongest man on the ground.
Yes, yes, yes.
Carl Lewis.
That's Carl Lewis.
What are you talking about? That's not him.
I remember the other guy.
He was a swimmer.
He's become a buzzword.
He said, I'm so frustrated.
Tajima, right?
Who else do you remember, Shiono-kun?
I remember the strongest Russian wrestler.
Yes, yes, yes.
Alexander Karelin.
That's Karelin.
Kibusaki Akiyama is all about Kare.
It's so embarrassing in front of people.
I made a mistake with the salt.
I put salt on it.
Your voice is too loud.
It's kind of realistic.
It's really different.
I can't help but be angry.
There was a Japanese judo player.
He won by one point.
Shinohara.
I think that was Shinohara's one point win.
I think that was Doie's one point win.
That's not true.
That was Shinohara's one point win.
That's exactly right.
Okay, I got it.
Let's do it again in slow motion.
Then you can see it clearly.
Let's do that.
I'm Shinohara.
I'm Doie.
Okay, let's do it.
Let's do it.
You're quite a technician.
You lost.
Why did you lose?
But that was completely one point.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
I'm Tanaka.
The topic for today is
the IT revolution and me and Tonbo.
Please.
The IT revolution and me and Tonbo
Let's do it one more time.
You're high tension.
The IT revolution.
The IT revolution and me and Tonbo
Tonbo
That's not true.
I'm sorry.
We did it again this year.
How was it?
Well, there were many things.
The combination of the top batter was
not only cowardly,
but also dirty.
I don't like it when it's so difficult.
To be honest.
When Shiho came here,
he smelled like shampoo.
What is this?