In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai, Tsukitsuki's Impersonation Voice Project,
Don't be found out!
Now, Matsumoto-san.
Yes, yes.
The rules are a bit...
The rules are difficult.
Hamada-san or me, we'll go to the other side of the wall.
Outside?
Yes.
The rest of you will do your best to impersonate.
I see.
If I go to the other side, I'll focus on hitting Hamada.
If you're found out, I'll give you 10,000 yen in fines.
I see.
That means...
The fines won't work.
Let's do our best.
Let's do it.
This is a sudden project.
What's the sudden project?
I just thought about it.
You can't do it, can you?
That's why it's fun, even if it's sudden.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
I'll guess first.
I'll tell you the number.
Tell me the number.
What number am I?
Yes.
First, we'll decide on the topic.
This?
Ah, let's go with this.
This is easy to understand.
Let's go.
I don't know.
I'll ask carefully and I'll understand.
Matsumoto, what's your specialty?
Guess me.
Yes.
I was imitating you just now.
Whose?
Isn't that right?
What are you doing?
You'll be found out.
That's Matsumoto.
First.
What are you doing?
Second.
Third.
What are you doing?
Fourth.
Fifth.
What are you doing?
Sixth.
Seventh.
What are you doing?
Eighth.
What's your number?
Seventh.
I was confident just now.
I knew it.
By the way, which number was similar to Nijiwan?
Endo is good.
Who is number six?
I'm number six.
What are you doing?
I want to be praised.
I'm number six.
Thank you very much, you idiot.
You didn't have to do it twice.
Number one.
Hey, Kitaro.
Number two.
Number three.
Hey, Kitaro.
Number four.
Number five.
Hey, Kitaro.
Number six.
Number seven.
Hey, Kitaro.
Number eight.
This is difficult.
The first half.
Number two.
I'm number two.
What's your number?
Number three.
This is difficult.
Let's go with this.
Number one.
It's amazing.
Number two.
Number three.
It's amazing.
Number four.
Number five.
It's amazing.
Number six.
Number seven.
It's amazing.
Number eight.
I really don't know this one.
Number four.
Who's number four?
I'm number four.
I don't know.
I don't know this one.
So the prize money is 10,000 yen.
Thank you very much.
Number one.
My beloved one that remains in my heart.
Number two.
Number three.
My beloved one that remains in my heart.
Number four.
Number five.
My beloved one that remains in my heart.
It's amazing.
Number six.
My beloved one that remains in my heart.
Number seven.
Number eight.
It's amazing.
Number one.
When I'm in Kyoto.
Number two.
Number three.
When I'm in Kyoto.
Number four.
Number five.
When I'm in Kyoto.
Number six.
Number seven.
When I'm in Kyoto.
Your voice isn't coming out.
Number eight.
When I'm in Kyoto.
Number four.
It's amazing.
An amateur can't win over the fun.
Number one.
Number two.
Number three.
Number four.
Two.
Number five.
It's amazing.
That's it, right?
Ah, I get it now.
You get it right away.
You have to do it better.
You're too bad at it.
I can't help it.
I want to get it in that pattern too.
Two, two.
If you do this, you won't get it.
I'm going to win.
I'm nervous.
Number one.
What the hell is that?
That was funny.
Number two.
What the hell is that?
Number three.
Number four.
What the hell is that?
Number five.