Gaki no Tsukai Meibutsu Kichihenge
In the middle of a meeting, he disguises himself and makes everyone laugh.
It's simple, but it's a project that requires a lot of sense of humor.
Until now, Yamazaki, Kokoriko, and a number of staff have challenged him.
He has shown off his talent.
And tonight, he has come back for the first time in a year.
Now, who will challenge him?
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Meibutsu, Chikishiki, Ameawari,
and Hotohara Shihengne!
Hotohara Shihengne?
That's right.
I understand that he wants to challenge Ameawari,
but he's in the wrong spot.
Thank you, Ameawari!
Thank you!
He's from Hatsumiyasako.
You're finally here.
The Hotohara boom.
In the past 12 episodes, the one with the best performance was Kokoriko Tanaka.
Really?
The winner was Takasu, a high school football player.
Takasu won?
7,000 yen.
How much do you want to win?
About 50,000 yen.
Really?
Of course.
That's right.
He said I have a bad complexion.
Did he say that?
He said that.
He said I have a bad complexion.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
What should we do?
Don't you think this is interesting?
What?
It's only now.
Yeah.
We're selling character merch.
Everyone's selling a lot of stuff now.
Character merch.
But there's no way we can save him.
We're selling merch.
I think Saito-san's calendar t-shirt will sell well.
I think my back is going to break.
What should we do?
We played against Ujiwara and Kimoto the other day.
That's right.
We have a little more time.
What should we do?
You can tell us what you want to do.
What I want to do...
I don't know if I can do that.
Yeah.
Let's have dinner when it's cold.
But it's going to cost a lot of money.
Really?
Yeah.
It's going to be amazing.
If you get injured, you'll have to go see a doctor.
I can't see the concept.
You were looking for a table, weren't you?
Oh, that's how it is.
It fits your head.
It would have been fun if you had a piece of bread on your head.
Matsumoto-san's head is spinning.
Today, we're going to talk about the welfare issue.
How about you, Matsumoto-san?
It's cute.
Which one is it?
It's stretching.
It's pulling.
It's so sad.
Look at Miyasako's face.
What should we do?
Is this okay?
There's something.
It's cute.
It's funny.
It looks like you.
I want to do it with Korakuen.
Where is it?
Midorigame was a little bad.
Midorigame was a little funny.
It was a good one.
But Heipo was bad.
It was a bad one.
Who is it?
I'm going to kill you.
I won't forgive you.
Who is it?
Is it you?
It's you, isn't it?
Huh?
Do you want to die?
Is it you?
You want it?
Let's go!
That was close.
I'm not good at acting.
I've been acting for 11 years now.
It's Hakusoto.
That was close.
I don't want to talk about it.
I'm sorry.
Don't say that.
It's okay.
What?
You guys are strong.
I'm sorry.
It's all over.
It's 19,000 yen.
19,000 yen?
So it's 3rd.
Eh?
4th place?
Endo dropped.
Yes.
Really?
It's 4th place.
Thank you.
Miyasako is very depressed.
Why?
Your talent is sad.
Let's think about it.
I'm doing it.
Miyasako?
Yes.
Miyasako should do it someday.
I can't sleep for a week if I listen to this.
That's right.
Really?
You couldn't sleep at all yesterday, right?
Yes.
It's true.
You were awake for 20 minutes.
It's not funny at all.
Actually, thank you for saying wow.
But we have a problem.
No, no.
If it doesn't end soon, we have to take a taxi home.
No, you can do it.
You can do it.
But the program can't do it.
I can't do it.
You can't do it.
I'm sorry, but I'm late for downtown.
Someone come here.
It was 5 o'clock today.
But in the end, downtown was ready at 7.30.
What were you doing?
I have nothing to say.
I can hit you anytime.
What were you doing?
I have nothing to say.
Let's go.
Wait.
Don't make me late.
You were late.
I wasn't late at all.
You were late for two and a half hours.
Wait.
You didn't catch up.
I thought you threw your shoes, but you couldn't do it.
It's your fault that everyone was late.
No.
Then, where is Yuho?
Yuho was late.
I wanted you to hit me.
You're crazy.
Do you understand?
In the end, parents and teachers don't hit the bad guys.
That's why bad guys become bad guys.
I'm the type of person who is late.
I'm a person who doesn't eat much.
I was waiting for you to hit me for about an hour.
Who?
Me.
I thought you would hit me if I was late for more than two hours.
I was late for two and a half hours.
But you said,
I was going to hit you.
What are you talking about?
You're going to be late.
That was your idea.
He hit me.
That makes sense.
I think it's fine.
Yes.
Well...
Yuho,
I saw the weather forecast.
You saw it?
Yes.
It was Wednesday, right?
I was out of luck last week.
I was out of luck, and I saw a heavy snowstorm.
For two days in a row?
Yes, for two days in a row.
The next day, Thursday, it was 11 o'clock.
It was 11 o'clock again!
It wasn't a snowstorm.
If it wasn't a snowstorm, I'd be angry again.
If it was, then it was a snowstorm.
If it was, then it was a heavy snowstorm.
It wasn't a big one.
The next day, Friday, it was 10 o'clock again.
It was terrible, wasn't it?
It was going up.
It was terrible.
It wasn't a snowstorm.
I was watching it from 4.55.
It was 5.55, and I was like, what's going on?
It wasn't a snowstorm at all.
Then, it was 11 o'clock.
I was like, wow!
It was 5.55, and it was terrible.
I know.
What's with this light-hearted argument?
No, really.
I said so much, but you didn't listen to me.
I couldn't get up.
I was like, on Monday,
on the day of the awakening,
every week, I was looking forward to downtown matcha.
You said that.
I was like, are you kidding me?
What's with this?
That day, it was 2 o'clock or something.
And then, it was a little late.
I was a little drunk on Monday.
I was drunk.
No, no, no.
It was just a coincidence.
And then, from Monday to Wednesday,
I didn't watch it once.
I only watched the bad parts.
I didn't watch the good parts.
I was drunk on that day.
You shouldn't say that.
You know what?
You were number one again.
You were the light of a pecan.
Really?
You were the light of a pecan again.
You were the light of a pecan.
Stop it.
That's why you were the light of a pecan.
What?
I'm so angry.
I'm really angry.
Seriously.
Really.
If I were Tanaka Kakuhei,
I would have done it many times.
What?
What do you mean?
But you said that to me,
and you said it would get better.
No, no, no.
I got better because I was told to.
It just happened.
You kept saying that to yourself.
You're acting like an adult.
I'm an adult.
No, no.
I'm the one who's acting like an adult.
I didn't say that.
Kakeoka,
I'm a big guy.
Who?
He's an idiot.
I'm an idiot.
Animals and birds.
We can understand the feelings of living things.
The first bird to fly is...
What made it fly?
You don't know that?
First of all,
you can say that it's the first bird to fly,
and you think that it's the leader.
That's the mistake?
That's the mistake.
But isn't it usually like that?
I think it's sad that you don't understand that.
For example,
a cat chases a mouse,
and it goes like this.
Everyone thinks that a mouse is weak to a cat.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's up to you.
It's up to you.
A mouse may be like this.
Come here.
You may not understand what I'm saying.
If you understand, why can't you understand?
Hurry up! Hurry up!
You're talking nonsense!
What are you talking about?
I'm not talking nonsense.
You're talking nonsense.
There's something like that.
Do you understand?
That's funny.
That's what it is.
Don't put what you see in your head.
This is one of the things we're going to study today.
This time, we're going to talk about crossing the line.
We're going to cross the line.
But the one who crosses the line first is the leader.
Well, that's a lie.
That's why.
What?
Hold on.
The one who crosses the line...
Yes, please.
The second one is the leader.
Huh? Why?
You're the first one to jump.
Okay, let's go.
Who are you?
I'm the second one.
I'm the real leader.
Oh, the second one.
Oh, that's right.
Shut up.
Don't talk nonsense.
I'm looking at a human being.
So why are you looking at a human being?
I don't care what other people think.
They think they're looking at a human being.
Oh, that's what it is.
That's right.
Shut up.
That's what they say, and the first one jumps.
Stop it.
I don't want to.
I don't want to kick your ass.
I'm kicking your ass.
I don't want to.
So if you look at the ass of the first bird, it's a triangle.
There's mud on it.
It's like a lion.
It's running away in the deer, but it's a little rough.
My mom says,
When the lion says,
Run away.
No, no, run away.
If it's a deer, it's a real bad thing.
If you run away, don't come back to this program.
The deer is delicious.
It's delicious, but it's eaten at the end.
No, it's only when the deer is running.
It's eaten here.
How many years have you been in the world of TV?
You know that, don't you?
But it's natural.
There's something like that.
The lion came and said,
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
It's okay.
I really wanted you to come here.
The teacher came and said,
I'm counting on you from now on.
I have a question for Mr. Matsumoto.
Please tell me how to hold a super fork that is said to be lower than the leader of Yokohama Sasaki.
Oh, I see.
But I think Sasaki will hate this.
Why?
If you get hit by a fork that falls lower than Sasaki on TV, you won't be able to stand up.
I don't care about that.
Wow.
You have such a strong authority.
It's okay.
How about a super fork?
I understand that.
Please tell me.
How do you teach me?
How do you hold a super fork?
Oh, I see.
Don't you have a ball?
If you have a ball...
You don't have a ball?
Wait a minute.
Why?
It's easy to hold a super fork.
If you don't have a ball, you can't hold a super fork.
It's okay.
I'll look for it.
Oh, here's the ball.
Okay, I'll show you.
How to throw a super fork.
First, you have to hold it like this.
I asked you to help me.
You have to show me slowly.
What do you want me to do?
Please hold the ball.
As if you don't have a ball.
Because you are Kuroko.
You have to hold it like this.
And then...
You have to shake it like this.
Wait a minute.
Please do it until I throw it.
How do you throw it?
Like this.
Okay.
That's good.
Don't jump!
This is...
This is a very good match.
This program is...
Sponsored by the following sponsors.