Today we have a lot of things to do from the top of our heads.
Today we have a lot of things we can't let go of.
Have you watched last week's episode?
I actually forgot about it a bit.
I remembered it now.
You remembered it.
You said you'd give 5% in one minute.
That's right.
What did I do?
What?
To give 5%...
In one minute?
What?
You can go up again.
It's fine.
I don't know about this week.
But how did the players do?
Let's take a look.
Thank you very much.
Oh.
Is that okay?
Yes.
Wato-san.
This is one minute.
This is one minute?
This is ideal.
This is ideal?
If you want to go up 5%, you have to go up this much.
Ideal?
I thought it was going up.
5% means that about 2 million people have joined in at this moment.
I understand.
About 2 million.
2 million.
Let's take a look.
This.
Yes.
Please look at the order here.
Yes, I'll go in order.
What's going up here?
Yes.
The postcard.
It's going up.
From here.
Wait a minute.
This one minute.
It's going up.
What's going up?
Wait a minute.
What's going up is going up, isn't it?
It's going up a little.
It's going up, isn't it?
How much did it go up?
0.6%.
But it's not going down.
Isn't this amazing?
But it doesn't have anything to do with that.
This.
This is your punishment game.
Why?
I'm the one who gave you 5%.
But this is the reason why it went up.
Well, well, well, well.
Right?
That's why I keep saying it.
But it didn't go up to 5%.
It was 0.6%.
Yes.
Now.
What do you want me to do?
Because there's nothing left.
What?
No, no, no.
I don't have money.
I don't have anything.
You don't have money.
You have a lot of money.
No, no, no.
What is it?
After all, it's what you said.
As I said before.
Did I say it?
What are you doing?
Well, I'm doing this.
I'm doing this, so my abs are okay.
Don't come suddenly.
Well, I'm glad I have this.
If you're a weak man, you'll be in trouble.
What is it?
Punishment. Punishment. Punishment game.
Why is it a punishment game?
It went up.
It didn't go up.
I said I'd give you 5%.
5%?
It can't go up.
Hey, hey, hey.
You started it.
It took so much time to spend.
I don't know.
I know, I know.
Well, it's okay.
What are you doing?
Well, we talked to the staff.
What did you just say?
The abs thing.
Yes, the abs thing.
For example.
That's also TV shopping.
You know, the strong-looking foreigner is wearing a short-sleeved T-shirt.
He's doing it, right?
That...
Otaku-san...
But wait a minute.
Is there such a thing on TV? TV shopping?
Yes, there is.
Really?
Did you do that?
Yes, I did.
But that's just a video from overseas, right?
No, I can't do it.
Are you going to California?
Why?
I can't do it.
Where are you going to do it?
I'm going to get a proper studio.
You can do it yourself.
And I recommend it to everyone watching TV.
I bought it with my own money.
What is this?
What else is there?
Also, the revival of Hitoshi and Akiko.
This is the season of Akiko's school festival.
School festival...
I want you to wait for it.
Recently, my mother...
She's been in a lot of pictures.
Again?
Yes.
And I got a call the other day.
Yesterday!
I got a call yesterday.
Hitoshi said, thank you.
What?
What do you mean, thank you?
I said that.
In Osaka, a commercial was decided.
Wait a minute.
What commercial?
Nishin's Yakisoba.
This old lady has decided to do a commercial.
I don't know if it's okay.
I said, did you say okay?
She said, yes.
I said, thank you.
What else?
This is amazing.
What is it?
Lotte.
Lotte is good.
Do you know Cool Mint Gum?
Yes, Cool Mint Gum.
Everyone, do you know?
That penguin.
There's a picture of a penguin.
What do you think?
Penguin!
What?
Are you a penguin?
Yes.
The penguin in the gum is you.
That's because I'm delicious.
I don't have to do anything.
I'll take a picture.
Really?
Location, the South Pole.
I don't care.
It's getting cold in this season.
It's finally getting cold.
Why did you have to go to the South Pole in this season?
I just wanted to take a picture.
How long does it take to get to the South Pole?
It takes about two or three hours.
What if it takes that long?
I'm half way there.
It doesn't take two or three hours.
That's right.
It doesn't take that long.
Why are you so slow?
It's okay.
It takes two or three hours.
It doesn't take two or three hours.
I'm sorry.
The South Pole.
I don't care.
It's funny.
Are you telling me to choose?
I've prepared a lot of things.
If it's for us, we don't have to go to the South Pole.
As a guest, I'm a big fan of Machan.
Wait a minute.
Don't laugh so much.
I can't get rid of the feeling of pity for Machan.
Hama-chan is arrogant.
Machan is more arrogant than Machan.
It's okay to be arrogant.
Why are you laughing?
Let me tell you the story.
At this point, I have no other opportunity.
I can go to the South Pole.
I'm sorry.
I'm the second one.
Let's go to the South Pole.
Which one do you want to choose?
The South Pole.
Which one are you going to choose?
Why should I choose?
I've been to the Arabian Sea and the safari.
I want to go to the serpent, but I can't go to New York!
I want to go to the Indian, but I can't!
What are you doing there?
What am I doing?
What were you doing when I was being punished?
What the hell were you doing when I went to the Indian?
When you were in the Indian, I was about to die!
The schedule...
Let's ask the manager.
No, no, no.
It's all messed up.
Why is it all messed up?
I don't know why, but it's all messed up all of a sudden.
For now, on Tuesday, it's all messed up.
Do you want to go to the language school?
Give me a break.
No, no, no.
It's all messed up.
What the hell?
Did you do something so bad?
The Japanese national team is in a pretty bad state at the World Cup.
It's bad, right?
A lot of people are complaining about this and that.
But this is fine.
If Matsumoto does this, the Japanese national team will be able to go to the World Cup.
I see.
Please tell us.
First of all, I want to say something to all the players.
I see.
Everyone is like that.
After all, Suonome.
Every night.
First of all, from there.
And then?
It's like this.
Please tell us properly.
Let's go.
You know Lopez, right?
Yes, yes.
His handwriting is strange.
It has nothing to do with the game.
It's called Lopez.
What is that?
What is Pe?
I don't know.
I think it's better to go to the north.
That's not it.
Is that Pe?
Yes.
There's no Pe?
There wasn't that much?
I want to look for it.
I'm desperate.
Yes, yes, yes.
Low Armour.
What's Su?
Su is this.
Su of Nasu.
Nasu Kogen.
Takasuna.
That's right.
That was good.
Pe.
There was no Pe.
There's a word called Pe, but I don't think this is it.
I don't know, so I'm going to go with Pe.
Lopez.
What is that?
Sabu.
Recently, there is a tendency to use harsh words to patients in Japan and America.
Yes, yes, yes.
I don't think the doctor will be able to say it well in front of the patient.
Thinking about the patient.
What kind of announcement should I make to prevent injury?
I see.
This is really.
This program has finally hit the wall of the funeral.
Speak quietly.
Don't write it.
I'm busy too.
After all, it's a shocking thing.
But you have to say it.
One person has to say it to one person.
That's right.
I wonder if the doctor will say it too.
After all, under the word, there is a word called Noshi.
I'm talking about whether people live or die.
Are you a cancer or Noshi?
You're going to be beaten to death.
Yes, yes, yes.
I don't say the same thing twice.
I see.
Liar.
OK, OK.
Are you ready?
After all, what makes people anxious?
It comes from loneliness.
Anxiety.
I'll get rid of this loneliness.
Loneliness?
It's not just about cancer.
I can say it about everything.
Before you say it, say something painful to the other person.
For example, it doesn't matter if it's a sideburn.
It doesn't matter.
Before you say something to the other person.
It's the same for me.
I don't know if that's a good thing.
It's good, isn't it?
Yes.
Is it good?
But it's a complete lie.
Even if you think it's a lie, it doesn't make you happy.
I see.
Right?
No matter how kind he is, he can't get angry.
It's my sideburn that's bad.
I think so.
That's where it goes.
I think that's why doctors should be like that.
I see.
I'm not like that either.
You're a cancer.
Or you'll laugh.
That's not good.
That's not good for me.
I don't understand.
That's not good.
I told you it's bad.
This program was provided by the following sponsors.