Shichihenge, the masterpiece for children.
Many of the staff have been under tremendous pressure to make this project a success.
And tonight, the new challenger is...
Shinagawa Shoji, Shinagawa Hiroshi.
He's the number one young talent who has made his way to Stardom at once.
Tonight, Shinagawa World will carve a new page in the history of Shichihenge.
Shichihenge
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
This is the first episode of Shichihenge!
It's been a while, hasn't it?
That's right.
I didn't think there would be anyone else doing this.
It's the 18th person.
He's very motivated.
Really?
I don't know what he's motivated about.
Did you say it yourself?
I thought about what kind of relationship I should have with Shoji Shinagawa before the show.
But I don't have one.
You don't have one.
I don't have one.
It's cold even if I force myself to do it.
Today's star is Shoji Shinagawa!
Nice to meet you.
The staff said this.
This is the first time we've had a meeting three times.
We usually have a meeting once.
Then we talk on the phone and talk about small things.
I see.
We've had a meeting three times.
It's different from the past.
Where are you in the world?
I'm here.
Why?
I'm scared.
I don't want to say it.
I don't want to say it, but I'm still a little scared.
I'm scared.
What should we do?
Goodbye, Yama-chan.
Graduation ceremony.
If you want to do it, it's a prank.
But everyone is saying goodbye mentally.
What do you mean?
I'm not doing it at all.
I'll show you the whole life of Tsutsuno.
I'm curious.
Right now...
Oh, I see.
But what about the gas festival that everyone was addicted to before?
That's interesting.
It's hard to grow up.
I had a headache after it was over.
I stayed on the ship for about an hour and a half.
Suga-chan.
Yes.
How many kilometers are you riding?
Oh, that's right.
Shut up.
Yes.
Well, it's used.
Tanaka.
Did you give a marriage proposal?
How much is it?
I can't hear you saying it's noisy.
Yes.
Endo.
Did you give a birthday party?
How old are you?
I can't hear you saying it's noisy.
Your story is boring.
I'm sorry.
Matsun.
If you sell the book, it's 100%.
What do you think?
How many books are you selling?
I can't hear you saying it's noisy.
Yama-chan.
Oh, it's nothing.
Yes.
Well, let's go to the bathroom.
Let's go.
It's big.
Ayato, go.
He's not doing anything.
He's acting like a girl.
I laughed at Zaki-san's acting ability.
He didn't look like a girl.
He didn't say anything.
Thank you.
Let's do this.
Matsunoto, Heipo, Onuma.
Hanano, Dokushin Unit.
That's good.
Let's go.
Matsunoto, Heipo, Onuma.
He's being teased.
He's the best.
Why did you choose that?
I thought it was a good book.
You've raised the level of good books.
It's still the same.
What are you going to do?
I don't know if the final meeting is in Korea.
Hey, you.
What is this?
It's loose.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
You've been apologized.
I'm sorry.
I said don't apologize.
Hey.
Don't take it off.
Try it.
Idiot.
What is an idiot?
Hey.
What is it?
Look at me.
I'm sorry.
Mentally.
Let me see.
It's off.
Do it properly.
I'm sorry.
I don't have time.
You only have 30 minutes.
I'm sorry.
Do it properly.
Yes, I'll do it. I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
I'm sorry.
It's a new book.
He's putting it in.
Is it M or M?
It's all M.
That's right.
Can I go to Tanaka's new home?
No.
It's still a little messy.
Is it messy?
Yes.
It's the same place as before.
It's a mess.
Isn't it the first one in order?
That's right.
He's getting ready now, isn't he?
Well, well.
He went home early to get some fresh air.
Hey.
Yes.
Thank you.
Hey.
Yes.
Thank you.
Hey.
Yes.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
It's none of your business.
Come here.
I want to get beaten up this much.
That's great.
He's amazing.
Hard, hard.
He's hard.
He's amazing.
There's still some left.
Stop it.
Don't touch my butt.
That's why I didn't want to play sumo with Shinagawa.
I won't touch it.
Don't touch my butt.
I'll touch your butt.
Then I'll play billiards.
You'll touch it anyway.
That was dangerous.
Hello.
Yes.
Now?
In the meeting.
Yes.
What?
Why?
Why did you break up?
What's that?
Vegetables.
It's impossible.
I don't want to break up.
I got it.
I'll do it.
What I want to see is more important than anything else.
I look at what's behind the pain and dream.
Everything should start from there.
I'm sorry.
It's a lie.
You were surprised.
I'm a student of the M university.
I put one in.
It's 12,000 yen.
You've earned a lot of money.
Thank you.
How was it?
The fourth one.
My heart was broken from the end.
Do you want to do it?
I'm going to do it.
He's like an AV corner.
What kind of corner?
Do you cut your hair?
I'm sure you'll cut it.
It's dirty.
I'll cut it.
It's high tech.
I'll cut it myself.
Are you angry?
Why?
I cut it for sure.
I'm sure I'll cut it the next day.
I bought it from my parents.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
You've been betrayed.
I've been betrayed.
Really?
The scissors come out from this side, right?
That's right.
That's why I discovered it.
In short, when you cut it, it's like you're holding your breath.
That's why it's not good at that time.
Even if you're holding your breath, when you're done cutting, it's like a mirror.
I don't know if it'll come out at that time.
So when you cut it.
I'll continue.
If you cut it well, I'll cut it.
Is the machine okay?
I'll put the machine in properly.
I'll raise it like this.
You look angry.
When you raised your nose, your face was probably two times more angry in Yoshimoto.
Who's number one?
I don't know.
Don't be angry if you raise your nose.
I'm not angry at all.
You look angry.
You do it.
You're a family member.
Why?
That's terrible.
Your face is funny.
I'm not angry at all.
Your mouth is funny.
Your face is really angry.
I'm not angry at all.
Your face is funny.
You look like a Korean woman.
What kind of face is that?
Your face is really angry.
Your face is funny.
I'm a man like that.
I remembered.
What?
You have to do something.
Japanese series.
You told me.
What are you going to do?
Let's say it together.
If you break up, there's no problem.
That's right.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
What's the reason?
The reason?
Do you have a reason to be on that team?
Because it's like this.
Can I say one thing?
It's close.
It's really close.
Do you have a reason to be on that team?
I don't know much about baseball.
But I'm sure there's something like that.
I think it's better to win the championship later.
It's difficult.
Are you ready?
One, two, three.
Daiei, go!
It's really cool.
But I told you first.
Then I'll go.
I'm Daiei.
This is a punishment for one person.
It's not a punishment for four people.
It's a punishment for one person.
I'll go again.
One, two, three.
HANSHI.
No, no, no.
Daiei.
I don't know.
I've been doing it twice last year.
I've been doing it a lot lately.
Shut up.
You've been playing games all this time, haven't you?
I'm Daiei.
HANSHI.
I don't know.
I'll decide what to do.
I'll stop here.
Yes.
I have to do this.
Don't do it.
The book came out.
Don't put it out.
It's not that kind of character.
It seems to cry.
Can this book cry?
The second page seems to cry.
It seems to be a kid's book.
What kind of book is it?
I don't know.
It seems to be thick, but it's about eight pages.
And it's like a notepad.
Matsumoto-san, who always wants to leave memories for everyone.
That's right.
The hit single that Matsumoto-san released when he was an idol.
I want to hear it again.
Please let me hear it.
It's okay.
I need a lot of power.
I went to the mountains.
I went to the sea.
I want you to stop clapping.
It's hard to get a pen.
I see.
Is it okay?
Are you still okay with the time?
I'm fine with the time.
You can't sell 20,000 copies like this.
I got it.
Hey!
When your partner is doing his best to make a turn,
Is it the next postcard check?
I won't do anything.
Why don't you want to do it together?
I don't know that song.
You don't remember?
I can't remember the first one.
I went to the mountains.
I went to the sea.
I went to Nagisa.
Hey!
It's over.
I ran on a stolen bike.
I brought the song from a completely different place.
I can't sell it.
Please show it to me.
What are you going to show me?
Is it over?
It's not over.
Please show it to me until the end.
I'll do it again next time.
There are times when you can't do it.
Hey!
Don't be so angry.
What's wrong with you?
There are times when you can't do it.
Don't say that.
You said you would do it next time.
There are times when you can't do it.
Don't be so angry.
That's why I'm telling you.
There are times when you can't do it.
Hey!
Don't be so angry.