Special for 4 hours.
What the hell is this?
The second time, we're going to do it seriously.
The entertainer, are you ready?
Grand Prix!
This is the second time.
Let me introduce you first.
Mr. Mahoto Otake!
Next to him is Mr. Tenme Kano!
And the last one is Mr. Hitoshi Matsumoto!
Today's question is heavy.
I think you can do it without mosaic.
I don't know if you say that.
What mosaic?
You'll write your name here, right?
There's no mosaic here?
Yes, that's right.
It's too much, too much.
But there's no mosaic here, is there?
The first question is this!
He's popular, but he's ugly when you look at him.
What's with this ugly face?
Why are you so popular?
That's weird.
You look like a monkey.
There are a lot of talents like that.
Please.
I can't think of a name.
Please explain it to me.
First of all, Mr. Otake's answer.
First of all, I asked you to ride a horse.
That's obvious.
What's a monkey?
A monkey is a guy with a banana-looking face.
Who is that?
The most popular guy in Rock.
Kubota!
Kubota Toshinobu!
I see.
You're cleaning up with a monkey.
Mr. Tenme.
Kubota was in the Japanese Army at first.
You're lying.
Mr. Ishida.
He's the third one.
He's got a shy face.
He's got a silly face.
Finally, Mr. Matsumoto.
This is definitely true.
I'm right.
Yuji Oda.
I see.
There's no mistake.
He's just a potato brother.
Please see the correct answer.
Yuji Oda.
Noriuki Makihara.
Mr. Otsurugitan.
Yuji Oda.
He's like a gorilla.
Hiroshi Hase.
Toshiro Yanagi.
Noriuki Makihara.
Mr. Otsurugitan.
Yuji Oda.
He's got a human-looking face.
Hiroshi Fusei.
Toshiro Yanagi.
He's got a chicken-looking face.
Yuji Oda.
Makihara.
He's got a big mouth.
Otsurugitan.
The correct answer is Otsurugitan.
The society is worse.
The society is the same.
I thought it was a guitar.
The society is not the same.
I thought it was Noriuki Makihara.
Is Otsurugitan popular?
He's in a trendy drama.
Otsurugitan is the correct answer.
What are you going to do when you're together?
With a guy who's in a bad mood.
I don't like this show.
Here's the next question.
An actress with a big neck.
You're good at acting.
What?
Don't be stupid.
You're good at acting.
Mr. Tenmei.
He's got a big mouth.
There are a lot of actresses.
Please draw an actress with a big neck.
You're good at drawing.
What are you going to do when you're together?
Otake looks like he's got a big neck.
That's good.
This is not good.
Otake first.
An actress with a big neck.
Get out of the way.
I got it.
Next, Mr. Tenmei.
It's obvious.
Does he have a big neck?
I don't want to see him.
I think everyone goes to work after watching that channel.
That's scary.
Last one.
I'm good at drawing.
You look like you're going to get a big neck.
I don't know how strict he is.
You look like you're going to act.
You're pretty good at drawing.
Here's the answer.
Kashiwabara.
Yoshie.
Iwasita Shima.
Kato Reiko.
Koyanagi Rumiko.
Takesaki Eiko.
Iwasita Shima.
Kato Reiko.
Kashiwabara Yoshie.
Maeda Bibari.
Koyanagi Rumiko is getting bigger and bigger.
Kato Reiko.
Koyanagi Rumiko.
That's all for today.
Last time, I was asked by Tokojyozu Taisho,
Koyanagi Rumiko.
I can hear that you can't use anything but the bed.
I'm not saying that.
I think he's a very nice person.
I want to act.
Are you going to say that again?
I can't help it.
Here's the next question.
A talent that looks like he's going to be a model.
You're a model, aren't you?
Please welcome Otake.
Did you all write it?
Yes, from Otake.
It's Tokumitsu, isn't it?
Toku-san, did you write it at that age?
I...
I don't know.
Tamori-san.
Yes.
Kameoka Ryutaro.
I see.
Now, let's see the correct answer.
Here we go.
Tantan's Natsumoto-san.
Kase-taishi.
Makihara's Ryuuki-san.
Atsuno Rikihisa.
Karasawa-san.
Kataoka Tsureta.
Jimio Onishi.
Gobuhei?
Nanoshiro-san.
Makihara's Ryuuki.
Kase-taishi-san.
Machan.
Okama-poi.
Jimio Onishi.
Kase-taishi.
Makihara-san.
Machan.
Jimio Onishi-san.
Jimio Onishi.
Machan.
Makihara-san.
Kase-taishi.
Machan.
Okama-poi.
Jimio Onishi-san.
But, there is no way.
So, the correct answer will be the buryin Yuuki.
Y status is Oh knew Shin-Uros Samei.
The correct answer is the same because there is a different one to the answer you chose.
Then...
What about the correct answer of Tsukihisa?
Ok, this is the last question!
The question is...
What the hell is going on?
Ladies and gentlemen
I'm sure everyone listens to you in the rain
You don't have anywhere to go
But the other day, I rented an apartment in Osaka
I rented an apartment in Osaka and paid for it
Why?
Why did you leave an apartment in Osaka when you lived in Tokyo?
Let's talk about it from there
No, no
Then listen
When I left Osaka and Tokyo, I also paid for the apartment
You didn't pay for it, you left it
Why did you leave it?
I had to pay two rents
Why did you come so suddenly?
It's a TV show
Why did you leave it?
If you don't have an apartment in Osaka, you have to get a hotel
when you come back from work
That's what I'm saying
That's not good
What are you talking about?
Do you have such a heart?
Even if you look like this, you look like a romanticist
That's why you can't call it a hotel
When you're alone in a hotel, you get excited
You don't have to be alone when you're alone
You don't have to sleep
I can't be called a woman in a hotel
There are a lot of women in the front
You don't have to worry about it
The biggest reason is that you can't watch the video when you're alone in a hotel
You mean the video you like?
Yes
You have a video in your hotel
Yes, but there are times when I want to stop and watch it
You want to watch it as soon as possible
Yes, I want to watch it as soon as possible
What did you forget to do?
I want to watch it as soon as possible
That's right
I wanted to watch it myself
Then I watched the video for the playlist
I can bring the playlist
You want to watch a video like that?
I want to watch a video like that
Then I watched the video for the playlist
Then I went to the hotel's TV
I don't know if I can go
Then I called my friend in front of me
I called my friend in front of me
I asked him if he could watch the video for the playlist
He said he could probably do it
Then I went to the TV
I was able to do it
And I borrowed money from my friend
I was selling erotic videos for 1000 yen in Osaka
I bought it and went to the hotel
You went to the hotel
I called my friend in front of me
I heard from Mr. Matsumoto
He said he was going to install it
I asked him if he could do it
An electrician and a bell boy came into my room
Then I did it
I think I can do it
But I don't know if I can do it
Can you show me a little?
Do you have a video?
I have a video but I don't have it
I don't have anything to show you
I said I don't have it
But it came out of my bag
I could see the boy's eyes
He looked at me and said,
I don't have it
I have it but it's not an erotic video
He looked at me with his eyes
I don't have it
What are you talking about?
Can you talk like that?
After I came back
I took it out of my bag
I have a video of the hotel
The video and the erotic video are the same
So I was screaming
But there was an escalator
I was excited
It's the same
It was hard
I couldn't see it
I thought about it
I turned on the TV
Listen
You are a fool
I don't want to go to the hotel
I don't want to go
Then I became a star
What are you talking about?
I can't take it
It's an erotic video
It's naked
I bought a bag
You are spending a lot of money
I put it in
It's very heavy
If it was real, it would be like this
But when I checked in
It's cool
It's connected
It's an erotic video
I don't know what you are talking about
It's very heavy
I can't take it
It's an erotic video
It's hard
The screen is small
I'm not hard
You are strong
I can't take it
You are erotic
I'm an erotic person
Let's talk about my Okamoto
He is terrible
Did you hear the reason why he didn't come to my location?
Why didn't you come?
When I woke up in the morning, my shoulder was off
There is no reason
It took me a long time to get up
I'm a bad person
He was here
The other day
I was shooting a program
I wanted to go home
I wanted to prepare a taxi
I wanted to go by my car
I didn't have time to prepare a taxi
I understand
Okamoto, where are you going next?
To the right
Next is to the right
Go back
There is no left
Why are you going to the right?
Do you have a big will?
I understand
Are you going to the right?
I was excited
You are really stupid
I'm sorry
You are stupid
This guy
This guy had sex with me
You are lying
This guy
What do you mean by that?
What happens when you wake up in the morning?
I don't think you understand my explanation.
You don't understand my explanation.
I'm still in a bad mood.
Are you angry?
No, I'm not angry.
What happens when you wake up in the morning?
When I wake up?
Yes.
Like this.
No, no. You should try sleeping.
You should try sleeping.
Why do you want to wake up?
You're sleeping, aren't you?
That's how you sleep?
Yes, yes.
Well, that's fine.
And then?
Oh, you woke up.
That's not good.
You're not out of it yet.
I'm not out of it yet.
What happens when you're out of it?
If I don't stretch, I can't wake up.
I'm like this.
You're not out of it yet.
If I don't stretch, I can't wake up.
Don't make a face like when you're talking about sleep.
I'm not out of it yet.
But you understand.
Hold it like this.
Why don't you hold it like this?
If you don't hold it like this, you'll be in trouble.
What are you talking about?
What happens if you don't hold it like this?
Oh, I see.
That's scary.
Hold it like this.
If you do this, you'll be in trouble.
Do you know how to get out of it?
It's a habit.
Like you always do.
Like this.
Like this?
Yes, yes.
And then?
Like this.
I want to eat poop.
Here you go.
I had two of these when I was a kid.
Yes.
Which one do you want?
This one.
This is the only one.
There's nothing in the letter.
What is Soviet?
I'm from the North.
What do you mean by the North?
Aren't you from the North?
And there's nothing in the letter.
What's the pen name?
I don't know.
In the theme song of the TV anime, Doraemon, there's a line that goes,
An An An, I love Doraemon very much.
What does An An An mean?
Here you go.
Do you need to repeat it three times?
It means the love for Doraemon.
The love for An An An?
Actually, this is a children's show, so you can't do that kind of thing.
That's why it's called An An An.
But in the adult world, Doraemon means An An An.
An An An, Doraemon, shut up!
In the announcement of the train, there's always something like,
Next stop is the station, subway, transfer, and so on.
But why do you say it in such a dirty way?
I don't say it in such a dirty way.
It sounds like it's stuck in your nose.
Next stop is the station, transfer, and so on.
It sounds like you have something in your stomach.
It sounds like it's stuck in your nose.
Next stop is the station, transfer, and so on.
What's that?
I was the most angry on the plane.
What happened on the plane?
There was a brown-haired person on the plane.
All foreigners are brown-haired.
There's a brown-haired person who talks a lot.
His head is like this.
Oh!
It's like the character in Jump, Tar-chan.
He was on the plane, and he was reading a story.
He was sitting diagonally behind him.
A young woman was sitting behind him.
He was sitting under a juice, like a receipt.
And he was writing something on the coaster.
He was like a love letter.
And he was reading a love letter.
And he told the girl to give him the love letter.
And the girl who gave him the love letter told him to sit down.
And he said, Tar-chan, sit down and smile.
I was looking at her with a little annoyed face, but when I got there, everyone was going out, and my mother was always there.
Until that woman came, I was waiting for the bomber.