The first episode of Gaki no Tsutaya is next!
Summer, sea, sunshine, beach tour!
The sun is up.
Yes.
From now on.
It's the sea and the pool.
I don't know why the aloha of Endo and the aloha of Suzuki are the same.
They are not the same.
I think they are the same.
Let's go to the beach!
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Did you bring it?
Yes, we did.
I brought this too.
I brought it too.
This is good.
Can we start already?
Just a little bit more.
What?
Why is it stopped?
Let's go.
The sun will go down soon.
What is this?
What?
What is he doing?
He is carrying a gun.
What?
He is getting in the car.
Don't move!
If you move, I'll shoot you.
What are you talking about?
I took this bus.
Why don't you go to the beach?
I have a knife.
If you don't listen to me, I'll shoot you.
You don't know anything.
What are you talking about?
Let's go to the beach.
I don't want to go to the beach today.
What?
I don't treat people well these days.
Let's go.
I don't care.
If you move, I'll shoot you.
I don't treat people well these days.
I want to improve my image.
I want to do something cool today.
I thought about it.
Don't move!
I'll shoot you.
You shot me.
I'm sorry.
What is it?
I'm going to improve my image.
I'm going to do something cool.
Why?
I've been a bad guy.
When I was a Napoleon, when I was a king,
When I was a king,
I was a bad guy.
I want to show you a cool me.
I'm setting up myself.
Don't do that.
If you change the program, it won't work.
I don't want to go to the beach.
I'll go to the beach.
I think you know it.
I'm not good at it.
I don't want to go to the beach.
I want you to follow me quietly today.
If you follow me, I'll be okay.
A local bus jack.
What made Heipou so violent?
The problem seems to be his misbehavior as a kid.
And it seems that he has found an unexpected end.
So this time, he put his life on the line.
He set up an image-up plan of his own.
The jacked up members were taken to the scene where Heipou was ready.
What is this?
I'll explain from the big rock.
Mr. Kameda, are you ready?
I'm going to do this today.
Ta-da!
A big rock is rolling towards the girl.
A big rock.
Heipou is cool.
This is cool.
I'm going to be a superman and save the girl from this big rock.
That's what I'm going to do today.
I'm going to do the world's Heipou big present.
I'll stop the big rock in the middle of the road.
Will the world's Heipou big present image-up plan succeed?
Look at that.
That's the real Heipou.
It has a bell on it.
This is Heipou.
I want to do something with this bell.
It's a huge set.
The total length is 30 meters, the height is 6 meters, and the diameter of the rock is 2 meters.
The bell and the theme are all special.
A big rock is rolling towards the girl.
I'm going to make a cool image-up plan.
I'm only going to do it once.
Mr. Kameda, are you ready?
It's dangerous.
Can you stop it?
It's cool if you can stop it.
If it's like in the picture, you can stop it like this.
I can stop it with one hand.
If you can do that, it's a big success.
I think my wife will laugh.
Is that what you're going to do?
That's what I'm going to do.
Image-up, image-up.
Heipou is not laughing right now, so please hold on.
Please.
It's dangerous.
He's running away.
He's coming.
I'm a superman, so I have to change my clothes.
Heipou, hurry up.
I'm going to fall.
Hurry up.
It's too late.
Heipou, hurry up.
I'm waiting for you.
Why are you wearing a T-shirt?
It's definitely not good.
It's just that you're in a hurry.
I'm not in a hurry or anything.
What is it?
It says Saito.
Glasses, glasses.
Thank you for waiting.
It's dangerous.
What are you going to do?
You can't run away.
It's too big.
It's too fast.
I've never seen a girl like that.
I understand. I'll do it again.
I'll do it again.
I understand.
I'll set it up again.
The talent is waiting.
Hurry up.
I'm going.
I want you to run away.
It's coming.
It's scary.
I'm scared.
It's too late.
I'll do it again.
Really?
You just threw it.
I didn't throw it. I protected it.
I didn't protect it.
Look at it.
I protected it.
I didn't protect it.
Hurry up and put it up.
Please do it again.
Really?
I can't do it anymore.
Do it again.
Saito, do your best.
I understand.
I can't do it.
I don't want it to come out like this.
You don't want it to come out, right?
I don't want it to come out.
We'll start the show.
It's coming.
Is this okay?
The girl fell.
I didn't protect it.
Are you okay?
You can't go, right?
You spent a lot of money, right?
Yes.
You can go home like this.
But for the show...
Decide.
I can't take it off like this.
I don't want it to come out.
Saito, hey!
You'll get in trouble for that.
In the face of the ridiculous situation,
the comedian Yamazaki
stands on the battlefield of laughter.
Take it from the shelf.
Arushu.
What is Arushu?
Take Arushu.
If I go to help you, you can take it off.
If Ooiwa comes.
I don't know anything about that.
I don't know anything.
I'm just playing in the park right now.
I'm just holding hands.
I don't know anything.
The girl is dangerous.
I don't know if Ooiwa will come.
If you look at it,
It's like this.
I see.
What is this?
Dangerous.
Hurry up.
First of all, Hamada's medicine box.
Where are you?
Are you okay?
It hurts.
Hello, hello.
How are you?
Are you a little confused?
This year,
It's like that.
Something like a wind blows.
I don't know.
I don't know what to say.
If you don't say something like a wind,
Is this story a joke?
That's right.
What kind of wind is the problem?
But after that,
It's okay because it's big.
It's big.
This year,
Something like a wind blows.
It is said that Asia is very hot.
It is said.
So it's hot this year.
It's very hot.
It's because of the wind.
I see.
That's why I can't help it.
Really.
That's what it is.
Well, that's the end of this story.
Well, it's not that bad.
I want you to cut this.
If you know the name of the wind.
That's right.
How are you?
Really, these days.
I think I've said this before.
But at that time,
The customer's reaction was very bad.
There's a story I quit on the way.
What's that?
I'm not wrong.
I wanted to say this.
Can I say it again?
Please.
I live alone.
So I do the laundry myself.
Please ask the real estate agent.
I live alone.
The real estate agent.
It's up to you.
After that, it's up to you.
I live completely alone.
I do the laundry myself.
I wash my underwear.
I take off my underwear in the bathroom.
You can take it off anywhere.
I don't want to put it in a basket.
So I put it on the outside.
Do you understand?
It can be the back.
So I put it on the outside.
I do the laundry.
I put the dryer in.
I fold it.
It's definitely the back.
I'm angry.
What do you mean?
It's been turned around a lot.
I thought so, too.
I thought it was fluffy inside.
Once, I put about 10 pieces of underwear on the back.
When I saw it was done, it was all on the back.
Can you explain this?
If I can, I want to get smaller and put it in the dryer.
I want to see what's going on.
It's the back now.
It's definitely strange.
How can it be like that?
You don't understand, do you?
Look at it from the husband's point of view.
The laundry is pretty weak.
It's like a mountain.
I put it on the back and put it on the outside.
If I can shorten this time, how much better is it?
Then the number of meals for the husband who comes back will increase.
It's on the outside, so it won't increase.
That's not true.
I think I can explain that.
I put 10 pieces of underwear on the front.
How many pieces will come out on the front?
I see.
I think it's definitely strange.
It's okay.
I don't have a hand.
It's like a DVD.
There are times when even the shirt is turned inside out.
It's definitely a lie.
Such a thin shirt is turned inside out?
I don't know how many times it's turned inside out.
It doesn't matter if it's turned inside out.
If it's turned inside out, go back once.
No, go back once and go home again.
It's turned inside out again?
What is that?
Well, it's a kind of harassment.
It's harassment.
I don't want to be cut.
I don't want to be cut by you.
What do you mean by that?
Are you going to fight today?
It's strange.
Today's audience reacted well.
What are you talking about?
I think it's because of the atmosphere.
If you watch TV again, you'll think,
why is he talking like that?
It's not like that.
He's got a question about that.
And he remembers the anger.
And he's trying to solve it.
He has to get angry.
He's trying to make the shirt inside out.
Can't you make a dryer that doesn't turn inside out?
You're going to buy it.
I'll definitely buy it.
It's going to be a little more expensive than a normal dryer.
Everyone doesn't buy it.
You don't have to turn it inside out.
You can develop it.
And then you can do it with Project X.
It's okay to do it.
It's okay to make it.
I'll do it.
I'll think about it.
A dryer that never turns inside out.
I'm going to release Project X by myself.
It's okay if it comes out.
It's going to be a documentary.
I'm going to cry a lot.
Matsumoto dug in 10 sheets.
I couldn't turn it inside out.
I don't want to come out at all.
I want you to come out.
I want you to come out when I make it.
I'm really angry.
It's okay.
You don't wash it, do you?
When I was living alone, I washed it myself.
I'm not doing it.
I can't do it.
Why?
I've been wearing dirty underwear all the time.
It's a carotene.
I'm going to get a lot of shit on my underwear.
You threw it away, didn't you?
You too, didn't you?
I just remembered.
What?
I don't know the weather at that time.
There was a live drama before.
I think you were nervous at that time.
It hurts a lot when you're nervous.
I've been nervous since I got home.
I'm nervous because it's a live drama.
I think it's okay.
I went home and I thought it was okay.
It hurts a lot.
I think it's not okay at all.
If you were nervous at that time, you wouldn't have felt the pain, would you?
But I remember.
I remember Chippu.
I remember Matsumoto Chippu.
I remember it, too.
But I'm not talking about that.
Why aren't you used to the live drama?
I thought you'd talk to me more.
Why are you making that face?
What should I do?
That's right.
When I first talked to Endo, he looked like this.
He talked to Tanaka right away.
Tanaka, too.
I was looking at you in the middle of the play.
When I went out, you hit me.
It was amazing.
I hit you in the neck.
No matter how old you get, you're still young.
When you get older, you get muscle pain after a day.
What does that mean?
Please explain the mechanism of the body.
This is the muscle.
Simply put, it's aging.
When you're young, let's say you've done 50 push-ups.
When you're young, if you talk, it hurts.
From the 49th day, you're like, I'm moving.
But when you're in your 40s or 50s, you're like this.
When you're in your 50s, you're like this.
You don't realize it.
I'm still drinking tea.
The next day, I felt like I was moving.
You have to speak clearly.
You can have a laugh with any animal.
Please tell me the difference between a goat and a sheep's cry.
It's a classic writing.
You can't do a goat's cry.
You don't want to do it.
It's a joke.
You can't do a sheep's cry.
It's like that.
Please tell me the difference.
There's a difference.
Really?
It's completely different.
A goat's cry is like this.
A sheep's cry is like this.
It's like this.
It's different.
I'll ask you.
What's a goat's cry?
A goat's cry is like this.
If you say it in American, it's like this.
It's completely different.
Really?
That's right.
That's what I'm saying.
Why?
That's what we can hear.
We can't hear it.
You can't hear it.
A sheep's cry is like this.
It doesn't matter.
It's like this.
A goat's cry is like this.
You're not a telecom person.
I'm not.
A goat's cry is like this.
Try a lion's cry.
It's completely different.
It's just a feeling.
What are you saying?
A lion's cry is like this.
I heard it.
Seriously.
It's like this.
No.
What about a pig?
A pig.
It's the worst.
What did you say?
A pig?
Didn't you say that?
How can you hear a pig?
It's like this.
I said it.
Who?
I've never said a goat's cry.
They all said it.
What are you doing?
It's weird.
I couldn't hear it.
No.
I can't hear it.
It's like this.
I didn't say anything.
What?
What if I told you?
I'm sure you'd say it.
No, I'm not.
You have to say it.
No.
You don't say it clearly.
You have to say it clearly.
It's no good if you say it clearly.
You can't say it like that.
No.
I can't say it that way.
So you mean it.
Okay.
I think you should doubt Mimi.
But she's basically crying.
I didn't say anything. The cat is meowing, right?
I didn't say anything at all.
The dog is meowing, right?
We've been taught that since we were little.
The American dog is meowing, right?
It's fine if it's meowing.
It's meowing.
It's true that the American dog meows twice.
It meows once.
It meows twice.
It meows, meows.
That's fine.
It's fine if it's meowing.
The cat is meowing, right?
It's not meowing.
Let's solve this one by one.
Let's do the lion.
The lion is...
Do the chicken.
It's changed.
It's not changed.
Do the dog.
So the cat is...
Let's do the cat.
It's not the cat.
Let's do the other one.