This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
It's been a long time since I played a game like this.
It's been 3 weeks.
3 weeks of...
Punishment.
We played a punishment game.
The reviews were good.
I see.
I think it was good.
Let's go to the post office.
Yes.
The collar is standing up.
Cut it properly.
I've been doing drama for a long time.
That's right.
If you make a mistake, there will be a murder case.
Why?
You're not sleeping.
But everyone who does drama is like that.
It's amazing. The schedule for the post office is 28 o'clock.
What is that 28 o'clock?
It's natural.
We studied 24 hours.
28 hours.
One day.
I've been doing drama for a long time.
It was open for about 4 hours.
I thought I'd take a nap here.
I went to the sauna.
I didn't want to go to the sauna.
There was a place to sleep.
I wanted to take a nap.
I lay down.
What is that?
What?
There was a man without breathing.
What do you mean?
I was surprised.
I wanted to take a nap with a digital camera.
There was a man.
He was dead.
That's scary.
But he was sleeping comfortably.
He didn't wake up.
He was dead at that moment.
He wasn't breathing.
He was doing it.
But he was dead at that moment.
He wasn't dead.
He was fighting.
His body was still alive.
But he was dying.
I don't know.
I was surprised.
I don't know if I'm breathing.
I don't do it.
There are many people who breathe.
You do it too, right?
I don't do it.
I do it.
I do it lightly.
I don't know what he did yesterday.
He snores.
Sometimes he does this.
What is that?
I can't do it.
I want to do it if I can.
But I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
The sound was like that.
He snores.
This is normal.
This is the quietest.
Sometimes he does this.
There were no other customers.
There were two people.
Except you.
There were two people except me.
He was noisy.
I thought he was bothering me.
He was sleeping.
I didn't care about him.
This guy.
I see.
I'm definitely more tired than you.
Than him?
Yes.
You don't work when you wake up.
I don't know.
The money you earn is different.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I'm tired.
My underwear is dirty.
Tell me after you see if it's dirty.
He is definitely fat.
He is very fat.
He is fat.
I have a lot of fat.
He is not fat.
Tell me at the end.
Fat people don't have a sense of shame.
There was a manager in Nozawa.
Ishigori Meat.
He came to me in the morning.
He asked me to let him sleep.
He asked me to wake him up an hour before my show.
He said it was time.
I woke up and checked the clock.
It was about three hours.
It was an hour before my show.
It's okay.
That's funny.
Did that happen?
Yes.
Do you have anything good to say?
I don't know.
Fat people are usually like that.
The baseball game has started.
The Giants are still winning.
Have you been winning all the time?
I've been doing well lately.
I've been saying that I hate baseball all the time.
I was hoping for the collapse of professional baseball.
But that's impossible.
I finally understood that it was impossible.
I'm going to be a fan of the Giants from this year.
That's not true.
There are 12 baseball teams.
There are 12 baseball teams in the baseball game.
That's right.
You can choose one of them.
I'm going to be a fan of the Giants from this year.
I'm a fan of the Giants from this year.
Really?
I'm a huge fan of the Giants.
I'm going to be a fan of Uehara this year.
I'm going to be a fan of the baseball team.
That's great.
I can do it.
This year you joined the Giants in the FA division.
Do you know who is here?
Of course I know.
I'm going to win the Giants this year.
That's right.
Because he came.
He's a bit big headed.
That's not it.
Ah, so he's a bit big headed.
He's from Hiroshima.
He's here.
He's the guy who sold the 4th edition in Hiroshima.
The guy who sold the 4th edition is here.
He's here.
I don't really like his hairstyle.
He's a bit of a Chirichiri Parma.
Chirichiri Parma?
He's not a Chirichiri Parma.
He's not a Chirichiri Parma, but...
He's kind of like a Chirichiri Parma.
Right?
Do you know which team won 2 points last year?
Daiei.
Ah, that's right.
I know about that.
Because you were a kid's servant.
The guy who was the ace there...
He's here.
I was happy.
It was a happy day.
I want you to do it.
I want you to throw a lot of shinkas.
Shinkas?
I want you to study.
We're the same age.
Nakamura.
It's not Nakamura.
It's not Nakamura, but I was thinking of calling you Nakamura.
I dared to.
You're wearing a dog.
I won that!
I don't care if you call me Nakamura.
Nakamura.
I'll do it this year.
Maru Kano.
Maru Kano?
Maru Kano was in Hankyu, right?
Wasn't he there?
No, no.
He was in Hankyu, right?
Maru Kano.
There's no Hankyu Braves anymore.
That's not what Maru Kano means now.
Really?
Maru Kano means thank you.
Maru Kano means thank you?
It's like Maru at the end of the story.
Oh, really?
It's okay.
I'm a W giant fan.
Okay, let's go.
Remember.
I'm also interested in soccer.
Oh, soccer.
I don't know soccer.
You're talking about the Espans.
A big fan?
A big fan.
If you say that, you're a big fan.
There's no way you're a fan of the Espans.
I'm tired of it.
You're wearing dirty underwear.
You're covered in dung.
You don't know the name of the club, do you?
Well, if you ask me, I don't know the name of the club.
Okay, then.
The Espans.
The Veltis.
Do you know the Veltis?
The Juvelo.
The F. Marinos.
Like this.
I don't want to end it like this.
It can't be helped if you keep doing this.
It's over.
It's really...
It's really hard.
This is a question for the world's best
stripper, Matsumoto-san.
There's a place like that.
When you clean your room with a roller cleaner,
what sticks to it?
What sticks to everyone?
I want to ask the other way around.
I think my world is normal.
I want to ask what sticks to everyone.
I see.
I think my world is normal.
That's a bad thing to say.
Including my sister?
Including everything.
Wait a minute.
You live with your family, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
Why are you drooling?
We...
We live alone.
We have an outlaw.
Ever since I left the bath,
I've been drooling in the kitchen.
That's why I wash my hair.
That's right.
Because no one can see it.
You've never washed your hair with a roller cleaner, have you?
It shakes a lot.
Like this.
At the end, when the bubbles are thin,
it shakes a lot.
You don't know that.
If I wash my hair with a roller cleaner,
I usually don't tremble.
I've never washed my hair,
but I dry my hair.
With a roller cleaner?
Yes.
Because it's hot.
If I dry my hair like this,
it shakes a lot.
It shakes a lot.
It shakes a lot, doesn't it?
No, it doesn't.
When the cup is full of bubbles,
it shakes like this at the end.
At that time, it shakes a lot.
You don't know that, do you?
So we...
We're drooling in the bath,
but before our wives and children give birth,
we don't drool that much.
But still,
you'll fall, won't you?
Why would I fall?
If you scratch something,
you'll fall, won't you?
Like a jersey.
You'll fall, won't you?
I'm an outlaw,
so I'll fall.
Everywhere I go,
it's full of drool.
I've fallen more than here.
You're the best in the world.
That's why I...
I have a lot of hair fall.
If I do it like this.
But...
I have a lot of female hair fall, too.
Oh, I see.
In the world.
What?
You hate foreigners.
No, no.
I've met a lot of Australians,
and people from other countries.
If I do it like this,
I have a lot of hair fall.
It doesn't matter.
I have a question for Matsumoto-san,
who always smells fruity.
Matsumoto-san, who always smells fruity.
I have a question for Matsumoto-san,
who always smells fruity.
What?
Recently, Matsumoto-san has been
opposed to animal fortune-telling,
and has been criticized for fruity fortune-telling.
What kind of characteristic does Hamada-san have
when he praises fruits?
I think sushi fortune-telling is popular these days.
It's popular.
Oh, is that so?
Yes.
I think I've said that once as a kid.
I see.
That's just an excuse.
How do you do sushi fortune-telling?
Oh, how do you do sushi fortune-telling?
I'm not asking you.
How do you do the popular sushi fortune-telling?
Matsumoto-san,
what kind of sushi do you like?
Depending on the order,
what kind of sushi do you recommend?
That's stupid.
That's really true.
Shut up.
You're the one who's stupid.
Oh, depending on the order you like?
Yes, yes.
I see.
That's how you choose.
What you're doing is fruit fortune-telling.
Fruit fortune-telling?
Yes.
How do you do it?
Fruit?
Do you say the fruit you like?
Yours?
I don't mind if it's mine.
Do you say the fruit you like
to the person you want to fortune-tell?
Yes, that's right.
Let's say you say it.
That's how you know, right?
I know, I know.
I see.
Then what's your favorite fruit?
That's right.
You have to say it right away.
I'm sorry.
When you're thinking, that's a lie.
I see, I see.
What's your favorite fruit?
Nothing.
You said nothing.
What?
I got it. Nothing.
That's how you know?
Your eyes are twitching.
Nothing.
You can't say nothing.
Then say three things.
Nothing.
Strawberry.
That's gross.
Peach.
Nothing, strawberry, peach?
What's your blood type?
Type A.
Type A?
Okay.
It doesn't look like that.
Really?
What did you find out?
I found out a lot of things.
That's enough data for now.
And it's until May, right?
Yes, until May.
If you put that data into my head now,
the answer will come out of my mouth.
You already put it in, right?
I did.
You did?
Then 3000 yen.
Why are you taking my money?
I'll take your money.
Please.
You don't want to?
You know, right?
I know.
Please.
I said I know!
Don't be stupid.
Hurry up and say it.
What do you mean?
Listen to me first.
What?
Listen to my fruit.
Why do you have to listen to me?
Am I that?
Are you only interested in Matsumoto or Hamada?
Why aren't you interested in me?
No, no.
Wait a minute.
That's what makes me angry.
No, no, no.
What?
I'm the only one who's interested in you.
Do you think it's funny?
You're stupid.
Listen to me.
Then I'll answer you and that's it.
You're stupid.
Then I'll take off my suit.
No, no.
No one knows what a fortune-teller is.
If you don't answer me,
if I ask you,
how can I answer you?
Then tell me if you want to know or not.
What do you want?
Tell me.
Do you like me or hate me?
Do you want to know or not?
Then...
If you tell me how to answer,
I'll ask you and that's it.
I see.
I understand.
There's a way.
There's no way to answer.
Everyone watching on TV,
if you have a notepad,
please give it to me.
If you have a notepad,
What about you?
No.
N Broth An account of how many fruits Grown?
If you have a notepad,
10 a thing.
That's right.
Let's see how much you have.
How many lot is a notepad?
How many one?
Just it let me see it.
They just say this suddenly.
If they tell you before,
I'll prepare for it too
Then, we have loss when we have lot of it.
Of course we have that kind of thing.
If you use 1 N,
you will choose 2.
No 2.
Then if you keep
If you subtract 1 from that, it's 2, right?
And from there...
It's a lie!
The peach is left after the strawberry.
That's right.
I don't know what to do with this.
You add the peach, right?
Ah, you add it like this?
It becomes 43.
I don't understand why it's 43.
Why? It's noisy!
It's noisy, so what?
It becomes 43, right?
And in this case, 4 doesn't disappear.
Only 3 remains.
Yes.
What the hell is this?!
Are you stupid?
I'll call out your voice on the phone.
It's difficult.
What?
What's the result?
It's 43, so 4 disappears, right?
Ah, this one disappears.
4 disappears.
Actually, this one disappears.
The fact that 3 appears means that it's a gorilla.
3 is a gorilla.
In this case...
In which case?
I don't understand.
And you were born in May.
Ah, May.
Please add 5 to the gorilla born in May.
Adding a gorilla is strange.
I was told to add May and gorilla.
And what happens if you add a gorilla in May?
What happens if you add a gorilla in May?
I don't understand.
Why don't you understand?
Did you get a lesson?
I was told to add a gorilla in May.
If you add a gorilla in May, it's May, right?
Does the number 3 earlier have nothing to do with it?
In this case, it disappears.
If you add a gorilla in May, it's May, right?
Right?
If you don't understand here, you can't go to the next step.
Well, yes.
If you add a gorilla in May, it's May, right?
Normally, you don't add it, right?
It's nothing like that.
Normally, you don't add it?
If you add a gorilla in May...
Then, what happens if you add a fish in August?
It's August, right?
It has nothing to do with animals and the moon, right?
Originally, it's strange to add a gorilla in May, right?
You know that, right?
But I want to add a gorilla in May.
It's that kind of season.
May.
I wonder if that's the answer.
But even if you add a gorilla in May, nothing happens, right?
I know that you won't understand.
But I want to add a gorilla in May.
It's a melancholic night.
It doesn't matter.
Even if you add a gorilla in May, it doesn't mean anything.
It doesn't mean anything, but I want to add a gorilla in May.
If you say it doesn't mean anything, everything will be fine.
I want to add a gorilla in May.
So I added a gorilla in May.
But as I thought, no matter how many times I add a gorilla, it's May.
Gorillas are gorillas.
So please leave the gorilla here for a while.
Yes, yes.
It will come out again later.
Right?
And it's May, right?
And it's decided that it's May.
In other words, you were born in May.
So you can look for it in May.
It doesn't matter whether you like fruits or not.
It doesn't matter.
The result is the same, but there is an episode.
Please look at the history.
History is something you decided on your own.
It's the same with gorillas.
No, no, no.
What did I say earlier?
There are gorillas here again.
You also put gorillas here on your own, right?
But gorillas are still here.
There are three gorillas.
If you say three, it's a gorilla.
You said it yourself.
There are gorillas, so be careful.
If you say three, it's a gorilla.
You said it yourself.
You said it yourself, so I'm coming.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.