In the third episode of Gaki no Tsukai Arahen, Tsukitsuki Oogiri University!
This is Mr. Tan's hammer.
Now, in front of everyone, Oogiri!
Let's hear how everyone is doing!
Everyone, please come out!
Let's introduce ourselves.
First, please come this way.
The other day, when I went home,
there was a beautiful woman near my house,
so when I approached her,
she was my male friend.
She was beautiful.
Next to Jimmy-san,
I'm also a little shy.
I'm Team Zero's Noriyasu.
In addition to the nightlife of Downtown Matsumoto-san,
I also have a problem with my handwriting.
It must be difficult for us to study together.
My name is Hamada-san.
My name is Funanori.
What is your heart?
There is a woman in the port.
You guys have too many dirty jokes.
I have a bad image.
I can't be on the air.
I'll tell you a mystery.
My name is...
Say your name!
I'm surprised!
I'm Downtown Matsumoto.
Nice to meet you!
Next, our young man.
I've been a little red lately.
I'm Akamaru Kyoya.
First of all,
Tokyo-zen Murimondo!
Two of you,
please talk to each other in Tokyo-zen.
Team Zero's Yamazaki and Noriyasu,
let's go to Tokyo-zen Murimondo!
Thank you!
Speak!
Set 3!
That's right!
Your eyes are beautiful!
What is that?
Isn't it Tokyo-zen?
Tokyo-zen!
Your eyes are beautiful!
Your clothes are blue!
As you can see!
Otomo-kun is from here.
Me and Osaka-ben Murimondo.
May I?
We met in Osaka.
We were classmates.
We're childhood friends.
I see.
Let's go!
Long time no see!
How are you?
I'm fine.
You're still young.
How are you?
I don't have much time.
It's bad luck.
Stop it!
It's bad luck!
Okamoto-kun and Matsumoto-kun, let's go to Tokyo-zen Murimondo again!
I'm screwed!
Say it again!
We're going to talk about being screwed.
I'm screwed!
What?
Huh?
It's because of that.
What?
What are you talking about?
Stop talking!
Let's fight.
That was close!
What?
Who are you talking to?
It's fine.
It's over.
Finally, let's have a party!
Today, we have some stuff from the convenience store.
Let's have them sing a song!
Let's go!
Matsumoto-kun!
Yamazaki-kun!
Let's go!
Let's start with Onigiri.
Onigiri song.
Onigiri and Onigiri.
Matsumoto!
Matsumoto-kun!
Last one!
Ladies and gentlemen.
It's been a while.
Well, well.
We're in the rainy season.
I hope it ends soon.
Is that so?
I'm a little nervous.
But you're under the blue sky.
Wow, Hanako-san!
Who's Hanako-san?
You're not that kind of character.
I'm not going to run like this because it's sunny.
That's not what I'm saying.
You're not an outdoor person.
You used to surf like me.
Don't mess with me!
What?
I've been surfing for over 20 years, but this is the first time I've heard of it.
You used to surf?
Of course.
I used to be a little like that.
I had a mushroom.
It's true.
Nami is scary.
If you make fun of Nami, it's true.
How many years have you been surfing?
How many years?
I've been surfing for about eight years.
Since when?
Since I was about 13 years old.
What kind of experience have you had so far?
Have you ever thought of dying?
I've never thought of dying.
I went to New Zealand.
I just heard that.
You went to New Zealand?
For a tournament?
I didn't think I'd be surfing at that time.
That's right.
When I was in junior high school.
I went to New Zealand.
It was a stormy night.
I visited my acquaintance's house.
You don't have any acquaintances in New Zealand?
What's your name?
MacGyar.
Steve from MacGyar.
Wait a minute.
I don't know MacGyar.
Who is Steve?
He's my son.
MacGyar's son.
How many?
Four at that time.
Do you talk to each other?
I don't know four of them.
My father used to...
Look at my father.
He was a foreign exchange student.
And then...
I used to run around in a tanker every day.
Your father was riding a tanker.
He had a high fever.
Who?
Stephanie.
Stevens.
There was no doctor in that town.
Far away.
I had to go to the other island across the sea.
You lived in a big place.
That's right.
MacGyar.
It was a big storm.
My son had a high fever at that time.
What are you going to do?
I don't know what to do.
I got it.
I saw a wave.
What was that?
I don't know.
Was that a wave?
I saw a wave.
I don't know.
I saw a board.
My brother, it's hot.
My body is hot.
No.
It's dangerous.
What's dangerous?
If you leave it like this, it's dangerous.
It's dangerous.
I want to borrow it.
I'll borrow it.
You're a fool.
It's true.
It was good.
You're a man.
Is that so?
Yes.
I want to watch this show in the summer.
I want to watch the opening of the show in August.
I want to watch it on the beach.
What month is it now?
It's July.
It will be a month later.
That's right.
Why are you saying that?
Until then, I'll be a mushroom.
No.
What are you doing?
Your head should be a mushroom.
Well, that's...
You should prepare a mushroom.
The staff here are fools.
I'll do it for real.
I want to see it.
Everyone was holding hands.
Show it to me.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's dangerous.
When you light it up...
It's coming out, right?
I don't know if I should say it in technical terms.
Please say it.
There's a board, right?
Yes.
It's coming out under the board.
What is that?
What is it?
It's coming out.
This is a wing.
Do you call this a wing?
It's my group.
It's my NIAIYAGARA BOYS.
It's enough.
In general...
What's NIAIYAGARA BOYS?
This is a group we make.
What's that?
There's more.
You can't be so proud of yourself.
There's nothing.
You were born.
You need to challenge yourself.
I think so.
You do, right?
I'm doing most sports.
I'm already doing it, and then, what is it, I also play the drums.
Well, I'm pretty good at it.
When I'm frustrated, I go like this.
Where do you do it?
I don't know, I don't know.
Ah, I see.
Well, I'm already doing it.
How do you do it?
Well, I go like this.
Well, I'm already doing it.
Ah, I see.
Well, I can't say much about myself.
When I was doing a show before, everyone was playing the instruments.
You were playing the bass.
Why did you tell me at that time that you couldn't do it?
You were playing the castanets.
You were playing the oboe.
You were playing the chorus.
Everyone was doing their best.
I don't know why, but you were playing the udon next to me.
You were playing the castanets like this.
Why didn't you do it at that time?
Well, I was at the bacon kitchen.
That's enough.
If you don't say that...
Well, I got it.
I got it, I got it.
There was a black person I was dating.
There was a black person.
What's his name?
What? You always want to know his name.
No, I want to know his name.
It was a black person.
What's his name?
Well, Zucchin.
Zucchin.
You always say Zucchin.
Yes, yes.
It's a good match.
It's always a good match.
I'm thinking that he's on today.
What kind of contest?
Drum.
Drum contest.
I won't lose.
You lost, didn't you?
I was excited.
But we were good friends.
Oh, really?
But now, I don't have any new friends.
Why were you so good friends with Zucchin?
I'm dead.
Don't cry.
I was listening to the radio the other day.
Makihara from Donna Tokimono said,
I like you two from downtown.
Do you two like Makihara?
I was there the other day.
At the home of the Tokimono family.
Hama-chan.
In the back, there was a suit with buttons.
Short pants.
Round shoes.
I put it on like this.
That's how it is.
I can't laugh.
Oh, it's been a long time.
Like this.
Good morning.
I've been doing this all the time.
How is it?
What is it?
Makihara-san.
I don't like him or hate him.
Isn't it strange?
I like him or hate him.
Once, I was invited to the audition of Setouchi Shounen baseball team.
That's right.
With Toshichan.
Don't call him Toshichan.
Did you hear that?
He called me Toshichan.
That's cool.
That's right.
I'm Sawara-san.
Yes.
Setouchi Shounen baseball team.
There was another guy who was invited to the audition.
It was decided more than 90% before the audition.
When I went to the other side, he said,
It's okay if you don't get drunk.
I went to the other side.
I was asked to read a book.
At the end, most of them said,
Is that so?
That's great.
You said it in front of him.
That's right.
Hello.
Thank you for coming all the way from Osaka.
Can I ask you one last question?
What is it?
You were sitting, right?
Why did you say,
What is it?
What is that look?
I was sitting in this position.
I was about to go home.
Can I ask you one last question?
Do you like Tawara Toshiko?
That's right.
I don't like her.
Why do you like her so much?
If I were a woman, I might think she's cool.
But Tawara Toshiko is weird.
I don't like her.
Everyone was surprised.
That's why I didn't like her.
That's why I said I like Makihara.
No matter how much they want to be hugged by me.
I can't hug him.
I can't.
Why did you say that twice?
Well.
That's right.
I think I've heard this before.
Why do you have hair here?
I was wondering if it was useful.
At that time, I thought,
People shouldn't hurt people.
When we fight, when this hits,
Instead of a cushion.
Don't be stupid.
There's no cushion.
Even if you use a bow, you'll get hurt.
That's what you said.
I'm a peacekeeper.
I don't want to use this iron sword.
What?
I don't want to use it.
When you say, don't hit here.
If it comes out.
What's the cushion?
In my case.
What is it?
Actually, that's why I killed Zucchini.
Shut up!