Hello everyone, good evening.
First, Hanashika-san, please come out!
This is the 9th time I've attended the Oogiri-daigassen.
Oh, is that so?
During that time, a lot of new people have appeared.
That's right.
Today's guests are strong opponents.
Very strong opponents.
That's right.
Please introduce yourself.
I, the god of comedy, often come here.
The other day, when the three of us pulled the omikuji of the vending machine, Daikichi Daikichi came, and I was the only one who didn't win.
I'm Yoshimoto's Oochikoku Yaro, Yamasaki Osoji.
Yes, nice to meet you.
He came 2 hours late.
Yes, next to me.
I, with this Oogiri, would like to destroy the image of hohohoi.
Hohohoihoi!
Kogoriko Endo, please come out.
Yes, next to me.
I'm the child's servant Arahen, and my gyal is still 5000 yen.
I have no intention of doing it tonight either.
I'm Kogoriko Tanaka.
Yes, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Now, the new person.
You didn't say it!
Introduce yourself.
You're amazing.
My name is Zatsu, in English. I'm a rat. I'm a little smart. I'm Gatsu.
Sometimes, I appear on variety shows. I'm Gatsu Ishimatsu.
Yes, nice to meet you.
Today, I heard about Oogiri, but it seems that there is a smell of the wild on the side.
Yoshimoto Kogyo's Tachi Hiroshikawa, Go Hiromi.
I'm sorry, I'll do it again.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
First of all, we have the Atakamo Club!
Atakamo Club
Is it annoying? This is an order.
There is a book that has nothing written on it.
I'll give it to you in order.
Atakamo!
Please proceed with the story as if it has something written on it.
Here!
A Chinese Charisma, The Life of a Pigeon.
Right?
Isn't this good?
Then, please.
A Chinese Charisma, The Life of a Pigeon.
The Pigeon...
Loved Manman a lot.
What does that have to do with anything?
Let's go!
The food that the Pigeon is good at is, of course, as you know, Gyoza.
You're talking about the life of a Pigeon.
If you start like that, you'll get a trauma.
What should I do?
Start from the birth.
The Pigeon is born with charisma.
Surprisingly...
That's strange.
Tell me where you were born in which year.
1948.
I was born in Canton.
The Pigeon had a strong fighting spirit when he was young.
He kept fighting in the next town and the next town.
He developed his own power.
Power?
I like your stamina.
And the Pigeon met Chinese food for the first time when he was 15 years old.
That's a good thing to say.
If you don't tell me that, I don't know where I'll meet you.
And after three years of training, the Pigeon made the best food in the world.
The name is...
The Chinese food made by Chin Chin.
It doesn't matter if you make it when you're in a bad mood or when you're having fun.
Is Chin Chin a food?
Yes.
Chin Chin didn't add any chili and chili paste.
Why?
Why is that?
It's written in the book, right?
Yes, it is.
Why didn't you add it?
It's written in the book.
But when he was 20 years old...
Why didn't you add it?
When he was in Shanghai, he had a trouble to taste the food made by Chin Chin.
He had a trouble to taste the food made by Chin Chin...
Oh, it's the other way around.
I'm not ready.
You guys should learn from him.
Hey!
It's true.
The reason why Chin Chin was so charismatic was...
He liked garlic.
He liked garlic so much that he bit the garlic.
What are you talking about?
Chin Chin...
I don't know what you're talking about.
Let's leave that aside.
Let's move on.
I want you to forget what happened before.
Is it written in the book?
You should forget it.
That's what Yasaki thought.
Chin Chin...
Is he really that charismatic?
What's wrong with you?
Who are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
Come here.
I'm getting sleepy.
I'm getting hungry.
Next is the Headphone Dialogue Game!
This is the Headphone Dialogue Game.
Are you ready?
We always play this game.
Everyone, please put your headphones on.
I will say a word from this side.
Please say it in order.
The first word is this.
Are you ready?
In the middle of the world.
That was fast.
Say it as it is.
Here you go.
A big salad.
It's big, Gamera.
OK.
Here you go.
It's big, Tamori.
OK.
Don't pretend.
OK, Mr. Matsumoto.
Say the answer.
It's bigger than the world, Zabori.
What is bigger than the world, Zabori?
The answer is this.
It's bigger than the world, Zabori.
I'll do it again, so change the order.
I'll be the second.
Gachitan is the last?
Then, Mr. Hose is the fourth.
OK.
The question is this.
That's good.
I don't know what Mr. Matsumoto is.
I'll do it again.
Are you sure?
I don't know what Mr. Matsumoto is.
Don't be stupid!
Takaishi Daisaburo.
Hakaishi Daizaburou!
Hakaishi Dorobo!
You're really good at this!
Yes?
Okay, Gata-san.
The correct answer is...
A red stove?
From now on, according to Wild Ones' Memories,
everyone will sing one phrase at a time.
Yes!
When I come in front of everyone, I'll say, who's that?
I'll imitate that person, and sing until the end.
Let's go! Music start!
I found you on this shore
I can't stand on my own
Keisuke Kuwata!
Morishi Ichi!
I can't stand on my own
Ohiromi!
Takami Yama!
That's too high!
Sakuraga Junko!
Junko desu!
I said, Junko desu.
It can't be Sakuraga Junko.
I'm embarrassed.
This order is so bad!
Sanaka is delicious, right?
Music start!
I found you on this shore
I can't stand on my own
Ohiromi!
Wada Kiko!
I can't stand on my own
Kobayashi Akira!
Komori no Obachama!
I can't stand on my own
It's always delicious.
Tanaka Kakuhei!
I can't stand on my own
Okay, the last one is Takeda Tetsuya!
I'm going to the waves.
What is it?
I'm going to win!
It's a kiss!
It's a kiss this time.
The kiss character is here.
Are you ready?
I can't do this.
The two kiss characters are going to separate.
The first match is Yamasaki and Tanaka!
Let's go!
Excuse me.
Yes?
It's very intense.
Let's start the match.
The name of the beer is...
Kirin Lager!
Asahi Beer!
Asahi Beer?
No way!
Kirin Lager!
Asahi Beer!
Asahi Super Dry!
Let's start the first round.
It's coming! Don't look at me!
The next one is Machigota and Tanaka.
It's a fake talent.
Ogata Ken!
Let's go to the next round!
Let's go!
It's coming!
The ingredients for a convenience store rice ball.
Kombu.
Seachicken.
Ume.
Katsuo.
Sake.
It's coming!
Let's move on to the next round!
Hey!
Of course!
The lyrics were written by Kohaku in 1998.
Ready!
Gray.
Speed.
Ready?
Yes.
L'Arc-en-Ciel.
Is it out?
Yes.
Takeda Tetsuya.
Kitajima Saburo.
TM Revolution.
OK.
Grilli and Brie.
It's coming!
Grilli and Brie!
It didn't come out in that era, did it?
What?
You're Grilli and Brie!
There's no one like that anymore.
Teleco Teleco.
OK, let's move on to the next round!
It's coming!
I lost to Yamazaki-san.
Yamazaki.
Fight!
I'll do my best.
A foreign talent who is active in Japan.
Ready!
Kento Delicato.
Yes.
Kento Gilbert.
Wait a minute.
That guy.
Chuck Riso.
Yes.
Dave Spector.
Wait a minute.
Zogman.
Right?
Which one?
Zogman is here!
I don't know.
Wait a minute!
I'll move on.
This is a reach.
It's a reach!
Wait a minute.
I just did it!
No, no, no.
You can do it.
It's a service.
Sorry.
You can do it.
It's a service.
This is a reach.
Alright.
Alright, let's go.
I'm close.
The name of the company is Yamasaki-san.
Benz.
Porsche.
Jaguar.
Countach.
Lamborghini Miura.
Volvo.
Lamborghini Iota.
Wait a minute.
Alright.
I'll move on.
Isn't it fast?
Alright, a reach.
Double reach!
This is a reach.
It's close.
You're doing it with a look.
This is close.
It's close.
If it was a fan, there would be a lot of wind.
Alright, the last question.
Which one will be kissed?
Oh, both of you got it.
It's easy.
The one who says it wins.
Yes.
From Tanaka-san,
Ko-kon Tozai.
Sushi-neta.
Chutoro.
Otoro.
Yes.
Saba.
Tamago.
Yes.
Tako.
Ebi.
Yes.
Ika.
Amai.
Yes.
Tekka-maki.
Kappa-maki.
Yes.
Torigai.
Akagai.
Yes.
Milgai.
Milgai?
Yes.
Baigai.
Katsuo.
Katsuo?
Katsuo, you're holding it.
You're holding it.
Kani.
Kani?
Kani, yes.
Yes.
Uni.
Anago.
Yes.
Unagi.
You're holding it.
Wait a minute!
You're holding it!
It's there!
Wait a minute!
Iwa-shi.
What?!
Iwa-shi is...
Yes.
Amaebi.
Yamasaki just spoke.
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
Sorry!
Hang on!
It's over!
What did you eat?