From now on, we will begin the 3rd trial of Onuma Akihiro, the Dogechi trial.
Prosecutors and judges, please come forward.
Next, the defendant, Onuma Akihiro, please come forward.
The defendant, Onuma Akihiro, is 37 years old. He is the famous director of Gaki no Tsukai. In the last 2 trials, he was found guilty of the Dogechi crime. But now, he has no reason to regret his actions. He will be judged in the trial.
And tonight, the truth about Onuma Akihiro will be revealed.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Kenji Hamada, please give us the evidence.
This is a ski location broadcasted in February this year. It was a project meeting for the next week after this recording.
After the meeting at the hotel, they decided to eat first.
When they started to eat, one of them, the author, Suzuki Onuma came to them.
Why are you eating it? It's mine, right?
I ordered it, too. How can you say that?
What's wrong, Onuma?
It's nothing. I just wanted to make sure.
After a few minutes, Onuma went back to his room and started to eat.
But the room was heavy.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Napolitan was brought to his room.
At the same time, Onuma got up and started to eat.
Obviously, he was not satisfied with the atmosphere of the place.
Onuma, why are you eating it now?
I realized that Suzuki ate it by mistake.
It's a big deal, Onuma.
I can't forgive you. You have to do this properly.
After that, the atmosphere of the meeting became even heavier.
After a moment of silence, the sound of Onuma eating napolitan was heard in the room.
I'd like to make a confession about the incident.
As you all know, it was a black zone.
I was eating it, but I couldn't eat it.
Onuma was angry.
I thought he was arguing about the story.
I thought it was a good thing that the director and the writer quarreled.
I thought Onuma had grown up, so I asked him.
Suzuki ate my napolitan.
In the end, the waitress took my napolitan to Suzuki's room.
That was the reason.
I'm sorry to say this, but the napolitan didn't have any color.
Actually, the napolitan was redder than the napolitan.
The napolitan was redder than the napolitan.
Do you have any objections?
I was in charge of the ski project.
I've been busy since morning.
You haven't eaten yet.
Everyone's finally going to eat, and I'm going to be able to eat.
I asked the other directors to eat with me.
I asked for three or four people.
You asked for it.
As far as I could see, Suzuki didn't ask for it.
Let's hear it.
You didn't ask for it, but Suzuki ate it.
It's easy to say this.
The writer comes to the set in the afternoon.
I'm in the middle of the day.
It's not like I haven't eaten at all.
You're hungry, you're hungry.
It's completely different.
But anyone can eat it.
I said it out loud.
I said I asked for it first.
I thought I was mistaken, so I went to check the desk.
Onuma was a little ahead of me.
Onuma was a little ahead of you?
You went to the desk?
I went there to make it clear.
Normally, if something like that happened, I'd give it to you first.
Suzuki is really...
He's angry.
There may be people who turned on the TV right now.
What are you talking about?
This is all about Napolitan.
Onuma didn't think about the meeting at all.
How was it?
Since Napolitan came, you've only been thinking about Napolitan.
That's true.
I knew that Onuma was a little ahead of me, but I was a little surprised this time.
I've been in the TV industry for about 25 years, but this is my first time.
It all started after a certain program was recorded.
Onuma, do you want to eat something?
Are you serious?
At that time, I was living in a hotel in Odaiba.
I invited Onuma, who lived in Odaiba, and decided to go to a fancy Italian restaurant on the way home.
Eventually, the car arrived at the restaurant.
Then, at the entrance of the parking lot, a woman in a red coat was painting.
And the woman approached the two people who got off the car.
I'm always grateful to you. I'm Onuma's wife.
I'm sorry I can't treat you to dinner tonight.
As soon as Onuma found out that he was being treated, he stole a little space between the two of them and called his wife.
He called her to the restaurant.
You look like you're taking it for granted.
This foie gras is delicious.
You should eat it, too. Don't hold back.
One after another, the Onuma couple ordered food.
This is an Italian wine from 1992.
It's a little sour, but it's okay.
I was surprised that he brought his wife here before I knew it.
But I couldn't help it.
He served me a pretty good wine.
It cost about 40,000 yen at the restaurant.
Then, Onuma started tasting it.
When I saw him say something like this, I was getting angry.
If you say that, it's your money.
After the meal, the three of them left the restaurant.
Then, Onuma said,
Mr. Iwatashi is staying at Pacific Meridian right now.
That's amazing. That's a great hotel.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's right, Mr. Iwatashi.
Please show me your room before you go home.
It's nice, isn't it?
It's not like you're going to lose money.
In the end, Onuma pushed them away.
Iwatashi invited them to the hotel room.
Wow, what a nice night view.
Hey, come over here. The bathroom is big, too.
In a very rich room, Onuma and his wife were having a great time.
And they found something.
That's the high-class wine Iwatashi had bought.
I'd like to have a good wine while looking at this view.
Oh, really? Then I'll have a drink.
Just like that, the three of them started drinking wine.
However, an hour later,
Onuma and his wife found Iwatashi, the owner of the room, and they were in a good mood.
It's a really nice night.
Yeah, I'm glad you came.
I'd like to say something.
If it's for Onuma, I want you to become a millionaire as soon as possible.
I want you to wake up.
That's a bit of a surprise.
Did you hear what he said?
The reason why I'm here is because there's a story about the day after tomorrow.
After this, the two of them sleep in the double bed of Mr. Iwatashi.
Mr. Iwatashi sleeps on the sofa until morning.
Really?
When Mr. Iwatashi woke up, the two of them weren't there.
They didn't have bathrobes or slippers.
That's scary!
Really?
That's amazing.
This is an unprecedented event.
This is very special.
You don't have any reaction to this, do you?
I was invited by Mr. Iwatashi.
You wanted to go eat, didn't you?
No one told you to call your wife?
No, but I like Italian food.
I want to beat you up!
Did your wife come out when you called her?
She came out right away.
She was here a while ago.
The food was delicious.
I went to the hotel where Mr. Iwatashi stayed.
That's strange.
Why didn't you stay?
I wanted to get drunk.
What do you mean by that?
What?
The bathrobes disappeared after you woke up.
What do you mean?
I stayed the night, so I thought it was the same condition.
I don't get it.
I thought it was the same condition.
I think he's playing the piano.
I don't think he's laughing.
He's playing the piano.
If I were him, I'd watch the music fair.
In October last year,
Ryuusen, a high-ranking writer,
held a wedding at a first-class hotel in Tokyo.
The event was held at the venue.
Onuma was dressed as a taxi driver.
He was in a hurry.
Oh, dear.
I spent all my money on the wedding.
A wedding that costs tens of thousands of yen
is nothing but trouble for Onuma.
Eventually, the ceremony began.
The ceremony continued,
and the guests continued to greet each other.
Meanwhile, Onuma's eyes were fixed on the food.
And the host said,
I'm going to eat now.
Let's eat.
Onuma rushed to the kitchen.
And he found a dish that looked like someone else was eating it.
Hey, where's the beef?
You're the only one who's eating sushi.
Why didn't you tell me, you bastard?
Obviously, Onuma looked strange.
Then Eddie said,
Onuma, this meat sauce is delicious, too.
Meat sauce?
Are you stupid?
You can't make money with meat sauce.
I'm paying for it.
In the end, Onuma didn't care about the bride.
The ceremony was just an eating show.
Onuma's New Year's Eve
It was already New Year's Eve.
The incident happened after the recording.
Onuma was very satisfied with the recording of the day.
I'm going home.
At that time, when he looked at the table,
Crab and shrimp were folded.
I found it.
Onuma started to find it.
He went around the tables and started to collect them.
Then Nakai noticed Onuma.
That's for the cameramen who haven't eaten yet at work.
Please forgive me.
Onuma was surprised by what he heard.
But the next moment...
Hey, Yosuke.
Onuma caught the camera chief.
Can I have one of the folded ones?
But some people haven't eaten yet.
Onuma went home with a smile on his face.
What about the witness?
I was with Nakai at the New Year's party.
I was sad.
I was 30 years old at that time.
I was at the scene.
I've been working as a cameraman for many years.
I know how many cameramen there are.
There were more than that.
Can you look at the back of the camera?
Can you look at the camera?
I'd like to talk to you.
I'd like to ask you a question.
What is this?
10,000 yen?
What is it?
I tried to put it in at first.
But when I saw it, it said it was a divorce.
What do you mean?
This guy is amazing.
You don't feel like congratulating the two of them, do you?
It's not just a Viking.
I don't think there's a reason to hold back.
In the past, Matsumoto did a live show.
He said he'd pay me after he saw the money.
I asked him how much I should put in.
He said it was about 10,000 yen.
I asked him how much he was going to put in.
He said he'd put in 10,000 yen.
Why do you have to put in that much?
10,000 yen
I'm surprised, too.
The 100,000 yen crisis curry that was broadcast last week.
There was an incident here, too.
That was right after the recording.
Thank you for your hard work.
Yamazaki's breathing was really funny.
The cast and staff were very satisfied.
Now we're going to shoot the curry package.
Everyone, please go back to the living room.
As you can see on the screen,
To make it easier to see the correct answer,
You need to record the package individually.
For the sake of the package recording,
The set is getting ready.
The cast and staff are going to the waiting room for the talk recording.
A man who watches the situation.
I didn't know.
Get out of here. Get out of here.
And the moment the cast and staff left the studio.
It's delicious.
Oonuma is eating the rest of the curry in the studio.
It's not a problem to say that his will to eat has completely relieved the tension in the studio.
It's just about time.
We didn't know what happened after that.
Please confirm.
Please explain what happened after that.
There was a rumor about this before.
Especially during the Kiki series.
There was a rumor that something was going on.
At that time, I was in charge of the broadcast station.
I got a call from the AD.
I was able to jump in.
I took a picture.
What do you mean you were able to jump in?
I got a call from the AD.
I was able to jump in.
I'm scared, but everyone is scared.
The script was finally captured.
Oonuma's true form.
You are eating as much as you want.
This guy is terrible.
People often eat delicious food at restaurants.
I didn't eat much during the recording.
What would you do if you jumped in during the recording?
I ate a lot of rice.
Did you eat rice before that?
I ate rice before that.
I bought a lot of rice.
The verdict was finally given.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.