Tonight, the punishment for Bakium Fujiwara will be given.
We will be doing the revenge game for Bakium Fujiwara in the first episode.
The moment you see it, you will be sucked into the hell of Shumai.
What is it?
Before that, I have a feeling that this punishment game is not a joke.
I see.
That's right.
Is that so?
You don't have to play a penalty game.
You can be a comedian and use a steel bar.
You can use a steel bar.
We shoot in a great place.
This is not easy.
A small child looks at everyone and asks,
Who?
A child without a child's instructions.
Who is that person with a hat?
I don't know his name.
Let's call him.
Fujiwara, please.
Please.
I don't remember doing anything that I would be punished.
Sorry.
It's a waste of time to pull him.
Let's do it properly.
This time, there are a lot of Shumai in the city.
Bakium-san is really crazy about stomach.
He ate all the Shumai that he found.
That's all.
I don't agree with that at all.
Don't run away. You ran away.
I ran away.
Bakium Fujiwara, who aimed to be a foodie talent with the current boom.
He created a special set that he hopes for in the studio.
While his vision was blocked, he tried to eat 80 yookas.
However!
He escaped again in the middle of the night.
Tonight, he will be called a new member of the Kogui family.
You said it!
The time of the Shumai hell has come!
It started quite suddenly
If we find it, please tell Fujiwara
It's here
It's a bit sudden but
Oh, really?
The bar's tip!
This is how it is?
The tip is...
This is also possible, right?
Then, there are many things.
You should put soy sauce properly.
That's the answer.
You're the one who should put soy sauce.
Don't drop it.
Take it by hand.
The temperature is low today.
The rice ball is cold.
Don't drop it.
That's right.
I don't care about the taste.
It's like this.
What is it?
You started again.
What are you doing?
It's true.
It's a smile.
The punch is Shumai.
It's amazing.
Don't be shy.
It's food.
We can't walk without a key.
Excuse me.
His...
His face...
His face is like a Shumai hell.
Shumai hell.
It's almost over.
Ah!
It's in the book.
Shumai hell.
I have to take this.
Take it.
He's particular.
I'll take this.
The second button?
The second button.
Yu is eating a lot with this.
No, I'm not.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
7.
7th.
It's not easy to get this much money.
That's right.
Right?
I think it's 500 yen.
I can get 500 yen.
You can get 500 yen?
If you get 100 yen, it's not a game.
It's 1000 yen.
1000 yen?
Oh, look.
It's a radio.
Look at this.
Huh?
Wait a minute.
It's on the radio.
Huh?
Look at this.
This is a joke.
He's doing it so it doesn't get dirty.
He's so kind.
You're not supposed to be this kind in a punishment game.
It's a town before the end of the week.
It's gone.
Maybe it's on the back.
The tires.
I'll take care of the
How is it?
Is there anything?
It's a big one.
What?
Wow! It's ringing!
It's a Shumai tree!
Shumai tree rings!
It's ringing!
It's like a Shumai hunt
It's nice
This doesn't have a cover
It's not a cover
It's a standard
It's a cover
It's good that it's not raining today
It's good
Let's look for it.
What?
A girl's cell phone strap?
Hey!
Oh, a strap.
If it's not a
Thank you!
Look at my friends!
There's a lot of them!
You wouldn't ask me, would you?
Where did you buy them?
This is quite a lot.
I've already eaten 20 of them.
If we were going to do a penalty game, we wouldn't do this kind of thing yet.
We've only just started!
It's only the beginning!
It's nothing yet.
I don't like the toilet
I don't like it
It's a pretty bad place
You have to look carefully
Yes
Where is it?
It's gone
I was surprised
There are so many
There are 6
I have never eaten it before
I can eat it with my hands
It's amazing
There are people who are walking dogs, but they are not.
There are many children, so if you find them, you will be eaten.
As expected, Mr. Vacuum.
I will go ahead.
It's late.
Let's go, Mr. Vacuum.
Let's go slowly.
Vacuum Fujiwara comes here and slows down as soon as possible.
The meat is cold and hard.
I don't know.
It's a punishment.
Ignoring such an excuse, he goes to the residential area.
I'm sure you'll eat Shumai tomorrow, right?
That's right!
You said you ate it!
I came here to look for it.
That's right.
This is the place.
It's not that kind of park.
That's...
That's nice.
Shumai.
Shumai is delicious.
Shumai!
You're touching it a lot.
I'm touching it.
Shumai instead of rice.
Go away!
He's getting angry!
He's touching a lot!
But I don't know if it's good or not
It's a red wine from Furiya
It's here
What will it taste like?
Oh, this is good
It's good
There are so many Shumai in the city
Yes, there are
The factory
What should we do if it's a Shumai factory?
Shumai factory
There are so many
Mr. Bagumi, you're not talking much.
Really?
I think it's still going on.
I don't use the app at all.
Huh?
Cute.
I love puzzles.
Look.
He's playing with a dog.
He's a child.
Look at this.
Oh!
Hurry up.
Why did you step on my head at that timing?
You're slow!
You're not lucky at all!
You walked so calmly, why did you do that at that timing?
You're slow!
You almost got eaten!
When you're on Pau's head, you don't look so far away.
Somewhere...
I found something.
Thank you.
Which one is this?
Is this a person from the hell of Shumai?
But you are from the hell of Shumai.
But it's Shumai.
It's okay.
It's delicious.
If you do that, it's dangerous.
You should eat it quickly.
It's dangerous.
I don't like it.
Eat it outside.
Is there anything else you won't eat?
Nothing, we're fine with bread
That's a pretty good one.
The 32 Shumai have been sucked up by the vacuum Fujiwara.
After this, the hell of Shumai will attack.
Tokoshi Ginza.
Tokoshi Ginza is famous.
Here, they enter the shopping street.
Vacuum Fujiwara already feels satisfied, but the real battle of Shumai hell begins.
We have Shumai, but Mr. Hamada, do you want to eat?
Is that okay?
Seeing Shumai, the hungry one decided to satisfy his hunger at the restaurant
Then curry
Thank you
Three curries
Then everyone will have curry
I'll have pork ginger set meal
You don't know
What?
I want to change the taste.
No, you can't change the taste.
It's a hell of a world.
You can eat a lot.
No matter what I think, I'm enjoying it.
How many eggs are there?
There are still 20.
There are about 8.
Let's eat more.
Oh, stop it.
It's a good place to eat.
You can drink tea.
Thank you.
I'll go again soon.
It's in the tea shop.
Do you need a towel?
You have a lot of hair!
You should have told me earlier.
I have a lot of hair.
I got it.
You're wearing a lot of clothes.
Wow.
I'm going to eat.
I'm hungry.
Oh, oh, oh.
I'm going to eat.
Let's just put this in.
It's a topping.
Why did you put curry in?
I put curry!
It's your curry.
It's a special dish.
I'll eat it.
I'm glad it's rice.
It's a restaurant system.
Let's eat little by little.
This is so warm.
Why wasn't it warm until now?
It was all cold.
Let's eat.
What about udon?
Give me udon.
Ah!
I'm so scared.
It's 5 o'clock.
We came at this time.
That clock...
It's a bit late.
It's okay if it's 10 minutes late.
Ah, it's just 5 minutes.
Can I go to the toilet?
Why?
Can I go with you?
Why are you so free in this punishment game?
What is he?
It's not like a vacuum at all!
So he's not running away, is he?
Well, he's not running away that easily.
From here, to the toilet...
What happened?
I just went to the toilet.
The nose!
His nose is a little...
From the TV.
The restaurant is so good!
It's so good!
Why did you eat so much after going to the toilet?
Because I moved a little.
After clearing the restaurant, he goes to the shopping street where he can eat Shumai again.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, Mr. Pacquiao, I'm sorry, but I have to take this.
I made this for you, so please eat it.
Good luck!
Thank you.
It's important to be worried.
I wonder if he knows that he's being supported by anxiety.
You'll have a hard time with Shumai.
That's right.
Oh, oh, oh!
It's a Shumai!
It's a grilled Shumai!
Isn't this Mr. Kiyoku?
I always see him on TV!
This is a freebie!
It's a freebie!
It's supported by everyone in the world!
That's great!
Thank you!
Oh, there's more!
It's freebie!
Thank you for the phone call!
I can't believe it!
What's going on?
Yes, that's right.
That's right.
We still have a lot of money left.
I'm selling shumai on the street.
Look at all the earrings.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
Still, still, still
There are ears, ears
Both ears, both ears
Look at the ears, the ears
Both ears, yes yes yes
Yes yes yes
The other one, the other one
The way of eating
Good, good
There it is
Fujiwara, you're holding it in your hand, hurry up and eat it
If not, you won't be able to move on to the next stage
It's coming, you have to eat it
Then stop here. Don't move until I finish eating.
I see.
He stops here to suck up all the shumai he has.
What? Are you laughing?
Are you laughing?
You have a delicate face.
I'm jealous. I want to eat a lot of shumai.
Shumai is good.
I can't eat shumai at all today.
It looks delicious.
No, because I can't eat it.
It's the same thing as the vacuum cleaner.
It's not working at all.
Please.
It's a million times bigger.
Okay.
I'll do it.
You're not a headache.
It's a lot.
That's right.
With that momentum.
I'll do it.
I can do it.
Okay.
The person who has eaten 81 Shumai so far is Bakium Fukumara.
But there is another challenge.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Are you Mr. Bakium?
No, I'm not.
I'm a fan of your show.
Please give me your autograph.
You're not allowed to do that.
I'm happy.
Please.
You're a good person.
I'm angry.
I understand.
It's a good feeling.
It's a vacuum.
I've been stabbed a lot by a vacuum.
I'm not going to be noisy.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
Please do your best.
I'm a big fan.
You're a big fan.
TV is amazing.
Thank you.
You are a big fan.
I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
Don't be stopped by someone.
I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
Mr. Bakugou.
Please don't do that.
Finally, 1 in 3 of them are sitting down.
You're slow in terms of pace.
You're slow.
You're 1 in 3.
Hey!
Huh?
This is...
Isn't this Fujiwara-go?
This is Fujiwara-go's car.
This is Fujiwara's car.
Fujiwara, you're driving a Volvo.
This is really Fujiwara's car.
Right?
Wow!
What's wrong, Fujiwara?
What's this?
It's a dash board.
The color has changed.
That's right.
You're a great dash board.
Is that a Yankee?
That's right.
It's a Don Quixote.
Then, Fujiwara, you should get on.
I'll turn around.
Fujiwara, I'll wait for you.
You're amazing.
You're eating everything.
That must smell like shumai.
That's right.
You're so cruel.
He locked it.
Why did you lock it?
What kind of costume is that?
Jiro.
Don't ever take off your pants.
I can't help it.
We're only reacting to roughly the same weirdness.
Ladies and Juniors.
You are watching…
Long time no see, Tomoki.
This set one often leaves في
It does.
I share it often, in part.
I said a little bit of a joke on the radio, but I don't have a lot of sympathy for the audience, so I stopped on the way.
Where are the people who are talking on the phone at the convenience store?
Oh, you said that.
Look, the audience is like this again.
What is this?
Am I the only one who has seen the scene too much?
I'm the one who keeps talking in the convenience store next door.
But that's not true.
I've seen it, but I don't care.
It's okay if you put the product in the basket.
I'm talking while looking at it.
That's right.
Like a ha ha ha.
Of course, if you listen to the conversation, it's not that important.
I was like, I have to talk about it now!
I mean, I'm going to the convenience store!
There are products I want to see, but I want to get a Togari corn.
I was always in front of the Togari corn.
You were talking at the Togari corn?
There was a big convenience store the other day, and there were two guys like that.
Over here and over there.
I was like, if you guys become friends...
I'm talking to a different person.
But, no, I can't.
You're not really serious about it.
No, I'm not.
What are you saying?
For example, in the middle of winter,
That's definitely not good.
I can't make an excuse for that.
For example, in the middle of winter, it's really cold.
You're going to go into the convenience store and talk.
It's not like that.
It's this time of year.
You're talking all the time.
Anyway, you've been talking for five or ten minutes.
The other day, it was so bad, I thought he said it, but when I was listening to the conversation, it felt like my friend had died.
Oh, oh, oh.
And then, as expected, oh, oh, oh.
Ah, this is, well, it can't be helped.
Even so, it's even more out of reach.
It's not a good friend.
Hmm.
Ah, well, well, well.
But it can't be helped.
Somehow, after all, it's like this.
I'm convinced. I'm convinced.
Well, everyone, well, Yamaguchi-san and other talent-san too,
they send e-mails and phone calls. You too, you know,
you do that.
I don't use any of the phone calls.
I don't do this.
What do you mean?
If that's the case, I'll give you 200 million yen.
I don't do that.
My phone is old but I can only send 300 emails.
Can you send more now?
I can send 500 more now.
The oldest one I saw was about March.
What?
The mail.
The mail?
Yes.
March?
I have a lot of friends.
It's not gone.
It's gone, it's gone.
It's like, it's going to get colder.
Who said that?
You're going to laugh.
That's amazing.
That's true, but everyone uses their phones a lot.
You use your phone a lot.
I really have three batteries.
I think it's three.
It's three, right?
I've never seen it decrease.
One day?
But it's a charge-up disease.
I feel like it's decreasing.
I charged it right away.
You didn't hear it?
It didn't decrease at all.
I've never had a beep.
Hurry up to the convenience store.
You bought a 10-day vacation at a convenience store?
Not at all.
Ah, really?
If you go out for a day, you can afford it.
You can afford it.
Sometimes, I forget my phone at home.
I think it's okay.
I work all day and when I get home,