I'm going to show you how to break the mountain!
Today...
What are you doing?
We've been practicing for two weeks.
It's going to be tough today.
Look at this!
This is not going to be fun.
Idiot!
We're in this situation right now.
It's better for us to take turns.
If we fall, we lose.
If we lose...
It's a punishment game.
But we're hiding something like that.
Don't do that!
I fell!
The quality of laughter is low.
Who's the one who can't do it anymore?
Please come over here.
Akashiya-san.
Kasuga-san.
Beat Takeshi-san.
Shimada Shinsuke-san.
Nishikawa Kiyoshi-san.
Tamori-san.
Uchanan-chan.
Who was that?
Bonjama!
We're not going to do that.
I don't think it's true.
But there's someone who thinks it's true.
Who is it?
I didn't get it.
Do it again.
Actually, I think...
Who is it?
My hand...
My hand is going crazy.
This is Margaret.
She's in a different place from what she really thinks.
Are you serious?
No, no.
Who do you think it is?
Why do you want to know?
Who is it?
It's this guy!
This isn't what you think it is.
You don't have any resistance.
No, it's clean.
I didn't get it.
It's clean.
It's gone.
It's hot.
I got it.
Put a sticker on your face saying you drank too much.
When?
There was a sushi restaurant I went to before.
It looked expensive.
I'll put it up there.
In front of the restaurant.
I'll go, but I won't put it up if I didn't drink too much.
You drank too much.
It's because you drank too much.
Where should I put it?
Here.
Where?
Like this.
Like this?
Yes.
I can kick your butt, but you can't kick mine.
I kicked it hard.
I had poop on my shoes.
I can't do this.
Thank you very much.
I think that when I do this kind of work, I live in an apartment.
I don't want to be noticed by the residents of the apartment.
That's right.
The other day, I rented an apartment in Osaka.
When I was about to leave, I heard a voice.
From the outside?
From the outside.
It was from the other side of the door.
I looked through the window.
A man and a woman were hugging each other.
In front of your room?
That's right.
I saw a couple hugging each other in the park.
They didn't do anything.
They didn't move at all.
They were like,
Are you a squirrel?
That's right.
They were in the station.
They were in the station, right?
They were like this.
They didn't talk.
What was that?
They didn't leave the room.
I don't want to be noticed.
When I left the room, they were like,
This is my room.
They were looking at each other.
I was looking at them.
They didn't move at all.
What was that?
I don't want to be noticed.
They were in the station.
I wanted to wait a little longer.
I was watching TV for about 20 minutes.
I thought it was about time.
I looked at them again.
They didn't kiss.
What was that?
They didn't move at all.
It's worse than that.
They didn't kiss.
Wait a minute.
How was it?
Was it hard?
It was hard for both of them.
It was hard.
They didn't move at all.
They didn't do the dance.
I was glad they didn't.
I thought they would come out.
I didn't think so.
I often see couples like that.
In the park, in the station.
They are in the station.
There are many ticket shops in the station.
There are.
A little to the side.
What was the beginning like?
Until they go to the park?
I've never seen the beginning and the end.
Everyone is at home.
I see that.
What was the beginning like?
They walk to the station.
I think they will come back.
The woman.
They want to say goodbye.
Until they go to the ticket shop.
That's the situation.
From this situation,
how do they end?
In the end,
They can talk.
How do they end?
No.
Even if they kiss,
in the end,
how do they end?
Yes.
That's the situation.
It's not a preface.
But,
the ugly couple
is doing that.
The competition is terrible.
It's like a roundabout.
There is something strange.
Something...
What is it?
There is something like this.
Hey!
It's a manjigatame.
Manjigatame is funny.
It's funny.
In the past,
I was angry.
In Osaka,
from Monday to Friday,
I was doing a live show.
Yes.
At that time,
I was sleeping.
Do you know that?
Yes.
It was about 41 degrees.
It was sunny.
It was so hot.
I didn't know that.
Yes.
I was sleeping at home.
Then,
the bell rang.
Who is it?
It was my grandmother.
I came here a few times.
But,
she was not here.
When I saw the program today,
I heard that I had a fever of more than 40 degrees.
I thought she would be here today.
Please give me a sign.
It doesn't matter.
If it's 40 degrees,
I don't care who it is.
I don't care about this.
I feel lonely.
I know.
I can't stand it.
I've never been noticed.
What?
I don't look for big things.
How about now?
Now,
I'm in my eighties.
Eighties?
Yes.
You are in your eighties.
I'm in my sixties.
You are a mammoth.
What is that?
I was a child.
That's right.
The manager is my grandfather and grandmother.
I'm a little stupid.
When I first saw it,
I thought it was here.
Excuse me.
How long does it take to get to the station?
If you walk, it takes 10 minutes.
If I walk, it takes 5 minutes.
Why?
It's the other way around.
When I guide her on the stairs,
she doesn't come.
I'm guiding her when she doesn't come.
If you walk 10 minutes,
I walk 5 minutes.
I don't know if you're using your power.
I don't know if she's holding on until she gets to the station.
If you don't walk, you'll be stuck.
This is the time.
It's a time of change.
I'm going to get a heat stroke.
I can't stand it.
You've never had a fever of more than 40 degrees.
No.
I've noticed that I'm getting a habit of getting a heat stroke.
It's been a while.
When I first got a heat stroke,
I was surprised because I had a fever of more than 40 degrees.
I was so scared that I went home.
I thought I had a cold,
but I thought I'd just go to bed.
I couldn't get a fever in three days.
I didn't want to go to the hospital,
so I only took cold medicine.
I was sleeping alone.
My father and mother were sleeping next to me.
I couldn't sleep because I had a fever.
I woke up at 5 o'clock.
I don't know if my mother was sleeping.
We were talking.
Yes, we were talking.
My father said,
I don't think I can do it anymore.
I couldn't stand it.
I couldn't move because I had a fever.
My father said,
I don't think I can do it anymore.
What did your father think?
My father said,
Don't say such a thing.
I want you to say it.
I'm thinking about it now.
Is it true?
I'm crying.
I have a lot of memories of my elementary school days.
I had a lot of fun.
My father said,
This is a giraffe.
When I got on the train,
I got a big problem.
My grandmother was sitting in my seat.
My grandmother was like a high-class family.
I've seen my grandmother's belongings.
She was sitting in my seat.
When I came, she couldn't sit.
I don't know what to do, but you know, I'm an adult, too.
I'm a young man.
Yesterday, my grandma came home.
She looked like Masako Ohya.
She must have a lot of money.
She came home and looked at me.
Huh?
Her shoes were shining.
Is that my seat?
Are you serious?
Are you still interested in Masako Ohya?
That's a strange Masako Ohya.
I'm sure it's Masako Ohya.
Hey, doggy.
I got up and said,
Hello, this is my seat.
Hello?
Is that so?
This is definitely seat number 10.
I took it off and it was number 11.
This is number 10.
It's number 11.
It's number 10, right?
Number 10, number 11.
What? I'm surprised.
This is a different car.
Your story is very interesting.
Oh, you're so brave.
You're much bigger than when you talked to me before.
You're so brave.
What?
Are you still angry with me?
I enjoy watching Osaka while thinking of Osaka.
You enjoy watching Osaka?
Yes, I always do.
I was talking to my friend the other day.
When I was talking to him,
I thought, oh, I see.
I saw my mother's legs shining.
Oh, I see.
You're the only one who's shining.
I don't know what kind of mother I am.
But I can see it.
My mother's legs are yellow.
It's hard.
Mothers get excited easily.
Especially your mother.
Why?
Oh, my God.
When you say that, you can't stop.
It's true.
I just remembered it.
What?
I was at the Shimin Festival in Amagasaki.
We were invited to the festival.
We were invited.
And there were so many people on the stage.
On the other side of the stage,
there was a dressing room.
I said, Dantan-san, please come in.
When I went up,
next to the stairs to the stage,
my father was holding a video from his neck.
I said, long time no see.
He said, yes.
He brought a camera and a video.
I went up.
Dantan-san.
When I went up to the stage,
my mother was sitting in the middle.
What?
There were so many seats.
And there was a phone call.
I thought I'd sit there.
The girl in the front seat
was standing in line from 3 o'clock in the morning.
My mother was there.
What time did you get up?
That's amazing.
And there was a phone call.
Oh, yeah.
Dantan, do you know what happened the other day?
What's wrong with you?
Did you stop the delivery?
See, my mother didn't say anything.
Get out of the way!
In front of the child care center,
Hama-chan said,
if you have a yellowtail teriyaki,
you can eat as much rice as you want.
I'm trying to see how many times I can eat it.
No, it's not like that.
That's what it is.
So I'll do it in the open room.
I'll prepare yellowtail teriyaki
and eat as much rice as I want.
No.
No, you can't.
It doesn't matter where I'm eating.
It doesn't matter.
Did you lie to me?
You can eat as many times as you want.
That's human.
There's a limit.
But it doesn't say how many times you can eat it in two or three times.
If you can eat three times as much as you usually eat,
that's amazing.
How many times is that?
It's not how many times.
It's three times.
So how many times is that?
How many times do you usually eat?
About two times on average.
Two times?
More than that?
A lot.
It's a lot these days.
I don't know.
How much is it?
Something like this.
It's big.
That's right.
That's a lot.
I can't eat it.
But if it's yellowtail teriyaki,
that's a different story.
I cooked a lot of rice in the opening.
Do it properly.
I don't know.
Okay, okay.
Next time.
He's refusing.
No.
Why?
I was talking to my sister the other day,
and we had an argument.
There was a big mole on Nishimoto's face.
Where was it on his face?
By the way,
which one was the smaller mole
of Naomi Chiyaki, Kenji Sawada, and Kenji Nizuma?
It's here.
The mole.
Why is it there?
Where is Naomi Chiyaki?
Around here?
Which one was it?
Here?
Where is Nishimoto?
I think it was here.
Around here?
Why am I the mole?
Around here.
Nishimoto was here.
And then,
Senma-san was here.
Atsumi Kiyoshi was here.
Sometimes,
there are people who are pitiful.
You can't make a mistake.
It's scary, isn't it?
What would you do if you were his partner?
I'm down.
Right?
Why did you put it on?
You don't have an answer.
Who else?
Kuwata.
It's Kuwata.
Kuwata is...
Kuwata is like this.
It's scary.
Hello.
Today,
we have a promotion.
Yes.
Let's do it again.
Actually, we made this video.
It's called Dantan no Ryu.
It's been a while since we did a manzai.
It's a very exciting video.
It costs 4900 yen.
When will it be released?
It will be released on November 1st.
If you can, I want you to buy it.
Let's give it to the viewers.
Yes.
To the viewers.
How many people are there?
97 people.
97 people?
Yes.
3 people.
3 people?
It's really interesting.
Yes.
I want you to buy it.
We will give it to the viewers.
Here you are.
I'll give it to you later.
And...
This.
You have to put a sticker on it.
Yes.
It's good, isn't it?
But Akiko...
Your bangs are drooping.
I can't put it on.
You can't put it on.
So, you have to put it up.
If you put it on your hair, you can't do it.
You can't do that.
You have to put it down.
What?
If you put it down, it's funny.
But if you put it down, it's not funny.
As I said earlier, the video's address is the same.
If you want to see it, the address is the same.
Please come here.
I'll see you next week.
Bye.