In the first episode, we're going to play the roulette game!
Let's all have fun playing roulette!
Thank you, Kaki!
This time, the four roulette players will play a special game!
First, you have to decide who you want to play with the rock-paper-scissors.
There are 8 designated areas.
Then, with the second roulette, you have to decide on the person's costume.
Each person has a unique cosplay.
Then, with the third roulette, you have to decide on the person's actions.
There are unusual questions prepared.
Then, with the last roulette, you have to decide on the person's eyes.
The question is the last one, right?
You have to decide on the person's face.
For example, let's say that Yamazaki is dressed up as Superman in Nakano.
Then, you have to decide on the scene of the murder.
The sponsor you are about to see is here.
This game will continue until 3 out of 5 people get it right.
Please look forward to the punishment video of the person who gets it right.
First, Kokoriko Tanaka will challenge the roulette.
The roulette will spin a lot.
I will call Nakano Urai.
The roulette is spinning.
Shinbashi.
This game is cold.
The roulette is spinning.
Kaimun.
This game is cold.
This game looks like it will last longer.
You are running without rain.
What is this?
Why are you laughing?
It's too long
I'm scared
He barely made it
He did it
Let's continue
Tanaka Naoki
In a new horse
He's wearing a navy uniform
Even though it's not raining
He's running in a sports newspaper
And he's laughing
Let's see it
Please
Next is Endo
The place is a mess
What about his costume?
It's open
Candy candy
This is bad
It's not hard
It's cool
It's safe
Next is Hamada
What will he do?
Please
It's open
He put his one leg in the tofu
This is bad
He's laughing
He's not laughing
Next is Matsumoto
What will he do?
Please
I don't know
It's open
What are you doing?
Please
I'll do my best
I'll lower the saddle
And run
I'll do anything
This is bad
This is Tanaka's part
It's stopped
It's Tanaka's part
He's not here
What is this?
The last one is Yamazaki
He's not here
What will he do?
This is safe
Go
The second one
It's okay
Here
It's here
If you go from here, you'll go to the next one
And Hamada's second one
Hamada's second one
It's here
I want to see this
Please
It's here
And Matsumoto's second one
Matsumoto
Thank you
is allemaal
Let's do the Jyobachi pose with Odaiba and laugh together with the parachute.
Let's watch it.
The last one is Yamazaki's challenge.
It's a gap.
This is not good for a comedian.
It's a gap comedian.
This is not good.
Who will be the last one?
Endo, fate's third throw.
It's my first time.
It's like Nakadai Tatsuya.
Go in.
I'm counting on you.
Go to the environment.
Go out.
What?
Hamada, who was relieved that three people had been chosen,
What? One more person?
What is it, Mr. Hamada?
Who are you asking?
Who is it?
One more person!
It doesn't matter if it's that person.
It's Irie-chan again!
That gap, that gap.
Matsumoto, who is trying to fit Hamada,
and the fourth generation of roulette.
Are you laughing?
Isn't that strange?
I want to point it out.
Hamada, I've made an item like this.
What is it?
You're laughing twice as much!
Hamada and Yamazaki's one-on-one battle.
First of all, Hamada can't lose even if he wants to.
It's from that old movie.
This is also nostalgic.
I'll never say it.
It's nostalgic!
It's getting more stylish.
Stylish?
I don't think it'll fit there.
Stylish!
It's here!
Alright, let's go!
Don't make fun of me!
I can't run away anymore.
I caught it.
He did it!
He ran away again.
That's amazing.
I can't run away anymore.
And Yamazaki's one-on-one battle.
The one-on-one battle.
This is in line with the story, but it's not funny.
Come on, come on.
Let's go without him.
Come on!
I can't run away anymore!
Let's go!
Yamazaki Hosei is in Ginza.
He's in a Benha outfit.
He's laughing at the strategy.
Let's take a look.