Let's eat curry udon at Chikishiki Curry Udon at your own leisure, Grand Prix!
It's curry udon, isn't it?
Yes, it's curry udon.
It's delicious at this time of the year, so we eat it, but it flies away.
It flies away in this beautiful, freshly bought shirt.
It's a terrible story.
I want you to polish your skills to eat it cleanly.
If you can't eat it in four minutes, you'll get five points.
I see.
It's written like this.
It's one point.
If you can't eat it in four minutes, you'll get five points.
In the worst case, the person with the highest score will get a terrible punishment.
It's starting now.
I'm surprised.
I was surprised.
This program is brought to you by the sponsor.
The first group.
Ready.
This project has more strict conditions than you can imagine.
The chopsticks are slippery.
If there is a piece of noodles left, it is a draw.
It's delicious.
It's hot.
We don't have time.
Hurry up and eat.
The first group.
There is little time left.
How is the soup?
It's delicious.
I can't eat it.
The second group.
It's over.
The noodles are left.
This is a minus point.
It's empty.
It's in the stomach.
It's one point.
It's six points.
It's ten points.
It's eleven points.
It's over.
Sakamoto struggled.
But surprisingly...
It's seven points.
You saw the first group, right?
Let's eat more like a man.
Like a man.
Don't eat too much.
There is a lot.
What is that?
Why?
I don't know.
The second group.
Ready.
Start.
The second group.
Kokoriko is the first to join this year.
You are too close to Tanaka.
Don't talk while you are eating.
The last minute.
It's the last minute.
Start.
It's over.
What is that?
I saw something white.
It's pink.
I got it.
It's this.
This is dangerous.
Five points.
I can't eat this.
What about the bottom one?
Twenty-eight.
Downtown didn't miss a drop.
Twenty-nine.
Is it dangerous?
What about Kokoriko and Endo?
There are four here.
It's random.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen.
Thirty-one, thirty-eight, thirty-nine, forty-one, forty-two, forty-three, forty-four, forty-five, forty-six, forty-seven, forty-eight, forty-nine.
Fifty-five.
Endo, fifty-five.
HEPO.
Mr. Matsumoto.
Yes.
I left most of them.
What are you going to do with this?
What are you doing?
He's really angry.
And he's being scolded in a low voice.
It's even scarier.
It's okay if he gets angry.
Mr. Matsumoto gets 40 points more.
17, 18, 19, 20.
21.
22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 39.
32.
There are two here.
33, 34.
It's a child.
It's on his sleeve.
35.
How many did you get?
Mr. Saito got 75 points.
There's no way you can get 75 points.
If that's the case, you need a little more time.
Now, it's your turn.
Why are you reacting like that?
It's coming.
Let's go.
Ready.
And the final round starts.
Two minutes is pretty fast.
Two minutes is fast.
You'll lose points if you don't do it.
It's hot.
The last 30 seconds.
Hurry up.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Time's up.
Keep it up.
It's on his sleeve.
This is not fair.
This is 40 points.
It's not fair.
Look.
It's 30 points.
You should have 20 points.
Seriously.
If you win, you'll get a penalty.
This is not fair.
If we continue like this, Yamazaki will get a penalty.
Heipo and Yamazaki will play off.
Which one is the penalty game?
Ready.
You're a little too close.
One point.
You're getting close.
No matter how many times I say it.
Two points.
You're getting too close.
Bring the noodles.
Bring the noodles like Heipo.
Shut up.
I don't want to get involved.
Time's up.
Please look at this.
I'm sorry to my father.
There's a lot left.
At this point.
You're just complaining.
There's no point in counting.
It can't be helped.
The penalty game is Heipo of the world.
It's a curry.
Heipo will go to India.
He will go to India to clean.
He will bring the clothes he prepared.
He will clean the place.
He will come back.
He will get on the plane.
You can't be mistaken for a newbie.
There's a car.
I've finally arrived in India.
It's like a hot spring.
I'm scared.
I'm taking a picture.
I'm cleaning.
I'm scared.
I'm sorry.
I'm cleaning.
I'm scared.
I'm going to the center.
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to the center.
Bean soup?
Yes.
Japanese curry?
Curry?
Yes.
Go on.
Okay.
Sorry.
Thank you.
Another one?
Yes.
Sir?
Yes?
Thank you.
Very handsome.
Arigatou gozaimasu.
Oh, it's so beautiful. It's not attached at all.
There were a lot of these attached.
Alright, I can go back to Japan with this.
Ladies and gentlemen.
There were a lot of people here, right?
I didn't make any noise.
Today's guest is going to get beaten if he shows his moon.
That's why I think it's better to be natural.
It's not that.
I really don't want to change forever.
What are you talking about?
I'm just saying.
It's going to be a big era.
What do you mean?
The number of children is decreasing.
If we continue like this, the number of elderly people is going to increase.
I see.
I'm going to be in trouble.
Why?
No one is going to take care of me.
That's what you're thinking now, right?
I don't know what's going to happen next.
I don't want to get married.
That's why I think we should have children in various places.
You look a bit old.
Right?
Stop asking me.
I want to have a baby.
I don't want.
It doesn't suit you.
You mean, you're going to take over the family?
Yes, yes, yes.
No way.
More specifically, it's like a baby in an exam.
Even if you don't know who the mother is, you can take care of the child.
About 10.
10 people? What are you going to do with 10 people?
What are you doing?
I'm holding you
10 people?
What are you doing?
It's raining
It's raining?
I've been protecting you
10 people
You can go somewhere else
If it's raining
It feels good
It doesn't feel good
It's impossible
Why?
What do you do every day?
I don't go to work
Don't do something like Agnes
You're on TV all the time
Get out
Take off your gloves
Put it on
The golf course
The bottom is 90 and the top is 120
Mr. Matsumoto
Tiger Woods is very popular
in the golf world
From Mr. Matsumoto's point of view
Tiger Woods is still very popular
Mr. Matsumoto, please give me some advice
Do you know Tiger Woods?
Yes
He's on the news a lot
He won
The other day
Where?
Spielberg
At Hebel Beach
You know it well
Yes
I've been watching it
I thought he was good
But he's still
not very good mentally
He's good at technology
He's quite rough
But he was
much better at Hebel Beach
I wanted to say that
Is that so?
Yes
Can you give me some advice?
You're on a golf course
in the middle of the night
What are you doing?
I'm taking a lesson
I have a teacher
No, no
You shouldn't teach
I shouldn't teach golf
I should do it
Why are you angry?
You should trust me
Wait
What are you doing?
The balance is bad
Why are you doing this?
You're not doing it for Mr. Oka
You shouldn't fall down
First
You should open more
Like this
Open more
Lower your left leg
Left leg?
Like this
Don't bend
Yes
Good
I'm tired
Put your fingers up
Like this?
Like this
Put it on your forehead
How do you do it?
Like this?
I can do it
No, it's the same
What did you do it for?
If you can avoid it
Don't do it
Don't think you're alone
I look like I'm alone
That's why you're angry
How do you do it?
Don't try to learn everything from others
There are only hints today
Right?
I can't teach you everything
I know
Right?
Yes
Think about it
Think about it in English
It's too complicated
S-E-R-O
What?
G-A
No
I have a question for you
When your teacher hates you
How do you improve your image?
I have a way
I can get away from them
Even if you don't like them
You can't just get away
There's no one I don't like
For example, you can try to raise your chest
It's a woman's case
What about men?
Men don't matter
I can raise men's chest
But
I said, I don't know where it is, and from here, the valley is like...
But it would be nice if it was a woman!
What would a man do?
Even if it was a man, you can barely see the valley.
It's really...
Sensei, this...
I don't know.
Even if you shake it, it won't shake!
I think it was a woman.
I was resting yesterday, and I didn't hear it.
What's wrong with you? What's wrong with your body?
What are you doing?
At that time, I thought, what are you doing?
But after I got home,
Muramatsu, that guy...
I don't know.
It's about time for you to retire from the entertainment industry and get a job at MPM.
Yes, yes.
I don't want to do anything for two or three minutes while I'm waiting for my lunch at the convenience store.
I want to get rid of my laziness, but what should I do?
What about you?
I don't go to magazines anymore.
You're the farthest from the magazine.
That's right.
What would you do if you were waiting for your lunch at the convenience store?
Why?
If I'm called, I should go.
I don't even know your name.
Are you a customer at Young Hamburg?
I don't care. I don't care.
That's embarrassing.
Are you a customer at Young Hamburg?
I don't care.
Shut up.
Are you a customer at Young Hamburg?
I don't care.
That's embarrassing.
Food is one of the cultures.
You're warming up the food, and you pretend not to look at it.
I can't allow that.
No, no. It's just boring to wait like this.
Yes, yes.
You can just look at it and go in.
It doesn't change much.
What kind of lunch is that?
I'm a little late for that.
It doesn't matter if it's a McDonald's.
I'm warming up the food.
The food I want to eat is being warmed up.
So please listen to that scream.
Please listen to it.
The scream of grilled fish.
The smile of an egg.
How can I listen to it?
Tell me how to listen to it.
What?
How can I listen to it?
That's really...
Please listen to it.
How can I do it?
Like this.
Yes, yes.
It's amazing.
I was really lonely.
I was lonely for two of the Tokyo Dome.
I've been working as a counselor in the children's phone room for five years.
I always leave the lights in my room on and go to sleep.
My mother scolds me for leaving them on.
How can I convince my mother?
You need to have the courage to do anything.
For example, let's say you dig a hole in a car.
When you dig a hole, this is a problem.
You have to go down and apologize.
No, you can't apologize.
You can't apologize for this.
What?
It's the same.
What is that?
It's not something to be surprised about.
I didn't notice it at all.
When your opponent is weak, you can say,
I'm sorry.
This is my win.
Be careful!
Bang!
You can use this pattern.
It's always like that.
I see.
In that sense.
That's why I often say that life is about momentum.
The one with momentum wins.
I see.
Why did you leave it on?
If you say that, it's that pattern.
You can't leave it off.
I don't know what you're talking about.
If you say it with that momentum.
Tokihiko-chan!
Tokihiko-chan, who was so weak as a child.
The tiger?
The wolf?
It depends on the situation.
After all.
The wolf is good.
That's absolutely necessary.
That's right.
There are times when it's quite clear.
For example, when your girlfriend comes home.
When you take a bath.
You say, I had long hair.
I see.
At this time, you can't move around.
Didn't you have long hair?
You can't say that.
If you say you didn't have short hair.
I didn't have it.
That's not true.
My hair is short.
Or.
Didn't you have short hair?
After saying that.
You can't say that I didn't take a bath here.
You can't say that.
You can't say that this is my room.
What is this person?