Hello, this is the 7th time I've been here.
Are you a celebrity, So-chan, or Gramps?
Now, let's welcome tonight's guests!
Today's guests are...
Let's introduce them!
Nakagawami-san!
Have you seen this segment before?
Of course I have.
I don't know what you're talking about.
If I had a TP, I wouldn't be here now.
You're talking about Komaruya, aren't you?
I'm sorry to say this, but I'm not Komashiro from San Pol.
Why?
I'm the one who's been doing this for a while.
I know what's good and what's bad.
It's a little unpleasant.
It's a little unpleasant, isn't it?
Last but not least, Matsumoto-san!
I think so, too.
Strangely, this segment has good ratings.
I don't need good ratings.
You just said that!
Let's get started.
Are you a XXX-chan, or Gramps?
Here it is!
You don't have any fans in Japan, do you?
I've been doing this for a while, but you don't have any fans in Japan, do you?
That's a tough question.
Tell me your gender.
All of them are women.
Women?
Then you don't have XXX-chan?
That's not a talent.
Please write it down.
If I were a man, I'd be XXX-chan.
If you say that, I'll let you go.
Please, please.
Are you sure?
I'm sorry, but I'll let you go for now.
Please write it down.
Let's start with Mie-san.
You don't like it?
It's not that I don't like it.
I'm just saying the current situation.
But...
Okay, Otake-san.
Do you know this person?
Nakamura Azusa-san.
He's doing a commercial for Keirin, right?
That's right.
He's been in a lot of commercials.
Who's recommending him?
I'm in a commercial, too.
He's not recommending anyone other than the toilet.
He's good.
You shouldn't say something like that.
Okay, Matsumoto-san.
Matsumoto-san is...
I see.
Sakai Noriko.
Let's see the correct answer on the video.
Who is it?
I think it's Yamamoto Rinda-san.
Matsuda Seiko-san.
I think it's Rippy.
If it's not Hong Kong, I don't think it'll work.
Yamada Kuniko-san.
Itsuo Mayumi.
Sakunada Junko-san.
Wata Akiho.
Sakurada Junko.
Matsuda Seiko.
Kiyoka Nijiko.
Sakai Noriko.
Matsuda Seiko-san.
Kobayashi Tachiko.
I don't want you to wear that costume anymore.
Yamamoto Rinda.
Yamada Kuniko-san.
Yamada Kuniko.
Sakurada Junko.
Yamamori is Sakurada Junko-san.
Everyone, out!
I haven't seen it recently, so I totally forgot.
It was fun, wasn't it?
Even if I go to a dinner show, only people who are hungry come.
Even if you're hungry, you have to pay.
How much is it?
Next is this!
Actually, you're the killer lemon of the entertainment world!
It's hard to write.
Next, please.
This is a little scary.
Mie-san, please show it.
Here you go.
You have to go this far.
It's like Godzilla vs. King Ghidorah.
It's not my opinion.
Ah, I see.
That's right.
Next, Mako-chan.
What kind of joke is this?
There's no joke at all.
There's a story, isn't there?
That's not it.
This guy!
You have to work a lot.
You have to say the reason.
I don't have any reason, but on the Shinkansen,
I came in, put on glasses,
and wore a flashy shirt.
When I got in, I looked around like this,
and there was a person, me and my eyes.
I'm going.
Without anything?
Without anything.
I'm going to say hello.
You should say that properly.
That's right.
Okay, Masato-san.
Tamura Eriko?
This *** woman.
I can't say hello to her.
Really.
Why?
It's annoying.
Didn't you call her from behind?
No, I didn't.
Harada is ***, so I didn't call her.
Wow!
Who is it? Who is it? Who is it?
No matter how I think about it, it's Otake-san.
He seems to have a bad personality.
He often says that he's bad.
Ruu Oshiba-san.
Oda Yuji?
I think it's Nakao Mie.
Naga Mariko.
Naga Akiko-san.
Izumi Pinko-san.
Ruu Oshiba.
I think it's downtown.
Especially Hama-chan.
Kamioka Ryutaro.
Wada Akiko.
Because he's a great drinker.
Izumi Pinko-san.
Taito Yuki-san.
Otake Makoto-san.
I think it's Otake-san.
Wada Akiko.
Izumi Pinko.
Otake Makoto.
Wada Akiko.
Wada Akiko?
Now, everyone except Wada Akiko-san is out.
Oda-san is in second place.
Second place?
No, Izumi Pinko-san is in third place.
Izumi Pinko-san is in third place, right?
Now, let's go.
You look dissatisfied.
Next is this one.
You...
You're in an adult toy shop!
You don't know what you're doing.
If you don't come, you won't be able to sleep at night.
Please sit here for a while.
I have something to do.
Of course, it's a woman.
I don't know how to guess.
Now, let's start from Mie-san.
You're in a daily store, right?
Wada-san.
It's just that I don't look like it.
Masumoto-san.
Azachi Yumi.
Who is it? Who is it? Who is it?
Kawashima Naomi.
Ah, that's right.
I think you'll like her.
Okamoto Natsuki.
Isn't that Matsuda Seiko-san?
Kisamoto Masami.
I'm in trouble at night.
Okashiyama Ryoshu.
Okamoto Natsuki.
Kaku Chikako.
Soyanagi Rumiko-san.
My husband is young, so I wonder if he's satisfied.
Asano Yuko.
Okamoto Natsuki.
Koyanagi Rumiko.
Wada Aki-ko.
My husband is young, so I wonder if he's satisfied.
Kisamoto-san.
Koyanagi Rumiko-san.
Okamoto Natsuki.
Kisamoto-san.
Kisamoto.
Kisamoto Masami.
So, the last one is Kisamoto Masami.
I see.
Natsuki is possible.
It's possible.
I'm afraid of nodding.
Are you sure?
Ok, let's go to the next one.
The next one is this one.
You're just a chinchin enoki mushroom, chan!
Do you have that?
Wow, Mie-san, you're fast!
Why are you so fast?
I'm writing it as a memory of my trip home.
I'll write it as a memory of my trip home.
Welcome back, everyone.
It's hard.
Ok, let's start with Mie-san.
Mie-san.
Dan!
Oh, it's me!
I'm really big.
I'm not small.
Really?
I just get stiff when I'm excited.
What are you talking about?
Okamoto-san.
I'm Takeda, the melody.
But the character is different.
The character is different?
I'm sorry.
It's ok.
Ok, Matsumoto-san.
I'm not used to it.
What's that?
No, no, no.
It's a step forward.
There's a beeper over there.
Who is it? Who is it? Who is it?
Matsumoto-san.
Matsumoto-san from downtown.
He looks like he's about to get scared.
The sun-matchan.
The general Kazetai.
He's like a hero.
But he's lucky.
Tamori-san.
Sano-shiro-san.
Kazama Toru.
Sano-shiro.
Tamori-san.
Matsumoto-san.
Sano-shiro-san.
Giant Baba.
Tamori-san.
Sano-shiro-san.
Matsumoto-Hitoshi.
Sano-shiro.
Let's have fun!
Let's have fun with the Grand Prix!
Everyone out!
There were a lot of macho ones.
There were a lot.
How was it?
It was huge.
It was hard to breathe.
It was amazing.
It was like the hand of the Doraemon.
It felt good.
It's been a while.
That's right.
But this year, I've been a mess.
What do you mean?
From what to what, it's doubled.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to double everything.
I'm going to double the dip as well.
I'm going to make it crispy.
Are you going to double the gyara?
Of course I'm going to double the gyara.
Not only that, but more than anything, it's double fun.
It's double fun.
If you did it once, you wouldn't be able to do that.
If you did it twice, you wouldn't be able to do that.
Don't say that.
You've been doing that since last year.
I've been out all the time.
But you've been saving money.
I've been saving twice as much.
I see.
It's crazy.
I drink a lot.
I drink a lot and sometimes I can't stop.
It's an outlaw.
I see.
But when it comes to love, it's crazy.
Even if you're a kid, you say it was fun and go home.
But it's not like that.
Please stop.
It's crazy.
Let's look forward to it.
Are you going to do something?
Me?
What are you going to power up more than last year?
I'm not going to power up.
What?
The other day, I was watching the police for 24 hours.
The difference between Osaka and Tokyo was huge.
The police and the people in the other town were fighting.
There are a lot of places like Tokyo.
There's Nagoya.
Osaka was amazing.
The old lady and the police were fighting.
Stop it.
What are you talking about?
I kicked this kid first.
The old lady said it.
I'll kill you.
Osaka is a mess.
I kicked him when he took me to Osaka.
I kicked him.
A lot of people come to the police station.
This kid came to the police station.
I kicked him.
You're a hidden camera.
You just walked in.
HON MAN.
I like the timing of the police Verse.
And I'm the next.
and a bunch of other guys
When I came in
The police officer was writing on the counter
He was writing a document desperately
Excuse me
I don't have any money
I don't have any either
Can you lend me some money?
I said I don't have any
When I saw that in Osaka
There were a lot of weird guys and all the people walking were comedians
That's what they told me
So what did you say to that Osaka guy who's a foodie?
Why?
I didn't say I don't have any!
What's with you?
Why are you smiling?
Are you going to eat that?
But a long time ago
I did a video about you
I've been doing a lot of that stuff
Everyone's a fake
I'm a real fake
I'm not a fake
I'm my own original
Original, original, cheap
I sold it, I sold it, I sold it, I sold it, I sold it, I sold it, buy my own original
When I turn into me
What?
It's not good to say one thing
You should decide the punishment
I don't know at this point
That's right
What are we going to do?
What should we do?
Let's go with a strong one.
What do you mean by strong?
You know...
You have to do it with a 70-year-old old lady.
Urgh...
That's not how you do it.
I already know the other person's reaction.
It's tough.
That's no good.
There was a *** ***.
*** *** went to a love hotel with a girl.
The girl was like, no, no, no.
No, *** ***.
*** ***.
Where are you going, *** ***?
The girl ran away.
She went into the hotel to get some money.
What a waste.
She was sleeping in the hotel room.
The next day, the cleaning lady came.
The cleaning lady?
The cleaning lady came and said,
Oh, you're here. I'm sorry.
*** ***.
What the ***?
What are you talking about?
The cleaning lady ran away.
What a waste.
*** ***.
What's inside the calculator?
I don't know.
It's pretty thin, isn't it?
That's right.
I've cut it before.
You've cut it before?
Yes.
To check it out?
What's inside?
Inside, there's a strawberry.
Why is there something like that?
*** ***.
That's enough.
Why are you eating it?
It's just a strawberry.
But it's a calculator.
To be clear,
I think it's more precise to put a big one in the whole electronic product.
I think it's amazing.
The contents are pretty small.
You think airplanes are amazing, don't you?
There are about three types of parts used for that.
*** ***.
There's no way there are three types.
If you open it, it's a simple structure.
An airplane.
Is that so?
Yes.
It's simple.
What do you call that driver's seat?
Yes.
A cockpit?
A cockpit.
You've seen it on TV, haven't you?
It's amazing.
There are only three types.
That's the basics.
What do you mean by basics?
There are a lot of things.
There's a lever.
There's one here, too.
But you can't use it around here.
Lighting,
clock, etc.
That's the basics.
You can't just use a clock and lighting.
There are a lot of things.
There are only three types.
You can't just use all of them.
I don't like dummies.
I only like the previous ones.
Then why do you have to use dummies?
Because they're cool.
I don't want to be looked down on.
Who?
Who are you looking down on?
The sky.
Don't be ridiculous.
Idiot!
Today,
the driver's seat is the last one.
This is for everyone.
Thank you for your hard work.
I came to Tokyo
to do something.
I was asked to join this program.
I was able to get to know a lot of people.
I wanted to do it until the end,
but I had something I wanted to do.
I ended up missing it on the way.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for the four years.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll invite you to the opening party.