I'm Yoroshiku in the third time of the Gaki-no-tsukai Ara-hen
I'm a favorite entertainer
Are you so Chan-ka Grand Prix?
Good evening
Now everyone
It's already very popular
Are you so Chan-ka Grand Prix?
It's fun
Now
Guests and Matsumoto-san
Let's say the true name of the business
Now then, guests
Please
It is the usual member
Is it a book?
This is it
A book came out
Shift life
Is that so?
Well, thank you
Because there are guests today
Even if you put a beat here
These guys will speak
I think I can talk about it
There are too many mosaics
It's a mosaic
It takes a lot of time
I went in like that
It's okay now
I don't think it's good to put it out
The problem is here
Jaga-chan
If you look like you're out
Shingo-san family
Well, this problem is Shingo-san family
I have calculated
Let's introduce
I don't have to say it again
Why is it so wrong?
Well
Lega-in-chan or the captain
Who will be chosen as the captain in these three people?
For the time being
12 women and students
Among them
5 seconds
The person who entered the lock is
Lega-in-chan or the captain
Please come on
I've done it once or twice so far
I can't get this once
I want to do it once
Is that so?
I haven't hit it once
All of them are like this
Everyone is funny
That's the end
Let's go
First of all, Otake-san
Please
What did I say
Goroh
Nobichi Goroh
What is Yoko no Ewa?
Senbei-san
No matter what I do
Looking at this person's woman
After all it looks big
Hideki-san
After all young people are not against
I see
Why are you talking to a dangerous person?
Because I don't know the name
That's right
An older sister of this age
It's okay
I had this kind of person in my head
Yes, Matsumoto-san
Well
Hideki
I see
I just know the name
What?
What do you mean?
I'm watching
Well
It's Komewareru
Are you already in?
You guys are also happy
If you say now
Say yes
Mr. Goroh Nobuchi
I see
Hideki Taijo
Because it looks like a wild man
Go Hiromi
Mr. Goroh Nobuchi
Taisho?
Koohiro?
Boro?
Your face is ugly, so go to the bathroom.
Okay.
Well, then I'll go get rid of it.
And so, Taisho Hideki is the champion of the world championship!
It's the first time he's used it!
You did it!
You did it.
This is nice.
The next question is this!
A female idol who seems to be eating Hanako!
Who wrote this?
Now, please write it on the flip.
Go ahead!
It's obvious if you write it.
Is there anyone who is obvious?
I'm glad I wrote it.
What kind of person is it?
Let's take a look.
Mr. Ozaki!
Go ahead!
I wrote two people.
Yamada-san!
Yamada-san, Nami.
Well, really.
Well, this guy seems to be eating, too.
After that.
It's eating.
The vocal.
Did you see him eat?
Don't listen to me!
I wrote Chiharu and Matsumoto Akko.
I see.
The real name is Matsumoto Akko, right?
Matsumoto Akko is an idol.
It's obvious that such a person ate it.
Why is that?
I'm not surprised if such a person ate it.
I'll try to write it without the real name.
Chiharu.
Matsumoto Akko.
Matsumoto-san!
That's difficult.
Well, I'm...
Can you eat Hanako?
I don't know if I can eat it.
You're fine, too.
You can open a big office.
Right?
I'm sure I can open a big office.
I'm sure I can.
Miyuki Imori.
Hiroko Moriguchi.
Eriko Tamura.
Shizuka Kudo.
Hiroko Moriguchi.
If you don't watch TV, you'll probably lose.
Eriko Tamura.
I don't think it's a good idea to eat it.
From Nakajo.
Shizuka Kudo.
Eriko Tamura.
Imori-san.
Noriko Sakai.
I want to eat it with a beer.
Shizuka Kudo.
Eriko Tamura.
I'm eating it!
The first place is Shizuka Kudo!
The second place is Eriko Tamura.
There were a lot of them.
Moriguchi.
Imori.
Sakai.
Noriko.
Don't shoot this.
Why are you doing that?
I can't use it like this!
I'll put a mosaic here.
I don't know what's going on.
Shut up.
I'm talking about drinking.
In a week's time, everyone will be in Tokyo.
I'll put it in.
Inahama-chan.
Come over here.
You come over here, too.
It's fun.
I'll sit here.
You also sit here.
I'll do it properly.
I'm sure it'll fly.
It's illegal.
Osake-san.
Enjoy!
I'm gonna eat a great
That's good.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm going to eat Shreme-kun.
You've got changed your mind.
It's cute.
You're saying you went to the right person.
I think that's the most common thing in the book.
Why is the person who wrote it angry?
I thought I followed you.
I didn't go to the right person.
I don't even know if this is a joke.
I don't know.
Golden Harp's Eva.
There aren't many people who remember this.
Well, there aren't many people who remember this.
I understand.
Let's go!
Let's go to the world!
Please!
Kimo-mi Daiki
Matsuzaka Keiko
Izumi Pinko
Mori Mitsuko
Hatsumi Dori
I see.
It doesn't seem to be that good.
Izumi Pinko
Koyanagi Rumi-po
It's a pretty Matsuzaka Keiko.
Kote Gawa Yu
Izumi Pinko
Matsuzaka Keiko
It doesn't smell like something.
When I look at that man.
Hatsumi Dori
Rikako
Kondo Misako-san, Tsugai Kinji-san, Ohagi-san, Matsudaira Keiko-san.
So, Bun-chan and the others are Matsudaira Keiko-san.
Everyone, forget it.
It's not funny.
Let's go to the last question.
The last question is...
Here it is!
It's not funny.
It's not funny at all.
I saw it earlier.
Nothing has changed.
I've seen it twice.
It's not a big deal.
That's right. When you come out, you say,
Wow!
It's not because you're popular.
I just saw the people I saw on TV live.
I just said that.
But that's it.
After all, there are times when you can see something you can't usually see by watching it live nearby.
What does that mean?
After all, I've been watching you all the time, so I know.
After all, when people watch TV, when they watch it live, they wonder if there's a mole in that place.
I see.
That's what I found.
Of course, why is Matsumoto so dumb?
That's what you're saying because you want to say that.
I'm in trouble.
Look at this.
There's a rock maker in it.
That's cool.
If you look closely, you can see it from the other side.
This is really.
I can see it.
It's amazing.
There's a tree in it.
Well, that's one of the things.
Don't say that.
I might have said it before.
Why are you stepping on your feet?
I'm sorry.
Just leave it alone.
I don't know what that entertainer is.
I wonder if it's a nuisance.
Thank you.
I didn't know at all.
I thought it was a talent show.
It's quite a nuisance.
It's a nuisance that only entertainers have.
I'm checking it myself, who is looking at me, I'm not a Zura guy.
This program is a talk show.
I'm talking to my partner, but why am I here?
Talk to me!
But I like you very much.
I don't like you at all.
Is this it?
It's coming.
I think I should do it again.
I don't want to do it again.
I don't like you when you say it yourself.
Well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well.
Why?
I don't like you.
I met you before.
What?
We're moving, aren't we?
When I'm moving, I'm on the bullet train, and I'm next to someone.
There's something bad about that.
Next to you?
Next to me.
The man who was on my bullet train the other day.
He's talking to me.
I know.
You're like a poop.
You're there sometimes, aren't you?
What are you eating?
You're really...
I'm sorry, I'm going to poop in front of you.
There is.
Why is that?
I don't think I'm eating poop.
But it smells like poop.
Where do you poop when you eat rice?
Let's say you ate katsudon.
What?
It's still katsudon around here.
It's still katsudon.
In your case, I think it's a little different.
What's that?
The one with the poop.
So maybe it's fast.
What does that mean?
When you eat and go to the toilet, you're in a poop state.
I'm in a poop state.
Maybe.
That's why I'm talking, so I'm tired.
I don't know if this is 100%.
But I'm going to eat it.
That's what you're saying 100%.
Don't you know that?
I don't know.
That's why you're in a poop state.
I was told that.
What?
What do you mean?
Why am I?
That's weird.
I'm serious.
If you say it to Matsumoto, it's the same.
There may be people who think so.
There's nothing smelly in my body.
What are you talking about?
Well, maybe it's because I eat it.
You smell like squid every time.
That's because I eat squid.
I don't know if that's the case.
When I'm talking, I'm in a good mood.
I'm having a lot of fun.
If you smell like squid, I'll be late for the tsukkomi.
If you're going to say something like that, I'll have you say it.
What is it?
There are times when you smell like squid.
What do you smell like?
What is it?
It's me, isn't it?
That's a good joke.
Matsumoto is also in a good mood today.
I'm going to write that I'm in a good mood.
I'm in a good mood.
What are you going to write?
I'm still a little scared.
I'm going to write this.
That's what I wrote.
I think it'll be good for the opening.
What do you think when you see it?
White.
What?
Why?
What do you think?
Before you ask me why.
I'll take the white one.
Why?
I said white.
No, I'm sorry. It's white.
I'm telling you.
It's white.
I'm the white one.
That's why I'm telling you.
I'm telling you it's white.
Wait a minute.
Did you decide on this?
Make sure you decide on that.
I don't decide on rock-paper-scissors.
No, no, no, no.
I'm telling you I don't decide on rock-paper-scissors.
I want to play rock-paper-scissors.
Why are you suddenly talking about rock-paper-scissors?
It's okay, so I'll do it.
Rock-paper-scissors.
What is it?
I'm the white one.
I won the rock-paper-scissors.
Don't say stupid things.
I'll do it properly in the opening.
I often see men with a split chin.
That split eye is useful.
It's there to hold up paper.
Why do you hold it up?
Why don't you hold it up?
You're doing this on purpose.
In Harari Man, you hold it up a little more.
But why don't you hold it up?
It's better if you stop!
I often say that there is nothing inferior to the human body.
Is that so?
That's why there must be some meaning in the fact that the chin is cracked.
There must be some meaning.
What do you mean?
Do you have a meaning?
There is a meaning.
What's the meaning of this?
That's what I'm going to say.
If you ask why it's cracked like this, it's because it's easy to eat.
What?
It's cracked all at once.
If you ask why it's cracked, it's because it's easy to eat.
If you eat the contents of it, you're supposed to eat it when it's cracked.
It's easy to eat when it's empty anyway.
It is easy to eat when it's empty.
That's what I'm saying.
It's easy to eat when it's empty.
You're saying it!
I'm saying it!
No, no, so...
What's the point of this?
If it's open, it's easy to eat!
Yeah, if it's open, it's easy to eat!
If it's cracked, it's easy to open!
If it's open, it's easy to eat!
That's why!
Those who open and eat it are being ungrateful!
I'm not talking about eating it or not eating it!
If it's open, it's easy to eat!
That's strange!
Hey, you!
If you're angry, come here!
If it's open, it's easy to open!
I can't open it anymore!
I'll tell you what you can really do!
It's better to hold it here!
Ah! Not yet!
As a joke, I think it's okay!
No, master, really!
Open it!
Come on!
I'm trying to get something in there!
Not yet!
If there are only those two!
Open it here!
If it's open, it's easy to eat!
Eh?
Am I mistaken?
Ah! If it's open, it's even more open than the mouth!
I think it means that you can put a lot of things in it!
I'm addicted!
What are you talking about?
If there are ten eyes on the back!
It's easy to open!
No, wait a minute!
It's like this, isn't it?
It's open, isn't it?
What kind of state is this?
That's why it's all open here!
Are you saying something like this?
What is it?
It's open, isn't it?
Then it's easy to eat!
It's easy to eat, isn't it?
What's easy to eat?
The inside!
That's right!
That's why we've always thought that it's open and easy to eat things!
It's easy to open and eat!
What the hell!
Are you pulling out the inside?
I'll tell you!
I don't eat!
It's easy to eat!