Kono Music
It's Kono Music
What is this, suddenly
It's pretty much the same
I also want to rehearse
Music start
I want to dance
What are you doing
I can't say it
I'm doing my best
I'm laughing
It's fun
It's not a tree
It's written
I see
It's hard to be a choreographer
Merry Christmas
It's almost over
Today
2005 Gaki no Tsukai
Funny VTR
Best 10
Are you mad?
I'm not mad
This year
8 years in a row
I was chosen
Downtown manager
My name is Kojiro Koryuki
It's cut
It's not cut
What is this?
It's the most important part
It's not cut
Let's stop here
It's not cut at all
It's broken
There were many good things
Downtown's DVD
The DVD
1.5 million
It's amazing
I can't imagine DVD
Kojiro
What is this?
You have a good reaction
There are not many people
who can make a good reaction
in Hamano's room
Today
We have a special member
New face
Why are you there?
Please
Please tell me
Help me
Someone stop this bus
This program
is sponsored by
the sponsor
Slowly
It's dirty
If you tear this
I see
This is a success
It's a success
It's me
It's amazing
It's broken
Stop
You have no right
Now, Yamaram, it's time for you to go to sleep.
She came here on purpose, right?
I was working with Kona, but what was that?
What's going on?
Yamaram...
Yamaram suddenly became quiet.
What's going on?
Yamaram...
Good night.
I'll do my best like this.
A big event once a year, the celebrity fishing competition.
This year, five guests gathered in Kawaguchiko.
They want to catch a giant black bass and have a serious fight.
This time, Eguchi-san couldn't participate due to work.
Next year, we'll be waiting for you.
The winner is Matsumoto!
Matsumoto wins!
This is the fourth time in two years.
That's a lot.
I haven't seen this.
Really?
Hamada, the boy who works as a waiter, gets the members involved.
A heavy metal band, Souseiki, is formed.
And the practice is almost over.
Souseiki is Misato's...
Why did you do that?
That's too much.
What is this?
This is the worst.
Thank you.
I'm addicted to Souseiki.
I'm laughing so much that I'm going to faint.
You're a fool.
You're a complete fool.
I love it when Hamada-san is suffering.
Everyone in the family is laughing.
Please hug me.
Can I take off the lever?
The enemy's loyalty is 100%.
The miracle lever fortune teller, Piccadilly Umeda...
...kills the members with a dangerous prophecy.
He kills them.
The prophecy about Matsumoto is...
...that if he doesn't get married this year, he'll die.
The studio is filled with tension.
What advice did Piccadilly Umeda give to avoid this?
The prophecy about Hamada is that he's in danger of divorce.
To prevent this, he tells his wife that he loves her once a day.
This is where Endo's line came from.
I think everyone will agree.
Shouldn't you say his name?
I don't have to say his name.
It's a joke.
Chiaki.
I love you.
Itao has been asking for money since he appeared on the show.
This time, he came to sell the format of the quiz show.
This week's quiz has started.
It's a quiz between his wife and Itao.
The Itzy dance has started.
Everyone, please give your answers.
Say safety, safety, Yamazaki-san.
Safety, safety.
Yamazaki-san, safety, safety.
He has been completely locked up.
Please sit down.
It's 1,100,000 yen.
And the assistant's wife won for some reason.
He has been asking for money and the format of the show.
It's here.
Are you going home, wife?
I didn't have that idea.
No, it's different.
Of course it's different.
It's different.
While playing a game on the bus, they go around the city.
However, the winner of the game has to kiss Madonna who is waiting for him at the destination.
Who is Madonna?
The first one is Kochouran Abeko.
Who will be the loser?
What is it?
Abeko!
It's here.
The size of her face is different.
The next Madonna is Tsubaki Funako from Mahaha Honpo.
The game resumed with 6 people other than Matsumoto.
Who will be the next loser?
Shinji!
Matsumoto.
It's me.
Wow, it's amazing.
This is the most difficult.
I can only see the salaryman.
10 years couple.
Tanaka's kiss is decided in the last game, Kokon Tozai.
Who will be the last Madonna?
Madonna.
It's Mimata.
It's a fierce face.
It's here.
It's hard.
It's different from here.
It's a separate place.
Look at this.
It's a star that I gave birth to.
That's right.
Why do you two work together?
It's amazing.
It's from here.
The third place is the project that encouraged the boy who was left alone in the room.
Murayama Toinichi will be appointed as the Prime Minister of the Republic of Japan.
Everyone will have their opinions.
You can't do that.
Is he an actor?
He's an actor.
Mr. Murayama will be appointed as the Prime Minister of the Republic of Japan.
There is a party in here.
He's happy.
This was a long time ago.
I'm not going out anymore.
End! End!
End!
Hide! Hide!
Join! Join!
Join!
Hide! Hide!
What are you doing?
Suddenly, in the form of the western police, Daimon, the Suga chief producer appeared.
Because one person alone is not enough, he told the other members to decide in the game.
The staff and the talent challenged various games, and one person was taken away with another person.
Finally, the 5 people of the western police were decided.
I'm hungry.
Right hand, right?
It's a pot.
I see.
Most people with black eyes appeared, right?
I wanted it to be like that
Is it 1st place?
I don't know
I don't know which one is 1st place
Downtown
Don't underestimate it
This is it
Inoue and Maa are the ones who are going to play football
The end of this year
Wait a minute
Who did you lose to?
You
Who?
This is
Yaman is laughing
He's laughing
I was behind Endo
I only stretched my legs
Excuse me
That's it
Isn't that it, you?
I don't know
I think Endo said a lot
Actually, he said a lot
Endo
It's a bad guy
Finally, the prank has reached its climax.
Okay.
Thank you for your hard work.
I don't know what to say.
I feel like I'm going to be licked.
Should I go?
No, it's okay.
I think they think it's me.
Why?
For some reason, he declared that he was the culprit.
Kohori goes to Hamada's dressing room.
What did Hamada show in the climax of the prank?
Excuse me.
I feel like I'm going to be licked.
Kohori.
What are you doing?
Are you drunk?
I'm not angry.
You're not angry, but you're going to hit me like that.
Next, he calls out to Iwao, who doesn't know anything.
What will happen?
What are you doing, Iwao?
In the end, Hamada himself hits the dressing room where the other three are.
You guys are different.
Hey.
It's useless.
It was a great face.
What's wrong?
What's wrong, Goto?
In addition, he makes another prank on the late Karate face target.
This time, all five young people are the target.
Matsumoto is angry.
That's right.
Irie is angry.
Don't be angry.
And as planned, the riot begins with the beginning of the Hanataba
Everyone is running away.
They're all running away.
Stop it.
You can't do that here.
I'm not tired.
Stop it.
You need to take off your mask.
If I take off my mask, I'll be laughed at.
In the same order as before, they gradually drive the Karate face into the fear of the
They gradually drive the Karate face into the fear of the
And Matsumoto 마지막 attacks tão
And finally Yabe goes to Matsumoto's dressing room to apologize.
They lose Yabe.
Yabe comes andarsi, Yabe leaves.
Yabu-chan, Yabu-chan, Yabu-chan, Yabu-chan
Obe-san
Yabu-chan
In the end, Matsumoto goes to Irie who doesn't know anything
Yabu-chan, Yabu-chan, Yabu-chan
What's wrong?
Because it was really scary
Who were you?
Aoi
I see
This is interesting
It is
But the image of downtown is really bad
It's not that scary
It's just that Kokoriko is being teased
I heard it during the meeting
Kokoriko might go a little
If you don't go a little, you might get caught
I thought it was ok
It's not a little at all
Everyone was beaten up during my time
I'm sorry
How many times did you get beaten up?
Lastly, we will say goodbye while watching this
Everyone, have a good year
Thank you
What is this sound?
No matter how you look from here, it's a hard game
I can't move at all
This is not good for this program
This program was brought to you by the sponsor of this program