In the first episode of Gake no Skyer, we're going to talk about a good story that really happened.
Manager vs. E-Episode Contest!
What are you doing?
This is a bit strange.
It's not strange.
It's hard.
E-Episode Contest?
What do you mean?
This time, we're going to have each manager compete with each other in an E-Episode.
E-Episode?
The manager is already tired.
Are you okay?
When I came into the studio, no one said hello to me.
I can't see you.
That's strange.
It's strange.
This is hard.
I've only slept for about two hours.
Matsumoto is in charge of Tajima.
Hamada is in charge of the 7th grade, Kimoto.
Yamasaki is in charge of Miyamoto.
Endo is still in charge of Yoshida.
Tanaka is in charge of Nishibayashi.
Each manager will introduce his talent in writing.
There will be two rounds.
The judges will give you points for each round.
There are judges?
There are judges.
What?
I called them.
The person with the highest score will be the winner.
Do you fine with it?
Excuse me.
Are you wrong?
Please explain the rules.
No, let's talk about it later.
He must be the most grandmother.
He is the president of SUGONEXECTIVE.
Hello!
I brought a character with me.
A character?
Next is Heipo-san.
I'm Heipo. Nice to meet you.
Please remember my name. I'm Heipo.
Really?
I don't need that.
What kind of character?
What kind of character do you have in mind?
And this time, we have a gentleman from a woman's point of view.
It's Yatsu Megumi-san.
Nice to meet you.
This is a rare opportunity.
I'm surprised why you called me here.
Right?
Nice to meet you.
You can't see this kind of high-profile scene, can you?
This program is brought to you by five sponsors.
First, we have Tanaka-san's manager, Ryo Nishibayashi.
Nice to meet you.
Tanaka Naoki's manager, Ryo Nishibayashi.
About two years ago, I had an important job.
I had to wake up on the morning of the recording day.
One morning, I fell asleep.
I got a call from Tanaka-san.
I was in a hurry and I thought I was going to get in trouble.
When I got on the phone, Tanaka-san said,
Nishi-kun, were you sleeping? I'm awake, so I'm fine.
Please call Endo.
He didn't blame me at all.
He was concerned about his partner.
I was so kind.
I felt Tanaka-san's kindness again.
After that, I called Endo-san right away.
Endo-san was already awake.
I thought he was sleeping.
When I left him alone, Tanaka-san was late.
I thought it was funny, so I kept quiet.
He said, ha ha ha ha.
As you can see from this,
Tanaka-san is a really nice person.
Thank you very much.
It's nice to be compared to me like that.
At least accept it.
He's a really bad guy.
That's true.
Tanaka's story is true.
It's embarrassing.
Let's see the score.
Please show us the score.
8 points, 7 points, 8 points.
That's a total of 23 points.
It's a bit sweet, Nishi-san.
It's sweet.
Yatsu-san, what did you think of the story?
As you can see, Tanaka-san is a really nice person.
He's kind.
Hama-san, Hama-san.
Let's move on to the next story.
Endo-san's manager, Yoshida.
Thank you very much.
This is a story I heard from Endo-san's favorite junior comedian, Kōri-san.
Kōri-san used to take Endo to DisneySea.
Kōri-san remembered that he had a show in Lumiere that day.
He couldn't tell Endo-san about it.
On that day, there were a lot of people in the park.
It was evening when he got on one of the rides.
Kōri-san, who was in a hurry, shook off his courage and said,
I'm sorry, Endo-san.
Actually, I forgot that I had a show in Lumiere today.
When he said that, Endo-san was shocked and sent Kōri-san out.
When Kōri-san called Endo-san right after the show at 9 p.m.,
He said, I have something to talk to you about, so come back.
He was called out by the manager.
Kōri-san thought he was going to get in trouble, but when he returned to DisneySea,
Endo-san was waiting near the entrance.
When Kōri-san came, he said, let's go.
He had already started walking towards DisneySea, which was closed.
And when Kōri-san made up his mind,
You've only been on one attraction, haven't you?
I've already paid for it, so I can't take the ride, but let's take a walk.
Kōri-san was so moved that he couldn't stop crying.
I thought it was really good that I was his manager.
Thank you very much.
Is this true?
Everyone went back to where they were going.
I thought it would be hard for the juniors to play.
What? You feel sorry for them?
I felt a little sorry for them.
I think it would be better to return DisneySea from Shinjuku.
That's true.
Thank you very much.
3 points!
5 points!
16 points!
There's something about this, right?
Sugata-san got 3 points.
Endo isn't that kind of guy.
What?
Some of the juniors said,
It's close to harassment, isn't it?
You can think of it that way.
Let's go.
I'm Hosei Yamasaki's manager, Miyamoto.
Thank you very much.
Go ahead.
Hosei Yamasaki.
Let's do it again.
It's okay, it's okay.
Yamakawa-san, Yamakawa-san.
How can you say the name of Hato's talent?
What do you think?
Yamakawa-san, Yamakawa-san.
Let's go.
I'm Miyamoto's manager.
I'm Hosei Yamasaki's manager, Miyamoto Yu.
This is a story from when I was just in charge of Yamasaki-san.
Yamasaki-san will be participating in the R1 Grand Prix.
When I was making up a story with the intention of winning,
He listened to my opinion, who was a new employee, and gave me an idea.
As a talent, he didn't treat me badly.
He adjusted the length of the story, the sound, and the length of the story.
He did everything from the same perspective.
I was so happy that I couldn't put it into words.
I was so happy that I could put it into words.
Unfortunately, I lost in the semi-finals.
I was in the car on my way home, and I was about to eat a pot.
I was sorry at that time, so I said I would help.
Yamasaki-san said, looking at the TV in the A,
I'm making a special dumpling for Yamachan right now.
We drank together on the way home, and he said,
I'm sorry, Miyamoto. I had you do a lot of things, but I couldn't answer you.
I will never forget that I was about to cry.
To be honest, the story of the semi-finals wasn't interesting.
But I swore to myself that I would follow him for the rest of my life.
Thank you very much.
He's not just an amateur, he's a manager.
He helped me.
He's a new employee.
Thank you very much.
5 points, 9 points, 9 points.
The total is 23 points.
Yasu-san, 9 points.
It's a good story.
I made a dumpling.
Yamachan dumpling.
I would be very happy if I were a manager.
I see.
I didn't agree with everyone's story.
Hamada-san's story.
I'm Hamada-san's manager, Kimitoshi.
Please.
It was like this.
It's okay.
It was a hot summer day.
It's not hot.
It was hot.
It was a hot summer day.
Let's go.
I'm Hamada-san's manager, Kimoto.
Please.
It was a hot summer day.
I was filming a drama outside.
The staff was tired.
When I got tired, Hamada-san asked me.
Can you do it in the heat?
Kimoto, buy ice cream.
I bought ice cream and came back.
Hamada-san saw the ice cream and bought it for everyone.
I gave the ice cream to everyone.
But this was all Hamada-san's care.
Hamada-san didn't want to eat ice cream.
He said he'd let the staff eat it.
He was actually listening to me from behind.
I was supporting him to buy ice cream for everyone.
I was impressed by Hamada-san's kindness.
Thank you.
I've heard that before.
I'm not good at talking.
It's a one-sided story.
Please give me a score.
7 points, 10 points, 6 points.
A total of 23 points.
Heipo got 10 points.
It's not something I can do.
I've worked with many people.
I don't have any ice cream memories.
That's what I'm saying.
I'll give you ice cream.
I don't know.
Yasu-san, what do you think?
I don't think it's a big deal.
Let's move on.
I'm the manager of Matsumoto-san.
This is when I helped Matsumoto-san move.
Matsumoto-san had a big TV and a massage chair.
I was wondering if I should get rid of the sofa and microwave.
They're all new and expensive.
I didn't have any money, so I asked for it.
Matsumoto-san said yes.
Matsumoto-san looked like a god.
Then I asked Matsumoto-san to sell it.
Matsumoto-san sold all the
Did Matsumoto-san make me feel like?
He's selling everything for 100,000 yen.
What are you talking about?
That's a good story.
Let's go to the end.
At this time, I was moved by the greatness of Mr. Matsumoto, who is not only kind but also considerate of the opponent's feelings.
It's over.
You are being deceived.
That's great.
What are you talking about?
This is a good story between me and Tajima.
Don't be so stubborn.
This is a strange story.
You are being deceived.
I'm a little disappointed.
Please judge.
3 points, 10 points, 7 points.
20 points.
10 points.
This is not something that can be done easily.
You gave it to him for free, didn't you?
What?
Which way do you want to go?
I'm sorry.
What kind of feeling do you want to get?
Give me a snack.
I was originally given a snack.
After this, Tanaka hit the car and made an honest apology.
He got 28 points.
Endo got 19 points.
Yamasaki refused Matsumoto's invitation.
He got 23 points.
Let's continue.
This is Mr. Hamada's manager, Mr. Kimoto.
I'll leave it to you.
Mr. Kimoto.
Go ahead.
This is a story about a certain year.
There was a game competition where players and staff won various prizes.
Two people in downtown won Don Quijote's prize.
Matsumoto received the prize and opened the bag immediately to check the contents.
He said, I can't put it in my wallet because it's big.
He was happy to receive the prize.
However, Mr. Hamada gave me a prize saying,
Thank you for always working hard.
Buy what you like.
Not only me, but also Tajima, who is in charge of Matsumoto.
He said, I can't get it from Matsumoto.
He gave me a gift card.
Mr. Hamada, who cares about his partner's manager,
I felt his heart as a man.
Thank you.
This is a wonderful story.
There is a hidden theme in this corner.
There is a hidden theme.
I don't know if you asked Tajima.
Actually, even now.
Why?
I got 10 tickets for 10,000 yen.
I used 9 tickets, but I gave one to Mr. Hamada as a souvenir.
There is no evidence of what Mr. Hamada gave me.
I gave it to you because it's Don Quijote.
Mr. Prodigy got 10 tickets for it.
He obtained the manager's prop 240shore equally.
This is amazing.
10 points.
It's a sincere story.
That's right.
It's wonderful.
I'm a little curious about the price of the ice cream and the products.
That's right.
It's a little bit of an object.
I'm a little curious about that, but it's a good story.
It's a good story.
I'd like to go to the end of the second lap.
I'm the manager of Mr. Matsumoto, Mr. Tajima.
Go ahead.
I want you to show me that.
This is a story I heard from Mr. Fujiwara, my senior manager.
When I went to pick up Mr. Matsumoto at home, Mr. Fujiwara found a plate in the garden.
I was wondering why there was a plate in the garden, and when I looked at the plate,
I saw a cat that looked like a stray cat in the neighborhood approaching the plate.
Actually, Mr. Matsumoto put a plate in the garden so that the stray cat in the neighborhood wouldn't get hungry.
And when the cat meowed at Mr. Matsumoto,
Mr. Matsumoto was embarrassed and said to Mr. Fujiwara,
Let's go.
When I heard this story,
When this person said, let's go, I followed him everywhere.
My chest got hot.
Thank you very much.
Is this true?
It's embarrassing.
It's a previous apartment.
A little cat came to the garden.
I fed the cat twice.
Let's go to the other side.
The cat meowed again.
6 points, 10 points, 9 points.
It's a little high.
It's high.
A total of 25 points.
Now that we've finished the two rounds,
From now on, let's go to the next episode.
Let's go to the next episode.
When I got on the car with Mr. Tanaka after work,
On the way, Mr. Tanaka said,
I want to go shopping, so I'm going to Urahara.
Is this the face of Urahara?
Mr. Tanaka said sorry.
I'm sorry to have you go out with me.
I'll buy you shoes.
Why shoes?
I don't want to hear it.
I'm fine until I get your feelings.
I don't like that story.
I was surprised that you were doing that.
I was surprised. I was rejected at that time, but I thought he was such a nice person.
He was kind.
I'll give you a minus.
2 points. 5 points. 5 points.
12 points.
That's amazing.
He's kind.
Who wants to go?
Yoshige.
Go there.
There's only one person.
If you say something, I'll hit you.
I can't stand it anymore.
Let's go, Mr. Kimoto.
It's a recent story.
Mr. Watanabe's family happened to pass by a house near his house.
He said hello to his family and went shopping.
He brought a cold drink and a cold beer to the house.
He can do it in an instant.
He's different from everyone.
He's getting used to it.
Let's see the scores.
Please.
1 point. 5 points. 4 points.
Listen to me.
I'm sick of these things.
That's right.
Hamada, Yamasaki, and Endo's team added an extra episode.
The score so far is as you can see.
Who has an episode?
Let's go.
Who is it?
I can't wait any longer.
We've already seen most of it.
Tashima, go.
Let's go.
I've been working with Matsumoto-san for about four years.
We had dinner together.
We had ramen when we got our license.
We had ramen for the first time.
That ramen was...
That ramen was really good.
What happened then?
He said nice things.
He talked about martial arts.
That's no good.
You're the one who said that.
I was really happy.
Okay, that's the end of the show.
It's the end.
It's finally over.
It's the end of the episode.
It's the end.
The winner is...
72 points.
Hamada-san.
Thank you.
This is a good one.
What is this?
The winner Hamada-san's team will receive these five prizes.
This is a TV call from Academy Japan.
This is a hair watch from Fossil Japan.
And this is a cruiser bike from Marui.
How was it?
If there's something like this, I want you to do your best.
I don't have anything to say.
I have a lot of stories about having a son.
Seriously?
Unfortunately.
Why are you saying that?
Tell us about your son.
Now you're telling me to save him.
I don't want to hear that.
Tell me about your son.
It's simple.
I'll tell you.
It's going to be quick.
Get it quick.
This is recent.
It's recent.
It was about your son.
My son...
Kojikawa, Kojikawa, Kojikawa
The two of us
I want to eat Kojikawa
This program was brought to you by 5 sponsors