Yōkan Fusai wa nakayoshi da
Matsumoto, who has made many great songs, has recently made a song for the Dango Brothers.
This time, we will invite a great singer to do a public recording of Yōkan Fusai.
Don't look down!
This is Matsumoto's first public recording of Yōkan Fusai, written and composed by Yōkan Fusai!
Hello!
You're finally here.
Yes, I am.
The song you recorded before was a temporary song.
Yes.
So this time, you're going to do it with a book in your hand.
Who are you going to sing it to?
The vocalist.
That's right.
There's no one else but this person, right?
I don't think you want to get involved too much, but let's get involved.
That's right.
It can't be helped.
Let's do it.
Let's have two real entertainers sing Yōkan Fusai.
Please appear!
How is it?
Hello.
I'm wondering what it's like to have two real entertainers.
It's really fun.
That's right.
Why am I playing the husband?
No, the husband is over here.
Why?
Why did you ask me to wear a dress?
What kind of school are you in?
This time it's the other way around.
This program is brought to you by the sponsors you see.
Of course.
I'm going to sing, but I'm going to ask the couple.
Can this guy sing?
Certainly, there is a problem with his singing ability.
If he can't sing, he can't sing.
I don't have that kind of singing ability.
That's right.
You are a person who makes a contribution to Yōkan.
You have to sing mainly.
But is it really a song?
It's a song.
Because there is a band.
We will do a band.
What?
It's live.
Is it different from karaoke?
It's not karaoke, it's a live band.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to play the piano.
Endo is going to play the foot bass.
Wait a minute.
What is a foot bass?
Foot bass.
Is it a foot bass?
It's a foot bass.
Is it really a foot bass?
I'm going to play the foot bass.
And then?
I'm going to play the drums.
The rhythm is the hardest thing to sing.
That's right.
Please.
Are you okay?
Don't think about that kind of thing.
Think about it.
But I'm going to write it down.
I'm going to write down the rhythm.
Have you ever heard of it?
No.
Oh, no?
What are you?
What a rude woman.
It's a song for three brothers.
That's right.
Why don't you listen to it once?
Let's listen to it once.
I can do it live.
Are you ready?
Yo-kan, kan, kan.
Yo-kan is a red color.
It's the same as always.
Yo-kan, kan.
Yo-kan's wife.
The night is beautiful.
Yo-kan.
Oh, my God.
Wait a minute.
Is that a song?
Are you going to sing that?
It's okay if you sing it with soul.
It's like a syncopation.
I don't know.
That's a syncopation.
It's okay.
I'll change it a little bit.
It's only up to number one, but from now on, it's up to number three.
Is it up to number three?
There are other things to dance to.
Is that song up to number three?
Can you do a headspin?
Break dance.
That's right.
That's great.
That's what a trainee should do.
Are you okay with robot dance?
I don't know why this happened.
But I'll ask you this.
Everyone, you should open the New Year's Eve party.
I can't tell you much.
You should open the New Year's Eve party.
Year of the Ox.
Year of the Ox?
You can't open it at the New Year's Eve party?
Year of the Ox.
You can't open it at the New Year's Eve party.
Then what should we start with?
I don't know.
Oh, I see.
The lyrics board.
Is this okay?
Wait, wait, wait.
What is this?
This is why you should go in.
What?
This is you.
That's why Ako-san said,
Youkai and I are good friends.
We always drink water together.
It means you don't need water, right?
No way.
You have to go in here.
You have to go in smoothly so you don't get in the way.
Youkai's husband.
Youkai's wife.
This is EI, right?
Youkai's husband.
You can call her that.
Me?
Yes.
Then you can do a light reaction.
Subway reaction.
Youkai's wife.
Wife.
Then you can do a reaction.
Then you can say,
The night is the year of the ox.
Wait a minute.
What is this?
Isn't it obvious?
The night is the year of the ox.
What kind of face is that?
Wait a minute.
I'm embarrassed after a long time.
No way.
It's okay.
He's the one who says this.
You're a clumsy type.
Why am I clumsy?
I'm not.
Let's start the rehearsal with Matsumoto's instructions.
Let's go.
The night is the year of the ox.
Wait a minute.
Is that song like that?
It's called the night is the ox.
What do you think of this part?
This is the first part.
That's right.
It's like this.
I see.
The night is the year of the ox.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
The drums are wrong.
Really?
No.
The night is the year of the ox.
I'll count the beat.
It's not like this.
Do it more clearly.
It's wrong.
How do you do it?
I don't know how to move forward.
Just make it bigger.
Do it more clearly.
Try it.
It's wrong.
How do you do it?
It's not like this.
Do it more clearly.
It's wrong.
We don't know how to do it.
The piano is the most accurate.
Match the piano.
Let's do it again.
This is a hard work.
The night is the year of the ox.
We are always together.
Wait a minute.
It's hard to see.
Is the piano right?
It's right.
It's good but it's not good.
How do you do it?
Do it more clearly.
It's wrong.
I don't know how to do it.
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's okay.
How do you do it?
It's not good.
It's weird.
I don't know.
It's okay.
I know.
Really?
Yes.
Let's do it.
I don't know how to do it.
It's weird.
I don't know.
The night is the year of the ox.
Okay.
How do you do it?
Beautiful.
This is good.
It's not bad at all.
I don't need a lyrics.
It's okay.
It's good.
I don't know what he says.
Really?
It's okay.
Let's go next.
Let's go to number two.
Number two.
Number two?
You should go.
Number two is Yokan-san and Nakabushi-san.
Yokan's husband is a technician.
That hand and this hand is a bean yokan
Ah, Zen-Gi
What?
Zen-Gi is a bean
I am? Ah, Zen-Gi
The husband of a yokan is the wife of a yokan
The husband is a plum yokan
It means he is sick
Ah, this is ***
Wait a minute
Can this be broadcasted?
It's okay
This kind of...
Wait a minute
I will sing this to the singer that I took from Kouhaku
I will sing this
Let's go to number 2
If you go too far, it will be like
You don't have to look over there
That's right
That's why this *** is not a yokan
That's why when you say ***
At that time, the girl will be like
I will erase it
Erase it
Erase me
With the feeling of erasing
You don't have to say that
But I have to say that
I will say a line
What?
At the end, at the place where you are not sick
You
Yes
I like you
I like you if you think about it
If you die, I will die
That's long
If you think about it, I will die
You just want to say yokan
You don't have to sing
I will sing
Listen to that
Good day, crab balls
How do you sing that?
Then I will go to number 3
I will say number 3
Number 3
Yokan, you are not sick
Always in bed, bug yokan
You are in bed
Yokan's husband, yokan's wife
Today also bug yokan
I don't know if I don't say this
I will say a line and it will be completed
Is that so?
You haven't done anything yet
I don't think you can do this
What are you talking about?
It's a mess
I forgot the melody
Yokan, you are not sick
Always in bed, bug yokan
You are in bed
Yokan's husband, yokan's wife
Tonight also bug yokan
You are in bed
Yokan, you are not sick
Always in bed, bug yokan
Yokan's husband, yokan's wife
Tonight also bug yokan
I like you
Wait a minute
Stop stop
It's a mess
Let's sort it out
The song itself is a mess
I put in a lot of lines
There was quite a bit
What should I do now?
You are always saying ha ha
Shut up
Can you be more firm?
Why are you saying shut up?
You guys don't do that
What should I do?
No
My lyrics
The lyrics are good
It's not good if everyone does it
The sound is not recorded
Do it again
Why is the sound not recorded?
It's not good
Do the bass
Yokan's husband, yokan's wife
Tonight also bug yokan
That's the only thing you remember
You are mistaken
Yokan's husband
I will try it
I will go home
Yokan's husband is a good friend
They always watch together
You are acting
Follow me
I will follow you
Let's go Ako
Let's go
The lyrics are not good
It's getting serious
Are you okay?
I'm okay
It's good
Yokan's husband
It's not good
Wait a minute
I remember it
I tried to remember it
Yamazaki can't play well
So he asked a teacher to help him
Yokan's husband is a good friend
They always watch together
Yokan's husband
I can't get it
Yokan's husband is a good friend
They always watch together
Yamazaki can't play well
I will go home
Are you okay?
Yokan's husband
Why?
The people watching are strange
I'm teaching him
Where?
That's okay
The image
Let him do it
What are you going to do?
I can't play the bass
The drums are strange
I'm doing my best
This is the limit
The best you can do?
When did you start?
Yesterday
Hey
Really?
Sorry
I did it in a hurry
Are you okay?
I'm okay
No one is bad
What are you going to do?
I will do it with Masa
Like I'm teaching
Really?
Can you play it again?
Yokan's husband
Yokan's husband is a good friend
They always watch together
Yokan's husband
Yokan's wife
The night is coming
Akiko is singing
Let him do it
But
It's none of your business
I can't sing because I want to sing
I can't sing
I understand
What?
I don't need you
I will sing in acapella
You can do it later
It's difficult
Is it over?
No more
No more?
No, you
You are not
In this world
Really?
And
And?
Let's do it in acapella
What?
Complete acapella
Let's do it
Yokan's husband
Yokan's husband is a good friend
They always watch together
Yokan's husband
Yokan's wife
The night is coming
Yokan's husband is a technician
Let him do it
Complete acapella
Yokan's husband
Yokan's wife
The night is coming
You are sick
I love you
If you die, I will die too
I will die too
Yokan's husband is a good friend
They always watch together
Yokan's husband
Yokan's wife
The night is coming
You can do it
Good
I think it's good
Is it?
What is it?
Do it again?
Who told you to do it?
You are the producer
Let's do this part
Let's do this part again
That's good
Is it good?
I will do only FUHA
Yes
FUHA
OK
What is this?
When will you finish this?
In 2005
Why?
Will you use this for the next show?
Of course
Really?
I just decided
I will appear in Heihei
Wait a minute
Will you appear in Heihei?
Let's do it together
I have a school
This is the main
You can't appear in Umeyokan
It's OK
I will be in a good mood
Yokan Fusai is the best
Yokan Fusai is finally completed
Yokan
Yokan Fusai is a good friend
Yokan is always together
Yokan's husband
Yokan's wife
Kuri Yokan at night
Yokan's husband is Kuri
Yokan's husband
Yokan's wife
The husband is Umeyokan
It means you are in a good mood
I like you
I like you if you think about it
If you die, I will die too
If you think about it, I will die too
Good day, KANITAMA
Yokan Fusai is the best
Yokan is always together
Yokan's husband
Yokan's wife
Kuri Yokan at night