This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Excuse me.
Here you are.
All right.
It was hard, wasn't it?
Hamada?
Mr. Hamada.
What?
Why suddenly?
It was hard.
Well, I was pretty bad.
When you were a student?
I was boxing.
What?
Is it your first time?
Yes.
I started to like boxing.
What?
Is it your first time?
That's amazing.
You've been boxing for a long time, haven't you?
Is it your first time?
That's right.
I started to like boxing.
But I didn't practice properly.
You didn't?
I didn't.
I see.
Well, I hit my body.
You hit your body?
I hit my body.
I hit my body during practice.
You hit your body during practice.
My grandfather said,
Hit your body.
I don't understand it at all.
Who is your grandfather?
My opponent was strong.
I hit him a lot.
Who did you hit?
The champion.
The champion?
Did you go that far?
Is it a world championship?
What?
Is the champion different?
It's different.
I don't know.
The champion.
He was very strong.
I was beaten up.
What happened?
Did I lose?
I don't know.
I was beaten up.
I remember you were saying,
Adrian!
After the game.
What?
What is that?
What's his name?
At that time,
You were in the show.
That's right.
What is Adrian?
What do you mean?
This is the first time I've heard of it.
I don't want to do it anymore.
You've already quit?
Just once?
No, no, I don't want to talk about this anymore.
I see.
It was hard. I didn't think I'd be talking about this.
There's a lot of things we don't know.
We've never heard of it before.
That's true.
Please, I'm begging you.
I don't want to talk about this anymore.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Ready, set, go.
Thank goodness.
What's wrong?
Was it hard?
It was.
There's one thing I don't want to talk about.
Really?
Yes.
I've already said it, so you should say it too.
I don't think you'll believe me, but please listen to half of what I have to say.
No, no, no.
I'll listen.
I believe you.
I believe what Endo has to say.
About being bullied by a monkey.
What?
You were bullied by a monkey?
What do you mean?
I don't know.
I believe you, but...
I had to jump out of the earth.
Jump out of the earth?
It's really sudden, but the spaceship broke down on the way.
The spaceship you're on?
The spaceship I'm on.
Why?
There was an engine trouble or something.
That's amazing.
You were saved?
Yes.
It started from here.
I jumped out of the earth.
That's amazing.
That's where the monkey bullying started.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
Why?
That's where the monkey bullying started.
Why can't I be bullied by a monkey?
I don't think you'll believe me, but humans control the earth.
The monkeys control the earth.
Really?
There was a goddess of freedom.
In America?
Yes.
There was the earth here.
That's what I felt.
There are so many things.
It was normal.
It was good that you came back.
Thank you.
What do you mean?
There are a lot of things I don't understand.
But it's hard to remember the old days.
That's right.
It's a short story.
Cheers.
You're not talking.
I'm not going to say it now.
I'm Joe.
What?
That's it?
I heard you were boxing.
Yes.
I used to do it, too.
Really?
I don't want to say it.
Why?
What made you do it?
An old man...
Well, how should I put it?
He had an iPad.
He said, you're an artist.
You should come to the match.
I was surprised.
Really?
I was happy.
I went to the match.
There was a girl.
I wonder if there was a girl.
What are you talking about?
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's an old story.
I'm not talking about a girl.
You're talking about Morimaru.
My opponent was a foreigner.
He was a hose mendoza.
He was the last one.
He was in front of me.
I was shouting.
His iPad said,
Stand up.
I was sitting.
I was dancing.
Stand up.
Yes.
I did my best.
I died at the end.
What do you mean by that?
As a boxer.
I died at the end.
I turned white.
What happened?
He was very angry.
I didn't want to remember it.
What happened to you today?
It was a long time ago.
I remember it.
I love you.
I want to hear your story.
Yes.
You've been through a lot of things.
I heard that you don't have a voice.
I've never heard of you when you were a kid.
I've never heard of you.
When I was a kid,
I was taken to a temple.
Because you were a bad kid.
The big guy at the time was a bad guy.
I don't understand at all.
Who?
When you were a kid.
I don't understand at all.
There's a bridge.
A bridge.
Yes.
At the bridge.
There's a sign that says,
Don't cross this bridge.
I don't like it.
But you did cross it.
There's a sign that says,
Don't cross this bridge.
But you did cross it.
I don't like it.
I was walking in the middle of the bridge.
I understood the message I was trying to say.
When I was a kid,
I was a tough guy.
A little bit.
I had a hard time.
I did it quite often.
You did.
I did.
It was hard.
No, but if you listen to the old stories, it's fun.
So that's how it was.
Well, well.
I don't know if you hated it or not.
I'll just say something.
On the contrary.
It's a lie.
It's okay.
My memories.
Why?
I can't do it.
It's not easy.
You know what?
I was wearing an ice hockey mask.
Who?
Me, me, me.
When you were a kid?
No, not when I was a kid.
Recently.
Recently?
Why?
What are you talking about?
I was so excited.
I was wearing an ice hockey mask.
And I was killing people with a sickle.
Why?
You can't get tired of that.
Who?
People who were already there, people who were coming to stay.
Where?
It was last month, or actually, Friday the 13th.
Were you doing it?
Friday the 13th.
Scary.
I'm scared.
I was definitely coming to stay.
I don't like it at all.
It's scary.
It's really scary.
Tanaka, have you ever told me that you're not interested in baseball?
That's right.
What do you mean?
When it comes to baseball, there's something like Endo.
I've never heard of it.
Endo has a strong image of baseball, so it's hard to say that he was hiding it.
I know, I know.
My dad really loves baseball.
It's Sparta.
I don't like it anymore.
I'll tell you.
When I told him, he turned the table over.
He's a scary old man.
He said, I'm scared.
What did he say?
It's a spring.
A spring?
He had a spring attached to his whole body.
Why?
So that he could throw a fast ball.
I see.
He said something like, put on your hand and do it.
What?
You can't say that.
He didn't say anything.
My sister was worried about me.
But she just looked at me.
She didn't say anything?
She didn't say anything.
She's a weak sister.
She said no.
And then I joined the Giants.
What?
Really?
That's amazing.
I don't know much about it.
I didn't know at all.
There was a result of training.
He threw a fast ball.
A fast ball?
A fast ball that disappeared.
Disappeared?
What disappeared?
It just disappeared.
Everyone, like Bang-kun.
Who is Bang-kun?
He's a catcher.
Hanagata.
Who is Hanagata?
Who?
He was in the Tigers draft.
I didn't know that.
You should have seen him.
I didn't know.
He had bangs.
Bangs?
Bangs.
He had bangs.
How did the ball disappear?
He spread his arms.
He put his hands on it.
He jumped.
That was Bang-ba-bang.
That's not right.
I heard it for the first time.
If I had a chance.
I want to hear it again.
You want to hear it again?
Matsumoto-san.
How was it?
When you were young.
Well.
This story.
I don't know if it's a story on TV.
Please let us hear it.
That's right.
Well.
I was born in a hospital.
I wasn't born in Samba-san.
You were born at home?
Well, I was born at home.
I'm still Teio Sekkai.
But I was born in Araimo.
I was more Arai Teio Sekkai.
I was very Arai.
You were more Arai Teio Sekkai.
Was it like that?
I don't believe it.
I believe in all kinds of memories.
Well.
I was protected by something like a fruit.
What were you protecting?
I don't know.
What are you saying?
To put it simply.
It was like an abandoned child.
I was put in a fruit-like thing.
I was washed away by the river.
I thought it was a terrible parent.
My grandmother picked it up in the red valley.
Now that I think about it.
I think it's a bad thing.
I lived with my grandfather.
What was my grandmother doing?
She was washing clothes in the river.
When I think about it, it's like being homeless.
Well.
I think so.
On the contrary.
After all, it's hard to be a fan of the old days.
Gaki Gaki-kun Gaki Gaki-kun Gaki Gaki-kun Gaki Gaki-kun Gari Gari-kun
I don't have anything to say.
Mr. Tama has made it clear that he will be punished.
The staff is still laughing.
Really?
I think it will start soon.
What are you doing?
Well.
Please go on a trip for a while.
I'm sorry.
I'll apologize twice.
I don't know much about the trip.
I'll be back in February.
It's okay.
No, no, no.
I'm not a radio station.
You've been talking for so long.
It's okay.
I'm really sorry.
I'll apologize three times.
I've always wanted to say this.
If there's a good place.
I always forgot something.
I see.
I remembered today.
Please say it.
There's something I'm angry about.
Please.
For example, when you want to find out the number of the store.
Yes.
You call.
For example.
Yes.
I'm looking for it myself.
Well, you're looking for it yourself.
Oh, that's fine.
Yes, yes, yes.
Do you know how much it costs?
Of course.
This.
Surprisingly, everyone doesn't know.
Yes.
It costs 150 yen.
Everyone has to be more angry about this.
To that old woman.
What's your voice?
And this is a machine.
It costs 150 yen.
Did you know?
Yes, yes, yes.
Most people don't know.
Yes, yes.
You didn't know, did you?
If you ask twice, it's 300 yen.
If you ask three times, it's 450 yen.
It's a bye-bye game.
I'm crying at the bye-bye game.
I think so.
Yes.
You've been in downtown for more than 20 years.
Right?
Yes.
You've been hitting my head 40,000 times.
Well, I don't know.
I'm going to take 150 yen from you next year.
I'm sorry.
It's a bad story.
150 yen.
Yes.
I think I can take it.
Why?
This is obviously an obstacle.
Because you hit me?
Well, the taste is a little...
You're lying.
That's not true.
I know it's sweet and sour, but it's sweet and sour.
You don't have to know that much.
Sweet and sour is important.
Sweet.
Sour.
I don't know.
I don't care.
I don't care at all.
You don't have to eat that much.
It's sweet and sour.
I don't eat that much.
Rather than that...
It's better to say that 150 yen is strange.
150 yen is amazing.
I don't think so.
This is all I have.
Why does it take so much money just to tell me your phone number?
It's impossible.
I wonder if you can't do that in the second half of the show.
What do you mean? I don't understand.
Ask the old lady and tell her to wait a moment.
Wait a moment?
In the second half...
It changes to tape, right?
It changes.
It's not tape, is it?
It's not tape.
It's not tape?
It's more like a computer.
Ask her to wait a moment.
You're recording right now.
That's strange.
It's not tape.
It's connected to a line.
It's connected to something.
When a voice comes out, it's connected to a line.
When I press the button, a voice comes out.
What are you imagining?
There's something like Naniku's food.
I wonder if there is.
There's something like that.
What?
That's amazing.
What are you doing?
It's like a stick.
When I press the button...
What's going on?
That's amazing.
It's like a stick.
Are you okay?
You have plenty of time.
I'm not saying that.
I'm just asking if it's okay to use tape from the beginning.
If I say it simply.
There's no tape at the beginning.
What is it?
Tape, tape.
It's like you're stuck.
I'm saying tape.
What is tape?
Shut up.
Yes, 150 yen.