Gakki no Tsukai, the usual Gakuhyaku scenery
I went to have a drink yesterday
Good morning
I'm a little worried today
What room is it?
Please come in
Busy
It's just a little
Do you have a bento?
You have to drink the bento staff
Don't say that here
Hamada said to eat a bento
I'm sorry
You're a bad guy
What
Why are you saying that?
I'm a senior
I'm angry
What are you angry about?
Why are you saying that?
Various human shapes are on the stage of the entertainment world
Jealousy, jealousy, confrontation
Decorate the backstage of the entertainer
Yamazaki Hosei, the fastest to cut off in the entertainment world
Jimmy Onishi, who doesn't know what's scary when it's cut
Inside the power to leave a deep impression on the back of this smile
Now, the first in a lifetime
The battle of human rights in the entertainment world
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching
What is it?
It's natural
I'm not natural
Are you really calculating?
What
Do you think about the story even when you're alone?
Why are you doing that?
What are you doing?
Don't put your hand out
Wait a minute
What did you do?
Stop it
Don't put your hand out
What are you doing?
What is this?
Don't put your hand out
It's useless
Stop it
What do you mean?
Wait a minute
Which one is faster?
Which one will you follow?
We're all in the same company
It may be strange, but I'm a senior
Don't do that
You have to talk to me properly
Why?
I don't recognize you
If you know, tell me
Do you recognize me?
I recognize you
What?
I recognize you, so you should recognize me too
I recognize you because you're a senior
If you have a problem with me, I'll solve it
Don't say that
I've been watching you for a long time
I think you have the final power
It's okay
Let's see
Let's see which one can do it
You're strong
You can drink goldfish
Hey
You can drink it
Go into the bath
What
Ichiro
Yamazaki!
What are you doing?
He's drinking salt water.
Yamazaki!
Huh?
What are you doing?
You're spilling water.
It's really small.
What are you doing?
It's hot!
It's like he's going to give birth.
You can't do that.
If it's Yamazaki, I can drink it all at once.
What are you talking about?
My Jimmy can drink it all at once.
Yamazaki, are you crying?
No, I'm not.
I hate milk.
Let's go!
Ready...
Start!
It's hot!
Can you win?
I can't drink it.
Yamazaki, what's with your left hand?
It's like he's going to give birth.
I don't like it.
I don't like it either.
What are you talking about?
Can you do it?
I can't.
I can't do it.
If you want to do it, you can do it.
I can do it.
I can't.
My Yamazaki is good at...
Kawa-ra-wari!
What?
What are you talking about?
Didn't you know?
My Jimmy can do it.
I can't do it.
My Jimmy is sweating.
Yamazaki!
In this program, there are two episodes.
We'll see how today's guests feel.
Today's guests are very strict.
You guys win or we win.
It's a short time, but thank you for watching.
What did you say?
My last words.
You're so rude.
What?
What is that?
I can't talk.
What is this?
It's a salon pass.
I don't know if it's a salon pass.
What is this?
What?
You have to put it on.
I can't put it on.
I put it on here.
Why?
If it's hard, my head hurts.
You have to put it on before the show.
How many times have you been a strict guest?
It depends on the guest.
If I take it off, it hurts.
You have a hole.
You don't talk.
This is not a hole.
What is this?
You can contact me anytime.
What kind of contact?
Who contacted you?
I received it.
Then take it out more.
It's not two.
Wait a minute.
It's about eight.
The real one is one.
There's nothing else.
It's a movie.
You're rude.
Don't talk about money.
Everyone knows that you have money.
You told me.
You're not making money.
I'm not making money.
I'm not making money at all.
Everyone is cheating.
I'm just explaining.
I'm just being honest.
Why did you get a shoulder massage?
I'm a movie star.
What do you mean?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I said that I was a movie star.
I'm not doing anything.
I know that.
I don't think I'm losing to Yoshiko Mita.
That's what I said.
No, no, no.
I said that this is not good.
But how can I save money?
For example, let's say a thief comes in.
He took a lot of money.
But the tax money doesn't come in.
That doesn't matter.
But it's strange.
He took the money.
He doesn't have money, so he can't be paid.
He can't do anything about it.
For example, I'm walking down the street.
Let's say I was robbed on Sunday or something.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let's stop Sunday for now.
Let's go somewhere nice.
I don't care.
He's a bad junior high school student.
He's in third grade.
Are you talking about junior high school students?
He's in third grade of junior high school.
He's in the military school tomorrow morning.
Stop laughing like an old lady.
He's surrounded by such a guy.
That's scary.
You have money too.
What money?
No, no, no, it's money, it's money.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's all square.
I can see it now.
I can't tell with the silhouette.
It's all in the air.
What are you talking about?
I'm getting dizzy.
It's all in the air.
So if you take all of it,
and if you say you're going to make money,
I can't do anything about it.
But I get my taxes, right?
That's true.
That's weird.
It's definitely weird.
First of all,
why do you have to take half of it?
Explain it to me.
Well, if you say that,
it's like that.
It's like that.
I don't have any money.
People say I have a lot of money,
but I don't have any money at all.
I have a one-week break now,
so I'm going to use that
to buy Dunkin' Donuts or something.
Do you get it?
I'm going to take these guys,
and I'm going to show them my heart.
Right?
You're going to be in trouble if you go.
Which one are you going to choose?
Are you going to do it like that?
I'll do it.
But really,
it's not as much as you think.
But more than half of it
is going to be taken away.
But if it's like this,
if it's number one next year,
I'll take it.
Really.
Your target isn't even in the top 20.
Oh, really?
Your target is already out of the top 20?
It's already out.
I'm going to be number one.
Really?
I'm going to take out Yoshiko Mita.
I didn't do anything to that woman.
That's what I'm saying.
I said I shouldn't do it.
You tricked me.
But really,
I don't have any money, so...
So...
Umm...
Oh, right.
What? What?
Who are you talking to?
What are you doing?
Give me back my 3,000 yen.
I said I don't need it.
It's okay. You don't need it, so give me back my 3,000 yen.
I don't need it.
3,000 yen doesn't hurt that much for you.
You don't need it either.
But give it back to me.
I don't need it.
I'll give you 5,000 yen, so give me back my 3,000 yen.
Is that okay?
I've been saying this for five years.
This is the end, right?
Give me back my 3,000 yen.
I'm serious.
Why are you so angry?
I said I don't need it.
Where are you going?
Give me your wallet.
Seriously.
I don't have any money in my wallet.
It's okay. You can bring it to me.
You have 3,000 yen, right?
I wonder if I have it.
But I won't give it back to you.
I won't give it back to you.
In Nagasaki, when I went to buy clothes with you,
you said you wanted a T-shirt.
But you said you didn't have any money,
so you held your head up at the emergency stairs and did this.
No, no.
That was when I was in Kyoto Kage.
Kyoto Kage is different.
I lent you money at that time, so please give it back to me.
No.
When I was in Kyoto Kage, I lent it to you.
I lent it to you.
I don't know anyone.
It's okay. You have 3,000 yen.
No, no.
Give it back to me.
I'll give it back to you.
No, no.
Wait a minute.
Why didn't you take my money?
It's really 3,000 yen.
Well, okay, okay,
tell me then.
3,000 yen, really...
It's okay if it's not that much,
you have exactly the same amount as 4,000 yen.
But this, I don't need it anymore.
Oh, I see.
The same amount as 4,000 yen?
Thank you very much.
You're exactly what I need.
I'm going to take this back.
What are you doing with the money?
I'll take it back.
No, I'm serious.
I'll take this back.
I'll take it back.
I'm not going to do it again.
No, I'm serious.
I have a lot of other juice.
I'm the one who said that.
When I was in junior high school, I was angry with you twice.
Isn't it worth about 100 yen?
That's amazing.
You're a fool.
If it was 100 yen at that time, it would be amazing.
I'll take this back.
Isn't that printing strange?
Printing is strange.
I'll take this back.
I have a lot of money.
I'll give you 100,000 yen if you don't take it back.
You don't have it, do you?
I think I have it.
You don't have it.
I'll give you 100,000 yen if you don't take it back.
Where's my money?
Give it back to me.
You can't just give me 3,000 yen.
Why do you care so much about 3,000 yen?
Where's my money?
I'll take this.
Which one?
This one.
I have a lot of money.
I missed this.
I have this all the time.
You're a fool.
Are you a child?
My hands are full of your saliva.
I have 7,000 yen, so give me back 10,000 yen.
You don't have it, do you?
I only have 1,000 yen.
I don't have money.
OK.
I can feel good with this.
Take it to me.
I found a video of a child using it 4 years ago and watched it for 6 hours.
Then I realized that the attitude of the two of you is completely different from 4 years ago and now.
I don't think so.
I wonder if the audience thinks so, too.
I'm not talking about you.
I'm serious.
I'm not modest at all.
The eyes of the world are wrong.
I'm not the kind of person you think I am.
It's different.
What's different?
When I go home, I don't go straight home.
I go to a child care center.
I wear an umbrella when it rains.
I'm the kind of person who does that.
I don't have money.
I have a license.
What kind of license?
I don't have a license.
It's a matter of feeling.
I have a kind license.
Are you stupid?
It's a matter of feeling.
What kind of license do I have?
Is it your kind of license?
It's not my kind of license.
It's different.
What are you talking about?
It's my kind of license.
It's your kind of license.
I just want to say it because it feels good.
You said the same thing today.
Why did you say it twice?
I thought about it.
You said it twice because it felt good.
Are you stupid?
It's a kind of license.
I'm laughing, but I'll tell you when I get home.
You want to say it now, don't you?
It's a kind of license.
You should definitely say it when you get home.
What do you want to say?
It's a kind of license.
I'm looking forward to it.
Can you pierce this toothpick through here?
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.