Chikichiki! GENERATION OMAE SOU-CHAN-KA GRAND PRIX!
Thank you for your hard work.
This is the 9th episode of OMAE SOU-CHAN-KA GRAND PRIX.
Today's guests are lucky.
Let's go!
Who will give me the answer?
These people!
First of all, I'd like to introduce Mr. Makoto Otake!
Thank you!
I didn't think you guys were human beings.
Otodari Kano Tenmei!
It's been a while since I've seen you.
That's right.
How are you doing?
I'm doing fine.
You've been on a lot of shows lately.
I've done a lot of shows.
Thank you for coming!
It's been a while since I've seen you.
It's been a while.
You should have called me.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
As usual, I'm in the city and doing an interview.
The person who gets the answer is the winner of the grand prix.
Let's get started!
The first question is...
You were asked to go buy cherries, right?
This is Dan-Yu.
Dan-Yu?
Then it's not him.
Who is it?
Makihara.
He's definitely going to drive.
Even if you say he's definitely going to drive...
We're interviewing 17 student salarymen.
Please show us the clip.
This is what the person who interviewed me said.
I don't know if he knows or not.
He's being bullied.
That's a given.
What do you mean by a given?
It's his job to drive.
He's being used by Hiromi to drive.
Hiromi is Dan-Yu.
That's the worst.
It's Dan-Yu.
I'll just say he's young.
It's not Morishige.
He's saying he's young.
If you say Dan-Yu, it's definitely Morishige.
Let's go.
First, Otake.
He's definitely going to drive.
He's going to drive in a commercial.
Tenmei.
Is he Issei Ishida?
Issei.
Matsumoto.
I'm Abe Hiroo.
He's like this.
Abe.
The one who drives a beer?
I don't know.
Takeda Shinji.
Issei Ishida.
Toshiaki Karasawa.
Kasedaishi.
He looks weak.
Sanoshiro.
Karasawa.
Kimura Kazuya.
He looks weak.
Takeda Shinji.
Naoki Kosaka.
He looks kind, so he's going to be taken in.
Issei Ishida.
Karasawa.
Toshiaki Karasawa.
Everyone is wrong.
I thought it was the answer.
The next one is...
This one.
You're having sex without kissing.
Wait a minute.
Who is this?
You're a potato.
Who came up with this?
You're a famous woman who seems to be having sex without kissing.
That's true.
You don't have any right or wrong.
You're not being taken in by a man.
Who was it?
What?
You're having sex without kissing.
No, no, no.
It's you.
It took me about two hours to get ready.
You're having sex without kissing.
Here you go.
Who's being taken in when you're naked?
Aren't you running away?
No.
It's easy.
You're not running away.
Stop it.
Rewrite it.
What should I do?
I'm going home.
You're running away.
No, I'm not.
I'm sorry.
You can run away, but you don't have to show it.
Let's go, Otake.
I think this is good.
I'm not Otake.
I'm a critic of So-chan and the Grand Prix.
I'm the closest woman to you.
That's not good.
Homo is here to shop.
I think it's good.
Otake.
I think it's a shopper.
I think it's good.
Otake.
That's ***.
What?
Tenmei.
I'm not a shopper.
***
I see.
Matsumoto.
I don't know what to write.
Are you running away?
I'm not running away.
Let's see.
***
I'm not running away.
I'm Otako.
Kaga Mariko.
***
Natsuki Okamoto.
Only your body?
Yes.
Kisamoto.
Natsuki Okamoto.
***
Akiko Matsumoto.
Hiroko Moriguchi.
***
Masami Kisamoto.
Thank you.
***
I'm using this for the first time.
I shouldn't be so happy when I think about it.
Stand up.
I've never done it before.
This is the last question.
The last question is the reverse pattern.
First, let's see who the Grand Prix is.
Please answer the question.
***
Hitajima Saburo.
What is ***?
***
It's a young person.
What do you call young people?
Young people who have arms and legs and move
I don't know
Do you have a hint?
A hint?
He's talking about a certain person
You're playing around in Nagoya, right?
You're still like this
I'm still here so don't leave me
I'm playing with Oda Yuji
Please write it
I don't think this is a common thing
Let's start with Mr.Otake
You!
Could it be?
Yes
From XX
Who told you to read it?
Who told you to read it so slowly?
Could it be that XX is bigger than XX?
I see
You're still like this
If it's about a racer, it's a racer
It's like a raccoon
You're playing around in front of people
But you're really a playboy
There's no matcha
That's a weird story too
Why is it a weird story?
If I were to use this as a reference
You're only playing with the women that Matsumoto played with
That has nothing to do with Oda Yuji
Are you playing with Oda Yuji too?
That's weird
The women you played with are playing with Kurajima Samuro
That's not true
Let's watch the video
Who doesn't like downtown?
Oda Yuji
You don't like downtown?
That's the problem
The winner is Oda Yuji
Everyone is wrong
I didn't have a matcha in it
I'm tired of being chased
You're being chased
I'm being chased
I'm being chased because I'm being chased
I'm not being chased
This case is really weird
What's weird?
And...
I'm not talking about anything.
It's not connected.
Why would you say that?
No, no, no.
So...
They're denying it.
I'm denying it, too.
But the proof is in the photo.
Why are you so desperate?
No, no, no.
I'm just saying it because I can't say it in a big way.
If there's a photo or something,
I still know.
There's no photo.
You don't know because you say that.
No, no, no.
What's with that kid?
You're saying that because there's no photo.
Just move.
No, no, no.
It's not cold.
It's not cold at all.
Taka-chan!
You!
It's not cold.
It's not cold, but you're saying it's cold.
That's not good.
I thought it was cold.
It's not cold at all.
The camera's out of focus.
I'll laugh at anything.
Especially the guest of the show.
That's true.
But what is it?
What have you been up to lately?
But it's that.
It's that on this show.
I'm going to release the record of Geisha Girls in Japan.
Oh, I see.
That's good.
Are you going to buy it?
The guy who's here is going to buy it.
No, but...
Are you going to be on a singing show?
A singing show?
But I don't have one right now.
You don't have one, do you?
Is it that?
Music Station?
The TV station?
The TV station's Music Station.
But Gyo-san, I don't know what you're talking about.
It's the same as the lyrics.
You're such a bad singer, Tamori-san.
Who said that?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Did you say ta?
Ta?
That's what I'm saying.
No, no, no, no.
Are you going to write a letter?
Matsumoto-san, when a big, strong-looking person comes to you,
or when you're about to get beaten up,
you say, I'll do it if you come to me next time.
Or, I won't be quiet if you come to me next time.
You say that a lot.
Matsumoto-san is really strong, isn't he?
Another one like that.
Which one is stronger, Hama-chan or Matsumoto-chan?
I see.
No, but this is that.
You...
What she's saying is right.
I've never seen her move.
But,
the question is, which one is stronger, Hama-chan or Matsumoto-chan?
Right?
You're like that.
No, I'm not.
You're strong.
You're unarmed.
Why am I unarmed?
You're late in time.
I'm late in time?
You're acting as a clumsy, clumsy man.
I'm not acting?
You're like, what?
I'm a man.
I'm saying I'm a man.
I'm always saying that.
What are you saying?
You're like that.
I'm not saying anything.
Your fashion is like a man.
What?
You're like a rice paddy.
A rice paddy is your strength.
You're like that.
I don't know.
You're like a fish.
If you're grilled, it's good.
You don't need any seasoning.
You're a man of the sea.
You say things like that.
I'm not saying anything.
You never say things like that.
It's just an episode.
What?
It's not an episode.
But you're sending out messages like that.
I'm not sending out messages.
It's not like that.
You've been saying that you're going to apologize for the yakuza.
You're making me look like a man.
What are you trying to say?
Are you jealous?
It's not like that.
I don't want to be looked down on.
I want to be strong.
I want to say it out loud.
I don't think so.
It's not a club.
I don't want to be looked down on.
See?
That's all.
You don't want to be looked down on.
But I don't care about that at work.
It's not like that.
Why?
If you look at downtown, most people think that Hamada is stronger.
But in reality, you don't know until you think about it.
Yes, I understand.
Did you do any sports?
I did kendo for a year when I was in high school.
Kendo?
I did judo.
Only Matsumoto's technique.
What do you mean technique?
If you use Matsumoto's technique, you can eat as much rice as you want.
I don't care.
I'm not weak at all.
If you eat as much rice as you want, you can eat as much rice as you want.
Matsumoto's technique means that you can eat as much rice as you want.
That's how good it is.
Who said that?
I don't care.
Can I use your technique?
Don't say such things.
It's okay.
Do you know how many people use your technique?
I don't know.
How many people?
Kami shihō gatame.
Kami shihō gatame doesn't mean that you can use your technique.
You can use your technique.
It means you enjoy eating.
I'm asking you to use your technique.
Don't you understand?
If you hurt your partner, who will be happy?
It's okay.
If you say so, I won't hurt you.
Before you fall?
Yes.
You'll fall soon.
Will I fall?
You'll fall.
You'll fall and lose consciousness for a while.
Really?
Yes.
I have to do it hard.
I'll give you a sign before you fall.
Really?
Yes.
Please.
What should I do?
What do you mean?
Can I stand here?
Please tell me what you want me to do.
What do you want me to do?
Please tell me.
Please tell me what you want me to do.
Well...
Koso-de tsuri.
Koso-de tsuri?
Koso-de tsuri from Tsuriyashi.
Koso-de?
From Tsuyasu to Koso-de tsuri?
What do you want me to do?
I don't know.
Can I stand here?
I'll give you a sign.
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't do it hard.
I have to hold it here.
I know that.
Don't do it hard.
It hurts.
Koso-de tsuri.
Please.
Don't do it hard.
I told you you shouldn't do it hard.
You have to leave your body to do it.
I was talking.
You were falling for a moment.
It's bad.
I woke you up.
I didn't know for a moment.
It's bad.
It's a little bit.
It's forbidden here.
Because it's sweet.
Because it's sweet?
It's too sweet.
This is...
In the past, you dropped it many times.
I dropped it.
The other day, I went to see the UWF.
It's a bad thing.
It's forbidden.
Love is not a fun thing.
It's a painful thing.
How can a man cheat on his love?
What kind of theory is that?
You know.
I think it's okay to get married.
Who?
Me.
It's okay to get married.
No.
Don't say it in a small voice.
I don't think it's okay to play with other women after marriage.
Don't say such a beautiful thing.
If you do it, you will do it.
I'm scared.
I'm not saying scary things.
Adults say I'm bald.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.