High Tension! The Best Ten!
Hello everyone! Good evening!
Long time no see!
That's right!
Ah, that's right! Long time no see!
Long time no see!
Ah, you're so dirty!
What are you talking about?
I'm really beautiful!
I was like that yesterday too!
Yes!
Let's start right away!
I will announce the rankings!
First of all, this week's 10th place is...
24 points!
Electric Illumination!
Kogoriko Tamakorouki!
Congratulations!
Yes!
The difference is 10,000 years!
10,000 years!
That's amazing!
I have to work a little harder!
Well, the studio's temperature hasn't warmed up at all, but...
Please raise it!
Please leave it to me!
Eh?
Please take it!
Last!
Please take care of me!
Yes!
Then let's go!
This week's 10th place!
Kogoriko Tamakorouki!
Electric Illumination!
Hora!
Yes, take care!
Eh?
Roden!
Teiki!
Yes, Teiki!
It's leaking!
Yes!
Gari!
Gari gari gari gari!
Electric!
Yes, thank you very much!
That guy hasn't changed much since last year!
That's right!
He always looks like a brain!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Then let's go!
That's right!
This week's 9th place is...
43 points!
Save the Earth!
Karateka Yabetaro!
Please give him a round of applause!
He's Yabe...
Yes!
It's my first time too!
Yes, it's your first time too!
Nice to meet you!
Yabe-san, how old are you?
I'm 25 years old.
25 years old!
Don't touch me like that!
You're the one who's talking!
How is it?
It's like seeing your senpai sliding around!
Right?
To be honest, I'm starting to feel confident!
That's right!
When I see that...
I'm like, is this really okay?
Yabe-san, please give him a round of applause!
Ah, that's right!
Are you okay?
Let's go! This week's 9th place!
Save the Earth with Karateka Yabetaro!
Hey, Kannon! Hey, Kannon! Hey, Kannon! Hey, Kannon! Hey, Kannon! Really, Kannon! Really, Kannon! Really, Kannon!
Thank you very much!
Well, it's better than 10th place.
Let's go to 10th place!
Let's go!
This week's 8th place goes to...
51 points!
The men who became the wind, Osaru!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Today, we have important news from our manager, Osaru-san.
What is it?
Osaru-san, since April, you were told that the new regular was decided, right?
Yes, I was told.
Actually, the other day, it was changed to Sakamoto-chan, so I'm sorry.
Now, let's raise the tension!
I want you to overcome this with high tension.
I thought I finally got in.
Are you still going to use Sakamoto-chan?
It's the same, the manager.
Is that so?
My eyes are dead.
It's still the same, from the beginning.
Then, let's go to 3rd place!
I understand.
I should have said it before doing it.
This week's 8th place goes to...
The men who became the wind, Keirin!
There's no bridge!
You're still blue, huh.
Don't turn around!
You want to beat me?
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
As expected, Sarasai-san's sense of rhythm is amazing.
Then, let's continue.
This week's seventh place is...
The winner is...
Congratulations, Izurin Okada!
Please come over here!
Wow, Izurin-san!
This is humorous.
This is your first appearance.
It's my first appearance and I'm seventh place, so this is a big deal.
Thank you very much.
Izurin-san, this is your first appearance.
I heard you have a special skill using your tongue.
Oh my, that's good.
It's called high-speed
That's a good thing.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll show you.
Huh?
You're going to do it separately?
Separately?
I can do it with anyone!
Izurin-san, please come over here.
This is your first appearance.
Then, this week's seventh place is...
Izurin Okada's...
Nishinippori no Yoru!
Monday Choice! Monday Choice!
Finger Vibe!
Nishinippori! Nishinippori!
Stalker? Stalker? Stalker?
Stalker? Stalker?
Look! Look! Look!
Yosemite Park! Yosemite Park!
Y-O-S-E-M-I-T-E
Yosemite! Yosemite!
Y-O-K-O-M-I-T-E
Yoko-Mite!
Thank you very much!
That was great.
I'm so excited that I'm going to do it separately.
You're going to do it separately, right?
Then, let's take him!
The sixth place goes to...
113 points!
Noboshiku Kangen Ram!
Hamewari Keshitai Miyasako Hiroyuki!
Thank you very much!
He's got such a wide body.
Miyasako-san, by the way, Christmas is a family service, right?
That's right.
I spent Christmas with my family.
I heard you went to buy a lot of toys.
Toys for the house.
Oh, really?
You bought a lot of toys for your children.
I often forgot toys in my apartment.
I see.
Can you say something?
He's crazy.
Thank you very much!
I'm so excited.
Let's go!
The sixth place goes to...
Hamewari Keshitai Miyasako Hiroyuki!
Noboshiku Kangen Ram!
Gorilla!
Run!
It feels good!
You're lying!
It doesn't feel good!
Your arms are like this!
Oh, I see.
Thank you very much!
During that short time, I could see you wavering.
Yabe-kun probably doesn't laugh much.
What do you think, Yabe-kun?
What do you think?
I wonder if it's like this.
Everyone, the fifth place goes to...
137, Iipara Fukawa Ryo!
Congratulations!
Fukawa-san, do you remember last time?
Last time it was around here.
What?
Around here.
Then just talk normally.
It's hard to overcome the five walls.
I see.
It's difficult.
Fukawa-san, we have a special guest today.
Please welcome!
What?
Why?
How are you?
If you have energy, you can do it many times.
If you have energy, you can be a great high tension entertainer.
Fukawa!
Don't be a fool.
Relax your stomach and pull your chin.
How was it? Did you have energy?
Yes, thank you.
Don't say that if you don't have energy.
I understand.
Don't make a scene where I come out.
You can make a scene.
Fukawa-kun!
Let's do our best!
This week's 5th place is Fukawa!
I don't want to say this, but...
Recently, people are saying that you can take a video or a photo.
I don't care about that. Just break the last one of the battery.
Break it!
Break it here!
Don't be a fool!
You'll be a guide until the end.
If the screen is clean or the sound is clear.
I don't care!
Break it here!
Hey, if it's a download or a thumbnail.
I don't care!
Break it here!
And...
Don't be a fool!
Yes, thank you very much!
There was one more, right?
I'm sorry.
Fukawa-san, do you want to sit down?
If you can sit down, please sit down.
Next, Sakoji's number one is...
148 points!
Do as you please!
Mugendai Amiwari Kestai Hotarakon!
Thank you very much!
Wonderful!
This is wonderful!
Are you ready?
It's getting better, isn't it?
It wasn't good at all last time.
Ah, is that so?
But you can come this far.
That's right.
But it's powerful.
It's better than last time, this time.
That's a matter of course.
I see.
Then, please!
Thank you very much!
Everyone's attitude is...
Why do you want to enter from the other side?
Even if you enter from the other side, it will be the same as before, right?
Then, let's go.
This week's number four is...
Amiwari Kestai Hotarakon!
Do as you please! Mugendai!
Come on, beard!
Let's go!
It's a smash!
A beard smash!
Come on, beard, come on!
Come on, beard, beard!
Come on, beard!
Come on! Smash it!
Two at infinity!
What?
Thank you very much!
This is...
But it's wonderful!
Yes, yes, yes.
The tension is quite high.
That's right.
Is that tension?
I don't think you're underestimating me.
I'm doing it seriously.
I'll do it like this.
What is this?
What?
Let's go!
This week's 3rd place is...
171 points!
To the heart of the earth!
Kogoriko, Endo Shouzo!
Congratulations!
No, after all...
You're definitely...
It's a dignified thing.
Is it 3rd place?
I used to be called Ai Hou Hoi.
Well, I got 1st place.
Well, Ai Hou Hoi is...
0!
How about this time?
Did you get it checked by your wife?
I...
I didn't take a video!
After all...
Next year...
The junior will be born.
I told her to record the video.
It's okay.
Please go to 3rd place.
Oh, that's good.
Really?
I think I just decided.
Let's go!
This week's 3rd place!
To the heart of the earth!
Bring me the pancake right now!
Bring it quickly!
Pancake?
And Miso Ramen?
Bring it right now!
Be a good child!
Do you have a brain?
Do you have twins?
No, I don't.
Thank you!
As expected!
Here's inside and there's another two!
Let's go!
This week's 2nd place is...
195 points!
Congratulations!
Alright!
High Tension!
Long time no see!
I'm going to skip this year!
You're going to skip this year?
It's over!
You're so high-tension from the start!
Are you okay?
Do it more!
I'm tired.
You're tired, aren't you?
Your fingers are like this.
You're doing well crispy!
Thank you very much!
From Tanjiro Mitsubishi for steps gift from you,
Nakano Shivasu!
Does he work out?
He says bad things now...
Does he?
So I'm going to skip a page!
I'm done with the eggs!
When the egg is finished, the chicken won't come out.
I remembered.
I don't understand the feeling of the egg.
When the egg is finished, the chicken won't come out.
Spanish.
I remembered.
Cabs.
What?
I don't understand the feeling of the egg.
Thank you very much.
Amazing.
It's good.
Everyone.
This is not the end.
The person who stands at the top will appear.
It's good.
Let's go.
This week's number one is...
208 points.
It's Kuwabara Kuwabara.
Yamasaki Hose.
Congratulations.
You are very good.
You know that, don't you?
Well then, Yamazaki-san, you're in first place.
I've prepared a pair of socks for you.
Here you go.
Yes, please play it.
Yes, congratulations!
You're in first place!
Well, isn't this something everyone is looking forward to?
That's right.
It's something everyone is most proud of.
Here you go.
Are you okay?
No, I don't feel like I'm okay.
But from here, I'll use my power to take you to the first place, Kokoro-e.
Well then, please stand by.
This is really...
You were in first place last time too, right?
Yes, this...
Really?
Of course not!
Who are you?
Well then, let's go.
This week's first place, Yamazaki Hosei, is Fuwabara Fuwabara!
What is this?
Ah, it doesn't matter.
That was when I debuted and had my second live performance.
Let's go to the next one!
I'm going to take away your itchiness!
I'll protect you! I'll protect you!
I'll take away your itchiness! I'll protect you!
I'll protect you!
That didn't work.
Thank you very much!
Well then, let's go to the next one!
I'm in first place too.
No?
Yes.
How easy is it?
Spotlight.
Spotlight?
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.