Please enjoy the commercial of Gio's.
Next time, at Gaki no Tsukai, Chiki Chiki Gaki no Tsukai OPEN!
Today, we'll be using a special club.
A special club?
That's right.
And we'll be playing golf.
This is probably a serious story.
I think someone will get hurt.
There's no doubt about that.
But first, let's take a look at what we have here.
This is our special club.
This is our captain.
Our director.
Your sleeves are so long.
Look at your feet.
They're too short.
Don't say that.
Oh, you're saying it.
You're so loud.
You don't sound like a human.
You're so high up.
The dolphins are gathering.
You're the first one.
Is that okay?
Tamao is the first one.
You can't do that.
Okay, let's go.
One, two, three.
It's OB.
I'm sorry.
Tamao.
Tamao is jumping too high.
Let's go with this.
One, two, three.
Okay.
It's okay.
Let's go with this.
This is good.
Wait a minute.
Let's go.
Do it slowly.
That's...
You're talking too much.
Wait a minute.
What?
It's dangerous.
One, two, three.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Don't jump.
It was a slight slide.
Hey, hey, hey.
One, two, three.
It was a slight slide.
We can do the same thing.
One, two, three.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
No, no, no.
I'm going to get a phone call.
Don't tease Chibikko.
Tamao.
With the sand.
Yes.
That's the most interesting one.
One, two, three.
Don't jump.
It's close to the end.
Let's go with the putter.
It can't be helped.
One, two, three.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
My body twisted.
Why can't you jump?
Because I'm a putter.
It was a slight slide.
Let's change the ball.
I was able to do this with Nikki Golf.
It's a good ball.
Oh, sorry.
I can't get in.
The game is over.
Yes.
We can't go home with this club.
They were not as good as I thought.
Let's return this club quickly.
Yes.
I've prepared an expensive bottle.
OK.
I'm sorry.
Get in.
Hello.
Good morning.
Why are you wiping your hands?
Well.
Let's have a beer.
I'm sorry.
Ladies and gentlemen.
The fuel limit of this program is increasing.
Is that so?
Yes.
Well.
This year.
It used to be 18 years old or older.
It's not even 18 years old now.
Is that so?
Yes.
It's more than 18 years old.
What?
It's 21 years old.
It's going up more and more.
That's why I've been working overtime lately.
It's like I'm putting up an oasis.
That's a big deal.
It's getting tough.
I can't control it.
It depends on the fuel limit.
That's right.
Don't eat too much.
The age limit is increasing.
It feels like I'm an adult.
What's going on?
That's proof.
After the program is over.
It's like a chase.
I'm all alone.
I'm lonely when I'm on the stage.
I don't think anyone is there when I'm on the stage.
It's like a guard in a book.
Yes, yes, yes.
I don't like it.
It's like I want to go home.
It's all right.
But as you said, I have to decide on the top.
How many?
It's a program, so I want a young laughter.
It's like a needle.
I'm in my 20s.
I see.
It starts at 21.
21 is right.
What about me?
Older people are worse than me.
That's proof.
If we go up, the program will go up.
It's 29.
What's the current limit?
The current limit is 29.
What about my mother?
Your mother is already out.
It's over 50.
I didn't say that much.
It's about 60.
You're lucky.
Well, that's it.
Did you hear that?
Yes.
Really.
Who said really?
What happened recently?
Something has changed.
What?
Michael Jackson is still something.
What do you mean?
Will it come in December?
I don't know.
Michael Jackson is still sick.
Except for his strange face?
He has a lot of things.
He's strange.
When I came to Japan,
He said he didn't like cigarettes.
He rented all the rooms in the hotel.
He put up wallpapers in the hallway.
He said he smelled cigarettes.
In the room.
He's an idiot.
He said he didn't like cigarettes before he sold them.
What did he do before he sold them?
Before he sold them?
He was a bad guy before he sold them.
He didn't like flowers.
He didn't say that.
He can't stand it.
He's a bad guy.
When he sold them,
He changed his face a lot.
When he came to Japan,
He took a monkey with him.
He said,
That monkey smells bad.
If it smells bad,
Put it in your nose.
In your plastic nose.
He's a bad guy.
He said,
He likes amusement parks.
That's right.
He's an idiot.
He didn't say that.
There's a roller coaster.
It's amazing.
What?
It's inside the building.
No matter what it is,
It's a roller coaster.
It's inside the building.
That's right.
No matter what it is,
It's outside.
I've heard of it.
Who?
Everyone says it.
Who says everyone?
The people who live around here.
Have you ever talked to them?
It's so weird.
It's an amazing house.
I don't know.
I don't know if it's him.
They are not making money.
That's why they love it so much.
That's why they went crazy to that place.
That monkey isn't him.
Why?
Why are you talking so small?
He's singing, and when he turns, his nose goes like this!
Don't look for me by my pen name.
I'll read it.
Do you think women are more beautiful than men?
I don't think so.
What does that mean?
For example, we're in Osaka, but women are more beautiful than men.
Women are beautiful.
And, well, a good woman comes here, a good man comes here,
they're tied up here, they're born here, they're raised here, they grow up here.
In that sense, the overall level is high here.
I see.
But there are far more ugly women.
You know, the beautiful wife who was killed by something.
I've never seen a beautiful wife.
That's right.
You're not beautiful at all.
That's why I told you before, the beautiful wife.
That's right.
You're not a beautiful wife.
If you say something like that, it's hard to get a job.
That's right.
I was born in 1929.
Who are you?
I've never seen a beautiful woman.
I see.
You're all ugly.
What?
Ha!
Do you hear that?
The tires.
Ha!
Do you hear that?
If you hear that, you'll be angry.
You're all ugly.
I cried a lot.
I thought you were a parking violation.
I apologized normally.
I'm not Yuta anymore.
I'm sorry.
By the way, you have an ugly face.
Who is responsible for this?
It's an ugly face.
It's all over the place.
That's right.
That's why I can't say it's all right.
It's definitely an ugly face.
For example, today, I was most afraid of being hit by a box.
You're nervous.
I'm nervous.
I looked at it.
Oh, you're a pretty good woman.
What do you think?
Wow!
I can't help but look at you.
This is.
It's amazing, isn't it?
The more I look back, the more amazing it is.
I don't even know what kind of person I am when I look back.
This is the reason why I hate it.
I don't know.
I see.
Don't look at me.
That's right.
Men are at a higher level, aren't they?
Women say a lot about men.
From my point of view, there are a lot of cool men now.
But there aren't many cute women.
Why do you say that?
Oh, it's completely different.
Hasn't there been a lot of cool men walking around with ugly women lately?
There are quite a few, aren't there?
Are there still a lot of cool and beautiful women in couples?
Right now, there are a lot of cool men with ugly women.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Why?
Because the level of men is generally high.
Because the level of women is low.
It's true.
I've seen a lot of different patterns.
What kind of women?
I've seen a lot of people with ugly men.
There weren't many nice couples.
Oh, I see.
Hiromi Okawa and Tohdo.
I don't think they're a nice couple.
They're a nice couple.
They're not a nice couple.
What are you thinking?
What?
Mr. Tohdo has a beautiful wife.
What are you talking about?
They're not a nice couple.
I haven't seen a lot of nice couples lately, but men are definitely...
Everyone says, but they're definitely on a higher level.
Women are getting out of hand.
I don't think I'm bad at all.
I'd like you to think about it.
Now, my sister is working hard to aim for the entertainment industry.
I used to hear a lot about how if you didn't have sex with the president, you wouldn't be able to sell it.
Tell me the truth.
What do you think?
Even for idols, if you don't sleep with the president, you won't be able to get a push.
I've never heard of it.
It used to happen a lot in the past.
It was selling well.
Think about it.
It was selling well, but suddenly...
There are people who suddenly fall in love.
That's enough.
That's all the president's women.
The president asked me to draw a picture.
I've been chasing Mr. Matsuzaka ever since.
Oh, I see.
There are women like that.
There are.
What?
For example, Tetsuo Ishidate.
Why?
Well...
He's in good spirits.
Why is Mimikuso sweet?
It's Hanakuso.
Why is Hanakuso sweet, but Mimikuso spicy?
I think this is really good.
You mean Hanakuso is sweet, but Mimikuso is spicy?
Wait a minute.
Hanakuso has been eaten once by anyone.
How? What do you mean?
Hanakuso is crushed, and it's pretty good.
Don't you eat it with your clothes on?
Don't you eat it even when you're a kid?
No, no, no.
You don't eat it?
Everyone eats Hanakuso.
I can't eat it.
You guys are full of lies.
Hey, that's not true.
Look, Hanakuso.
I ate a lot.
You ate it, didn't you?
I'm sick of them.
Why did you eat it?
I'd like to ask you something here.
When Hanakuso was eaten and there was nothing to throw away,
When there was nothing, I was able to get a lot of Hanakuso.
It's dirtier to put this under a chair, isn't it?
If you're going to put it on, eat it.
Why are you talking like this?
That's right.
It's dirty.
It's better to put it on a chair or something.
Why do you eat such a thing?
Are you okay with putting a Hanako on it?
I'm fine with it.
No, no, no, no.
I don't like it at all.
There's nothing in there I've ever put on.
I can't get rid of it.
Even in the summer, when you wear shoes,
You smell like you want it, don't you?
What the hell is this guy?
I've seen him a lot.
That's true, isn't it?
Well, that might be true.
No, that's not true.
If you take off your underwear and poop, you smell, don't you?
What are you talking about?
I don't smell at all.
You don't smell at all?
I thought you did.
I'm sure there's poop in your underwear.
100% there is.
You can tell when there is.
After you went to poop, you didn't wipe it off, did you?
That's why you smell.
You can tell when there is.
I went home.
You went home.
Well, just a little bit of fun.
I'm sure there's poop in your underwear.
100% there is.
You can tell when there is.
I'm sure there is.
But I don't think there's much poop in your underwear.
I wonder.
I don't think there's much poop in your underwear.
How many times do you wipe your underwear?
I usually wipe it once or twice.
What?
You only wipe it twice?
Twice.
You only wipe it once, don't you?
Then the poop must be everywhere.
The first time is a little weird.
That's the second time.
It's pretty obvious.
Then you'll wipe it the next time you go.
You know you're going to wipe it.
Don't even do it if you know you're going to do it.
I don't care anymore.
What are you talking about?
Idiot.
Just one more blow. That's it.
It's not good to blow too much.
That's why you should blow as much as you can.
I can't blow as much as I can.
Why?
I don't know.
I can't blow as much as I can.
Idiot.
My science skills are getting better and better.
Just a while ago, Mr. Mori's shuttle was blown up again.
I'm living in such a great era.
I don't know why the phone still works.
I don't know why I can talk to someone who is thousands of kilometers away.
I can't even imagine PAX.
Am I living in such an era?
I see.
It's true.
There's no one who can explain it.
It was amazing.
I saw something on TV the other day.
There were thousands of phones in one phone line.
They were connected like this.
They were doing something like that.
Isn't that all?
No, no, no, no.
I don't know how to say hello.
I don't know.
That's no good.
Do you know?
I know.
It's a dream.
Can I go?
Are you an amateur?
Are you awake?
Are you waiting for me?
It's a dream.
There was a person called Bell in the past.
That's no good.
It doesn't matter if you're a master.
I'm talking from here.
I see.
I don't understand.
There was a person called Bell in the past.
That's no good.