F1 Grand Prix in Tokyo
Today we are going to have an F1 Grand Prix
We are going to have a race with our cars
What?
Why did you find out?
Everyone knows
This is an antique car
This is a Nissan Impala 630R
I have owned this car for 5 years
You must have a lot of money
What is that shop?
This is a monster exotic car
It has a lot of energy
Do you want to take a look at the engine room?
I don't want to
There is a Ume-kichi inside
F1 Grand Prix in Tokyo
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
This is Mr. Kenji Suga
What is this car?
This is a 1975 911
Excuse me, I can't look at the camera
You are not an amateur
How many years have you been eating?
This is a 1974 Carrera
This is a 1974 Porsche 911 Carrera
How is it?
It's good, but I'm not good at driving
You are not good at driving?
The staff is going to bite you
Thank you
I'm Ume
How many kilometers have you driven so far?
The fastest is 220 km
Where do you live?
I live in Setagaya
What is the nearest police station?
Tamagawa Police Station
How many kilometers have you driven so far?
80 km
This is a RX-7
I like your car
Everyone, talk
Open the door when the weather is nice
Don't open the door
This is a Nissan Safari
I heard that you dug a hole on your way home from skydiving
That's right
Did you dig a hole with me?
The place where the tissue is placed in front of the car is an industrial area
It can be used immediately
What is this?
This is a Hilux Surf
You don't care about this car?
No
What is this?
You don't joke with me, do you?
I heard that you dug a hole on your way home from skydiving
A hole?
I see
Do you want me to write that you don't joke with me?
No
This is a Takasu
Takasu
Stop
This is a Takasu
Take this
Hold this
What is this?
I'm sorry
Is it funny?
I didn't expect this
I'm sorry
I see
This is a Norias
This is a Aisa
This is a Met-In-Tact
You can fix your helmet here
That's right
Like this
You came all the way here
That's right
You have too much knowledge
No one can fix a helmet like this
Even if you lose a helmet like this
It's the same as covering a ugly woman
Shall we start?
Yes
Everyone is standing in front of the car
Run
Get on
The goal is the line in front of you
Run as far as you can
The winner will win
Be careful not to get wet
Be careful not to slip
I'm afraid of hydroplaning
Don't joke with me
The reason why I don't joke with you is because of this rule
Ready
I'm sorry
I made a mistake
I turned on the radio
It was my favorite song
I'm sorry
Mr. Matsumoto
The winner is Mr. Yanaoka
Let's see the winning run again
I'm sorry
I'm glad
Mr. Yanaoka
Congratulations
Can I express my feelings with my attitude now?
Yes
Thank you
It's been a while since I came to Asakusa
It's been a while since you came to this company
I think it's rare for a star like you to come to Asakusa.
You still haven't said it?
I thought I'd have to talk about this today.
I really don't know what to say.
The other day, I was with a local friend in Aokawa.
I said, I'm going now. I was pretty happy.
In the middle of the night?
In the middle of the night. It was about 1.30 or so.
It was late, but I thought I'd have a cup of tea.
I went down to the house, and I got a call.
From your friend?
Yeah.
He said, come out.
So I went.
I called him the other day.
I found out later how old he was.
A 16-year-old woman,
in the middle of the night,
holding a plastic bag,
she was walking towards me.
What was that?
Was she having an affair?
At first, I thought she was eating something.
She was eating one by one.
So I called her, and I fell asleep.
At that time, I was completely shocked.
Whoa!
Tea!
It's tea!
I said.
I can't believe it's so late at night.
You don't know that.
Of course I don't.
What am I doing at this time of the night?
I shouldn't be doing that.
My parents, too,
have been working to raise young boys.
You're just an old lady in green.
When I was in elementary school,
I was sent to your aunt's house,
and then I was sent to your uncle's house.
You're just an old lady in green.
I said,
you shouldn't be doing that.
Go home.
I said that.
I called her,
and she said,
I'm home.
I said, okay, I'll be right there.
When I looked at her,
she was in my car.
You're lucky.
Lucky?
If you saw me like that,
what would you think of me?
That's true, but...
What are you doing?
That's not good.
Go home.
I said that.
I'll ask you later.
Go home.
I said, okay, okay.
I called her,
and she said,
my friend came.
I looked at the passenger seat.
What happened?
That woman said,
she's my girlfriend.
Don't lie to me.
You just met me.
Why am I your girlfriend?
She said,
she's my girlfriend.
You brought her here.
She's my friend from elementary school.
Don't believe what I say,
or what other people say.
What did you do after that?
I said,
just throw away
that dangerous thing
you're holding in your hand.
It's not dangerous at all.
I said,
just throw it away.
Did you really say that?
Of course.
I threw it away.
Did you take her with you?
No.
I said,
go home.
Go home.
I said,
I won't go home.
take me somewhere.
Come on.
I said,
I don't want to.
You don't want to?
She's 16.
She's your strike zone.
She's in the middle,
if you say that.
Even if she's a local from Tokyo,
in front of the TV,
you say,
I did it.
No,
I said,
I did it.
I don't think so.
I said,
did you do it?
Question.
I'm asking you.
Did you do it?
That's right.
I did it.
I said,
For example,
if the police say,
what are you doing there?
They probably won't believe me,
if I say that.
I wonder.
That's...
I can't get away with that.
What do you mean?
If they don't believe you,
you're doing what you're doing.
That's right.
I'm doing something.
They'll think I'm a accomplice.
In the drama,
when I open the door,
no one comes out.
The door was open,
so when I went in,
I was hit by a vase,
my head was broken,
and I died.
When I was about to die,
the woman next door,
said,
I'm going to kill you.
That's exactly what happened.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to run away.
You can't run away.
Even if I run away,
I can't remember her face.
In that case,
I have to kill her.
That's what I say.
When I go to her place,
she makes this face.
I'm going to kill you.
I can't remember her face.
When I ran away,
she made a normal face.
That's nonsense.
Normally,
including that,
you have to be trustworthy.
You can't trust anyone.
Normally,
you have to be trustworthy.
That's a good opportunity.
That's right.
I was shocked when she said,
I'm more trustworthy than her.
I got an energy shock.
Normally,
on TV,
people make fun of me.
I'm lying to myself.
I have to be trustworthy.
I can't help it.
I can't use lies.
I have to be trustworthy.
That's a joke.
That's a real story.
I don't know anything.
You stole your gasoline.
That's a joke.
I can't believe you.
I didn't steal gasoline.
Oh, my!
Sorry, Maria!
Sorry, Maria.
Did you steal it?
No, no, no.
I stole it.
Well, well, well, well.
I can't help stealing other people's things.
I really shouldn't do that.
I'm not bragging, but I've never stolen anything.
This is funny.
So, what did I steal?
First, you went to your housemate's house on New Year's and stole all the New Year's presents.
You stole it, didn't you?
Um...
What's good?
You stole it, didn't you?
Don't push me!
I thought you were going to come in.
You hid it, didn't you?
You stole it, didn't you?
That's all.
What?
You might have stolen it with you, but I'll return it the next day.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
I've been told this by my mother all the time.
I shouldn't touch other people's things.
Even if I touch other people's things, I should return them twice as much.
I've been told this by my mother all the time.
My mother is the one who guides the young men.
I got it!
You green lady!
Didn't you steal the sweets before you went to the New Year's?
I stole them.
What did you steal?
What?
Chocolate and other stuff.
Poporon and stuff.
Poporon, ron, ron, poporon, ron.
That's not good.
You shouldn't steal poporon.
If you steal poporon, the next time you're born, you'll be Marimo.
What about Carl?
Don't think about stealing Carl.
He's a sea cat.
What?
A sea cat.
Sea cats are sad.
He's not even a cat, but he's called a sea cat.
Do you have any sweets?
No, I don't.
What the hell are you doing?
What did you steal?
What did I steal?
Potato chips.
I've had a lot of potato chips.
Why did you steal them?
I'm not dead yet.
If you're dead, come over here.
Potato chips? What flavor?
I can't decide what flavor.
It's obvious.
Really?
Potato chips can't be made with Koikeya and Calbee.
That's true.
It's obvious.
That's right.
That's true.
What flavor?
Nori salt.
Nori salt is the heaviest among potato chips.
Please take it out.
Good evening.
What's your name?
Yoshimi Takimura.
How old are you?
18.
18?
What's your father's name?
Koji.
What's your mother's name?
Ie.
What's your father's name?
Koji.
What's your mother's name?
Ie.
What's your name?
Yoshimi.
What are you from?
I'm Japanese.
I see.
You know everything about her.
I don't.
I just heard my father and mother's names.
I know.
Really?
I'll say it instead of her.
You mean her?
Yes.
When was she born?
Koji.
What's your father's name?
I'm sorry.
This is another interesting thing.
This kind of thing happens often.
That's the question.
Thank you very much.
So...
Let's introduce the post today.
I visited Kanda Pansy Hall with my friend and mother.
Until that day, I didn't know which one of us was a fan.
I didn't think about it.
You didn't think about it.
I realized that I was a fan of Hitoshi Matsumoto.
I went to Matsumoto, who was trying to go home with a pen and notebook.
I thought the staff would say no.
But Matsumoto took the pen and signed it.
When my mother said thank you, I looked back at Matsumoto's smile.
I can't forget it.
Hey.
Are you a fan of Fujiyama?
He smiled.
There's another thing like this.
This is a cutout from the newspaper.
I received this.
This is Shisayo from Aichi Prefecture.
I'll read the cutout.
It was in the newspaper on the weekend.
It's a famous scene from the 13th.
When I saw the last scene of Flanders, Matsumoto said he cried.
But I couldn't help but cry.
It was impressive.
I was moved by this.
Did you come all the way from Sontan?
I thought it would be better for me to be a bit reckless.
So I changed myself.
But I could see my true self.
It's something you can't hide.
You can't help but cry.
It's very beautiful.
That's right.
Have you ever cried for someone?
For someone?
I used to cry a lot when I watched Don't Call Me Papa.
You're talking about such a low-class story.
You can cry in a drama.
Don't Call Me Papa.
You're wrong.
Isn't there anything you cry about in your daily life?
For example, when you go home and twist the faucet, water comes out.
Ah, the faucet.
Can you cry?
Can you cry like that?
Can you cry when you go home and twist the faucet and water comes out?
I can cry.
Don't lie.
Depending on how much water comes out of the faucet,
do you think about how many people work to make water come out?
Do you think it's natural for water to come out of the faucet?
You're wrong.
You need to think about that.
The person who makes water come out of the faucet is called a faucet man.
He's wearing a red cape.
That's a good story.
If it was really a woman.
What?
If the faucet man was a woman,
wearing a red cape,
I would be grateful.
I wouldn't cry.
I would cry.
I've never seen it.
I wouldn't cry.
I've never seen you cry.
Actually, I don't think it's funny to say this, but I'll say it.
I came to the venue today.
I thought I was going home.
There's no way out.
That's the great thing about the faucet man.
I was lying.
The faucet man...
Please wait a little longer.
Let's take a break.
People who watch this show are fools.
If he didn't come, I'd have forgotten.
That's not true.
It's true.
When was it?
Even today's audience was making a stupid face.
That's not true.
I'll tell you a little later.
Please wait a little longer.
That's all for now.
See you next week.
Goodbye.
I don't like this part.
What?
This part...
It stinks.
It doesn't stink.
It's a little hard to hear.
There's a dog and a rabbit in the back.
This is a present for you.
I see.
Miki Suzuki, 17 years old.
She's here today.
Let's give her a present.
Thank you very much.
Here you go.
Here it is.
Yes.
It's on now.
I was going to bring it home and put it on.
I heard you need electrical work.
It's a lot more expensive than the general price.
I'm sorry to say that.
I have a lot of people I want for the next person.
Do you want to take it home?
I'll do it.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.