What should we do to celebrate the 100th anniversary of Daki's Skyline?
We have to decide soon.
That's right.
The date is getting closer.
Even if we get excited, the viewers won't care.
Because it's the time.
It's Yuka-fensei.
He's pulling the string.
Let's make it clear today.
Taku-san, do you have anything to say?
No, I'm not going to think about it.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Team Zero's street TV.
What does this mean?
I don't know.
Say it roughly.
It's a street TV.
We're probably...
Don't say probably.
We're probably carrying a TV.
You're carrying a TV?
If I were a trident, I'd probably get hit.
We're probably carrying a TV.
I see.
That's what Team Zero's street TV means.
Let's move on.
Pick one.
It's a live VTR.
What does this mean?
It took you quite some time.
That's why...
It's a live VTR.
Oh, so that's how we do it.
So we'll show it like a VTR.
Oh, I see.
Hamada, please hold onto this.
Hey, what do you think about this?
I don't like it at all.
That's not it.
Team Zero.
Team Zero's watch.
I think this is quite interesting.
What do you mean?
I've grown up.
And this guy has become single.
I see.
And Mr. Perlman,
Mr. Perlman No. 2,
Mr. Perlman No. 2 has become sick.
That's not it.
I see.
It's a big watch.
You know,
it's like real time.
When we're talking,
like a swimming competition,
in a random way,
he goes like a whip.
Then, he comes out.
Does he come out?
He comes out when the restaurant is full.
This is the first time I've heard this.
It's a live show,
so in thirty minutes,
The one who can bring it.
The superstar will eat it,
and he'll come to the restaurant.
No one else can do it?
I think it's better to be a talent.
You call them at the beginning, and bring something before the end.
That's a good idea.
It's a common thing.
This is really...
Is it okay for a writer in Osaka to do this?
No, no, no, no.
The audience's room.
What about this?
What does this mean?
This is the light of the main power.
The warm peach is different.
I've been warming it for five years.
I put out a paper in a big mammoth's house.
At night, the guy who's looking at the child turns on the light.
Help me!
He's a bad guy.
This is the emergency press conference.
What do you think, Suzuki?
I thought of a soft head.
Suzuki, you're really good at talking.
This is important, too.
No, no, no, no.
I see. This is Suzuki.
This is Dada's room.
Get out of here!
A dreamy present to celebrate the 100th anniversary.
This time, it's a really luxurious gift.
I've done it a hundred times.
I'm thinking of preparing a present that will make everyone happy.
I see.
That's all.
Can I mix it?
Yes, you can.
I can do this.
I've decided to do this live.
Live?
I'll do it live on Tuesday at 1 o'clock.
I'll do it live from 1 o'clock 40 minutes.
I'd like to focus on the 100th anniversary this time.
I'm going to recruit people to come see it.
100 people? No way.
100 people.
People who come to see the 100th anniversary have to dress up as 100 people.
I have to dress up as one of the 100 people.
But it's a live broadcast.
You know what I mean?
100 people.
What are you going to dress up as?
Don't say that when you're told to.
Think about it.
It's a live broadcast.
I'll check it out in advance.
So I'm not going to say what kind of clothes you're going to wear.
I'll check it out when I'm told to.
I'm not going to say what kind of clothes you're going to wear.
I've been doing this 100 times.
Usually before the show, the audience is informed that they won't be able to laugh.
That's right.
When it's tough.
There's a lot of information that it's going to be tough today.
That's right.
Really.
As I said earlier, the world is getting excited.
Is it getting excited?
Is it going to be a lot of fun?
The audience is going to be excited.
Is it going to be fun?
I don't know about you, but it's totally different when the audience is there and when they're not.
It's totally different.
We've been waiting for the concert.
There's a terrible place.
Where is it?
Maizuru.
Maizuru?
It's terrible.
It was terrible.
It was about the number of people in the entertainment world.
We were doing our best at the concert.
We sang the whole song.
You sang the whole song.
Yes.
And then, the paper.
The big paper.
At first, only the silhouette was shown.
When we were in the audience, our silhouettes were shown.
And then, it was like this.
You ripped the paper.
You ripped it.
The opening song was like this.
The fans were like this.
That's right.
That's Maizuru.
Really.
It's true.
We were singing like this.
Really.
It's true.
When the concert was over, most of the people in the hall said,
Please leave immediately.
We have a taxi waiting at the back door.
We were panicking.
We were like,
Is that so?
Maizuru.
It's totally different.
When the concert was over,
Who was there?
Before the concert started, it was terrible.
Normally, before the concert starts, there are many people.
But Maizuru, 5 minutes before the concert starts, there are no people.
And then, about 2 minutes before the concert starts,
The car is coming.
Really.
The car is coming from everywhere.
We were not excited at all.
We were in a low tension.
We stopped the car like this.
Right?
It was terrible.
When the concert was over,
Everyone was like,
What are you doing?
We were selling goods.
Give me that.
It's a downtown T-shirt.
After the concert was over,
Everyone went to the bicycle park again.
We were like,
The yakuza is leading the way.
It's terrible.
Normally,
Can you listen to me?
Yes.
At the concert,
The people in front of us are really excited.
They came all the way here,
And they were riding the yakuza.
We were riding the yakuza.
The yakuza was leading the way.
While everyone was riding the yakuza,
The yakuza came in front of us.
Hey!
Excuse me.
I'm singing.
Sit down.
Everyone was sitting down.
It's true.
Everyone was singing like this.
Like this.
Yes.
Everyone was standing up.
Sit down.
It was like this again.
There was no concert like that.
No.
We were standing here.
The yakuza.
It wasn't just one person.
Everyone was standing here.
It's true.
Everyone was standing in front of us.
Like this.
It's like this.
When we have concerts,
We want to look like musicians.
Even if we say that.
So,
We put up posters on the poles.
Downtown Concert.
If we put up more cool posters,
My face will be smiling and smiling.
And my face will be in the picture.
And my tongue will be in the picture.
Like this.
Do you understand?
It's like a picture of a supermarket.
Yes.
My face will be smiling.
And my tongue will be in the picture.
I can't do that.
Even though I'm dressed up.
Yes.
That's how it is.
Do you want to go to the theater?
Sure.
Do you want to talk more?
I went to the theater in Osaka after a long time.
It was a summer vacation.
When I went to the theater,
The next door was on fire.
I saw the spirit of Osaka businessmen.
NGK is a takoyaki shop next to the theater.
And there is a karaoke box next to it.
That's the fire.
There are five fire trucks.
There is no line in front of the store.
It's amazing.
But the man in the takoyaki shop is baking takoyaki.
I was surprised.
And there are people who come to buy takoyaki.
Then the man said,
It's not baked yet.
Do you want to eat takoyaki?
Yes.
Why do you come here?
What?
It doesn't mean anything.
Don't look at me like that.
Why?
What?
Don't look at me like that.
I was cold in my friend's dressing room.
What?
Tetsuko's room.
I want to go out.
It was very painful.
It doesn't mean anything.
You kicked me.
I have a lot of fans.
I'm sorry.
No.
You said it was your fault.
Why do you blame me?
It's dirty.
It's my job.
No.
I have a different job on Tuesday.
You said we should find another job.
I came here today.
Someone is coming to your room.
When did you call me your friend on Tuesday?
I didn't know that you were my friend.
I know, I know.
You know?
That's why, I heard that you are doing many movies.
You can do it with me.
If I finish that, I can't go to the next job.
You have to do it properly.
No, if you want to do it, you have to do it.
It's big.
It's already a big mess.
No, then,
I said I'll do it on Tuesday from the beginning.
No, let me do it. If you do that, I can't do it.
It's better to do two jobs than three jobs.
Your opponent is Satcher.
You don't know a man and a woman.
But I know that it's a big mess.
Then, tell me what you were doing.
Satcher?
Yes, Satcher is that.
He is the chief of staff.
At that time, the country is different.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Are you talking about that Satcher?
Which Satcher are you talking about?
I'm talking about Satcher.
I don't know about that.
I'm talking about Satcher on TV.
That's strange.
Oh, Satcher. I know, I know.
Then, tell me what you were doing.
I know about Satcher very well.
So what?
Satcher had a hard time.
That's right.
But it looks like that.
It's the part of the housekeeper.
I didn't know that.
I knew it was hard,
but I didn't know it was the housekeeper.
Why?
Satcher was in a bad mood.
Oh, I see.
How can I say?
When he was angry, he was angry.
What are you talking about?
I've been talking about politics for a while.
Actually, there was a painting we went to the temple before, right?
It was the painting of the secretary of Kaifushou.
Is that Mr. Memoto Ryuichi?
He's a great person.
He was chosen.
Do you have a name card?
The other day, too.
What's your hobby?
Kaifu Toshiki.
Watching downtown TV.
That's amazing.
That's me.
I'm the secretary of the Prime Minister of the Cabinet, Memoto Ryuichi.
What kind of work do you do?
I make tea.
What?
Do you run?
Is that so?
That's my job.
Do you have a secret?
It's a trick.
Yes.
What is it that you're doing in the Prime Minister's room?
I don't have a secret.
What do you do sometimes?
It's really funny.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Thank you for coming.
I didn't think it would be such a light program.
I'm watching it.
I can't say anything bad.
When I was listening to the live broadcast of the F1 race, the announcer said,
Ayrton Senna is dancing in the first place.
But he doesn't look like he's dancing at all.
What does this mean?
I can't see it, but he's doing this.
When he's doing this, I feel like he's doing this.
I don't know.
If he's Japanese, he's not dead yet.
Why is a foreigner doing this?
I can't see it, but he's doing this.
What is this?
I'm saying how I feel.
How about you?
How do you feel when you take a step forward when you're competing?
I'm happy.
You're happy, aren't you?
That feeling.
I can't see it, but he's doing this in his mind.
I understand.
That's right.
I see.
He used to say that.
He said he was dancing.
I have another question.
Why do you call Kyoko Suizenji a cheater?
I'm sorry, Machan.
I really don't know.
Actually, this is...
Why?
It's true.
Normally, names go well with each other.
Like this, I guess.
That's a really good one.
This is wonderful.
It is!
Well, it would be great if you could wear it, but if someone asks you to do something, or if you want to make a phone call to the opening, I don't know if you can do it.
We don't know about this.
We don't know.
It's a problem.
Why do you always wear shirts, neckties, and suits? When you were in school, you wore T-shirts, checkered pants, and berets. You were so young.
But you always wore a strange-looking shirt and pants.
I don't think that's cute.
Next time, you should try wearing your clothes.
Hey, do you want to wear this?
So, let's do that next week.
Next week?
So, I want you to prepare your usual clothes. I don't know if I should wear it or not.
But I don't want to wear it.
You have to fix it.
I'll leave it as it is.
You have to change it.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
I'm going to fold my pants a little.
What?
You're going to fold your pants?
It's too long, so I'm going to fold my pants.
What kind of word is that?
There's no word for it.
What kind of sentence is that?
I don't think there's a word like that in this world.
In your novel, Makiko was folding her pants.
That's what happens when a real Osaka person writes it.
That's not true.
It's true.
I've never heard of it.
That's not true.
So, I'm going to leave it as it is.
All the hem.
That's fine.
When this is over, I'll change it to your clothes.
All right.
Well, everyone.
Goodbye.
Hello.
Hello, hello, hello.
Here we are.
It's the 100th anniversary.
That's right.
I said it in my head, but this is a live broadcast.
It's a live broadcast.
That's great.
But there's a condition for you to come.
There's a night's event.
There's someone who can go home from there.
I'll be on time.
I'm running the train.
Only on my way home.
Only on your way home.
I'd like to have someone who can go home properly.
It's a 100th anniversary.
I said it in my head.
It's a costume that's one of the 100.
That's right.
There are various costumes in Kanda.
Is it Hyakutaro?
Well, that's what I thought last year.
Is that what you mean?
Yes.
Well, if you come, there's definitely something good.
Really, really.
I came to see it.
I became a guest.
That's right.
The staff probably thinks so, too.
I want a picture of Parman No. 2 at the previous ending.
I want this, too.
I put it out here.
Yes, it's out.
Is it out?
Time and place.
Yes.
Please gather here.
I want that panel.
It's a Parman No. 2 panel.
People who come.
That's the kind of costume.
I don't like it.
It doesn't have to be No. 2.
It can be Parman.
It can be Paran.
It can be Pargo.
Well, please come in that kind of costume.
Otherwise.
My Parman No. 2.
I'm waiting in that kind of costume.
I see.
Yes.
For those who came.
Commemorative photos and signs.
I understand.
And handshakes.
Yes.
I've got that kind of thing ready.
That's right.
Please gather at the place where it came out earlier.
Yes.
Parman No. 2.
Please.
That's it.
I don't know how to use it.
I'll use it next time.
Goodbye.
Mayonnaise.
That's right.
Thank you very much.