Director Heipou, why did Heipou end up like this?
4 hours ago, Heipou suddenly appeared at the usual bar.
Why does he never set up his own party?
The frightened downtown was planning to set up Heipou's party.
Hey, you guys!
It's really amazing.
What the hell are you doing?
Read the atmosphere!
You know what's going on, right?
You guys are always doing stupid things.
Do it again.
What the hell is this?
Hey, you guys!
You guys are always doing stupid things.
Read the atmosphere!
We've been together for 10 years. You know how I feel.
Hey, you guys!
You guys are always doing stupid things.
What the hell is this?
Matsumoto!
Yes?
What's going on with the party you've been planning?
Party?
Party!
My parents are telling me to do it quickly, so I have to do it.
What's so funny?
Are you angry?
I don't know.
If you don't get married during the wedding, your parents will be sad.
So let's do it!
Let's do it!
We don't know what to do.
Look at this.
It's a tie.
I've always wanted to do this.
Hurry up and do it!
Why are you laughing?
What should we do?
We don't know if we'll get a call.
Matsumoto, call Yamazaki immediately.
I'll do it.
Hurry up and do it.
Hurry up and do it!
He's crying.
Okay, let's do our best.
Let's do our best.
Anyway, Heipo's wish came true.
Heipo's wife, Soru Hokusaki, who has been searching for Heipo, has failed.
Who will she meet this time?
The legendary queen of the women's wrestling world, Heipo was in love with her sexy body.
Emergency Project.
The return of Heipo's wife.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Do you want to do it again?
Yes, I definitely want to do it again.
You have a different feeling today.
After all, it's the end of the 20th century, so I'd like to get married.
Married?
I'll do it.
Really?
You'll do it?
That's what I'm going to do.
I'm the winner.
But he'll do it.
He'll come and do it.
I'll call him.
Please.
It's really like skiing.
It's a completely different image.
Is it different?
Yes.
Thank you.
He's here.
Please.
I'm sorry for the sudden visit.
I was surprised.
I'm not good at introducing myself, so please introduce yourself.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Saito.
I'm going to be 45 years old.
I heard that you're single.
I've been a fan of yours for a while.
Really?
Yes.
I brought you here today.
I've been watching you for a while.
Don't look at me like that.
You have a huge nipple.
Thank you.
I've been wanting to see you for a long time.
Really?
Yes.
Everyone was talking about you.
But I couldn't talk to you.
So I've been wanting to see you.
What kind of man do you like?
If I like him, I don't like him.
That's good.
I like someone like you.
Someone like me?
Yes.
You have a lot of hair.
I look like him.
Do you have any special skills?
Do you want me to show you?
Saito has a special skill.
I want you to see it all the time.
Let's see it.
Yes.
It's okay, right?
Thank you.
Thank you for waiting.
You look cool.
Today, I've prepared a sea bream.
It's still alive.
Yes.
I'd like to show you how to make it alive.
It's pretty big.
It's big.
Are you scared?
No, no.
It's a sea bream, right?
I'll give you a pat.
Please open your mouth.
I'll do it.
It's a sea bream.
Okay.
Don't let it fly away.
Mr. Saito.
It's a little bit annoying.
Please stop.
It's still alive.
Mr. Saito, you should handle it.
Yes, that's the main thing.
You should handle it.
This is a job for fishermen.
Yes.
I see.
Okay, okay, okay.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Saito, Mr. Saito.
What did you say?
Be careful.
Oh.
It's bad.
Put it on the cutting board.
Sorry to make you wait.
Yes.
Please do it.
It's a sea bream.
Yes, yes.
Wow.
Ah.
Oh.
What are you doing?
I'll do it.
He's getting mad.
I'm going home!
Wait a minute!
Are you kidding me?
No, I'm not kidding.
It's a little hot.
I'm sorry.
On the other hand, we're here, so you're relying on us too much.
Oh, I'm sorry.
We don't rely on you at all.
We just want to be on TV.
We just keep appearing on TV.
Zaito-san, there's a scale here.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Now that we're alone, I think we can talk about this.
It's like we're in the way.
We can have a conversation like this.
I showed you a picture earlier.
Let's take a picture.
Isn't it nice? It's so beautiful.
Oh, thank you.
I'd be happy if you could sign this.
Yes, I understand.
Can you sign it for me?
Who's going to sign it first?
I want you to sign it as if you're a soldier.
I'm a soldier.
It's easy to understand.
I'm signing it, too.
Jaguar Yokota.
Thank you very much.
It's wonderful.
I can't pull it out.
It's stylish.
And since you wrote this, what is this?
I'd like you to wear a mini skirt.
Hey, hey, hey.
It looks good on you.
I've never worn a mini skirt.
I think black stockings are nice.
I'd like you to wear this.
It's a shame to wear it at my age.
It's very stylish.
I'd rather not wear a mini skirt.
Let's wear it.
I bought it from Jaguar.
It looks good on you.
Black and gray go well together.
Why are you so persistent?
I can't pull it out at all.
Black stockings are a must.
It's a must.
I like this.
I'd like you to wear this.
It's a must.
It's a gift.
It's a shame.
I'd like to see it.
You're a pervert.
It's just for decoration.
I'll change my clothes if I wear it.
That's right.
It's very stylish.
I can't do that.
I think it's good, but I chose it.
You're changing clothes.
It's from Jaguar.
That's right.
Hobby is important.
I like black stockings on my skirt.
You're looking down on me.
It's beautiful.
Is it okay?
Let's sit down and talk.
It's embarrassing.
It looks good on you.
It's okay.
It's embarrassing.
You don't like it, do you?
I don't like it.
It's embarrassing.
Do you like children?
I like children.
I have children around me.
I want a child.
I want to meet my child.
Already?
That's right.
It's not over yet.
It's okay.
What kind of answer is that?
I'll put this next to you.
What is it?
Yes.
I'll give it to you.
Wait a minute.
I like it.
It's okay.
Wait a minute.
I like it.
It's okay.
Wait a minute.
I was aiming for that from the beginning.
I like it.
It's okay.
I'll close it for you.
Go.
It's a scary conversation.
It's a scary world.
What is it?
I like it.
You haven't put it on yet.
It's a scary world.
I like it.
You can't get married forever.
You idiot.
I like it.
I'll show you this picture.
Why is it like this?
Don't fall in love with me.
I'm going to be a flower.
I'm going to be a wind.
I can't wait.
I had a fight with a man who was on the highway.
I'm a ticket.
What?
I'm going to be a flower.
You don't have to get a ticket.
It's easy to get a ticket.
When I gave the ticket to Harada, he grabbed it.
He grabbed the air.
I threw it at him because I was angry.
I said, you idiot, you don't have to throw anything.
Harada, who did you ask?
Who did you ask?
It's your fault.
Is that so?
I didn't think he would come down.
I said, you don't have to throw anything.
I thought it was over.
He came down.
He was angry.
I was surprised.
I threw it at him.
I saw a small rice field.
Three old men came out.
There are many old men who are calculating.
I was surprised.
Everyone was wearing a mask.
Four old men came out.
The next car was coming.
I was surprised.
Everyone was wearing a mask.
Everyone?
I was surprised.
I was embarrassed when I was forgiven.
I was embarrassed.
I thought I was wrong.
I don't think you can get angry at cars.
I want you to do it properly.
When you turn right, you wait for a car coming from the front.
When a car comes from the front, you give priority to the front.
If you wait for a long time, you can't stop.
I see.
That's not right.
You should ask the teacher again.
You give priority to the front.
But it doesn't matter from the second generation.
You wait for a long time.
I see.
When you get angry, you get angry.
You don't get angry?
I get angry.
But I can't help it.
You think so, right?
I think so.
Then you can say it together.
Why do you only say it to me?
What's wrong with you?
I can't help it.
I think so.
You're not the only one who stands out in the commercial.
Don't say that.
You're like a soldier to me.
You're an outcast.
I heard that there are many creatures that have not yet been confirmed in the deep sea.
Mr. Matsumoto, who has been diving in the sea for 3,000 meters,
Please tell me what kind of creature you met.
All right.
3,000 meters in the sea?
You're going to die.
I knew in advance that I was going to die, so I tried not to die.
How did you do it?
It's 3,000 meters.
I was told by force.
Well, it's 3,000 meters.
After diving, it's show.
What kind of creature is there?
I don't think anyone knows this.
Is there a creature?
Basically, it doesn't change that much.
There's a sea bream, a flounder, and a fish that's usually in the deep sea of Japan.
It's 3,000 meters, so there's something like this.
Basically, they're all the same.
What do you mean by basically?
Octopuses and squids.
But what's definitely different is that it says 3,000 on its forehead.
That's a big deal.
Tell me what kind of creature you met.
There were a lot.
I'm sure there were.
Is there anything we've never seen before?
There are fish in shallow places, but if you go further down, there's a deep sea creature.
What?
Deep sea creature.
Sea creature?
Sea is the sea.
Human?
Human.
What kind of creature?
Deep sea creature.
What do you mean by what kind of creature?
What does it look like?
It's almost the same as humans, but it's slightly translucent.
Slightly translucent?
Basically, they all look like they're suffering.
They look like they're suffering?
Can you explain?
They're dead, aren't they?
They're dead.
But they're suffering.
They can't breathe.
There are salaried people, and deep sea creatures.
No, it's not like that.
Sometimes they go up and they can't breathe.
That's right.
They're suffering.
It's 3,000 meters.
There are salaried people, and students, but they can't breathe.
It's very painful.
That's strange.
That's why...
They're living there, aren't they?
The salaried people who are waiting at the bus stop...
They're suffering.
They want to breathe.
For them, they go up to breathe on weekends.
They're suffering on Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays.
They're quite strong, aren't they?
On Friday, it's unbearable.
They want to go up.
It's unbearable.
They don't have a family to talk to.
Deep sea creatures.
That was really amazing.
I've never seen it before.
It's the same as a normal human being.
No, it's not.
They want to live right above you.
No, it's not like that.
They're suffering on Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays.
It's unbearable.
That's amazing.
Why do they have to go up to the sea?
They don't want to cause trouble.
How many years?
They say that if we go up, the population will increase.
They're very tall people.
They wear tights.
Why?
Because they can't go up.
They're walking like this.
What is that?
Sometimes there are people who die.
They can't stand it on Thursdays.
They have a nose.
It's amazing.
They can go up to 3,000 meters.
They fly away.
It's unbearable.
They can't stand it.
They can't go up to 3,000 meters.
That's not good.
There are many people who die.
What do you mean after-life?
I said it's not fun.
I understand.
They'll die of hunger.
That's right.
What I want to do the most is eat silkemon.
It's in the water.
I think it's hard.
But it can't be helped.
They were born there.
They were born there?
They're from the deep sea.
I see.
They fly away.
We can't see it from 3,000 meters.
We can't see it.
I want to see it.
One thing is different.
The thumb of the foot and the index finger are very developed.
The nose is like this.
You grab it.
I grab it.
You can't talk.
That's right.
I said, why do you make it low?
If you make it a heavy boot, it won't stick here.
I didn't have that idea.