Wato Wato-kun.
Yes.
Where's the camera?
Why aren't you outside today?
No, this isn't outside.
Oh, where?
This is a set.
Are you kidding me?
Do you have such a funny set?
I told you last week that I didn't want to shoot.
Nittere made a set for me.
But today, after a long time, I feel like I'm back in the city.
That's right.
Do you call it an adult town?
Aoyama.
How old are you?
16.
Are you a first-year high school student?
Are you going home?
It's already 1 o'clock 40 minutes.
That's right.
At this time of the day, why are you so excited?
I'm sad.
This is the venue for today's Gaki no Chikai Arahen.
Instant Ramen Paradise.
If you enter here, it's free, right?
Free.
But it's free.
If you can eat ramen for free, not all people come.
Today's venue is...
Here.
It wasn't here before.
It's an event where you can eat instant ramen for free.
That's why the stage is like an instant ramen.
It's delicious.
It's not very good.
Did you prepare this chair?
I think so.
No, it's a waste.
What is this? I can't see it in a place like this.
Today is a little different from before.
This is amazing.
It's different from before, right?
It's different, isn't it?
You can see it.
At this stage, let's do a story.
Let's do a story that suits this kind of place.
Something you can enjoy.
That's right.
I'm looking forward to tonight's Gaki no Chikai Arahen.
Thank you.
This program is produced by Soyo.
Oyama International Products.
Provided by Soyo.
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
Today, with everyone...
No, it's not like this, is it?
I'd like to learn about the intonation of words.
In Kansai and Kanto, there are many places where the intonation is different.
Today, let's learn about those places with everyone.
Please welcome the researcher of intonation, Mr. Matsumoto.
Mr. Matsumoto, nice to meet you.
Today's intonation is to play with lines.
Hey, you.
What is it?
I'm telling you to study, but you're telling me to play.
Let's play with lines.
Everyone, together.
I'm a little tired.
Let's play with lines.
I'm ignoring you.
I'm telling you to study.
I can't continue.
I'm sorry.
Let's play with lines.
Say it out loud.
You're annoying.
I can't continue.
Let's play with lines.
There are many kinds of lines.
There are many differences depending on the lines.
For example...
You're a dirty person.
You're such a dirty person.
This is me, Mr. Lupin.
This is a normal line.
It doesn't feel like Lupin at all.
That's right.
It changes a lot by changing the lines.
This is me, Mr. Lupin.
If you say it like this...
It's the way you say it now.
Let's do it again.
This is me, Mr. Lupin.
This is how you make it look like Lupin.
This is the line of Lupin.
I see.
Let's move on to the next step.
I don't want to learn it.
It's a little hard to understand.
Let's move on to the next step.
The lines are all different.
What is this?
This is me, Mr. Lupin.
This is a normal line.
It doesn't feel like Mr. Lupin at all.
It depends on how you say it.
By adding a line to this...
This is me, Mr. Lupin.
I think the audience around here will remember this.
I've been thinking it's strange since I came out.
I've never seen anyone who looks like this.
It's strange, isn't it?
The group is different, isn't it?
Everyone here looks like this.
Who does this?
I think the audience here is nice.
I think the audience here is funny.
Don't say unnecessary things.
Please.
What are you doing?
You're not good.
If you get angry, I'll kick you.
Let's leave the previous ones aside.
Next, let's separate Tokyo and Osaka by a line.
Let's show the difference between Tokyo and Osaka.
I'd like to hear that.
For example, it's better to write it in hiragana.
Should I write it?
There's a word like that.
If a person from Osaka says this,
If a person from Tokyo says this,
Hamachan.
If it's Osaka, it's Hamachan.
There's a difference.
If it's France, it's Hamachan.
It's a line like this.
I gave you a little ad-lib, but it's still heavy.
That's the end of the story for now.
Let's do our best to liven up this place with free talk.
If you don't like it, just grab it.
Why are you laughing?
You're Japanese, aren't you?
That's right.
No matter where you look, you're Japanese.
If you don't understand the language, you can't help it.
There are no foreigners.
That's all right.
We're going to play with the line today.
Thank you very much.
It's been 10 minutes.
Oh, it's been 10 minutes.
That's right.
It was so much fun today.
I don't know why some people are so uncooperative.
Some people?
That's why.
Today, we have an invitation and a letter request.
They're not completely mixed up.
Oh, really?
I think so.
This person wants to see the letter, right?
That's right.
And this person doesn't have much time to see it.
They're so into it.
It can't be helped.
I think it was a lot of fun today.
I wasn't feeling well today.
You can't run away like that.
Why are you not feeling well?
I'm really tired today.
I played baseball yesterday.
That's right.
I was playing baseball with the Yume de Aetara team.
I moved my body for the first time in a while.
That's right.
My body got a little tired today.
I was too excited yesterday.
What are you talking about?
I haven't played baseball for a long time.
I haven't played at all.
I stopped playing baseball after I broke my shoulder in college.
Tell me about your final grade.
High school.
I did my best.
But you must have felt good.
I played baseball at the Seibu stadium.
It was a beautiful place.
How about playing baseball once in a while?
But I'm pretty good at baseball, right?
After I finished playing baseball, I was listening to the radio on the bus.
I was excited because my name was on the radio.
What are you talking about?
I'm sure the Seibu players were watching me somewhere.
Seibu players were watching you?
The draft was just getting started.
But the Seibu players were practicing and watching me from behind.
Practicing?
I was really excited.
I didn't think I was going to win first place.
But after that, I think I won about 5th place.
Who told you that?
I've been studying and playing sports since I was a student.
That's strange.
I'm the ideal person for Japanese people.
When I was studying, your high school was a mess.
What?
During class, you were cleaning the cigarette butts between the desks.
That's right.
It's unusual for a teacher to throw away the cigarette butts like this.
You had a big head like this.
And you were wearing a small skirt.
But your IQ was really high.
Really.
What?
You were really good.
I could study better than you.
And you didn't even know the numbers.
If you say that...
I was really surprised.
I couldn't say anything.
I couldn't even tell the difference between the numbers.
And then...
I played baseball yesterday.
Are you serious?
Everyone who watches TV looks like this.
But I'm a kanji teacher.
Wait, I haven't let you go yet.
I'll let you go after you play a little bit of baseball.
Bring me a whiteboard.
Even if you know the numbers, it's useless for the society.
What?
You're more useful to the society if you know the kanji.
Of course it's useful.
The numbers are the most important thing.
You're like that.
What?
You studied on a comedy show.
Isn't that funny?
What?
You don't have to think about it.
If you don't think about it, I'll go next time.
What?
You're like that.
Two-thirds...
One-half...
What year were you in elementary school?
You're like that.
Everyone here can't do it.
Anyone can't do it.
I don't know.
If you pull it up and try, you might not be able to do it.
Try it.
This is...
This is serious.
Right?
This is...
Yes.
It doesn't stand up.
What?
It's wrong.
This is...
Yes.
You can't write it.
This is wrong.
You can't erase it.
Two-thirds...
If I were your mother, I'd make tea for you.
In front of the door.
Masato Shinkajan!
Your mother is studying.
I'm sorry.
This is...
What do you call this?
Three.
So what do you call this in the case of two-thirds?
Two-thirds.
It's two-thirds.
Yes, two-thirds.
This is called two-thirds.
What is this?
It's called two-thirds.
That's right.
Right?
This is two-thirds.
What's with the big ear?
It's two-thirds.
Right?
You have to match this and this.
Why?
This and this have nothing to do with each other.
Right?
That's right.
I'm going to be stupid, aren't I?
Are you stupid?
I'll teach you next time.
Masato!
I know this.
He can't write it.
I'll admit it.
I wrote a lot of haji in Osaka.
I'll teach you next time.
The elementary school students who are watching this are encouraged.
Really.
How do you read this?
What?
Kasuga no Tsubone.
That's right.
How do you read this?
What?
I know a lot of difficult kanji.
How do you read this?
Beautiful Tsubone.
Why is it Tsubone?
Don't you hate Tsubone?
You don't know, do you?
What?
Yes.
Tsutsumotase.
That's right.
It's Tsutsumotase.
I'll write the kanji that everyone says.
I'll write it.
I'll write Saba.
Saba.
Do you want to write Saba?
Saba-kun.
Please sign it.
Saba.
I just got a bit excited.
Who do you want to meet at the fish market?
I was going to write it now.
I was going to write it, but he said he wanted to meet.
Is that so?
Yes.
Say anything.
I can write anything.
What?
Katsuo.
Katsuo?
Yes.
What?
What is this?
I don't know what Katsuo is.
I can't do it with you.
Let's go with the letter.
I'll bring the letter.
I've received a lot of letters.
I'd like to introduce them.
Let's go with this one.
I found a picture of Machan and Hama-chan in Harajuku.
Really?
That picture was taken a long time ago.
Hama-chan's hair was a bit long and he didn't have much hair.
Machan's beard was long and one of his lower teeth was missing.
What kind of person are you?
They look like they're having a hard time.
I wonder when this picture was taken.
We're having a hard time.
Really?
I've never lost a tooth.
This tooth is a bit deep.
Sometimes it looks like that.
I can only see the lower teeth.
That's right.
I can only see the upper teeth.
Right?
Yes.
Is it deep?
It's deep.
Why can't you see the upper teeth?
I can't see them.
Why can't you see them?
I can't see them when my mother is looking at me.
Why?
I can see the lower teeth when I'm talking normally.
Why can't I see them?
Try to open your mouth.
Open your mouth.
Even if you open your mouth, you can only see the lower teeth.
I can only see the upper teeth.
What are you going to do?
I can only see the upper teeth when I'm talking normally.
If you do that, everyone will be worried.
My fans will be gone.
What if you can only see the upper teeth?
I can't see them.
I can only see the upper teeth when I'm talking normally.
I've been talking like this from the beginning.
I'll keep talking like this until today.
Even if I don't say anything, I can see the upper teeth.
I can only see the upper teeth when I'm talking normally.
I'll keep talking like this until today.
I'll go home now.
I'm not a lover.
I'm a fan of Uchan Nan-chan.
Maybe.
Or B.
You're laughing, but your voice isn't coming out properly.
You're funny.
You're laughing like a gentleman.
I'm laughing like this.
Who do you like? Tell me.
Who?
Who do you like?
Hama-chan.
I like her.
What?
You're a proper customer.
I'll stop the button properly.
I see.
What is it?
They're people.
You should have told me earlier.
That's all.
That's all for today.
We went to many places again.
We did, didn't we?
We haven't finished talking yet.
When we're done, let's have a drink.
When we're done.
We did, didn't we?
We slept for a month.
No one laughed.
When I thought we'd finally laugh,
I called a champion and kicked him.
A boy champion.
That's why some people want to go home.
That's all for today.
What are you talking about?
It starts at 1.40.
It's a 30-minute program.
It's 2 minutes to 30 minutes.
There's no commercial today.
We have to hurry up.
That's right.
What?
What are you talking about?
That's fine.
That's not funny.
That's all for today.
That's all for tonight.
See you next time.
Hello.
What is it?
It's over.
We're sitting in the audience's seat.
That's right.
We're sitting in the second seat in front of the stage.
Looking from this position,
It's a funny story.
And until we go on stage today,
We're tired from traveling.
That's the best.
Long-term location.
A long-term location.
In the cold.
For a long time.
It's like a recital.
A grand location.
If you're coming to see us,
He's someone in the fan-ranking.
You pick him up in a group.
He's something like ałem for the company company.
He lives life for the people he's然後
I can think of a lot of people who work hard for him.
He works for us.
I worked hard for the potential sub.
The off-site sub.
I don't have it next time.
I'll be clear.
I can't use it anymore from next week.
If the title comes out all at once,
Let's get into the story.
Oh, really?
Oh, it's okay.
I told Saito-chan.
Saito-chan, you like the outside, right?
Oh, really?
I told him.
I told Nozawa and Hyoudo to film you.
So, that's it for today.
Thank you very much.