An emergency special program
Matsumoto vs. Hamada, Men's Big Game Special
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors
The winner is...
Start
Matsumoto wins
Stop, draw
Start
Matsumoto wins
Wait
Stop, draw
Matsumoto wins
Hamada wins
Start
Matsumoto wins
I don't know how to do this
I've never done this before
I'm scared
It's hot
It's not cool
Can you do this?
Can you?
Yes
Hamada wins
Ready, start
It's hot
Start
Matsumoto wins
I can't do this
Start
It hurts
Why do I always do this?
It hurts so much
Sorry
And then
Matsumoto wins
I don't want to do this
Ready, start
It's hot
No
Really?
Matsumoto wins
Hamada wins
Ready, start
How do I do this?
I can't do this
Matsumoto wins
Start
I can't do this
It's dirty
What should I do?
First, Hamada
Then Matsumoto
I can do this?
Change
Okay
I can't do this
I'm nervous
Okay, Matsumoto
Really?
It hurts
Okay, change
Really?
Okay, draw
Draw
It's swollen
Start
Okay, draw
Draw
Haya-mukashi-no-ada-nayobi
Matsumoto wins
Start
It's bad
Matsumoto wins
Start
It's really bad
This
I can't do this
Matsumoto wins
It hurts
Start
It's really bad
It hurts
Ahhhh!
This is the last round. See you next week!
The two of them will continue their competition.
Ready, start!
I don't know.
This is red.
This is cheap.
I don't eat umeboshi.
This is red.
Eat it quickly.
I want to eat it quickly.
It's a voice for you.
Kazumoto wins.
Let's go.
Start.
It's a celebration.
Let's see.
I don't know if I can do it.
It's good.
I can't lose.
You win.
OK.
I can't do this.
We are very scared of blindfolds.
I don't know.
I'm very scared.
We are very scared of blindfolds.
What should I do?
Are you ready?
Wait a minute.
This is for you.
No.
Start.
I'm very scared.
I can't do this.
It hurts.
It hit the glass.
I don't need that.
It's scary, so it doesn't hit the glass.
Hold it.
I can't do this.
Let's finish this quickly.
I don't know.
Don't say that.
I'm very angry.
I really don't know.
I'm very scared.
What?
What are you scared of?
Let's finish this quickly.
I'm very scared.
I can't do this.
Let's finish this quickly.
Wait a minute.
Ready?
Start.
I can't do this.
Let's finish this quickly.
Ready?
Start.
It hit the glass.
You should do it.
Start.
It hurts.
Can you leave me alone?
Hamada lead.
It hurts.
Oh my god.
I get angry sometimes.
Marathon.
You did a marathon on TV, right?
I did it in Tokyo International Marathon.
You should do it.
You were driving a truck, right?
It was a marathon.
Why didn't you drive outside?
Why did you stop the car for that?
Why didn't you stop the car for that?
Don't you remember?
I don't remember.
You should drive 42.195km, right?
That's right.
intelligent.
That's your fault.
Don't you remember the Goro show?
You should do thecho-cho.
Your smile turns red.
You told me.
I said you could do.
I heard you listen to music.
My friend told me at R OMG.
Can you drive 48.195km, my friend?
Have you ever done 48?
Have you?
Really, I don't get it.
No, it's not like that.
What are you doing?
Well, how should I put it...
This country...
Let's cut the country.
It's a country with a majority, right?
It's more than a small number of people...
What are you saying?
Isn't that right?
It's a country where you can't beat 100 people by yourself.
And yet, you still think you know it.
Even though you're a seaman, you only know about the population of the marathon.
Compared to people who can't ride cars or people who get caught in traffic,
you're completely different.
But you still prioritize the marathon.
You don't get it.
It's because I don't listen.
I think it's better to quit.
Everyone should listen.
But you think so, right?
You know that what I'm saying is right, right?
No.
Why?
There's nothing.
What kind of youth is this?
What kind of youth have you been through?
That's none of your business.
What are you eating?
That's right.
This is the New Year's Eve in Japan.
The New Year's Eve in the world.
Even if you say that, the place you're running is different.
That's different.
It's the same no matter where you do it.
It doesn't make sense if you don't do it under the same conditions.
It's the same as a baseball stadium.
It's the same.
Right?
You get it, right?
It's the same.
That's strange.
Let's get rid of it together.
It doesn't make sense.
Why?
When I was doing the broadcast,
I went in like this.
You must have gone crazy.
Do you want to get caught?
Yes.
But you can come out right away, right?
Well, I'm doing it.
You must have gone crazy.
Your pants are all over the place.
Are you waiting for that moment?
You can't do that.
It's really strange.
I wonder what it's like.
Running, swimming, riding a bicycle.
You don't know what it's like, do you?
I don't know.
At first, you swim and come back.
You ride a bicycle and run at the end.
It's a mess in the second half.
Well, it's a mess.
It's not like that.
It's a plan.
That's strange.
It doesn't make sense.
It makes sense.
It makes sense one by one.
It's okay to run all the time.
Why don't you swim?
It's not like that.
Which one do you use?
I want you.
It's strange.
Do you suddenly think like this?
I don't think so.
I'm going.
It's strange.
No one does that.
At the end, you cry.
Well, it's okay.
I don't do it for fun.
Do your best.
Which one do you use?
When you go to a hair salon,
if someone asks you,
what are you going to do today?
How do you answer?
Is it cool?
Of course, there are many cool words.
I don't understand the meaning of cool.
It depends on the dimension.
Well,
it depends on the person's lifestyle.
Do it like this.
Do it again.
Do it properly.
It depends on the environment.
I see.
For example,
if someone asks you,
what would you say?
If it's something you always say,
it's okay.
Then it's not cool at all.
What is it?
That's what I don't understand.
What is cool?
For example,
you have a child.
When someone asks you,
what do you want him to do?
It doesn't matter what happens to me.
Buy me a son.
It's cool.
You are waiting for the right moment.
You are going to the public bath.
It's not cool.
When you go to the public bath,
how do you make it look cool?
I see.
You sit down.
When someone asks you,
what do you want him to do?
I see.
It's different from other people.
It depends on the person.
It depends on the person,
but I'm more beautiful than that.
That's enough.
You have to say it.
That's right.
What do you want him to do?
There are many things,
but today...
Today...
It's cool, isn't it?
Yes.
Today...
Make it messy.
Yes.
That's not what I mean.
Make me messy.
That's why the situation is different.
In the first episode...
The two people who are rivals
are fighting like this.
It's Masota vs. Masota.
It's a three-on-three fight.
I'm not going to lose.
Because it's the New Year.
The first event is
a flying box battle.
Why did you blow up the box?
Come on.
It's okay if you get caught by Mr. Muzo.
How is it?
Okay.
What are you going to do?
Do you have a mask?
No.
It's because it's a little cold.
I've never played.
No way.
What's that?
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Wait a minute.
It hurts.
What are you going to do?
I prepared a hammer throw.
Mr. Ikemoto.
In the first episode,
the two people who are rivals
are fighting like this.
It's Masota vs. Masota.
It's a three-on-three fight.
I'm not going to lose.
It's a hammer throw.
It looks good.
No way.
I won.
14 meters.
Thank you very much.
There's smoke coming out.
It's scary.
If I didn't have a hammer,
I wouldn't have won.
Why is it exploding one by one?
I can't pay for it this time.
What is this?
It's a strange taste.
What should I do?
How about a hammer throw?
How many times can you do it?
This is enough.
Is that okay?
That's fine.
Really?
In the first episode,
the two people who are rivals
are fighting like this.
It's a three-on-three fight.
I'm not going to lose.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.