GAKUYA before the show.
As usual, he had a hard time in the opening show.
However, Mr.Hitoshi Matsumoto wanted to do something.
What should I do?
I've tried a lot of things.
Recently, I've been away from the challenge.
I want to participate in the challenge series this time.
Mr.Hitoshi Matsumoto has succeeded in many challenges so far.
What kind of challenge will he do this time?
I ran up the stairs on a motorcycle.
Many people say that I succeeded in many challenges.
But I didn't think it was that big a deal.
Let's not talk about dangerous things.
Let's not talk about big things.
I have a different way of thinking.
The meaning of the word Dantan comes from the word Kamihitoe.
That's a good idea.
This is a talk show, right?
No, it's not.
It's a stunt show.
I want to die.
In a sense, right?
What are you talking about?
Even if you say that, if you listen to my challenge today, I think you'll think it's a good idea.
That's right.
Speaking of summer, what is it?
I've been thinking about it since last week.
Speaking of summer, it's a roller coaster.
Why is it a roller coaster in the summer?
I'm going to be pulled by a roller coaster this time.
This is summer, isn't it?
That's strange.
A Japanese summer windmill, a roller coaster.
Will it be able to overcome this 10-ton wheel?
It's a desperate challenge for a roller coaster.
Are you okay?
I think it's okay.
Why?
Are you okay?
I think it's breathing.
If you come to Lamaze 4, Lamaze 4.
If a roller coaster comes at just the right time to breathe, I think you can go there.
Is it okay?
What?
I'm going to die.
No, it doesn't have to do with ratings.
I want to do it again.
That's true.
I can't help it if I want to do it.
I'm going to die.
Really.
Please.
I don't know.
Even if you don't know, I want you to see it.
I'm not doing it.
I want to do it.
I'll do it.
I really don't know.
Okay.
Do it.
I'll see it.
Do you understand?
With Matsumoto Hitoshi, who is determined to die, he heads to the scene.
Hitoshi's whole body is stiff because of the extreme tension.
Is it okay this time?
Unexpected anxiety surpasses Hitoshi's ability.
Hamada can't hide his anxiety in this reckless challenge.
Something's wrong with your skin.
Hitoshi wants to get some air outside, so he shows his face from the window.
He desperately fights against the anxiety that comes just before the show.
Hitoshi, what are you looking at now?
He's late.
Let's eat.
You're ready, aren't you?
If you don't hurry up, it'll be too late.
Let's hurry up.
There's a talk.
Here it comes.
It's coming.
He's good.
He's really strong.
That's right.
I saw you racing yesterday, but I'm sure you'll die.
I don't know.
It's dangerous.
Are you okay?
Okay.
It's better to talk.
I'm focused.
Look at the roller coaster over there.
Look at the roller coaster.
Did you get in?
Please stop.
What are you doing?
It's okay.
Get out of the way.
It's dangerous.
I don't care.
I'll do it.
It's okay.
Let's go.
Let's do it properly.
There's a talk.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
Please start the engine.
Let's go.
I've been waiting.
It's okay.
Let's start the engine.
Thank you for the great adventure.
We will never forget your courage and your way of life.
Thank you very much.
This program is brought to you by the sponsor you are watching.
Ladies and gentlemen.
What a wonderful figure.
Look at this.
Pretend you're wearing it.
I'm not wearing it at all.
I'll wear it if I wear it.
If I don't wear it, I'll leave it in the dressing room.
But I don't care.
I don't care.
I want you.
Here.
It's nice.
It's a nice figure.
Is that so?
I'm a little annoyed these days.
I've been doing a lot of Takanohana bashing.
The other day, right?
I kicked the wall.
I poured water on it.
I've been doing it.
That's a Takanohana bashing.
I don't care.
I see.
That's what you think.
But.
And.
What is next?
Well.
Yokozuna and?
Let's start from the top.
Are the top three worst?
Well.
What is it?
What is the next best?
Ozeki.
Yokozuna should be put here, right?
Yes.
Yokozuna.
Sekiwake.
Komusubi.
Wonderful!
I don't know much, so I can't be stupid.
I'm scared of saying things I don't know.
If I say it, I'll get hit.
If you say it, you'll get hit.
It's a battle field.
That's strange. I've been waiting for you.
G-5 threw a bat at the ball.
What?
What do you mean he threw a bat?
What are you doing with a fresh ball?
You guys are kicking that fresh ball.
I just threw a ball and threw it.
That's strange.
For example, if you throw a bat at a man you're looking at, he'll get angry.
Of course.
But even if you kick a man, he'll get angry.
Why do you make a soccer ball and a man two?
A man has nothing to do with it.
But it's an elephant.
You have something to say about that, right?
What?
Are you interested?
I was doing it.
You're just saying nonsense.
When did you do it?
I didn't do it, but I can't complain.
I don't know about that, but you're doing it like this.
What does that mean?
What do you mean?
I just said what do you mean.
Why do you say what do you mean right away?
You do this after you win, right?
I do it about three times.
Does that mean anything?
Of course it does.
Mom.
It's my dad's line.
I can say it now.
You said mom three times.
No, no, no.
Mom, dad.
Right?
Who is it?
Say it.
Relatives.
That's not true.
There's a reason for that.
Thank you.
Really.
I understand that.
Why do you say that?
Ah.
It's about Sagariko.
Sagariko?
Did you just say Sagariko?
What?
It's a Japanese national flag.
Before I go to Tokyo, I say Sagariko to Tsukibito.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Yes, it's Sagariko.
4,800 yen.
That's cheap.
It's not cheap.
It's expensive.
It's cheap. 4,800 yen.
Does it make sense?
Of course it does.
Why are you wearing it?
Can I say that?
What?
I don't know. I want to hear it.
Can I say that?
Who are you talking to?
No?
There's a reason for that.
You were laughing.
I was laughing.
I did all of it.
What are your special skills?
You're really stupid.
If you have a special skill, it means you have a special skill that you're not good at.
If you go back to the beginning.
I'm the almighty.
So I can't choose what my special skill is.
So what are the skills you've been doing frequently?
Skills I've been doing frequently?
Yes.
Can I say that?
Kama Soto Gari.
Kama Soto Gari?
From Kama Soto Gari to Uchi Gake.
Uchi Wake.
Which one?
That's more interesting.
From Kama Soto Gari to Uchi Wake.
Uchi Wake?
Can you do it for me?
From Kama Soto Gari to Uchi Wake.
What do you do?
First of all, how do I get into your voice?
Just go in like this.
Wait a minute.
Can I step on you?
You can step on me.
From Kama Soto Gari to...
This is Kama Soto Gari.
From the outside.
Kama Soto Gari.
It's beautiful.
Draw a circle.
From there, Uchi Wake.
What is Uchi Wake?
In the end, it's a fortune of 4800 yen.
Who is that Uchi Wake?
You say that to people, but do you play sports?
I don't play.
I sometimes play golf.
I stopped playing once.
No, I don't understand the rules of golf.
When you decide the path, you shouldn't go sideways.
You don't have to go sideways.
But even if you just walk like this, you'll say,
It's like I'm standing on my own.
No, no.
If you step on it and go,
I think it's a little hooked.
After that, I think it's a little sliced.
I don't know if there is such a thing.
Then the ball line changes.
I don't know if the ball line changes.
If that's how the ball line changes,
Don't do that.
Why?
With a small stone.
But you did it once and quit.
There was no such scene once.
You quit because you didn't hit the ball.
No.
You hit it.
I didn't hit it.
No, you didn't.
No matter how strange it is, you hit it.
It just so happened that the hole was over there.
If it was over here, it was in.
No, it just so happened that the hole was over here.
You hit it with your eyes open.
No.
I was aiming for my own hole.
No, no, no.
What are you talking about?
There's only one.
You hit it with your eyes open.
No.
You guys were aiming for your own hole.
I don't want to do the same thing as you.
Everyone does the same thing.
No, no, no.
I don't want to do the same thing as you.
No, no.
You were aiming for your own hole.
I don't want to do that.
I was aiming for my own hole.
Why are you so hard on him?
Japanese people lie right away.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to burn you.
I can't change my mind.
Hey.
Ignore.
I don't care.
Aren't you Japanese?
No.
I've been wondering about this for a while.
There are many rescue ships in the mountains of the Alps.
There's a small barrel hanging around your neck.
What is that small barrel?
What is that?
St. Bernard.
That's right.
What is the purpose of the dogs?
Isn't there alcohol in the barrel?
That's a mistake.
Isn't it?
There's no doubt about the barrel.
The reason I chose this document is because there's a big mistake.
Is it a mistake?
You've seen a barrel, haven't you?
Yes, yes, yes.
What is a barrel?
It's something like this.
The big one.
It's a barrel.
But there's a small one.
No, no, no.
That's a big barrel hanging around your neck.
It's small.
No, no, no.
It's not a small barrel.
It's a dog hanging around your neck.
No, no, no.
No, no.
It's a small barrel.
Who is it?
Is it your grandmother?
It's your grandmother, isn't it?
It's a small barrel.
It's a big barrel.
No, no, no.
It's a dog hanging around your neck.
It's a big barrel.
You see a dog hanging around your neck on TV, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Why don't you think it's a big dog?
Why don't you think it's a small barrel?
The dog is big.
It's about this big.
How can it be a big dog?
Is it about this big?
Yes.
This is a question for Mr. Hamada.
When I see your comments, I'm surprised because I see Mr. Matsumoto's forehead and his nose.
What?
I heard that you have 15 other comments.
I do?
What kind of comments do you have?
Like this.
It used to be like this.
And then, like this.
And here and here at the same time.
Wait.
Does it hurt?
A little bit more.
Ah, sorry.
And what else?
It's strange.
Like this.
It used to be like this.
Well, it used to be like this.
A little bit more.
Right now, I'm not fooling around.
I'm not going to do that.
You know, right?
Yes, I know.
I know everything.
It's Hamada-kun, right?
That's right.
You know me, right?
Matsumoto-kun.
Okay, okay.
Well, there are things like that.
There are, right?
What else is there?
Other than that...
In my way...
In your way, there are 15 things, right?
Well...
A little bit more.
A little bit more?
It hurts so much.
The audience might get angry.
But I was laughing.
You know, I can't bring my hand to my forehead right now, right?
Right now.
It hurts.
Do you know why?
I don't know.
I feel like I'm bleeding.
There's something I don't understand.
Why does Love Hotel take 2 hours?
Well, isn't it about 2 hours?
Oh, is that so?
Well, you can take a bath, too.
Together?
Well, it's an individual service.
If you're always doing it, you should take a bath together.
I've never taken a bath with a girl.
Have you ever taken a bath together?
Yes, I have.
I'm an old man.
Why?
I think there are a lot of things to decide with an old man.
Am I one of them?
It's an old man to take a bath with a woman.
Is that so?
I'm an old man.
And I'm old enough to eat sushi while laughing.
I'm young enough to do that.
Young enough to do that?
That's...
That's true.
No.
It's funny.
It's funny to talk.
While laughing.
That's an old man.
That's not true.
Old men eat sushi while laughing.
That's true.
That's not true.
You're like a kindergarten kid.
Naginagi-chan.
Ko-chan, Ko-chan.
Is that true?
That's true.
Old man.
That's...
That's a funny way to do it.
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.