The next day
This straw is the same as the straw that came during the power outage
What do you mean?
The straw that came during the power outage
Last week?
Ah, that's right
It's the same
Then why didn't you say it a week ago?
It's not like you're going to say it now
It's a bit small
Why?
What?
Why did you come again?
I'm sorry
That's none of our business
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors
I don't know what's going to happen
If you say that, I don't know if I'm going to get angry here
I want you to get angry
I really want you to get angry
My back hurts
Really?
It's been a while since I had a backache
To be honest, this isn't the time to be talking
I want to go back to Ichimoku-san
What's wrong with that?
I want to go back barefoot
I don't want to go barefoot
I'm really sorry
Do you have any feelings?
I don't have any reason
You just have a backache?
I have a backache
To be honest
Really?
That's right
What are you doing?
What did you do to your partner?
I don't know if my back hurts
I've never had a backache
Do you have any feelings? This is really hard
Right now, it's about level 2
I've been to level 8
No, it's about level 7
Where's the highest level?
At that time...
I don't know
It's level 6
That's your goal
I don't know
It's level 6
It's really hard to brush your teeth
Humans don't notice unless they're worried
It's okay if you do it like this
If you do it like this, it's okay
You can't bend over
You can do it like this
What do you mean?
You can do it like a man
You can do it like this
But it's not always like that
It's hard to wash your hair
I see
Why don't you take a shower and do it like this?
That's right
You have to do it like this
Like this
It's really hard
You can't do it at once
Really?
You can't do it at 23
You can do it at 22
I'm sorry
I can do it at any age
You can do it at any age
You can do it at 20
You can do it at 2 or 3
You can do it at 10
That's the only way
In the morning when I was about to put on my socks
When I was about to put on my socks
I heard a thud
It came suddenly so I had to be careful
You fell?
I fell
I heard a thud
From there?
From there
Really?
Really
I can't do it anymore
It doesn't hurt
I'm not saying it hurts
No
If you stay still it will hurt
It hurts
It's flickering
It's tingling
That's not it
It can't be helped
If you get more tired it will hurt more
That's fine
I'm sorry
You don't have to say it
Really
This year the cherry blossoms bloomed quickly
That's right
That's good
How was it? Did you see the cherry blossoms?
I didn't
You didn't?
I didn't see the cherry blossoms
You didn't see the cherry blossoms
I'm sorry but to be honest
I don't think the cherry blossoms are pretty
What is it?
The people who are excited
That's the only way
What do you mean?
There's no other way than drinking and getting excited
The cherry blossoms are pretty when you look at them from a distance
What do you do when you dive into them?
You can see them even if you don't dive
You don't see them, right?
You only look at them like this
No, you can see them
It's the first time I've seen them from a distance
You didn't say they were pretty
I want them to be bigger
The villas
They're big
If they were even bigger, I'd be even more excited
You'd be excited even if you didn't drink
If they were this big
They're amazing
If they were this big, I'd be excited
That's no good
I'm really sorry
No, it's okay
I'm sorry
Let's move on
He hasn't introduced himself yet
Right?
If there was a Japanese Katsura leader, I'd definitely ask Matsumoto-san
When do you buy Katsura?
Everyone doesn't know much about Katsura, right?
What do you mean?
I read a book about people wearing Katsura
There's a story about it
There's something about it
For example, if you say you bought a new car
It's obvious
If you say, how are you doing?
They'd say, I'm not doing well
But you don't say, I bought a new Katsura
So no one asks about the Katsura
So no one knows about the Katsura
It's information that can't be leaked
There's a lot of things that people can't talk about
Do you buy Katsura?
There are only people who buy Katsura
Where did you buy it?
That's fine, but they're all individual players
They'd say, this guy, this guy
You know who's wearing it, right?
Yes, I know
Definitely
They'd say, I don't like it
Even in the elevator, they'd say, I don't know what to do
But you can't say either
I know
That's the sad part
You made it for yourself, didn't you?
Yes, that's right
It hurts a lot
In the winter morning
Why?
It hurts so much
I don't want to do it
But you can't help it
You can't not wear it
When I wake up in the morning, if it hurts, I wear it
But in the afternoon, I wear it
So you wear it once
Yes, once it's warm
You can't do that
In the winter, the wind is strong
You can't wear it in a post
You can't
Why not?
It's really hard
Did you know? Katsura only wears a button
You can take it off if you wear it
There are times when you have to take it off
Katsura never wears a V-shape
He only wears buttons
It's not like that
Even if you look here, you can't tell
You can't tell
It's really hard
He said it's hard if you sweat
There's no one who doesn't have anything
It's definitely growing
There's some left
You wear it
If you sweat, your hair will get wet
But Katsura doesn't get wet
It's obviously wet from here
Katsura doesn't get wet
That duality is amazing
He said that
He said it, didn't he?
He wrote it
It's really hard
I see
Tell me when to buy it
Damn
I wonder if this will end
When will you buy it?
Tell me when to buy it
Of course there are times when you have to buy it
There are times when you don't know what to buy
There are
For example, when you have to buy pants
Yes
When it gets dirty
That's right
That's when you have to buy it
I don't know
It's when you have to buy a bra
This bra is no good
What do you mean?
Even if you wear it normally, your nipples are sticking out
You have to wear it twice
If you wear it properly, your nipples will stick out
Does a bra make your nipples stick out?
I don't think so
I want to hear it
I want to hear a bra
Are you sick of it?
I'm sick of it
I'm sick of this pattern
Is that so?
It's not like that
The fabric is coming off
My nipples hurt
The cup
Are you going to change it?
You can't fix the cup
It's like this
I don't do it many times
It's the inside
If you change it, it's over
I don't know
When I buy a bra
I want to know more than Katsura
Yes
The pattern is coming off
When it gets dirty
That's when you have to buy it
Really?
Yes
It doesn't last that long?
It doesn't last that long
People who have money have a version
Yes
Like summer or winter
A version with long hair
Well
That's right
If you don't wear a long version
You'll be told to go to the market
Everyone will think that
I'll go to the market
I'll change it to a short version
I'll go back
If you change it to a short version
You'll have a long version
That's amazing
I don't know what to say
It's so annoying
I'm worried
It's scary
It's a kind of threat
It's not a threat
It's a threat
If you can say it, say it
I can't say it
There are people who are important
Hamada
Right?
Yes
Actually
I'll do it like this
Your posture is strange
Why are you doing it like this?
When I say it, I do it like this
When I say it, I'll do it like this
I'll do it like this
Hamada, I won't do it
This is not me
This is me
I have a question for you
You are the only one who knows that
Please teach me the transformation pose of Kamen Rider Eros
It's interesting
Kamen Rider Eros
Please teach me
What is it?
More than the transformation pose
What is Kamen Rider Eros?
What does it look like?
To be honest, there is a shocker
All of them are naked women
If the shocker's father is shaking
I won't shake your father forever
What kind of clothes does Kamen Rider Eros wear?
I only wear underwear
There is no reason to transform
If you transform, you won't only wear underwear
Really?
I only wear underwear
I'm just a pervert
I'm following the rules
Do you want to stop?
It's not red yet
I'm doing it
Please teach me the transformation pose
Sure
What does it look like?
I'm only wearing underwear
Kamen Rider Eros
If the shocker's father is shaking
There is a woman like this
I found it
I'm doing it
Shake your father more
I'm walking like this
Say something
I didn't do anything
You said shake your father more
Say something
I always think
When a hero comes out
He gets beaten up
He doesn't do anything
I see
I don't like that
It's discrimination
He looks bad
There were a lot of monsters
I didn't do anything
There was one
I was just looking out the window
There was a game
It was a game
I was looking out the window
I wasn't looking out the window
It was so bad
No
I was just looking
I was just looking out the window
I was surprised
So
Teach me the transformation pose
You have to transform
Of course
It's okay
I'll do it
You guys are not evidence
Right?
Yes
You guys are not evidence
Wait a minute
This hero
This hero is bad
Is it bad?
I won't let you do what you want
It's dangerous
Don't do that
Every year at this time
I feel like there are a lot of road construction
I heard that you are looking for something
other than the purpose of fixing the road
What are you looking for?
This is
Well
It's been a while
Should I decide?
Your nose is sticking out
I think it's better to decide than to wait
Really?
Yes
It's just a road construction
I'm not looking for anything
Well
If I say this
It's too obvious
To be honest
I'm too cool
I don't want to be hugged
It's okay
What?
Your nipples are sticking out
I'm excited
Why are you excited?
I'm too cool
Can I decide after a long time?
Are you looking for something?
What do you mean by deciding?
I'll decide right away
I see
Can I say that?
Go ahead
It's a road construction
That road construction
Well
Can I decide?
You should decide as soon as possible
If you wait too long, you will
That is
I'm looking for organs
Even if it's organs
It's annoying
It's tax
What is this way of deciding?
I haven't decided
I haven't said it
You've decided, haven't you?
Well
Hey
You've decided, haven't you?
If everyone's applause and laughter say so
It's okay
Why do you look like you've taken a step back?
You've decided
Everyone is doing this
Why can't you do it together?
I'm doing it
Let's do it together more
Yes
Follow me
Hey
Yes
I beg you
If you do it again, I'll decide
Let's do it together
Really?
Yes
Actually
I'm looking for organs
Don't say it's tax
My face is dead
Did the audience have it?
You can't do it at all
I'm sorry
Do your best
I'm laughing
Well
Are you ready?
I'll do Kamen Rider Eros
Eros?
Eros is embarrassing
Hold it, Deshi
Me?
I don't have a beard or a shape
It's Yasu-san
Yasu-san is doing it
If Yasu-san says, hold it, Deshi, I'll throw it back
You have to throw it back
Kamen Rider Eros
Yes
Let's do it
I'm just waiting
OK
You don't have memory
It's hard
What?
It's easy
Don't choose easy
I don't have Eros
Don't say it's hard
I can do it
OK
It's amazing
It's dangerous
Change it
If you change it, it's easy
Because I don't have anything
Idiot
This program was brought to you by these sponsors