Ladies and gentlemen.
Today was a tough day.
It was a tough day.
I think those who are here already know this.
Last week, at 6 o'clock,
I said to Alta, come to the front.
I put out a teleprompter under the program.
At 6 o'clock, I did a teleprompter.
Before that, there were a lot of people.
I couldn't see them.
It was painful.
If I had gone to Alta today,
I would have done teleprompter.
Idiot.
Do you have such energy?
How many people will go?
Are you ready?
In the end, I couldn't broadcast it.
There were too many people.
I'm going to the bathroom.
It hurts.
I will hold your hand.
I will beat you.
What a pain.
At 1 o'clock in the afternoon, watch Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai, okay?
Watch Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai, okay?
If a cow gets killed for something like this, it won't do anything, right?
Even though we know the name, we don't really know what it is.
It hurts.
It hurts, doesn't it?
What kind of game software is this?
It's a software touch, the rope.
Really? Is it like this these days?
I used to play it a lot when I was a kid.
You're lying!
Masato-san!
Yes?
Yano-san, I'm going to tie you up here.
Hey, don't eat it!
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
Shut up!
It hurts! It hurts!
I'm going to pinch your hand!
Ah, it hurts!
Look, look!
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
Shut up!
This is good!
This is the best!
This is the shape of the camera.
It was fast.
If you write the letter Man here, it's the Man of soy sauce.
This is good.
That's all.
Thank you for your hard work.
Yano-san did a good job today.
Yes.
I'll do a proper promotion for my show.
Thank you very much.
Yano-san, let's go this way next time.
Our show is over.
Kayo... Kayo's 1 o'clock...
What?
What time is it?
Kayo's midnight is 1 o'clock and 40 minutes.
I don't know how to write.
Please watch it.
Do you want to watch a show like this?
What?
Kayo's 1 o'clock and 40 minutes.
I don't know how to write.
Please watch it.
I see.
I was really embarrassed.
I was more embarrassed than Nyororo.
It was close.
It was a waste.
Let's think of something.
This is this.
Yes.
Let's take it to Shibuya.
109.
Really?
This?
This.
I've done the same thing many times.
You're not cool.
I'm looking forward to it, Hama-chan.
What are you talking about?
You know it yourself.
You know you have to make me do something.
Well, it was like this.
Yes.
Kayo-san, are you here?
Thank you very much.
Let's do something again.
If we gather like this, we can do something on this show.
Yes.
Other than that.
We don't have to open our eyes.
We can do something in a big hall.
That's good.
I don't know about this.
I think you said it.
Let's do something.
An event.
Yes.
Something exciting.
An event?
Yes.
You're right.
In April of next year,
I want to take a bus or something like that.
I'm going to study.
I don't want to do that.
Why?
I don't want to force myself to do that.
I don't want to.
Let's do it.
I'm going to help you.
What are you talking about?
I don't want to do that.
Why?
I'm going to go to university.
You're going to go to university.
Let's get a certificate.
A certificate.
On this show.
Isn't it?
Certificate.
Yes.
Something special.
Something something.
I can makeRadio.
Like farting.
Covering your face like this.
fails the grade.
It's not bad, but how're you going to shoot.
Something at the set shouldn't do.
Before the show.
It means...
That's right. That's one of the reasons why I can't do anything about it.
Well, I'd like to think about it again.
I'm really sorry about today.
It can't be helped.
Yes.
Well, let's lower this a little bit.
Well, in that case, what shall we do after this?
What shall we do after this?
Yes.
Well, the postcard...
Shibitori? That's not good.
That's enough.
What about the postcard?
Let's read the postcard.
Let's take a picture of it.
Here you are. What do you think about today's postcard?
What is this?
Where have you been hiding until now?
What?
How old are you?
Four years old?
Yes.
What's your name?
I'm Aya Suzuki.
What?
Aya Suzuki?
Yes.
What?
Oh, this is it.
This is it.
There's a picture in it.
Oh, you're looking for an assistant?
Yes, an assistant.
This is it.
Her name is Aya Suzuki.
My wife and I are big fans of Downtown.
We were offered to be the assistant of the program.
She accepted it.
Are you kidding me?
She didn't accept it.
My wife and I were offered to be the assistant of the program.
Is that so?
Which do you like, Aya?
Why do you like this man?
What do you like about him?
What?
You don't know?
What do you like about him?
I can't talk to you anymore.
It's been a long time since I last saw you.
You look like a young girl.
I see.
Aya, thank you for coming again.
Where did you come from?
Tokyo.
Do you know that?
Where in Tokyo?
A hotel.
A hotel?
A love hotel?
What's with your reaction?
It's like you know.
Is that so?
When you grow up, I'll marry you.
Don't do that.
You'll get a bad name.
I'm waiting for you.
Are you serious?
You can't lie to me.
You can't cheat on me.
I can't do that either.
Come again next time.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
I have one more.
I'll start with Nakano-kun.
Miwa-chan, Yuna-san.
Good evening, Matsumoto-san.
Good evening.
I always enjoy watching you.
A few weeks ago, you said that you were mistaken for the driver of the taxi, Hiromi-san.
Actually, when my mother was in the taxi, the driver made a mistake.
The driver said,
It's always hard, isn't it?
I was watching.
My mother replied,
It was hard to hear.
I said,
Thank you.
And the driver smiled at his mother again.
You're still being called a teacher, aren't you?
That's right.
My mother was mistaken for Tetsuya Takeda.
After my mother came home, she went to the barber shop and went back to the short hair.
Matsumoto-san, Matsumoto-san,
Did anyone else make a mistake?
Hey.
The worst mistake I've ever made was,
This is the best of all.
I think I've told myself once.
That was about six years ago.
Yokosuka incident.
I went to Yokosuka to shoot Mr. Donuts commercial.
That was Yokosuka, wasn't it?
Was it?
I was staying at a hotel in Yokosuka.
With my manager.
I was so hungry at night.
I couldn't stand it anymore.
There must be a Yoshinoya or something somewhere.
I thought I'd go.
I didn't even know his face.
I was walking around the hotel at about 2 o'clock at night.
There were about five middle school students.
I was a little drunk.
I didn't want to get involved in this mess.
I ignored it as much as I could.
I tried not to get involved.
One of them came up to me and said,
Yu-chan, where are you going?
I called you Yu-chan.
I don't know where Yu-chan is.
I thought, what's wrong with him?
I thought I'd quit right away.
I was walking all the way.
Yu-chan!
He kept following me.
He kept calling me Yu-chan.
It was a dark place.
No matter what I say now, he's drunk.
There's nothing I can do about it.
He came all the way to the bright place.
I'm not Yu-chan.
I'm going to make it clear to him.
I put up with the dark place.
To the bright place.
Yu-chan! Yu-chan!
He's been following me all the way.
When he came to the bright place,
What is it?
I looked back.
Yu-chan, don't get angry.
I know he's angry.
I know he's angry, but I don't know if he's not Yu-chan.
He ran away so much.
He ran away so much, he was in the town.
About two kilometers away.
You should go home.
You didn't want to eat jyu-don like that.
I didn't want to eat it.
He kept following me.
Yu-chan, don't get angry.
Don't be like that.
So I stopped and told him not to talk to me, and told him to come over here.
I'm not Yu-chan!
I'm talking, but you can tell, right? I'm from Osaka!
I'm Yu-chan!
I was so scared!
I was like, what the hell is Yu-chan talking about?
You were flustered.
I couldn't do anything about it.
So I kept thinking, I can't do this anymore, so I went back to the hotel.
I went back to the hotel, and when I got to the front of the hotel, Yu-chan, where are you going?
I'm going to get in trouble!
You can't do that, Yu-chan!
Really?
I'm telling the truth!
I'm starting to get angry.
So I went to the front of the hotel, and I had my keys.
And the hotel there was covered in glass.
You couldn't see it from the outside.
And when I was holding the keys at the front of the hotel, I was looking at it like this.
And when I got out of the elevator, went in, and closed the door...
What?
It's fun to watch people's movements, right?
Movements?
I call it movement.
There are a lot of things, right?
There's an old lady's toothpick.
I was so angry.
I can't just pull out my teeth and do this.
This hand was so angry.
The little finger was floating.
I knew what you were doing.
I knew you were doing it.
I was like, what is this?
But as a woman, it's normal to do this.
No matter how many times you do it.
But you put a lid on something that stinks.
What do you mean?
You put a lid on something.
No, no, no.
I'm trying to hide my dirty part.
I know that, so I don't think I need it anymore.
It's more annoying to be told that.
I don't want to be seen as a toothpick.
If that's the case, I'd do it like this when I'm writing here.
I can't do it.
It's not embarrassing to write here.
It's embarrassing to do it like this.
Why?
My teeth and gums are all out.
If I can take it out, I'll be in trouble.
I don't care if you hide it.
It's just a thing to do at 10 o'clock.
I'm writing here.
I know that.
It's more annoying.
I don't want to be seen as a toothpick.
If it's a nose, I'd do it like this.
I don't think it's good.
I don't want to be seen as a toothpick.
It's fun to watch that kind of thing.
When I went to Thailand before,
I was eating other people's food.
I was eating alone.
We were drinking beer together.
It was hot in the afternoon, so we went to Thailand.
The local person on the other side said,
There's a long spaghetti called pasta.
It's a combination of pasta and meat.
It's a good food to eat with the local person.
I usually eat pasta.
When I eat meat and vegetables together,
I eat it with a smile that I can't stand.
It's fun to watch that kind of thing while drinking beer.
It was fun the other day.
I went to a coffee shop.
I was shopping at Daimaru.
I had a bag.
I sat down.
I was drinking coffee.
I was looking at the paper bag.
Are you laughing?
I'm laughing.
I grabbed it.
I'm glad I did it.
I opened the ribbon.
You opened it.
I opened it.
I left the paper bag slowly.
I opened the paper bag slowly.
It's hard.
I understand.
I opened the ribbon.
There is a comb.
I pulled out the comb from the plastic bag.
What is this guy?
I wanted to go here as soon as possible.
That's funny.
I was in a car.
I was parking in Shingo-machi.
There is a comb from the other side.
There is a comb from both sides.
I was in a car.
There is a comb.
One person's comb.
I thought there was a comb.
There is another comb.
I was wrong.
This doesn't馴 análize anything.
Let's look at people together again.
It's time.
We've seen a nice thing here.
Let's think about something again.
Let's think about it next time.
Let's do it again.
Everyone, thank you very much for today.
Please come and see us again.
Hello.
I think the people who are watching the TV right now have noticed something.
What do you think of this?
You don't look back.
Actually, this is the front, but the back is like this.
Staff G.
Staff G has been completed.
I haven't decided on a gift yet, so if you want it, give me a postcard.
I'll do it when I'm in the team.
I don't know what it's like to look at the postcard.
I'll do it when I look at the postcard.
This one.
I'm waiting for the postcard.
I'll think about it after that.
For the time being, the staff and we all have it.
Everyone is coming.
It's okay.
Because it costs a lot of money.
That's right.
At that time, the girl will be an assistant.
I think that kind of thing is also possible.
I'm still looking for an assistant.
Yes.
I'll send it to you.
That's all I have to say.
That's all for this time.
Goodbye.
This program was brought to you by Sunlux and the sponsor you are watching.