The incident is always sudden
Manager Shimizu came in before the recording
The chief manager Okamoto is calling everyone again
Emergency special project manager Okamoto is angry again
Okamoto suddenly stopped last time and asked for reverse bungee
His anger seems to have subsided
Why are you telling me to do bungee?
3, 2, 1, go!
What is his purpose this time?
This program is brought to you by the sponsor
Where are we today?
I'm a little scared
You are a little fast
Don't come!
You are very fast
I've been doing it for a year
I thought I was doing it for a year
What is this?
I've done it 3 times
Okamoto is very serious
After the incident, I was in a good mood
I felt like I could do it again
I didn't say anything at the scene
I was surprised
Did I look like I wanted to do it again?
I was looking at it with my eyes
I was looking at it with my eyes this time, but I didn't know
Let's go home
The scene is close
An inexplicable anxiety touched everyone's hearts for a moment
Over there
Over there?
Where?
I'm here
It's hot
Over here?
When we finally arrived at the scene, we looked for Okamoto
There he is
Hurry up
Run
I have to run
What are you doing?
Come closer
I don't know you
I'm your manager
What are you talking about?
I know you
What are you doing?
I'm fixing it
It's easier if you do it by hand
I can't do it by hand
It's strange
You guys are not doing well
All of us?
Yes, the cast and the staff
Are you too lazy?
It's dangerous
Sorry to keep you waiting
He's not doing anything
He's hungry
He's walking
Hamada
Have you been working lately?
Look, he's angry
Why are you walking?
That's why you're slacking off
This is the second time you're angry
Why are you angry?
Wait
What?
He's angry
I don't care about the cat
Let him go
Look at that
The numbers here
It's good
Why can't I get 20?
It's 0.1
It's 24
Here
Sorry
I see
0.1
You're noisy
I'll do the opening
Can I do it?
It's the manager's line
No
Why are you doing this to me?
I don't want to do it
We don't even think about it
0.1
It's hard
You have 20 in your head
It's close
Let me do the giant guillotine
I'll do it
I don't need you
Manager Okamoto challenges the giant guillotine
Wait
Is this it?
Yes
This is impossible
This is bad
The giant guillotine is 15 meters high
It falls at a speed of 80 km
You don't have to do it
I'll do it
I'll make a good face
Let me do it
0.1
It's ok
I'll do the giant guillotine
I have a camera here
I can make a good reaction
It's up
Okamoto
Are you ready?
I'll do it
5, 4, 3, 2, 1
Start
Okamoto
It's amazing
It's good
It's Okamoto
He's looking at me
Wait
Are you doing the next one?
The next one?
You were doing our reaction
Our reaction is not good
Just look at me
He's angry
I can't see his teeth
That's right
I'm sorry
3, 2, 1
Start
It hurts
Are you ok?
You're not angry anymore, are you?
I'm good
I can do it
What do you mean?
My face
I can do it
You passed 20
Yes
I got it
Here?
Let's go
Excuse me
Thank you
Hey
I passed 20
I don't know how to do it
Take this off
Hey
Can I do it?
He's crazy
It's hard
Animals are crazy
Chimpanzees are crazy
The chimpanzees are crazy
They are happy
I don't know if they are happy
They are crazy
There is no one who can do it
There is no one
They say chimpanzees are crazy
But that's not true
They don't like being reacted
A smart chimpanzee is like this
It's just a short story
You can sit down
But he welcomes you
He welcomes me?
Ah
Hey
He attacks me
He's so angry
He is so angry
He has the same temper
It's a welcome ceremony.
What?
You're eating a banana with your hand?
It's like, okay, okay.
But if you do it the other way, it's natural, right?
I'm getting paid for it with my hand.
For yourself?
You're getting paid for it.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's kind of nice.
I have a new project.
I don't really want to say it, but...
I'm going to throw a pie at various animals.
At first, an elephant.
I went to the elephant and did it right here.
I don't know what's so frustrating about that.
I don't think it's frustrating.
I thought it was hard, but there was a giraffe over there.
You saw it, didn't you?
The giraffe started to make a noise.
What should I do?
It's being thrown.
That's what I'm talking about.
Your friends are heavy, aren't they?
It's kind of like that.
It's a crocodile.
The crocodile came out like this.
If you do it like this, it's just like that.
It doesn't matter.
Well, yeah.
Animals are so stupid.
I don't know what to do with that.
They're so stupid.
It's not going to work on humans.
I don't know what they think.
What?
What do you mean?
I don't know what they think.
They're really low-education addicts, aren't they?
I'm not an addict.
It's a lot of work.
I guess so.
You don't clean, do you?
What do you mean?
Your house.
I clean my own room.
You don't like cleanliness, do you?
I like cleanliness.
That's not it.
Oh, it's stuck.
What's stuck?
I don't know.
I don't clean cleanliness.
I don't like getting dirty.
Oh, I see.
You know what?
They're all wrong here.
You say you like fish, right?
I like fish.
How many times do you eat grilled fish?
If you really like fish, you can't eat it.
If you say that, you can't eat anything.
You're so excited.
Damn it.
If we don't do it together, we can't do it.
That's why I'm worried.
Let's do a impersonation first.
Sure.
The one you like recently?
It's Toyokawa Etsushi.
I'm the only one who can impersonate him in Japan.
You said you liked it recently, but the audience is brainwashed.
Let's do Toyokawa Etsushi.
If it's Yamada-san's impersonation, the letter won't get through.
This is very similar.
Really?
It's amazing.
I'm the only one who can impersonate him in Japan.
It's Toyokawa Etsushi.
If it's Yamada-san's impersonation, the letter won't get through.
Let's do it.
If you want it, I'll give it to 200 people.
You should go to a bookstore and buy it.
I'll ask Mr. Matsumoto.
What is the fastest way to swim in the current water sports?
You haven't swum yet.
I've been swimming for a long time.
I was born underwater for the first time in Japan.
I'm sorry about that.
It can't be helped.
It was 31 or 32 years ago.
You've been swimming since then.
I still remember when I used water.
You didn't swim.
I did.
When?
I don't understand what you're saying.
When did you start?
I'm still swimming.
I don't understand what you're saying.
I only swim when I'm at work.
Basically, I'm underwater.
Where do you swim?
I swim in the pool.
In the pool?
Really?
I swim in the reservoir.
Where?
Don't go home.
You swim in the reservoir.
I don't care about that.
I just want to say that I can swim faster than a crawler.
I don't understand what you're saying.
Swim like a crawler.
This is the fastest.
It's no good.
Can you swim faster?
What's the fastest?
Like this.
What?
This is the fastest.
You just want to dance.
I just want to dance.
I swim like this.
I swim like this and I run like this.
Your posture has changed.
I'm swimming in the water.
What happened to your legs?
I was wondering if your legs were like this.
No.
They are like this.
Do you have someone you like?
No.
How much rock spirit do you think you have?
I'm a guitarist.
I'm not a guitarist.
I don't have a guitar today, so I can't help it.
I'm a guitarist.
Your posture is strange.
I've done almost everything you've ever done.
I'm a guitarist.
I smoke up here.
Young people are crazy about dancing.
With that performance?
Of course.
I've done a lot of pre-recording.
I went to A-chan's concert.
I want to see A-chan.
Have you ever done A-chan's concert?
That's right.
Go home! Go home!
Play A-chan!
But...
Your music is different from A-chan's.
Why can't you get on?
A-chan is good.
How many people have you done?
One.
Have you ever done someone's back?
Of course. I've done almost everything.
I've done almost everything.
Can you give me an example?
I've done a lot of things.
Sting, for example.
You're talking about a bad time.
How many people have you done?
Don't you know that?
You can't talk to that guy.
Can you tell me?
How many people have you done?
About four people.
Four people?
Sting, four people?
It's not four people. Why four people?
Calm down!
You're making me nervous.
What do you think you are?
I'm alone.
You don't think you're alone.
That's right. You're alone.
You laughed a lot today.
I was a little confused.
Okay, okay.
Who else?
Most of them are over there.
You can tell me.
I don't know.
There are a lot of people.
I'm nervous because there are a lot of people.
I like a lot of people.
I've done a lot.
I'm really worried about being called alone.
Please line up in order.
What kind of person did you come with?
Yes, yes, yes. Chicago.
Yes, yes.
Don't you have to say that?
There's only one Kiri.
I've done a lot of things.
Chicago?
What?
It's okay.
You're a lot more relaxed than before.
And Basie Rollers.
Oh, is that so?
It's old again.
Don't say that it's old.
Basie Rollers.
And Neil Sedaka.
You're an old man.
Why?
It's too cool.
Have you ever done a chart?
Of course, joint.
I've done it.
I did it with my wife's voice.
Your music knowledge.
Everything now.
You're trying to twist it out.
Oishi Goroh is desperate.
I understand.
You don't have a guitar now, do you?
I'm basically a twin.
You twisted it out again.
Where did you see it?
I'm going to do this from now on.
It's amazing.
It's not working at all.
What?
Can you play something?
No, I can't.
Can you play Spring Toe Fold?
What's that trick?
Don't you know?
I do.
Why are you surprised?
What's that?
I don't know what you're talking about.
There's a lot of basics.
You're twisting it out.
That's not Spring Toe Fold.
That's different.
What do you mean?
Spring Toe Fold.
If you don't have a guitar, it won't work.
You can say it with your mouth.
I don't know.
I'm getting angry.
You can say it with your mouth.
It won't work.
It's really dirty.
I'm really angry.
Don't get angry.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it next time.
If you don't do it, it won't work.