It's been a long time.
Hello, hello.
No, no, no.
Everyone is full of energy.
That's good, that's good.
At the end, everyone is going to cry.
Are you going to cry?
I'm going to cry.
I'm going to cry at the end.
What a show.
That's right.
What is that?
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Why do I always lose?
It's the rules.
I want to kill him.
I don't even want to say his name.
I'm going to pull out all of his internal organs.
Tonight.
I can't help it.
I lost.
That's true.
My parents told me.
Even if everyone was caught, you'd be the one flying.
That's right.
Even if I'm not the one flying, I'm the one flying the most.
But in total...
I don't have enough.
Why is he running?
What?
Let's go.
I did it.
When I'm flying, I can't help it. I'm scared. I'm scared of how high I'm going to fly.
Don't make that sound.
I'm running, so I can't help it.
He's really...
How has he lived until now? And where will he go from now on?
I don't know.
I haven't heard anything about it.
But there was no phone call like,
I feel sorry for Machan.
Not at all.
If it were me, I'd think about it.
I feel sorry for Machan.
Who is he talking to on the phone?
Who is he talking to?
Who? Who are you talking about?
It doesn't matter.
You're so shocking.
And he's been whispering something like a punishment game.
I've been telling you before this.
If I lose, I'll get a punishment.
Let's look it up in the dictionary you have.
What's a punishment?
What punishment?
I just lost.
No, no, no, no. This is a problem.
What?
I can't help it.
I lost.
That's tough.
But I didn't think he would...
Huh?
I thought the same thing. I didn't think it would be that bad.
If he was flying as much as we did, it would be no doubt.
No doubt.
Because...
He didn't fly half of us.
I'm really surprised.
I think he's getting the hang of it.
What?
It's like a hop, step, jump.
But...
That's all there was to it.
But one thing I think was good was...
I think my share went up a lot.
What was it?
There's no other 38-year-old who can jump this much.
It was amazing.
What was with that jump?
Well, he did fly.
I wonder where the spring comes from.
I don't know.
I'm serious.
But you're only good at jumping.
I'm...
You're also good at high-jumping.
That's right.
You're not good at ball games at all.
Well...
It feels like it's coming to me.
I don't know for sure.
You don't know for sure?
It suddenly came to you.
You're good at ball games.
What are you talking about?
That's right.
What should I do?
It can't be helped.
It can't be helped that you've already done it.
I'll leave it to you this time.
Leave it to me?
I haven't made that many mistakes.
Let's make it a softer punishment game.
That's why the other day, we played tag three times, right?
That was when you guys lost, right?
30% more tag.
30% more tag for that? I'll probably die.
And you guys are four.
It's fine if you're four.
If I'm alone, I'll definitely be chased until I'm caught.
There's no point in running away.
No, no, no.
There's still that.
Seriously.
I can't punish that idiot.
I'll think about it.
Yuta is also my responsibility.
That's right.
You'll have to do something about that.
Seriously.
I don't know what to do about that.
That's not it.
I wanted to make the rules a bit clearer before the game was over.
I wanted to make it look like it was my team.
What is that?
Have you ever seen it live?
You haven't, have you?
It's even smaller.
It's smaller than it looks.
Even if I ate it, I wouldn't be that full.
I'd be hungry again in about two hours.
You're not hungry.
I'm not hungry.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Let's do it.
The other day, there was something that surprised me.
What is it?
It's a store that I go to often.
It's really good.
It's really small.
There's a private room in the back.
I thought it was nice, so I went there sometimes.
Everyone had noticed it before.
It's a private room for five or six people.
So it's really small.
Everyone had noticed it before.
One of the employees was really...
Level 4.
So where's Max?
He's Level 4.
He's completely dangerous.
Because he has a thousand private rooms.
Even if he doesn't have one, he has one.
If it's Level 4, he has one.
He has one.
He has a lot of them in his room.
It's in our hearts.
It's in everyone's hearts.
It's in the ceiling.
It's in our hearts.
It's in our noses.
His memories are...
If that's the case, you shouldn't have gone.
But it's really good.
When I went the other day, it was a little hot.
It was a little steamy.
It was terrible.
When I put it down, it came out like this.
It came out like this.
Under his hand.
It's really like CG.
It's really good.
Even if you eat it, it's really good.
You shouldn't do that.
I don't like that kind of thing.
It's because it's food.
I called the manager.
I asked him to change the person who would bring it to the table.
I see.
I was wondering what the reason was.
I had to do it quickly.
I couldn't do that.
Then Yamazaki said,
I'm sorry.
He came back and said,
The manager will be here soon.
I was wondering what he would say.
He came to me and said,
The manager will be here soon.
He's that guy.
You?
I said,
Is that so?
I couldn't say anything.
That's why.
I was told to call the manager.
I thought there was something.
My face looked like a fish.
I was wondering what it was.
I said,
It's okay.
What is it?
I'm sorry.
I misunderstood.
I want to say it.
I often say that.
That's terrible.
I couldn't help it.
There was a stupid guy.
He was bald.
He was a waiter.
He said,
You're not bad.
I didn't understand what he said.
He said,
I like you.
I want you to be in charge of this table today.
I asked him 40 minutes ago.
He didn't come yet.
He forgot.
I called him again.
He said,
You forgot.
Is that a good reaction?
It's true.
I told him to behave.
It's not harmful to eat at the counter.
That's right.
It's not good to eat at the counter.
But it's still May.
I'm going to play a game.
That's terrible.
I couldn't help it.
I couldn't understand it.
I felt sorry for him.
There was a girl who guided me.
I think she was angry.
She said,
Did you do something?
I see.
That's why I was called.
No.
It's you.
Everyone knows that.
But I'm good at it.
I don't know what to do.
If I don't do it well,
I can make you understand.
Are you talking about me?
That's hard.
I'm careful about it.
I hate it.
Are you okay?
There are a lot of people.
I don't like it.
But if you say,
I saw a child's desk.
I'll be angry.
Also,
I saw a child's bra.
I can't close this.
That's right.
It's a child's thing.
This is a child's thing.
It's funny.
I don't think so.
I'm a store manager.
That's right.
It's okay.
But indirectly,
I was saying something about you.
I can't say it.
If I can say it, I'll do something.
That's right.
It's better to be aware of it.
Say the name of the store.
People around you,
look at this.
It doesn't have to be that person.
Maybe it's a customer service.
That's right.
That's no good.
Really.
I have a talent.
It's just a problem with the costume.
There are a lot of food stores.
That's right.
You have to be careful.
Let's stop.
I have a question for Mr. Matsumoto.
The other day,
I saw an angel with broken wings.
Where did you see it?
I saw it at the pet shop.
You saw it at the pet shop?
Inside?
I saw it inside.
It was sold.
It was sold?
Because it was broken.
It was sold because it was broken?
That's right.
Why?
It was about 32,000 yen.
It's cheap.
It's not cheap.
But it can't be helped.
No one will buy it.
You should have fixed it first.
You shouldn't have sold it even though it was broken.
It was full of poop.
It's a cleaning product.
This one was broken.
This one is slightly moving.
This one is broken.
It's because it's hot.
You should have noticed it first.
If you show it, it won't be good.
On the contrary.
The old lady said,
I put in some food.
You put in some food?
It hurts.
It's not dry at all.
I put in some food.
It hurts.
What are you doing?
Please wake up.
I was struggling.
It hurts.
Where did you catch it?
I was helping.
What are you doing?
It was 32,000 yen.
It hurts.
It's hard to see.
It's strange.
When it's broken, it looks like a Toyoji.
Really?
When it's like this, it looks like a European one.
When it's broken, it looks like...
The man who understands women's feelings the most in the entertainment world.
That's right.
Please tell me how to hire a woman who isn't embarrassed.
Is it embarrassing?
Women?
You can't hire a woman who is embarrassed.
Is that so?
Everyone thinks too much.
I see.
There are men who are embarrassed sometimes.
There are men who can't hire a woman who is embarrassed.
They think too much.
It's okay to be normal.
I will hire a normal woman.
When I want to watch a normal movie,
or when I want to hire a woman for a movie,
I dare to make a movie with this.
I don't like it.
I don't want to hide my English.
I want to watch it.
I want to watch it in order.
That's how I feel.
That's how you feel.
What do you think?
Do you want to hire a woman?
I don't know.
I think I want to hire a woman.
But it's hard to hire a woman.
Is it hard to hire a woman?
If there is a way to hire a woman.
There are many ways.
Is that so?
Please tell me.
I look at her.
This is me.
I am popular.
I miss her.
And this.
I can't look at her.
This is a lie.
Are you embarrassed?
I'm embarrassed.
Is that so?
Men are embarrassed.
Women are not embarrassed.
Have you ever seen an AV?
It's cool.
You should watch it.
It's not good.
That's right.
I like you and Imada.
How much do you like Imada?
That's terrible.
I bought a lot of self-videos.
I borrowed money.
I watched the AV on the night of the day.
It was different from that.
I could watch it anytime.
I could watch it now.
I could watch it today.
That's great.
Do you feel the same way?
I haven't watched it since I joined this year.
What?
I haven't watched it.
I watched it for about five minutes.
I've been watching it a lot lately.
I've been watching it a lot until the end.
That's right.
It's cool.
I haven't watched it until the end.
Really?
I have to tell you my point.
Your point?
You also tell me your point.
My point.
What's your point?
My point and your point are different.
That's different.
That's right.
It's all the same now.
That's strange.
When I look at the line, I want to see it lined up.
I have a question for Mr. Matsumoto.
What are you waiting for when you follow the line of ants?
What?
There are many things waiting.
Have you ever followed the line of ants?
No.
It's better to follow the line of ants.
Have you ever followed the line of ants?
I have.
I stopped following the line of ants halfway.
I've followed the line of ants for a long time.
What did you see?
I don't know where it started.
I can't explain where I stopped following the line of ants.
I don't care about that.
I followed the line of ants because I found ants.
I followed the line of ants until something came out.
What did you find?
What do you mean?
What are you waiting for?
I'm waiting for something sweet.
I see.
That's normal. I've seen it.
Something sweet?
I've been walking with candy in my hand.
I've never seen it.
Don't give candy to an old man who is 40 years old.
You are a fool.
You are the type who says, ''Age-san''.
I can't say ''Age-san''.
You say, ''Oimo-san''.
Do you want to be cute like that?
Everyone in Osaka calls you ''Ame-chan''.
I don't call you ''Ame-chan''.
You used to.
I call you ''Candy''.
You used to call me ''Ame-chan''.
I never call you ''Ame-chan''.
What is it?
What are you waiting for?
You've been waiting for something sweet.
I've been waiting for something sweet.
That's normal.
What do you want to be when you grow up?
That's right.
What is it?
How long have you been following him?
What are you talking about?
Just say it.
About 20 meters.
You've been following him for 20 meters?
It must be hard to follow him for 20 meters.
The problem is that the width of the ant is different from ours.
It must be hard to follow him all the time.
But still, let's try it.
That's why I did it.
I'm not going to go straight.
There are times when I go through the wall.
I'm not going to go straight. There are times when I go through the wall.
I'm not going to lose today.
Congratulations.
Why are you so angry?
Why?
I did it about two months ago.
What?
It feels like that. It's too early.
I see.
But it's a big celebration.
It's already changed.
I thought that introduction was interesting.
It's a big celebration.
It's already changed.
Mori Sanchu isn't here.
He might be here.
At times like this, this time...
Oh, you're going to sing?
Thank you.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, dear Hamachan.
To you?
To war?
Hamachan!
39 years old!
Thank you!
Thank you in English!
Let's do it!
Cheers!
Thank you!