The first episode of the Gaki no Tsukai Arai-hen,
Tsukitsuki Demai o Warakase,
Gainin-Orai Bakushou Hengei Daisakusei!
Mr. Matsumoto, how was it today?
This is exactly like the title of the previous episode.
You know, we often ask for delivery food, right?
At that time, we don't know if it's a delivery man, an old man, or an old woman.
I'll bring it, but they don't laugh much.
That's right.
Well, it was funny, wasn't it?
I really hated that.
After all, I'm a comedian.
I want you to laugh at times like that.
That's right.
That's why I'm going to do some action today.
I'm going to make a delivery man laugh.
Let's do it.
If you do it once, it's 500,000 yen.
500,000 yen?
I'll give it to you.
What?
That's cool.
If you do it once, it's 300,000 yen.
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
Even if it's downtown, I'm thinking of doing it.
Well, we're still going to be there.
It's still you guys.
I can't get downtown out.
If we do it and make us laugh,
I'll give you 500,000 yen.
It's hard.
500,000 yen?
You three, collect the money.
It's almost time.
Can you laugh at times like that?
Excuse me.
Yes.
I'm Kanda.
What about you?
I'm a comedian.
Do you have a size M?
But this is slippery.
It's 1,100 yen.
This is...
It was very sticky.
I don't have a bad hand.
It's a little bad.
This is...
I can't say I got it.
It's 8,000 yen.
Please take it.
Thank you very much.
It's a business payment.
This is not a normal 100 yen.
Do you want me to call you?
Let's all get together.
I was smiling.
But that's...
It's a business payment.
That's right.
If you get it, you'll smile.
There's nothing wrong with this.
Do you know the story of the three of us?
The story of the three of us?
One will break right away.
Three won't break.
Let's talk about it.
The three of us are together.
Let's do it one more time.
May I?
It's a completely different pattern.
76 times.
I'm laughing a little.
It's funny.
I'm watching the video.
I don't know.
Wait a minute.
I'm laughing a little.
I'm watching the video.
I don't know.
Let's all gather.
I'm laughing a little.
Did you laugh?
I laughed a little.
No, I didn't laugh.
My face is dead.
I'm laughing a little.
I ate it.
You ate it.
You ate it?
Your face was more proud than the pizza guy.
It was fun.
But you should praise the delivery guy.
What?
You don't understand.
I don't understand at all.
You should praise him.
There's a way to say that.
Let's go.
I have an idea.
What?
There's a way to say that.
Let's do it.
You're late.
Did I do it on time?
No.
How many times did you do it?
I did it twice.
You did it three times.
You did it naturally.
I did it three times.
Sorry.
You should have done it naturally.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
I don't understand.
Wait.
He's showing a joke.
I'm scared.
I don't want to pull it.
It's 4,095 yen today.
I want to eat a little.
I don't want to pull it.
I pulled it.
What is this?
A comedian?
Did you get a voice?
I don't think I'll get a voice.
No matter how funny it is.
I was able to put up with it.
But to be honest, I can't do it.
It's the worst place for a Kansai comedian.
And there's a dead man.
It's the worst place in Yoshimoto.
Hey, go down.
Please go down.
You two.
You two go down.
Please go down.
You can't show us the difference in strength.
It's okay.
It's very difficult.
It's a dead man.
Don't say that.
Yes.
Let's go home.
I'm sorry.
What?
Let's go home.
Are you okay?
Good morning.
I'm sorry.
That's right.
What are you doing?
I'm scared.
That's not good.
What are you doing?
Don't cry.
I'm not crying at all.
Don't worry.
I'm not worried.
Are you okay?
It's 1,800 yen.
What?
Damn it.
What's wrong?
I can't stop crying.
Bring it over here.
It's okay.
I'm scared.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Come on.
What's wrong?
I should have been a calendar.
I'm sorry.
It's the opposite.
He's making me laugh.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Shall we go home?
Can I eat it?
Thank you very much.
Let's go home.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Wait a minute.
It's the opposite.
He's making me laugh.
I should have been a calendar.
What the hell are you talking about?