In a corner of a big city, there is a legendary child slave family that lives in the present day.
This mysterious family lives.
This time, a young man will perform a ritual to join the family.
His name is Naohito Tsukimura. He is 25 years old.
For the first time, a young man will enter the family.
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
This ritual was performed two years ago by a senior member of the family.
The young man, who is unknown to the family, goes to the ceremony hall.
What is waiting for him?
First of all, the ceremony started with a welcome dance.
The young man's clothes are taken off by the family.
The sound of drums raises the atmosphere.
The first ritual is the rite of passage.
The young man's body is cleansed by the holy fire.
The second ritual is the interaction with the family.
The third ritual is hot water.
The time has come for the young man to show courage.
The fourth ritual is the snake dance.
The snake dance is said to have been passed down from generation to generation.
The young man's body is healthy.
The fifth ritual is the martial arts.
This is the last ritual performed by the family's martial arts master.
This is the last ritual performed by the family.
The ceremony is over. Will the young man be welcomed by the family?
The young man seems to be recognized as a friend.
Finally, the young man meets the family.
The young man's clothes are taken off by the family.
The ceremony is over.
This is the last ritual performed by the family.
Thank you for watching.