Thank you very much!
Today, the other day...
It was the worst!
It was the worst project!
I don't think there's anything worse than this.
It was short.
But it was shot diagonally.
Really!
It means that they watched it a lot.
It seems that they were moved.
I think my frame will be used up.
Who uses it?
That's right.
When she found out that she was pregnant,
She finally decided to marry a 33-year-old man.
Comedian Hosei Yamazaki
The other day, a touching performance was held with only relatives.
Today, we will show you the whole picture!
Let's have the main character, Hosei Yamazaki, come on stage!
Hello!
Hosei Yamazaki
Why do you have such a face?
Thank you very much!
Are you going to cry?
If you don't cry,
Human skin...
It's human skin.
If you cry like this.
You don't understand, do you?
It's human skin.
Give me back my frame!
It's okay, Hamada-san.
You'll definitely cry.
It's a human skin.
The size is different.
It's not a human skin.
It's about the same size.
It's definitely not a human skin.
If you don't cry like this.
It's so touching.
Today, there are four of us and 25 staff members.
Let's see if it's moving.
After we're done, let's do the math.
I see.
We'll give Hosei a special gift.
I think it's this.
It's a gift for 5 people from 0.
It's for 5 people.
That's about it.
It's for 6 to 10 people.
It's this.
It's a gift for 5 people from 0 to 5 people.
You're always like this.
I don't like it.
11 to 15 people can enjoy a bike with three people.
16 to 20 people can enjoy a luxury car.
21 to 24 people can enjoy a luxurious chandelier.
I don't need this.
It's a wonderful gift.
It's a gift for 5 people from 0 to 15 people.
If it's perfect for 25 people, it's this.
It's a gift for 12 people.
It's a gift for 12 people from anywhere in the world.
Really?
Yes.
You're going to give me all of this?
This is amazing.
I'm the only one who gets to give you money for a trip to Shizuoka.
Is that true?
This program is brought to you by the sponsors.
Now we will start the grand opening of Yama-chan's happy wedding.
I can't go down one more time.
This is the way to do it, right?
Something like this.
No one laughs.
Please laugh at the one behind you.
Please.
No one laughs.
Heisei 13 years old, October 21st.
Husband, Hyousen Yamasaki.
Wife, Aya.
You talked, didn't you?
I can talk.
You can't talk.
What is this?
It's like crying.
This is like a wedding how-to video.
What is this?
It's a very beautiful image.
This is a video that looks like this even if you play it in a song.
It's a lie.
This is a lie.
This is a rare scene.
Why?
You don't cry that much.
I don't cry.
I'm crying, so I can't cry.
Why are you crying?
You don't cry, do you?
The bride and groom will enter.
What is this?
You don't cry, do you?
Why do you enter with such a sound?
The bride and groom will enter.
You are laughing.
Are you ready?
The bride and groom will enter.
Congratulations.
You are laughing.
The bride and groom will enter.
I'm looking at the bride and groom.
Please pay attention to the screen on the right.
This is a picture of you two when you were young.
Let's go.
I don't want to see it.
There was a genius comedian in Nishinomiya City, Hyogo Prefecture.
I told you myself.
Thank you.
There is a great symbol of a genius comedian in the lower center.
I'm laughing.
The bride and groom will enter.
This costume is enough.
I'm laughing.
The bride and groom will enter.
Congratulations.
The bride and groom have arrived.
What is this?
I wanted to see this.
Congratulations.
This is strange.
What is this?
I don't know what this is.
I think this is a little different from the previous one.
No, no, no.
This is fine.
Wait.
This is hard for us, too.
This is really hard for a person who shot at the scene.
This is hard.
This is fine.
What is this?
Who is this?
You can see it now, right?
Thank you.
This is a little different from the previous one.
Why are you wearing this?
I don't care about that.
Dad, mom.
Thank you for raising such a selfish child.
And mom.
Until I met my current father,
I have been a woman for the rest of my life.
Our father.
He took care of me.
What are you talking about?
Mom, thank you for your hard work.
From now on, I will do my best as a mother and a baby.
Mom.
From the bottom of my heart,
I was born as a mother's child.
I was born as a grandfather.
I am grateful that I was born as a grandmother.
Thank you very much.
And Hosei's father and mother.
It's a long story, but
I will do my best as a wife of Hosei Yamato.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations on your birthday.
Please give a round of applause to Hosei Yamato.
That's all.
He is crying alone.
Please tell us what you think.
Hama-san, do you have anything to say?
I think it was a typical wedding ceremony.
He is smiling.
I don't know.
I don't know if you are impressed.
Please tell us what you think.
If you are impressed, please turn on the switch.
It's zero.
Zero?
Really?
I didn't think it was zero.
Zero?
But there is a product, right?
This is toilet paper.
Unfortunately, it was zero.
Really?
Yes.
I was a little impressed.
He is crying on the other side.
It's hard.