Good evening.
I came to Asakusa today.
That's great.
When customers come to the ticket office, the discount is 1,100 yen.
That's right.
When I say that the discount is 1,100 yen,
it's usually 1,800 yen.
I'm surprised.
Look.
When a great person comes out,
Candy Boys is our master.
I didn't know there was a place like this.
This person was a tough guy.
It was tough.
I got to know this person.
My head was hit.
The name of the person I met was Bontaname.
Is that so?
Is Juna North Carolina?
That's right.
He said it had to be the rain of today.
This is Asakusa, France.
It's famous.
Mr. Takeshi and Kin-chan.
What do you call them?
It was a time when they were training.
Miss Baby.
What kind of person is that?
Miss Natasha.
She's Japanese.
Today, we're going to a great place.
Here comes a tough guy.
Let's talk to this tough guy.
Good evening.
Dad, where are you going?
I'm going to a bar.
A bar?
Dad, we're local people.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to Osaka.
I'm not going to Osaka.
It's fun.
I don't think there's a place like this in Osaka.
Dad.
I'm scared.
I don't have a ride.
It's here.
We're going to do it here today.
Let's do our best.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hey, you know.
I'm not going to say anything, so I won't say anything about my costume.
I won't say anything about my costume.
You're right.
Today is the second time.
However, we are doing a manzai in an amazing place.
It's amazing.
There is no manzai like this in Osaka.
This is the second time today.
Last time, it was a little more youthful.
But today...
What is this sound?
There are about four people here.
This is like an amazing theater.
Sada Ryuji didn't come out.
That's right.
This is the second time today.
I don't think we've ever seen a manzai.
I think so.
Recently, I've been going to Tokyo.
I'm glad I went to downtown.
The name is...
I don't think downtown is cool.
I'm glad I went to downtown.
The name was different from downtown.
That's right.
I don't have a master.
I was given a name by the boss of my company, Yoshimoto.
I met a boss.
When I made my debut, I was more popular.
It was dark.
I was doing a dark manzai.
I was called by the boss.
I was given a name.
I've been calling my name for a long time.
I'm Teruo Haruo.
That's right.
I'm Teruo and Haruo.
The atmosphere of today's stage is Teruo Haruo.
That's right.
I don't have a costume.
You're particular about it.
That's right.
There's a lot of talk about it these days.
It's been like that since before.
That's right.
I've been on this song 24 hours a day.
I've been saying, I'll save the earth.
I've been saying, I'll save the African refugees.
I think it's better if everyone thought about how to do it.
That's the best.
What are you talking about?
Even if there's a woman in there,
If you're in there,
Put a dollar or five dollars in the bottle.
There may be people who take it.
I don't have anything to eat.
I don't have anything to wear.
You're giving me something to eat!
I have to get her for you in the first place.
There's no food.
Give him food.
They should be having more than that.
Kuroyanagi Tetsuko is wearing a life jacket.
It won't be.
Oh, really.
It's closer than a life jacket to a teenage richest man.
Take a look at my aioli, I'm going to have it.
You see it and it's annoying, isn't it?
I didn't even know my facial expression.
Maybe with the dead lash....
You're lying!
You're not going to clean it up, are you?
It's really annoying.
But it can't be helped.
They don't have anything to eat, so it's a pity.
They're all hungry, aren't they?
I can see their bones.
They're not going to use it, are they?
They're all being fooled.
They don't have anything to eat, they don't have strength, they don't have strength.
If you look at them, there are a lot of babies.
They have a lot of strength, don't they?
They're doing what they have to do, aren't they?
That's a different kind of energy.
No matter how tired you are, you do what you have to do, don't you?
Well, that's true.
What are you going to do if you admit it?
That's their brain reaction.
What's that?
What's that brain reaction to those people in America?
When I look at the camera, even though I'm giving it to everyone,
it's like this.
That's...
It's hard.
You've seen their physical strength, haven't you?
Even so, when I give it to everyone,
even when I look at the camera,
it's like this.
I'm not going to do anything.
You're not going to do anything because you don't have that energy?
I'm not going to do anything because I don't have that energy.
I don't care about that.
You don't care about that at night, do you?
I'm not going to be fooled by them.
What?
They say that you're a rich man in Japan, right?
That's right.
Compared to Shura, I think Japan is a little too rich.
That's true.
Even if you watch the TV program, you have to pay a lot of money.
That's right.
That's a quiz show.
You have to pay a lot of money.
That's right.
I'm going to give you a quiz today.
That's not it.
You did that last week, didn't you?
What?
Last week, you said you were going to give me a quiz.
It's the second time.
You can't do that.
It's been a week since then.
You're famous in the comedy world
for not doing the same thing.
Where is it?
Is it in the quiz?
It's in the quiz.
I've been big since then.
It's different from that quiz.
It's a different quiz?
Are you okay?
Do you want to do it?
I don't know what it is.
I know what it is.
That's not it.
What's that?
It's the one on the left.
Good luck!
Is that what it means?
Where do you work?
I work at a unclean restaurant.
I like what I hear.
I got a little bored.
Do your best.
Do you want to go there?
That's what it means.
What was it?
Do you want to go there?
What are you talking about?
What is it?
Do you want to go to America?
Do you want to go there?
Where is there?
This country is where everyone wants to go.
That's why it's usually decided on the show.
This time it's America, this time it's Switzerland, right?
If it's Switzerland, do you want to go to Switzerland?
Do you want to go there?
Where is it?
Today's corner is that corner.
Do your best, Mr. Miyahana.
Do you want to go there?
If you want to go, you have to get it right.
That corner looks good.
If you get it right, how about that corner?
I'll definitely get it right.
Now, the first question.
Today's first question is very easy.
Eat upside-down words!
Eat upside-down words.
If you answer with upside-down words, it will be the answer.
It's very easy.
It's as it is.
It's easy, right?
Let's practice.
For example, the height of this upside-down.
Low.
That's right.
Far.
Close.
This is Hamada-san's problem.
What is it?
It's coming from the first shot, Mr. Hamada.
That's amazing, Mr. Hamada.
It's the same if you get it right.
Thank you.
Now, the first question of the upside-down quiz.
Let's go to the question.
Yes.
Ta-da!
Tanihayato.
Wait.
What are you doing?
What is it?
The word upside-down.
It's high.
It's low.
It's close.
It's far.
What is Tanihayato?
Tell me the word upside-down of Tanihayato.
Tanihayato.
Marine blue quiz.
Shut up!
Wait.
What is it?
Marine blue quiz.
Listen to me.
What is the word upside-down of Tanihayato?
Marine blue is fine.
I want to hear the answer.
Please ask the question.
Answer me.
What is the word upside-down of Tanihayato?
Marine blue quiz.
You know it, don't you?
I asked the question to 100 people.
Just say it.
What is the word upside-down of Tanihayato?
I asked the question to 100 people.
That's right.
What is Marine blue?
Marine blue quiz is...
Please do your best, Hamada-san.
Hamada-san is...
You know that I asked the question to 100 people.
Yes, I know.
Our staff asked the question to 100 people.
The answer is the most.
That's the answer.
You said it before.
I want you to do your best.
I'll do my best.
Today's question is...
In Shibuya,
100 people are listening to Oakman.
Why?
I'm playing the music.
Can you hear me?
What should I do?
Hamada-san, you have to listen to the question.
I asked the question to 100 people.
100 people?
You didn't answer me.
So I asked the question again.
But you didn't answer me.
I want you to listen to the question.
I'll do my best.
Do you want to go there?
Yes, I want to go there.
You can say it.
It's like they're welcoming you.
I'll go.
I asked the question to 100 people.
I asked you to remove the Oakman.
I'll ask you one more question.
I asked the question to 100 people after I removed the Oakman.
How are you doing recently?
Are you kidding me?
Hamada-san.
Hamada-san, what kind of answer is that?
How are you doing recently?
Dad, don't touch me.
Hamada-san.
How are you doing recently?
Dad, don't touch me.
Hamada-san.
You speak clearly.
Dad, don't touch me.
How are you doing recently?
Answer me.
I asked the question to 100 people.
Blue Sky Quiz.
What is Blue Sky Quiz?
It's time for Blue Sky Quiz.
I hope you do your best.
Your quiz has changed a lot.
Thank you very much.
Hamada-san, do you know Santa's Quiz?
Yes.
You know it, right?
The answer is one out of three.
This Blue Sky Quiz is 20 questions.
Do your best.
It's even more difficult.
This quiz is very easy.
Don't say that.
Let me tell you the question first.
What is it?
Today's question is very easy.
I think you will be angry if I make fun of you.
The question is, what is the name of the current Prime Minister of Japan?
Is that OK?
The name of that person is already on your mind, right?
It's already on your mind, right?
It's obvious that you got it.
Wait a minute.
The staff thought of 20 questions.
You have to answer them.
When the time comes, you have to answer.
Don't be impatient.
I know that.
Maybe it's a river, right?
It's OK.
Hamada-san, do your best.
It's 20 questions.
When the time comes, you have to answer.
I got it.
Yamashita.
Kato.
Kubo.
Hagino.
Nishio.
John.
It's definitely wrong.
Takeda.
Kaifu.
Hamada-san, you have to answer.
It's already on your mind, right?
Yes.
Please answer.
Kaifu.
Hamada-san, please answer with a number.
Say it earlier.
I got it.
Kaifu.
How many times have I forgotten?
If you don't remember this, you can't answer Blue Sky Quiz.
You have to answer with a number.
Do you understand?
What the hell is this?
This is the last quiz of today.
Please do your best.
You don't understand.
I'll do my best.
Today's quiz is very easy.
It's the last quiz, so it's very easy.
Please do your best.
I don't understand.
Hamada-san, be motivated.
Dad, be motivated.
I'll do my best.
Please do your best.
Today's quiz is very easy.
Here is the question.
What is the weather in Tokyo on October 10th?
You answer.
You have been asking questions, but you can't answer.
You have to answer.
Hamada-san, I'll give you a special time today.
You can go outside to see the weather.
There is no such problem.
I'm grateful for that time.
The person in front of the TV is making fun of you.
Why don't you understand this?
Today, you are a loser.
You are a loser.
I don't understand.
I understand.
The answer is rain.
The answer is sunny.
The answer is cloudy.
I'll leave the rest to the editor.
I came to Asakusa for the first time in my life.
How is it?
I'm going to get used to Tokyo.
But I can't accept Osaka people.
Really?
I don't like it.
You are listening to the story with a loving eye.
I'm not a man, but I'm usually cold.
Are you cold?
I'm cold.
I don't like the way girls talk.
Why?
What?
Girls are better than Osaka people.
Tokyo girls repeat what people say.
I'm tired and my head hurts.
You are tired and your head hurts.
I'm saying it.
I'm not saying it.
I'm tired and my head hurts.
I'm saying it again.
Why are you saying it?
I'm tired and my head hurts.
I have a nose.
You have a good sense.
I think Tokyo is good.
Taxi drivers are good.
Really?
Yes.
They are kind.
They listen to me.
For example, if I ask them to go to Fuji TV, they listen to me.
I can't ask them that in Osaka.
But I don't like one thing.
For example, if I ask them to go in the opposite direction, they go in the opposite direction.
In Osaka, they go around.
If I ask them where they want to go, they say it's the opposite direction.
It's the opposite direction.
It would be great if you were there.
I think taxi drivers in Tokyo are good.
They listen to me.
I don't know where to go.
I don't know.
They are kind.
I don't know where to go.
The people I rode with the other day were really kind.
How do you feel about the taxi?
What?
Everyone is saying that.
I'm surprised.
It's cute.
Really.
In that sense...
Is there anything good about Tokyo?
Something good about Tokyo?
But it's still a new place, so what's good about it?
For example, if it's famous, they say the food is different.
I think girls in Tokyo are good.
Really?
Yes.
The girls in Tokyo have thin legs.
Don't look down.
Osaka girls have thick legs.
You have thick legs.
Your legs are about 8 meters long.
It doesn't fit.
Really?
That's strange.
Did you kick a club in your past life?
Don't say that.
It's a joke.
I heard you had a cold today.
Yes.
I got a shot because I was tired.
Do you really have a cold?
You're trying to get attention from everyone, aren't you?
You lie and say you have a cold.
Are you a transfer student?
I'm trying to get attention.
You're trying to get everyone's attention.
When I came to Tokyo, I didn't make the same mistake as I did in Osaka.
I tried to make a cute character.
Osaka fans are controlled by Hamada.
I'll make the same mistake again in Tokyo.
It's been a long time since I got a shot.
I went to the hospital in Nittere.
I can't get a shot very often.
The doctor told me to get a shot.
It's in the Nittere station.
You can't get a shot like this.
I asked him if I was going to get a shot.
He said I was going to get a shot.
I got a shot in the end.
But there was a lot of air left.
I didn't get a shot yet.
The nurse hit me with a needle.
I thought it was strange.
What if I got a shot?
We don't have a chance to do a manzai in Tokyo.
I'll do as much as I can tonight.
It's a little late.
It's 1 o'clock and 40 minutes.
I want you to do your best.
Thank you very much for your time today.
See you next time.
I had a lot of fun.
How many times are you going to do this?
It's a manzai.
I was born with a manzai.
How many times are you going to do it?
I'm asking you the number of times.
How many times are you going to do a manzai?
I've done it 18 times so far.
Really?
I'll show you the completed video.
At 7 or 8 p.m. on Saturday, I'll show you the golden manzai.
I'll pay for it.
I don't pay for this program at all.
I want to hear the opinions of the people who watch TV.
I don't want to do a manzai.
I'm waiting for your opinions.
We're preparing for it right now.
Are you ready?
Yes, we are.
I want to hear the opinions of the viewers.
I want to hear the opinions of comedians.
I'm curious about what the people who work in the field think.
I don't know.
I'll buy the program.
I'll pay for it.
Well, let's do it.
Let's do it at a later time.
It's a drama.
It's about time for us to say goodbye.
Yes.
It's so hot in here.
It was a little difficult.
See you next week.
Goodbye.
This program was brought to you by Toyosui-san,
Ginza Jywai Yokuchuru Maki,
and the following sponsors.