Now, Dantan's kid's hand.
Uwaaaaa!
I'm not scared at all.
I don't understand anything.
I understand.
I see.
Yesterday, the boss was like this.
He was like this.
In this way, he was like this.
I'm right here.
Today,
I just finished shooting.
I'm removing my make-up.
Well, I always do it easily.
I'm going to remove it.
This is the first time.
I'm going to use the kid.
I'm going to take a bath.
Now, let's get back to the game.
I got injured quite a lot, didn't I?
I was wondering if my face would be the same as before.
I guess the medicine worked.
I look so much better now.
The other day, my staff went to your house to pick you up.
He said, this is terrible, but I won't make it to the next shoot.
That face is terrible.
So he set it up like this.
I was supposed to be doing the same thing as last week.
But it looks like you've already recovered.
I'm sorry.
Did you know that your staff came to our house to spy on you?
I'm not a spy.
I came here because I was worried about you.
That's not a secret.
I came here to find out what's going to happen next week.
That's why I'm worried.
I know that you were on the phone downstairs.
I know that you've been watching a lot of TV shows.
Do you watch VTRs?
I have a funny one.
What is it?
It's on TX.
Can I borrow it?
It's funny.
What is it?
The air bag in the car.
The one that inflates?
Why is it funny?
The comedians are dying.
What?
We started this program today.
Before the time changes.
You were doing a story from last night, right?
Yes, I was.
From now on.
There's also a time limit.
If you keep it up,
we'll have to take a break again.
The title of the story doesn't really fit.
It's called the upside down word quiz.
Let's take a look.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
I don't really have anything to say.
But I don't smell bad at all.
There's a lot of talk about the refugee issue on TV.
In this song,
they talk about saving the earth.
They've been talking about saving the refugees.
There's no food.
There's nothing to eat.
They're all so poor.
There are things that we should do.
They want to see the flies that are on their faces.
They're irritated.
They don't know what to do.
Are they angry?
They're not going to fly away.
That's crazy.
But it can't be helped.
They're all so poor.
They're so fat.
They're all being fooled.
They don't have anything to eat.
They're so weak.
They don't have a lot of strength.
They're doing something.
That's a different kind of energy.
They're being fooled.
They talk about rich Japan.
I think Japan is richer than Japan.
That's true.
Even if you're watching a TV show, it costs a lot of money.
That's a good point.
It's like a quiz show.
A quiz show costs a lot of money.
You get a prize of 1 or 2 million yen.
But today, we're doing a quiz.
This is Hamada-san.
He's been here for a while.
Good luck today.
Your daughter is here today.
That's right.
Where is she?
She's over there on the left.
Good luck, dad.
Good luck.
Dad, good luck.
Where are you from?
I'm from Momoya.
It's easy to understand.
I was a little nervous.
Good luck, Hamada-san.
Hamada-san, do your best.
Do you want to go there?
Do your best.
What do you mean?
Do you want to go to America?
Do you want to go there?
Where is that?
Today, we're going to the corner over there.
We're going there.
Good luck, Hamada-san.
Do you want to go there?
You have to get it right.
What?
That corner looks good.
Do you want to go to that corner?
I'll definitely get it right.
You'll definitely get it right.
That's nonsense.
Good luck with the first question.
Today's first question is very easy.
What is it?
You have to answer it in reverse.
If you answer it in reverse, you'll get it right.
It's very easy.
It's easy, isn't it?
Let's practice.
For example, what is the height of this?
It's low.
How far is it?
It's close.
This is Hamada-san's problem.
What?
Hamada-san is coming from the first round.
Let's go to the first quiz.
First question.
Jageran.
What is the height of this?
It's low.
It's close.
How far is it?
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
What is the word in reverse?
It's high.
It's low.
It's close.
What is the word in reverse?
You have to answer it in reverse.
Let's hear what is in reverse.
I can't understand it.
This is Marimbulu Quiz, what is this?
Okada-san, ask me again.
Could you listen to me?
Answer no one.
What is the word in reverse?
Marimbulu Quiz.
You don't know, right?
Did you mention a quiz to 100 people?
You need to tell me the answer the same message.
Yes.
What is Marimbulu?
It's the Marimba quiz.
Please do your best, Hamada-san.
Hamada-san, that is...
Do your best?
You know that there are 100 people, right?
Yes, I know.
Our staff went around and asked 100 people.
The answer is the most.
That is the answer as it is.
You said that before.
Yes, I want you to do your best.
I'll do my best.
That's good.
Then, today's question.
In Shibuya,
there are 200 people who are listening to Oakman.
Why is that?
I'm telling you to listen!
What should I do?
Hamada-san, you have to listen to the question until the end.
So, I asked 100 people who are listening.
100 people?
They didn't answer, so I asked again.
You have to listen to the question until the end.
Dad, listen to the question!
I'll do my best.
Do your best.
Say it.
It's like they are welcoming me.
I'll do my best.
I asked 100 people, but they didn't answer.
One more question.
I asked 100 people after they answered.
I asked 100 people who were listening to Oakman,
but they didn't answer.
How are you doing recently?
Are you laughing?
Hamada-san.
Hamada-san!
How are you doing recently?
Hamada-san.
Dad, listen to the question!
I'll do my best.
How are you doing recently?
Dad, listen to the question!
I'll do my best.
How are you doing recently?
Say it.
Answer me.
How are you doing recently?
I asked 100 people, but they didn't answer.
Blue Sky Quiz!
What is the Blue Sky Quiz?
It's time for the Blue Sky Quiz.
I'll do my best.
Your quiz has changed a lot.
Thank you.
Hamada-san, do you know what the Santa Quiz is?
Yes.
You know it, right?
It's one of the three.
This Blue Sky Quiz is 20 questions.
I'll do my best.
It's even more difficult!
Think about it.
The question is very easy.
What is it?
Don't say it!
Let's talk about the question first.
What is it?
Today's question is very easy.
I think you can get angry if you make fun of it.
The question is...
What is the name of the current Prime Minister of Japan?
Is that okay?
Of course.
You can think of his name, right?
Of course I got it.
Wait a minute.
The staff came up with 20 questions.
You have to answer them.
When you get the answer,
it's your turn.
You don't have to rush.
That's right.
You know it, right?
I know it.
Excuse me.
It's a river, isn't it?
It's okay, isn't it?
It's a river.
I'll do my best.
There are 20 questions.
When you get the answer,
it's your turn.
I got it.
Let's start.
Yamashita.
Kato.
Kubo.
Hagino.
Nishio.
John.
That's definitely wrong.
Takeda.
Kaifu.
Wait a minute.
That's your turn.
It's your turn.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Kaifu.
Yamano, please answer with your number.
Say it first.
I got it.
It's Kaifu.
How many times have I forgotten?
If you don't remember this,
you can't do the Blue Sky Quiz.
You're lying.
You told me to answer with my number.
You said so many names.
Why didn't you say it with your number?
Do you understand?
Spring, summer, autumn,
what is this?
I don't understand.
Spring, summer, autumn,
this is today's last quiz.
Do your best.
You don't understand.
I'll do my best.
Today's quiz is very easy.
Here's the question.
Ta-da.
Today,
October 10th,
what is the weather like in Tokyo?
It's hot.
You say it.
You've been giving me questions,
but you haven't given me an answer.
You always give me an answer.
You answer today.
You answer.
You answer the question.
I got it, Yamano.
I'll give you some time to think.
You can go outside and look.
That's not the problem.
I'm grateful for that time.
The person in front of the TV is making fun of you.
Why don't you understand this?
Today,
you're
a loser.
You're a loser.
I don't understand.
I got it.
The answer is
rain.
sunny.
The answer is
cloudy.
I'll leave it to the editor.
You're back.
Yes.
Look.
The program
has given you
such a big prank.
Oh, is that so?
Congratulations.
Is this from Nihon TV?
Nihon TV.
Dantan.
It's a staff member
in Gaki no Tsukai Arahen.
And here.
Yoshimoto Kogyo.
Team Zero.
This is
easy to ride.
Yes.
Was it expensive?
Well,
Dantan.
Yes.
How much was it?
It was expensive.
Say it.
10,000 yen.
10,000 yen?
Is this
worth 10,000 yen?
Well,
I've been living here.
What?
You guys?
Yes.
You went to live here?
For Mr. Matsumoto.
I see.
Where did you go to live?
I went to Shikoku.
Next.
We talked on the phone with the kids.
Yes.
We watched this video.
This.
This program is very popular.
I'm grateful for that.
Yes.
These days,
I don't usually appear on TV.
But,
it's not very interesting.
Well,
movies are popular these days.
Is that so?
Yes.
The same goes for videos.
If you have a rental car,
you can watch movies all the time.
But,
movies are hard to make.
It's hard to make one.
In the past,
I was
the main actor of Ogata.
I was moved.
Of course!
You know,
this video has some important words.
What can I say?
It's difficult!
At least,
I think that
I didn't write them correctly.
Let me say it again.
The same result with Japanese movies.
I don't know whom the Cat Ohashi
is.
I'm sorry.
Why would a character
of Ogata
have to be gets the wrong name?
TEGAWA is
the same as another character of Ogata.
I think it's quiteware.
Is者
What kind of picture are you drawing?
It's funny.
From O-bun to Ogata prefecture, the ass is up.
I drew it and it's over.
Idiot!
What?
I've been drawing the ass all the time, and it's over.
It's funny.
I'm more interested in radio now.
Oh yeah?
Radio is like a child's phone call.
It's pretty popular.
I can't ask.
Things that my friends don't understand.
Things that are a little hard to ask my parents.
I see.
Hello?
Yes?
This is Hamada Nii-san.
What's wrong?
Hello?
Answer me!
You said it's a child's phone call.
Hello?
I don't know if it's a voice message or not.
Don't come over there.
It's a little smaller.
Smaller?
Yes.
Hello?
This is Hamada Nii-san.
What's your name?
Matsumoto.
Matsumoto-kun.
What's your name?
Sato.
Sato-kun.
What's your name?
Matsumoto.
Is it Matsumoto-kun?
Matsumoto-kun?
Yes.
What's your name?
Sato.
Sato-kun?
Yes.
Matsumoto-kun?
Is it Matsumoto-kun?
Yes.
Where is Sato-kun?
What are you?
Matsumoto Sato.
Is your name Sato?
Yes.
This is so funny.
You.
Why didn't you say Sato-kun is hot?
Hello?
Well.
What's wrong?
I have something to ask you.
What is it?
Recently, there is a movie called...
I think it's called Ikaiyo.
What should I eat?
Ask your mother.
Don't call me all the time.
If you call me that much, your mother will be angry.
I don't know what to say.
I'm so busy.
I'm sorry.
You should ask your mother.
I'll ask you something childish.
Why is your neck so long?
That's a good question.
This is the first time.
This is a neck...
No, it's not a neck.
It's called a neck.
Don't laugh.
I don't want to laugh.
It's called a neck because it's very relaxing.
That's why I can't wait for the snacks at 3 o'clock.
My neck is so long.
It's true.
Who is the turtle?
It's not me.
It's me.
It's not you.
It's a snake.
It's like this.
What are you doing?
You're a fool.
If you say complicated things, I'll be in trouble.
I'll call your brother.
Hello, I'd like to ask you a question.
What do you want to ask?
It's the same thing.
No one calls a girl like this.
Brother?
Say it.
Hello, I'd like to ask you a question.
It's the same thing.
I'd like to ask you a question.
Why is the door open?
Get out of here.
Hello.
I'd like to ask you a question.
What is it?
I'll explain it to you.
I'd like to ask you a question.
I'm Matsumoto's sister.
I'm not your sister.
I'm Matsumoto's brother.
I'd like to ask you a question.
What is it?
Well...
I'm sorry, but I have a catchphrase.
What?
You don't have a catchphrase.
I'm doing a lot of things.
I don't use catchphrases.
I speak politely.
Hello, what's wrong?
I'm your brother.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Is the catchphrase okay?
It's okay.
Hello.
What is it?
Well...
I'd like to ask you a question.
How can a baby be born?
I see.
It's a baby.
Hey!
What kind of phone call is that?
It's a baby.
It's a very childlike answer.
It's a childlike answer.
Hello, what's wrong?
Hello, brother.
Yes.
I'd like to ask you a question.
How does a dog bark?
Hmm...
That's a great question.
Is it a great question?
You're very tired.
I see.
Yes.
How does a dog bark?
That's right.
This is a very difficult question.
Is that so?
That's why I'll look it up.
Don't hang up. Wait.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'll be out soon.
Okay.
Wait for me.
Don't hang up your phone.
Who's calling?
Hello?
Is that clear?
...
That was the last one!
It's over.
Time flies.
There's still more.
Yeah.
Next time I'll take a break.
You should take a break.
We're not breaking up.
I don't know if I'm going to be attacked.
I don't want to get hurt because of this song.
But I don't want to get hurt because of this song.
That's enough!
Thank you for watching.