New Year's Special Project
Happy New Year!
Today is the New Year's Special Project.
At the 99th Gaki no Tsukai Arahen,
we will be giving you the top 10 most interesting videos.
Today, I will be the general director.
I am Yoshimoto Kogyo, Fujiwara Hiroshi.
Congratulations!
This is the end of the formal greeting.
Everyone, looking back on 1999,
how was it for you, Matsumoto-san?
Well, I don't know how to put it.
It was a year without much of this.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm Hamada-san.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Let's start with the top 10.
The video will be played.
This is a game where you play in the bus.
The adults are trying to play the game.
The second point is Akihabara.
Akihabara.
Katsura.
Sanshi.
Irasshai.
Katsura.
Sanshi.
Good job, Riki-chan.
You're doing it wrong.
Let's start from the end.
Katsura.
Sanshi.
Irasshai.
Katsura.
Sanshi.
Irasshai.
Katsura.
Sanshi.
Kazura!
Sanshi!
Welcome!
Let's go apologize!
I was looking at Masamune for a second.
Why?
Can't you borrow it?
What is this?
I'm really moved.
What are you talking about?
You're a pervert.
This is weird.
No.
Fukuoka Taihei Hokusu Japan 1st place! Congratulations!
This is funny.
It was fun.
I want to do this.
There's a lot of money on it.
Everyone, listen!
Maybe...
...Chuunichi will win.
Let's change it.
Let's change it to the Chuunichi version.
Chuunichi will win! Congratulations!
Wow!
B-class is here again.
B-class comedians.
B-class actors.
B-class musicians.
C-class copywriters.
Copywriters?
It's a big event once a year. It's an event that gathers people from all over the world.
This time, there are a lot of people from all over the world.
It's an exciting battle on the water.
Today's winner is...
...Kato Akari!
Amazing!
Bye bye.
7th place is a child-friendly game.
It's a kiss-and-kiss game.
The players who have competed in the past have become the target of the game.
The downside of this game is that it's an exciting battle on the water.
The name of the person who took part in the Chouja Banzuke in 1999...
...best 10!
Akashiya-sanma.
Akashiya-sanma!
You're the one who said it!
No, no, no, wait a minute.
Now...
Please come out!
I'm sorry.
That face...
This guy licks his nose.
It stinks!
This idiot licked his nose!
He has a good face.
That old lady really has a good face.
She even brought me a beer.
I mean, she did bring me a beer.
I read it and came here.
What's with the rain?
I was about to drown.
You're fast!
Why are you so slow?
I'm getting really angry.
No, no, no, no, no.
Who saw that?
You just said it and then...
I'm going home.
Really.
Good luck.
Not yet, not yet.
That's scary.
I was looking at you.
This is no good.
Why are you so slow?
What are you doing?
This is no good.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, go!
Go, go, go!
Are you okay?
I hit you, I hit you!
Hey!
What's wrong?
I hit your leg.
You're dead.
What?
You can call an ambulance.
Where's the ambulance?
There's an ambulance at the shopping mall.
Why?
I think that's strange.
You'll understand when you see this.
When it's your turn, call an ambulance.
It's an ambulance.
You'll understand when you see this.
I think you'll say the same thing.
But you should come here.
You're an ambulance.
An ambulance is strange.
I'll go for now.
I got the money.
Itabashi-san.
Madam.
You can read it.
Of course, I can read it.
Tanaka Dayo, everyone, gather around!
The red one.
Tanaka Dayo, who started the game with his own vision, has gathered around.
But at the end, Hamada was waiting for a tough prank to beat him.
You're the winner!
I'm the winner?
Tanaka Dayo is the winner?
Why is it Tanaka Dayo?
I think this is strange.
What do you mean?
What do you think, Yano-kun?
What do you think?
What?
You haven't done the same thing twice.
I'm sorry.
I did it on purpose.
On purpose.
You're on purpose!
I'm sorry.
What are you?
This is scary.
I'm sorry.
Hey, you're getting older!
What are you doing?
It's a trap.
What is this?
Sorry.
You're lying.
I'm not lying.
Wait a minute.
What's the problem?
You're crying.
I really thought you were going to cry.
That's not cool.
Please wait a minute.
This is fun.
You're so mean.
Well, that's for the cut chocolate sauce.
That's all right.
It's a bad way to say later.
Would it have been okay if I was in first place?
Well, that's too bad.
You got a lot of punches.
Well, I know.
As a good partner, this guy is a scary guy, a scary guy, and a good guy!
This is also...
This is also a famous scene from last year.
This project was carried out by Hamada, an inexperienced scuba diver, to the pool.
At the end of the year, we were supposed to take a commemorative photo at the bottom of the pool 5m deep.
Don't make me laugh!
Please let me go!
That's right!
Hey, listen to me!
You can't talk about yourself at all, and you can't give it to me at all!
I'm screaming, but you can't give it to me at all!
Finally, the 10th anniversary underwater commemorative photo was taken.
What happened to Hamada and Matsumoto?
Hey, I'm starting to lose my confidence!
I'm definitely going to blow my head off!
That's shocking!
I don't care if I blow my head off on a TV program like this!
If Hamada can't make it, I can't make it!
Let's go over there!
It's okay, it's okay!
The 10th anniversary underwater commemorative photo was taken.
I wonder if I can get out of here?
I think he's going to pass!
He's going to pass!
In the end, only Hamada was not able to dive.
Even the commemorative photo was taken without Hamada.
24 hours! Hamada and Matsumoto are open!
Today is the 3-second campaign of Nippon TV.
I'll challenge it live for a whole day!
It's raining today, so everyone, please bring an umbrella and go out!
We're in the middle of a commercial for Super TV!
Four minutes until the next commercial.
Hamada changes his clothes in a hurry.
Matsumoto's master is Stan Hansen.
This is a commercial for Super TV.
I didn't have time for this.
I don't understand at all.
I'm watching TV!
I don't understand at all!
Everyone is in the middle of a commercial!
He's the uncle of pudding pudding.
The cooking show is also in the middle of a commercial!
I didn't have time for this.
Next, Matsumoto's instruction is...
Oh, I'm sorry.
The same person is also in the middle of a commercial in the weather report section of the news platform.
Super TV, tonight at 9 o'clock.
Next, Matsumoto's instruction is...
What is that?
My face is hotter than the one I know!
I'm preparing for the avilence.
I'm wearing tiger pants.
Are you kidding me?
24 hours, Hamada Masatoshi is in the middle of a commercial.
He only has one thing left to do.
I'm sorry, but this is the last one.
What is it?
Is it a mess?
Of course.
I think it means the last one.
Next, Matsumoto's instruction is...
Sakura fubuki no sarai no sora
Mabushii to
Finish it!
I see.
That's right.
Isn't this number one?
It's number one.
That was the best.
Sugachan no Panchira Gekisha Dai-san.
I wanted to see that.
That was also my favorite.
Is it that?
Is it the God of Gags?
What is it?
Is it that?
This is the announcement of number one.
Number one.
Now, let's start the VTR.
What are you doing?
I think it's probably that.
And the number one is this project.
I'm getting nervous.
Kawasaki!
Stop it!
Alright!
I'm counting on you!
Here I go!
Good!
I'm getting nervous.
Do you see the difference?
It's vertical.
Where is this?
It's here.
It's this big.
0.3 seconds.
It's 0.03 seconds.
It's the button.
I can't get the button.
It's the God of Gags!
Alright.
I admit defeat.
Wait a minute.
I'm resisting.
Do you admit defeat?
No, I don't.
I win!
So, Team Hamada!
Penalty game!
You're really looking forward to the penalty game.
That's strange.
No, I don't want to do it.
I just want to do it smoothly and get a penalty.
That's right.
You're definitely thinking about something bad.
In the history of a battle that has created many great battles,
there is another battle that has carved a new page.
It's a battle of 100 meters of sweat and tears.
As a result, Team Hamada challenged Matsumoto, who betrayed the expectations of the big guy, and won.
And there is only one task left.
What kind of penalty game will Team Hamada play this year?
It's connected here.
It's connected.
That's right.
This is it.
The first place.
That's right.
The penalty game is also progressing steadily.
This time, it will be a penalty game with four people in total.
There are four people, so even if one person loses, there are three people.
Even if one person loses?
For example, if one person dies.
It's the same as the next game.
It's a penalty game.
There's nothing I can't do.
If I had said something good, I wouldn't have been punished.
It's your fault.
That's right.
It's really your fault.
I don't think the ending is that bad.
If Hamada-san had caught it, he wouldn't have lost.
This is your fault?
That's right.
What's wrong with this?
Of course, this person is also bad.
But if you look at me, you can see that I didn't make a mistake.
If you made a mistake there, Matsumoto-san would have panicked and we would have gone smoothly.
That's the start.
I know you're losing in the end game.
I can't make a mistake in the end game.
That's too naive.
You would have made a mistake.
That's the answer.
Look at my belly.
I made a mistake.
What? What is it?
What are you trying to do?
I don't know.
I wanted to say, look at my belly.
But there was a button.
Calculate it.
That's the answer.
I made a mistake.
Please take care of me this year as well.
Don't do that.
More importantly, look at my belly.