This is the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Arai!
Chikichiki Warasube Chouja Daigashisen!
Dun dun dun dun dun dun!
Today, we're going to do a quick exchange.
You and I are going to take a copy of the Japanese TV show
and go all the way to Akasaka.
For example, this is the product you have.
If you take a picture of this broadcast paper...
This is the set of Arai.
This is what it looks like.
This is pretty nice, isn't it?
It's pretty good for children and old people.
It will make a wide range of people happy.
This is the set of the Japanese TV show I like.
I don't need it!
It's too weak.
This!
But it might be good on a rainy day.
Really?
It's better to take each of these and buy something more expensive.
How much would it be if I bought this?
About 1,500 yen?
That's about right.
Well, let's go.
Do you have 20 minutes?
I'm counting on you.
You spent a lot of time the other day, didn't you?
That's a pretty good deal.
I don't know.
It's cowardly.
I don't want to waste my time.
I'll give you 400 yen.
That's a problem, so I'll do my best.
It's a problem after all.
Well, let's go for now.
Do you have anything you can exchange?
A tissue.
Are you kidding me?
Mom, come here.
Mom, let's talk.
That's a good character.
I'm going to the supermarket.
I'll take this.
3,500 yen.
Excuse me.
This.
How much is it?
3,500 yen.
Here you go.
That's not it.
Who's going to do it?
This is a Japanese TV show.
I'm going to exchange things.
I'm going to buy something from your shop.
I'm doing it.
So I'm going to buy something from your shop.
I'm going to buy something from your shop.
The most expensive one.
And this.
I want you to exchange this with this.
I'll do it.
Are you sure?
Yes.
You did it.
This is a persimmon.
You like persimmons, don't you?
It's delicious.
And this.
This is nice.
This bouquet.
I'm going to exchange it for 4 of them.
Please wait a second.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
It's okay?
Yes.
It's a good thing.
I'm going to tell you about the shop.
This is in Akasaka.
Kirishima Flower.
Akasaka.
I'm looking for a part-time job.
I'm not asking for experience. I'm asking for a person with guts.
Why do you need guts to be a flower gardener?
Thank you very much.
It's about 3,500 yen.
3,500 yen?
I can't go anywhere.
You can't go anywhere?
Can't you go to Kyushu?
Do you have a day trip tour to Kyushu?
If I'm going to walk, I can.
You're going to walk? You idiot.
Excuse me.
Well,
I'd like to give you this bouquet of flowers.
I'll give it to you.
Can you put a perm on my hair?
I can't help but look at you.
Excuse me.
This bouquet of flowers.
Can you buy me a more luxurious one?
I'll sell this at this store.
Can you give me a bouquet of flowers worth 10,000 yen?
That's a lot.
Is this okay?
It's okay.
You're not saying this is cheap, are you?
It's not cheap.
I'm just showing you the melon.
Excuse me.
Can you give me a Piero of this pistol?
Which one do you want?
This one and this one.
With melon.
Do you want to do it?
Yes.
Please give it to me.
I'll give this to you.
This one.
This is the last one.
Where did you get this?
From Jaeger.
Jaeger.
This is a shirt worth 12,000 yen from Jaeger.
Plus Christian Dior's handkerchief set.
In the end, it's back to this.
Idiot.
You're such an idiot.
It's Christian Dior.
Well.
This is 12,000 yen and this is 3,000 yen, so it's 15,000 yen.
I'll stop here.
Then I'll go.
With this bouquet of flowers.
This kind of thing.
Yes.
Here you are.
This...
What is this?
This girl.
When I said I'll give you this bouquet of flowers, she followed me.
Can you do it with a bouquet of flowers?
Yes.
Yes, I can.
Really?
I really did it.
You did it with me, right?
I did.
I said I did it.
Really?
Yes.
Let me do it, too.
Really?
You have to do it.
Three pieces?
If you don't have flowers, she doesn't have eyes for flowers.
I'll go buy some.
I'll run around with flowers.
Yes.
That's amazing.
That's right.
If you don't bring me a bouquet of flowers.
Yes, I'll go to the center.
I see.
But I brought the manager, too.
Did you do it with the manager?
Can you do it with me?
Manager.
The manager was good.
Hello.
What's going on?
He's already laughing.
What's so funny?
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting for so long.
I was thinking about what to do today.
It's embarrassing to make a mistake.
A mistake?
The day before yesterday.
There was an ugly woman who always came to the apartment.
She told me to leave the apartment alone.
I didn't care.
If it was a normal person, I would apologize.
I like to lie.
I'm sorry.
My fans are usually ugly.
Why?
I'm really shy.
I'm walking in the morning.
I'm scared.
I'm walking like I'm possessed by something.
I thought this stupid woman would come again.
I stopped the car and opened the window.
I looked at her.
She was completely different.
She looked like you.
She looked like me.
I looked at her.
She was completely different.
Her face was expressionless.
I couldn't do it.
Why?
Her face was expressionless.
What did she say?
She said,
Walk on the sidewalk.
It's dangerous.
She looked like her sister's brother who died in a car accident.
She was like a parent.
She was like,
It's dangerous.
She closed the window and looked at me.
I feel sorry for you.
I said,
I did something bad.
You didn't do anything.
You just came to my house.
I said that, but I didn't like it.
Why?
I don't know what the middle and high school students are thinking.
There was a man who took a picture of the door of the apartment.
What did he take?
You didn't do it.
I didn't do it.
That's why everyone laughed.
He said,
Bring it here.
When I came back,
Are you stupid?
That's all.
That's not me.
It's a picture.
I was surprised when I came back.
Well,
What?
There's something we have to do.
We have to communicate with each other.
Yes.
And I can communicate with anyone.
For example,
Let's say Hamada says,
Yuuri.
Then,
Rinsu.
First of all,
I'm the owner who can always return it with su.
What did you think?
He says it's impossible.
It's impossible for me.
That's why we're going to play a game of winning and losing.
The loser has to play a penalty game.
Yes.
It's like a zoom-in in the morning.
And we said,
Let's think about it.
Did you think about it?
I didn't think about it.
I can see your enthusiasm for this program.
I've thought about it a lot.
Penalty game.
For example,
Alta.
Studio Alta.
There's a big screen of Alta, right?
The loser has to come out there.
Oh,
That's good.
Yes.
How do you come out?
I have to tie the rope.
SM rope?
Yes.
The rope is like this.
The middle is like this.
The ground is like this.
One by one.
It's like this.
Yes.
On the big screen of Alta.
Look at the staff.
Next Tuesday.
Yes.
At 1.40 pm.
I'll be in charge of the staff of Alta.
Yes.
What is that?
Don't you have to say that it's hard to tie the rope?
Yes.
I see.
I'll do that.
Yes.
Do you understand?
Let's do it.
I'll do it.
You do it.
Yes.
I'll do it.
Suwashi.
What?
You're at this distance.
Where did you ask me?
Suwashi.
What is Suwashi?
It's Suwashi.
It's a foot that doesn't wear socks.
Shiwasu.
You're beautiful from the front.
Five, four...
Suito.
Why?
What?
It's Suito.
Usu.
Suika.
Karasu.
Swimming.
Grease.
Wait a minute.
Suetto.
What?
Tosu.
Tosu?
Wait a minute.
You've been breaking the rules.
What?
You should have told me earlier.
Su?
I didn't hear you.
You shouldn't have told me.
You should have told me.
I didn't hear you.
I'm thinking about it now.
What?
What are you doing?
I'm going to finish this.
You're scary.
Suomachi.
What?
It's in Osaka.
You can't say the name of the town.
You're breaking the rules.
You've been breaking the rules.
I don't care.
I'm a professional wrestler.
You're a wrestler?
I didn't hear you.
Say it.
I'm from Scandinavia.
You can't say the name of the town.
I'm from Skye.
What?
You can't say the name of the town.
Skye.
Is.
Fine.
I don't care.
Skye.
What?
I'm from Skye.
You're strange.
You can say the name of the town.
I can say the name of the town.
You're stupid.
I'm from Skye.
You can't say that.
Say it properly.
Explain it.
What is Skye?
It's a pronoun.
It has nothing to do with it.
You can't say it.
Say it.
Say it quickly.
Shut up.
I won't listen to you.
It's been a long time.
Sukiyaki.
Kirigirisu.
Skip.
Prince.
Pan.
Scuba.
Burth.
What is the name of the town?
Is it strange?
Why?
Is the name of the town strange?
It's fine.
Don't laugh.
I'm thinking while doing this.
I'm a double young.
Do it quickly.
Wait.
You don't need my song.
Three.
Wait.
Say it quickly.
It's been a long time.
Scratch.
What is that?
Chadan-su.
Skate.
Base.
Tsukekomashi.
You can't do that.
Why?
Make it something that can be brought.
Tsukekomashi.
Yes.
How many people are there?
That's small.
Yes.
Tsukekomashi.
Let's end it.
Let's stop it.
What are you doing?
Shihira Kansun.
I lost.
Sugoroku.
It's fine.
You lost.
No one saw it.
There's nothing left.
Sugoroku.
Cross.
Sushi.
Shiwasu.
Yuta.
The shiwasu I said earlier is from the day before yesterday.
It doesn't matter.
You lost.
It's over.
It's not good.
Aruta and Matsumoto-kun.
I'll be with you when you take this.
I'll help you tie it up.
Really?
I'll watch over you.
It's just the two of us.
Don't make me laugh.
After graduating from high school,
I got a job at Nippon Arbite News.
Matsumoto-kun called me Matsumoto-kun.
Matsumoto-kun, let's go to Yoshimoto together and do it.
Where did you go at that time?
What are you going to do with our history?
Why don't we do it together?
But that's...
That's...
Matsumoto-kun.
The two of you are careful with your eyes.
That's not the case.
Do it properly.
Let's do it together.
No, I can't do it.
I'll watch over you.
You're really dirty.
What?
That's it.
I think it's out now.
I think it's out.
We'll meet in front of the altar at the time of the event.
Please look forward to it.
I want you to come to see it.
That's for sure.
The people who are here today are crazy.
It's true.
You guys are the only ones who remember the face.
Do you have enough time today?
Please give me a postcard.
Today, too.
Assistant.
It's been a long time since I've seen you dressed like this on our show.
Why don't you try to tie your hair?
I'd like to see that.
Do you have a boyfriend?
No.
You're looking for a boyfriend?
Who do you want to see?
Well...
You don't have to tie your hair like that.
I don't like it.
Thank you very much.
I put it in here, too.
Do you have a postcard?
No.
This was pretty interesting.
I'll introduce it to you.
This is a person who says hello.
What's your name?
Mr. Yasukawa.
Yes.
I found something similar to Hamada-kun from the textbook.
This is it.
It's similar.
The one in the front.
What?
From the left.
It's similar.
It's really similar.
Is that so?
Yes.
That's about it.
You talked a lot today.
It's been a long time.
It's been a long time since I've seen you dressed like this on our show.
Really.
I'll do a lot of impersonations next week.
Really?
Yes.
What are you doing today?
Shut up.
Watch the show.
Thank you very much.
Also today,
Yes.
in the rain.
That's right.
It was difficult.
Yes.
Is it not gonna rain?
On Ame-no-Hi
Right?
I am but why...
Let's have some fun.
If you complain about it in the rain, I don't know what to do.
Let's do it.
Before that, more than that.
What?
I don't feel like I've lost.
You idiot.
You're still a kid.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to be an adult and be tied up.
What kind of adult?
Well, for the time being, that's what happened.
Let's tie him up.
I hope he doesn't get angry.
It was out.
Please enjoy the time.
And do you have time?
As usual, I'm an assistant.
People who help me with my body.
I'll take a picture of the reaction.
I'm waiting for various questions.
That's it.
That's it for today.
Thank you for watching.
Goodbye.