Okamoto's funny or not funny quiz!
Mr. Okamoto, you were rescued by a cat, right?
What about you, Mr. Okamoto?
It seems so.
I don't know myself.
Funny or not funny.
I see.
It's out of tune.
Especially recently.
Out of tune?
Very out of tune.
Out of tune.
Downtown out of tune.
Now, let's start with downtown.
I'll check everyone's funny or not funny.
I see.
Okamoto has absolute confidence in his comedy.
His sense is more than downtown.
This time, he'll use his junior, Isomata, to check out Hamada Matsumoto's sense of humor.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Okamoto's funny or not funny quiz part 1
Look at this.
Is it starting already?
It's starting already.
Don't let your guard down.
What's your problem?
That's right.
I'm a strange old man.
It's out of tune.
What's this?
It's not funny.
I'm sorry.
I don't think it's funny.
I can't help but laugh because it's funny.
It's not funny.
It's out of tune.
I don't think it's funny.
It's funny now.
Isomata is funny now?
If you don't tell me it's funny, I can't help it.
It's out of tune.
You guys have a lot of complaints.
I'm really sorry.
You take too much time off.
I'll tell you the truth.
I'm counting on you.
You take too much time off.
If you notice it.
You don't tell me anything.
It's scary that there's no one to tell me.
I'm a strange old man.
It's not funny.
It's out of tune.
I'm a strange old man.
I don't know.
I'm kind of a weird old man.
Don't you want to go home?
I see.
Then, I'll go home.
I like the first half.
Don't you feel bad because it's too long?
It's the same.
The first half was good.
The second half was too much.
It's incorrect.
What?
It's incorrect?
What is it?
Yamazaki.
I don't know this.
I don't know either.
I see.
He doesn't sleep.
He works like a horse.
He works a lot.
The last one.
Yes.
Meow.
How was it?
Was it interesting or not?
Was it interesting?
It wasn't interesting.
I'm sorry.
I don't know.
What he does is interesting.
It's interesting.
Including the staff.
Okamoto, who was worried about the sense of downtown, continued to ask more difficult questions.
Okamoto, interesting or not?
Check part 2.
First of all, this.
Tell me it's a matter.
Stop it.
I was surprised.
This is interesting.
It's like a woman eating her teeth.
Next.
Do you love me?
No.
No, I don't.
Do you love me?
No.
This is also interesting.
Naturally.
It's also interesting.
I'm not a funny guy.
I'm a funny guy.
I think the woman is funny.
That's it.
I thought that would be funny.
It's a little off.
I think so.
I don't want to write on the bulletin board.
That's funny.
The last one.
The last one?
No.
I love you.
I love you too much.
I love you too.
I love you.
I love you too much.
I love you too.
I love you.
It doesn't work.
I'm sorry.
It was fun.
Did you get it?
I'm sorry.
What?
What is good?
That...
I can't do it.
Take a break.
I'm sorry.
Go home.
I said go home.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
Go home.
You're back.
Why don't you go home and change your manager?
The audience is close.
Right?
There's a big difference between when the audience is cheerful and when they're not.
What do you think about today?
We're in a bad mood.
Yes, what is it?
When I came down here earlier,
I thought I'd go to the bathroom.
I asked if it was okay to go to the bathroom now.
My manager said,
It's okay because you're not here.
That's not what I meant.
I don't want to go to the bathroom again.
That's how it is.
Hana-chan.
What is it?
Hana-chan, this is...
There's green onions stuck in my teeth.
It's terrible.
Take it off.
No, no, no.
I'm going all the way to the end.
I can't take it off.
I've already eaten green onions stuck in my teeth.
There's a lot of cicadas in there.
Wait a minute.
It's really amazing, so you should take it off.
It's all green.
I don't have teeth like this.
It's not.
There's a lot of green onions in there.
I don't know if it's green or not.
It's hard.
What is it?
I don't know.
Bring me a mirror.
It's all green, so you should take it off.
It's definitely a lie.
It's true.
No, no, no.
This is...
It's a fairy tale.
That's where we meet.
We don't talk in the dressing room.
No, no, no.
You can't do that.
What kind of mirror is that?
It's a mirror for makeup.
This is my own work.
What kind of mirror is that?
It's my own work.
I can't see the upper teeth even if I talk.
Basically, I've already taken it off.
You've already taken it off?
How many times have you taken it off?
It's blue.
Oh, I saw it a little.
Why am I so nervous?
That's how it is.
I'm always sleepy.
That's what I think.
Tokyo is...
What is this?
There's a lot of crows.
There's a lot of trash in the neighborhood.
There's a lot of trash near the bar.
Why am I near the bar?
I live near the bar.
I live on the second floor and play the trumpet.
Did you bring it?
No, no, no.
What is it?
Osaka is...
Wait a minute.
What is it?
What?
You took it off.
What are the boots?
It's the worst.
There are no crows in Osaka.
I've never seen it.
It's definitely the fourth floor.
That's what makes me angry.
When I play the trumpet,
Ah!
No, no, no.
That's not true.
It's definitely the fourth floor.
I won't drop it on the fourth floor.
It's nice.
Like you.
It's Hollywood.
Why?
Hollywood?
It's not Hollywood.
It's Japan.
It's not Beverly Hills.
Not at all.
No, it's definitely Beverly Hills.
Why?
Because, you know,
when a celebrity has a family,
it changes a lot.
Even Higa Shino's daughter
goes to an American school.
I can't think of that.
That's your parents' way of thinking.
Daddy!
That's what they say.
I'll beat you up.
You're the one who says that.
If you have children,
you'll understand.
No, that's not true.
It's very strict.
I don't understand that.
If you have children,
you'll always have a paper knife.
You can't do that.
That's not true.
It's not that bad.
In the end,
if you care about your children,
your parents...
they don't care about you.
That's right.
If you look at their eyes,
you'll understand.
Your eyes are dead.
They don't care about you.
At that time,
your father didn't care about you.
That's not true.
Well...
You can say that.
Can you say that?
You were brought up like a child.
That's not true.
That's what everyone thinks.
You were raised in love, right?
I was raised.
Your father was a bit strange too.
You're really overreacting.
There's nothing wrong with that.
I wasn't a good father, right?
You weren't a good father?
No way!
Why are you lying?
I wasn't a good father, right?
You weren't a good father?
I always wore a kimono with a UZUMAKI pattern.
Why?!
You were wearing a obi-kone.
I was wearing a obi-kone with a UZUMAKI pattern on my cheeks.
Right?
That's funny.
That's the opposite.
For example, if you did that, I would do the same.
That's fine, but...
We started with the story about Higashino.
That's right. Everyone is like that.
They're going to Hawaii this New Year, right?
That's right.
They're going to Higashino with their families, right?
It doesn't matter!
Everyone really likes to go abroad, right?
It's cold.
I want to go somewhere warm.
For example, if I do that for a week or two.
You can't do that?
It's cold.
Just like when you wake up in the morning,
you're like a timer.
You're like a timer.
What?
Don't exaggerate it!
Everyone is like that.
I don't know.
Everyone knows.
And if you ask me where I'm going, I'll say Hyakka-tei.
You're a poor man.
Why? I don't feel cold at all.
That's not true.
I'll go to the toilet. The toilet seat is warm.
There's nothing cold about it.
If you ask me, the toilet seat is Hawaii. It's the same as Wai-kiki.
The flow is the same as Wai-kiki.
It's Honolulu.
What the hell?
Which would you like to compare it to?
It's the same, right?
What's so interesting about it?
What's so interesting about Hawaii? Tell me.
The beach? Do you run on the beach like this?
This is the most interesting part.
Like this?
That's enough.
Okay, I got it.
Like this?
It's fun when you can see this part.
Where is it?
This is from the entertainer Mohan Matsumoto.
This is my eldest son, Koichi.
I can't wake up early. What should I do?
It's an impact.
What?
I put cutlet in my body.
Cutlet.
I put a surprising cutlet in my body.
Do you understand?
If you put that in, you can't wake up every day.
That's right.
For example, I'm sleeping and I wake up.
I'm still in a daze.
My body is also in a daze.
I think he's going to brush his teeth.
He's got a body.
I'm surprised.
My body is like grilled meat.
It's like a body.
From the morning.
I've had a hard time since the morning.
I'm surprised.
And it has nothing to do with you not being able to wake up in the morning.
Why?
I'm not telling you how to wake up.
That's right.
What you're doing is what you do after you wake up.
How do you wake him up?