Next time, let's play the original game of the Genshin Impact!
It's amazing that you can still be so strong while sitting on this chair.
You don't have to use your abs.
Stop messing around with the Donami.
I don't want to get in the way of the game.
What are we doing today?
What are we doing?
Don't eat my chin!
This is that, right?
When I was being made a castle by Kun-chan
We all played a game together
The future-lover Cookie who was broadcasted in May has come
Actually, he is behind Hamada's make-up
I'm going to start playing some simple games now.
Please look forward to it.
Isn't that hell?
Hell? It's okay.
He made him play a game that was hard to understand.
But Hamada-san, that was cut out.
That's right.
Oh, really?
You're saying we should play that game that was cut out?
I don't know.
So you did it because you knew it?
There are many games like that in the world of Tomaoka and Yoshi.
It's a second half, isn't it?
It's a game that was first halfed.
I played board games a while ago.
It's fun.
But it's a game that comedians first halfed, so I can't lose to that.
It's so funny.
I'm thinking about something really interesting.
I'm in the back!
It was a cover!
I'm looking forward to today's show.
Let's do it together.
Let's go.
The first one, please.
The first one is...
Oh!
Please come here.
This is a very interesting game that we thought of.
Don't say it!
You haven't explained it yet!
Chocolate Planet.
What is the original game they thought of?
Original!
The game we brought is this!
It's a scary game.
I was given a role of Motoya Izumi.
In that role, I walk slowly and slowly with a strong voice.
It's a funny joke.
I used that as a game.
It's a game that returns the subject to the original meaning.
For example, if the subject is a banana, it's a little bit sly.
It's like this.
If it's frozen, it's cold.
It's cold.
You put it on a rhythm and then you return it.
The rhythm is...
So-lori, so-lori, pon-pon, banana, zuru-ri, zuru-ri, pon-pon, kouri.
You connect it like this.
Do you understand?
Is it okay?
No, if you put a rhythm in...
I'm not confident right now.
But it was really fun, right?
Uuuhhh!
Dondaga!
What are you doing?
What is this?
No, no.
The game quality is too high.
It's not even close.
I'm really happy.
The game is called Kyogen Sorori Sorori Game.
You have to connect the words with the rhythm of the word.
If you can't say the same word, you will be out.
I will start.
and I'm going to start a saying game
Solori Solori
Pon Pon,...
Towel
Fut자를 finish
Pon Pon
T-shirt
Mel cast
OK celebrate
I can't become a woman
You have to repeat it once.
That's right.
If it's Melody, then say it.
I can't do Melody.
If you say Melody, then it's Melody.
Please answer once.
Slowly.
You're doing it slowly.
We're professionals.
You're too focused on that part.
I understand.
I'll start again.
Let's start with a different topic.
You'll say it with a different one.
I'll do it slowly.
Slowly.
One, two, three, four.
PON PON
Camera
Pashari
PON PON
Dog
Ne-me-ri
What's with that?
What does that mean?
Ne-me-ri?
Ne-me-ri and...
If it's Ne-me-ri, then I don't get it.
Ne-me-ri.
I've never heard of it.
Even if it's Ne-me-ri, it's in the director's head.
It's Ne-me-ri, right?
I'm sorry, but it's not turning at all.
I want you to do it!
It's a rule now!
I'll go first
Please say the next word
I'll go
Pon pon
Kame pon pon
Sorori sorori
Pon pon Udon
Pon pon
What are you doing?
Just a little bit.
What are you talking about?
Oh, that's right.
You're talking about slurries.
It's okay if there's no pompon.
Say it again.
There's a lot of pompon.
It's better to have pompon.
No, no, no.
I want pompon.
I'll put in pompon.
I understand.
I'll do it with Pon Pon.
I think it'll be a little difficult.
I'll do it.
Pon Pon
Tsuyu
Jimeri
Pon Pon
Gorilla
Gorori
Please, please.
No good.
Gorori is a very difficult word.
It's amazing.
You're not even a bit old!
I feel sorry for the ChocoPla!
I'm sorry!
I didn't think it would last this long!
Even YouTubers are prettier!
Even though you're adding the sound effects!
You're spending time thinking!
I'll just do it normally from now on.
Pon pon
Ramen
Cheating
Pon pon
Beer
Gokuri
Pon pon
Tobacco
Pucari
Pon pon
Water
Hey!
What are you doing?
You are the same!
I'm sorry! I'm worried about this!
I'm sorry!
And the water came out!
I told you!
It's useless!
I can do it!
Pon pon! Kimono!
Pon pon!
Softly! Softly!
Pon pon! Ramen!
Pon pon! Slyly! Slyly!
Prickly, Pon Pon
Chair, Pon Pon
Sit, Sit, Pon Pon
Three times, Pon Pon
Refreshing, Refreshing
Pon Pon
La, Pa
Prickly
No, no, no, no
No, no, no
Even if you wear it, you'll be dragged by my three times
Three times
But he said something good
That's true
If I say more, he will pull my ramen into my udon
The world view of money
But he said something good
But it's interesting
It's not just a match, it can be done by two people
It can be done by many people
What if it's two people?
Can you do a little downtown?
Downtown?
I can't lose to this
But don't get influenced by me
Don't take my world view
It's a completely different approach
Who should go first?
You go first
You two go first
You
You go first
Oh, well, okay
I'll go first
Ton-ton sumo
Ton-ton
No-sori
Hige
Ton-ton
Jogiri
Helmet
Ton-ton
Sporri
Pants
Ton-ton
Nugiri
Nukeri
That's too bad
I'm safe!
You're safe!
You're a grown-up now!
I'm a cute kid!
I'm a grown-up now!
Please welcome the next comedian!
Hello!
Hello! Thank you!
Thank you!
Shimofuri Myoujo!
The original game tour that they co-authored!
It's like a human bingo, but I want to test your intuition and luck today.
I will explain it.
Seiya's word derby.
I will sing a song that I will sing in a loud voice.
You guys write a word that I will say.
It's a game of luck.
It's difficult if there are too many words.
For example, if the theme is animals,
If you draw an animal, and I say,
I got it!
The person who got it will immediately reject it.
That's the point.
Yes, it's a quick win.
If I get it, I'll break it big time.
Break it big time?
I'll do something amazing.
I can't clear it without luck.
That's what it is.
I can't let someone who doesn't break it break it.
5 people entered the answer without being seen by Seiya
The genre of singing is animal, here are the 5 people's predictions
Will it be the correct answer?
Seiya-san, please
Then, you can't go back to the answer
Asaka-san, you!
You're the one who said it first!
Seiya's word-play derby!
There is only one winner!
Animal!
Start!
Looking up, it's a condor
It has nothing to do with me
To the right, it's a horse, to the left, it's a rabbit
Letting go, it's a horse and a donkey
Al-majiro, Al-majiro
Your attitude is so Al-majiro
Jackal, you're a jackal
Neeee! Neeee! Neeee!
The three-syllable-nose is watching! The three-syllable-nose is watching!
Nakamura Tamao's big picture.
Rabbit! Bonus time!
Dog, turtle, dog, lion, cheetah!
It's here!
Amazing!
How was it?
I don't feel like I've done it.
It's amazing.
It feels good to say yes.
Matsumoto-san, what did you say?
The beaver didn't appear.
The beaver didn't appear?
It's quite rare that it's shown
Like the Narmajiro
Jackal
Yama-chan and I have a giraffe
It's not shown
It's not shown as expected
This one is likely to be shown too
It's an elephant
An elephant won't be shown
It won't be shown
It's really likely to be shown
Next is the second round
The topic is the job that children admire
Here are the 5 people's predictions
I really want you to get it right. I want you to make the best one today.
Here we go!
The second round of the Seiya's Tango Derby!
The food that children long for! Start!
Chan chan chan chan chan chan chan
Zousen Gishi
You only talk about the Hanko family, right?
You always talk about the Hanko family, right?
Electricians don't move like this, right?
Electrician
Lying again.
Was not so cruel.
The guy who Lisa прочagi.
The guy who procede the balance sheet.
Was not so hard.
The guy who preceding the tension sheet.
She patted the wall.
Amazing text.
He should stand his ground.
I love this game!
I think this game can be played by Endo.
Oh, I see.
Endo's Derby.
Endo's
Let's all ride the Shinkansen together, the ambulance!
Suddenly, the Endo Shouzou's Tango Derby is held.
The topic is, Norimono!
Please.
Are you okay?
Everyone, are you okay?
Yes, we're okay.
Did you all get it?
It's Norimono.
Norimono, right?
If I tell you what I said, it'll be amazing.
Here we go, Norimono.
Here we go!
The word of the brain is...
DUMMY!
Oh!
There is a Shinkansen here!
Let's all get on the ambulance!
Oh! There is a helicopter here!
Why? Why?
Why?
What kind of song is this?
I don't know.
Amazing!
I don't know who it is, but thank you for letting me see it early.
Well, it's a little bit of an imagination.
Next, please come on the comedian.
Hello, we are TENSEGO.
TENSEGO also has an interesting game.
Yes, it's so much fun that I'm amazed.
It's so much fun that you're amazed.
It's very simple, so you can play it right away.
I think it's the simplest game out of all the games we've played today.
It's also easy, so anyone can play it.
You don't need to ask your age or gender?
I forgot my clip.
Ah, sorry.
And you don't even notice your calf is being patted.
I can't do it!
What can you do if you don't have the sense of the club?
Semi-Soup!
This time, the person who waited for the comment will come up with an original game!
This is what we came up with!
Was it that kind of voice?
Yes!
If you can see it with your hair, it's a successful game!
Oh!
What does that mean?
There is a paper napkin in the pub.
You take one of them and put it on your forehead.
Then blow it.
Then the paper napkin will be flipped.
If you can make eye contact with everyone, you succeed.
It's very simple.
What is it?
How did you come up with that?
When?
What?
I thought of this at 3PM when I was drinking with a comedian
This is a game that comedians play when they go to pubs
Who came up with this idea?
Me
It has nothing to do with me
You were trying to liven up the atmosphere
What's wrong with your pocket?
What?
I'll liven up the atmosphere when I succeed
What's wrong with your pocket?
I have one. I was thinking of making it more exciting, but Yukio-chan is still thinking about whether to do it or not.
Ah, I see.
I just put it in my pocket.
Well, you'll never know until you try it.
Scary, scary, scary.
It's a failure. It's a failure.
It's a failure.
The game is called, If you can see with your eyes, you win.
If you can see with your eyes, you win.
Let's start the game.
Take a piece of paper napkin.
You have to cover your eyes.
You have to lift the rice cake up to the top.
You have to lift it up and blow it.
That's how it works.
The game starts with picking the paper napkin.
From here...
The one with a strange habit.
I think it's better to have a dry surface.
Everyone is looking at this.
I'll just look at Mr. Matsumoto.
While I'm turning around, I'll look at everyone.
Can I not move?
You can just put your face up like this.
Can I put my hands up first?
Yes, you can.
Please put your hands up.
Can someone say something?
Ready, start!
Find her
You failed
Can't you see?
Your eyes響きません
Not bad
This is a new standing
I can't see
As犬
Autograph
A h den
This is not good
Your eyes are doing well
Here
Both eyes?
Yes
Even with one eye?
I thought it was the same with one eye
Ready, start!
It's there
It was your chance
You were that slow?
I can't see everyone so fast
I'm doing it
Next, Hamada challenges
Please cover it up to the top.
Yes, that's good.
I'm ready.
Is this guy dead?
This guy is dead, right?
The white one, right?
It's a failure.
It's a complete failure.
Let's do it again.
I'll try the other way around.
This one is better.
I can do it.
I see.
This way.
Ready, start.
He's dead.
I can only see his eyebrows.
It's so funny.
Why is it so difficult?
Matsushita shows his example.
Really?
He's a champion.
If you can't see it, I won't say it.
I see.
Let's go. Ready, start.
Wow!
What a great sound!
I didn't hear that.
It was a good sound.
It's from the World Cup.
I don't know.
I didn't hear that.
It was a good sound.
I heard it from the town hall.
You can't do it with Yukio?
I've never done it before
I'll try it once
How do you do it with Suigouji?
I don't know
Shiopara 2018
The bus that is familiar to the series of the kids' use and the series of the kids' use
This year, it is also going through a hard time
Will the viewers of the comedy that are coming to watch it be able to endure it?
We are waiting for you!
Get it!
Finally, Ueno will challenge
I'm going
Ready, start!
Ah, it went into my mouth
Oh, did it succeed?
It didn't work
It's a success!
You used too much of your energy
I can't say that I split the winning searching
91st South Key game
I'm so deceiving
And becoming more exciting