Chikichiki! Dr. Matsumoto's sudden-strike entertainer!
Score!
Teacher.
Yes?
This is the second time.
That's right. You can't finish this machine in one go.
But I understood the size of the first entertainer.
After that, the guests came to my studio.
Why did you understand?
I was surprised.
Isn't it the same?
It's the same, Masao.
Well, this time too.
Well, this year we don't have enough water.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's true.
It was last year.
It's a project that really shows the entertainer's ***.
We don't have enough rice.
Last year, right?
Yes.
Let's go now.
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
I'm Kageki Shimoda.
I'm a teacher.
Do you have any stories like that?
Well, it's not a story.
I had an interesting dream when I was in my 20s.
I fell asleep in the field of spring and woke up suddenly.
I was wondering what had happened to me.
I saw a wing and I was waiting around here.
It's a wonderful dream.
I will never forget it.
I see.
Let's see Kageki's ***.
I have two questions.
Let's go.
It's impossible to buy a condom, so I use a semi-transparent garbage bag.
That's not true.
When I was an electrician, UFO contacted me for some reason.
I have a similar feeling to that.
Is it true?
It depends on the angle.
Yes.
It's like an antenna.
I got it.
Did you get it?
Yes.
Please.
It's moving away.
I got it.
This is good.
This is a good one.
It's thin.
It's thin, but the front one is cool.
Is it cool?
Yes.
But it's not that long.
It's not that long.
I see.
It's blue and red.
Is it like this?
It's closed.
It's like this.
Right.
I see.
It's like this.
Kageki's ***.
Next one, please.
It's a man.
Good evening.
He's a professional.
It's morning.
I see.
Thank you.
I didn't hear it.
Really?
I didn't hear your ***.
I wonder what it is.
I've been *** since I was born.
I'm serious.
Really?
I was born in America.
I see.
It's like that.
He's saying I'm a ***.
I understand that.
Really?
When I see a small ***, I feel like I'm going to throw up.
Why?
Yes.
Why do you feel like you're going to throw up?
I don't know.
Say it out loud.
***.
What?
Who said ***?
It's okay.
It's like that.
You're like a TV host.
Thank you.
What's your favorite name?
Does it matter?
What?
Daikoku?
Daikoku.
That's good.
Okay, I got it.
I got it.
Let's go.
Kuroda's morning ***.
What?
I got it.
Are you sick?
You have a big fat.
It was so big that it didn't even come out of it.
Number 3.
Congratulations.
What are you talking about?
I look forward to working with you again this year.
Thank you.
What's your case like?
It's a little bent.
Normally people turn towards themselves.
This *** is facing the other way.
It's facing the other way.
It's looking at the future.
Is that so?
I've thought about it.
Please sit down.
When I went to Africa, for some reason, people I met mistreated me.
That's the problem.
That's the brain.
Please shout out the name of the teacher.
What? Teacher?
Teacher Yuya!
Yes, okay.
What's that?
Is it okay?
Is it in?
The answer is out.
The *** in the class.
It's out.
What is it?
The *** in the class.
And it's yellow.
What is it?
It's a tough ***.
It's Kuroda Awa-san's ***.
What?
Kuroda Awa-san's *** is amazing.
Look at this.
It's this.
It's dirty.
What is it?
But this is a future type, right?
This is a future type.
Is this a future type?
It's called a ***.
This is Ebisu.
This is Ebisu-san.
Speaking of Ebisu-san, the shadow of a woman is always there.
Where is it?
It's not there at all.
Is there anything like that before?
Once, I was walking around Osaka.
There was a place called Nozokibuya.
There was a man with a placard.
It said 1000 yen.
I thought it would be nice if it was 1000 yen.
Did you go in?
I went in.
When I went in, a woman came.
She said she would give 5000 yen if I showed her something nice.
When I gave her 1000 yen, she said she was sorry.
She said she didn't have any change.
She said she would call a younger man.
A young man came with a beer.
It's a long story.
It's okay.
A woman came and gave me money.
I told her that I had already done it.
I told her to wait for a while.
I waited for about 10 minutes and no one came.
I looked over there and it wasn't funny at all.
Then she came back.
I didn't do anything.
Don't you think your story is funny?
This is a joke.
It takes a lot of time.
She came back.
Mr. Ebisu is like this.
Let's go.
When you get on a plane, you are treated as valuable.
Why is that?
What is this?
This is a joke.
Please imitate it.
Imitation?
Anyone is fine.
The sun is burning red.
Imitation of Hibari Ebisola.
It's not similar at all.
I said I couldn't imitate it.
Please jump.
This is good.
I got the answer.
Did you get it?
What is this?
This is a joke.
I'm scared.
What is this?
This is a joke.
This is not so big.
This is amazing.
Mr. Ebisu was scared to run away.
He was about to be pulled by his own butt.
What is this?
I'm really angry today.
It's an article on Tohsupo.
This time it's disbanded.
Thank you very much.
What do you think of this theory?
I'm really surprised.
It happened before.
What is this?
It's disbanded.
Suddenly, I have a cramp.
It's not a cramp.
Suddenly I have a cramp.
I have a cramp in front of me.
Is that so?
I'm fine now.
Let's deceive Mr. Kaizawa.
I will be caught.
Recently it's terrible.
What is terrible?
A while ago, I was sent to the police station.
I don't care about that.
How many hours did it take?
What?
I was sent to the police station.
Two or three hours.
The other day, I was caught by a woman in Ikebukuro.
The woman woke up the next day and saw me.
I said, good morning.
I don't know how to put it.
Why me?
There are many people who don't say good morning to that woman.
Why you?
When I said good morning, I was caught.
I don't know how to put it.
What do you want me to do?
I can't help it because I'm selfish.
Since the day I made my debut, I have been selfish.
You say you are late.
I have never been late.
That's right.
I don't want to be hit by you.
I beg you.
The number of times I hit Matsumoto has decreased.
You can't do that.
You can't write a newspaper or a weekly magazine.
It's all the thoughts of a reporter.
You write your opinion.
Finally, you write the name of the person involved.
I wrote it.
There is no reason to say that.
Everyone around me likes me.
Do you think so?
I'll say that, so wait.
It's better to say good-bye.
If you don't say good-bye, the audience's reaction will be strange.
When is next year?
February 14th.
Good-bye on Valentine's Day.
Good-bye.
The audience's reaction will be strange.
That's right.
It's because you're in the way of my work.
Do you have a lot of prank calls?
I don't know.
The other day, someone knocked on the door of my house.
Is it a prank call?
It's a prank call.
It's not a prank call.
Do you know?
There was a movie about a prank call.
After the prank call, I called him.
I told him not to call me again.
If he calls me again, I can't call him again.
That's good.
The problem is, for example, where are you?
I'm not dead.
Wait a minute.
I'll call you a different prank.
I'm not dead.
It's a joke.
I'll call you and tell you not to pick up the phone.
For example, you came to my house to play.
I don't have a phone.
You don't have a phone.
I'm going to call your house.
If you don't pick up the phone, you'll be caught.
You'll be caught.
I'll call you.
I don't have a phone.
It's okay if you don't pick up the phone.
I'll think about it.
That's good.
This is the first time this year.
Nice to meet you.
What do you want to do this year?
I want you to call me.
I don't want to change anything.
What is your goal?
You said something last year.
What did I see last year?
You said you'd be twice as good as last year.
I said I'd be twice as good.
You said you'd be twice as good.
Everyone doesn't know, but I'm twice as good.
No.
No, you're twice as good.
You're saying everyone is twice as good.
Everyone is twice as good.
I didn't know why.
This is a mistake.
I didn't expect everyone to be twice as good.
I see
I'll do it too
What?
I'll tell you what I'm planning this year
Yes
Time limit
That's enough
If you came on time, you wouldn't have recorded it
I'm sorry
Why?
At work, I went to work at 2 o'clock
No one was there
This is...
I went to work at 2 o'clock
I went in before 3 o'clock
I went in and I was sitting
I went into the dressing room and I was sitting
I was like this
There was nothing
I remembered a lot of things from my childhood
That kind of time is necessary
So you were in the dressing room
You were 3 hours late
I was 3 hours late
Right?
That's why you can't be on time
I have a problem
The more I'm late, the more the show will fail
That's just what you think
If I come on time...
It's shaking
It's shaking a lot
It's hard
Why?
That's why you can't be on time
You don't have to say it
What should I do?
What do you mean by what you just said?
The building will collapse
I don't want to work with these people
I can't beat the earthquake
The earthquake of the time machine is also the origin
Zabutomo teacher
It's okay here
It's over
I'm the mother of the first man
Thank you
Our skyline was damaged
Really?
The car fell down
Don't talk too much
I saw on TV that the car was a lie
I see
It was true
Are you in the car now?
I took a picture of the car
I changed the light
I'm a beautiful woman
I feel good
That's all for today
You can go home
It's still okay
It's okay
You can go home
I don't know what you're talking about
It's amazing
What about dogs?
Dogs can't swim like a dog?
But dogs can't swim
Dogs can't swim
I don't think so
That's all
Don't look down on dogs
Why did you say it again?
Say it again
I'm a man
I'm sorry
Am I looking down on dogs?
I'm looking down on dogs
There's one more thing
There is
Can you teach me?
Diving
He's dead
He's a man
I don't know
I don't know how to teach
What happened to the fight between Keisuke Kuwata and Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi?
I was at Izumiya's show the other day
I said I'll join if you fight
I said you'll get beaten if you say that
He said yes
I'm weak
I thought the same thing
Wait a minute
What do you mean?
I wanted to join when something happened
I don't know who you are
I think you know who I am
I don't have anything to do with you
When you look at me like that
I don't know who you are
There are a lot of celebrities
I'm the only one who knows
This is the truth
Is that so?
Even if Keisuke Kuwata and Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi fight
I'll say wait a minute
Have you talked to him?
What?
With Kuwata and Nagabuchi
Where did you come from?
From your house?
No
From Tsuyoshi's house
I'm the one who said this is a harmonica
How many years has it been?
Machan
Who is that?
Nagabuchi
Machan listen
What's wrong, Tsuyoshi?
Why are you shaking so much?
Are you shaking?
This is no good
He said
I want to play the guitar
I want to play the harmonica
Machan, what should I do?
Cry
I see, listen to that
Put this on