In the first episode, we're going to have a chiki-chiki-hustler game!
You've been doing this since you were a kid, and now you're doing it again.
Oh, really? I have two parents and two children.
You're lying!
When I did something bad when I was little, they made me four times bigger.
And they made me a master at the top.
You're a fool.
Today, we're going to have a game of billiards.
Look behind you, just like the numbers.
You see this box?
If you drop the same number as the number in this box, you'll get the same number as the number in this box.
That's the system.
I see.
So you drop it from the number you want?
You can drop it from the number you want.
If you want it, you don't bother your opponent.
That's a skill.
By the way, the number you dropped will be taken home today.
It's a promise.
In this rain.
I got it.
No matter what you get, you have to bring it home.
If you drop the same number as the number in this box...
It's a handball.
Here it is.
Nitta Atsuo.
All the staff, including us, will be hit by Nitta Atsuo.
First, I'll drop the number one.
Boiled octopus.
I'll give you this.
This is so delicious that my throat is bleeding.
It's a lie.
I'll drop the number two.
But this is...
This is...
It's good.
You don't bother your opponent.
And I'll give you a bonus.
I think it's good.
I'll drop the number three.
I'll give you this.
It's cheap and good quality.
It's a gift.
I'll give you a big camera.
What's number four?
Ta-da!
I'll give you soy sauce for a year.
I'll give you a big camera.
This is so good.
I'll give you soy sauce for a year.
I'll drop the number five.
This is wonderful.
This is a sponsor of the program.
This is a single malt whiskey from Scotland.
I'll drop the number six.
I'll give you a love-hate relationship.
I'll drop the number seven.
I'll drop the number six.
What's this?
I'll give you two flowers.
I think every Japanese wants this.
I'll drop the number eight.
Ta-da!
What's this?
This is a gift.
I'll grill you.
I'll drop the number nine.
What's this?
This is open.
I don't need the number eight and nine.
I'll drop the number eight.
What's this?
This is number two.
I'll give you a T-shirt.
This doesn't get in the way.
Stop getting in the way.
I'll show you my miracle shot.
Are you surprised?
The number eight was about to get in.
Grandma has been in the way.
Grandma is number eight.
That's right.
When I'm in trouble, I'll call her grandma.
Grandma must have been very tired in the past.
I'll take you home.
This is for you.
Thank you.
I'll aim for the number eight.
This is for you.
I'll put the number six in my pocket.
This doesn't get in the way.
This is for you.
Thank you.
I have six and seven, so I have two.
You have one, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
I won.
I'll give you a camera, a T-shirt, an octopus.
I'll take them all home.
Thank you.
I'm going home.
Take them all home.
Hitchi from Hichimen-cho.
Don't say Hitchi.
My name is Umekichi.
Why Umekichi?
I'm your grandma.
I'll take you home.
It's a long trip, but take care.
Shall we go together?
I wonder if the skin of Osaka fits.
What should I do with Hichimen-cho?
I'll send you.
Grandma, let's go.
I'm old, but I'm free.
I'll find a seat myself.
I got a towel.
This is a flower.
Thank you.
This is for you.
It's a promise, so take it.
I'm a little angry.
Wait a minute.
You stand up and make a circle.
You guys.
That's what my brother did.
What's funny on TV these days?
I don't watch much.
It's popular to watch TV dramas.
I like anime.
Hey, but the anime is really popular in Japan right now!
You know what anime is, don't you?
I'm not an idiot.
That's right! Chibi Maruko-chan!
I've never thought of laughing at an anime like that.
You're an idiot.
I'm just saying, Chibi Maruko-chan,
Isn't that from yesterday and today?
It's been about a year since I read a word book and liked it.
But that's all in the manga, isn't it?
Chibi Maruko-chan?
Yeah.
That's about it, isn't it?
That's a memory I almost forgot when I was a kid.
What the hell are you talking about?
It's like the stupidity of my childhood is almost forgotten.
Children are stupid.
That's interesting.
Children are really stupid, aren't they?
I was talking about it yesterday.
When I was a kid, my dad said,
It's hot in summer, so I'll put a blanket on.
Your dad said that all of a sudden, didn't he?
He wasn't that kind before.
He said it all of a sudden.
He put it in front of the blanket.
He runs around like this.
I thought I was going to be dumped.
I thought I was going to be dumped from today on.
Really.
Right?
When I was a kid, I looked like this.
I didn't look like I was going to be dumped.
I was going to be taken somewhere.
But on my way home, I looked like this.
I thought I was going to be dumped.
I don't know.
I don't know if you're going to be dumped or not.
I thought I was going to be dumped.
That's not true.
I think children are stupid.
Even if it's such a small thing.
That's what Chibi Maruko-chan thinks.
Someday, I'm going to publish a comic book.
Yes.
My comic book.
Your English is good.
Yes.
My English is good.
No, really.
What?
Your reactions are amazing.
Someday, I'm going to publish a comic book.
Really?
I'm working hard.
It's quite difficult.
Why?
The comic book.
I've published a comic book before.
That one.
Manga Dojo.
Why?
I've published two-page manga.
There was one that was published by the general public.
Yes.
I published it.
How was it?
At least in the bonus corner of Eva and Dan-kichi.
I thought I wouldn't get anything.
I didn't write it.
Have you ever published it?
You wrote it, didn't you?
Yes.
There was a comic book about chewing gum and sending it.
I've published a comic book about the first meeting.
The one on the back of the manga.
Yes.
I know.
The first meeting.
What did you buy?
I didn't buy anything.
I bought a cigarette-pushed doll.
I know that.
It's a strange one.
Yes.
Really?
It's a strange chocolate.
I know that.
I feel sleepy when I feed it to a woman.
And in the meantime...
I don't eat it.
Oh, that one.
I brought various goods.
Yes.
And Kimiga-kun ate a strange chocolate.
How can I sleep?
And there's something I want to do.
Yes.
A chocolate that makes a woman excited.
Something you want to do.
I want to do it.
This is something that a man should do.
Yes.
I don't know if it's true.
This is great.
Let's do it.
Yes.
And the glasses are so beautiful.
If you put them on, you can see them.
Yes.
I'm serious.
You can see them just by taking off your clothes.
I'm going to be mad if you do that.
Yes.
It was written as Marumi-e or something like Marumi-e Scope
I looked at it like this so that the inside of the room looks wide
I couldn't see anything if there was no hole in the room
I've thought about a lot of things
For example?
When I was a kid, I didn't know that I saw 11 PM
At that time, it was a tragedy
I didn't have a room
My parents were sleeping in the other room
It was a glass room
If there was a TV, what would they be watching?
The light would reflect
So it was a cardboard
It fit perfectly on the TV screen
It got smaller little by little and became like this
But I didn't notice it
What?
I was confused because it suddenly came in
If there was no TV, what would my son do?
He would put something on the TV screen
Well, that's true
I've done a lot of research
I found out that there is a special feature
I don't know
It's the easiest to make a combination
It's like making a radio with a radio and a cassette
That was a special feature
There was no such thing
You can add something to the box
It might be popular to add something to the box
There is something in the box
You can put something in your mouth and eat it
It might be a big hit
Idiot
Let me see the postcard
What?
What is this?
It's a gift
I don't know what it is
I'm sorry
It's not mine
What is this?
Where is she?
Were you with her?
Really?
Where are you?
What is this?
Are you kidding me?
Give it to me
Do you know what it is?
Did you wear a uniform at that time?
How old were you at that time?
How many years ago was this?
More than 6 years ago
I don't know
You gave me a postcard
I was the first one
I was 22 years old
I was in a commercial with Mr. Donuts
Do you remember?
I don't remember
Really?
I remember 2 or 3 girls like this
Thank you very much
This is the ultimate choice
Let's do this
If you go to the town
Are you naked with a mask on?
I'm naked with a bikini
I'm not joking
I'm naked with a mask on
Why?
I don't think it's embarrassing
to be seen naked
Take off your mask
Well
I don't think it's embarrassing
I'm not ashamed of being seen peeing
Really?
I'm not doing it
I don't know if it's funny
It's funny
I don't mind being seen peeing
I just
Great, you have a strong voice.
I can't bear to see you pooping.
But I don't want to hear you say, mmm.
For example, I don't want to hear you say, mmm.
For example, I don't want to see you pooping.
I don't want to see you pooping.
Because when I see that, people think I'm a clean person.
Of course!
If you do that, I'll...
I didn't do anything wrong.
I didn't, but if you do that, I'll...
I'll say, ahhh!
If you just go like that, I'll...
Hey, hey, hey!
I'll say, wait!
I'll say, think!
But seriously though...
If I were you, I'd still be wearing a bikini and walking around barefoot.
What are you talking about?
I don't want to see you pooping.
A long time ago, we were two.
We went into our house.
What?
We went into our house without telling anyone.
We didn't go anywhere.
We were bored, so we lived in an apartment.
Our parents were working, so they couldn't come home until late at night.
So we locked ourselves in their house.
We didn't want to go to school, so we took a break.
We thought, let's hide in their house.
So we locked ourselves in their house.
You made a locked door?
We made a locked door.
Please forgive me for being young.
We went in, and during the day, we watched TV.
We did a lot of bad things.
This guy said he wanted to poop.
So we went to poop.
And this guy said he didn't want to pee.
Right?
This guy pooped like a kid.
So he pooped like a kid.
He pooped like a kid.
This guy also tried to pee, but...
No!
That wasn't pooped!
That guy was conscious and said he didn't want to pee.
He said he didn't want to pee, so he tried to pee with water.
It was like this.
He tried to pee with water.
It was like this!
Why did you avoid it?
You didn't even try to pee.
Go away!
You're in the way!
That guy was conscious and said he didn't want to pee.
I've never seen anything like that.
If you put it next to the toilet, it's like a rock.
You're in the way!
It doesn't smell at all!
It doesn't smell at all.
Who said it doesn't smell?
It's either the mother finds herself in porn, or the mother finds the porn she finds herself in.
Hey!
I'm sure you found yourself in porn.
Not yet.
Not yet?
I was asked by a friend, so I did it.
What kind of a friend would read porn?
This is the only one I have.
You don't want to see the can, do you?
That's right.
I'll go home and prepare it.
Now, with this...
If you open it, the can will...
That's about it.
Isn't there a type of lighter?
Yes, there is.
It's a type of lighter.
Did you see it?
It's different!
The one before is the one that goes like this, right?
It's different.
The shape is different.
It's the same thing twice!
This is...
This is great.
I'll prepare the right hand.
Is that okay?
This is it.
I'm stupid!
That's about it.
Thank you very much.
Instead of staff G,
we're going to make some goods.
For everyone watching on TV,
we want you to make something like this.
With that in mind,
We want you to make something like this.
If it's possible, let's think about it.
That's it.
What else?
What else is there?
That's right.
The postcards are always like this.
I'm happy with today's corner.
That's right.
We'll send you the postcards.
Let's send them.
There are many things we want to say.
Please send us more and more.
Is that okay?
Let's do it here.
In that case,
all the postcards are here.
Please send them to us.
We'll be waiting.
See you next week.
Thank you for watching.