Gakuya is in a peaceful atmosphere. However, he is nowhere to be seen.
I'm already swollen.
I'm not swollen.
I don't think so.
Masubo-san, Masubo-san.
I'm sorry.
Okamoto-san suddenly appeared in front of the staff.
I'm really sorry.
Are you angry?
Of course.
You're angry, right?
I don't care about that.
So I'm not going because I was called.
Today, Yamazaki is going to Shibagi.
Let's go.
What should I do?
You dropped it from your waist.
I'm a talent.
That's right.
Until now, he has been dancing in the dark of the night.
Sometimes he sticks his neck out with a huge blade.
Sometimes he flies in the sky for bananas.
And last time, he was under the sky of Selvian Blue in Okinawa.
He is the strongest man in the entertainment world.
He is the manager of the company.
The staff of Downtown Wika arrived at a river in the outskirts of Okinawa.
This is really good.
Come here.
I'm selling it.
Did he have such a hairstyle?
What is it?
It's been a long time since I left Okinawa.
Why don't you tell me anything?
You don't tell me.
What is it?
I've been waiting all the time.
But it's over 20, right?
It's over 20, right?
It's over 20.
Why don't you tell me the number?
You tell me the number.
I don't want to tell you.
If you tell me that, I don't know what to do.
I have something I've been wanting to do for a long time.
Do you have something?
Yes.
I have something.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Okamatsu.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
Stop it.
Mr. Okamatsu.
I'm begging you.
I don't have any enemies.
Your voice.
It was a serious voice.
I've been wanting to do this for a long time.
Is that so?
What are you doing?
What?
I'll show you.
What are you doing?
Did you see that?
What?
I'm Inoki.
This is Muhammad Ali.
Yes.
Right?
I'll fight.
Tohkon Furiko Okamoto Bombaye.
What?
Manager Okamoto.
Tohkon Furiko Okamoto Bombaye.
I'll fight Okamoto Tohkon Bombaye.
Tohkon Furiko Okamoto Bombaye, right?
It's the same.
It's a bit different.
It's like that.
I know.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
What are you doing?
You're amazing.
I want to see it.
Antonio Inoki.
Okamoto is the strongest pro-wrestler in the world.
This time, Okamoto was caught by three 30-meter high cranes.
Inoki's eternal rival, Muhammad Ali, who was waiting on the other side, was released like Furiko.
And the moment he punched, he changed into Inoki.
Okamoto.
The enemy is over there.
Really?
Don't come to the red place.
You look like you're angry.
Please let me punch you in the neck.
I'll punch you.
Hey.
It's you.
I'm sorry.
Are you angry?
I'm angry.
Hey.
What did you see?
I didn't see it.
I saw it.
Everyone saw it.
I'm sorry. I made a mistake.
What did you see?
I made a mistake.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
I don't know.
I see.
The highest point is 20.
What?
It's 30.
I didn't know you liked cranes so much.
Okamoto.
What?
Are you ready?
Yes.
Let's go.
Open it.
Okamoto.
It's time to stop.
What are you going to do?
I'm thinking.
Are you going to stop?
I'm sorry.
What are you going to do?
I'm getting scared.
I'm getting scared, too.
What?
Wait a minute.
You've been talking about cranes.
What are you doing?
It's high.
What?
Wait a minute.
I'm really scared.
What?
You're scared, aren't you?
I can see the bottom clearly.
Okamoto.
It's OK now.
It's OK.
The setting is complete.
Wait a minute.
Let's go to Okamoto Mountain.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Start.
Bungy.
Okamoto.
I'm sorry, but I couldn't get the camera.
You're the one who got it.
I couldn't get it.
I'm really sorry.
I'm counting on you.
You took out your underwear, didn't you?
What?
Why are you like this?
You look like a girl in middle school.
I'm sorry.
Please lift it up.
Now, the audience is half and half.
Bungy.
You know, you're going to go down like this.
It's really scary.
It's scary.
Okamoto, go down.
Start.
It's really scary.
Okamoto, go down.
It's scary.
Okamoto.
It's the face when a dog poops.
It's a little funny.
I'm sad.
When you first came here, you got eyes, right?
Yes, I did.
I saw you a lot.
Okamoto-san, we'll let you go home now.
But thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's too early.
Okamoto-san, you won't do it five more times after I go home, right?
I won't do it.
The men...
Oh, really?
The men in front of you...
I'm really sorry about everyone today.
I'm really, really tired.
Really.
Yesterday, I went home in the morning.
I went home in the morning and...
I thought I should go to bed.
What's that?
I'm like, da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da!
Ah.
It's a construction.
What do you call that?
That's the thing!
Da-da-da!
It's that thing, right?
That's the old man's.
The old man's?
Well, it's not owned by the company.
The old man doesn't get angry at all.
The old man is a good old man.
No, the old man is doing it.
But he's just doing it.
But the old man is switching it on.
But the old man did it yesterday.
Have you ever talked?
It's 9 o'clock in the morning.
That's the time for the old man to work.
Everyone is working at 9 o'clock in the morning.
You guys are so annoying.
It can't be helped.
Right?
I'm fine even if I don't get enough sleep.
But if I do a show like this,
with my head in a daze,
in the end, it's going to bother the viewers.
His nagging is not very useful.
It would be better if you let me sleep and work well.
It would be good for Japan.
Well, I'm fine with that.
What are you digging?
There was a piece of string in my pocket.
I'm worried about it.
Someday, I'll be thrown away like that.
What are you talking about?
I'll be thrown away like trash.
Are you a woman?
No, it's really hard.
I'll do my best.
But it's just...
Most of the time,
I'm at work.
You're talking about yourself again.
Most of the time,
with my head in a daze,
without any meetings,
the two of us are talking.
When I hear that,
it's a miracle.
When I think about it,
I can't think normally.
Your voice is getting louder.
Right?
It's your proud face.
What's wrong?
I'm scared because I can do it.
Stop it.
I'll do my best.
I didn't shave my beard.
That's fine.
I've gained a lot of weight lately.
You're...
You're hiding
my secret.
You're revealing it!
You're revealing it too much.
Don't touch me.
I'm telling you what I saw.
Who are you telling that to?
I'm curious.
It's fine.
Come on in.
That was funny.
After this,
come with me.
I'm sorry.
I can't believe it.
I was surprised when I saw the picture.
The poster was cut.
I was walking in the alley.
I was wondering what was going on.
I went out and saw
a poster of Maekawa Kiyoshi.
He was sticking his face
to the poster.
I was wondering what was going on.
I thought it was fine.
I went into the alley again.
When I went back,
I saw Maekawa Kiyoshi again.
That was funny.
Your wife must have been old.
She must have been ugly.
If I was really
going to get married,
I would choose someone like that.
I'm serious.
Marriage is not about appearance.
It's about staying together.
What do you mean by staying together?
Your father is weird.
He's already gone.
He's already gone down.
He's trying to go back.
He's trying to go back to his father.
If you put a CCD on your neck,
it will be like this.
It won't look like this.
I think it's fine.
Your wife will take good care of you.
I know what you mean.
It's hard to find a wife who doesn't get married.
It's not like that.
It would be nice if you could be a heroine.
You can't do that.
I'll do it properly.
What will you do?
I'll do everything from start to end.
I'll do this and that.
Let me do it.
Why are you doing that?
Are you trying to cry?
No.
Why am I the one who's trying to cry?
You're so stubborn.
You're the one who's trying to cry.
No.
You're like a monk.
I'm like this.
If you two fight, I'll go to you.
Even if you cry,
I don't want you to cry.
Why?
Why am I the one who's trying to cry?
I like people who cry.
You don't have any connections.
There are many diet rules.
The Matsumoto diet
is to lose 17 kg in 3 days.
I heard that.
What are you going to do?
Normally,
if you write it in a book,
it's easy to sell.
It's easy to make money.
I don't want to make money dieting.
Can you clap for me?
You're tired.
I don't want to make money
by doing that.
I'm fat.
They're telling me to do the big lunch.
I told you how to lose 17 kg in 3 days.
I don't want to make money.
I don't want to make money dieting.
Do you?
At home,
you have a knife.
I have a knife.
If I had one,
What?
Can you do that?
What do I do?
Can you be a model?
Sure.
You can use a knife.
You go like this.
And you cut all the edges.
You cut it?
You cut it.
How deep?
About 1cm deep.
Make it deep.
How deep?
About 1cm deep.
You go around it.
And you grab it like this.
If you go like this,
you can pull it out from the spine.
How do you pull it out?
Wait a minute.
If you pull it out,
does that mean you don't need it?
What?
I don't understand what you're saying.
What happens if you pull it out?
If you pull it out, it stays as it is.
Where does it stay?
If you put it in a box, it stays in a box.
No, no, no.
From here,
the spine is connected, right?
Yes, yes.
Where does it stay?
If you put it in a box, it stays in a box.
I don't know.
I don't know even if you ask me.
It's already over.
When you pull it out,
what's over?
It's from now on.
Why is it from now on?
Rather, it's from now on.
Why?
That's weird.
It's weird.
I think there are only two weird points.
It's weird that you pull it out like this.
Then why didn't you tell me at that time?
I want to ask you the rest of the story.
Then you're in the same boat.
What?
Who is that man in the soup spa?
Who is it?
I'm the most angry man in the world right now.
What kind of guy?
Do you want to have a soup spa?
I'll tell you clearly.
He's very narcissistic.
Maybe.
Why are you so angry?
Do you want to have a soup spa?
You're always angry.
You always say,
let's have a soup spa.
Why are you doing this?
I don't understand the meaning of that.
What is a soup spa?
In the car,
soup spa.
He's very cool.
It's rare.
I don't know if he's a model.
Recently, when he comes out, he goes home.
When he comes back, he comes out again.
It happens.
I don't like it even if it's like this.
When he comes back, it's just around here.
It happens a lot.
It's about to happen tomorrow.
If you're going to use it like that,
I really don't use it.
I only use it once.
It's a little better than that.
Why?
Because you get angry and go home.
But even if I say,
let's have a commercial,
a windmill will come.
Why do you want a windmill?
A commercial for a book store.
What?
You'll get angry if you go to a commercial.
I won't get angry.
You'll be late, you'll be early. You shouldn't get angry on the set.
You're the one who says that, so I won't be a bad guy anymore.
You're the one who's bad.
Oh, really?
You're the one who's always got an iron rod.
Is that really a rumor?
No, it's not me. It's downtown.
What are you talking about?
The other day, Mr. Takeda, from GX.
Mr. Takeda, Mr. Tetsuya.
Mr. Tetsuya came, didn't he?
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, downtown is...
What?
He's always got a stick in his hand when he's playing golf.
Why is that?
Well, the staff is hitting him.
He's got a stick in his hand.
Well...
Why is it so low?
It's your hexagon, so it hurts.
I don't have it.
It's my circle, so it hurts.
In the end, they're both bad guys.