In the baseball tournament full of Hamashio, a number of super plays came out, and in the end, the Hamashio team won with a dramatic goodbye home run.
And once again, the Hamashio team started a new fight.
We will now begin the Hamashio Sports Day.
Ready!
Please tell us the story of the dog, monkey, and the fox.
I don't understand this story.
What do you want to say?
I think you're saying something, but you can't talk in front of people you're not interested in.
I'm answering this for Yamamoto-kun.
Yamamoto-kun, that's strange.
Yamamoto Takehiro-kun.
Yamamoto Takehiro-kun, that's strange.
Why is that?
I don't understand what you're saying.
That's because...
What did the dog, monkey, and the fox do to make you so excited?
You went to see the monkey, didn't you?
You didn't?
Is this wrong?
I want to say this first.
If it's wrong, then you're wrong, Yamamoto.
This is nothing.
Right?
What do you think?
You went to see the monkey, didn't you?
You didn't?
To be honest, I can't say that yet.
When are you going to say it?
I'm going to say it now.
I'm going to say it as if I went.
What?
If you accept it, you can say it.
What are you talking about?
I'm excited because you did something.
I'm going to say it now.
Listen to me, Yamamoto.
Yamamoto, you're like Hirotani.
I'm going to say it now.
You're going to say it now?
You seem to be motivated.
I was motivated.
But what are these guys?
This is the worst.
It's a sad story.
I'm always half laughing.
That's funny.
Even if I say, I'm going to say it, it's not funny.
If I say, only one person will say it, the other will say it, and the other will say it.
I hear it because it's pitiful.
I get really excited.
I see.
I can't help but get angry.
You're saying it.
I'm saying it.
Alright, let's go!
Over there!
I'm saying it.
When I'm saying it,
from behind,
I'm like,
why are you in the peach?
My face is like this.
My face is red.
Why are you in the peach?
Like that,
I'm saying it.
I'm getting angry.
That makes you angry, right?
My tension goes down.
Your tension goes down.
That's right.
You should have asked me directly.
I see.
My face is completely red.
My face is redder than the red demon.
My face is redder than the red demon I'm going to meet now.
That's a bit too much.
Eh?
I should have finished it before that.
If you keep saying things like this,
you'll turn into a blue demon.
Hey!
Someone come here!
What is the toilet war that Matsumoto-san thought of?
I thought of it?
Inatsuchi Shota wrote it.
Today's writing is a bit strange.
It's hard to understand.
But there is indeed a toilet war.
Is that so?
Yes.
It's too vague.
It's hard to understand what it is.
For example,
whether it's a big one or a small one.
What is that?
If you have something to ask, go ahead.
No, I don't.
I don't.
What is that?
I'm more interested in the toilet than my story.
The toilet seat?
Of course, that's right.
I see.
Whether it's a big one or a small one,
it's amazing.
Four people died because of this.
I see.
That's amazing.
There is a new type of toilet.
It's called S type.
What is S type?
What do you do with it?
How do you use it?
It's called S type.
It's like this.
Where is the toilet seat?
If there is no toilet door,
there is nothing.
There is no toilet door.
You don't have to force yourself.
I have one.
What?
S type.
How do you use it?
That's why...
Why do I have to do this all the time?
This is the toilet seat.
This is the S type toilet seat
that has recently been added.
It's all over the place now.
Do you put your butt here?
I put my butt here.
You shouldn't be here.
Your butt is here.
The poop goes all the way here.
I told you that it's hard to clean the toilet.
My feet are full of poop.
This is not good.
That's why I don't need this anymore.
People become tearful as they age.
What is the most useless thing that you have done recently?
Can I say it seriously?
Of course.
I thought it was the age.
What happened?
People become tearful as they age.
That's what I thought.
Seriously.
What happened?
You were playing Alien 2, right?
The complete version.
I watched it three times.
When was the first time you played it?
I was about 20 years old.
I don't know.
You're 38 years old now.
You should watch Alien 2.
To be honest,
Schwarzenegger was falling down with a chain.
That was Terminator.
Thank you very much.
Let's go home.
You're old.
You're not getting any older.
This is embarrassing.
Say it!
You didn't play it the other day!
At that time, you said,
No, Machan is wrong!
You guys call Machan by his name, right?
Say it!
You made a mess of people.
We just played Alien.
You guys are so dirty!
I know you're going to stop it,
but you shouldn't have stopped it.
You stopped it and then put a chain on it.
You call it Alien?
You didn't play Alien 2 the other day.
I don't know when you played it.
When Schwarzenegger came out,
you should have said it!
I don't know when he came out.
When Schwarzenegger came out, you should have said it!
That was Terminator.
You're so dirty!
You made a mistake!
You should have said,
No, Machan is wrong!
You don't know how to play it anymore, right?
You don't play Alien 2 anymore.
You should have said,
No, Machan is wrong!
You don't play Alien 2 anymore.
You should have said,
No, Machan is wrong!
You're so noisy!