Tsukitsuki, what are you doing?
Are you an expert?
Before the competition,
I want to practice.
I see.
That's fine, but why do you have such a dirty image?
The uniform.
What?
It reminds me of dynamite.
Is that so?
Isn't it refreshing?
What is this sound?
Why is there only one person in this room?
It's because of the budget.
Why did we change it to red?
Because most of the members are
the same age as me.
So I didn't want to be noticed.
I see.
So I changed it to red.
By the way,
I don't know what this sound is.
Then...
Stop it!
That's my team!
You're a Daphons!
At the time of writing the letter,
I knew it,
but I had to wait until the car came.
Thank you very much.
Shall we take a look at your place?
Yes, let's take a look.
Noriyasu-kun gave me the first place.
I'm sorry.
I'll go to you at 9 o'clock.
Well, his...
There's no one in here who can shoot a bullet.
That's right.
I don't know yet.
Well,
I think he's a little different.
Why?
Why are you hitting him in the direction of the Union?
What?
It doesn't matter.
Well,
as you can see from my team,
we're all together.
He's a secret weapon.
Really?
Well,
I don't know yet.
I'll go around the town and have him come back.
It's really snowing.
I'm really shivering in the city.
Don't wear cold clothes.
Don't jump.
Come on.
A jumper came out of the cold.
You're so stupid.
Wow.
Are you kidding me?
Get ready.
Let's go.
Stop the camera at the right time.
Stop it?
The taste is the best!
You are the number one in the draft!
Wait, wait, wait!
What are you doing?
I'm sad!
What is this?
That one is easy to ride.
It's the worst.
But I have a member who is a big tool.
It's fast if you take a hammer.
It's like a direct ball.
Is it like that?
It's like wearing a handkerchief.
If you take that, it's really fast.
If you take that, it's dangerous.
If you take that, you may fly to Korakuen.
Next
Practice in two groups.
I see, I see.
Let's go, Otomo.
It's dirty.
Otomo.
Who? Sato.
It's dirty.
Your glove looks like a banana.
Old man.
Old man is good.
Let's take a hammer.
Hey, Watamoto.
Can't you take that off?
Watamoto.
What?
Is it better to take it off?
If you take it off, it will be a big deal.
Let's take a hammer off.
It will be a big deal.
Can't you take it off?
Let's take a hammer off.
If you take it off, it will be a big deal.
Really?
Let's go.
I can't see.
Hamada, try it.
Why am I the director?
Hey, hey.
Let's go.
Good job.
Hey.
Hey, hey.
Good job.
50,000 more.
Hey, 50,000 more.
Hey, hey.
Good job.
I failed, so 70,000 more,
Hey, hey.
Jump!
Run running running
Look!
Here! Here!
Look! Look!
Over there!
Good! Good!
Here! Here!
A dog?
I want to show you the practice scene at the opening.
Next week, you will be able to watch the game on the monitor.
Today, I did a knock.
That's it!
What?
Ah!
Is it funny?
It's funny, but I'm scared.
Suddenly, I'm scared.
I'm not surprised.
You are weak.
I will win.
I will definitely not win.
It's a mess.
I will protect the third, knock, and reach the first.
I will catch you.
Who is that?
I'm going to drop the ball.
Is the ball hot?
Who is that?
The ball is not hot.
You are a knocker.
He is a knocker.
That's you.
You are a knocker.
That's because the opponent is watching.
I was saving my strength.
You were shaking your body.
You are a knocker.
Don't you know that?
What?
Don't you know that knocker?
I don't know that.
I'm a knocker.
What?
Why?
I don't know.
I'm a knocker.
You are a knocker.
I know that.
I don't know that.
I will win.
I played with your player.
Who do you want?
Noriasu.
He is fast.
Really?
He is not good at the game.
What?
He is surprised.
Noriasu is not good at the game.
You are not good at the game.
What?
You and I are the pitchers.
Everyone else is not good at the game.
I'm not good at the game.
Why?
I'm a high school graduate.
What?
When did you say that?
When?
When you were in college.
I was in college, but I said that when I was in high school.
You were not a baseball player.
I was a baseball player.
I don't know if he will notice.
You were not a baseball player.
I was a baseball player.
Maybe I can win.
He found out.
You are lying.
I'm not good at the game.
I'm good at the game.
I don't care.
I'm serious.
I want to be serious.
If you lose, you have to get a punishment.
Even if I lose, I don't get a punishment.
Are you crazy?
The losing team will get a punishment.
I won't lose.
I don't know if you will lose.
But the losing team will get a punishment.
I won.
If I win, you will be my stylist.
Why do I have to go to the play house for you?
I have to change my clothes.
I'm sure.
Do you have an old man?
What?
I have an old man.
I have to change my clothes.
I won't let you change your clothes.
He is good at the game.
He is a real elite.
Don't say that.
I'm serious.
I will do my best.
Which number do you choose?
I choose number one.
I won't lose.
Can you win?
Of course.
I will win.
What kind of change is going to happen?
This is not a curves ball or a suit.
I'm going to throw the ball.
No.
This is a bear ball.
This is the name of the ball.
I'm upset if this ball comes to me.
I think I will win.
Why don't you throw?
I'll throw.
You can only throw straight.
What can you throw?
Curve.
Can you throw a curve?
Of course.
You can't throw a curve.
Listen to Noriyasu.
You idiot.
Hello.
It's been a long time since I saw you.
Really?
I'm looking for an assistant.
I don't have many pictures.
You don't have many pictures.
You look like Ikeike.
This picture is your father or sister.
My father or sister.
This picture.
You were more brown than now.
You were black.
You look like Zashikiwarashi.
You can't say that.
Zashikiwarashi can't be hurt.
I don't know what you are talking about.
Zashikiwarashi is a monster that appears in tatami.
I don't know.
You can't wear clothes.
Really?
Zashikiwarashi.
Thank you very much.
By the way, I have a question for you.
On January 22nd.
Yes.
Is there any fact that your sister came to Tokyo?
No.
On January 22nd at 5.50 pm.
I saw a woman who looks like you at Yamatesen Hamamachi-cho station.
Really?
She said she was a woman.
She is 150 cm to 155 cm tall.
Her name is like that.
My little sister?
Her hair is semi-long and she wears a shrimp tea coat.
Her face is like Hamamachi-san.
She looks like a female monster.
She looks like him.
She said she came to Yamatesen Hamamachi-cho from Hamamachi-cho station.
She was your sister.
I don't know what to do.
If she wasn't your sister, it would be a foul.
There is no such fact.
Really?
Yes.
Let's think about it.
What?
Your sister doesn't come to see you.
She doesn't come to kill you.
Don't say that.
Why are you a spy?
You are a rich man.
You are kind.
I went to your house once.
When I went to your house, I thought you weren't there.
But when you came home, you were 5 meters away from me.
You are like a cat.
I feel sorry for you.
You have been tortured many times.
Don't say that.
I haven't been tortured.
I just had a brother-sister relationship.
Why do I have to be tortured?
You have done a lot of bad things.
You cut people's nose between their nose.
Dolphins.
Why are you so particular about taking everything back?
I mean
Don't you feel sorry for your sister-in-law?
You have blown up her.
YOKOHAMA'sところ has sent this.
I think she is very handsome.
Don't call me like that!
I don't look like a manzai player.
When I ask my friends about it, they say,
What? Where?
They say I have a bad taste.
This is like that.
I'm a person of both good and bad.
I like it when people ask me if I like my face.
But I really hate it.
That's how I am.
But that's how I really am.
I like people I like.
I hate people I hate.
That's how I am.
But that's not the case with Hamada.
There is.
Why do people call me an old man?
That's not a face.
It's a personality.
I don't know my personality.
I get angry when I watch TV.
That's not a face.
I haven't done anything recently.
I went to work in Osaka the other day.
I was told by a taxi driver,
You've been round lately.
That's not good.
You can't be round.
I was told by a taxi driver.
You can't be more aggressive.
He said that I should go further.
When I'm done with this, I'll cut my hair.
You idiot!
You shouldn't be so strange.
I didn't cut my hair.
You had a fan's head in Osaka.
It's you!
You didn't have a head.
You had a face.
But that was funny.
Why?
I have a theater in Osaka.
It's called No. Grand Kagetsu.
It's about five times bigger than here.
It's a great theater.
I'm doing a show in Osaka.
With new actors.
We're doing a play together.
There's no such thing.
There's a flower road here.
It comes out of the flower road.
The cola comes out of the audience.
One person.
Listen.
I'm done.
Are you done?
I didn't do anything.
Listen to me.
I came out of the flower road.
Then, I'm singing.
In Minato, this kind of thing.
There's such a thing.
I want to see it.
I had my head here.
I was trying to get it on.
I'm trying to avoid it with a fan.
I thought I dodged it, but I couldn't dodge it, so I just kicked him.
Why did you kick him?
You were like, huh?
I've done a lot of things before.
He was the only one who kicked me.
And then he kicked me really hard.
I got up on the stage and did a little kick.
And then I went into the small room.
Why did you go back without even apologizing?
It's not like that.
Think about it. You've done a lot of bad things.
I'm not the type to be hated even if I kick like that.
You're definitely the only one who gets caught.
I'm really telling the kids.
You don't have to think so much about it.
It's just that the kids are so small.
There aren't that many living things in society.
If it's a dog, it's cute.
Think about it.
It could be a dog.
That's where you got big.
I didn't have much when I was a kid.
What do you mean you didn't have much when you were a kid?
Because my mom, my dad, my mom,
If I'm told these three things, I'll go to work next time.
Thank you very much.
Next week, we're finally going to have a baseball game.
I see.
I want you to watch it on TV.
Baseball, right?
That's right.
I don't know who's going to win.
I'm looking forward to the results next week.
I want to play fair.
I'm looking forward to it.
That's right.
If you lose, you'll be punished by the whole team.
It's dark.
That's right.
And I don't know how to play with the kids.
This is on Monday, February 11th.
From 4 to 4 o'clock.
It's a special edition.
I'll send you this.
The four of us.
Our theme song, Four Men.
Our catchphrase.
As it is.
We've been offered a song.
Song.
Various.
Color.
It's a special edition that's spreading the talk.
From 4 to 4 o'clock on Monday, February 11th.
4 o'clock, 4 o'clock, 5 o'clock.
It's a kid's play.
Don't miss it.
The look is.
The effect.
And the 11th.
One day.
There are two left.
Two.
Shut up.