After this, it's time for the last episode of Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai Arai-hende.
The first episode of Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai Arai-hende will be broadcasted monthly by one person!
So, on the 11th of April, on Saturday, there will be a special edition called Downtown Special.
That's right.
From now on, the staff, including us, will do the promotion for this program.
The loser will go to the Zoom and do the promotion.
Will you be able to get involved?
No, that's my own power.
I understand.
I can't take care of it until then, so I'll go and do it somehow.
I'll do this promotion somehow.
It's like this.
I see.
Actually, there's one more person who hasn't come yet.
Motohichi Adachi hasn't come yet.
He said he'd start at 5.30, so I thought it would be helpful if he moved.
That's why he hasn't come yet.
Motohichi has already been decided.
You can do it in a pack.
If you lose now...
I'll do it.
Okay.
Just one, okay?
Yes.
What are you talking about?
How many sheets are there? I don't know.
Three or four.
Is that so?
Everyone should have come to me to get four sheets from the beginning.
Why am I like this?
I don't know what to do.
I can't help it.
I'm selling quite a bit.
Oh, that's mine.
What?
But there are still two sheets left.
If you do one pack with three sheets, it's 5,000 yen.
This is Tsutsun.
What?
It's Tsutsun.
Why didn't you say anything during the show?
Who do you want me to show it to?
It's Tsutsun.
Do you want me to show it to anyone?
I don't want you to know, but it's Tsutsun.
Don't say it.
Excuse me.
What?
It's so close.
I'm laughing, but I don't know if it's a little higher.
It's a little higher.
Who is it from?
So I'll go from here.
It's so close.
I have a really bad pattern.
It fell.
It's okay. It's okay.
What?
It's over. It's over.
It's over.
I don't have any.
It's increasing. It's increasing.
What?
Seriously.
You don't have anything I want at all.
This is always like this.
I think I have ten of these.
What are you doing?
I can't do it. I can't do it with two.
This was there. You took it.
It's over.
Even if I take it, even if I can't take it, I won't put it on my face.
This is the secret of downtown.
If you get caught with this, there will be a problem.
There will be a problem.
Nitta, who's behind you?
You read it yesterday, didn't you?
It's okay.
It's just increasing.
When the next one is over.
It's over.
It's a tie.
This is Sangamon-chan.
Sangamon-chan.
It's still light.
Let's bet your life.
Okay, this is it.
Congratulations.
Let's go.
It's sad.
But it's not just a child.
It's a pack.
On Friday the 10th, at 7 o'clock in the morning.
Let's go to the night game.
Hold this firmly.
It's okay.
Please forgive me for the strange school.
But what should I do?
Because it's a girl.
I can't let you do that embarrassing thing.
It's a full body.
It's cold, but it's high.
It's high.
The tension is high.
Maybe it's the coldest day of the year.
It's really cold.
These guys were waiting in there.
It's really good.
On a day like this.
Such a public program.
It's better not to do it.
After all, the tension of the audience is low.
But it's a fool, so it's high.
It's a fool, so it's high.
The audience who comes here is a fool.
It's not a fool.
I don't know who comes here.
I'm fine, so when I'm talking, the tension is low.
There are times when I don't go home at all.
The audience here and the weather in the mountains are different.
I don't know.
It changes from time to time.
Have you ever been angry recently?
What?
Have you ever been angry?
I've never been angry.
I took a taxi.
There are some things that are hard to do in a car.
There is a cockpit.
There is a driver's seat.
It's pretty hard.
There is a Japanese doll made of paper.
It's hanging on this.
It's hard.
There was a lot of exhaust gas.
There was a traffic jam, so I thought I'd smoke a cigarette.
Can you stop smoking?
I'm not saying anything.
I put out a lot of exhaust gas and got in the car.
Why don't you stop smoking?
It's easy to say that.
If you don't smoke, there will be smoke near you.
It's not good for your body to smoke.
What?
I didn't say that.
If you smoke 20 cigarettes, even if you don't smoke, you smoke one.
You're saying something.
It's very bad for your body.
Who smokes 20 cigarettes?
If you say it's bad for your body, you shouldn't smoke.
That's strange.
I'm doing this in class.
It's the same as saying that it stinks.
I don't know if you stink, but what about me?
That's strange, too.
It's not strange at all.
What?
It's not strange.
You have to think about this.
What about the one who wants to smoke?
The one who wants to smoke?
You smoke, right?
You want to smoke, but you have to put up with it.
You have to put up with the fact that you want to smoke.
You have to put up with it.
You don't want to be smoked.
You have to put up with the fact that you want to smoke.
Men and women are the same.
You don't want to be smoked.
Women don't want to be smoked.
Maybe you don't want to be smoked, but I want to be smoked.
You should be smoked.
You don't want to be smoked.
That's right.
That's strange.
The world is wrong.
The wrong thing is...
You smoke.
You can't buy a pet in a mansion.
There are many places where you can't buy a pet in a mansion.
That's right.
In the end, everyone endures it.
In the end, if you ask everyone who lives in a mansion, everyone wants to buy a pet.
There are more than half of them.
I see.
That's why there is an exercise that you can buy a pet in any mansion.
That's right.
It's better for people who want to buy it.
That's not good.
Humans and animals have to be together somewhere.
That's right.
Why do you want to buy a dog or a cat at home?
Where do you want to buy it?
You have to buy it outside.
If you get too close to animals, they won't be able to do that.
What do you mean?
Animals are animals after all.
Are you getting angry?
No.
You have to open up.
That was a good question.
I'm sorry.
For humans...
We're animals, too.
We're a bit shy.
We're shy.
That's what animals are like.
Recently, we've been trying to buy them at home.
Huh?
We're pretty good.
You can even wear clothes.
Yeah!
That's right.
Who?
I'm wearing a stylist.
A caretaker.
You don't have to do that.
I'm selling them.
You're selling them.
That's the pain of being a caretaker.
The animals will gradually remember.
They'll misunderstand.
They'll think,
I'm not that different from humans.
You're the same.
I'm the same.
That's what they'll think.
I see.
That's when animals come into this human society.
On this earth,
it's going to be a mess.
We're animals after all.
Are you kidding me?
It's going to be an animal world.
We're animals.
We're going to keep buying them.
We're letting them stay at home.
They're all talking.
They're listening.
Are they listening?
What do they remember?
Words.
They're starting to learn how to talk.
They're starting to talk.
They're starting to stand up.
They don't understand.
It's going to be a mess.
It's going to be fun.
It's not going to be fun.
Why?
What?
They're going to talk a lot.
That's what it's going to be.
You're talking about a dog and a cat.
You're talking about a caterpillar.
It's going to be a mess.
The caterpillar is going to be a mess.
But they can't say that.
They can only talk about what they remember.
Humans are the same.
What you're talking about is...
Don't interrupt me.
It's what you taught your mother.
Stop it.
You're asking me to stop.
It has a stronger meaning than the word stop.
It's what your mother taught you.
She's asking you to stop.
This way of talking is...
your mother...
Stop it.
Even this way of talking is what your mother taught you.
It's what your mother taught you.
I want to tell them to stay away from them.
That's why I told you not to do such things at home.
Yes, yes, yes.
There are many kinds of people, but...
Glass monkey.
I've heard of it, but I've never seen it.
What?
Glass monkey.
Glass monkey? I've never seen it.
There are animals that look like glass monkeys.
What kind of face do they have?
That's why they look like this.
And they do this with trees.
Sometimes they do this.
You're laughing, aren't you?
I'm a big fan of cleanliness.
Oh, really?
So I clean as much as I can.
You know, I look pretty wild, don't I?
No, really.
Ah, I see.
I feel like I'm going to die of starvation.
That's dangerous.
You shouldn't do such a thing in this day and age.
No, no, no.
I feel like I'm going to die with a knife.
I feel like I'm going to die.
No, it's serious.
Can you see it?
No, I can't.
I can see it.
That's dangerous.
But I really like cleanliness.
Oh, really?
You're dirty, aren't you?
You're normal, aren't you?
As a man.
I'm a bit too clean.
What's normal about it?
You haven't taken good care of yourself.
I asked Takasu today.
What do you mean?
You haven't taken good care of yourself.
You have a lot of freckles.
No, no, no.
I'll leave it alone.
Like this?
I have this much.
You have this much?
If you have that much, this is a beach.
This is an accessory.
What is this man talking about?
If it's like this, you're the father.
You're the father.
No, you're the one who's attached to the father.
You're the one who's attached to Hamada.
Is this Hamada?
This is the father.
This is my partner.
If it's like this...
Let's talk here.
The child is cute.
Why?
Does that make my child do something?
You're going to get caught.
Your mother only sings when she's embarrassed.
Your father is an old man.
Please tell us a little more about the exciting thing you talked about on air the other day.
What is exciting?
The fight is about to start.
It's about to start.
What will happen?
That's because the skit is over.
Look, look, look, look.
This whole thing is not included.
This is exciting.
This space has been peaceful until now.
That's why we can call it exciting.
Yes, yes, yes.
You get it now, right?
That's because the exciting thing has already started.
Wait a minute.
What is exciting?
Is it a person who has that kind of shape?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You did this with all your might.
But you can't see it, but is it a person who has that kind of shape?
I've seen it before.
That exciting thing.
What kind of person is it?
That's what I want to know.
It's a person, isn't it?
It's not a person.
It's this mouth.
You've seen it before, haven't you?
I've seen it before.
If you do this in the New Year, it's a person.
To be honest, it's a human-shaped thing.
It's a human-shaped house.
I know.
But it has this kind of shape, doesn't it?
Yes, yes, yes.
It's a provocation, isn't it?
It's a provocation.
This is what we call exciting.
You should have told me something else.
I'll tell you something good.
What is it?
Exciting is not just one person.
Then how many people are exciting?
Exciting is me when something exciting happens.
No, no, no.
Then how many people are excited when something exciting happens?
What?
Exciting is me when something exciting happens.
Then how many people are excited when something exciting happens?
Exciting is a completely different person.
It's a completely different person.
It's not a person.
If you say it wrong, it's a different person.
Yes, yes, yes.
Exciting is also a fight.
Yes.
A circuit.
There are many things.
What I saw was the excitement of a fight.
So he had long hair, didn't he?
He had long hair.
He had a lot of hair.
What kind of hair?
He was a man with a scar on his cheek.
Was he a barber?
No, he wasn't a barber.
He had a scar on his cheek.
And when he was off...
Why do you know so much?
You don't have a girlfriend, do you?
He was swimming in the pool on the roof of a hotel.
That's Yakuza.
No, no, no.
That's not it.
I want to rest.
I want to rest in the hotel pool.
I'm Yakuza.
No, no, no.
And there was a small band in the house.
I can't see it.
What?
That's the worst.
I don't know.
I want to learn more.
You can learn anything.
Do you have a license?
That's because I have a boyish heart.
On Monday morning after this broadcast,
about six o'clock in the morning,
on Zoom,
Tatsuo Umemiya was mixing a special edition of our Dantan Special.
He was on Zoom as a punishment game.
I lost the punishment game.
I went there in the morning.
I want you to do it.
Yes.
Everyone watching this,
in a few hours after this,
everyone will be out.
In a few hours?
Yes.
Tatsuo Umemiya will sleep.
I can't do it.