Chikichiki! Hensei Ponpoko Tanuki Neiri Gassai!
Today we have two teams, the downtown team and the Yamasaki-Kogoriko team.
Each team chose a tanuki.
Which of the two teams will be able to beat the Tanuki Neiri?
Who will be the judge?
No one.
No one? But they're all lined up over there.
The judge is Mr. Kenji Suga.
Nice to meet you.
Who is it?
What a strange character.
Why are you dressed like that?
You're all dressed up.
I look like a fake talent.
Who are you?
I don't know.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Let's start with the Tanuki from the east.
That's us.
The Tanuki from the west.
The Tanuki from the Yamasaki-Kogoriko team.
Let's begin!
This is getting interesting.
I wanted to be a Tanuki too.
The Tanuki from the west.
The Tanuki from the Yamasaki-Kogoriko team.
You're all dressed up.
The Tanuki from the west.
Did you drink something?
Who will be able to sleep in the first round of the Tanuki from the west?
No matter how much you sleep, your body will be strong.
This is a boxing box.
I'll put this on my belly.
Here I go!
Who are you going to hit?
Wow!
You said wow!
But look at this.
I can't get up.
I can't get up at all.
What about me?
As you can see, I have a lot of muscles.
This is a meat bun.
And this is a shumai.
I can't get up at all.
He can't get up at all.
You were angry when you woke up, weren't you?
It was itchy.
When you were sleeping, it was itchy.
That's right.
It was just a coincidence.
It wasn't itchy at all.
It was itchy twice.
What is the score of the Yamasaki-Kokoriko team?
8.9 points, 9.8 points, 8.5 points.
42 points.
What is the score of the mountain team?
10 points, 8 points, 7.9 points, 7.5 points.
40 points.
The second round.
Who will be the one to continue?
I have a favorite.
This is my favorite.
This is huge.
I don't want to eat it.
What do you do with this?
I stick this to my body.
I put it in here.
I can't get up.
I can't get up at all.
I want to put it in from here.
It's quite rough.
I have a favorite.
I can't get up.
I can't get up at all.
I can't get caught.
I put it in the lid.
I can't get up.
Go in.
The third one.
Whose head you are lying on?
Who puts his head on it?
It's important.
This is huge.
It's okay, right? It's okay at all.
This is amazing.
What do you mean by doing it right and left?
What does this mean?
This is amazing.
I understand.
Let's look at the scores.
Yamasaki and Koryuho's team's score is...
We'll do our best.
5 points, 7 points, 10 points, 9 points, 10 points.
The total score is...
41 points.
Yamasaki's team's score is...
10 points, 9 points, 9 points, 10 points, 7 points.
The total score is...
11 points.
The third round.
Please close your eyes and sleep.
Please play the music.
Please.
What?
Please play the music.
I've never played this before.
It's creepy.
Please make it into an H.
This is an H.
It's coming.
It's an H.
It's cute.
Does it hurt?
I want to act.
Let's take it off.
Teacher.
There's something like juice coming out of this skull.
Isn't that sweat?
It's not sweat.
What is this?
It's like it's coming up.
I'm amazing.
I'm going to appear from here.
Please.
What is it?
It's a new raccoon.
It's like Mr. Ishimoku.
What kind of idol is this?
A new raccoon.
What are you doing?
What are you doing without talking?
It's amazing.
He's licking his nose.
Do you know what happens after licking your nose?
He licks his mouth too.
It's amazing.
He doesn't talk at all.
That's it?
His face is scary.
He's an amazing character.
He's amazing.
Fujiwara got 43 points from the water ball attack.
Fujiwara got 47 points.
Next, they will have a match at the same time.
Let's go.
At the same time.
Yes.
Ignition.
Okay.
I have to keep an eye on it.
Let's see how long it takes.
Isn't it hot?
What?
Do your best, raccoon.
Do your best.
Raccoon.
Why are you talking?
It's hot.
That's right.
You sleep well.
I sleep well.
It's a good season to sleep.
What?
I'm all right.
I'll stick to it from now on.
What are you talking about?
My raccoon will be from now on.
What?
It's a great movement.
You're good.
Do your best, east.
I'm going to drop it
I did it!
It's finally the last match
With 55kg of hot water bath, Tanuki's true strength will be revealed
Let's see how he does it
Let's do it
1,2,3
It's heavy
Put it in slowly
Gently
From the legs
Put the squid on the legs
Will it wake up?
It's okay
You can do it
Put it in
Why?
It's already awake
I'm going
I'm counting on you
You're fast
Why are you doing that?
1,2,3
Put the squid on the legs
It's okay
You're fast
1,2,3
He's trying to sleep
The current record is 2.28 seconds
This Tanuki's record is 2.34 seconds
This is a very interesting sight
I'm very happy
Yesterday
I was boxing in the morning
Did anyone see me?
I was laughing
I couldn't help but laugh
Boxing
There are many names
Fighting Harada, Guts Ishimatsu
I was surprised by the name
I was surprised by the ring name
Cyborg Koichi
Really?
At that time, I became a fan
Cyborg Koichi
First of all
The announcer and the commentator
They call me a cyborg
But
Now Koichi has a good punch
Koichi doesn't say that
Cyborg moves fast
I'm a cyborg
I forgot the name of the opponent
I have too much impact
You have to stop the movement of the cyborg
I can't stop
I'm a cyborg
I was surprised
How was the fight?
It was amazing
I was surprised
Turn around
In the first round
The cyborg was amazing
After the first round
Cyborg won the fight
In the second round
Cyborg won
I was surprised
In the third round
Cyborg won
Cyborg
I didn't stand up
I ran out of fuel
The announcer said
The cyborg doesn't move
Is that true?
It's true
The cyborg doesn't move
The referee
Of course
The cyborg
The cyborg lost
Really?
The man with the microphone
He came to the ring
He explained
I'm a cyborg
At the end of the second round
The opponent's left hook
I don't know
I see
The cyborg's left hook broke
How did it happen?
It doesn't break
The first round was amazing
It was amazing
It was a lie
I thought the lid was open
The lid was open
You can open it
No matter what
I can open it
It's like the lid under the TV
It's like
I've done it twice
I thought it was open
I think I can open it
It's okay
I think it's open
It's like
The club president did it
He did
Seriously
That's right.
Well then...
Yesterday...
Yes, yes.
Isn't this sashiba?
You, right?
Yes.
Yesterday...
Don't say it like that.
Suddenly...
It fell down.
Ah!
Ah, no, no, no!
No!
That's no good.
And then...
Oh!
That's no good!
That's no good, right?
I'm glad it didn't happen today.
It's the last time!
I can't even open my eyes.
What were you doing?
I wasn't doing anything.
Yesterday, I was talking to the staff.
That's right.
I thought something was stuck in my bone.
After I ate the sashiba.
And then I dropped it.
I looked at it.
No one noticed.
I noticed.
Everyone knows that you dropped your tooth.
I said something.
I looked at it.
No one noticed.
I probably didn't put my face on it.
But the staff also noticed.
You put your face on it and did this.
There's a place like this, too.
Hama-chan...
There's a place where she gets shy.
She says that.
She says that on the phone.
Why?
Shazuna.
Every Little Thing.
Matsumoto-san is the parent of a recently popular band.
That's right.
Actually, she's about to change her name to Downtown.
I can say that.
Matsumoto-san, please tell us your current favorite name.
And why did you come up with that name?
Please tell us the reason.
Did you come up with the name Shazuna?
I came up with it.
Why Shazuna?
It doesn't matter what it feels like.
It feels like it has a lot of vitamins in it.
What kind of world has a name like that?
So you're going to change your name to Downtown.
Downtown is...
I'm starting to get bored of it.
Even if people call me Downtown, I don't feel like looking back.
That's your personal feeling, isn't it?
In that sense, my favorite name right now is...
Attention, please.
You have to think about a lot of things when you put on a band.
When you get called by the staff.
There are a lot of things.
Attention, please.
It's kind of...
I can say, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I think it's better to have a name.
That way, you'll remember it.
Yes, yes.
I'll remember it.
For example, when everyone goes on a trip to America or overseas,
You'll definitely hear the name Downtown.
Even for a moment, the name Downtown will pop up in your head.
It's the same thing.
When everyone gets on a plane,
They'll say, attention, please.
My and Hamada's faces will pop up.
That alone is worth it.
Next month, or the month after that,
I think it will gradually be reflected in that direction.
Mr. Matsumoto, who was once the judge of the Supreme Court,
What is the boundary between rape and not rape?
Rape, right?
I'll tell you this, because you're all stupid.
I'll tell you in a way that's easy to understand.
Why?
It's okay to say it normally.
It's easier to understand that way.
It's easy to understand, right?
For example.
Crying out of courtesy.
Crying out of courtesy, right?
A girl I don't like.
A girl I don't like!
Say it with confidence at the beginning.
Crying out of courtesy!
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry about that.
Go home!
I'm sorry.
Rape.
Rape!
I've reached the letter E.
Here I go.
Crying out of courtesy!
Crying out of courtesy?
You should have said it yourself.
Crying out of courtesy!
A girl I don't like!
It didn't come out at all.
I thought it would.
It was too early.
It was pure white.
Then why did you say such a thing?
I couldn't panic.
But you have to say it.
But I couldn't.
I wanted to lie down.
I wanted to lie down on the letter E.
It didn't come out at all.
I ask Matsumoto-san, the man who sends a message to every staff member.
When I went to the sauna the other day, a man with a picture on his back suddenly sat next to me.
I couldn't get out of the sauna right away, and I was so sweaty that I almost died.
What should I do to get out of this situation?
You don't have to say anything like that.
You have to lie so that you don't hurt the other person.
Just by saying a few words, your image of the other person changes completely.
When I get out of the sauna?
Yes, yes, yes.
When I get out of the sauna, I see the Yakuza coming.
It's not that hot.
I can tell.
Why do you sound like you're sulking?
Let's fight, Yakuza.
This is the best place.
Why do you want to fight? It's not like we're going to get out of the sauna.
So I say, sorry, it's not that hot.
And he says, hey, you're the Yakuza, right?
So I say, why are you going out?
And he says, I don't know.
At that time, I have no choice but to fight.
So I say, you're the Yakuza, right?
He says, I'm not that kind of Yakuza.
What kind of Yakuza are you talking about?
I don't know.
What the hell are you talking about?
Are you stupid?
What are you talking about?
Don't look at me like that.
I don't know what you're talking about.
The Yakuza?
It's hard to get out of the sauna as soon as you come in.
That's not true.
You shouldn't have come out.
I told you at the beginning.
You shouldn't have come out when I came in.
Did you say that?
I didn't say that.
Did you really say that?
Wait a minute.
You've been with me for 15 years.
You don't even know if I point my finger at you.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.