I'm not a kid.
O-Haka is dangerous!
Super Mile
I'm not a kid.
Chiki Chiki Hettare Yamazaki One-man Project, Part 3
A behind-the-scenes story on the night of O-Haka
and a great strategy to test the time.
I'm in O-Haka.
It's on the signboard.
This is Yamazaki's One-man Project, Part 3.
I'm sure he'll show us something cool today.
Yeah, even if you say that.
Until now, it was a little different meaning.
This time, it's a matter of temperament.
It's a test of courage.
So, the star of the night is Yamazaki.
Here you go.
Your voice is so low.
Who's this girl next to you?
You're in trouble.
Of course, it's pitch black.
Look at this.
You can't see anything, can you?
There's nothing black.
If you look at it all the time, it's a signboard.
It's on the road.
The woman in the back is an old lady.
What are you talking about?
You know what?
At the very end, there's a card.
Take the card and come back.
I can't run away on the way.
You can't run away.
I can't run away, but I can't come back.
If you run away, don't come here.
Where are you going?
I don't think there's a seat in Yoshimoto anymore.
Good luck.
Are you waiting here?
I'm scared.
I can hear the sound.
It looks bright.
The infrared is amazing.
A dog is barking.
Is this a real dog?
I was surprised.
A dog is barking.
The dog's face was very funny.
Why are you so surprised?
The dog's face is scary.
I'm scared.
I don't know why the dog is barking.
This is a dog.
What are you talking about?
I'm confused.
Who are you talking to?
You're not talking to me.
What?
I'm confused.
You're not talking to me.
Come here.
I'm confused.
You're not talking to me.
Wait a minute.
Yamazaki.
Yamazaki?
Why are you naked?
Are you my partner?
I'm looking down.
Yamazaki?
I don't have a shoe.
Yamazaki.
Yamazaki?
I was so scared.
Yamazaki.
There were five of us.
A ghost?
It's a yakuza.
I have to say.
You look like a yakuza?
Yamazaki?
I don't remember.
I'm not yakuza.
They called me.
Yamazaki.
A lot of trouble.
It's hard to say.
Yamazaki.
I don't know.
Maybe.
Chidori.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
No, it's not like that.
It's not like that at all.
I don't know.
There's not a lot of people today, right?
There's not a lot of people, and it's the same age as usual.
That's right.
Well, it's fine.
I'm sorry, but I'm a little confused.
Why?
The engine is not doing well, so please take a look.
No, I'm not.
Wait a minute.
Is this fashionable?
That's right.
It's fashionable.
I heard you're connected to fashionable talent.
I heard you're raising the price a lot.
It's not like that.
I don't think so.
That's fine.
But I can't play with cars.
That's right.
There's a story about the price of high-speed cars.
Really?
It's 600 yen now, right?
I'll make it 700 yen.
Even if you make it 700 yen, you have to ride it.
I think so, but high-speed cars should be made directly.
You're a sushi restaurant, aren't you?
You should definitely do that.
But I think a lot.
An old man at the window asked me for money directly.
I'm free, so I'll give you 2,000 yen.
2,000 yen.
What?
He's not alive.
I'll do that.
You may be like that.
That's not true.
That's why the price is written on the bottom.
It's going to change.
Of course.
It's impossible for an old man to ask for money directly.
It's an old man's good price.
That's right.
You shouldn't do that.
Next time, if an old man sees a person,
I'll give you 5,000 yen.
That's not good.
I'll give it to you before the price goes up.
Of course.
It's okay now.
That's fine.
If you don't do that, I'll give you a lot of money.
I've been to Harajuku once.
I didn't know.
You've been there, haven't you?
There was a red box.
I didn't know.
Wait a minute.
In the past,
I was working on a dirty Marmaron.
I was making a new one behind it.
When I came up,
there was an unmanned box.
I looked at it, and I had money.
But there was no old man.
So I thought,
I don't need it today.
And then,
there was an old man standing right next to me.
He was screaming,
but I was screaming, too.
I was screaming at the same time as the old man.
I just left.
I don't need it today.
That's not it.
I've been on the highway many times.
I've been photographed many times,
but I've never been sent there.
All of them aren't in the video.
Just the flash.
They react to it at high speed.
That's right.
I was angry.
I was photographed once.
It was like my friend's friend.
I was angry,
I got off the car,
and I had a will.
I had a will,
and I threw the car.
When I got off the car,
I reacted with that will,
and I threw the umbrella.
I was sent there many times.
You were photographed like this?
Yes.
The police called me,
and I said,
I want to see this.
And I threw it.
That's not true.
You're lying.
It's true.
That's not true.
I've never lied.
You're lying.
But you can take a good picture.
That's not true.
Who thought of taking a picture?
You haven't been photographed once?
I've been in a taxi once.
In the taxi,
an old man was in the taxi,
and the old man was very happy.
Is that so?
He was very happy.
That's not true.
But it was very difficult.
He was very happy.
Then the old man suddenly...
The old man was photographed,
and he was wearing blue.
He was wearing blue.
Then he started to talk a lot.
That's strange.
An old man who does business,
once he does that,
he can't rest.
That's right.
I often say that,
but that's written on the side of the car.
It's written on the side.
It's a sign.
Yes, yes.
It's quiet.
It's like this, right?
Oh, it's your mother.
It's true.
Right?
I love you.
I'm very popular with my mother.
Is that so?
I called her once before.
You called a woman.
Your mother.
My mother came,
and she said,
are you waiting for me?
She found out.
I heard it from my daughter.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'll call you again.
Wait a minute.
What?
If you don't invite only your daughter,
invite your mother too.
It's like that.
No, no.
Are you serious?
I'm a little angry.
Did you make that face?
Yes.
It's true.
It's funny.
It's like that.
It's not good for young people.
What are you talking about?
It's true.
You can't rest.
What do you mean?
You're not working.
That's not true.
I can't sleep.
I can't sleep because of that.
After I finished it,
I asked how many people had done it.
No, I didn't do that much.
No, if I did it,
30 people would have done it.
Is that okay?
I thought it was okay.
I can't say this.
It's a lie.
Girls are doing it these days.
It's amazing.
It's amazing, isn't it?
What's your mother like?
When I was young,
I was told that.
Your mother was beautiful when she was young.
Thank you.
I'm going crazy.
A long time ago,
Mr. Matsumoto said,
The person who made the phone is a bell.
When I heard that,
I was convinced.
At the same time,
I had a question.
Is the person who made the chuck
Mr. Chuck?
Or is it Mr. Fasner?
I want to ask this.
But this is true.
Everyone is like that.
The name of the person who made it is all
Maruyama Vaccine Maruyama.
I know that.
Everyone knows that.
It's not like that.
Tell me what's written in the newspaper.
You guys are really stupid.
Chuck E.H. Fasner.
What?
Don't say E.H.
The minister has a lot of names.
It's made up of three or four names.
That's why there's a person
called Chuck Fasner.
That's why you're using both.
I'm using both.
That's all.
It doesn't matter if it's a little difficult story.
It's a very simple story.
Is that so?
Yes.
Everyone says that.
I don't mean everyone.
I made a sandwich.
What?
That's just what everyone knows.
Everyone...
You've never said anything that everyone doesn't understand.
Why?
No one believes in Chuck and Fasner.
Check it out.
I'll check it out.
It's safe.
What are you talking about?
What?
That's right.
What's that white thing on the back of the bike
that the police officer is riding?
You're the one who put the ticket in.
What?
You put the ticket in, right?
You don't know anything about the police or the yakuza.
What are you learning?
I see.
I wonder if there was something like that before.
The man on the Shinkansen has a dash case.
Don't tell me what's in there.
That's the Shinkansen's way of riding.
Hand-pulling?
Hand-pulling.
Remember it before you ride it.
I'm not scared.
If you drive while looking at it.
It's like you're holding your fingers together.
Next question.
Is it warm or cold if you turn on the cooler and the stove at the same time in the same room?
It feels good.
It feels really good.
Everyone doesn't believe me.
It's raining.
It's raining here. It's raining here. It's not raining here.
Have you ever stood on the slope of that?
Have you ever stood on it?
I've never stood on it, but I've seen it.
There is.
But I've never stood on the slope.
I've seen it.
That means what I'm saying is so unusual.
I've never seen it. I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
I'm more amazing.
Really?
Let me hear that. Let me hear that.
That's why it's not wet at all here.
I'm telling the truth.
I can't stand it anymore.
If that's the case.
I'm telling the truth.
I can't make up a story like this.
No, no, no.
I'm telling the truth.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's really wet here. It's not wet at all here.
I'm glad. I'm glad.
No, no, no, no.
It's been like this all the time.
No, no, no.
Go to the side.
It's funny. It's only wet here.
It's been like this all the time, but you should go to the side.
What's that? Were you walking alone?
Yes, I was walking alone.
No one was watching you?
No one was watching me.
There's no witness, is there?
I got it.
I'm hungry.
I have a lot of stories that you don't believe.
Don't say that.
I've known it for a long time.
One day, when I was in elementary school,
I came home from school.
What's that?
You're making such a scary face.
What should I do?
This is a real story. This is a real story.
I came home from school.
This is a real story.
I got it. I got it.
I'm especially curious about this.
Yes, yes, yes.
A man is a king.
That's enough.
Stop it.
As long as you're alive.
When I came home, there was a table.
There was an animal I've never seen before.
Goodbye. See you again.
This is a real story.
No, it's a lie.
An animal I've never seen before.
What kind of shape was it? What kind of outfit was it?
Stop it.
I don't care about your face.
It's brown and long.
What do you mean it's long?
It's long like this.
That's not true.
It's not true.
It's not long.
It's short.
It's two legs.
You're a fool.
It's like this.
You're making it more and more.
It's a real story. It's a real story.
It's getting more and more.
There was a pot and I put it in the pot.
Hey, hey.
That's not true.
You said, oh, and you looked at me.
Oh.
I didn't do that.
That's not true.
Why are you saying that?
It's like a fly.
Tell me quickly.
I'm telling you it's going up!
And then the transparent wings go like this
It's transparent!
It's like a fly
And then it goes like this
You can't take it off
And then the tail
Ah, the tail
The tail goes like this
What's that?
It's like Fujiyama
Good morning
What's that?
It goes like this
I saw that when I was in elementary school
You're so noisy
I'm going to make a joke out of this
It's you
It's true
I broke it
What happened to it?
It went like this
And the other one went like this too
No matter what you do, you hit the set
The other one went like this too
They're both like this
You can't do that
They're like this
They're glaring at each other
They don't even look at each other
They stay like this
And then the other one went like this
So you're really doing it?
You're really doing that?
No
What's that?
I'm hot
You're hot? That's scary
You shouldn't look in the hot water
You shouldn't look away
If you look at me, you're going to get hit!
I'm looking at you!
Look over there.
What is this?
I can't lose either!
Did you do it? Did you do it?
I'm going to stare at you forever.
Are you okay?
Yes!
I can't do it anymore!
It's that time!
Good morning!