It's time for the 1st Gaki no Tsukai Arahen, Chikitsuki Gendo Kai Babanuki Senchiken!
It's been a long time.
It's been a long time since we've had an opening like this.
It's nice.
Today, Yamagata-san will be in charge, so we haven't been told anything.
Yes. Today, we're going to have the Gendo Kai Babanuki Senchiken.
Did you say it?
Yes, I did.
Did I say it out loud?
Yes. From now on, there will be 31 pictures of the celebrities on the cards.
Ah, so each of them will be given out.
Yes, each of them will be given out to two people.
Yes.
Then, based on the capacity of the Babanuki Senchiken, one will be taken out one by one.
Yes, yes.
Then, the celebrities with the same common interest will be shown here.
I see.
Do you understand?
Yes, yes.
And if they really have the same common interest, they will be called Babanuki Senchiken.
So, the big treasure will be taken out.
Yes, it will be taken out.
It will be taken out.
Then, there will be one left, right?
Yes, yes.
That person will be the Babanuki of the entertainment world.
I see.
That's how it is.
That's right.
He's not the Babanuki, though.
This person is not needed in the entertainment world.
No, he's not needed.
That's your interpretation.
That means he doesn't belong here.
He doesn't belong here.
Why does this person have a grudge against the entertainment world?
It's forced.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Please take a look, me?
Of course, take a look.
Have a look, please.
Please take a look, one after the other.
Stiff.
There's a whole lot that you dislike.
I'm just not good.
There's a whole lot of stuff you don't like about me.
I'm wasn't.
I can be properly 굿 on the stage.
Yes, go ahead.
I don't like this game.
I'm having a lot of fun too.
It's not fun at all.
I'm having a lot of fun.
Everyone used to sit like this a long time ago.
You drew a good one.
In a way, he's an idiot.
Did you find it?
Yes, I found it.
This is...
What?
Hamada Masatoshi appeared.
What do you mean?
It's hard to wrinkle.
Safe!
I wrinkled!
It's very safe.
You're an idiot.
That's right.
We do our best to wrinkle.
Because it's a game.
Here it is.
This.
What is it?
Oh!
Okay!
Let's go.
Please draw a good one.
Okay.
You drew a good one.
Did you draw the best one?
But in my hands...
There's no one who can transform.
This is not good.
It's easy to understand.
It's not common.
It's supposed to be like this.
Okay.
I want to say something good.
It's true.
There's nothing good.
It's hard.
This is...
Hinagata Akiko.
Here it is.
Matsumoto Hitoshi.
What does this mean?
It's supposed to be like this.
Ukeuchi.
Shakure.
Here it is.
You drew a good one.
Matsumoto Hitoshi.
Nagabuchi Tsuyoshi.
I remembered a good one.
Here it is.
Matsuyama Chiharu.
What does this mean?
This is...
Please judge.
Shut up!
I don't know.
What is this?
What should I say?
This is good.
Mokkun.
Both of them are handsome.
I would definitely do that.
Shut up!
Moriwaki.
A character who is loved from young to old.
Please do it.
This is a great battle.
Really?
Here it is.
This is it.
Safe!
This is a big safe.
Please draw.
This is bad.
Wajima Sensei.
Sensei?
Why Sensei?
Moriwaki Kenji.
That was easy.
Fujita Tomoko.
Please put it down.
That was it?
I don't think so.
No, no, no.
There is no problem.
Drink it.
Who will it be?
There is a problem with your hair.
Safe!
What a great combination.
My old lady!
Old lady!
It was something inside of my head.
I see.
That's what it means.
That's right.
It is a great opportunity.
Do you want to do it?
I can't do it.
I can't.
I'm not that kind of guy.
I'll do it if it's easy to get on.
Easy to get on.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
This is interesting.
It's been a while.
I'm not that kind of guy.
Hello.
It's been a while.
It's a nice place.
Is it nice?
If you look at this.
You're not motivated.
I'm not motivated.
Hey.
What was it?
It's okay.
Why is it okay?
I was about to forget.
No, no, no.
Somehow, you two are getting along badly.
Are you showing that shit again?
It's often written in magazines
When I put it in my decree
It's a disgusting piece of shit.
I understand.
It's terrible.
I'm a really unpleasant group.
And you, you know,
I said too much.
Wait a minute.
You've become a mess.
It was too much.
And Hamada, you know, I was too much in his eyes.
I didn't say it.
I said it.
I said, you're such a fool!
Why did you get caught?
And we got along.
The reason we got along was because I was the one who was bad.
And you were always following me around.
It was like you were tired.
Yeah, I was tired.
That's why when I came out, it was like this.
The other day, you were doing it like this.
I thought it was terrible.
No, it's not that.
It's because you didn't say it properly.
What are you talking about?
You didn't say that there was no such thing.
I didn't say anything.
Because I was told.
100,000 yen, 50,000 yen.
What?
You didn't say that.
What are you talking about?
You didn't say that there was no such thing.
You didn't say that.
You're always like this.
No, no, no.
Let's do it again.
Earlier, you said it in the dressing room.
Really, how many years have I been doing this?
What?
How many years have you been doing this?
How many years have I been doing this in this world?
15 years.
It's been 15 years.
I've been doing this for 15 years.
I've never complained to the AD or the staff.
That's not true.
You're like Kodama-san.
I've never complained to the AD.
Let me tell you this.
If there's a mistake with the AD,
if complaining is love,
then maybe there's no love.
Wait.
Wait, wait.
I'm not that kind of person.
Right?
That's not true.
Why?
I've never complained to the AD.
That's not true.
I've never complained to the staff.
It's hard to complain.
That's not true.
I don't want people to think I'm a good person.
I'm not a good person at all.
That's true.
I do my best to make people laugh.
But I don't like people who are bad at lying.
What?
For example,
in Downtown Deluxe,
there's a poll of 1,000 people, right?
Yes, yes.
Out of all the talented people,
this guy is in 5th place.
4th place.
He's in 4th place.
But out of the 1,000 people, he's in 1st place.
He was in 1st place.
He's a villainous talent.
That's why.
Please stop it.
I might not be able to say I'm a good person or a bad person.
But,
but,
I'm not.
I'm not that kind of person.
I'm a great old man.
That's not true.
That's not true, old man.
Why not?
Downtown Deluxe...
This makes me angry.
Listen to me.
Downtown Deluxe bullying.
There's a poll like this.
There's a picture on the side of the poll.
This is my picture.
We're walking together.
We're riding the same bullet train together.
This is strange.
That's strange.
Why?
It's okay to take a picture of me, but it's okay to take a picture of a normal person.
That's strange.
It's like that.
That's a bad choice.
That's right.
So it's okay to be a bad person with two people.
Okay.
Okay?
You have to treat me like that.
I feel that way.
What?
I'm really sorry.
Ah, you scared me!
Don't be scared.
You look like you're the one who's calling the staff and saying,
Hey!
You look like you're doing it.
I see.
I've never hit anyone since high school.
I don't know anything about that.
I've never hit anyone.
No, it's not that.
You do this kind of thing at work, right?
Yeah.
It's nothing more than that.
No way.
You're being ridiculous.
I'm not.
Say something!
What do you want me to say?
Last week, after Kangaroo, you twisted your neck, right?
I didn't do anything.
Why did I twist my neck?
I don't know.
Everyone was calling the staff.
Why did you do that?
Kangaroo, you twisted your neck!
You twisted your neck.
But the staff didn't see it.
I can't believe it.
Oh, I remember.
There's a pachinko, right?
Our?
Our downtown theater.
This makes me angry again.
Why?
Your pachinko is too thick!
Right?
I don't know if I did it or not,
but Hamada's pachinko is too thick!
I always get in the way.
Please don't do that.
It's not good for my image.
You don't care about your image.
Yesterday, when I was eating at this restaurant,
you said,
Hamada is often on the show, but you don't come.
Even if you say that...
I don't care.
I made it like that.
Why am I always on the side that gets in the way?
Please don't do that.
I'm glad.
I came out properly.
I'm glad you said that.
I didn't do anything wrong.
But you have to apologize.
I have to apologize.
I can't read it.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey.
I always get in the way.
I didn't get in the way.
You're elegant.
I don't care.
It's funny, so it's okay.
It's not funny.
Don't worry about it.
Give me your hand.
Look at this guy.
Get out of the way.
You're laughing behind my back, too.
Love professional Matsumoto-san.
I'm wearing glasses.
I'm always worried when I kiss.
What?
I'm going to kiss you.
There's no way for a woman to take off her glasses while she's in the mood.
Take off your glasses and kiss me.
Let's talk in the dressing room.
I'm wearing glasses.
I can kiss you lightly.
It's hard to kiss when I'm wearing glasses.
That's why...
It's obvious.
It's obvious, but it's very natural.
For example, when you're having sex, you take a bath, right?
When you take a bath, you take off your glasses.
Of course.
You take a shower and take off your glasses.
Why do you have to wear glasses?
I don't know where my girlfriend is.
She's a new girl.
I can't wear glasses yet.
Why do you always wear glasses?
When I take my girlfriend to the dressing room, I wear glasses.
Otherwise, I'll hit the wall.
I don't have a girlfriend like that.
I don't know how to drink.
That's why you have to wear glasses.
I'll hit the wall.
I take off my glasses.
Of course, I take off my glasses at that time.
But it's hard to take off my glasses at that time.
I don't know how to take off my glasses.
It hurts.
In the past, there was an actor named Kenta Oka.
He was wearing glasses.
He was wearing glasses in the morning.
That's cheating.
You can see it even if you don't wear glasses.
It's annoying that you can't concentrate.
It's annoying that you have to do this all the time.
My father is doing this, but I'm doing this.
There are also women who wear glasses.
There are also couples who wear glasses.
I win! I win!
I wonder if men take off their glasses.
You're kind.
But I let them lie down and take them off.
That's where it starts.
That's right.
Otherwise, if you take off your glasses before you take off your female glasses, you won't be able to see your female glasses.
Youkihi, Cleopatra, and Ononokomachi are the three most beautiful women in the world.
Matsumoto, who are the three most beautiful men in the world?
Who are the three most beautiful men in the world?
What do you think of beautiful men?
If you think about the world, the first thing you can't get rid of is Alain Delon.
I see.
Next is America.
Who is America?
That's it.
Ah, John Lone!
I'm not in America.
Alain Delon, John Lone...
You like Alain Delon, don't you?
Next is Kato Goh.
Among you, Kato Goh is definitely the most beautiful.
The fact that your male image is Kato Goh is...
I can't throw away these three.
The Japanese representative is Kato Goh.
Wait, wait, wait.
Who is the most handsome man in Japan?
Kato Goh, and then there's Tani Hayato.
What is it?
What's so funny?
No, no, I can't say it's ugly.
Who is it?
Who is the most handsome man in Japan?
In the world, it's said that it's Kimura Takuya.
Yes, yes.
Who is it?
Among you, Kato Goh is more handsome than Takuya.
That's true.
He has a beautiful face.
It's a big face, isn't it?
Kato Goh.
The price doesn't matter.
But it's a big face.
I've seen it at the supermarket.
Whether it's big or small, it doesn't matter.
It's the last box of your underwear.
It's hard to tell if it's big or small.
It's big, so it doesn't matter.
Don't look at me like I'm a sub.
Who is the most handsome man in Japan?
I'm doing it with you, but Sorimachi is the most handsome man.
No, it's not Sorimachi.
It's Sorimachi.
He's 33 years old.
He's still 22 or 23 years old.
His skin is smooth.
He's as chubby as us.
Bring Sorimachi here.
I'll bring Kato Goh.
What kind of connection do you have with him?
Team Zero.
Hey, Team Zero.
Your eyes are long.
Okay, pull it out.
Okay, Shinobu.
This is dirty.
Okay.
Pull it out.
Oh, this is...
Ichihara-san.
This is it.
Who is the most nutritious?
Yes.
Why?
I'm looking forward to it.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.