On September 24, in Sagara-cho, Shizuoka Prefecture.
In this town, which usually looks calm and calm,
on this day, a silent sense of tension began to flow.
Now, the legendary long day is slowly beginning to open its curtain.
Downtown Special 24-hour Talk.
The staff of a total of 500 people are gradually preparing.
At 3 o'clock in the afternoon, Hamada arrives.
50 minutes late, Matsumoto arrives.
I can't do it, but I'll turn the camera.
As the curfew approaches and the weather worsens,
1,000 people are starting to come in.
The rain that never stops,
and the excitement of the audience waiting for downtown is increasing.
It's starting.
Finally, the 24-hour hot battle begins.
The rain that never stops,
and the excitement of the audience waiting for downtown is increasing.
It's starting.
The rain that never stops,
and the excitement of the audience waiting for downtown is increasing.
He's clearly lost.
His smile got choked up.
Just do it л
did we lose again?
We lost?!
It's about time we spent some time with our fans.
It's so hot in here!
Oh dear.
It's finally here
There's a lot of people
Yes, hello
In this rain
Yes
It's weird to do this
It's weird
We can't do this
We can't
You guys can't come either
We can't do this because you guys are coming
Because I don't have any weight today
In the middle
I don't have any weight today
So I thought I'd go drink some tea
So I came all the way to Shizuoka
What are you doing?
There's a lot of things
What is this? Is this a broadcast code?
No, no
If it's that, it's too late
It's too late
You said you had a lot of ideas
Yes
You said 24 hours
You said 12 hours
What?
No, no, no
That's not it
You said 6 hours
I said it
You only said 2 hours
That's right
It's only 2 hours
So even if we talk for 24 hours
22 hours is useless
Is this allowed?
And it's not like anyone is coming
There's no one
You can go out and talk
24 hours, please
No, no, no
If I say this now
Some of the people we talked to are laughing
But no one is laughing
If that's the case, I don't need it
There's also a meal time
There's a lot of things
But you have to do it for 24 hours
It's called downtown help
Choose that
Yes
You have to help
You have to spend a little bit of time
There's a lot of things like that
Let's go to the post office
Not yet
If you do that, I won't be able to hold it
It's a long way to go
This is real
I can feel it
For the time being, it's good to talk
That's right
Don't go around
Let's stay here
There's a lot of things
No, no, no
Let's go together
Nice to meet you
We met
Wait
No one noticed
You can't talk about that
Are you tired already?
Please bring out the post
Let's introduce
The postman, Nakamori Akira
When I first came out, there wasn't much reaction
What are you doing?
I'm Nakamori Akira
It took a while for me to notice
I told you not to come
I'm from the post office
What are you talking about?
To explain the situation
I always do a free talk show
But today is 24 hours
So the Filipinos who live in Japan
I'm happy to be back
It's an event
Japanese budget
Do you want to introduce the post?
This is Akina-chan's question
This is Akina-chan's question?
Yes, let's do that
Where did the phrase that you can't go anywhere
Come from?
I see
Do you know?
Of course I know
He knows everything
I know everything
You're thinking right?
I'm not thinking
I'm just remembering
I remembered
Look
Animals
What do you like about animals?
What do you like about Akina?
Horse
That's it
What?
Horse has a special skill
For example
This is a horse running on a person
What other animals do you have?
Dog, cat
Cat has a role of smiling and telling the next day's weather
Dog?
Dog
Dog can bark at people and tell their owner
Dog can...
All animals have roles
That's fine
But Bulldogs doesn't have any role
I've got it. I've got it. I've got it!
That Bulldog is really...
I sang that before I came out.
What is that?
What kind of person do you like as a man?
I like someone who is fun.
Someone who is fun?
If you're asked which one is which, which one is which?
Which one am I?
Which one do you think is more manly?
I'm not kidding. If you just say the face, it's really...
Really.
What do you think?
Wait. Don't look too far.
You're doing a drama with a pretty good character, right?
If you look at that, I really like that kind of impression.
But since you didn't come out, you're a fool like this.
I'm sorry. I'm not a fool. I'm just doing this kind of comedy.
I got scared.
Did you write something? Do you want something to drink?
Yes.
There's a fridge over there.
Of course.
Let's drink sake.
You can't do that.
If I had to drink this much, it would be easier for me to drink it as it is.
Please sit down.
I've prepared a lot of help stories.
Let's take a look.
Do you want to see the help story?
I've prepared a story that will help us.
This is the first time.
It's a fireworks show.
Please enjoy it.
It's amazing.
I can't stand it if I get hit in the house.
This program is brought to you by Tiger Magic.
Moelia Asahi Beer.
Sponsored by Lion Nipro.
I don't want anything like oolong tea.
Go get it yourself.
Hayaki, don't you think it's time for you to stop?
I don't know if it was a mistake to light a fire so early.
It's beer.
I'm waiting for it.
It's tea.
It's like oolong tea.
It's oolong tea.
I know.
It's a non-smell sky.
I'm getting drunk.
If you're drunk, I'll sue you.
Let me go.
I don't have a partner.
I do.
I can't kill my partner.
I can do it if I'm a master.
No way.
Do it.
Shut up.
Why are you acting like a junior high school student?
He's taking a video letter.
Video letter.
Machan, Hama-chan, how are you doing?
24 hours talk.
You did a good job.
Machan, Hama-chan, you're always like a father with a bad son.
Don't give up until the end of 24 hours.
It's hard to say, but please do your best.
Machan, Hama-chan, you've been doing this for 24 hours.
I won't do it.
Machan, Hama-chan, you're great.
Even if it's a week, you're still the same.
That's what I like the most.
I was really surprised to hear that you two were going to do a 24-hour stage.
When I'm tired and sleepy, I'll do it at my own pace.
I like the combination of Hamada-san and Machan.
Please do your best.
Happy New Year, everyone.
I'm Kyoshi Ishikawa.
I used to think that 24-hour TV was a show about welfare work and love.
Is that so?
Are you making money?
I'll do my best from now on.
Machan, Hama-chan, you're going to do a 24-hour free talk.
I wanted to see you for about two hours.
Please do your best.
Machan, I love you.
Machan, Hama-chan, you've been doing this for 24 hours.
I was surprised to hear that you two were going to do a 24-hour TV.
I've been doing 24-hour TV for 17 years.
There's only one thing that can make it last 24 hours.
Don't overdo it.
It's going to kill you.
Hamada is already crying.
I'm not crying.
He's crying.
This video letter is a little cowardly.
Why?
I don't like it.
Are you serious?
Are you trying to make me cry?
Turn it up.
Don't cry like that.
This is cowardly.
I'm not crying.
This video letter is a little cowardly.
Don't overdo it.
He's the one who cried for 24 hours.
I want to go home.
I was happy when I was in elementary school.
I don't think so.
What?
Call talent.
Call him.
Please bring out the board.
Mr. Magno.
Yes.
Please come to our show.
I have a lot of money left.
I don't care.
Please come to our show.
Hello.
Marina.
I'm the best.
I don't know if it's true.
Marina?
Is that you?
That's right.
Can I call you Pino?
Pino.
Where are you now?
Tamori.
Please change it to Tamori.
Really?
Tamori.
What?
It's Hamada from Taotao.
Can you buy it for me?
Hello.
What are you doing?
I'm shooting a show right now.
What kind of show?
It's a special for child users.
Is it a special for child users?
That's right.
Tamori's picture is on the big screen.
I'll tell you something.
Yes.
Are you two making fun of me?
It's not like that.
Hey.
Why are you doing that?
Tamori, it's time to introduce your friend.
I'll buy it for you.
Thank you very much.
Hello.
Yes.
I thought you were going to eat yakiniku.
What do you want?
I want caviar.
Caviar?
I just want caviar.
I got it.
I'll be waiting for you.
Yes.
Please take care of Tamori.
Good luck.
Thank you very much.
It's been a long time.
What?
Let's listen to the new music.
Oh, my God.
It's been raining a lot.
Don't get wet.
The weather is not good.
But it's strange.
It didn't rain when I did it.
It's hard now.
But after a month or two,
I had a good memory.
Do you remember?
I don't remember.
It's been raining a lot.
I don't like it.
Good luck.
When you say good luck,
don't hit me.
I'm not your enemy.
I don't like it.
Shall we play badminton?
Let's do it.
It looks fun.
Shiritori badminton corner.
Lion.
Don't call me Shiritori.
I have a lion.
Let's play Kompachi.
You have to eat something.
Okay.
You play first.
Mochi.
Chimpon.
I lost.
I can eat.
Menrui.
Ramen.
Yakisoba.
You don't say anything.
What did I do?
I didn't expect you to come back so beautiful.
I don't know.
Don't talk to me.
The species of insects.
Okay.
Cob.
Tombo.
Wakata.
Insect.
I know that.
It hurts.
Let's do it again.
Again.
I'm sorry.
I'll scream.
You are not a normal guest.
But I'm happy.
I'm so excited at this time.
You are the only one.
I'm sorry.
Actually.
I'm hungry.
There is a restaurant near here.
It's called Tonkitsu.
I'm not lying.
It's really delicious.
This is good.
It's hot.
You are a German toast.
Don't eat it close.
You two eat it deliciously.
I'm really hungry.
Because.
I ate meaningless badminton.
I saw it on the monitor.
I don't know what it is.
I've never played badminton.
It's already 12 o'clock.
Let's eat dinner.
He will cook for us.
I'll make curry.
If you don't help me, I'll make curry.
I understand.
You don't cut the potatoes.
I'll fry the flour.
You fry flour.
It's too big.
I'll warm the frying pan.
I'm scared.
It's okay.
I'll do it slowly.
I'll hold it.
I'll fry this.
I'll do it slowly.
If it's too soft, I'll do it like this.
If you have a lot of hands, please do it like this.
Everyone is hungry.
I'll fry the onions.
Please do it.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it at all.
It's okay.
Your reaction is weak.
Curry smells good.
It's okay.
I'll fry the potatoes.
I'll fry the onions.
What can you do?
Curry.
It doesn't rain.
Tomorrow afternoon will be hot.
I'm hungry.
I'll fry the potatoes.
I'm looking forward to what you can do.
I'm sorry.
I made it with a great tool.
This is the thing from before.
This is a curry rice made by SUMU.
Which is better than the fried rice made by TOMITOKU SHU?
Don't bite.
What kind of music is this?
Don't get too into it
It's done!
Is it a little spicy?
No, it's just right
This is balanced
For the time being, let's make it 20 people
For the remaining 980 people, please take the curry from this person
What is it?
Speaking of curry, it's Chi-Chi
It's Chi-Chi
If you don't have it, you can't come here
Are you going to pour it all over?
Of course
Chi-Chi, smile
Don't be moody, smile
Shut up
You're eating so much
Don't be like that
It's delicious
It warms you up
Good evening
It's the timing you were aiming for
Did you all aim for this?
It's not like that
Are you going to pour it all over?
No
It's delicious, but I'm sorry
What are you talking about?
When there's something in your stomach, you want to sleep
That's right
Let's go
This is a strange time
I can't make a sumo club
Sumo club? Who's going to do it?
For the time being, let's start with 2 people
Master
I'll let you be the master
From now on, you're the master
Master
Stop it
It's funny because it's this time
I'll do the whole thing
I'll do it all with bare hands
It's been a while
This time, many things
Karaoke
Case
Glasses
Necklace
I'm saying it
I heard it from the king!
No! I gave it to him!
Chikuwa
Wa
I'm Dai-chan!
Why did you become a word?
Tama-negi
Gisu-gisu
Why did you become a word?
Wan-wan-nyan-nyan
Repeating words
Isn't that a video game?
Kota-i
Say it
Mic
Kusu
Come
Okay, come
What is it?
Explain it
Explain it so that I can understand
You're getting shy
What is it?
You're laughing
It's kusu
What is kusu?
Say kusu
Kusu
Frisbee
Bee
Bisu
Come
Are you the one who sat down?
I'm sorry
I'm scared
What is it?
I'm sorry
There are a lot of words in the world
What is it?
Donita Tsuchiya
Hello
Good evening
It's 2 a.m.
7 hours have passed since the start
The audience's tiredness reaches its peak
But on stage
The talk of downtown will continue soon after the break
Why do people get older
When you become an old man and an old woman
Do you get smaller?
No, that's not true
I have a big old man
What is it?
Please teach me how to greet a fish
It's like it's flying in the sky
This is good
Thank you
Tamura Masakazu
Please teach me how to greet a fish
What is it?
When we first met
What was your first impression?
I was surprised too
Why?
I thought you were a high school student
Why is that?
You were wearing a long hair and pants
I thought you were a cameraman
Goodbye
I don't think I'll be able to shake your hand until tomorrow
That's the worst
You're wearing a headlock
Let's listen to the weather tomorrow
On the phone?
On the phone
I have to press D10
Shizuoka's weather forecast
It's raining heavily in the western part of the prefecture
It's raining heavily in the central part of the prefecture
Please be careful
It's okay to sleep
We'll play here
Right?
I'm sorry
I had an unnecessary event
I'll start
That's strange
I don't want to
Hey
I came to Yoshimoto to do this
1, 2, 3, 4
That's nice
I laughed and went back to Tokyo
I have to wait for the rain to stop
The rain is getting stronger
There are times like this
I'm a little scared
Everyone
It's pouring
It's like
Totoro is coming out
I'm scared too
What is this rain?
Free-talk is a big problem
Do you know the intro of the movie?
Do you know what movie it is?
Yes
Emmanuel Fugin
Champion quiz
The next quiz is
It's not a movie
Guess the title of the song
I'll do it
Yesterday
Yes
Hamada-san
What is that?
That's amazing
Thank you
Grand champion quiz
What are you folding?
Let's see
That's amazing
Yes
What are you turning?
That's amazing
No
Gag
50 times
Please look at me warmly
I won't tell anyone what I saw today
Good morning
Gag
50 times
Good morning
Good morning in France
Bonjour
Thank you
It's a big deal
If you do it, it will rain suddenly
That's right
Everyone will be fine
It's sunny over there
What was the weather forecast?
Let's do it together
5 seconds
6 people
Good morning
Today's brother is Mr. Yukio Iketani
Mr. Downtown is good too
Let's do it
Grand champion quiz
Please look at me
Raise your arms from the front
It's a big movement
It's a hand-and-foot movement
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
I'm tired
3, 2, 1, 2, 3
I'm very tired
3, 2, 1, 2
Hand-and-foot movement
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
Thank you
Please give me a gold medal
I'm still half way through
That's good
It's 7 a.m. and 12 hours before the start
They finally pass the starting point
The tired body wakes up and the venue starts to get back on track
Everyone is eating something
I'm eating a banana
You're eating a banana?
It's a pear
A pear is delicious
If you have a pear, you can eat as much rice as you want
What newspaper?
Are you ready?
Browse 970
You don't need to know that kind of information
His left hand is looking at me
Is it a novel?
Read the article
If you're persistent, you'll get angry
That's stupid
Get up
Let me read it
Browse 970
Up to this point, we have provided reliable daily necessities
Tiger magic bottle
Asahi beer
Noelia
Nipro
Lion
And many other sponsors
From now on, we will provide sponsors
Let's decide on a dance
When?
Let's dance
Teach me
1, 2, 3, 4
Let's start with boxing
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
1, 2, 3, 4
What is this?
Madrom
1, 2, 3, 4
5, 6
What is this?
I don't need a man
Is it a woman?
Of course
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
I'll leave the big ones
Teacher, you like this, don't you?
It's not about whether you like it or not
1, 2
Let's turn
3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
Where did it end?
Here
What dance is this?
1, 2
3, 4
5, 6, 7, 8
Isn't there a song that goes well with this?
Look for it
I'll dance to it
I'll do my best
Let's learn it
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6
You're slow and fast
It's hard
That's what the teacher thinks
Teacher Izumi
I don't know that
I'm not doing it
Where did it end?
It's a difficult part
It's cool
Look at each other
Like this
Look at me when I say 1
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
From the beginning
I decided the music for the concert
I'll do it according to this
Let's go
Your birthday
1, 2, 3, 4
Stop
I'm sorry
Go home
Music start
Applause
It's not good
Why?
Didn't you hear when I said Takane no Hana yo?
When?
Takane no Hana yo
Amazing
I can't hear
Why are you sighing?
Do you understand?
I don't understand
I'll do it later
Natsukashi concert
Start
I might really fall
It's hot
It's so hot
What should I do?
This is good
It's so cool
It's spinning
It's good
If I sing in the rain
Hey
I don't like it
If I take it like this
I wonder if it's good for the futon at home
I'll do it
My honeymoon
Hello
I'm Yuma
Yuma?
My name is Yuma
I'll introduce myself
Hello, I'm Kenji
Wait
You said Yuma, so you introduced yourself like Gorohase
Are you going to be Kenji again?
There's a wedding season
Where do you want to go on your honeymoon?
There's a lot of places
I want to go to Hawaii
I want to go to a hot place
Hawaii
There's a lot of places
I want to go to Shoya
Shoya
This is hard
I'm nervous
Hanako
Yes
I got a first class hotel
I'm happy
It's a suite room
Let's go in
I'll open it
Why?
It's a first class hotel
You can't say that
It's a suite room
It's a small suite room
It's a big room
Why are you saying it like that?
Don't raise it
It's here, Hanako
That's amazing
The time has finally come
I'm sorry
Can you turn off the light?
Light?
I'll turn it off
Stop it
It's a first class hotel
It's a suite room
Why is it a candle?
I'll turn off the light
Turn it off
Stop it
Don't loosen it
Use the button
Wait for me
Yes
I'll take off my clothes
Sabah
Look at this, Hanako
It's embarrassing
What are you saying?
Hanako
Stop it
It's a first class hotel
Hanako, you are
You're not a woman
Smile
Thank you
I'll talk to Yamazaki for 30 minutes
It's too early
I'm sorry
It's a first class hotel
Thank you
I'm doing a manzai
It's not profitable
There are many profitable businesses
It's about 40 million yen
That's too much
The doctor is the coolest
The doctors are good at surgery
I don't want to see it
I'm nervous
Doctor
It's a first class hotel
Woman
Yes
It's just a woman
Woman
Kiss
Hey
Can I dance?
I'll cut it
Please
How far are you going to cut it?
I know
Look at it
I won't
I know
What kind of situation is it?
It's a traffic accident
Traffic accident?
Yes
I see
It's going to happen
What?
Look at it
It's a car
Sweat
tweezers
Kikunohana
It's dead
Thank you
Let's think about the second one
Yamazaki
Kareena Deka
I got it
Just
Just this time
I'm nervous
Kareena Deka
Please
Hello
I don't want to do it
It's not cool
There are many jobs
It's cool
The detective is cool
It's a detective drama
It's cool
Really?
It's going to be hard
Is this a murder scene?
Deka-cho
Hello
I'm Deka-cho
Nice to meet you
Where is the office?
Here
It's closed
Why?
I know
This is terrible
That's right
There is a knife inside
This is a professional trick
This is a murder
Really?
But it's a case of a lake
That's right
It's a murder
It's outside
I'm not talking about the lake
I know
This is a knife
That's right
It's heroin
It's blood
It's hot
I know
This is terrible
Yes
What?
What is this situation?
I know
Shut up
Don't say it again
Yes
I'm sorry
I'm a great veteran of this road
That's right
You're not bad
This is a miracle
Yes
I don't know what it is
A miracle
Yes
Hold on
I'm a great veteran
What are you talking about?
What?
I'm a great veteran
Hold on
I'm holding on
I'm fine
Yes
What?
Ah
This is a trick
Yes
I think this is his trick
What?
What do you mean?
It was about 5 years ago
Yes
It was a similar murder
There were several serial murders
Is that so?
But we managed to catch him
Yes
He saved his life
Don't talk nonsense
He's a bad guy
That's right
He's very similar to that
I'll tell him it's a trick
I see
Is that so?
What is this?
Ah
Isn't this a costume?
A costume?
Yes
I don't want to think about anything in this world
I'll go on my own
I got it
What?
You're the culprit
I'll kill myself
Helicopter
Yes
Let's have fun
Are you ready?
I'm glad I read the history
Why?
This is the first time I've seen them all together
I've never seen this many drug addicts
How can you do this?
I've started to feel the power of the last one
Thank you
Can you say this line?
I'm frustrated
That's normal
You can sing it
I'm frustrated
Let's draw
Ha
Na
Drawing is fun
Drawing
I'm crying
Ha
I'm frustrated
Show me
Yes
It's hot
It's so hot
It's dark here
I
I want to go home
I only have Yamazaki
Do I have to rely on him?
Will I die?
You won't die
I want to go home
Let's practice
Let's get in the mood
But
It's cold
There's a wind
It's getting dark
It's easy
You can do it in 2 and a half hours
You don't have to do it anymore
You can do it
Marina is here
Marina
You're so slow
Marina, don't take off your sailor clothes
Wait a minute
Don't take off your sailor clothes
No
You can't do it now
Be patient
You don't have to dance
I forgot
It's a little scary
But it's not boring
Before it's too late
Eat a delicious heart
Everyone has a refreshing face
Yes
Human beings are great
There is a biorhythm
There were many times
Yamatani, Yamatani
The face at the time of the valley is amazing
Everyone was there
There were customers
There were many people
The boss was this person
Boss
You were there once
In the corner
There was a rooster
I was surprised
I stopped and moved
I thought it was a story of an old lady
We danced together
What?
Do you want to see?
I want to see
You look happy
Your smile when you were doing this
It was really amazing
It's dirty
The dirtiest smile
I want you to clap
I don't like it
You are completely different
You have a blue face
You haven't done it
I want to see
Hamada, you're the first one
Stop laughing
You can go home
What are you doing?
Nimi sensei
Thank you
It was an unexpected guest
It's an unexpected dancer
Let's practice dancing
Let's start with boxing
1,2,3,4,5,6,7
Are you okay?
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8
You can go home
Thank you
You have to go higher
Higher
5,6,7
Let's start from here
Are you stupid?
I'm okay
I'm watching you
Please do it
It's tiring to teach 4 people
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8
No,no,no
Sensei, please
Smile more
Let's go
1,2,3,4
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8
Who was bad?
Everyone was bad?
That's not good
What?
Can you do it?
From Tokyo
I was free
You were free?
The drama is over
You played a bad role
The drama will be called Dancer from tomorrow
From tomorrow
If you do it, it will be extra
Let's make a team and go to business
What?
You're the only one who thinks about it
That's amazing
If you do it well, it will be amazing
If you do it well, you will get a UFO
Let's get a UFO
Stand up and I will look at you
Everyone remembers
Look, they are practicing
3,2,1
You guys are scary
You guys are good
Let's do it
Stand up
1,2,3,4
You guys are turning the wrong way
You can stop
It's amazing
It's funny that time has passed
The time has passed
It's fast
It's been an hour
One last time
Please give me everything you have
Music start
3,2,1
OK
It's amazing that there's no one who hasn't done it
It's moving
It's amazing
There are couples inside
My girlfriend is dancing
I'm like that too
Music start
It's been 24 hours
It's been 19 minutes
It's fast
It's annoying
I was like, should I stop or go home?
But it's been 19 minutes
I'm wondering if this was good
I have a lot of memories
What was the most memorable for you?
When Hideki came out and did IMCA, everyone's smile
I'll never forget it
I just realized
These people want to dance
That's why I told you to dance
Everyone's butt must hurt
Thank you
Everyone worked hard
Everyone worked hard today
It's a record
It's been a minute
Thank you everyone
Let's count down together
It's fast
20 seconds
It's so fast
Everyone worked hard
Let's count down together
8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1
We did it
We did it together
Everyone worked hard
I said it like a joke
I think anyone who can stand this can stand anything
I think anyone can stand this
I can't do it
Everyone worked hard
I said it like a joke
More than farewell, more than sadness, the longing is strong
A journey of loneliness and a single breath of back to back
At the window of the train that started to move
I just watched the scenery flowing
The sky of the cherry blossom tree that bloomed
It was so blue that it was so sad that my heart trembled
If we are separated, we will be separated
This feeling that grows even more
I can't forget the night when I opened my eyes
Wrapped in the mother and father of the day
If you trace the life of the soft days that have passed, you will live
To the sky of the cherry blossom tree that bloomed
Someday I will come back, someday I will come back
I will definitely come back
Thank you!
Don't forget to dance!