In the next episode of Gaki no Skyer, we'll be talking about the image change project, I'm Nii-san!
Well, we said it's the first episode, but we can also think of it as the second episode.
Yamazaki-kun's...
Yamazaki's, you know, the one where he gets mad at us, the one with the most views.
This time, it's Jimmy-san.
Because it's Jimmy-san, it's amazing.
It's amazing.
I can go over one roof.
Let's introduce him right away.
This is Jimmy Onishi-san.
Nice to meet you.
Well, it's written here, but I'm Nii-san.
Well, if you think about it, he's really our Nii-san.
No, we're two months apart.
Well, this time, it's the image change project.
He's back to his original self, Onishi Hideaki.
It's an image video.
I have to show you a strong Jimmy-chan.
The world is changing, isn't it?
Of course it's changing.
When you're walking down the street, there's a lot of things that people look down on you.
I was riding a bullet train, and I was hit in the head from above.
That kind of thing is gone.
Why does that happen?
By doing this project from now on, all of that will be gone.
Really?
All of it will be gone.
Let's get rid of it.
Jimmy Onishi is a cutie.
It's okay to cut it, isn't it?
That's right.
That's why it's a video, isn't it?
Yes, that's right.
Oh, it's you, Nijigori-san.
I'm the manager of the Yonyodo factory.
I'm Nijigori-san, in charge of Jimmy Onishi.
You're always so beautiful.
I often make mistakes when I'm in trouble.
What kind of work does Rie Mama do?
Well, she's...
Well, Jimmy is...
She's a cutie.
At that time, she's the only one I can stop.
Only Rie Mama.
Be careful.
You're usually doing it, aren't you?
Well, I don't know.
What the hell are you doing?
Get some juice.
Get more juice.
Stand up.
Everyone, stand up.
Good morning.
Let's go to the bathroom.
What?
It looks like a bathroom.
Let's go to the bathroom.
Don't push me.
Hey.
Yes?
I want some udon.
Udon?
Yes.
Go get it yourself.
I don't want udon.
What's wrong with you?
Hey, let's do it again.
Let's eat.
Ahhhh.
Don't do it again.
What's wrong with you?
It's your first time.
Let's do it again.
Don't laugh.
Good morning.
Excuse me.
You're early.
Yes.
What's wrong with you?
I told you.
I heard it was 6 o'clock.
I saw it on TV.
What?
I don't know.
I saw it too.
I didn't laugh.
I'm sorry.
It was cold.
There is no vacuum cleaner now.
Hey!
I took this shirt.
You're small.
As you are, don't talk too much.
What is the curtains for?
You must not speak.
Are you angry with me?
What's so funny?
Why don't you say something?
What are you doing?
You look serious.
If you hit me, I'll grab you.
What are you doing?
You're not going to hurt me, are you?
Stand up, you guys.
There's no one to be a gentleman.
It doesn't matter.
I'm fine, but you guys are going to lose.
Don't say, please.
I'm not saying anything.
I'm a senior, too.
I'm asking you to get rid of me.
Get rid of me.
What's going on?
I've been asking you for a while.
Stand up.
Everyone, stand up.
Two months is a thousand and a half years.
That's right.
I'm a junior.
I'm not going to fight you.
I'm not going to beat you.
What are you thinking?
I'm waiting.
You're too stupid.
Sorry.
Go to hell.
Hey, get some juice.
Get some juice.
No.
Go to Nishimori.
Nishimori.
You're a fool.
This is a hot spring.
You know you can't go home.
You want to go to a hot spring once in a while.
Turn off the heat once in a while.
Why are you hiding behind me?
Get out of here.
You always turn on the heat.
That's golf, isn't it?
Why are you playing golf?
It's cold.
It's good to go.
But you have to sell it.
You're a fool.
You're too stupid.
Be honest.
You always turn on the heat.
Why are you hiding behind me?
Sorry.
What's the matter with you and me?
Don't make fun of me.
Apologize to me.
Hurry up.
Sorry.
I can't stand it anymore.
What?
I've never been mad at you.
I don't understand.
I'm sorry.
From today on, the set has changed.
It's a little more beautiful.
I see.
It's good.
But it doesn't cost much.
It doesn't cost much, but the design is good.
Really?
Issei Miyake.
Don't lie to me.
I'm tired.
You!
Why didn't you appear at the opening of the game?
What are you looking at?
You guys are scary.
I don't know if the brass band will come out.
I usually come out, but I didn't come out on that day.
I don't do that in front of people.
Why are you doing this now?
I feel like we're friends.
It's the first time.
It's the first time, but when I see his face, his family structure, his blood type, it's really good.
Really?
It's really good.
I have a boyfriend.
I have only one boyfriend.
How many?
Six siblings.
It depends on the person.
You were good just now.
Six siblings?
Six siblings.
Really?
How many siblings do you have?
Six siblings.
Six siblings?
I'm glad you were born.
I see.
But you're a beautiful sister.
When my sister doesn't break, she looks at her underwear.
My sister is not very beautiful, but when she doesn't break, she looks at her underwear.
When my sister's siblings are at home,
For example, my girlfriend is with her brother, and her brother knows everything.
Everyone knows the man my sister is dating.
I've never seen my sister eating a flower.
But the husband doesn't know that at all.
I don't know you're looking like this.
My sister is looking at me in the mirror.
I'm looking at her behind the mirror.
I've never seen it before.
After that, the mirror doesn't move.
I've seen many things about my sister.
I don't want to talk to my sister's boyfriend.
I don't want to talk to my parents.
When I was in the second or third year of high school, I smoked a lot at home.
My husband came to my sister's wedding.
He gave me a tie.
It looks good on you.
I'm sorry, Mr. Ota.
Did you go to your sister's wedding?
My sister looks like you.
She looks like you.
It would be better to be on TV.
She's always saying, thank you for everything.
I knew it when I saw her.
That's all.
She's amazing.
I don't know how long she's going to say it.
When I came from the other side, I was wondering if she was a barista.
I feel sorry for my family when I see a celebrity.
I don't usually laugh at Nan-chan's sister.
I know Nan-chan, and I'm watching her, so I can laugh at her.
I can laugh at her.
How much do you have in your pocket?
How much do you have?
I think I have more than you.
Even if you say so, I'm a high school student, and I have a name.
I have money.
I have money, too.
I'm not proud of it, but I have 50,000 yen.
How much do you have?
I have 50,000 yen, too.
You have 50,000 yen, too.
Is that so?
Actually, I have 60,000 yen.
I have 50,000 yen, but I haven't received a dowry yet.
You're in the way of taking it home.
Well, that's...
You two can have it.
No, you two can have it.
I'm so angry that I can't take it.
Why do you have a dowry for a wedding?
Well, it's not decided yet.
But you have a lot of dowry.
Why don't you have a dowry?
And you have a lot of dowry.
A lot of dowry?
Everyone has a wedding like that, right?
Even amateurs give dowry to each other and ask them to go home.
You're the only one who has a phone card.
What's a phone card?
And it's a 50-degree phone card.
I don't need it.
It's winter.
Can't you see it?
No, I have a ring on my nose.
I'm not proud of you, but I have 100,000 yen in my pocket.
Are you serious?
You have a phone card and a ring on your nose with 100,000 yen.
You're so cool.
If you have a phone card, you can use a normal phone card.
You two are a stupid couple.
If you take it, you can't go home.
I don't know if it's because you're called P-chan, but if you take it, you can't go home.
You don't look like a normal guy.
I thought I'd have to hit him once.
You're a bad guy.
I don't want to see you in a suit.
I know.
I don't care about that.
I'll look at your feet and you'll see a silver high heel.
Hey!
Hamada!
Hey, Shimoda!
What's that?
He's ignoring me.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Today, I had a high heel and my body hurt.
Well, that's the result.
Well, if you look at the picture.
What should I do when I take a picture of my passport?
Just leave it as it is.
What do you mean?
That's no good.
Why?
That's going to be a disguise.
That's not going to change.
Shut up!
You know what happens when you take a picture of your passport, don't you?
When you sit down, you go like this.
When you're taking a picture, you go like this.
You don't have time for that when you take a picture of your passport.
That's why I'm going to change my passport next month.
I can't wear a high heel when that happens, can I?
You can't, can you?
If that's the case, I'll wear a high heel.
But you don't have to take a picture of your passport.
People who wear high heels are in some way worried.
That's true, but...
They wear high heels to hide it.
That's right.
And then, for example, if you have a nose injury,
and you have an accident, and you don't like it,
and you're wearing nose glasses, that's not good.
That's not good.
As a human being, as a human being,
a man who shouldn't be on the field should wear nose glasses.
Should he go out?
Even among those who wear high heels,
some women think they don't know,
and some women hide it.
No.
No?
How can you say that?
You!
You're worse than my head!
Idiot!
Is that true?
It's true.
My wife knows it's hard.
But she doesn't take it off in front of her.
Are there any women in Japan who don't realize it?
No, there aren't.
Of course there aren't.
I wonder if there are.
There aren't.
No matter how you think about it, you can't tell.
I shot a commercial.
I had to make my child ride a stroller.
Children can easily hold their heads like this.
I didn't do that, but if it was me,
if my hand didn't come this close,
I would have done this.
But children...
Children can't do anything.
They don't have a stroller.
It's dangerous.
You have to hold it somewhere.
Hold it like this.
It's not stable, so hold it like this.
That person did the same thing.
She passed away, but she did this.
Oh, really?
She told me to knock before entering the teacher's room.
She told you to knock before entering the teacher's room?
That's terrible!
The teacher was in the room at that time.
I wonder if she was exposed.
I wonder if she was in the room at that time.
Yes.
The teacher had a mannequin on her neck, right?
Oh, Zurakamon-sensei?
She rode on it and wrote,
〇〇.
Konkon!
Yes.
It's a beret of this.
The teacher...
There were a few of them, right?
When the teacher was going somewhere,
the assistant was cleaning the room.
The teacher was going somewhere, but she was sitting on the desk.
Teacher?
Don't ask!
Answer me!
The assistant was sitting like this.
You'll get in trouble.
There are a lot of people in the entertainment world.
Also,
there are people who quit recently, right?
Oh, really?
Is that possible?
But it wasn't that big a shift from before.
It was a partial shift.
〇〇.
When the makeup artist was fixing her makeup,
she said,
〇〇.
No, really.
Who else is there?
There are a lot of people.
〇〇.