This is the end of this year's show.
Today is the last day of this year's show.
I see.
You've been doing this for a year in a different hall every week, right?
Yes, I have.
You can't even use the studio.
That's not what I meant.
I don't want to brag about myself, but this show is doing pretty well, right?
Yes, it is.
The ratings are pretty good, right?
But there's one more thing.
What is it?
You should have brought the director's award.
Of course I did.
You said you were going to announce the opening tonight.
I did.
But you didn't even appear on the screen.
I don't care.
I want to be on the screen.
What are you talking about?
I don't want to be on the screen.
I'm lucky to have you here today.
Let's play a penalty game.
The loser of this game will go to the director's office.
I don't want to go to the director's office.
I don't want to be on the screen.
I'm serious.
I didn't know you'd come back.
I was told to go to the director's office.
In Osaka.
There was a event for Japan's broadcast.
You were there at the Osaka Festival Hall.
We went to Osaka.
You're doing a lot of things there.
Please watch.
Let's watch it.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Penalty game! Penalty game!
Let's start!
Penalty game!
I need to go to the bathroom.