From now on, I, Yamazaki Hosei, will start a small-scale trial.
Prosecutors and lawyers, please enter the court.
Now, the defendant, Yamazaki Hosei, please enter the court.
I'm so happy.
What's with that attitude?
Prosecutors, please read out your testimony.
I, Yamazaki Hosei, have been a regular talent since the 2nd episode of this show.
I've been a bad influence on the ratings, but I've contributed to the show and created a lot of laughs.
I've found out that I'm causing a lot of trouble to the people because I'm a small-scale person.
I, Yamazaki Hosei, will start a small-scale trial.
Prosecutor Hamada, please read out your testimony.
Last week, we had a meeting regarding this trial.
I, Yamazaki Hosei, have been a regular talent since the 2nd episode of this show.
I've been a bad influence on the ratings, but I've contributed to the show and created a lot of laughs.
What's with that attitude?
I've found out that I'm causing a lot of trouble to the people because I'm a small-scale talent since the 2nd episode of this show.
I, Yamazaki Hosei, have been a regular talent since the 2nd episode of this show.
What should we do next week?
Matsumoto-san, we've been doing a lot of studio stuff lately. Why don't we do something with Yamazaki-san next week?
Oh, that's a good idea.
But...
I'm sorry. Actually, I have a sore rib, so I can't do anything with my body.
What? Really? You didn't do anything until now.
It hurt a lot, but I've been holding it in for a long time. So, next week...
Is that so? Then, it can't be helped.
I'm sorry. It was a careless mistake of mine.
Yamazaki-san, who doesn't like physical things, does a lot of planning with all kinds of lies.
Moreover, all of these lies are spread during the opening project.
This is a scene in a fight between Yamazaki Kokoriko and a young comedian.
Yamazaki tries to show his veteranism in a fight with a young comedian, but...
It hurts! It hurts!
Shinko! Shinko! Shinko!
Shinko! Shinko!
Shinko!
Okay, let's do it again.
Let's do it like this.
What?
What did you do?
It's a prank.
It's my fault.
Really?
You're lying!
Where?
I don't remember.
What is it?
I'm sorry.
You're lying!
Okay, let's do it like this.
You're making a lot of small lies.
I can't think of anything.
Everyone will be relieved because you're lying.
But at that scene, you'll think,
What? I can't do it?
You'll think,
It's nothing.
It's a really small lie.
That's right.
At that time, it wasn't a lie.
I really thought it was broken.
You should have told me.
It was really painful.
It's not a big deal if it's broken.
I've never broken it, so I don't know.
Don't tell me!
I don't know how it's broken.
Tell me maybe.
Tell me maybe it's broken.
Well,
About that,
To be honest, a young man from Osaka asked me.
I heard that he was really nervous.
He was nervous.
From my experience,
If a young man gets nervous in that way,
It's going to be a really scary thing.
If you work too hard,
It's possible that a middle-aged man like me will be killed.
I know that.
I have a strong sense of it.
If I don't let it go,
I will be crushed.
I made a decision like that.
That's why I told him that it was a lie.
I admitted it.
Other than that,
If there is anyone who has a lot of small lies.
I don't think I'm going to say this.
When we were doing mahjong together,
For example, if Mr. Matsumoto calls you,
You want to play mahjong, right?
I'm in Nagoya right now.
I'm listening to that side by side.
Wait a minute!
Don't talk to me!
It's a fact.
It's true.
Don't talk to me!
Wait a minute.
Say it twice.
Don't talk to me!
Wait a minute.
Hikobu, what was that?
That's not good.
Miyasako, that's not good.
Tell me the meaning of that.
What do you mean that's not good?
Don't say something that will drag the program down.
But it's not like this.
Don't talk to me!
By the way, I've been told a couple of times in Nagoya.
That's not good.
Don't talk to me!
This guy is annoying.
That's terrible.
Even when I was playing golf, my fingers were broken.
I couldn't play properly.
There's no way someone with broken fingers can play like that.
How about you?
No, it's broken.
It's broken.
It's a finger.
But it's a really amazing finger.
Well, that was last September.
Hamada-san, look at this.
What?
This.
What's that?
It's a little swollen, right?
I don't know.
What are you talking about?
Is there anything else?
I've been told a couple of times in Omiya.
I see.
For example, when I was about to go out to eat,
Tanaka-san said,
I found a really good ramen restaurant.
Really?
I said, please let me go to that restaurant.
And I introduced that restaurant to Yamazaki-san.
That's not cool.
Is there such a thing?
No.
I didn't know the meaning of the word trauma.
I told him about it.
He told me about it.
He said it was a trauma.
And he answered what I said in some kind of interview.
Who is this guy?
What are you talking about?
The answer is what I said when I went to eat.
Really?
Yamazaki-san.
This story began a year ago.
The fourth episode of the Gakinosukai Alliance.
The Gakinosukai Tournament.
Every year, the Gakinosukai Tournament is held in Kawaguchiko.
Itoi Shigesato, Okuda Tamiyo, Eguchi Yosuke.
Yamazaki can work with big names.
For Yamazaki, it was his favorite project that made him realize that he was a member of the Gakinosukai Alliance.
The event was held after the fishing competition last year.
It was late, but the location was completed.
Good job.
Yamazaki came to Aisha to go back to Tokyo.
I had a lot of fun today.
Tamiyo and Eguchi-chan had a lot of fun.
Well, I had the most fun.
Yamazaki was in a good mood.
When he entered the highway, he stepped on the accelerator.
Let's go, my Benz.
At that time...
Ah!
I was caught.
I was caught by the police.
What should I do?
Yamazaki was depressed.
Later, he was called to the police and was beaten up.
I'm sorry.
And on the day of the fishing competition this year, Yamazaki went to Kawaguchiko with Matsumoto.
Good morning.
Sorry, Yamazaki.
What are you talking about?
It's okay.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm going to fish.
It was the first fishing competition in a year.
Yamazaki's tension was high from the beginning.
The car was going well.
Yamazaki went to the president.
I'm waiting for you.
I'm not going to lose.
You're in a good mood.
Yamazaki flew to the president.
I remember.
What's wrong, Yamazaki?
What are you doing?
Yamazaki suddenly hid his face while driving.
Yamazaki is driving at a speed below the speed limit of 70 kilometers per hour.
Actually, I was taken a picture by an office last year.
So I have to do this.
You can't be taken a picture even if you don't speed up.
I'll be taken a picture.
Get out of my way.
I can't move.
After that, Yamazaki kept hiding his face until he left Kawaguchiko.
I have a witness.
Please.
It's almost the same.
Actually, Yamazaki drove about 60 kilometers.
To be more precise, Yamazaki was riding a tanaka.
Yamazaki was fine.
The office said it would be fine if the speed limit was 140 kilometers per hour.
But Yamazaki didn't move at all.
That means Yamazaki didn't believe what I said.
That means Yamazaki was angry with Yamazaki.
I thought Yamazaki would be angry with Yamazaki.
But Yamazaki was taken a picture by the office again.
Yamazaki was taken a picture by the office again.
Do you have any comments?
First of all, when I was arrested for the first time, I was on the same boat with Matsumoto.
Actually, that's right.
When you were killed, you were on the same boat with Matsumoto.
At that time, I was on the same boat with Matsumoto.
Matsumoto was on the same boat with Matsumoto.
To be honest, I want Matsumoto to be on the same boat with Matsumoto.
I went with Matsumoto to send Matsumoto.
Why did you go with Hiroko?
I've done a lot of other things.
When I was a student, I played a game of punishment.
I hated it very much.
But I finally became a student.
I was surprised at the next action.
I bought a wig somewhere in the neighborhood.
I took it to a hair salon and asked them to cut my hair.
Why do you care so much about me?
Is that so?
Yes.
This is Yamazaki vs. Moriman.
This is the story of the first time they fought.
This is the first time Yamazaki vs. Moriman.
This is the story of the first time Yamazaki vs. Moriman.
I was defeated.
Good morning.
Good morning, Yamazaki.
Is Moriman in the game?
Yes, he is.
There's something I'm worried about.
What is it?
Even if Moriman says he's strong, he's a woman.
I'm sure I'll win.
I don't think I'll lose no matter what I think.
Is that so?
I'll tell Moriman.
Yamazaki went to Moriman's secret room to find out where he was confident.
Hi.
Good morning.
Moriman and Yamazaki have almost never met before.
He's a little nervous about Moriman's appearance.
I have a plan for today.
But if you don't come seriously, I'll be in trouble.
Okay.
It's not fun if I think I'll win, is it?
Are you sure you're okay?
If you hold back, I won't forgive you.
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
Then I'll leave it to you.
Yes, thank you.
Yamazaki thought he would win, so he had a big show.
But the real game was...
Yamazaki's secret room
Throw it, throw it.
I saw it, I saw it, I saw it.
Come on, come on.
Yamazaki's secret room
I'd like to hear from the witness about this incident.
Is that okay?
Yes, sir.
Then witness, please.
Help me.
Hey, you.
Hey, you in the courtroom.
You in the courtroom.
Witness, witness.
I said that twice.
Witness, is that the same VTR?
Yes, that's the same.
After the first attack, he came back to the dressing room.
After that, he said, are you going to go too far?
He said, come on.
He said, are you going to go too far?
What?
Well, I did try too hard.
No, no, no, no.
It's okay if you play the game.
It's okay if you win.
Well, how should I put it?
Do you have more fun?
What is this?
There are times when words and this don't match.
But, of course, I will lose in the ring.
I admit that.
I want you to play on my field.
Where?
In the water.
What?
So, why is your field in the water?
I have a very strong lung capacity.
Ever since I was in elementary school, I've been playing on the brass band.
It's okay.
I'll accept that challenge.
Are you sure?
Wow.
Hey, hey, seriously.
This is your field.
I want to say something.
Today, too.
Today, I came to the school with my seniors.
I came in with a bad feeling about smoking.
I had a surgery 10 days ago.
So, even if there is a battle, don't come here too much.
Be careful.
Let me say something about this.
I'm doing a TV show.
I put Mr. Yamaguchi in there.
Then, I took a break.
What do you mean you took a break?
I had a surgery and my penis hurts.
I want to take a break.
Hey, you're funny.
In the past, Miyasako had to make a child laugh in a TV show.
What should I do?
It's hard to make a child laugh.
Miyasako was very worried.
But in the actual show...
Pussy, pussy.
She made a child laugh and won a big prize.
The next day, the show was on air.
Miyasako's joke was very popular.
After a few days, Miyasako was suddenly called by Yamasaki.
What is it, brother?
The joke you did on that show is funny.
Really? I'm glad.
Really, really.
That pussy, pussy.
Thank you very much.
By the way...
Give me that joke.
Give me that joke on TV.
I don't want to hear it.
Miyasako was confused by Yamasaki's joke.
But Yamasaki didn't take a step back.
Then Miyasako saw something unbelievable.
What is this?
Pussy, pussy.
Yamasaki had already done Miyasako's joke on his regular show.
Miyasako was shocked.
Yamasaki's intention was to be forgiven before the joke was revealed.
After that, Miyasako hid this joke.
Pussy, pussy.
I'd like to hear the witness's testimony.
Please explain.
He didn't put any color on the video.
It was the same as it was.
He said, give me a joke.
I don't want to hear it.
He turned on the video and went to the bathroom.
He was wondering what video he was filming.
He was doing it with his butt.
This is scary.
This is terrible.
You talk.
I'm talking.
I'm not talking.
I'm talking all the time.
I'm not talking all the time.