Good evening!
Today we started with Dance Dance Dance!
Yes!
Every week we have a lot of people participating.
And what kind of dance will they show us?
Yes, so...
First, let's introduce the judges!
Yes!
First, here!
Next, Keisuke Sho!
Wonderful!
What's wonderful?
Keisuke Sho, it's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Do you know us?
Yes!
I'm a fan.
Thank you very much.
What do you think of our dance?
It's interesting.
Thank you very much.
You don't look like a real person at all.
Next, we have Kishi Chieko-sensei!
Yes, hello!
I want you to look at us with professional eyes.
Yes, I feel like I'm already in a dance.
You're already dancing like a chicken.
Thank you very much.
Lastly, we have JJ Jefferson-san!
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Your Japanese is bad.
It's bad.
Are you married?
Yes.
With a Japanese woman?
How is your relationship with a Japanese woman?
It's amazing.
Thank you very much.
That was long.
Please introduce yourself.
What's your name?
Fumio Fukaba.
How old are you?
I'm 75 years old.
75 years old.
Do you go to the disco often?
I go there 3 times a week.
That's amazing.
Really?
Do you really go there 3 times a week?
Yes, yes.
What's the name of the bar you go to?
Circus.
Circus?
You're so sexy!
Why are you hitting me?
Let's ask him.
First, Mr. Sugi.
Mr. Heisuke.
How was your dance?
If I didn't have bad legs, it would have been better.
Really?
Yes.
I can do anything.
You can do anything?
Yes.
I can't do it if I don't have bad legs.
Mr. Shio, you go there 3 times a week.
If it's me, I go there once a week.
You hate losing.
I don't like losing.
That's right.
Next person, please.
Entry number 2, Chiki Chiki Hawaiian Sisters.
Chiki Chiki Hawaiian Sisters
Thank you very much.
It was a wonderful performance.
Did you learn the dance right away?
I learned it in 3 months.
You learned it in 3 months?
Some people die before they learn the dance.
Was there anyone like that in the past?
No, not until now.
There was someone like that.
Not until now?
Let's ask the judges.
Mr. Heisuke.
When you shake your hands, you stop in the middle, right?
Yes, yes.
I think it's better not to stop.
If you go with that, your hips will be like this.
What are you talking about?
Are you crazy?
You!
As expected, it's an interesting reaction.
I see.
Is there a age limit?
How old do you have to be before you can enter?
Not at all.
Not at all?
If you look at it, you're about 1 or 2 months older than your master.
You're doing it, right?
I'm doing it, right?
I'm glad.
I'm looking forward to what Mr. Jefferson will say.
How was it, Mr. Jefferson?
Very, very wonderful.
You know the Kura dance, right?
In Hawaii.
It really feels like Hawaii.
He's such a foreigner.
I got it.
The last person.
Let's go!
Entry number 3.
Fujiyama Geisha dancers.
Come on, let's dance.
It's okay, it's okay.
Grandma, too.
How old are you?
I'm 65 years old.
If you look closely, you really look like you have Japanese characters on your face.
And the mother behind you.
Yes.
I'm already 1 year old, and I'm 70 years old.
Mom, do you eat gold powder?
Yes!
For today.
I went to the dentist for today, but I didn't make it in time, so I was going to hide my age.
You talk too much about unnecessary things.
Shion!
Yes.
How is it?
Hey!
Hey, what are you doing?
Why did you stop me when I hit you?
But really.
You're having fun, aren't you?
I'm having fun, aren't I?
Japan has become rich.
What are you talking about?
Ms. Kishi, how is it?
Yes.
But you're pretty good at this kind of thing, aren't you?
Yes, yes.
The record I'm playing right now is a record I played when I was 16.
Oh, really?
Fujiyama Geisha came out, but it was flat, wasn't it?
When I was dancing, I couldn't see my face, and the umbrella was reflected very well.
I see.
The one I like the most is...
Good, good.
I like it.
I like that one.
If you like it, please take one home.
Good, good.
The best...
Oh, the best...
Right?
It's going to be an interesting key holder, isn't it?
You're mistaken.
Now, let's announce the winner from the ace final.
Please.
It was Osomatsu.
No, I didn't say that.
I didn't say anything.
I said it was Osomatsu.
Well, I...
Yes.
After all, I'm good at hula dancing.
Hula dancing?
It's hula dancing, isn't it?
Yes.
This week's champion is number two, hula dancer.
He won.
But I have a championship tournament.
But the championship tournament is five years from now.
I wonder if everyone will be there.
I'm really busy.
Busy.
It's a lot of work.
Today, well...
I don't know what to say during this broadcast.
The lightning.
That's right, today.
There was a lot of lightning.
It was like this.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
That's probably because the sky is angry.
Why is that?
That's because humans do things they don't need to do.
What do you mean by things you don't need to do?
Like trying to fly into space with a rocket.
What do you mean by things like that?
What is it?
TBS is making a lot of money.
Well, that's fine.
Next year, well...
I heard a little bit about my fortune.
Who?
Well, on the show.
On the show?
The people who came.
I saw their fortune.
Yes, yes, yes.
I don't have much luck next year.
Do you trust them?
No, I don't trust them very much.
I don't think next year will be good.
They say it won't be good.
What?
It won't be a big deal.
What are you talking about?
That's why I don't think I'll be in the entertainment industry next year.
Already?
No, no, really.
Really?
Yes, really.
Do you believe in fortune-telling?
No, not really.
For example, what do you mean by fortune-telling?
Well, like carrying a coin or something.
Well, not really.
Well, the fortune-telling that used to be described as a normal punch is really annoying.
I don't know why.
I was so angry that I was about to blow up.
Last week, you were like...
You...
Yes?
You should have put it together first.
Why are you trying to put it together after talking?
That's why last week you were like...
You know I'm tired, right?
You're always like that.
You're laughing because you're always laughing when you're angry.
I'm a little...
I'm a little old-fashioned.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter usually.
I was reading the normal punch on the Shinkansen.
Last week, did you have a secret?
Yes.
This week is bad.
Say it last week.
I'm telling you to say it when it's dangerous.
Everyone goes to the Shinkansen for the first time.
And when the exam season starts, they go to get an amulet.
They go.
You can't trust them as much as an amulet.
The one who has it is a fool.
There's someone hanging it on the car.
There are quite a few.
That's a fool.
Have you ever had one?
Never.
Really?
What's that?
Even if you don't buy it yourself, your fans sometimes give you an amulet.
Can you trust that?
If you throw that amulet on the highway and go to pick it up, you'll get pulled over.
No one does that.
Can you avoid the car?
No one goes to pick it up at high speed.
What would you do if you were in that situation?
I wouldn't go to pick it up.
There's no point in getting pulled over.
That's right.
Right?
That's strange.
I'm not saying that I trust them.
If you throw that amulet on the exam hall, you'll get dropped.
I'm being told to go out because I'm going to throw it.
I'm not saying that because I don't have one.
I'm just saying that because I'm going to throw it.
But normally, if you throw it, you'll pass the exam.
What kind of amulet is that?
Nothing.
If you throw that amulet on the exam hall, you won't pass the exam.
I'm just saying that because I trust them.
What kind of example is that?
Then it's your amulet.
If you throw that amulet on the exam hall, you won't pass the exam.
That's strange.
Then where did you throw it?
It's just an example.
You won't pass the exam.
If you throw it on the exam hall, you won't pass the exam.
But if you're throwing it on the exam hall, you won't pass the exam.
Just as he agreed.
That's not true.
That's strange!
You're the one who's strange!
I'm not strange at all!
I don't understand what you're saying!
You're not even born yet!
I said it so Aoi would understand!
It's not like I'm smart, but...
People will think my head is in a crash!
No, no! You're in a crash!
A traffic safety warning!
There's that thing hanging from the front window!
For example, there's a bigger traffic safety warning!
There's a longer string hanging from the front window!
You'll hit it someday, right?
Huh?
Ah!
If the traffic safety warning is hanging from the front window, you'll hit it someday, right?
Oh, that's hanging from the front window?
Can I take a look at it?
Yes, yes, yes!
At that point, that example is impossible!
Why is it impossible?
You'll hit it because it's hanging from the front window?
Isn't that annoying? You should have made it shorter!
If it's too long, you'll hit it, right?
You'll hit it, right?
No, no, no!
I don't understand that!
Then make it even more understandable!
If you make sunglasses out of the traffic safety warning and walk down the street...
At that point, it's over!
It's over, it's over!
Why do you have to make that thing into glasses?
Even so, if you can't pull it off, I'll trust you!
The warning!
You understand what I'm saying, right?
You're shaking your neck, right?
You understand, right?
These people are strange...
Well, that's about it for today.
Oh, that was quick!
What is it?
Do you want to go to the post office?
It was quick?
It wasn't quick at all! I was talking a lot!
It's been 20 minutes since you left, right?
You can do 100 rounds!
It's good!
I might be in the White Knight 2.
Oh, really?
With that technique?
Do your best!
Yes!
Please bring out the postcards!
You can stay there and look at me!
I'm not a third party!
I thought it was going to be this interesting!
If you want to see the postcards, you can use this ring and the one she's wearing right now.
This blue zone and this ring.
This is similar to my CX, but this is a special edition.
I did it the other day, so I'll show it to you.
I did it the other day...
You should have shown it to me earlier!
I don't care!
Why don't you show it to me?
If you show it to me, that's the end of it, right?
She was born in 1945.
How old is she?
She's 20.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I don't have one.
You don't have one?
You should put on more makeup.
Thank you very much.
I heard from a friend that you used to do Chichikurimanbo.
What is it like?
I don't know Chichikurimanbo.
You do!
Do you know Chichikurimanbo?
I do.
You do?
I don't know.
You guys don't know Chichikurimanbo?
Chichikurimanbo? Chichikurimanbo?
Chichikurimanbo!
Thank you very much.
That's dirty!
Why are you doing that?
I don't know Chichikurimanbo.
What are you doing?
Do it!
Don't make me cry!
You do it properly!
I can't do it. It's embarrassing.
I'm doing it.
I don't think I'll be able to do comedy from next year.
After that, you were dancing.
Do it properly!
I can't do it if there are so many people.
Why?
It's embarrassing.
I've been told to do it.
I can't do it if I'm applauded like this.
Really?
Yes.
I can't do it.
You know what I mean, right?
I know.
I can't do it if people expect me to do it.
We've known each other for a long time.
When I do it, when I don't do it.
I know.
When I don't do it.
I can't do it.
You're still doing it?
It's embarrassing.
Why am I doing this?
Last one.
Rumi Yoshida from Ibaraki.
There's an Olympics in the last corner of the show.
I watch it every week.
I always think about it.
Matsumoto is motivated.
Hama is not motivated at all.
He looks like he doesn't want to do it.
Hama, do you hate that corner?
Why are you crying?
I'm not motivated.
I'm really doing it.
I'm doing my best.
Don't lie to me.
Don't pull out your hand.
You're the one who's doing it.
I've never pulled out my hand.
What are you talking about?
What?
You haven't pulled out your hand?
I haven't.
You've pulled out everything.
I'm doing my job.
I didn't hear you.
What?
What's wrong?
Have I ever pulled out my hand?
You've pulled out your hand.
For example, this kid.
Have I ever pulled out my hand?
I've known it for a long time.
You've pulled out your hand.
How many percent do you think it is today?
I've known it for a long time.
Today...
I'm really your master.
I'm not.
I'm not telling you.
I'm telling you.
You don't even have a breathing disease.
The doctor told me to stop.
I'm telling you the truth.
There's a doctor in Tokyo.
What's the doctor's name?
What?
It's Dr. Kuwahara.
There's a doctor in Tokyo.
The doctor told me to stop when I go to school.
Osaka!
I was working with Aja Kong today.
I was training Aja Kong with a female professional.
You were just laughing in the ring.
I was trying to catch Aja Kong, but you were laughing.
That's why I'm pulling out my hand.
You're pulling out your hand, but you're still walking.
Why don't you walk a little more?
That's what it is.
I'll stab you.
No one watches the 7 o'clock program on New Year's Day.
Hey!
Then you're not in the program.
Of course!
By the way, Masahoto is finally going to the bus game next week.
I'll show it to you.
I remember that.
I'm sure the viewers are looking forward to it.
I'm playing the punishment game next week.
Please watch it.
What are you doing?
And...
Special!
Saturday, December 29th.
From 2 to 3 o'clock.
We're going to have a special program.
That's it for this week.
We're going to play the punishment game next week.
Please look forward to it.
Good-bye.
It's fun.
What are you doing?
Okay.
Thank you for your hard work.
What are you doing?
Hey!
Otomo!
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.