You! You do Gyros, G cabur, hee hee!
What did you do?
Well, our time is ап seasoning a second pair-
You know me?
My waist hurts.
A lot.
Okay.
You did win,
but your usual printing didn't work.
It's because were overconfidently confident.
Earlier, everyone was trying to jump with 130cm, right?
You can't jump with such a thing.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Well, I'll try it.
I'll jump with 230cm if I can do it twice.
I'll jump over here and jump right away.
Like this.
I'll do it like this.
Well, the rule is simple.
You have three chances.
Is three chances okay?
Yes, it's okay.
How many centimeters should I start with?
At first, about 120cm.
120cm?
I can't believe it.
I can't lose twice with a belly roll.
It's dangerous.
I can't lose twice.
I can't wait until I fall over here.
You should jump over yourself.
This is a punishment game if you lose.
That's right.
Well, I won't say it here this time.
Well, we're both hiding it.
That's right.
I'll announce it at the end.
Okay.
That's what it is.
Let's get started.
Matsumoto vs. Hamada.
The 10th match.
Run and jump.
How will the game go?
First of all, Hamada.
The first jump.
120cm.
In the midst of tension.
This is easy and clear.
I can still afford it.
Next, Hitasu Matsumoto.
I don't like the atmosphere.
Hamada clears in front of me.
I feel the pressure.
120cm.
A great belly roll.
This is also easy and clear.
There's a lot of wild animals over there.
130cm.
I wonder if I can jump like this.
Hamada.
130cm.
Oops.
It was cut.
So far, the game is full of tension.
I feel the pressure that I can't lose.
Let's measure the timing again.
It fell like this.
130cm jump.
Hamada hits the butt.
It's a little cold.
No.
Matsumoto.
I want to clear this in one go.
It's a great clear.
Matsumoto with a belly roll.
I can still afford it.
In the midst of tension.
This is the second try.
Will Kando's throw be decided?
It's barely clear.
The bar will be raised to 135cm.
How was that?
Was it easy?
Was it good?
It hurts.
Will he be able to show a jump that exceeds his potential?
135cm.
Hamada's first try.
The timing is not right.
Matsumoto is a tough guy.
He is nervous.
The second try.
It fell.
Is this the limit?
It's a heavy movement.
It hurts.
It's the limit.
It's quite high.
Matsumoto is ahead of the game.
135cm.
It's the first try.
It's a great clear.
Matsumoto was once called a high-flying kid.
He still has a long way to go.
135cm.
This is Hamada's second try.
Hamada is in the center.
What will he do?
This is all he can do.
It's a great clear.
The bar goes up to 140cm.
Will he be able to beat Matsumoto?
It's a fail.
Matsumoto is losing his composure.
He wants to clear this in one try.
Nice jump.
Have you seen Matsumoto's serious expression?
It's a great jump.
This is Hamada's second try.
Will he be able to catch the timing of the new jump?
It's a fail.
It's a close call.
This time, it's the same as before.
It's a great clear.
Matsumoto prays not to fly.
It looks like he has nothing left to do.
This is Hamada's last try.
It's a great clear.
It's a jump of fate.
It's a close call.
It's a fail.
It's a great clear.
It was a close call.
He was flying.
I don't know.
I lost.
Matsumoto's way of flying is great.
His eyes are white.
The third try was his head.
I had to put my head in.
I hit the head with a bang.
That's all.
It was a competition of running and jumping.
Matsumoto's way of flying is great.
Why did you slow down?
I wanted you to do this.
Matsumoto's way of flying is great.
That's all.
I lost.
What was that?
Did you want to see the stick?
Why did you slow down?
I was looking at the stick until the end.
Did you want to see it?
Are you looking at the stick?
I lost.
You won't say it here, will you?
I won't say it here.
It's in the back of this picture.
I see.
You can watch this video.
Did you see it today?
What?
The wide shot.
Shinkase Taishu.
Did you see the photo?
It says Shinkase Taishu.
If you look at the picture now,
it looks like a genius.
Shinkase Taishu has two lines on the side.
There are two cameras.
What's going to happen?
I don't know.
It's that.
Everyone is here, right?
Speak clearly.
What the hell is that?
Everyone is here, right?
Speak after I tell you.
What the hell is that?
This kid.
This kid and that kid.
Who are they?
Who is the other one?
Everyone is here, right?
What?
There are a lot of customers.
We can't give them any money.
Everyone is here, right?
Everyone's laughter is unified.
That's right.
I don't think that's the case.
That's why everyone's laughter is different.
Sometimes I can't stand it because it's so funny.
That's right.
I was on a plane the other day.
I was sitting by the window.
When I got off the plane,
I landed on the ground.
I've never seen anyone like this.
When I landed on the ground,
I had to stop.
What the hell is this?
It's funny.
No one thinks it's funny.
I'm the only one who thinks it's funny.
That's right.
Why?
I can't imagine it.
I'm flying.
I can't stop.
It's funny.
That's funny.
That's right.
Everyone thinks it's funny.
Let's go home.
That's cool.
There's nothing to talk about.
Why?
Why don't you come out here and talk?
It's my job.
Today,
I'm going to talk about something interesting
one by one, one by one.
Are you a newbie?
It would be nice if we could stand here and talk.
It's true.
I'm tired of talking.
I heard on the news that Japanese words are getting messed up.
Young people are saying that words are getting dirtier and dirtier.
I see.
I'm pissed off.
I don't care.
It's getting dirtier and dirtier.
I'm particular about it.
For example,
there's a saying that there are only two times.
I have to protect it.
Why don't you protect it?
What are you angry about?
There are only two times.
Why don't you protect it?
I don't care.
You think so.
It's funny.
I don't know where the time is, but the old people around there are saying,
If you do that, the number of times will increase.
The number of times will increase.
It's too cute.
There are only two times.
What are you going to do?
I don't care.
There are only two times.
It stinks.
Why?
Why does it stink?
There are only two times.
I don't care.
I don't know.
Damn it!
What is this?
I said I'll go.
Damn it!
If you can't protect it, you can protect it, but don't you protect it too much?
You make a system.
I don't care.
I can't bite it.
It's a shame.
It's a beautiful place.
It's like a panda, isn't it?
It's a great system.
It's terrible.
It's a great one-room.
It's a concrete house.
If you look at the park, it's a dirty old man sleeping on a bench.
It's rare to see an old man sitting on a bench.
You can't see it from there.
It's a stupid old man sitting on a bench.
You're all black around your eyes.
It's not something I was born with.
When I was born, I was black around my eyes.
Old man, later, later.
Little by little, little by little, I was alive.
Isn't that amazing?
It's not amazing.
The panda is cute, but it's not cute.
The old man is cuter.
It's not cute.
The old man is cute, isn't he?
The old man is like this with a cardboard box.
That's cute, isn't it?
It's cuter than a panda.
If you make a noise, it's cute.
In fact, I have a friend who has a very bad armpit smell.
Wow!
Wow! That's a wow!
He doesn't seem to have noticed that.
I can't help but want to ask him about it.
I can't help but think about his feelings.
Are you close to your acquaintance, Mr. Armpit?
No, I'm not.
Oh, I see.
If I had to say...
What are you talking about?
Don't make a big deal out of it!
This is an important post sent by a fan.
Why are you crying?
This is often the case that the person himself doesn't know.
That's right.
I don't know.
There are many people who don't know.
I'm sure there are about 10 people in the audience.
I understand this.
Let's just say it.
What?
If there's someone with an armpit around you,
there's something you can't say, right?
It's an armpit.
This is...
Let's just say it.
Tomorrow at 10 p.m.
You should have told me sooner.
I don't have an armpit.
I don't know.
You should have told me sooner.
At 6 p.m.
Tomorrow...
This is a Sunday report.
Monday evening at 6 p.m.
If there's someone with an armpit around you,
at exactly 6 p.m.
There's an armpit.
And you clap your hands.
You clap your hands.
If there's someone with an armpit around you,
at exactly 6 p.m.
Your armpit will be revealed.
If there's a woman with an armpit around you,
it'll be hard.
You can't do that to a woman with an armpit.
This is...
What?
You can't do that.
You have an armpit.
Let's just say it.
At 6 p.m.
You decided that.
Let's just say it.
At 6 p.m.
What?
This is interesting.
Don't put your upper lip and lower lip together when you say Hokkaido.
Hokkaido.
Even if you say it normally,
your upper lip and lower lip won't stick together.
What?
Taka-san, Taka-san.
I don't want to sit next to you.
What's wrong with you?
Taka-san seems to be having a hard time.
What are you talking about?
You and me?
Are you practicing?
No, I'm not.
How did you do that jump?
I'm scared, but it was pathetic.
What are you talking about?
That's why.
What's wrong with you?
I'm not saying I won't do it.
Have you been jumping since then?
No, I haven't.
You can't do it either.
I can't do it either.
Ebiyan.
Ebiyan, come here.
What?
Come here?
Ebiyan, come here.
Come to the site.
Come here.
Ebiyan, come here.
You can't do that.
I can't do it.
Come here.
Don't run away from me.