A great plan!
Hello!
Good evening!
Welcome!
Today, my staff and my boyfriend are not here.
We're looking for them.
Are you serious?
Yes, I'm serious.
We have 5 of them here today, so if you have the same feeling as our staff, you can go out with them.
I wonder if we'll get along.
First, let's have the ladies come on stage.
Ladies, please come on stage!
What's your name?
Yoshiko Nakahama.
How old are you?
I'm 21 years old.
I'm Yuki Takahashi.
How old are you?
I'm 21 years old.
I'm 5 months old.
You're 5 months old.
You don't look like you're in trouble.
Did you get dumped when you broke up?
What?
Did you get dumped?
Yes.
Oh...
You're 5 months old!
I'm Miyoko Ooura.
I'm 23 years old.
I'm Akiko Yamaguchi.
I'm Reiko Yamamoto.
I'm 22 years old.
I haven't been here for 22 years.
Well then, let's go!
It's finally time for the ten men to come on stage!
This is so much fun!
I can't take it anymore!
Number 1, this is Nitta Atsuo.
Your father is an atelier, right?
That's right.
A director?
Are you a director?
Sakamoto-chan, you're D, aren't you?
You're lying!
I've always been an AD.
And then...
Irie-san.
B-san.
B-san of B-san.
In this era of Heisei,
there's the Gingham check.
That's a high point, isn't it?
Ootomo.
I'm a little...
I'm a little excited.
Why?
Ootomo is...
Ootomo-kun's drawing has been going around lately.
It's become a little Tengu.
It's become Tengu.
I see.
Adachi Motoichi.
Yes.
Look at this jumper.
It's the worst.
It's a camera.
Normally, you'd have to stand there.
Isn't that a surfer?
No.
It's not a surfer?
Why do you have a beard?
You look like a surfer.
Right?
You're just an Eskimo.
Is she a girl instead of a surfer?
This guy is quite...
An Eskimo.
Come on.
A pervert.
We often go to karaoke together.
When I go to Keats,
I bring a girl I don't know.
See? See?
See?
Hey, Hama-chan.
You're there, aren't you?
I bring a girl I don't know.
You're just a pervert.
You look like a surfer.
Really.
I'm Taka-san.
I'm a broadcaster.
We're from the same town.
I'm a watchmaker.
It's amazing.
He's a villain.
He's the chief director.
He's in charge of everything.
I stopped growing up when I was in 6th grade.
Five female members.
The first impression is good.
From number 1 to number 10.
It's good.
Five members.
We'll count them now.
I thought you were wearing a mask.
Number 1.
Number 2.
Number 3.
Number 4.
Number 5.
Number 7.
Number 9.
Step forward, please.
These people...
are...
and the others are...
Goodbye!
No way.
You know...
We were wearing masks.
Who...
Who was wearing masks?
Check your numbers.
Number 2.
What are you all riding?
All of us.
I don't buy it.
You don't have much money?
I don't like it.
I don't ride a car.
It's called a Hilux Surf.
It's a 4WD.
It's like a 4WD GV.
It's big.
It's popular.
It's an AD.
It's a new car.
It's two years old.
This is my light truck.
You're wearing a jacket.
You're riding a light truck.
This is the busiest place in the center.
We don't ride a lot.
Yamato-san.
I heard you often go out to play.
Where do you go out to play?
What do you do to play?
I see.
I was taken by Matsumoto-kun to an SM club.
Everyone, you have to tell the truth.
The people watching are going to get the wrong idea.
Why?
I'm the one who gets the blame.
Hey!
If you were to compare yourself to someone, who would you compare yourself to?
It's only once in a long time.
To Tahara Toshihiko.
That was when Tahara Toshihiko wasn't around yet.
How much do you practice?
I think this is an honest question.
Of course, it's the same with marriage.
Just going out with someone isn't enough.
Don't look so serious!
This chair suddenly became this long.
I think it's about 2.5 million yen.
Really?
That's a bonus.
Every week?
Yes.
About 1.8 million yen.
I think it's about two or three times as much as a regular salaryman.
That's pretty expensive.
How much is it?
It's 2.5 million yen.
If it's 2.5 million yen, then it's about 2.5 million yen.
Hey, you!
What kind of question is that?
Someone who goes around the world.
To be honest, which do you like more, Machan or Hama-chan?
If I'm going to be honest with you,
I don't like either of them.
What number is your first girlfriend?
Number 9.
Takasu.
What kind of music is that?
It's going to be a mess.
Number 9.
Number 4.
Oh, Tomo.
What kind of reaction is that?
Okama.
Number 4.
Number 7.
Yanaoka.
Number 9.
I got 3 Taka-san.
But to get Nitta-san, I couldn't get it all.
Because you're going to see it, put it on your cheek.
It's ok?
You're full of motivation.
Hello, everyone.
Today, we're going to use all of the kids.
Today's opening was fun.
Today's opening was amazing, wasn't it?
Oh, really?
That's how it is on the show?
That's right.
You ate garlic.
Sorry.
I ate it in the middle of the day.
You're pregnant with your wife and you're eating garlic.
Where do you get that from?
It's not like...
It's not just that I eat garlic because I'm pregnant.
I went to the train station the other day.
There was a nervous waitress.
What's that?
It's not because it's you.
It's because I'm a high-ranking talent.
That's enough!
What's high-ranking?
What?
It's because I have a lot of talent.
That's enough.
When a high-ranking talent comes, the waitress gets nervous.
I don't get nervous, but I'm nervous because I'm a high-ranking talent.
It's interesting to see a nervous person.
It's interesting to see a nervous person trying to suppress it.
They come to me.
What's wrong with me?
I'm not like that at all.
That's because there are people like that.
This person and that old man over there are the same.
They're all the same.
They're trying their best to separate themselves.
There were three people who ordered.
They ordered iced coffee, Americano, and so on.
I said, okay, I got it.
And they left.
And over there, in this trench,
they had iced coffee and Americano.
They were all piled up.
Hurry up!
Right?
All the people who ordered were ready.
And they came to our table.
They said, welcome.
What would you like to order?
Really?
That's what they said.
It's true.
How many years has it been since they came to our house?
That's right.
It's interesting to see a nervous person.
You don't get nervous, do you?
What?
You don't get nervous.
I don't get nervous.
Have you ever felt like your body was shaking?
I was really nervous.
The skydiving that was done on this show.
I was really scared.
I was really scared of the cold.
Other than that, nothing.
Other than that?
Nothing.
Your body was shaking.
Like a newborn baby horse.
That's right.
That's a yakuza.
I've never been involved with a yakuza.
When I was involved, it wasn't a big deal.
I was scared about 5 or 6 years ago.
That's because you touched a yakuza woman.
I didn't touch her.
No, that was...
That's true.
No, no.
If you did that...
I didn't touch her.
So...
That's not true.
My friend...
My friend has a fan.
He wanted me to touch her.
I said no, no.
That's not true.
Don't say that.
I said no, no.
Oh?
I said, just once.
I didn't touch her.
Her makeup was really thick.
I like it.
She looked like a girl I liked.
I like her a lot.
I like girls who are pure and innocent.
Pure and innocent?
Right?
I thought it was hard.
I didn't want to touch her.
So I said no.
Why did you go to her room?
I sent her to the apartment.
I'm a gentleman in comedy.
Shut up!
I sent her to the bottom of the apartment.
She said she wanted to go to the top.
So I said I'd have a cup of tea.
I thought I could have a cup of tea.
I didn't want her to be rude.
She's my wife.
She's your wife.
I thought I could have a cup of tea.
I'm a man.
Don't say unnecessary things.
She's the apple of my eye.
What do you mean?
She has a big heart.
She went to the top.
It was about the ninth floor.
She went in.
She was like an angry woman.
When she went into her room, she started to sing.
With a loud voice.
She didn't want to do anything.
She was drinking tea.
She was singing.
I thought she finished singing.
It was so noisy that I couldn't hear her.
When she finished singing,
She opened the door.
He kicked the door.
That's an amazing sound!
At first, I thought it was Bon-chan's song.
I thought the next song was Anne-Louise's song.
I don't think Anne-Louise can sing a song like this.
It's definitely different.
He kicked the door.
And he lived with that woman.
He has a spare key.
I asked him why he kicked the door.
He said it was just a chain.
The door was open.
It was like in an occult movie.
You could see his face.
I couldn't see his face.
I couldn't see his legs.
It was like he was a newborn baby.
He said,
I can't open it!
That's terrible.
He's a big boy.
You're pulling a man again.
He's doing it again.
He likes women.
Open the chain!
If I open it, I'll be killed.
That woman is also very brave.
I don't know who should open it.
You shouldn't say that.
Why shouldn't I open it?
Don't say that.
You shouldn't say that either.
I thought you shouldn't open it.
If I open it for a while,
the man won't come back.
I thought he went back.
He won't come back.
After a while, he'll come back.
Will he come back?
I just called a young man.
If you open the chain right now...
It's really scary.
That woman is also a member of that group.
Her father is also a member of that group.
That woman is also very strong.
My father is...
I don't think I should open it.
That man kicked her again.
I just called Mr. Tsukaguchi.
Who is that?
Tsukaguchi said something.
I don't know, but he looks bad.
But this woman is the daughter of the leader of the Yakuza.
I thought Mr. Tsukaguchi wouldn't come.
Then that woman said,
Why are you calling Mr. Tsukaguchi?
Let's go to the postcard.
Postcard.
Thank you.
Let me introduce you.
This woman is...
Yuka Teranishi.
She was born in Tokyo and went to Fukuoka once.
Then she came back to Tokyo.
Why did she go to Fukuoka?
She is the ostrich of the circus troupe.
What is the ostrich of the circus troupe?
The leader.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I recently had a boyfriend.
But she is pretty cute.
You can have a boyfriend soon.
That's right.
Good luck.
This is one of the things.
I'm going to get a man.
If you come to this program, someone will definitely ask for your phone number.
Please check it out later.
I think someone will ask.
Thank you very much.
Let's move on to the next postcard.
Let's see.
Let's go to this person.
This is from Kawasaki City.
Hello, Mr. Okunohama.
You suddenly woke up in the middle of the night.
Here it comes.
Your girlfriend was sleeping next to you.
She was sleeping next to me.
You chopped the part where she was sleeping.
You woke her up.
What are you talking about?
You suddenly chopped her.
This way.
What are you talking about?
She was angry.
And you said,
Thank you for the meal.
You fell down and fell asleep.
When you were drunk,
when you fell asleep,
if you did something like this,
please tell me.
Got it?
I fell asleep?
Yes.
You wrote down what you did.
That's right.
I don't know if you went shopping and fell asleep,
but you said that.
That's right.
I just happened to see this.
I saw my dream when I was flying.
I got this.
I baked in the car.
And then I woke up.
There are a lot of it recently.
Maybe it's because she didn't sleep deeply.
I snore.
You do.
I snore a lot.
Only that is not careful.
Also, you should be careful of that.
snoring and smoking.
You can't get it right away.
What are you talking about?
You light up a cigarette and leave it on the table.
I've never seen you smoke so many cigarettes.
Your cigarettes are amazing.
Really?
Really.
There's no oil on the table.
There's definitely going to be a fire.
It's obvious.
Your wife and you are smoking.
I'm sorry.
There's a menu.
It's like a drift show.
There's definitely going to be a fire.
You have to be careful.
Lately, I want to be your manager.
Really?
I said that today.
She wants to be your manager too.
What's wrong with being a manager?
It's a big deal to be a housewife.
It seems like Nitta is slowly getting sick.
Is that so?
I didn't have Nitta at first.
I was a woman's manager.
I quit after three days.
I couldn't keep up with her.
Then Nitta came.
Yoshimoto has a lot of managers.
Nozawa's manager is amazing.
He's 100% fat.
He's amazing.
Look, he's fat.
His house is a butcher's.
He's fat and has twins.
This is amazing.
If it was just one person, what kind of fat would he be?
If it was just one person, he wouldn't have twins.
Everyone's going to be surprised.
I think that's enough for today.
Isn't that enough?
I think that's enough.
We have to do this.
Yes, yes, yes.
Please give us some goods.
Which one should we give them?
Let's give them something interesting.
I think I'll give this guy a helmet.
Is that so?
Yoko Izumida-chan.
Please give me Mach-chan's helmet.
I'm a laborer.
I can't do it without it.
I'll get scolded by my boss, so please give it to me.
I can't help it.
It's nice.
This is a helmet.
I'll give you a helmet.
I'll give you this.
I don't want it, so I won't give it to you.
That's right.
I want to wear Mach-chan's helmet.
I don't want it.
I want to wear it anyway.
I won't give you this either.
There are a lot of helmets.
I'll give you this.
Suemoto Yuko-san.
I'll give this guy a plate.
Yes, yes.
I'll give it to you.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
That's all for today.
There won't be much sound today, will there?
Thank you very much for today.
See you next week.
Hello.
As I said before, I have a letter for you.
The person who was read during the program.
Suemoto Yuko-san.
I'll give you this.
This is from Terese.
I'll give it to you.
Read it.
And...
I'll give you a letter.
On the 3rd of November, Saturday.
At 12 o'clock in the afternoon.
At Arakawa-no-Kawara, Hinode-ryokuchi.
If you want to do it with me.
On the 3rd of November, Saturday.
At 12 o'clock in the afternoon.
At Arakawa-no-Kawara, Hinode-ryokuchi.
The outfit at that time.
It's a gold-haired outfit.
With long hair.
Necktie and jacket.
If you don't wear it, you can't participate.
I'll leave it like this.
That's all.
I'm a child's servant.
I'll write something and put it in front of you.
You can get a jumper.
The address is the same.
Please write it.
I'll wait for you.
I'm a child's servant.
I'll see you next time.
Good-bye.
See you.
It's on the 3rd of November.
On the 3rd of November, Saturday.
At 12 o'clock in the afternoon.
At Arakawa-no-Kawara.