What kind of comedy is this?
I don't know.
Well, it has started today as well.
I thought I would get 100,000 yen today.
I went to Nagabuchi Tsuyoshi's concert.
After the concert, he asked me to come to his dressing room.
He said, you are amazing.
Normally, after the concert, the staff would be busy, right?
I would write a letter and say, thank you for today.
I imagined it in my head.
I really liked Higashino and Kurano.
They invited me to their dressing room.
I said, this way, please.
I was really surprised.
I was sitting alone in this big room.
I thought I was going to get beaten up.
I was waiting for the staff to come.
I was sitting alone in this big room.
I said, this is a family.
I have been doing this for longer than usual.
I said, this is a family service.
They came to me.
Higashino is always like that.
I was surprised when I went to them.
When I reached out to them, they hugged me.
I wanted to drink coffee on my own will.
They said, I'll wait for you in Kurano.
They drank coffee with the three of them.
They were really cool.
Who is the real guy?
Shall we?
Let's go for a red light.
I have a question for Matsumoto-san, the killer.
What is Matsumoto-san's killing technique?
And what is Nakama doing now? Please tell me.
Umm...
It's not really a killing technique.
If you think about it, anything can become a weapon.
Anything can kill people.
For example, a washing machine can kill people.
It's not a killing technique.
When you want to get rid of the water, you have to get closer to the machine.
Like this.
It's an old washing machine.
It can kill people.
You don't have to think about it.
You can just grab it and kill people.
It can kill people.
That's embarrassing.
What is?
It's obvious that you can kill people.
You can laugh at it.
I can laugh at it too.
I won't get killed.
Oh my.
I'm surprised.
I'm surprised too.
It can kill 6 people.
I won't get killed.
Do you have friends?
I have friends.
Can you tell me what you are doing now?
Why do I have to tell you?
I have a job, so please contact me.
You can contact me.
How many people do you have?
Two people.
That's a lot.
What are the other two people doing?
One is at the soap factory.
How about the other one?
The other one is at the highway.
How about the one at the cashier?
It's an old man.
I don't care.
You're a great trio.
You have a sister and an old man.
That's right.
That's the most suspicious.
If you say it on TV, the three of us have to walk like this.
That's right.
Old man and sister.
How are you going to kill them?
Old men usually aim at the highway.
That's a long story.
It's a long story.
The old man opens the door and says,
I'll give you 600 yen.
600 yen.
700 yen.
He pulls me.
Stop that.
You old man.
The old man cuts into your heart.
That's right.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
700 yen.
Kendi Gyakodon.
You can do it!
Old man!
But if it doesn't do that much damage...
Well, it's fine. I don't mind.
It's just soap.
It's not even something to use.
I just do this, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap.
Then roll it up,
then it comes,
and it's crumpled!
It's crumpled!
What the hell are you doing?
What's with the crumpling?
This is strangely interesting.
So even if the manuscript is stolen, it's not a big deal.
Mr. Gozo, I have a cat, but there are times when I don't know where it is.
Please tell me where it is.
I think he can say that he is from Todai.
Oh, I see.
For example, looking for glasses, looking for glasses while wearing glasses here.
But first of all, I think it's the same as that.
Do you think it won't break?
Yes, I do.
Nearby?
Yes.
Where is it?
No, it's on the back.
I don't know if it's here like the glasses.
You can tell by the weight if it's on the back.
Yesterday, when I was watching the video, a fly was flying.
I was worried about it while watching it.
I turned on the light with a moa gun and looked at it from the side.
I thought I wanted to go to Nagabuchi.
When I turned on the light, the fly disappeared.
I looked for it, but it wasn't there.
First of all, I thought it was somewhere in my house.
Did you get drunk?
What?
No, I didn't get drunk.
I looked at the picture and watched the video again, but the fly didn't come out.
That means...
I was right.
Why?
No, no, no.
I was right.
No, you weren't.
You didn't feel anything, did you?
No, I didn't feel anything.
You did feel something.
What was it?
Something like a thud.
That's a fly in the stomach, isn't it?
It's screaming.
It's screaming at the glass.
I don't know why.
I don't know either.
There's a fly that can't be cleaned.
Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang.
The one that was in the glass?
When Masumoto-san was in Takarazuka,
the president of the Japan Theatre Association told him that he had been killed.
He said, show me the pantomime where you catch a runaway bird.
He was in Takarazuka.
It doesn't matter.
He wasn't in Takarazuka.
What?
You're lying.
There's a lot of letters and you have to wait in one place.
That's right.
It's a pain in the ass, so don't do it.
The runaway bird.
What are you doing?
I'm starting.
Do it.
The pantomime where you catch a runaway bird.
Where did it run away?
That's something you have to think about.
You have to act it out yourself.
It's all over the place.
Where are you?
Hey.
You're drinking in such a small place.
On the top of the building.
On the top of the building?
There's glass here too.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Let's assume there's glass here.
Hey.
You can't talk.
Say something better.
Hey.
Drink slowly later.
Where are you now?
What is this?
I just caught it.
This is a question for Matsumoto-san who has been married hundreds of times.
What's in your bride's hair?
Do you know this?
I know what's in it.
Do you know what's in it?
I'm just covering it.
Why are you covering it?
I'm matching it with my kimono.
You're matching it with your kimono.
You're saying you're matching it with your kimono.
I'm saying it.
Say it more specifically.
What's in it?
It's not in there.
You're covering it with your hair.
Hey, hey, hey.
Are you angry?
It's in there.
What's wrong with that?
That's not true.
It's in there, so it's like this.
It's not in there.
It's my kimono.
I can't talk to you.
Whatever.
Tell me what's in it.
Shall I tell you?
The memories of walking with your parents.
The memories of sitting with Matsumoto-san.
You're a relaxed person.
It's often said that Matsumoto-san was the one who decided on the 12th.
Thank you very much.
What was the standard for deciding?
Please tell me.
In the end, it's a natural enemy.
A natural enemy?
It's a natural enemy.
Thank you very much.
Please tell me.
Hey, I'll catch a mouse.
What does that mean?
A mouse.
A mouse is eating a mouse.
Did you think you could get away with it?
That's mean.
Why?