Next, everyone is crying! Yama-chan's Happy Wedding!
Today, the other day...
This is the worst!
This is the worst kind of show!
I don't think this will be on the show for a while.
It's short.
But the V-app is pretty long.
Really?
That means you'll be able to watch it a lot.
I heard that it was very moving.
I think I'm going to get a lot of money for this show!
Who's going to pay for this?
That's right.
After finding out that she's pregnant,
the 33-year-old comedian, Yamazaki Hose,
happily decided to get married.
The other day, he had a very moving show with only his family.
Today, we'll reveal the whole story!
Let's have the star of the show, Yamazaki Hose, come on out!
Why do you have such a face?
Nice to meet you!
Please take care of me.
Are you going to cry?
If I don't cry, the skin of a human...
The skin of a human, right?
If I don't cry, the skin of a human, right?
You don't know the meaning, do you?
If I don't cry, the skin of a human...
Turn the camera around!
It's okay, Hamada-san!
I'm definitely going to cry!
This is the skin of a human!
A human?
A human!
But the size is different.
It's not a human.
You have to say something about the same size.
This is definitely not a human.
If I don't cry...
That's how moving it is.
Today, there are four of us and 25 staff members.
We're going to see if we're going to be moved or not.
After we're done, we're going to count.
We're going to think of a present for Hose-san
with the points from the counting.
I think this is going to be the best.
If there are 5 people from 0, it's going to be this kind of product.
It's about 5 people.
It's about this much.
6 to 10.
This is it.
It's about this much.
We're a couple.
How about you, Aya-chan?
No, no, no.
From 11 to 15,
it's a bicycle for 3 people who can enjoy it with their children.
From 16 to 20,
it's a luxury product that's safe for the elderly.
From 21 to 24,
it's a luxurious chandelier.
I don't need this.
It's a wonderful thing.
I'm not going to give it to you!
And if it's perfect 24,
this is it!
Wow!
This is amazing.
Anywhere!
Anywhere in the world!
This is amazing.
I'm going to eat it.
Really?
Yes.
You're going to pay for all of this?
This is amazing.
I'm the only one who's going to pay for this.
It's similar.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Now, let's begin Yama-chan's happy wedding performance!
I can't go down once, can I?
This is the ceremony, right?
I, Seishi,
hereby announce the grand wedding of Izumo Oyashiro.
I'm going to get married today.
We are going to perform a ceremony
in this shrine
where the newlyweds are going to get married.
From now on, we are going to pray to God.
What?
We are going to love each other.
No one's laughing so far.
We are going to dedicate this ceremony
to the newlyweds.
Even Miko behind us is laughing.
We are going to pray.
No one's laughing at all.
On the 13th of Heisei,
It's like a skit.
on the 21st of October,
the husband, Hyosei Yamasaki.
Wife, Aya.
She spoke.
She can speak.
She can't speak.
What is this?
This is like a wedding how-to video.
It's true.
What is this?
It's a very beautiful image.
If you play this in a song, it won't look like this.
It's a lie.
Where is this?
It's a rare new bride.
Why?
Aya isn't crying that much.
I'm not crying.
I'm crying so I can't cry.
If you cry,
you'll have to cry.
Why aren't you crying?
The bride and groom, please enter.
What is this?
This is where you cry, right?
Yes.
Why are you entering with this sound?
Wow.
The umbrella role isn't working.
Don't laugh.
Now, we will begin the wedding ceremony of the Yamasaki family, the Ito family, and the Goryo family.
Cameras, are you ready?
Please enter the wedding cake.
Congratulations.
He's laughing.
The bride and groom, please enter the wedding cake.
What?
They're taking pictures of the umbrella.
That's what I thought.
I'm impressed.
Everyone on the right, please pay attention.
This is a photo of you two when you were little.
Let's begin.
I don't want to see it.
A genius comedian has arrived in Nishinomiya City, Hyogo Prefecture.
What do you think of this?
Thank you.
At the bottom of the center,
there is a great symbol of a genius comedian.
Wow.
It's so long.
This costume is enough.
He's laughing.
He's having fun.
It's so expensive.
Who is this?
Is he your friend?
No, he's my relative.
Everyone, please give him a big round of applause.
The bride and groom, please enter the wedding cake.
What is this?
I wanted to change my clothes.
Congratulations.
This is strange.
What is this?
The bride and groom, please enter the wedding cake.
I think you're a little different.
No, no.
Is this okay?
I'm scared.
Again?
It's hard for me too.
I'm a person who shot on the spot.
It's hard.
What is this?
Who is this?
Congratulations on your wedding.
The bride and groom, please enter the wedding cake.
Look at this.
You can see it now.
I was given this.
I drew it when I was young.
And I forgot it someday.
It's like a dream.
Why do you use this?
It doesn't matter.
Dad, mom.
Thank you for raising such a selfish child.
And mom.
Until I met my current father.
I've been a woman all my life.
Our father.
He raised me.
I'm going to cry.
Mom, thank you for your hard work.
From now on, I will do my best as a mother and a baby.
Mom.
From the bottom of my heart, I am a mother.
Thank you very much.
Hosei's father and mother.
I will do my best as a daughter-in-law and a daughter-in-law.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
Dad and mom, please give me a round of applause.
This is the end of the screening.
I'm crying alone.
Do you have any comments?
I think it was a normal wedding screening.
I don't know if you're impressed.
If you are impressed, turn on the switch.
It's zero.
Zero?
I didn't think it was zero.
There is a toilet paper.
Unfortunately, it was zero.
Really?
I was a little impressed.
But if you cry, it will be broken.
It's hard.
I want to give you a medicine box.
Thank you very much.
Please give me a round of applause.
Congratulations on your 20th anniversary.
I think this is a good thing.
There are only two cars in the front row.
I'm about to cry.
I want to give it to everyone.
Why are there only two cars in the front row?
I talked a lot about driving on TV.
I don't want to talk about it.
But let me tell you this.
There are two cars in the front row.
I'm going to go in from the front row.
The car next to me is going to turn left.
So I can't go in from the front row.
I wanted to go in between the white and black cars.
Who are you paying attention to?
If you pay attention, it's me in the back.
The way you use the keys is strange.
I'm tired of it.
There are three cars in the back row.
There are four cars in the back row.
In fact, being the front seat is similar to me.
This time I went in between the two true car why I was given a space.
If you were the only person in the back row, you would have been the person in front of you.
That's right!
If that's the case...
This is a difficult topic.
I want to turn everything upside down.
I want to turn everything upside down with that Okonomiyaki thing.
With a slightly bigger one.
Can I call it?
If you can go with a bigger one, I'd like you to go.
I want to go. From the top, too.
You're this way.
This is also possible.
No, no, no.
Why are you doing it this way?
I want to do this, too.
I want to do this with a smaller one.
Like this.
It really makes me angry.
I want you to stop running when you're in a traffic jam.
That's all I care about.
I'm the one who opens the gap.
Even though I'm in a traffic jam.
I'm right in front of him.
It really makes me angry.
That's...
When I'm running away from him.
I'm like, I'm going to get in trouble.
I'm like that, but when I look at the number.
He's from the countryside.
And I'm like, I'm going to get in trouble.
I'm going to get in trouble.
I'm like, I'm going to get in trouble.
You know the function of raising the seat, right?
You know that, right?
It's like this.
I can't be a fool.
That's a chair.
I can't do this.
I can't be a fool.
I want to put a big trailer on it.
I want to crush everything.
That's not possible.
What?
I want to look at it from above.
You're crazy.
That's not possible.
I want to look at it from above.
This is a question for Matsumoto, the only athlete who can compete with Keiin Kosugi.
Yes.
The three-stage jump is a hop, step, and jump.
I heard that Matsumoto completed the first five-stage jump in human history.
In the case of a five-stage jump, what happens next?
Yes.
Actually, hop, step is English, right?
And then it becomes French.
Hop, step, and then it becomes German.
That's not possible.
What?
Hop, step, and jump.
Please explain the movement.
What is it?
Please explain what happens when you say something.
Otherwise, I don't understand.
It comes like this, right?
It's a hop, right?
It's the same here, right?
It's a step, right?
Originally, it's a jump here.
It's a jump.
This is the end.
What comes next?
Durban.
What?
When it comes to Durban, it's both legs.
Durban.
And then it becomes Serre-Lego.
I don't understand.
I don't understand this.
Do you understand?
Why don't you understand?
I don't understand what this means.
It becomes Serre-Lego, right?
Ah, no.
No, no, no.
Hop, step, Durban, Serre-Lego.
Stop, stop, stop.
Stop here.
I can't stop.
What comes next?
It becomes Serre-Lego.
And then?
What comes next?
Serre-Lego.
Durban.
What's that?
What's that at the end?
It's a landing.
What's that?
It's a Grand-Madiam.
Grand-Madiam.
And then, the 15cm distance between the front legs is recorded.
The 15cm distance between the front legs is recorded.
It's tiring to watch, isn't it?
It's tiring to do it, isn't it?
Ah, sports is...
It's going to be a big deal.
But there's no one doing this, right?
That's right.
Eh, that's not true!
That's not true at all.
When I stand next to you, I always smell the good smell of shampoo.
I have a question for Matsumoto-san.
When you're shampooing, you feel something behind you.
Who's behind you?
Ah, I see.
Yes, yes, yes.
This is something that even the UnBelievable hasn't done.
I see.
This is really like that.
Do you feel it?
Ah, well, it's like...
Someone.
But I don't think there's anything to be afraid of.
Is that so?
Yes.
It's not a bad example.
How do you know that?
I don't know if it's a bad example.
No, no, no.
In short, when you're shampooing, the feeling that's behind you is...
It's the linseed.
What do you mean?
Eh?
I'm the next one, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
It's the linseed scent.
Hurry up and put it on.
The next one is me, right?
The scent of the linseed is...
Hurry up and put me on like that.
I'm really used to scalp.
Eh?
You're looking at me like that?
You're really behind.
If that's the case...
You're really looking at me from behind, right?
I'm really looking at you.
But that's not a bad example at all.
Ah, is that so?
Everyone's a little scared, right?
I'm scared.
I can't believe you're wearing a linseed.
But what you have to be careful about is that when you suddenly linseed...
This shampoo's grudge is scary.
I jumped over it and said it was linseed.
It's me, isn't it linseed?
That's what it is.
This shampoo's...
This female cat!
Thief cat!
That's not for you.
It's for the linseed.
You have a young body!
What are you trying to say?
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.