Chikitsuki downtown presents at the 1st Gaki no Tsukaya
We will give you a free lunch
It's just like the title
It's our free lunch season
Let's give them a free lunch
Thank you
We are your producers
That's it
We will give you a free lunch too
Thank you
Azazaki is here in the rain
You are so humble
Are you going to eat?
I will throw this ball
Matsumoto will hit it
I will catch the ball
That's easy
If you make a mistake, you lose
I will give you 1000 yen each
I will give you a charity
I am serious
We are warriors
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
Everyone, let's go
Azazaki, you look like a poor guy
You look like a rich guy
He must have poop on his pants
Let's start
Somen Tsume Awase
Are you serious?
1000 yen
I can't do it while running
Wait a little
1000 yen
This is the worst
Please
Next
Nori Tsume Awase
Is this possible?
Why?
I didn't do anything weird
Next
Polaroid body shot
This is sponsored
1000 yen
What?
You tried to take it
1000 yen
Next
Hokkaido Kegani
No Kegani
I can't do it
Are you out of your mind?
Why did you shoot the speedball?
Somen Tsume Awase
1000 yen
You should have done it
He should have done it
1000 yen
Congratulations
Polaroid body shot
1000 yen
You should have done it
We are done with soy sauce and beer
We have a big present
Downtown presents
Porsche 911 Carrera
Check it out
What?
It's good
Porsche 911 Carrera
Is it a new car?
It's a new car
Gasoline
It's a set
Let's do our best
Go
Let's go
Porsche 911 Carrera
What?
What is this?
That's weird
Stop it
I thought it would float
I'm not angry
It doesn't float
I understand
It's not funny
One more time
Stop it
I forgot the bat
The bat
He's angry
What?
He took the glove
It's the second time
Which one was better?
Mine was the first one
Did you really do it?
Yes
Let's do it
Porsche
Hey
That was amazing
I was one step behind
Damn it
I can't help it
I can't hit the ball
I just hit it
I did it
Let's do it
I'll use Porsche at my office
Thank you
I'm sorry
I'll take care of you
Let's have fun this summer
I'll take care of us
I'm counting on you
Why are you so happy?
The audience is happy
That's not good
I'll cut it
I'm getting older
Why are you so old?
I'm serious
You're cool
You're a man
I like Japan
I'm serious
I'm getting older
I used to drive a white car
It was raining
I was excited
It was about 100 meters
I wanted to think about it
I wanted to take it easy
I got off the car and ran
Do you think I can do it?
I don't think I can do it
I heard later that there was an explosion in the car
As soon as I ran, I got a backache
I can't run
I want to run
My body can't keep up
But if I stop, I'll break it
My back hurts
I ran like this
I got a lucky punch
It's a strange way of running
But it's dangerous
I can't do this
I've been saying that for a long time
I don't think I can do it
Please think about it
Let me do it
I don't think I can do it
I'm serious
Really?
Yes
Thank you
Was it hard today?
Today's baseball
It was hard
I was born to play baseball
My body
Everyone is
saying that my body is amazing
Is it amazing?
I've been doing the same thing
I've been doing it since I was in Japan
Is it amazing?
I don't like baseball
I'm not interested
I'm more amazing
How amazing?
Tornado-like
Tornado-like?
That's just you
I'm more amazing
You are
Tornado is amazing?
It's my tornado
No
What kind of tornado?
Like this
I don't know
Old man
Why are you acting like an old man?
I do it like this
Then?
Normally you do it like this
Normally
I do it like this
It's a stick
I don't know
You have to show me your tornado
I can't do my tornado
Like this
That's a tornado
What kind of tornado is yours?
My tornado is like this
Like this
Right?
Okay
Here you go
Don't ask me
My tornado is like this
Your tornado
No
My tornado is like this
Don't ask me
I don't know
Everyone knows my tornado
Your tornado
My tornado
Show me your tornado
I don't have a tornado
You have one
I have a tornado
Okay
What is that?
It's your tornado
My tornado
Here I go
It's normal
You threw it normally
I didn't throw it normally
I just threw it and it became like this
No
My tornado is
My feeling
You have a lot of feelings
I don't have a feeling
Everyone can't tell
It's a tornado
I don't have a feeling
Show me your tornado
Everyone knows
I told you to throw your tornado
Why did you throw my tornado?
You said it's different from your tornado
It's your tornado
It's not time for me to think
While I was doing my tornado
I was thinking about my tornado
Are you stupid?
You are my tornado
You can do it right away
Have you seen my tornado?
Are you my enemy?
You have to support me
So that I can laugh
Don't interfere
That's why
I'm working
Look at Nomu's tornado
Look at Nomu's tornado 4 or 5 times
Why?
It's okay
Do it
It's sudden
It's okay
Wait
I don't like him
What?
It's okay
It's different from your tornado
It's different
Everyone is like that
Me too
This person too
They are different
They are great
I'm not
You are the best
Don't laugh
Don't be friends
It's a friend
I know
Who is this?
Please try
Summer is the season of conversation.
Yes.
Mr. Matsumoto, who is also a spiritist, what was the most amazing spirit you've ever fought?
You're a spiritist, aren't you?
I can feel your spirit.
I'm not a spiritist.
Yes, you're a spiritist.
Why were you so strict?
You see, I...
Are you trying to be serious?
I have a phone number at various places.
Are you going to pay me?
Yes, yes, yes.
Really?
Well, I'm not going.
Because you can't?
No, because I'm busy.
No, I've been busy lately.
What have you been doing lately?
In the past, I went to places where I was told to go.
So what kind of things are you going to pay?
I'm a bad spirit.
Well, well, I'll give you an example of a house in the pond.
What was it like in the past?
That was when I went to Gunma Prefecture, wasn't it?
Yes.
The children were very mischievous.
I was hungry.
Well, well, that's why I solved it right away.
Look at it.
I wrote it because I thought it was different.
Be careful.
Parents are bad.
Please rap for each other.
I can't do it.
Do it.
You really can't do anything.
I'm sorry.
You don't have a sense of rhythm.
Is that so?
Yes.
Please tell me.
I don't know if you're in the mood to sing.
It would have been better if I hit it.
I don't have this tempo anymore.
Hey, hey, hey, right?
You remember it well.
Stand up.
Hand.
Right?
You too.
I don't have a sense of rhythm.
Do you have a lot of otaku?
Of course I have.
I have two rockabilly.
Please tell me about the rockabilly.
I can't do that much.
It's like this.
Basically.
What basically?
Rockabilly.
Please tell me.
Shall we go downtown?
What?
Shall we make the theme song of downtown rockabilly?
Oh, please.
I'm getting tired of that.
Yes.
The theme song of downtown is the one you're doing now, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
That sound is like rockabilly.
Oh, that's fine.
I don't care at all.
Really?
Yes.
By all means.
Please.
Hamada and I are fans.
What is it?
Rockabilly.
Don't be embarrassed.
I'm not embarrassed at all.
Really?
I'm a little embarrassed now.
Oh, really?
If you're okay with it.
I'm okay with it.
Can I continue?
I don't really want to see it.
Hamada and I are all night.
All night.
It's a great lyrics.
Hamada and I are all night.
I'm in it, too.
Of course you are.
You can still go at night.
I'm not like that.
Hamada and I are all night.
I said I'm not like that.
What?
Who are you talking to?
I'm not like that.
Hamada and I are all night.
All night?
I'm scared.
You have to study hard.
What?
Sing, sing.
Hamada, you're funny.
Next is the second one.
That's great.
What are you going to do if you get married?
That's right.
You have to do it once.
You have to go back to the dressing room.
If you go out, I'll design it.
What?
Clothes, clothes.
No, it's okay.
I'll make it with wood.
With wood?
Why wood?
Wood is warmer.
That's true in Japan.
I can't do that.
I'll make it with wood.
It's like a guy in a suit.
Wood, wood, wood.
If that's the case,
I'll make it with wood.
You have to do it.
Why do you have to do it with NHK?
It's embarrassing.
Who's going to talk?
What?
Your wife will be happy.
Your wife will be happy?
You're a fool.
What is that?
It's weird.
It's a white group, so it's weird.
It's weird if it's a red group.
It's weird if it's a white group.
But it's a wood group.
It's weird.
Even if it's a group, why won't it come out?
I won't put it out.
No, no, no, no, no.
You're a little too much.
When I say, hey, hey, hey,
It's like a pop.
You're a fool.
Make it right.