die
them
ah
In Okinawa, let's buy a lot of Chikitsuki at Gaki no Tsukai in the second time!
You got 10,000 yen just now, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
With this 10,000 yen, you can get 10kg.
Oh, I see.
You can buy it later and put it on the weight.
Well, compared to Tokyo, Fukuoka is cheaper, isn't it?
Well, yes.
You may be able to shop more than before.
Yes, yes.
Where are you going?
Well, there is only this shopping street.
So I'm not going to the other side.
I'm going in the same way.
What?
Because there is only this shopping street.
No, there is only this shopping street.
You don't do anything here.
20,000 yen.
It's amazing. Listen to it.
It doesn't matter what it is.
I'll play it, so you dance.
Hey, dance.
What am I doing?
This is it.
Wow.
This is the dance.
This is bad.
No, no, no.
Do you take this?
Yes.
This is bad.
I don't know if I'll get caught.
Look.
This is bad.
Mom, wrap it with this.
What?
Wrap it with this lid.
If I do this, it will collapse.
It's okay.
It may collapse.
It's heavy.
Grandma, come on.
It seems to be Okinawa.
If I give it to all the staff, it may weigh about 5kg.
Well, then.
Yes.
What each of you bought is 10kg?
I think so.
Let's find out.
Yes.
This, this.
Ah.
Try it out there.
Well, then.
Crab.
This is a bite of black sugar.
It's funny.
This was laughed at by the staff and Haraka.
This is a joke.
It's funny.
How many did you buy?
This is one.
This is a joke.
That's good.
This is.
What is this?
A pig's face.
Do this.
Do this in front of your face.
I don't like it.
I hate it.
What?
Stop it, you idiot.
Don't call me brother.
Wow, it's good.
I was told that you were good at it, so I bought it.
You are the last.
What?
The last?
Do you want to drink this with everyone?
What is that?
Then you should measure it.
It's not a big deal.
3.5 kg.
No way.
It's 4 kg.
It's not.
3.5 kg.
8 kg.
It's good.
You idiot.
It's increasing.
What kind of calculation is that?
What?
At this point, it's 7.5 kg.
If you add 3 kg, how much will it be?
I didn't say that anyone could add 3 kg.
Really?
I don't know.
I don't know if it's used in Okinawa.
I don't know if it's used in Osaka.
Then add all the juice.
It's just right to add all the juice.
Add it here.
Wait a minute.
Do you hate me?
Put it here.
What are you going to do?
Put it in here.
Where are you going?
Hey.
I give up the game.
This is my victory.
You're annoying.
You killed me.
I just turned on the lights in the back.
What kind of idea is that?
I was really worried.
Everyone was coming.
What if there was no reaction?
I was wondering if there would be a reaction.
Everyone was talking like a fool.
Well.
I'm the one who came.
We've been to Okinawa a lot.
That's right.
This is the fourth or fifth time.
When I first came, I was deceived by Okinawa.
Why?
I went there first.
I went to Haimurubu Island.
I went to Akko.
When I first went to Akko, I had to buy souvenirs.
I didn't know what to buy.
I asked the local people.
Are you local?
After all, when I came to Okinawa, this was the only thing I had.
You were introduced to me.
I was introduced to you.
I thought about it.
What is it?
When I went back to Japan.
You're not good.
You're angry.
When I went back to Osaka.
I gave it to him.
He didn't like it.
The local people said,
This is amazing.
He said, This is delicious.
Did you eat it?
That's right.
What did you give him?
Chinsuko.
That's not good.
Do you like it?
Is that true?
I gave him that.
That's right.
Orion beer is delicious.
Beer is delicious.
Beer is really delicious.
I went to Okuma.
That's right.
I was only two people.
The manager didn't use anything.
That's right.
We were left alone.
It was hard.
That's right.
At that time, we became a couple.
What are you talking about?
When he got married, I was frustrated.
You were sleeping at that time.
What are you talking about?
That's right.
What about Okinawa?
We live in Okinawa.
What do you think about being invited to Tokyo or Osaka?
What do you think?
I don't like it.
But I understand.
Have you ever been to Osaka or Tokyo?
That's right.
What do you think?
Have you ever been to Osaka?
I have been to Osaka.
What do you think of Osaka?
What do you think of the city of Osaka?
It doesn't change much.
Don't lie to me.
Osaka is famous for Dengana and Mangana.
That's right.
When I was walking on the street, it was Dengana and Mangana.
What is Dengana?
What is Mangana?
I have been walking on Kokusai Street.
This street is called Chochune.
That's the word only Mr. Gushiken uses.
Is that so?
Everyone says that.
Chochune! Chochune!
That's strange.
I have to go to the hotel.
I don't know which way to take a taxi.
I asked the staff at the hotel where I should go.
He said Chochune.
That's true.
Don't lie to me.
He said Chochune.
I said it.
Please teach me how to say it.
I don't understand.
What?
Is this your program?
I don't know.
Can you talk?
You can't talk.
Please teach me.
Please remember.
Young people don't use the phrase.
That may be true.
The old man is angry.
What? What? What? Tell me.
Shirasundo!
What?
I don't understand at all.
What? Again.
Shirasundo!
Shirasundo.
What? What? What?
What?
Shirasundo.
Shirasundo?
I don't understand.
Shirasundo!
Shirasundo.
How do you say that? Shirasundo!
I don't think so.
In my image, there's a young wife,
and the husband comes home from work.
Ah, I'm tired.
Today is a little... Shirasundo.
That's just the way it is.
You don't have to say Shirasundo all the time.
I can't do it straight.
That's not what I'm saying.
Why do you always say Shirasundo when your husband comes home from work?
That's not it.
But the way I say it is different, right?
I'm a little angry.
I use it when I'm angry.
Is there anything else?
What?
Don't laugh.
Kusumaya.
What? Kusumaya?
What?
Kusumaya?
Kusumaya!
Don't talk to yourself!
Kusumaya.
Do you say Kusumaya?
Ah, Kusumaya!
No, no, no, no, no.
That's not it.
I don't think so.
What is it?
You know, the feeling of baseball.
That's not what you're saying!
No, no, no, no.
That's not it?
That's not what you're saying!
But you're a bad guy too, Kusumaya.
That's not it.
Kusumaya.
Itadakimasu!
Itadakimasu is fine!
Kusumaya!
Don't talk to yourself!
Ah!
What?
Are you crying? Are you angry?
It's not time to eat.
Poop!
What?
Poop?
Poop cat!
What?
What's a poop cat?
You're all looking down on me!
What?
Are you saying that I'm all dirty?
That's not it!
Then don't get angry!
I'm listening!
Why are you getting angry?
That's not it?
But you said it was poop.
You're all pooping!
Kusumaya.
Kusumaya!
That's amazing!
Seriously!
You're all pooping!
You're saying Kusumaya!
The people who are doing it are...
Sensei Naenae is doing Kusumaya!
Let's introduce the postcards.
Please bring the postcards.
Here.
In the middle.
What?
This is the queen of Awamori in Okinawa.
The queen of Awamori?
Awamori is a drink, right?
Yes.
Did you do a lot of things there?
A campaign.
You became the queen?
Yes.
That's amazing!
What's your name?
I'm Kuniyoshi Yuko.
Kuniyoshi Yuko?
Yes.
How old are you?
I'm 21.
21?
What are you doing now?
I'm a junior high school student.
A junior high school student?
Yes.
Do you do Kusumaya?
You're a star!
How many times a day do you do it?
Thank you.
This person is from Chiba.
Tanaka...
Bibari-san?
Mikari-san.
Lately, there are a lot of boys who come to learn the piano.
They're piano teachers.
Do you have any hobbies that you wanted to do when you were little?
A hobby?
A hobby.
I didn't do it.
But I did karate.
Really?
Even now, I'm confident in this.
What is it?
It's Go-kyu.
But this is a very strict style, so even Go-kyu is like a normal karate.
You have such beautiful fingers.
So I don't have a chance.
So even if you try to touch my body, you can't touch me.
I can't lose.
When the martial arts club dodges...
I can't dodge.
You're like a crane.
I can dodge sideways.
I'm Daniel-san.
What are you doing?
I was careless earlier.
Really?
Earlier, I came to Okinawa and my head was in a daze.
This time, it's okay.
You can't touch me anymore.
It's true.
When are you going to stop?
I can't make a comment.
If I was doing it too.
I didn't do it at all.
You didn't do it.
What is popular in Okinawa?
There is a special dance in Okinawa.
Everyone can do it, right?
I can do it.
I can't do it.
Everyone can do it.
I was told to do it when I came here.
Everyone can do it, right?
I can't do it when I'm an old woman.
The wrist is amazing.
It's like a grandmother's wrist.
I watch it every week.
By the way, I have a part-time job now.
Did you have a part-time job when you were a student?
If you did, what kind of part-time job did you do?
When I was a student?
We did a newspaper delivery together.
This is...
There was.
Was it the Ryukyu newspaper?
No.
Why did you come all the way from Osaka?
Every day.
No, it was in the evening.
It was when I was in junior high school.
I've been working since junior high school.
I did a lot of things.
Really?
When I started thinking, there was no key.
I did it for the time being.
Newspaper delivery.
Waiter.
Central market.
And newspaper delivery.
Waiter.
Central market.
It's a little different.
Newspaper delivery.
Hello.
I went to the market in the afternoon.
I saw a lot of strange things.
There are a lot of things that you can't buy in Osaka.
That's right.
There was.
I bought a lot of things in Tokyo.
I went to Okinawa.
That's good.
Why are you tired?
Also, the children in Okinawa are doing well.
That's right.
We would like to call in the audience.
The audience is...
Mr. Matsumoto from Anagasaki.
It's you.
Mr. Hanagata from Okinawa is waiting for you at the booth.
Last week, Mr. Matsumoto was waiting for you at the booth.
That's funny.
Mr. Matsumoto from Okinawa.
Don't repeat it.
Mr. Matsumoto from Anagasaki.
Mr. Hanagata from Okinawa is waiting for you at the booth.
He's waiting for you.
Please come to the booth on the second floor.
That's it.
I see.
I went to play.
I wasn't caught.
I wanted to see the scenery behind me.
I see.
I can't see it if it's dark.
I was looking desperately.
That's right.
I was found, but I couldn't see it.
That's why I did this.
I see.
I'm here.
That's all.
I don't think there will be any more endings.
I'll be in Okinawa again next week.
I'm looking forward to it.
As usual,
I'm looking for a postcard tomorrow.
The address is here.
I'm waiting for your postcards.
That's all for today.
Goodbye.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's hard.
A little more.
I'm tired of everything.
But I didn't lose a little.
Thank you very much.
I hope you'll continue to support us.
I don't have anything like this.
Thank you very much.