Don't touch me.
Coordinated Operation!
OK!
Awesome!
Today, we are in Jizodori shopping street in Tsubamu.
That's right.
This is the place called Grandma's Harajuku.
Is that so?
I heard that a lot of old ladies gather here.
They are looking for a place to die.
Also, I heard that a lot of old ladies shop in this shopping street.
Is that so?
Yes.
That's why we came here today.
Yes, I understand.
Coordinated Operation.
Yes.
We will choose our clothes.
That's right.
Let's choose.
OK.
Each of us will bring 30,000 yen.
We will go to the store.
OK.
Then, we will go to the fashion show.
That's right.
OK.
Let's go.
I think so.
I can see my friend.
What do you think?
I see my friend.
Good, good.
What is it?
I do not know.
Then, buy a hat.
Oh, that's fine.
But, this hat is fine.
You know..
But, That kind of design...
Oh, Oh...
It's tough.
That's nice.
I do not know.
What's this?
That's nice.
This is good.
It's nice.
Yes.
It's nice, is not it?
Why?
I really found out about it.
Excuse me.
Wow, this hat looks like you've done something.
It's selling well now.
These clothes are selling well now.
Even adults can wear this.
No, you can't.
Why not?
You can wear this.
I'm a child.
How old do you think this is?
I don't know.
You look like a 23-year-old kid.
It's okay.
You look like a kid.
What is this?
Hip-hop.
Hip-hop?
I'm definitely going to buy this.
You've done it.
You've chosen a cool outfit.
I've done something amazing.
What is it?
The theme is one-piece.
First, Hamada-kun will change your clothes.
When you change your clothes, make sure you don't look.
Keep your eyes closed.
When you come out here and stand here,
you'll see my naked body for the first time.
It's not naked.
It's naked.
I want you to see my naked body.
Here comes the fashionable Hamada-kun.
Hamada-kun, go ahead.
The theme is one-piece.
One-piece.
Mom, help me.
This is my theme.
Please open your eyes.
Go ahead.
What is this?
I'm curious.
This is for two-year-olds.
Tell me one thing.
I'm an eight-month-old kid.
Take a look at this.
This is for one-year-olds.
Thank you.
My theme is
what kind of person are you?
Please come out.
Go ahead.
Open your eyes.
What is this?
Is this for sale?
It's a chandelier.
What is this?
He is very energetic.
His legs are
very strong.
He is like a chandelier.
Yes, he is.
Hamada-kun, you look tired today.
No, I'm fine.
I've been doing this for a while.
I'm tired enough.
But you are doing this.
You are like a big-time athlete.
Why can't you be more energetic?
That's because
I'm not the main character.
I think
Hamada-kun is cuter than Taishu Kase.
I think Hamada-kun is cuter than Taishu Kase.
Well, I got it.
It's quiet.
What should we talk about?
I don't know.
What do you want to do again?
When I was in elementary school,
I wanted to be a police officer.
Really?
That's right.
You always said you wanted to be a police officer.
Why do you want to be a police officer?
Instead of being a police officer,
I want to wear a uniform,
a uniform and a uniform.
I want to wear that.
I want to be with you.
Hey, come here.
What are you doing?
That's my explanation.
Police officers
Why are you so arrogant?
When I do something bad, I can't help it, but you suddenly come to me from the first meeting, right?
So, when I was in high school, I was just riding a bicycle.
Hey, what kind of person are you?
Such a rude thing!
What kind of person are you?
I know you are Japanese, so what kind of person are you? I told you in Japanese.
You know that young bird, right?
They are all older than us.
Why do you say that?
They have grown up watching the sun, so they are always like that.
That's the generation. So, when they are walking like this, they are always like this.
Don't say that!
I don't know, but I think so.
I really think so.
Really?
When they are chasing after you.
That's right.
That's absolutely right.
When they are chasing after you, they are always like this.
When they have a headache, they are always like this.
I don't think you can do everything by yourself.
What kind of person are you?
I am the leader of the circus troupe.
Such a rude person.
Answer me seriously.
I really want to be a circus troupe leader.
How can you be a circus troupe leader?
I don't know that, so I quit.
What's next?
I want to be a kick-boxer.
That looks good on you.
I want to wear this.
Let's go to the post office.
What?
You have a bad breath.
It's cold, isn't it?
It's cold.
I want to wear a patch.
I don't think it's cold.
I don't say patch.
What do you say when I don't say patch?
What's that?
You're in trouble, aren't you?
I don't say long shoes.
You do.
How much did you make fun of me?
Do you have rubber boots or something?
They're weird.
I was watching the news and I got angry.
Himeji, Himeji.
Today is Himeji.
Himeji people say,
Hello, I'm from Himeji.
Oh, you're from Himeji.
He's weird.
He's Kanabun.
Kanabun.
It's Kanabun.
That's Kanegon.
What you're saying is Kanegon's pronunciation.
It's Ooyama Masayo's pronunciation.
It's Kanegon.
It's Ootteru.
I'm making fun of Osaka.
I think Osaka is a tough place.
I'm scared, I'm scared.
Osaka is scary.
Osaka is full of yakuza.
In Osaka, even for dinner,
they serve takoyaki.
You're making fun of me.
That's not true.
It's not as peaceful as here.
Well, yeah.
A lot of my acquaintances got beaten up and died.
It's true.
Right?
Who?
A lot of my acquaintances got beaten up.
It's true.
Tokyo has a lot of A-car.
In Mercedes or BMW.
Osaka is like this.
You can't come to Osaka if you're in a Mercedes.
In Tokyo, there are many big cars in the back of Mercedes.
They're going like this.
I can't do that.
I can't think of that in Osaka.
You should do that in Osaka.
I'll kill you if I stop at Shingo-maAPPLAUSE,
I'll kill you if I stop at Shingo-ma earnings.
I'll mess it up.
What am I supposed to do?
You should come out right away.
I don't know what I should do.
It's true.
Don't comeJust keep your feet behind if you like to do that.
You should step soon.
You can't leave me while I'm being beaten up.
Where are you getting kicked by me?
I don't catch you.
I don't like it.
I'm watching the children's show.
By the way, I have a question for you two.
Why do you call ginger as gari in a sushi restaurant?
Soy sauce is purple, so it's purple.
You drink tea at the end, so it's agari.
I got it so far, but I don't know what gari is.
Otare, please answer.
Gari, right?
Gari.
Don't you know?
What is it?
What?
I don't know.
No, no.
I don't know what it is.
You're an uneducated person, aren't you?
You have to expand your antenna more.
I'm going to judge whether what you're saying is right or not.
So if you have time like me, go abroad and see a lot of things.
I've never heard of you!
What is it?
Why gari?
I think I said it before, but everything has a name, right?
For example, this.
What do you call this?
Wagon.
This was made by a person named Wagon.
It was made by Christine H. Wagon.
What about the microphone?
The microphone is also a microphone.
It's called a microphone.
What's a microphone?
Mic...
Yoshida.
What?
What are you hesitating about?
Yoshida?
It's a microphone called Yoshida.
It was made by Nikkei Nisei.
That's why gari.
Gari is completely different from that.
You don't need to talk like that!
That's why.
Why don't you say gari?
What?
Why gari?
A craftsman often makes things short, right?
What's that smell?
Lemon scotch or Lesca?
What's a craftsman?
A craftsman makes lemon scotch, right?
What's that? A designer?
No, no, no.
Everyone says it.
Wait a minute.
A craftsman makes lemon scotch, right?
What's a dancer?
A dancing child is a dancer.
What?
That's enough.
What's wrong with Lesca?
That's why.
I've been told the same thing over and over again.
A craftsman makes lemon scotch, but Lesca is a dog.
I don't know if a craftsman is a dog, but that's enough.
That's why.
That's why gari.
What?
What does gari mean?
You can say it, but it's a long name.
I don't care.
What's the name of this gari before I omit it?
Gan.
Ectopic.
Sazan.
Fran.
Britannic.
Stone.
Myo.
Rumo.
Riri.
It's a long name.
I can't remember it at once.
What was it?
It's a waste of time.
I don't care.
What's this?
Can you say Kin-chan's Don?
I saw a very unpleasant scene.
That's Chibikko Uta Gassen.
Sing a song in the head of Mr. Shichi.
Bow slowly while closing your eyes.
Chibikko Yashiro Aki, who only thinks that he was forced to put on makeup like a child.
I can't stand it anymore.
Mr. Downtown, please do something.
There are many.
The parents must have pointed it out.
Basically, I don't like children.
There is nothing more useless than a child.
Everyone is getting tired of it now.
You were a little kid, too.
I've been good since I was a kid.
Is that so?
Yes.
Children.
It's stupid.
Suddenly, it's a crisis.
What?
Nothing has changed since then.
If you do this, I'll say something like this.
Even if I say something, I'm saying something.
It's stupid.
It can't be helped.
Even if I do it, I can't bite it at all.
It's childish.
It's still out.
Where are you going?
That is.
I really like Shimoneda.
Poop poop.
It's a song with a little bit of fushi.
Poop! Poop! Poop!
I have a boyfriend now, but he is a pervert.
You have a boyfriend?
I have a boyfriend, but...
You know it.
Read it properly!
Shut up, you idiot!
Where is the idiot?
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Shut up, you...
gold medalist!
You should be angry!
You dancing hippo!
I have a boyfriend now, but he is a pervert.
He told me to teach him English, so I went to his house.
But when I went into his room, he beat me up and beat me up.
He and I are still in junior high school.
He beat you up?
What kind of relationship should we have from now on?
What if he beats you up?
I think that...
If you resist, you can't do anything.
If you really resist?
If you really resist, you can't do anything.
There are lots of women, but if they are so badly beaten up,
you can't say,
No! Stop!
that's why you can't do anything.
It's more than that.
Men and women will feel like this.
Stop it!
You are already getting pheromones.
Men have to be able to act like that.
They don't have to look dirty.
If they are like that, they will think that it is okay.
That's right.
It's like this.
Right?
I've been liking this lately.
That doesn't make any sense at all.
I was walking on the street at night and I thought there was someone following me.
When I suddenly turned to the corner.
Wow!
I can't do it, but I can't stop laughing.
How do I explain this?
It's true.
It's absolutely necessary.
When I suddenly turned to the corner.
It's like this.
I don't know.
But I forgot how long I've been feeling this way.
You were in grade school, right?
No, I think it's earlier.
You think it's earlier?
Yes.
It's like this.
When you think of children, it's a big mistake.
When you go to the bathroom, there are those people.
There are people who are standing up with six people standing up.
No matter who says this, it's definitely a lie, but the old man is angry.
When I came to the bathhouse, I had a headache, and the old man was very angry.
He was shaving his hair at Bandai.
He was shaving his hair.
When he came, he didn't just sit on the floor.
He sat down and there was a place to flow.
He was shaving his hair there.
He said, there is no such thing.
What is this?
There is no such thing.
I think he had a fight with his wife.
Why did he have to shave his hair?
He was told to shave his hair.
What?
It's not like I'm a real bastard.
What is this?