In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai, it's time for the last episode of Showa
It's the 7th episode of World's Fair!
It's the 7th episode?
Are you still going to do it?
We haven't gotten married yet
We don't have to do anything
When was the last episode?
2 and a half years ago
It was Jaguar Yokota
He was beaten to a pulp
I thought I could do it
Heisei's Oliver-kun
It's the first episode of World's Fair!
Will Heisei be able to get married this time?
Today's star is Heisei!
Where's Heisei?
Heisei!
Don't treat me like a fool
I'm sorry
It's the 7th episode
I want to do it again and again and get married
Please decide today
I heard you have a plan
Actually, I have one
I want to sing and dance in front of everyone
I want to get married
You're biting the bullet
I'm sorry
It's fine
Singing and dancing!
I've been good at it
I'm from the disco generation
I go to the disco every day
If I can do it
How old are you?
I'm 48
48?
I want to get married before I'm 50
You've never been married?
You're still single?
I'm single
You're single?
You want to get married?
I've been married twice
But at the end...
That's a lie
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
Let's welcome the first girl
Please come in
Good evening
You're so young
Is it better to be young?
I like young people
Miyabi Kamisaki is 23 years old
She's always bright and beautiful
She's beautiful
Do you know Heipo?
I've only seen her on TV
What do you think of Heipo on TV?
She's an interesting person
She's not interesting
She's funny
I was surprised when I saw her
She's like soft vinyl
She's my favorite talent
Do you want to go to an amusement park?
I don't like rides
I have a height limit
Do you like haunted houses?
I want to go to Fushikura Island
Please take over
I don't think it's possible
There are many things
Please welcome Heipo
What is this?
What is this strange distance?
What is your first impression?
She's cuter than I thought
That's a good impression
Please talk to each other
It's a waste to talk to Heipo
It's a waste
You can call her your daughter
She's 48 years old and 23 years old
She has a cute voice
Nice to meet you
I'm Heipo
You are 23 years old
I'm 48 years old
Do you like older people?
When I think about marriage, I like strong people
You are strong
Why have you been alone all this time?
You are like a fortune teller
I'm a cheap fortune teller
What are your hobbies?
I like dancing
I don't understand this
I have a big dream
What is your dream?
That is
She has a strange voice
I'm not good at singing
Heipo is 50 years old and still alone
Heipo likes women and is afraid of ghosts
Her son is 20 years old
Her husband is married
She is still alone
She is making a lot of money
She gives her husband all the money
If she misses this chance
She will be in trouble
It's the end
Heipo, go Heipo
Get married
It's the end
That was great
The dancers were great
It was disgusting
That was great
That was a good kick
Heipo did his best for his girlfriend
That's right
Let's see
Why?
He doesn't like ghosts?
He is afraid of them
I don't think I can rely on him
Heipo failed
He did a good job
He danced well
It was great
I didn't feel anything
I was surprised
Let's have one more person
It was strange when he said the first person
Let's have a girl
Nice to meet you
She is 24 years old
She is beautiful
You know Heipo, right?
Yes, I watch it on TV
What do you think?
She is funny and I like her
It's not funny
You are mistaken
Let's have Heipo
What is this distance?
What do you think?
It's strange
I think it's good
Nice to meet you
How old are you?
I am 24 years old
Are you OK?
I hope we can have fun together
It's fun to go on a trip together
I haven't been there recently
I go to Paris every year
Really?
I like to spend New Year's Day in Paris
I haven't been to Europe
Let's go to Venice
It's nice
It's nice, isn't it?
It's over
You look like you are having a hard time
I often get a massage
I am good at massage
Let's try
I am good at it
Why do you play a monkey once?
I want to touch it
It's warm
It's nice
How do you think of a man who is good at massage?
You go to Paris and get a massage
I like to go on a date
I want to go shopping
Do you like brand stores?
Yes, I buy a lot of things
I live next to Roppongi Hills
Really?
I will give you a present
I am happy
What do you like?
I like money
You opened a beauty salon this year
I don't like beauty salons
Do you go there often?
I don't like it
Are you happy?
You have a good reaction
Do you want to go out with me?
I am a little nervous now
You don't hate it, do you?
I want to talk to you
I will invite you to the Hills
I want to cook
Do you cook?
I can cook anything
What kind of food do you like?
I like...
You have become so small
You did it seriously for the first time
This is fun
You are moving
What is this subtle feeling?
Is it over?
You did a good job this time
Did you watch the show?
Yes
It was good
It is better to listen to the half of the story
Let's judge
This is good
Please
What?
Why?
What is the reason?
You are smaller than I thought
Because of the size
You thought it was big
You shouldn't say that
Heipo failed again
You can go home
It's not over yet
I have something to think about
I want you to help me
I can't do it alone
I want you to do a musical with me
If you do it with me, the girl will fall
I have something to think about
It doesn't make sense if you fall because of me
If you fall, it's mine
What?
What are you talking about?
Please take a look
I will start
Oz's magician
You do this?
Yes
I can't do it
You can do it
I have already decided
Please take a look
The main character is Doroshi
This is Heipo
This is the most prominent role
By the way, Mr. Hamada Kakashi
Mr. Hamada is similar
Mr. Matsumoto Burikiga
Mr. Yamachan is the lion
Mr. Yamachan is good at lions
This is the first time
I thought you were good at it
The witch is Tanaka
Witch?
Yes, I want Tanaka to do this
This is the end
It's random
I'm confused
This member will go to defeat the witch
It will be like this
Tanaka will be defeated
Heipo will be defeated
It will be a happy ending
It will be like this
It's okay
Please do it
Heipo's life depends on Oz's magician
First, read the script
Mr. Heipo
It says to bring the witch to the pond
Will you fall into the pond?
I have a pond
You have to do it
I have to go into the pond?
Yes
It's annoying
Why?
I don't know
If you get wet in the water, you'll be in trouble
Take good care of it
Next, the dancers
They learn the choreography
Mr. Hamada
Mr. Kakashi
I'm dancing
I'm the best
It's not that movement
It's coming
The witch is coming
Please
There is no monkey
We are here to defeat you
Don't laugh if you defeat the witch
It's weird
It's like this
It's harder than I thought
It's hard
I'll practice
I'll call the teacher
Mr. Hamada, please do it
Why am I the only one who says it?
The practice begins
In order to get the happiness of marriage
He has been practicing for more than 20 years
He is teaching the magic of Oz to the five artists
Mr. Hamada, please do it
I'm doing it
It's weird
It's like this
What should I do?
It's not that I slipped
It's not that
Yama-san, you said it clearly
Yes, I said it clearly
Let's do it
Is it okay?
It's okay
It will be decided
It's the happy ending of the flower
The happy ending of the flower
I'm happy
Please come out
Sakura-san is a glamorous beauty with a cute smile
Who is the type with economic power?
I'm a student
I want to get married as soon as I graduate
Heiko-san has a lot of economic power
I'll go to the student
The student is okay
What do you want to ask?
What is the most expensive gift you have ever given to a woman?
I like women's necklaces
I gave about 500,000 yen to two or three women
It's amazing
Yes
What do you do on your days off?
I don't go out much on my days off
Then
Come to my house
I've lived here for 10 years
I don't do anything
You really don't do anything?
Don't worry
Even if I do something
You will do it
I'll take responsibility
Please meet my parents
Suddenly?
Let's start with friends
Let's go to defeat the evil witch
I am the witch of the west country
Do you want to give me something?
We came to defeat you
Don't make me laugh if you defeat the witch
How about that? Be prepared
Come on
You can't defeat me
Are you okay?
Leave it to me
What can you do to a little girl like that?
I know your weakness is water
I'll throw you and your daughter into the pond
It hurts
Please marry me
That's fast
Why?
It's better to be a little more modest
It's too much
Heipo failed
It was cold
Let's go home
Please do it again
What are you doing?
How about me?
Let's go home
It's over