I don't want to say this at the end of the year, but really, in the true sense, aren't you going to quit?
Eh?
Ah, Yamasaki
Yamasaki
No, I've been doing this for 14 years
Why do you have to quit?
Even if I quit in this world, I'm still a kid
Please be quiet
I've been sleeping since the second time
No, no
It's said that this is the worst period after the war
Ah, it seems like that
Are you going to continue doing this?
I'm a gyara thief
Why are you a gyara thief? I'm doing my best
What about you guys?
I've been doing this for 5 years
Before I was called, I thought I didn't need it since I was watching Gaki
I thought of it when I was a winner
If I quit, what are you going to do?
Who's going to fill my hole?
You can't fill it, right?
The hole called Yamasaki Hosei
No, there's no hole
The hole is like this
I have one person
I think this person is different
Who is it?
Muragami Shoji
Shoji-san
Shoji-san is really amazing
When he was cornered, it was like an explosion
He said something that surprised me
For example, this tissue
He asked me to do something with this tissue
He said something that surprised me
This is strange
But if you do that
Can you do it?
I can do it
Really?
I've been doing this for 14 years
I can't believe you did that
It's amazing
For example, this
The tissue is handed over
Like this
Take it off
It's broken
I can't take it off
Pia-chan
It's funny
I think it's better if Shoji-san does it
Shoji-san is not like this
Can you do it?
I think I can do it
I don't know
But I think Shoji-san can do it
Shoji-san is not like this
Eat properly
I think I can do it
I think Shoji-san can do it
This program is brought to you by a brand sponsor
I can't do it
I'm sorry
No
But
I told you I can do it
Why?
But I think I can do it
Really?
Then you
I think you can do it
This is difficult
What are you going to do with this?
If you tell me with this
Can you do it?
I can do it
What are you doing?
But if
If Shoji-san is here
It will be like this
Huh?
Can you do it?
This is difficult
Um
You can do it
This is difficult
Anything can be done
That's right
There are many like this
This is good
I don't know
This is
I can't do it
This is amazing
I wonder if Shoji-san can do it
You can do it
In the past, when I went to the kitchen once
There were a lot of things
Now this is just this
There are things like this
You're good at it
For example
Tokkuri Seita
Tokkuri?
Yes
Tokkuri Seita
You wear it like this
The moment your face pops out
I'll just say something amazing
You're good
Really?
It's probably like this
Um
This is amazing
What was mouths like?
No
For example
There are slippers
If you don't say slippers
Well, there are quite a lot
Well, there were many people in the past
Take this
That's a lot of tricks!
Endo, that's too easy
It's completely different
It's too easy
But, maybe...
If it was Shouni-san, it would be like this
Shouni-san's room
Coffee and...
One
That's amazing
It's amazing
It's still on, right?
The scissors and sandals are still on
That's amazing
It's amazing
You can do anything with two people
That's right
I think you can go to places where it's impossible
For example, something that looks like this
You're wearing it
It can't be
Something that looks like this
The scissors and sandals are completely different
It can't be
I think this is a call
What?
Hey!
Who is it?
Hmm?
Well, well
This is for editing
That's right
You know
It's not just one person
It's like
Even when you're with an amateur, it's explosive
You can do that?
Even when you're with an amateur
I've never seen anything like that
For example, when you go to the hospital and the doctor says you have a cold
The response is amazing
There's no such thing as an interesting response
There's no such thing
Because the doctor says you have a cold
That's the end
If you do it, will you do it?
Hmm, you have a cold
Don't say stupid things
You're a very good student
You have the same eyes as me
When you say a person
It's like a room runner
It's noisy
The person below
It's noisy!
It's angry
When it's angry
The response is amazing
If it's interesting
You can avoid the people below
It's funny
I'm nervous
It's angry
It's funny
But this is
I don't know
Shut up
I'm not in the goal yet
Wait
It's angry
It's the opposite
I see
I'm not in the goal yet
And it leaves with the angry residents
That's the calculation
You live here
We went out together
It's normal to go out
We went out earlier
You know
It's a normal thing
You go to a sushi restaurant
You ask what you want to eat
It's hard
Welcome
It's open
What do you want to eat?
Tetsubo
It's amazing
Right?
We took you to a sushi restaurant
It's amazing
What do you think?
I think it's amazing
We didn't do that
It's strange
It's a catch
It's not realistic
It's not
Next
It's amazing
You can't say anything
You're scared
You're surprised
You can't say anything
I don't know what to do.
You were cold last week, weren't you?
I didn't have a fight.
The final words...
After all the fighting...
But...
I think it's amazing.
What if it's Yamazaki?
Do you want to imagine it?
Wait a minute.
That's right.
What if it's Yamazaki?
Yamazaki and a 2 meter tall black man...
Wait a minute.
Is it like this?
Really?
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
I quit.
It's been about three weeks since the talk.
Is that so?
I haven't done it for a while.
I'm not feeling well.
Are you feeling well?
I'm not feeling bad.
I'm not feeling bad because you're feeling bad.
I feel like I've accumulated.
What?
What you ate.
And...
It smells so bad that I can't laugh.
I'm so angry.
When I'm angry?
When I'm angry.
It smells bad when I'm angry.
It's four times as bad as you think.
It smells bad.
I feel like my nostrils are closing.
It smells so bad that I don't want to go to the bathroom.
Why don't you go to the bathroom?
I have to go to the bathroom.
Have you ever been to the bathroom?
I have.
I've never been to the bathroom.
I've been to the bathroom every morning.
Really?
Yes.
Why?
I'm trying to live.
No doubt.
I don't want to be late and die.
You want to live.
I want to live.
Really?
One of us will die first.
One of us will die first and one of us will go to the funeral.
We can't die at the same time.
That's right.
When I was asked by a reporter, I wanted to be on the EU side.
I don't want to go home.
Kiyosu said that.
I'm a little embarrassed.
He was always angry.
Why are you so angry?
I don't know.
I know everything.
I used to work part-time as a judge at a track and field competition.
I have a question for Matsumoto.
Where do you sell the stick?
Please tell me.
It's a simple question.
Where do you sell it?
Please tell me.
To be honest,
I don't sell it at the store.
No.
There is a high jump.
It's not a stick high jump.
What do you call it?
It's a running high jump.
You have to enter from there.
For example,
We have a car license.
It's a temporary stage before that.
What?
It's a running high jump.
So
A person who has gone to a certain level of running high jump
Can't go to the stick anymore?
It's completely different from what you do.
It's the same as jumping.
So, it depends on whether you can go to the stick or not.
It depends on whether you can go to the stick or not.
The name is Kanzaki.
Kanzaki is a stick.
I don't know if the stick is good or bad.
What are you talking about?
There is a man.
There is a man in Sumo.
The owner of the stick.
The owner of the stick is decided by the five of us.
So, Kanzaki says,
Bring out the stick.
I don't know about Kanzaki.
I just say it.
Who is it?
Shinohara.
Shinohara says,
Bring out the stick.
Thank you very much.
You can fly or not.
I want to do this.
Shinohara flew.
You did it.
Next is the stick.
What did Shinohara do?
You can't say this on TV.
An amateur shouldn't have a stick.
What?
What did Shinohara do?
Shinohara?
Tomorrow morning,
There is a person who comes to sell secretly.
Don't miss it.
And,
Shinohara is sleeping.
Did you start from there?
It's about 7 o'clock.
It's 9 o'clock.
It's about 9 o'clock.
Throw the stick.
I think this is just a stick.
Think about it.
Where is the person who sells only a stick in this big city?
That is a camouflage of a stick seller.
Really?
Really.
He goes down to the wallet.
Excuse me.
Is it a stick seller?
The person who was pretending to be a stick seller
He asked me.
Then,
He goes down.
It's about 9 o'clock.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching!