The second trial
From now on, we will begin the second trial, the light trial.
Now, the judges, judges, and the jury, please enter the court.
The defendant, Saito Toshihide.
Not only as the chief director of Gaki no Tsukai,
but also as the chief editor of Gaki no Tsukai, he has created a lot of laughs,
but his true nature is that he is a very timid person,
such as a coward, a liar, and causes a lot of trouble to people.
Therefore, he was sentenced to a light trial and was sentenced to a sentence of imprisonment,
but he still seems to be without showing any signs of regret.
This time, he will be put on trial again.
From now on, we will begin the second trial, the light trial.
Mr. Onuma, who is over there, will be put on trial again.
I would like to make a declaration here.
Is that so?
Before that, I wanted to say something.
The chief judge.
Actually, I came here by bus today.
The third trial, Mr. Onuma Akihiro will be put on trial again.
However, this time, the second trial, the light trial will be put on trial.
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
Prosecutor Hamada, please present the evidence.
Yes, this time as well, as in the last time,
we are doing a VTR of various evil deeds of Heipo.
First of all, please take a look at this.
This is an incident in the rehearsal of a local program produced by Heipo.
I would like to start the rehearsal.
Mr. Shomei, are you ready?
I'm ready at any time.
Then, let's start the rehearsal.
First, two MCs will appear.
And then,
the rehearsal will proceed smoothly.
I'm late again. I'm sorry.
But suddenly,
What is this? This dark Shomei.
I can't record a TV program like this.
This is the reason why the MC is always a minor.
Who is the person in charge of Shomei?
Whether he appears or not, Heipo is angry with the darkness of Shomei.
You?
Why is the Shomei so dark?
No, it's the same as usual.
That's not true.
My eyes are not a hole in the wall.
It's dark. It's completely dark.
Heipo, who gets angry with more energy,
and at that time, there is only one AD.
Um, Saito-san?
Sunglasses...
Sunglasses?
It's bright.
It turns out that Heipo was angry with the darkness of Shomei through the sunglasses.
Yes, yes, yes, shall we go to the main show?
He is the worst man.
Now, the judge, there is a witness about this.
I understand.
The witness, please come in.
Nakamura Yoshinobu.
Um, the AD found the sunglasses.
Well, he knew it.
However, as usual, he laughs and deceives.
There is no apology.
And Shomei-san was a little angry.
That's why.
We went and apologized next to him.
This glass was expensive.
What is that?
I don't know what you're talking about.
This is the second trial.
Don't mess with me.
Well, that's true.
What I want to say is that such a thing,
why do you wear sunglasses?
Basically.
It's not a talent.
It's not a skill.
But it's ugly.
It's a small man.
It's ugly.
There is a reaction.
Actually, the recording of this local song was done in Alta.
Then there was a young girl down there.
She was stabbed in the face.
Really?
It's ugly.
It's annoying.
Do you believe it?
Really?
It's true.
Well, Yoshinobu said it,
but if you wear sunglasses and notice that you made a mistake,
I'm sorry.
I forgot.
You can make an apology.
I said this in the last trial.
You can't change what the director said.
You're completely wrong.
You're wrong as a person.
It depends on who it is.
The belief is...
That's the same thing.
Let's watch the next VTR.
A staff came to the cabaret at the end of a certain program.
There was also a figure of TETSURO DEGAWA.
Then HEIPO was there.
We are the treasure of the staff.
We can't make a program without a talent.
We are the staff with talent.
No way.
I'm ready to do anything for you.
Don't worry.
For some reason, HEIPO said he was passionate about his talent.
And the show ended.
DEGAWA, come here.
And then...
It's DEGAWA.
It's really DEGAWA.
DEGAWA is here.
A group of bad-looking young people came to DEGAWA.
Do something.
Hey, you guys.
Let's talk.
DEGAWA's manager tried to stop them.
But...
Shut up.
It's not a big deal.
A group of young people came to DEGAWA.
Help me.
DEGAWA was in a big trouble.
But the staff tried to protect DEGAWA.
But HEIPO said...
Hey, taxi.
He stopped the taxi and went back to the hotel.
Really?
There is a violent incident.
It's scary at night.
It's really bad.
After that incident, I asked Yamada-kun.
Yamada-kun tried to help me.
But he was stopped by SAITO-san.
He said, don't get involved. Let's run away.
And then he got on a taxi and ran away.
I'm disappointed in him.
And the other thing is...
I think all the talents are in trouble.
When I go to an edgy bar...
I want to go, but I use a talent's name.
DEGAWA wants to go.
We're in trouble.
If you really want to go, use your own money.
Please go alone.
Please.
Do you admit the truth?
I admit the truth.
That's the worst.
Why are you laughing?
What do you mean?
Please tell us.
Because it's scary.
That's the worst.
When I stopped the taxi...
I wanted to get Tetsu-chan on the taxi as soon as possible.
If you do that, the scary guy will chase you.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
I don't understand.
This is the story when Heipo went to Osaka.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I came to Osaka.
Do you know there's a good cabaret in Osaka?
I heard that the number one there is really cute.
Really?
After all, a director has to be with a good woman.
Let's all go together.
Heipo, who had been wanting to make a girlfriend in Osaka for a long time,
appointed her as his girlfriend as soon as he entered the store.
Number one, please.
And the woman who was appointed sat next to him.
I'm Saito, a child care worker from Tokyo.
As expected, number one is cute.
I've been to Osaka twice a month, so I look forward to working with you.
Heipo liked her very much, but after a while...
Ai-chan, I've got an order.
I'm sorry, I was called.
The popular girl left the seat immediately.
Then Heipo...
Number one, please.
He appointed her.
I can only be number one.
I hope you don't come soon.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm Saito, a child care worker from Tokyo.
I've been to Osaka twice a month, so I look forward to working with you.
Ai-chan, I've got an order.
I'm sorry, I was called.
Again?
You're as busy as me.
Saito-san, shouldn't you appoint someone else?
What are you talking about?
I'm number one in Tokyo.
Number two doesn't match me.
I'm sorry.
Number one, please.
Heipo called her back several times after she left the seat.
But after that...
Ai-chan, that customer is calling you again.
Again?
This is the fifth time.
Heipo didn't even notice that the girl was bothering her.
Number one, please.
I'll appoint her.
Understood.
Please appoint her.
Okay.
I've been to Osaka once every two weeks.
I go there with Saito-san.
At that time, I was asked who the number one was.
So I came.
At that point, I was like Onogori-san.
I came, I came, I came.
Wait, why are you all so good?
We're all good, right?
If you can't do that, you can't be a staff.
I heard a loud voice from around me.
When you go to a store like that and stand there,
you say that you wanted to be there more, right?
That it was fun.
I see, I see.
But I don't have time for that.
So I repeat it over and over again.
So when I look around me,
I can see that the third time around,
the girl is a bit attracted to me.
That's right.
Are you misunderstanding?
I don't know.
Hikoku.
Yes.
Don't you notice it yourself?
That you're attracted to her.
No, I'm not attracted to her.
Do you only like the number one?
After all, there's a difference, right?
Difference.
In that sense,
if it's a girl like this, it doesn't suit her.
Where does your confidence come from?
That's why soap is good.
Yes.
If you like the number one, it suits you.
Yes, yes, yes.
But soap is not interesting.
So-called.
You don't like soap very much?
No, I went to the 20s a lot,
but about twice a week.
I think that's a lot.
At that time.
It's more than a piano class.
It's really thin.
It's not thin.
Is it still a fuzoku?
That's a story from a dozen years ago,
when Keipo went to fuzoku with Suga.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's refreshing.
After all, fuzoku is good.
I work hard and play with my cute sister.
I'll get to Vector Myoujin.
Right, Gass?
Yes.
But today's child was cute.
I gave her a name card without thinking.
What?
Did you give her a name card?
What are you doing?
A name card is not just an individual thing.
It's a sacred thing as a journalist.
You can't give it to her.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Recently, Vector Myoujin will soon be in the industry,
so please proceed with caution.
Please.
And the next week.
You did a good job today.
Gass, let's go play.
Speaking of Heipo's play, of course, fuzoku.
The two who got a job came to the fuzoku store as usual.
Welcome.
Is the customer going home from work?
Yes.
What kind of work are you doing?
It's a TV relationship.
Wow, that's cool.
Then, do you know this person?
He seems to be a pretty famous person.
The person who was offered in front of the store was Heipo's name card.
While saying such a great thing,
Heipo was handing out name cards at various stores.
My name is Saito.
Then, the most difficult one.
The witness.
I understand.
The witness, please enter.
That's a manga.
This is the current VTR.
The first witness, Mr. Suga.
Yes.
This is also pretty cool.
This is not the current VTR, but the name card incident.
Yes.
It's the same as before.
Really,
that person is not a journalist.
That's why you're not a director G-man Ichi.
That's what I was told.
If you're told that, you'll die, right?
Yes, that's right.
Heipo, I'm sorry,
but the other day,
the place I went to yesterday,
your name card was there.
What do you mean?
No, it's important to be a director first.
It seems that he's in the jail.
That's the worst.
I don't understand.
What do you mean?
What's your reaction?
People's talk makes me angry.
Somehow.
So I don't want to make it so.
Especially around me.
You're giving it to people, right?
You want to have a good name, right?
I say it with a face that I'm good at.
I was very angry.
So I just said, why are you giving me a name card?
But if you're giving it to me, you've had a good name, right?
I'm good.
It's strange.
Because when it started,
I said, let's go to Seikan.
I don't feel like getting on.
When the door closed,
I heard the sound of a pink rotor.
Here you go.
One night,
Heipo was drinking and walking alone.
He was so excited.
Then...
Ouch!
Who are you to play with me like this?
I'm sorry.
Where are you looking at?
I'm Heipo, the servant of a kid.
What are you going to do if I get hurt?
That's why I don't like it.
As soon as he realized that he was weaker than him,
Heipo, who started shouting like a thief,
left the scene without realizing that he had lost his name card.
And the next day,
Heipo got a call on his cell phone.
Hello.
It's Saito.
Are you Saito, the servant of a kid?
Yes.
What can I do for you?
It seems that you gave a big discount to my acquaintance last night.
What? Last night?
Yeah!
I'm going to go over there now and make you pay for it.
Wait for me.
What?
No, please don't.
Suddenly, Suga appeared on Heipo's phone.
Hey, Heipo, what's wrong?
Mom, I'm in trouble.
Heipo told Suga about what happened.
Heipo said it was okay.
If you think it's okay, tell me.
Ah, I'm going to change my new friend, Suga.
What?
Heipo, who couldn't say a word,
suddenly put his cell phone on Suga's phone.
Suga said,
Hey, don't be so sad over the phone.
If you're coming, please come.
I don't care if it's right now.
Ah, Gas.
If you say that, you'll really come.
What are you going to do?
After that, Heipo...
Excuse me.
Please knock.
Heipo, who screamed and was scared by a little sound,
called Suga and Kobayashi and asked them to be his bodyguards for three days and two nights.
I did something stupid.
Let's do it one more time.
The witness, please come in.
I'm Kobayashi, who appeared in V.
Yes, yes, yes.
Suga was there, too.
Bodyguards.
The two of us.
Yes, yes, yes.
So, how was it?
It was a little bit like a big brother on the outside.
Otomo was an AD at the time.
Heipo in the editing room said,
Excuse me.
He took the tea and said,
What are you doing?
What kind of education are you giving to your parents?
Knock on the door.
Next time I knocked, I knocked again.
What are you knocking?
There's no way he'd come to the company.
I'm scared of the sound.
I thought a man came.
I just knocked on the door.
That day, Kobayashi and I came to the company by car.
He said,
I'm scared, I'm so scared, so please stay with me.
Let's go for a drink.
I and Kobayashi said,
Let's drink and go home by taxi.
We went for a drink.
Kobayashi and I were drinking.
He kept silent for about 30 minutes.
He said,
I'm scared, I'm so scared.
Heipo, it's okay, let's just drink.
Suddenly, like the part before,
He bowed his head and said,
You've done something stupid, haven't you?
Me and Kobayashi said,
Let's go home that day.
It's okay.
He said,
No, I'll definitely attack you.
Forcibly, he took me to a capsule hotel in Akasaka.
He said,
If you come, I'll go to the middle bed.
Please surround me with Kobayashi and sleep.
I'm so scared.
Did you say something to the person you hit?
That's right.
I was a weak guy, so I thought I could win.
I think I said a lot.
He kept apologizing.
What happened at the end?
I said what I wanted to say, so I let him go home.
What happened after that?
After that, Kobayashi was dragged away.
I was with him for three days and nights.
Please don't leave me alone.
I was with him all the time.
I thought it would be bad if I didn't go home on the fourth day.
I'm sorry I'm leaving today.
When I said that, Saito said,
Then I'll go home, too.
I can't help it, so I'll send you home.
Why are you angry?
I went to the side of the house.
I always walk from there.
I'm sorry, but there's a suspicious person around the house.
Is there a car? Can you take a look?
I went to see him.
Who is Saito?
It's okay.
You can go in.
He's making a big fuss.
What's wrong?
A dog happened to pass by.
You're a dog.
You can't get out of the earth.
I found the person who called me.
Please come in.
Are you Saito?
Yes.
You're my friend.
I'll beat you up.
You're making a big fuss.
Yes.
What is it?
Please forgive me.
You're watching someone else's game.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Please forgive me.
You're making a big fuss.
I'm scared.
Please come in.
He's making a big fuss.
The defendant, Sougen.
I'll tell you the truth.
He's guilty.
That's right.
Everyone is very angry about this crime.
I couldn't laugh at the mini-prank.
The next day.
The victim was found dead.
This program was provided by the following sponsors.