Yōkan-kan
Yōkan-fusai wa nakayoshi da
Itsumo futari de mitsuyōkan
Yōkan no dana
Yōkan no yome
Yoru wa kuriyōkan
Ha-ha!
Well, everyone.
Well, that's it.
What?
Do you want to call it an industry term or an entertainer term?
Yes.
Well, the audience doesn't laugh that much.
Even if they laugh, they don't have the endurance.
It's like, ha-ha, ha-ha-ha-ha.
We say, well, today's guest is heavy.
Yes, yes.
Well, today's guest is heavy.
Hey, you said it first.
Hey, you're not here today.
You're fat.
You can't do that.
You're shiny.
I've been blowing.
You're really shiny.
When he said, I'm water and oil,
you definitely said, you're oil.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You shouldn't have made such a mistake.
No, no, that's not true.
Even though you're fat.
Shut up.
Well, there's a lot of things.
Let's do our best.
Let's do it.
What is it?
You seem to be very angry these days.
Who are you?
I'm not angry at all.
It seems that you want to say something about your master's lover.
Well, it's a rare thing.
I don't talk much before the show,
but Hamada came over and said,
I want to talk about my master today.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Give me some time.
I want two hours.
Ha-ha-ha.
I can't give you that much time.
Here you are.
I can't say anything.
Don't you have anything to say?
I don't have anything to say.
That's right.
It's okay.
I can't use this kind of story.
I'm serious.
I'm talking about Go Hiromi.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I want three hours.
Do you have more than three hours?
I don't know.
What's going on?
Nothing.
I don't want to talk about my master anymore.
Why?
The audience is dark.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's all in the show.
Really.
Don't drink alcohol.
You look like a bourgeois.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Who are you?
I want to invite a comedian to my house.
Shut up.
I saw a comedian today.
You shouldn't drink alcohol.
I went to see a comedian in Kansai today.
It's boring.
A comedian.
A comedian is no good.
It's like that.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
The person who was late today is this person.
Why are you booing at that time?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You're always booing at that time.
It's a fate.
This is good.
It's good to be fast.
The comedian is fast.
Don't drink alcohol.
You're late.
I'm not late.
I was late.
What time did you wake up?
1 o'clock.
What is the time?
I woke up at 1 o'clock.
It's boring.
It's disgusting.
Why is it disgusting?
I woke up at 1 o'clock.
It's cold.
My eyelids went up.
Your eyelids went up.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
This thin skin went up.
I knew what happened.
I was surprised.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Is it like this?
I really don't do my best.
Your neck will be scratched.
It's okay.
Why?
I like it.
I don't think it's hard.
I think it's hard.
Really?
If you move to another show, the show will collapse.
It's okay.
I talked too much.
Chef Matsumoto, who graduated from Hattori Cooking School with the highest grade in history.
Please tell me about the new standard of cooking, Akasatana, which is said to be more important than the basics of cooking.
Do you do the basics?
I do.
Please tell me.
I don't want to tell you today.
Sugar.
Salt.
Vinegar.
Soy sauce.
Why soy sauce?
Is it the standard of cooking?
Yes.
Is that so?
That's right.
Soy sauce.
Vinegar.
Miso.
It's Miso.
Is that all you know?
I can't forgive such a thing.
It's impossible.
I don't know who decided it.
I want to make a lot of money.
And I thought.
Please tell me.
Sashizusaso is about all the seasonings.
This is different.
I see.
Akasatana is about the tools related to it.
Is that so?
That's right.
This will be a great lesson.
What is it?
Please tell me the tools.
Tools?
Akasatana.
A net.
When you grill fish.
Without a doubt.
Can you grill fish without a net?
Why are you saying it again?
Just say it once.
Skin?
What?
Oh, oh, oh.
Kama.
Kama?
It's Kama.
You need a Kama to make rice.
Sa?
What?
Sa.
Just say it once.
Saibashi.
What?
If you don't have a saibashi, it will be too hot.
It will be too hot.
Saibashi, saibashi, saibashi.
Sa.
Ta.
What?
Just say it once.
Ta.
What do you think it is?
I don't know.
It's a net.
It's a tool, right?
That's right.
Ao.
I remembered.
It's a shelf.
A shelf?
A shelf.
Why a shelf?
When you can't use what you've said before.
A shelf is okay.
It's a shelf.
That's the point.
When you can't use what you've said before.
It's a tool, right?
Yes.
It's a shelf.
A net.
A Kama.
Saibashi.
A shelf.
Na-do.
Are you crying?
Matsumoto-san has the image of walking for 12 minutes.
Are you ready?
I didn't know that.
I'll do my best.
When you walk home.
Yes.
The part of the heel of the shoe often comes forward.
Matsumoto-san.
Whose work is this?
In the world, they say that there is no criminal who hates people and hates sin.
That's all a lie.
No matter what happens, there is a criminal.
There is a criminal.
I don't want to be a criminal if there is no criminal.
I see.
Even if you are said to be a genius.
In the end, it's a small pile of sins that humans have committed.
Right?
Hespo Kasparu.
I'm scared.
Tell me who did it under the shoe.
Let's say it in English.
I stopped speaking English.
What?
Who did it?
For example, a cat.
It's not a cat.
I know.
A cat did it.
I know if a cat did it.
I know if a cat came and did this.
But the answer is a cat.
It's not a cat.
Let's do it properly.
What is it?
I said it's not a cat.
This is a question for Mr. Matsumoto who defeated his father and entered the entertainment world.
Yes.
He says that he will surpass his parents someday.
Does he have a time to surpass his seniors?
This is difficult.
What do you mean?
I don't understand at all.
It's better to say it under the shoe.
You're not doing it properly.
I don't understand.
Why?
In the case of work, when a junior surpasses a senior, there is such a number of work.
That's right.
It's strange to ask such a question.
I think so.
I can't make a mistake like this.
I think it's better to say it under the shoe.
But there is no such thing as under the shoe.
There is no such thing as under the shoe.
I said that the rubber was loose, so I was walking.
Who is laughing?
No.
Wait a minute.
That's too honest.
What is your job?
Why are you here?
I'm just fooling around.
You can't say it loudly.
Say it out loud.
What is your attitude?
I'm scared.
Are you?
Yes.
I'm scared.
I'm so nervous.