You can't beat me!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
This is bad!
Put it in the bag!
Tie it with a rope!
Hold it!
It's stuck!
The water is weak!
A rope! A rope!
A rope!
I got it!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
You're so mean!
There are 15 more to see.
This is bad!
Now!
Here!
The water is weak!
What's wrong?
A rope!
Help me!
This is bad!
We have to fight back!
What do we do?
We have to run again!
Tanaka!
If you go that far, you'll get caught!
I can't do it!
The enemy is pretty much dead.
But you might not be able to do anything with this.
You might not be able to do anything.
Damn!
I can't do it.
Are you sure you want to do it?
5 seconds!
Are you serious?
Are you sure you want to do it?
Wait!
I can't do it!
Okay!
It's hot!
You can do it!
You're good!
I'm scared!
He ran away!
Run!
What are you going to do?
Wait a minute!
He's weakening!
Don't chase him!
Alright!
You can do it!
He stopped!
Wait a minute!
What are you doing?
You did it!
Good job!
What time is it now?
5 minutes and 59 seconds!
Alright!
You have to do it properly!
I'll do it properly!
Damn!
What kind of creature is that?
Ladies and gentlemen!
Well...
What can I say?
Takugai is really energetic, isn't he?
That's not true!
Everyone's in a good mood.
Even if you say that,
this is the last episode of this show.
Why?
Don't say anything!
I've been listening to your talking about Heisei!
Don't say anything.
You're so great!
You hate me so much!
So much that I'm ready to attack you!
It's you who really likes me!
It's been a while!
Long time.
The other guy finally flew out.
That's right.
He finally flew out.
He flew out in a hurry.
What's so scary about that?
I'm scared.
Is that so?
You haven't done it.
I don't think I'm scared of anything.
Do you want to do it?
No, I'm not. I don't mind doing it.
But I'm a completely unknown man.
What do you mean?
I'm a very alive man.
Oh, because you're a cowboy?
That's right.
I can do skydiving.
Oh, really?
But skydiving is something that people come up with.
I just don't want to do what people come up with.
So I'll do it if no one else has done it.
You don't have to do it.
So when I do it, I don't use a parachute.
Hey, Suga-chan!
I'll do it if you follow me.
I'll do it.
If you'll follow me, I'll do it if you want to see me do it.
I'll do it like this.
What's that?
It's like an acrobat.
The sky is amazing.
When I say, Matsumoto!
I'll do it like this.
You'll do it like this.
I'll do it if you want to see me do it.
But no one else has done it.
You don't have to do it.
But then, there's no art.
So I'll do it like this.
I'll do it like this.
But while we're talking, everyone's laughing.
But if you do it, it'll be cold.
I'll do it like this.
It's hard.
What's hard?
A lot of new shows have started.
How is it?
It's just that, right? The usual, stylish show on Mondays.
At 9 o'clock on Monday.
It's just that, right?
It's a big number.
There's nothing else.
It's just that.
It's a big number.
The other day, I thought I'd watch TV.
But there were only fools.
A woman reporter went to a good takoyaki shop.
There were two takoyaki shops.
There was a line of takoyaki shops.
A woman reporter went to the takoyaki shop and said,
It's delicious.
It's like cream puff.
Are you stupid?
You're praising food, but you're giving me food.
You're so naive.
A more stupid woman saw a beautiful scenery and said,
I want to see a beautiful picture.
What is that?
That's crazy.
What's crazy?
She's drawing a picture looking at the scenery.
That's right.
I don't even know which is which.
Don't say that.
It's like a firefly is shining.
It's not a good time right now.
It's beautiful.
It's like a firefly is shining.
That's right.
That's good.
It's exclusive to the drama you just watched.
That's enough.
It's already over.
Don't bring it back.
At this time of the year,
If you talk about the drama on Fuji TV,
I'm sure you'll talk about it again.
That's enough.
I'm following your instructions.
Why?
I'm being controlled by you.
Matsumoto, right.
Back, back.
I'm just moving.
What should we do?
Nothing.
Are you exercising?
I am.
What are you doing in the room?
Are you going to buy a training machine or not?
I've told you this before.
I'm promoting it on Teletalk.
Don't buy it.
I'm telling you it's dangerous.
It's for your abs.
It's here.
It's like a seesaw.
It's light.
That's right.
It's like this.
I'm holding it here with these two points.
If I do this,
It's going to shift.
It's going to be like this.
It's going round and round.
If you can go straight up, it's okay to go round.
I need a stopper.
I have to cut the stopper.
It's not good.
How much is it?
Mine is 5,800 yen.
It's cheap.
Why?
Buy a good one.
I'm going to the gym.
Really?
You're so cool.
You're amazing.
You're going to kill me.
Why?
I'm not going to kill you.
I'm going to the gym.
You have to move your body.
I'm wearing a bandana.
I'm not wearing a bandana.
I'm wearing a bandana and a t-shirt with a wrinkled sleeve.
That's a UCLA.
What kind of impression do you have?
It's cool.
Do you want to go with me?
You and I have different basic physical strength.
We have different quickness.
What do you mean?
This quickness.
I have the quickness of a rabbit's brain.
You're so slow.
Please ask Mr. Matsumoto to do the impossible-to-be-possible man.
Yes.
For one minute, try to make the viewer rate of the program the highest.
It says impossible-to-be-possible man.
For one minute.
It's okay.
It's not a big deal.
Really?
Please do it.
It's going to be hard.
If you raise it every minute, it'll be easier.
It's okay.
How high should I raise it?
If it's for one minute, raise it to 25.
Raise it to 25?
Okay.
I don't know how high it is now.
From here to 25.
Raise it to 25.
Is 25 okay?
How high is it now?
25.
If you raise it every minute, it'll be easier.
Okay.
Let's start.
Okay?
Okay.
Start!
Hey.
What are you doing?
You're cheating.
I'm not cheating.
I'm not saying that you're cheating.
Why don't you stop?
You said it was 21.
I didn't say that.
It's starting now.
What?
You said it was 21.
I didn't say that.
Really?
What kind of face did you make?
What kind of face?
Who are you?
Why don't you stop?
You've never raised it.
That's why Hamada is a ghost.
That's right.
As a producer, that's right.
Since 25 is there,
I can't stop it on purpose.
Who saw it?
It's going up.
It's going up now.
I thought it was going up.
I felt it.
I'm doing it again.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it.
It's going to be like this.
I should have done it.
I don't know.
I was so close.
But it went up.
Let's see next week.
How much did it go up?
It was short.
It went up 5%.
It went up 5% before the start.
1, 2, 3.
I don't know.
That's it.
It went up 5% before the start.
Of course.
It went up.
If it didn't go up, what should we do?
What?
Don't be stupid.
If it didn't go up, what should we do?
Of course it went up.
What do you mean by what should we do?
You have to do something about it.
You're angry because it went up more than 20%.
Wait a minute.
Is it 5%?
You said it went up 5% before the start.
You said it didn't go up.
But it went up 5% in that short time.
I didn't say that.
I said it.
You're so dirty.
But it definitely went up.
If it didn't go up, can the staff think about it?
I don't want to see Matsumoto-san's drawing on TV.
I want to do it.
Don't put your butt on it.
What's so funny about it?
What's so funny about it? I contributed to the show.
If it went down, you'll know the punishment.
It doesn't go down.
It goes up.
It does go up.
Why did you put your butt on it?
You said it went up.
You're so dirty.
It doesn't go down.
It doesn't go up.
It goes up.
It's a matter of whether it goes up or not.
That was a long time ago.
It was only a few seconds ago.
Can I see your drawing?
What do you mean?
I stopped it.
You stopped it.
Up to here.
Wait a minute.
Why did you put your butt on it?
That's all.
What's the punishment?
That's enough.
Stop using the speed.
I can't use the small one, either.
I want to play.
It's okay.
Let's think about it.
Everyone, that's all.
What the hell are you waiting for?
You are said to be the most important person in the entertainment industry.
You are the most important person in the entertainment industry, Matsumoto-san.
It's Jupiter, right?
If you were to propose to your girlfriend's parents, what kind of attitude would you have?
It's better to think that this person has a different attitude. It's a good attitude.
That's for rich people.
If they find out later, they'll be in trouble.
That's not true.
You're still a fool. You're a bonsai.
A good attitude means that you're a good person.
It's not that you're rich or that you have a piano at home.
It's your feelings.
I see.
It's not that your heart is empty. Your heart is a good person.
Understand?
Yes.
You should tell your parents that.
I see.
For example, what should I tell them?
For example, under the word, NOSHI.
I don't know.
I want an otaku's daughter to marry me. NOSHI.
NOSHI.
You're really crazy.
I'll make you happy, NOSHI.
You're really...
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
If you can't even do that, then you're NOSHI.
Ouch!
After you go home, tell them that my daughter is different.
In a different sense.
Don't go out with a rich man.
That's how it is.
What?
Ever since I went to Thailand.
And a handkerchief.
If you can make a handkerchief, then you're NOSHI.
What kind of school do you go to?
Well, well, well.
I want you to marry me, NOSHI.
If you get it out, then eat it like this.
Eat it like this.
Do you understand?
I want it to be big.
I definitely want it to be big.
Without a doubt.
The parents over there will be convinced.
Convinced.
How many times do I have to say it?
I'll say it as many times as I want.
The younger brother over there will also be convinced.
The younger brother will say,
Play with me, play with me.
I'll say, big brother.
I'm healthy and active, NOSHI.
The correct answer is,
I don't know, but it was beautiful when I saw it.
Dangerous, dangerous, dangerous.
Put it in, put it in.
Scary, scary, scary.
Now, now.
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
Your face.
Are you serious?
Are you checking it properly?
There was a strange sound.
It stopped, it stopped, it stopped.
It stopped.
Are you serious?
It stopped, it stopped, it stopped.
What kind of creature is this?
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.