In the first episode of Gaki no Tsugai Yaraen, Chikichiki Yamasaki presents Perfect Oekaki!
Today, since I'm the host, I'll be the host.
Now then, I'd like to introduce our guest.
Today's guest is downtown!
You're the guest!
Today, Yamasaki-san...
Oh, you're the guest?
That's right.
Thank you for coming today.
Please put a lot of them in your pockets.
Now then, let's get started.
Now then, let's explain the rules.
The 15 panels with the topic written on the back will be chosen by downtown to draw the picture.
After drawing all of them, the elementary school girl will have to guess what the picture is about.
Furthermore, as a bonus...
If you get 5 right, you'll get 100,000 yen!
If you get 10 right, you'll get 500,000 yen!
If you get 15 right, you'll get 100,000 yen!
I'll be giving you this as my pocket money.
You're lying.
No, no.
He's been saving up a lot of money lately.
He's been saving up money?
No way!
He has a house that's worth 60 million yen, so I'm thinking of buying it.
Really?
Yes, just one.
Now then, let's draw the picture!
First is...
Hamada.
Please choose one of the following sponsors.
Number 2.
Number 2!
Devil!
I can choose too.
Number 12.
Number 12!
Porsche!
I wanted to draw a Porsche!
This is terrible.
What is it?
Don't laugh when you're trying to draw someone.
Excuse me.
There's no more perfect.
No, no, that's...
That's right, there's no more.
I don't know about that!
Matsumoto is done!
Matsumoto, please show us!
The shape is...
What is this?
Let's take a look.
Hamada, here!
I drew a devil!
Let's continue.
Number 10.
Number 10!
A bag!
This is difficult.
A bag is difficult for me too.
Number 8.
Number 8!
It doesn't look like a bag.
What is that?
Matsumoto, please show us!
Was it wrong?
This is...
Hamada, please show us!
This is Hamada's bag!
This is...
Throw it away.
What is this?
This is terrible.
It's sold well.
Where do you live?
Don't laugh!
His face is cute.
Next, Matsumoto is done!
Matsumoto, please show us!
What is this?
It's pretty good.
Next, Hamada is done!
It's simple.
Number 9!
Hamada, number 9!
A ninja!
This is good.
Number 1!
Shishimai!
When Matsumoto was little, he used to draw.
Next, Matsumoto's Shishimai!
This is wonderful.
What did you draw?
I just saw it.
When he saw the bag, he looked like this.
Hamada is a ninja!
Next, Matsumoto's Antonio Inoki!
This is a great work.
Hamada is a foodie.
This is a service problem.
This is scary.
This is Hamada's foodie.
This is good.
This is like a slum.
Next, number 3!
Number 3!
This is good.
This is a service problem.
Number 6!
Number 5!
This is difficult.
What did you draw?
I think I can't draw a入り.
It's important to draw a入り.
I want to learn how to draw a入り.
I can't draw a bag.
Next, number 4!
I drew a wrong入り.
This is Matsumoto's drawing.
This is terrible.
This is difficult to draw.
I'm going to draw it.
This is Hamada's gun goddess.
This is...
What is this?
The student clothes are cut in half.
Something is stuck in my head.
This is a disco.
This is the last drawing.
This is Ryu's drawing.
This is an artistic drawing.
This is Michael Jackson and Gengoro's drawing.
This is my father's drawing.
This is Gengoro's drawing.
This is Hamada's drawing.
This is my father's drawing.
This is the last drawing.
This is Hamada's drawing.
This is Michael Jackson's drawing.
This is terrible.
What is this?
I don't know.
This is Moonwalk's drawing.
Look at this.
This is a napkin.
Now, let's welcome the answerers.
Please.
And the girl who will draw the two of them.
Hello.
What is your name?
I'm Ayami Kashima.
You are 9 years old.
Yes.
What is your favorite talent?
I'm Kimutaku.
Kimutaku.
Don't laugh.
Is there anything cool?
Do you like Downtown?
Yes.
Which one do you like?
Hamada's drawing.
Who is the cool one?
You still have a hairstyle.
I finished drawing.
I came here for the time being.
That's good.
I just said I had a hairstyle.
I don't think this is a good reaction.
I'm confused.
Are you done?
I finished one job.
You can't say that all the time.
I'm a producer here.
I was surprised at the end of last year.
Thank you for the year this year.
What is the end of the year?
I'm confused.
Hamada's hairstyle is popular all over the country.
You are the same age as me.
I'm the same age.
I have a handsome look.
Everyone is showing it.
It's hot.
Yamasaki appeared in the last episode.
It seems so.
He played the role of a gentleman.
Think about it a little more.
I said one word.
I said it about five times.
I don't know.
I just said one word.
Everyone is saying that.
I don't know.
I said one word.
Yamasaki did the same thing at ANPM.
He said,
Fresh bento.
He said it naturally.
It's terrible.
It would be nice if it was fresh bento.
He has savings.
Yamasaki is a great era.
He said he would buy a house.
It's terrible.
I asked him to come with me.
I asked him where he was going.
He said he was going to buy an adult's toy.
It's terrible.
He bought three toys.
I don't know.
I can't buy it.
I don't like it.
You can buy it.
I don't know.
I don't want to be attacked.
I'm going to buy a toy.
I have a lot of toys.
What kind of toys do you have?
For example, this.
What is this?
This is a black shirt and jeans.
It's easy.
What is Hamada?
This is an old jeans.
What are you talking about?
I'm just saying what I bought.
There are many.
From Hamada to Amura.
How many times have I said this?
Iijima Naoko.
I wrote this.
Naora.
I don't know what Naora is.
I don't know what Hitoshi is.
Hitoshi is looking down.
Everyone is looking down.
This year, everyone is looking down.
I don't want to say anything.
Ikeike, Kitsui, Bruta, etc.
I left a famous phrase that remains in history.
When you go on a trip to the moon and get off the moon, what is the phrase that remains in history?
This is a phrase that remains in history.
What should I say when I get off the moon?
Yes.
It's wider than I thought.
Who are you talking to?
Are you talking to the fish?
Wait.
You can say that.
You can't say that.
I'm sorry.
I've never been to the moon.
Wow!
What should I say?
Are you drunk on me now?
No.
If you were a questioner, you would have left a lot of questions.
When you get off the moon, what is the phrase that remains in history?
I see.
Can I say it?
Yes.
When you get off the moon, what is the phrase that remains in history?
I don't know.
I don't care.
Are you wearing something?
Of course.
I'm wearing space suits.
You can't go to the moon.
I'm wearing this.
You're wearing this.
It's transparent.
You can go down the stairs.
I see.
Speak!
You're wearing glasses.
I'm wearing glasses.
I spoke.
You're wearing thick glasses.
Whoever spoke, they were all like this.
There's no one where I am.
It's much like a manzai.
When my dog gets in the car,
he always sticks out his neck from the window.
Oh, I see.
I say it often.
He gets angry because it's dangerous,
but he never listens to me.
I see.
Why do dogs want to stick out their necks so much?
You're right.
Animals are like that.
You know a lot about dogs, right?
I know a lot about dogs.
I know why dogs are moving.
That's fine.
No, no, no.
What?
It's my job.
I get caught a little bit.
What?
Why are they moving?
Dogs have a heart, right?
Yes, yes.
Dogs have a heart.
Where does that heart go?
Here.
I know why this heart is moving.
And dogs also know what I know.
That sounds interesting.
So why do dogs walk like this?
I don't know.
What?
What do you want me to do?
I want you to love me a lot.
I don't want you to leave me.
I don't know.
I don't know why dogs want to stick out their necks so much.
How many years has it been since I started using dogs?
About seven years.
About seven years?
I've been waiting for this postcard for seven years.
It's not an exaggeration.
Why did you wait for such a postcard?
Why do dogs want to stick out their necks so much?
That's what I've been thinking.
Yes.
Why don't you let me talk?
Yes, yes.
Really, really.
I hit the wall.
But it's finally here.
It's finally here.
What's the answer?
What do you think is the best car?
What is it?
Rolls-Royce.
I think Jaguar is the best.
What is that?
Hey, I'm driving.
I'm not stupid.
Jaguar used to have something like this.
That emblem is a sign of Jaguar.
It's getting closer and closer.
Dogs are faithful.
I want my husband to think of Jaguar.
That was good.
I was about to lose sight of it for a while.
I finally caught it.
I think I managed to catch it.
What is this?
Think about it.
Put it on the microphone.
Really?
I don't know the name.
Oh my god.
Please answer.
It looks like a hippo.
hippo
The second one.
Be honest.
This one.
What is it?
Dracula.
I want it.
I want Dracula.
The third one.
Look at this.
This is pitiful.
Where is it?
Foreigner.
Like this.
What do you call this?
It's a dinosaur.
This is the correct answer.
The woman is getting bigger.
That's correct.
Ayami, how did you know this?
Where?
It looks like a ring.
What is this?
Next is Antonio Inoki.
Who is it?
Lupin the Third.
This is also his nationality.
It's not a castle, is it?
Castle.
Mazumos.
How about Michael Jackson?
I thought it was Zamos.
The seventh one.
How did you know this?
Dragon.
Correct.
I'm glad.
If I lose to Hamada, I'll...
Why did it take 32 years?
What is it?
The eighth one.
What is Machan's habit?
It's like a boar.
It's like a hippo.
It's like Moomin.
Don't eat it.
Ayami, how did you know this?
Ninja.
This is...
It's over.
That's right.
Mazumos, please.
Let's go.
If I win this...
Stop it.
Ayami, what is this?
This is...
A bag?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Why?
It's true.
That's right.
One more question and you'll get 100,000 yen.
Hamachan's A.
Slime.
Next, what is Machan's Porsche?
Sports car.
And Hamachan's...
Shokupanman?
Superman.
That was close.
This is Shokupanman.
I'm being laughed at.
And Hamachan's Gengoro.
Funkorogashi.
That was close.
This is the last one.
Okay.
If this doesn't work, I won't give you 1000 yen.
If you win, I'll give you 100,000 yen.
Okay.
Now, Ayami.
I think I know what it is.
Here you go.
Shachi.
That's right.
Good job.
Congratulations.
That was a good guess.
This is the result.
Hamachan got 3 correct answers.
Machan got 2 correct answers.
I knew it was a bag.
This is strange.
Why did you do that?
Funkorogashi.
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.
Takashimaya was arrested for violating the law.