High Tension! The Best Ten!
Good evening!
It's the beginning of the new year!
There are a lot of wonderful people here today.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, we're all standing here.
As a man, I was wondering why you didn't come to say hello.
I was wondering why you didn't come to say hello.
Oh, really?
I see.
You're such a bad senior.
Well, let's go.
High Tension! The Best Ten.
First, the 10th place is...
50 points!
Spartandy! Kogoriko! Tanaka Naoki!
High Tension! The Best Ten.
No, no, thank you, thank you.
Hello, Tanaka-san.
Good evening.
Spartandy.
Yes.
So, I wanted to cut off your education.
That's why I'm giving you this title.
No.
Are you doing it?
Well, the grammar is a bit...
Well, Tanaka-san, can I ask you a question?
Oh, yes.
I'm Ota Daisuke from Chiba Prefecture.
I'm in my third year of elementary school.
I love baseball since I was in elementary school.
I always play baseball with my classmates.
But no matter how many times I played, I couldn't hit the ball.
Everyone made fun of me and I cried a lot.
At that time, when I saw Tanaka-san's high tension on TV, I got a lot of courage.
The next day, I was able to hit a home run.
Well, how should I put it?
I'm aiming for the small kids.
So, I'd be very happy if you could give me such an opinion.
You're such an idiot.
Well, shall we start today?
Yes.
Please.
Well, in this way...
I'm aiming for the kids.
I'm sure you can hit a home run with such high tension.
Well, let's get started.
This week's 10th place.
Tanaka Naoki from Kokoriko.
Spartan D.
Thank you very much.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Well, time is running out.
Let's get started.
This week's 9th place is...
67 points.
Sad guitarist.
Animal Tei's Koala.
Well, Mr. Koala.
Do you like alcohol?
Yes, I do.
This is the famous sake from Niigata Prefecture.
It's called Koshinobairu.
This is very valuable.
This is...
If you like alcohol.
Can I drink this?
Please drink it.
Can I?
Thank you very much.
This is amazing.
This is a one-time drink.
One more.
I'm getting excited.
I can do it.
I got it.
Well, let's get started.
This week's 9th place is...
Sad guitarist.
Koala's Koala.
Thank you very much.
As expected, it's 9th place.
It's amazing.
This week's 8th place is...
Yes.
138.
Explosive soul's scream.
Amiagari Kestai.
Miyasako Hiroyuki.
It's 8th place.
It's a little different from the previous two.
That's right.
Miyasako-san, did you get married recently?
How is your marriage?
My wife's body is so soft.
I have a wide range of play.
Let's get started.
Thank you very much.
This week's 8th place is...
Amiagari Kestai.
Miyasako Hiroyuki.
Explosive soul's scream.
Thank you very much.
It's amazing.
The feeling of being approached.
As expected, it's 8th place.
Miyasako-san, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to throw away Ponpon.
I'm going to throw it away.
That's amazing.
Next, let's continue with 7th and 6th place.
First of all, this week's 7th place is...
151 points.
Matsui Gokuraku Tonbo.
Yamamoto Keiichi.
Next, 6th place.
183 points.
America's same Gokuraku Tonbo.
Kato Koji.
I'm Gokuraku Tonbo's client.
Actually, the two of you can't come to the studio today because of work.
We're shooting a VTR in advance.
I see.
Please take a look at that.
I understand.
That's right.
Yes.
Please appear.
I want to increase my tension.
I want to increase it.
I want to increase actually!
You won the award for YouTube heart right?
I took your heart!
Your heart!
Stop!
Stop! Stop!
Stop now!
Stop right now!
Stop!
Stop now!
Thank you
It was fun
The weather was good
Let's go to the studio
This week's 5th place is...
264 points
Last week's lonely battle animal team, Osaru
Thank you
5th place
Finally
Osaru-san, before you go to the high tension
You're good at the violin
Are you listening?
I'll show you
This is more interesting
This is wonderful
Thank you
But the next high tension is more wonderful
I'll do my best
I'm a very young man
This week's 5th place is...
The lonely battle of Osaru
Thank you
It was good because of the rhythm and tempo
It was good
This week's 4th place is...
359 points
6th place
Hodohara
Thank you
Hodohara-san, you don't have to go behind
4th place
359 points
This is unexpected
Please take a rest
It's very quiet
I'm looking forward to the high tension
This week's 4th place is...
Tai
Thank you
It was quick
It was interesting
It's difficult to get into the top
If you become a 4 member group, you will be able to do it
This week's spot light
Thank you
He hasn't been favored by many people
He was always in a side-side position
It's been a while
I thought a lot about the costume
I thought it would be a big hit
The moment I came out, I...
What to say...
Your face was about to cry
Really?
So this was a trick?
It was a trick.
I didn't know that.
You're treating me like a spotlight.
Please leave the spotlight to me.
I'll do something that will surprise you.
There's another one?
There's another one.
I'll do something that will surprise you.
I can't speak.
Then, the third one.
Why are you so relaxed?
I don't know.
It's like I'm ranked higher.
It's like I'm thinking of money.
Let's start.
This week's spotlight goes to...
Mr. Yamasaki, who ranked 18th.
It goes to...
Planet Race DiCaprio.
Hey, you!
Thank you very much.
Now, this one is ranked 18th.
This one is ranked 18th.
10th is a common number.
18th is a common number.
Now, the last one is ranked 3rd.
Let's start.
This week's 3rd place goes to...
375,000.
Human Genetic Power.
Water Torque.
I'm sorry.
I have to do three jobs for water.
That's not possible.
I can't come to the studio.
We'll watch it on VTR.
Excuse me, Mr. Hamada.
Mr. Hamada,
Mr. Hamada?
How are you?
Help me!
Because you don't have time,
We'll join you.
Let's go!
Is this 3rd place?
I think it's wonderful
Is it wonderful?
I understand
Let's go! This week's 2nd place is...
418 points
Hello, Kogoriko-san! Fujii Takashi!
Hello, Fujii-san!
Hello!
It's fun, so it can't be helped
That's right, Viva Jinsei!
Speaking of Fujii-san, I'm Yoshimoto Shinki
I received a telegram from a friend
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
If I slip, I'll go back to Osaka
Suenari Yumi-san
Yadayumi-neesan
Let's go to 3rd place
Thank you
I don't know about the tension, but let's go!
This week's 2nd place is Fujii Takashi
Hello, Kogoriko-san!
1, 2, 3, 4!
I walked looking for Kogoriko
Left and right, left and right
I'm glad to have met you here
You're happy and embarrassed
I'm happy to have met you here
One part of my body
Looking at his face
I think that's enough
Thank you very much!
This is wonderful
Let's go!
This week's No.1 is...
No.42
Ai! Hohohohoi!
Kogoriko! Endo! Shozo!
You...
You can't do that!
You have too much fat in your body!
It's completely different from when you're naked!
Really?
You're so fat!
You have a different face today!
Really?
You're so manly!
Your eyebrows are so thick!
It's hard to do it like this!
Just the face! If you pull it back a little...
Look! It's so hard!
Excuse me!
No.1 is...
Ai! Hohohohoi!
Let's go!
This week's No.1 is...
Do you know the samba rhythm?
Thank you very much!
That was amazing!
Endo-san!
As expected, you're No.1!
That was great!
The last move was good too!
To be honest, I don't know what to say from the perspective of the host...
I can't shake No.1 for a while!
Let's go!
Ai! Hohohohoi!
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
Like this?
Endo-san!
This is...
This is inevitable!
This is no good!
Why are you like this?
This is inevitable!
In this show
Sometimes a talent comes
And you suddenly understand it when you're talking
I was there then
You were there then
I felt like you were telling me to come up
Spice Girls?
You scared me!
Please give a song to Spice Girls and Mariah Carey
Yes
I'm very sorry but...
I heard Spice Girls are very popular
Who is that?
What?
You're doing a music program and you don't know Spice Girls?
What is Spice Girls?
It's amazing
I heard there are tens of millions of songs
Really?
I heard there are 9 million songs
What are you talking about?
I don't know
There are 90 million songs
90 million songs
Don't you think it's amazing?
Amazing
You're such a snob
Come here
You're so lazy
I don't care
When are you going to get up?
Get up
I'm very sorry but...
Yes?
I'm already bored of the talk show
That's how popular it is
I'm thinking of a new talk show with a new sound
But it's true that I'm bored
You too?
Please give me a new one
I'm already bored
Let's record
This time
I'll sing a summer song
Summer song?
I'll sing a song that makes you feel nostalgic
Please
I want a stand
I'm sorry, stand
I'm sorry
What are you laughing at?
Don't be silly
I'm sorry
I'll sing a song that makes you feel nostalgic
I'll sing it again and again
It's okay
I'm sorry
I was very embarrassed
You've already recorded the chorus, right?
Yes
I'll sing
My stomach is shaking
My love is shaking
I can't sing
It's okay
Really?
I'm sorry
I'll sing
My stomach is shaking
My love is shaking
I'm a taxi driver
What is a taxi driver?
It's an image
It's a taxi driver
I know
I'm a taxi driver
I know it's a taxi driver
No
I'll change the part
My stomach is shaking
My love is shaking
He's a taxi driver
This program was brought to you by these sponsors