You came all the way to Matsumoto today, didn't you?
Yeah, why did you come to a park in the middle of the night when it was so cold?
Oh, I see.
I didn't expect you to come all the way to Yamazaki.
Do you think I'll be able to sell?
If he comes here next time, I'll kick his ass.
What should I do?
You should just go home.
No, I'm not going home.
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?
In the entertainment world, there are two strong men who divide the power of the society.
They don't know the amount of blood they shed,
and the fight between the two men has deepened the conflict.
What the hell are you doing?
Stop it! Stop it!
They don't know what they're afraid of when they're cut off.
Yamazaki is the fastest to get cut off in the entertainment world.
He burns the flames of hatred.
Yotani Aimaniel
You haven't been on TV lately, have you?
I don't know.
You know, I'm choosing a job.
You know, don't choose a job at your level.
What the hell are you doing?
Even if you go on TV, the number of people who can't do it is increasing.
You don't know what they say over there?
It's a technical term.
What the hell are they saying over there?
That's not good. That idiot.
Isn't that the first time in your life that you've been cut off?
Don't say that.
Stop it, stop it.
Stop it
Which one is stronger?
I won't lose
Wait
Stop it
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
Yamazaki, you are amazing
What can you do?
I can...
I can put this cigarette on my back
What?
You can do that?
Put it on
Yes
Why did you say yes?
Why did you answer?
It's burning
My back is burning
Look
It's not burning
I can put this cigarette on my back
Are you stupid?
Right?
Look
Stop it
Why?
I won't lose
Really?
Yamazaki, you can't put this cigarette on your back
It's hot
It's a cigarette
It's frozen
It's like a spring
I will be more interesting than Yamazaki
Let's go
It's hot
It's cold
Yamazaki, you are amazing
What can you do?
I have a brain
After that
I will wash it with a firework shower
It's hot
My head is burning
Can I touch it?
It's scary
I don't have a brain
Yamazaki
You are teasing your juniors again
I don't do it because I want to
Thank you for saying that
One more time
I don't do it because I want to
Can you show us?
It's scary
Faster
It's sticky
It's too short to stay
I let Jimmy go
He stays until he stops
What are you doing?
It's a human
I did it
Look at the camera
Look at me
Jimmy
You do it because you like it
I don't do it because I like it
You do it
I don't do it
You did it
You came here
I didn't do it
I don't do it
It was long
You look like you are wearing a see-through
Look at me
I do what I do
Let's do it again
Look at this
It's a tank
You can escape with this
You can escape
Are you serious?
Yamazaki
Look at me
Speak in honorifics
Do you understand?
You are a senior
I did everything
I see
You are taking him
No
I don't do it
Do you understand?
I'm going
Who are you talking to?
You are talking to me
Issei
It's coming
Your face
It's beautiful
No
It's wonderful
You can't do it
What?
I went into the water
I went into the sleeping bag
I can't escape
Are you serious?
Yes
It's dangerous
I forgive you
It's the last time
Are you okay?
I'm okay
I don't know if I'll die
Don't worry
I'm sorry
I'm going to change my clothes
It's like a see-through
Jimmy
If you come with this
Yes
Don't use honorifics
I don't understand
It seems
Let's go
I can't escape
Your face is ugly
What are you doing?
We won
Really?
What?
Let's say we have the same score
Really?
It means we still have the same score
I don't know
We're going home
Bye
Remember next time
You too
Did you just say that to me?
Yes
It's a joke
Ladies and gentlemen
It's a little too early
Today is your first time in Seoul
Yes
I heard that
Why?
The truth is
The fool did it
He does it usually
He's a fool
Why is he like this?
He did it with his whole body
I see
I did a lot of research
You did research
Do you know what research I did?
Not at all
Genetic engineering
Recently
I couldn't solve it
I did a new research
What kind of research?
I can't tell you
Why?
I want to tell you
What kind of research?
I did research on comedians
I see
This is interesting
I did research
So what?
You can't tell me
I can't tell you
You can't tell me the result of your research
You can't tell me
It's an interesting movement
It's popular
What's popular?
It should be popular
I'm going to be called a fashion leader
I see
The result of your research
I don't know if I should laugh
It's amazing
A popular comedian
It's similar to life judgment
Has a poem
What do you mean?
Why does it have a poem?
His name has a poem
What are you saying?
Wait
You are a poet
Don't say that
I'm not the only one
A popular comedian always has a poem
There's no mistake
Why didn't you notice this?
Who else?
I'm a poet
This is
What is this?
I know
Hamada Masato
He has a poem
I don't know
Ask me anything
Who else?
Let's think
It's not a problem
Why?
Masato is a poet
There's a question
Where does the poem come from?
There's a poem
Shimada Shinsuke
Takeshi
Who else?
By the way, what's your zodiac sign?
It's G
It's G in April
Wait
It's G?
Of course it's G
You should have told me first
You are C
C is not G
I wanted to throw out this research
What are you talking about?
It's not
What's going to happen to Tamori?
Morita Kazuyoshi
That's his real name
I see
What?
Uchan Nanchan?
Uchimura Teruyoshi
That's good
What about Aikata?
What?
When I realized that
What are you talking about?
I thought
Nanchan is not included
Wait
Don't stop
What?
Aikata
That's why I thought
The combination
I don't know
It's okay
That's okay
If you do a combination
Everyone will be fine
There's nothing left
There's no G
There's no combination
There's no more
What about him?
It doesn't matter
It's not bad
Hiromi
B21
Kamio Kari Utaro
You mean Master?
You said it to the name
In the name
I was told that he was a bad guy.
That's strange.
He has everything.
Is there anyone else?
It's not selling.
Ma-chan is so bad at jokes.
What are you talking about?
See? Everyone is dead before the camp is over.
Try to remember!
Ootake Makoto.
City Boys.
Let's go with Drifters.
Drifters?
Drifters, right?
That's so sudden.
It's definitely Shimura Ken.
Nakamoto Koji.
Nakamoto.
Kato.
Sakagibu.
You know what I'm talking about, right?
What about Kato-chan?
It's Kato-chan.
It's different from his name.
Even if he is laughed at,
his name has nothing to do with it.
He is really bad at jokes.
My research will continue to develop in various fields.
It's wild.
It's wild in the middle.
Like this.
He is putting it in.
He is putting it in the necktie.
It's not moving.
Are you going to cut it?
This is going to be cut.
Yesterday, when we were shooting for Gottsu,
Takeda Tetsuya-san was there, right?
Yes, yes.
His shoulders were stiff,
so he was rubbing his shoulders to the staff.
When I saw him, I said,
Oh, good morning.
He was rubbing his shoulders.
Hey, you should be careful.
Why?
It's about your daily life,
so you might not feel it at all,
but if you look at it from a third-party perspective,
he was rubbing his shoulders like this.
Why are you doing that?
Wait.
Ah, ah.
Can you speak?
Today's guest,
Ah, ah.
Speak.
Ah, ah, ah.
Ah, ah.
I'm watching it, so it's fine,
but if you don't know it,
you look really great.
So, I went to a store,
well, what, disco,
well, I haven't been to it recently,
and everyone was sitting like this.
That chair is low.
Everyone was fine.
When a talent like me is sitting like this,
people say,
Matsumoto Ita is wearing this,
and he looks great.
But you can't do it with both hands.
But I can do this.
When I go to the neighborhood,
it's like this.
You'll get hit.
He doesn't have that kind of spirit.
That's right.
It really hurts my head,
so I rub my shoulders and hold my chest.
Well,
I don't think that your rubbing shoulders
are basically dead.
Why?
He's rubbing his shoulders.
Oh, that's enough.
No, no, no.
Touch it.
In the end,
Don't touch it.
No, it's fine.
He's rubbing his shoulders.
It's your morning.
Tell me what happens
when you mix something
that says don't mix.
Tell me what happens when you mix something
Oxygen and oxygen.
Speak clearly.
You won't sell that much.
Speak out.
Oxygen and oxygen.
Yes, yes, yes.
You just figured it out, didn't you?
The detergent is
oxygen.
It's oxygen.
Oxygen?
Why is the detergent oxygen?
Can't you say it properly?
Mom, dad, don't get angry.
Anyway,
Yes?
That's fine.
What?
Is that fine?
Of course, I've experienced everything.
Don't mix.
I've experienced everything.
Oh.
It's from the sesame seeds.
I've been with you all this time.
Please put in my favorite scanty.
I got it.
It's all over the place.
It's hard to take it off.
Oh, sticky pants?
Sticky pants.
A year of embarrassing sticky pants.
That's embarrassing.
A year that I got from my parents.
Sticky pants.
Why would your parents give you sticky pants?
Sticky pants that gave birth to life from my parents.
If you say it like that,
Sticky pants that your parents gave you.
Don't you think they're great parents?
A bright red body from my parents.
How do you know that?
Sticky pants.
I put it in.
I put detergent in.
It's dangerous to mix with that.
I put this in.
I thought it was going to explode.
What did you put in?
That's why I put that in.
I put in something that's said to be dangerous to mix with.
That's enough.
I thought it was going to explode.
It didn't explode.
But?
Yes.
What kind of phenomenon happened?
I don't know.
I can't even predict after this.
At this time, I didn't even want to know.
I know.
Tell me quickly.
What is it?
Don't think about it. I want to see it.
Sticky pants that your parents gave you.
It became a camisole.
It's magic.
Mr. Matsumoto is good at singing, dancing, and his face is also good.
Why isn't it Johnny's?
I'll ask him.
I didn't want to go to Johnny's.
I'll answer seriously.