Ladies and gentlemen.
Today, we don't have an opening.
We don't have an opening.
Why?
Why don't we have an opening today?
We're doing all kinds of silly things.
Today, we're going to smoke a cigarette.
On Sunday, at 3 o'clock on Sunday,
at the east...
was it Honkan?
West Honkan.
We're going to smoke a cigarette at West Honkan.
If you want it, come get it.
Kyo-san came.
Why?
Because I was there.
Why weren't you there?
Why didn't you come when I asked you to?
Everyone was waiting in line.
What?
No, no, no.
What's wrong?
Everyone told me to come dressed as a cat.
Really?
They only said, meow, meow.
Everyone said, meow, meow.
That's right.
Spring is coming.
I thought it was funny.
I was making a stuffed animal last night.
I thought, I'm going to wear a cat costume tomorrow.
I spent the whole night making it.
Don't make fun of me.
I didn't see that coming.
I woke up in time.
Come on, let's go.
I'm going to wear a cat costume.
You don't have to wear it.
Run until I tell you to.
I ran like a cat.
I was eaten by a dog.
You don't have to wear it.
Bring me the monitor.
The monitor.
I got an offer.
If it's too much, let's make it a lottery.
So I went to the store.
If I get a golden ball, I'll eat it.
Let's take a look at the people who won.
You don't have to wear a cat costume.
But I'm doing it right.
It's like a cat's eye.
I just came out like this.
What are you doing?
Let's have a lottery before smoking.
Camera, please shake it.
The person who said to wear a cat costume on Sunday at 3 o'clock is here.
You're stupid.
It's a very nice day on Sunday.
Why did you come here?
What time did you come today?
I came at 3 o'clock.
If I get a golden ball, I'll smoke.
It's white.
Bye-bye.
It's a loss.
What's a loss?
You even have a hanger on your face.
You're so loyal that you're a little angry.
This is the beginning of the date course.
That's not a cat.
You're going to get hit or not.
I made it myself.
What do you think of this dough?
It's okay.
It's fast.
It's a loss.
I don't like it anymore.
I don't like it anymore because I'm a cow.
Thank you very much.
Good luck.
It's a loss.
If you get a golden ball...
I'm editing this, but it's finally out.
It's a loss.
That means I have to take you home today.
Are you ready to take it home?
Where is your house?
Kawasaki.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Thank you very much.
I'll take you home.
Thank you.
It's a loss.
I made it.
Isn't that obvious?
I won!
I don't know.
Do you take this train?
It's a loss.
I don't know how to answer this
This is definitely a smelly foot
Did you see that?
You're not a good staff
What is it?
It's a bicycle.
I can't believe it.
There's still a squid inside.
Is this a slipper?
That's right.
Thank you very much for the nice shoes.
Thank you very much.
That's all.
I went on a train.
The bus was hard too.
It was nothing.
Nothing.
Just like that.
I brought it here.
I asked them to send me a picture of me wearing it.
I wore it.
I put my clothes in it.
You use it like this.
Like this.
It's the worst.
I put my clothes in it.
You don't smell it because you're not close.
If you put it on a train, you'll look like that.
It smells so bad.
The lobby was so smelly.
I think men will understand.
Why?
It smells like pee when you don't wear clothes.
That's all.
The commercial is back.
I'm glad.
You're a child user.
I'm a child user.
It's been a long time since I started this program.
It's been a long time.
What's going to happen to this program?
It's going to be hard.
Every time I talk, I don't think about anything.
There are many people who think that I'm having a meeting.
I don't think about anything when I talk.
I always talk for an hour.
I edit it.
It's been about 20 minutes.
If you let me talk, I can talk for five minutes.
Sometimes, I take a break.
There are times when you say things that you can't broadcast.
I can't do that.
I don't know if you just said that to him.
Let's study the broadcasting code.
I don't study.
I don't know how you do that.
I can't say that.
I don't get it!
Which TV station has a chinko that you can just play on?
What about a chinko?
No...
No, I can't do that!
I can't do that!
It's a chinchin, right?
Is a chinchin okay?
I don't mind if you call me a chinchin, but if you call me a chinko, I'll be shocked!
If you call me a chinchin, I'll be shocked!
What are you talking about?
Don't talk for so long!
This is only 20 minutes!
It'll be a waste.
But broadcasting is really hard, right?
Yes, that's right.
It'll get worse, so I won't be able to talk.
But if you call me a chinchin, I'll be shocked!
Right?
Like a chinchin?
Yes.
That's okay, right?
Yes!
I want you to do that.
This show...
Hey!
You have to cut a lot of scenes, right?
The other day, I was surprised.
Yasu-san was like BAM!
That was...
I was watching it at home, and I was sweating.
Yasu-san wasn't watching it, but other people were watching it.
Yes, yes, yes.
If it was a chinchin.
That's right.
It's scary.
There are a lot of seniors in Yoshimoto, right?
Yes.
So you have to be careful.
That's right.
There are about 250 seniors in Yoshimoto.
Yes.
So I can't say bad things about them.
Yes, yes, yes.
I don't know where they watch it.
You talk bad about people too much.
You've never said bad things about them, but you can't.
That's not true.
I'm going to cry if I hear bad things about you.
Really.
That's not true.
You say bad things about me, too.
That's another story.
No, no, no.
That's just the way you say it.
You're a senior.
No, no, no.
I've never said bad things about you.
That's not true.
There are a lot of bad things about you.
But it's in front of you, but it's not in the shadows.
Wait.
What?
There are a lot of bad things about you.
You're bad.
What?
There are a lot of bad things about you.
But it's in front of you, but it's not in the shadows.
That's not true.
Why?
What?
You're the best.
Okay.
But it's in front of you, but it's not in the shadows.
How many years has it been since you came into this world?
Okay, I'll say it again.
What?
You don't have long hair on your earlobes.
You shave your beard when you shave your beard.
Does this have anything to do with you?
I'm always worried about this because it's an accident.
It's hard to shave my beard.
What are you going to do?
Does this have anything to do with you?
You sometimes have a bad beard.
I told you so.
What are you going to do about my beard?
It stinks.
That's not true.
I know that you have a long beard.
I'm so angry.
That's not true.
What?
Don't shave your beard.
What are you going to do?
You've been angry for a long time.
Tell me.
Don't put a microphone here.
Damn it.
What are you going to do about my beard?
Do you want to go to the toilet?
Please come out.
You're a bunny girl.
Why are you dressed like this today?
Do you have a job like that?
What's wrong with you?
Mr. Hiroko Suzuki is 22 years old and he is a party companion.
He used to work for Marui.
That's true.
Why did you quit?
I don't like it.
Did you have an affair with your boss?
No.
Is that so?
That's right.
I always ask you.
Please tell me which one you like.
I'm not popular these days.
Which one do you like?
Mr. Hamada.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, too.
Let me introduce the story.
Mr. Matsumoto says that Hamada's sister is ugly.
Mr. Hamada is smiling and doesn't seem to be angry.
What about the real thing?
It doesn't matter if it's ugly or not.
I'm a comedian.
It's cool to say that.
What do you think?
It's a difference in human aesthetic sense.
It's ugly.
But I don't care about that.
I don't like it.
I can't go home because I don't like it.
The internet is bad.
If you go back to Osaka, you don't want to be called a housekeeper.
Everyone in the neighborhood is watching.
I can't go home.
I don't want to be called a housekeeper.
You don't know anything.
You're the one who says that.
I don't want to be called a housekeeper.
I don't care.
You say it yourself.
What?
You're poor.
Your father is weird.
That's not good.
My father gets angry when I go home.
He'll be angry if you say that.
But I'm poor.
I don't care about being poor.
My sister is poor, too.
She got divorced once and bought a new car and ran an electric car.
If you say that, your sister won't be able to stay at home.
I feel sorry for her.
I'm glad she bought an electric car and ran an electric car.
Why?
It's true.
How many times do you say that?
I didn't have an electric car.
Even if you didn't have an electric car, you don't have to say you brought it with your sister's car.
When I got an electric car, my family was amazing.
It's true.
It warms your cold heart.
That's right.
When my father came home in winter, he tried to get inside.
Get out of my way.
Don't look down on me.
I'm looking down on you.
What?
I'm serious.
Let me introduce this person.
Miki Hatanaka from Saitama Prefecture.
Maki-chan.
Yes.
Last week...
No. I watch it every week.
I watch it every week.
Let's get down to business.
Have you ever been told that you two look alike?
Please tell me.
I think you two look alike.
Hama-chan is Fumiya from the Checkers.
You guys, don't talk to me.
You always do that.
I can win against you.
I...
When I wear a hat like this, I look like a monster.
You should be happy to get hit.
That's what I've been told.
That's right.
When I do this, I look like a monster.
Your ears are big.
Don't say that.
But you look like a monster.
I don't say that I look like a monster.
Really?
How about you?
Hama-chan is Fumiya from the Checkers.
Mach-chan is a cockroach.
Don't you think I look like an insect like a cicada?
I've been told that I look like an elephant or a rabbit.
You're the worst.
What kind of cockroach do you think you look like?
It's just what I saw.
I don't know what other people think.
I think you look like something better.
If I've been told that I look like something,
I would say...
Watanabe Ken.
You've been told that, right?
I think I look like...
I don't know who else I look like.
I think I look like Rasaru Ishii.
There are many people who look like you.
You look like Fujiko Fujio.
Why?
I'm serious.
That's enough for today.
I'm tired.
What do you want me to say?
What?
The standard language?
The standard language has always been spoken.
It's always been spoken.
There's no such thing as spoken.
The standard language...
This is the standard language of our standard language, right?
That's right.
I'm still trying to speak properly.
Osaka people will never change.
No matter how long it takes.
We have a policy.
If you say something like that,
you'll get a runny nose, right?
I'm telling you.
You know...
The other day...
What?
You have to ask Leopard.
Tokyo has only one word.
That's right.
The word that changes to that is...
That woman.
That woman?
This one?
Tokyo?
That woman.
There are only two words.
In Osaka, it's that woman.
That woman.
That man.
That's all.
Yes.
It's getting hot.
Let's go to a cool place.
Let's go to a place where we can listen to the radio.
We'll listen to the radio.
We'll talk a little next week.
If I sweat a little, I'll go home.
You say it's hot.
You say it's cold.
I'm serious.
Let's do it in a cool place.
Everyone can work well.
That's right.
Thank you for coming.
Really.
I couldn't help it.
What do you mean you couldn't help it?
Were you sleeping?
No, no, no.
What are you talking about?
If I say it, it's going to be a long ending.
I don't think I should say it.
No.
It's going to be a long ending.
I just wanted to read it.
It's delicious.
It's my favorite place.
I don't smoke.
I smoke.
Is that so?
Yes.
I used to smoke a lot when I was in high school.
That's right.
I don't smoke.
Thank you for listening.
Let's do it again.
I don't smoke.