Next time at Gaki no Skyline
Viewers' investigation of Dokechiyonuma Salon
A tragic water chase
Today
We went shopping together
Yes
At Adidas
It's rare
It's a rare look
I can only say that
I don't know how it will look
It doesn't look new
You were in the hospital
I was in the hospital
I was in the hospital for 3 days
There was an interesting story
Let's go
The other day
I'm going to ask
Actually
Mr. Onuma
Yes
There was a trial in Dokechiyonuma
The punishment was decided
Yes
It's not good
The famous director of Gaki no Skyline
Akihiro Onuma
With his strong character
He made people say that he didn't know how to slide
The other day
His true nature was amazing
He realized that everyone was bothering him
The program was in a state of emergency
The trial was held
It was a hard to believe case
At first
He was confused by the sense of money
The verdict was of course guilty
He was punished with a severe punishment
But this time
The viewers' complaint was accepted
This is not a fake
It's not a fake
He is very angry
The other day
He said that the dance was sluggish
We were happy
It can't be helped
It's the viewers
That's right
If the viewers say so
I think I have to be punished with a severe punishment
Of course
I'm here today
Let's have the main character appear
Go ahead
It's dark
It's very dark
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
Since then
The fish material was sold out
I bought 150 ml of cola
I gave it to a few people
I didn't give anything to them
It's a waste to eat rice when I was a kid
I made rice balls at home and brought them
It's not completed
In addition
The Las Vegas 5000 yen incident
Many other things were discovered in a short period of time
The punishment this time
Onuma takes good care of this
It is said to be a one-point luxury
There is a clock
I want to throw it into the river
I put it in a capsule and throw it into the river
If I can catch it
That's OK
If I can't catch it, I'll chase it forever
It's a good flow
I want to throw it in the rain
Where is your clock?
This is it
This is Onuma's treasure
Swiss luxury car
Double name model
How much is it?
150,000 yen
This is the only one in Japan
Two
Two?
Why can you say that?
This is called a double name
It's a very valuable clock
I'm sorry
You made a funny face
You said it smoothly
There are only two in Japan
There are two in Japan
I have to be at your place
You have it or not
There are two
You can't say that
Let's do it
I'll do my best
It's OK
If I fall and roll, can you go?
OK
Let's go
I hope to see you again
Ready
Start
OK
The jet is fast
Onuma is fast
OK
What is this?
Onuma, do your best
It came off
It came off again
It can't come off
It's coming
Onuma
The ball is coming
It came off
Do your best
Onuma
Good bye
I hope to see you again
Let's go home
Please forgive me
I didn't want to do it
I hope to see you again
So
It was good
It's been a long time
Next week
Are you OK?
It's a side match
Next week
I'm going to play golf
A little
I'm going to improve the rules
Are you OK?
What is that laugh?
Is it a laugh that you can win?
Think about it
If 4 people hit, it's 1 hit
Even if you hit a green
Even if you hit a one-pad
One person hits a one-pad
If you hit a one-pad, it's 1 hit
That's right
It's a side match
Only green
Even if you hit a green
If you hit a one-pad
If you hit a green
If you hit a four-pad
If you hit a one-pad
I can't hit a one-pad
That's right
It's OK
If you hit a four-pad, it's 1 hit
It can't be helped
But
If you think about it, you can win
You are
As you can see from the previous video
How far does the circle go?
But we've been improving since then
I'm not doing anything
I'm doing it
I'm doing a lot of muscle training
What are you talking about?
I don't do muscle training
I finally won
What?
This
I'm doing a lot of muscle training
Really
Moreover
This is the second time
The first time, I did too much
The liquid crystal became strange
It's amazing
It has nothing to do with golf
It's completely different from me before
That's fine
Do whatever you want
Do whatever I want
I can see that you're going to lose
You have to think about the punishment again
What will you do if four of you lose?
What?
If you lose
The punishment game for four people
Four people?
Isn't it three people?
No, it's four people
It's four people
Who did you eliminate?
Yamazaki
Four people
It's four people
I don't know what the punishment game is
That's why it's a bit difficult
I don't think you'll lose
I'll try it
Next time, I want you to do E.T.
My mother's bicycle basket
Put my mother in the bicycle basket
Wait in the sky
That
Anyone
Darth Vader
It's similar
Why didn't you imitate Darth Vader?
I learned it from a child
And it's not similar
No one imitated
Everyone has a drawback
What's the drawback?
You have 2,000 to 3,000
What?
A drawback maker
The drawback is 2,000 to 3,000
I have 2,000 to 3,000
I don't know who it is
I think it can't be helped
The thing I can't forgive is
Cat tongue
I don't have it at all
I can handle it
I went to a ramen shop
It's a popular place
It's a ramen shop in a row
The person next to me is the same
It's a line of people
I looked at it for a while
What are you doing?
I'm exposing it
It's a foreign object
I can't shake it
I'm slowly doing it
Imagine drinking ice water
Do it like this
What are you doing?
I'm exposing it
I knew it
And then he goes like this again.
He doesn't go back and forth.
This is the second time.
And then he goes like this again.
I got it.
Ramen is one of the best when it's hot.
There are times when we eat a lot and get a little burned.
Yes, there are. But that's a man.
There are times when we see a man.
And then he goes like this.
And then he goes like this again.
I'm not that kind of man.
You don't have to go that far.
That's enough.
What were you doing at first?
What was it?
Gasoline.
I'm telling you to fill it up.
It's like you're wearing it.
I don't understand.
What about that example?
What is it? Gasoline.
I'm telling you to fill it up.
What is it?
It's not me.
It's really like that.
You can't spend too much time on it.
I want to eat as soon as possible.
I want to see the first page of the dictionary.
I want to put in a lot of bean knowledge.
In your mind.
I'm a math king.
I'm a great math king.
Do you know Mangrove?
What?
The tree of Mangrove.
I don't know that.
You just happened to see it.
I'm very impressed with this story.
What story?
I'm not trying to be impressed.
I don't know what you're talking about.
The tree of mangrove.
It's on the water's surface.
Why are you so...
I'm not interested.
Everyone's great.
This is a plant.
Seeds med mood to the water surface.
It's like eggs.
This seed...
It's all different in weight.
Some seeds sink deep in the water.
It's like floating in the middle.
It's completely different from weight.
All the seeds are different in weight.
Why?
It's my memories.
Because the weight of the seed is different, the seeds that flow to the other side are in various places, so in order for the mangrove to expand its territory, the weight of the seed is all different.
What is this?
Wow, nice to meet you.
What is it?
Look, there's another book.
What is this for?
It's the 10th anniversary of the mangrove's use.
1000 yen!
I can't see it at all.
It looks really bad.
You've been doing this for 10 years?
Yes.
I see.
It's not sold anywhere.
This is...
It's sold.
Even if Mr. Matsumoto throws a frisbee, why doesn't Mr. Hamada go get it?
He's coming.
He's coming, right?
What do you think this is for?
I don't know.
You wouldn't understand even if I asked you.
I don't know what you're throwing.
That's the point.
You don't know that I'm throwing a frisbee, do you?
I don't know.
Actually, I've been throwing 6 frisbees since I came out today.
I don't know when and where you've been throwing them.
Animals...
You know, there are animals that are often surprised.
It's a label.
It doesn't matter if it's a student's ticket or something.
In the end, it's a bad thing.
It's not a surprise or anything.
It's a legacy.
I see.
I'm just doing it because I get food.
In your case, that's what it's all about.
It's a lump of greed.
You're a man.
It's a lump of greed, isn't it?
You're talking about money.
Don't you have any money?
If you don't have any money, the vending machine will go off.
I've been throwing frisbees, but I can't go get it.
It's because there's nothing there.
I see.
You like burrito teriyaki, don't you?
If you give me a burrito teriyaki when I come to get a frisbee,
You're not a glutton.
It's a lump of greed.
If you're a Hamada Obu leader...
Hamada Obu leader...
But don't expect anything in return.
Why are you angry?
There's nothing in return in this world.
Wait, wait, wait.
What are you talking about?
It's about frisbees.
Actually, I've never seen you throw it.
In the end, I expect something in return, so I can't see it.
I can't see anything.
What are you talking about?
You expect something in return, don't you?
I don't.
I'm sure you do.
How about this frisbee?
How about the frisbee?
I don't know.
Okay, then.
What do you use the frisbee for?
You can't be honest with me.
That's right.
This is it.
It smells like this.
When I'm done, I'll take off my jacket and say,
This is 2 million yen.
Are you saying that?
You're saying that, aren't you?
That's what I want you to fix.
You expect something in return, don't you?
I don't expect anything in return.
It doesn't matter if you don't have anything.
There's no rain that doesn't stop.
There's no jeans that you don't wear.
I don't wear jeans.
Let's stop the life of a dweller.
What do you mean?
If you give this to someone,
I'm sure something like this will come back.
I didn't mean that.
That's strange.
I'm glad I was halfway through.
The way to the jeeper is a little different.
There were about three different ways.
I chose the wrong way.
If you go to the first one, you'll go the wrong way.
Star's money-sensitive corner
What's that?
This is that, isn't it?
How do you not forget the feelings of the general public?
I think it's going to be a guide.
You don't know, do you?
What's that?
Do you know how much it is now?
I know.
How much is it?
It's 110 yen, isn't it?
No, no, no, no.
How many years ago?
I'm so scared right now.
I was put in a dark room.
I'm so scared.
It's different.
Everyone's eyes are shining.
How much is it?
It's 10 yen, isn't it?
Was it 120 yen?
Since when?
Since April.
Since April?
I think I know that much.
How much is cabbage now?
Do you know?
I know.
How much is a carrot with four carrots?
How much is it?
I don't even know.
One carrot is about 120 yen.
What?
I'm saying it like a rabbit.
It's like a rabbit.
If I'm a rabbit.
No one knows what a rabbit feels like.
That's what I'm saying.
Actually, everyone is different.
Is everyone different?
It's different, but it's not the right answer.
Why not?
Why are you getting stronger and stronger?
I'm scared.
But I'm sure I'm shopping.
Because I'm the only one.
I shop at a convenience store.
That may be the case.
Do you know how much a house is?
You don't know, do you?
It's less than 200 yen.
I don't know that much.
It's about 170 yen.
Is that so?
No, it's an Indian sense.
If you say that, I can say anything.
Is there anything you can say?
I can't say.
What do you do when you can say it?
What?
Let's start with a child's play.
I'd like to ask Mr. Masumoto, who has the talent for writing and composing.
Let me hear you sing the famous songs of the prefecture of Japan.
I'm good at that.
Is that so?
As an example,
Potatoes are delicious in Hokkaido.
Why don't you put a song on this?
How many seconds have passed?
I haven't seen it yet.
What do you want me to say?
Do it.
How do you want me to do it?
Say something you're good at.
I can say anything.
If you say anything, it's going to be weird again.
Potatoes are delicious in Hokkaido.
I can say 50 different things with this.
That's a good pattern.
Potatoes are delicious in Hokkaido.
My head is getting bigger.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.