This is the 6th episode of Nenmatsu Kourei Taiketsu!
Who will be the winner of the 6th episode?
Hello, hello.
Good evening.
Well...
Who will be the winner of the 6th episode?
The 6th episode? That's a big deal.
That's right.
Up until now, we've been talking about the outside of the house.
What is this?
We've been talking about it.
But this time, inside the house...
I went inside.
It's a nice beach.
It's a beach in front of the island.
Today is a little different from last year.
Shall we take a look?
Let's take a look.
These are the members.
The host of the red group is Mr. Kaminuma Emiko.
Right?
This person...
Yes?
It's his first appearance on TV.
Who is this?
This is Mr. Okamoto.
Do you call him Okamoto Mayo?
That's right.
Moro?
I don't know.
You can say that.
Moro is Moro Okada.
This is the person you've been thinking about.
Who is this person?
Hana?
It's Hana, right?
It's Hana.
Look.
What kind of costume will Satchan wear this year?
I don't know.
I'm not talking about this person.
It's the title of the song.
Who is this?
I don't know how many people are here today.
Hana is the only one who can sing.
Hana is the only one who can sing?
It's not selling.
It stinks.
Wait.
Let's listen to Hana.
It's the same.
It's completely different.
Wait.
I know if you listen to this.
This is selling.
Tomorrow.
I'll tell you if I know.
This is selling.
I know.
I don't know.
You're lying.
I know if you listen to this.
This is selling.
I know.
I'll tell you if I know.
Wait a minute.
I'm curious about something.
What is this?
It says Nakamura Mitsuko.
I'm used to Hana.
You're used to Hana.
This is a difficult part.
If I say too much...
I don't have Hana.
I'm used to Hana.
Everyone did their best.
You're dirty.
This is difficult.
It's definitely difficult.
Who?
Gozen-sama.
What?
What is Gozen-sama?
It's a song.
Mifune Kazuko-san.
Asagata.
Look at this.
Gomutaina.
What?
Gozen-sama Gomutaina.
I'm used to Hana.
What are you talking about?
Let's take a look at the white ones.
Shikai Furutashi-san.
Yes.
Kitashima-san.
Old man.
Tani.
That's good.
Kenji Odawa.
Well, well.
H-Jungle.
I don't know.
What?
Hiromiko.
Does Hiromiko come out?
It comes out.
It sold well.
Yes.
Akira Kogai.
Atsuki Kokoroni.
But it's natural that it comes out like this.
Ah, the song.
It doesn't come out.
Sharankyu.
Yes.
This is the end of this year.
Please do your best from the beginning to the end.
You really hate Sharankyu, don't you?
No, no, no.
I hate him.
Everyone thinks so.
Ah, ah, ah.
But I'm cheering for him to do his best.
Hosokawa Takahashi.
Fuji Fumiya.
Tobaichiro.
What is this?
T-O-K-I-O.
Right?
You know.
Don't say that you know.
What?
You are really...
You are really worse than me.
I can't say anything else.
Why?
You can't say anything else.
Well, well.
I've been watching it so far.
I'm sure the audience has noticed it.
I'm sure you've noticed it, too.
What?
Obviously, this time the castle wins.
Well, I don't know.
The costumes here are also eye-catching.
In the last two or three years.
Well, En-chan.
Well, I want to see it.
For example, let's give the audience a round of applause.
The person who says the castle wins.
I can't laugh at such a thing.
Right?
The person who says the red team loses.
Applause.
Which one?
The person who says the red team wins.
Look.
The person who says the red team loses.
The person who says the red team wins.
Well, well.
I don't care about the opinions of the people who are here.
The problem is the actual performance.
The actual performance.
There are quite a few people who appeared for the first time.
Do you understand?
Then you go to the red team.
What are you talking about?
Don't say strange things.
I'm in the white team.
What?
No, that's enough.
White.
Wait a minute.
What do you mean by white?
No matter how you think about it, it's white.
It's annoying.
What is annoying?
I don't like the red team.
What?
No matter how you think about it, it's red.
What should we do?
I said it before.
Here.
It's like this.
I wonder if it will be negative.
Sometimes it's like this.
My body is shaking.
What should we do?
It doesn't matter.
Even if it shakes a little.
It's shaking to have an effect.
It's shaking to calculate.
I'm doing it to be called cute.
Let's play a game.
If you lose, I'll go to the red team.
I don't care if you go to the red team.
If I lose, I won't go to the red team.
That's right.
What is this?
There is a mistake.
If you pull it, the trigger will work.
What do you mean?
I can't do it like this.
But I pulled it out once.
What?
What about the potato?
What is this?
This is the usual.
Badminton black beard.
What?
Can I do it?
I'll do it.
Badminton will start when it floats.
I did it last year, too.
Let's do this.
What?
I have to hold this.
If you do this and float, I'll shoot.
That's impossible.
I have to wait once.
It's better to come out.
Why?
If you don't shoot in a hurry, it's over.
It's hard to do this.
Don't do it when I'm doing the potato.
You're the one who broke the potato.
Don't do that.
I'll do it.
I'll show you how to use it.
I didn't expect it to be so fast.
You're smiling.
You didn't notice that I was imitating Makoto, did you?
I'm sorry. I didn't notice it, either.
I'll do it again.
I'm sorry.
I just said that.
I love you.
I thought I saw you up close.
Your face is red.
I'm glad.
Hello.
It's the end of the year, isn't it?
Yes.
It's already the end of the year.
This year, too...
I'm being bitten by something.
Maybe it's because I'm stressed out.
My body is going crazy.
Here and here.
It's a double.
Really?
Yes, it's been a year.
A lot has happened.
It's been a hard year.
Do you have any big news this year?
I don't have any.
The biggest mystery this year is...
There's a show called Hei Hei Hei.
Tsuyoshi Nakabuchi will appear.
This is the biggest mystery this year.
Why?
Why did he want to appear in Hei Hei Hei?
What kind of attitude will he have?
He said he'd come.
He wanted to appear from the other side.
He said he'd come...
But he didn't say hello.
He didn't say hello to Nakabuchi.
This is not Nakabuchi.
It's not.
Has he ever seen Hei Hei Hei?
I'm sure he has.
What?
Shoro!
Mr. Shoro!
No, I'm serious.
I'm sure he has.
Mr. Shoro!
If you've ever seen him...
I don't know why he wanted to appear in that show.
What kind of attitude will he have?
And why will he call us?
Is he wearing glasses?
I'm sure he's wearing glasses.
Is he wearing a bandana?
I'm sure he's wearing a bandana.
What kind of attitude will he have when Hamada takes him off?
Why did I have to take him off?
I don't care.
I don't care about the bandana.
I'll take him off.
Nakabuchi!
At that time...
At that time, he would say,
Stop it, Aoi!
I'm going to take him off!
I don't think he would say that.
This is my...
Actually, I can't take it off.
You can't take it off?
I can't take it off.
I see.
I don't know what he's going to do.
It's really strange.
Is he going to wear a kimono?
Something like this.
You're going to take it off.
Stop it!
What are you going to do at that time?
Nakabuchi!
At that time...
Why does he look like he's driving a car?
Nakabuchi!
That's what I'm saying.
Stop it, Hamada!
There's no way.
I really want to see it.
But will they be able to talk while laughing?
You can laugh, I can laugh,
This person can laugh,
I can laugh, too.
Can you imagine that?
Nakabuchi is laughing with the three of them.
I don't think so.
It's okay, it's okay.
You don't have to worry about it.
Really?
It's okay, it's okay.
You don't have to imitate it.
I'm a little worried about that.
It's okay.
You don't have to do anything.
Please write it down.
It seems that there is still a big scar on Mr. Matsumoto's back.
Would you like to hear the story of that time?
It's from Fukushima Prefecture.
Fukushima?
Okino.
Shoji.
Masashi.
Which one?
Well...
It's a pretty big scar.
What?
How big is the scar?
Well...
From around here...
It's like this.
Really?
Really.
Why did it happen?
Well...
Well, that's how big the scar is.
Well, it's a beast.
Where did you get that scar?
When I went camping.
A beast?
Yes, a beast.
Well, it's a beast that everyone has in mind.
Say it!
Do you understand?
Everyone is waiting.
A beast?
What?
No, no, no.
It's a mongoose.
I'll say it.
It's pretty big.
I don't care if it's pretty big.
Just step on it.
What do you think a mongoose is?
What do you think it is?
I think it's this big.
If you step on it like this, is it a mongoose?
No, it's about this big.
Really?
Really, really.
It's as big as a bamboo shoot.
What's a bamboo shoot?
This is a mongoose.
I brought it here when I was camping.
I told him to come to this place.
Then I told him that I was going to die with the owner.
It's a mongoose.
Why are you talking about a mongoose?
You can't hurt a mongoose.
It fell into the book.
Oh, my God.
He must have had a lot of desire.
Did you turn your back on him?
Yes.
Then he said,
Oh, my God.
He said,
So this is not a bad wound.
Rather, as my technician...
As a technician...
Don't say that.
That's enough.
He knew well.
He knew well about Okinoko in Fukushima.
He had a wound in his back.
That's why he went with him.
This is a question for Mr. Matsumoto, who taught Yoshida how to wear a G-PAN T-shirt.
How do you throw away a Heinz T-shirt?
This is a great question.
It's like catching a spider.
Why did you ask me that?
I'll ask you.
For example, socks.
When do you throw them away?
Well, if there are a lot of holes, I throw them away.
Do you throw them away that much?
There are times when they become thin, right?
Yes, there are.
I want to see how far my legs can be seen.
Like a pot?
How far are they in?
I want to know the amount of my legs.
Well, it's not that bad.
Actually, there was a woman I broke up with.
She was a pretty good woman.
One day, when I came to her house, I saw that her heels were in America.
That's not good.
I was like, that's not good.
I broke up with her.
There are times like that.
I don't break down easily.
I usually wear this kind of rubber.
It becomes flimsy.
There are times when it becomes really flimsy.
There are.
There are, right?
There are times when it becomes really flimsy.
When I'm running, it becomes really flimsy.
What kind of shoes do you have?
There are times when it becomes really flimsy.
I can't help but laugh.
I'm not a bad person.
That's not good.
When it becomes flimsy, it's definitely not good.
I think it's the same with T-shirts.
What about your underwear?
I can't look at my underwear from here.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about the briefs.
Where should I look at from?
I can't have briefs like this.
I'm always like this,
Even though I'm walking in the summer, I can't look at my underwear.
I can't have briefs like this.
When it's a pair of pants,
it looks like I'm sitting.
That's love, though.
Wasn't it like that with old men in the past?
It's becoming more and more like a short-sleeved shirt.
The briefs.
My superior was like that too, the other day.
What the hell are you doing?
You're a pervert!
Change your clothes! Change your clothes!
What the hell are you doing?
Don't take it off until it's like this!
It's there.
It's there, right?
I think I should throw it away.
But I think I should throw it away.
But if it goes through my brain, I can do something about it.
That's right!
That's right. I think I should throw it away.
Put it in the washing machine!
That's right!
Why did you throw it away again?
I think I should throw it away again.
This is a question for you, Mr. Masaboshi, who was studying with Farvel, lining up your desk.
Now there are mysterious mass-produced poisonous spiders in Osaka.
Please tell us a good strategy to defeat them.
Poisonous spiders, right?
Yes.
The ones that are being discovered in Osaka right now, are they the ones with a bad attitude among the spiders?
They have a bad attitude.
What?
Their personalities are bad.
I'd like to hear about their personalities.
The personalities of poisonous spiders are bad.
What kind?
Their personalities are really bad.
Is that so?
Yes.
Please tell us about that.
For example, in a marathon, they say,
Let's run together until the end.
They go on and on and on.
On the day of the exam, they're studying a lot.
They're studying hard.
Yes, yes.
There are those kinds of poisonous spiders.
There are those kinds of poisonous spiders?
Yes.
They're poisonous spiders, so if there's no exam, they won't run a marathon.
That's not true.
But there are those kinds of poisonous spiders.
Why can't you say something like that?
I can laugh as much as I want.
If you don't tell me what I can say, I won't understand.
For example, if you don't tell me what I did.
I see.
Sometimes, you know, you borrow a video rental.
There's a manner to rewind it.
There are people who rewind it.
Yes, there are.
That's why.
I know that.
That's the kind of guy.
What did that guy do?
It's a poisonous spider, so a rental video is not enough.
It's not enough.
I know that.
For example, you have a bicycle, right?
The key to the bicycle.
There's a way to figure out how to steal a bicycle.
You take it to the police station.
It's parked in front of the station.
They say you lost the key.
Then you ask the police officer to open it.
There's no legal way to do that.
But the police officer says you lost the key, so you open it.
You open it.
That's the kind of guy.
I know that.
I've heard that so many times.
It's a strategy.
It has nothing to do with me.
You have a bad personality.
I just said that.
It's a lie.
It's a prank.
It has nothing to do with me.
It's a lie.
I was surprised.
I was deceived.
It's a prank.
I was surprised.
I'm glad it's a prank.
It's a prank.