Thank you!
Awesome!
It's amazing, when it's golden, it's colored!
The plate is colored too!
The plate is colored!
It used to be!
It used to be white, but now it's colored!
It used to be colored, but now it's colored!
It's not like that!
If you look at it, it's a child.
Ah...
The two of us,
we did a lot of changes.
That's right.
What will happen to the child?
Isn't it weak?
I see.
When we were born,
Japan was still a burning field.
There was nothing.
Today there are four men and two women,
but there is one more man.
Ah, is that so?
Toshihide-kun is...
Toshihide-kun!
Don't forget your name tag!
Chibikko-kun!
Please say your name.
I'm Ruge Daichi.
What?
Ruge Daichi?
Are you Chinese?
What?
Ruge Daichi!
What are you scared of?
I'm scared of E.T.
What?
It's there but I don't want to say it.
It's there but you don't wanna say it?
Tell them your name!
I know the name, but not the face.
You love people who knows not the face.
Ah, you're on Telekura!
Yui-chan, Yui-chan, Yui-chan!
You guys are still on Telekura!
What's going on?
I wonder if someone's going to cry?
Now, Masumoto-kun, go ahead!
Nagato is a house!
He's crying! He's crying! He's crying!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
I knew it! I knew it!
Ladies and gentlemen!
It's a beautiful place, isn't it?
It's my first time at a hall.
It's your first time at a hall, isn't it?
Today, there's an old lady who looks like Geronimo.
It's that thing, isn't it? What is it?
Is it the baseball Japan series?
It was all over the place, wasn't it?
Yeah, the west team won, right?
I can't always say that, but there are only 6-9 teams.
If it's a line, it's a line.
There are only 6-9 teams, so they win once every 6 years.
There's a good chance.
There's no such thing as a big deal.
But you can't win once, can you?
Look at this superstar.
He's running through the comedian world, and he's better than me.
I want to win, but there's a guy who's crying.
I've been working hard for a year.
Are you stupid?
It doesn't matter if you're a player or not.
There's a guy who's crying because you're supporting him.
That's because I've been working hard to support him.
For example, for example,
Oh, it's blinking. I can still do this.
From the other side,
I drank a little too much yesterday.
Are you okay?
Thank you very much.
Even your name is Akiyama of the west team.
If that's the case, I'll...
That's long.
I'm sorry.
I went to the store.
I thought it would be too much if I went any further.
I went in a little too early.
I went to the hospital next door, so I had to sleep for about an hour.
The funny thing about the disease is that I have a runny nose.
It's like a runny nose syndrome.
When you say it.
That's funny, isn't it?
I always have a runny nose.
Do you have a runny nose?
No, I threw it away.
Where?
Like this.
Who's going to take that garbage?
The old man comes every morning.
What? The old man comes?
The old man is going to take the garbage?
Of course.
I don't need it.
It's raw garbage.
No way.
Idiot.
What are you going to do with the old man's hair?
I'm going to cut it off and leave the old man wearing it.
By the time you go home, you're going to be thrown away in a garbage bag.
You're looking at it, aren't you?
While paying money.
I think.
Why is the human nose in a place like this?
In order to be in a place like this.
It smells when you eat it.
There are things that smell but taste good.
There are things that you want to lick but can't because they smell bad.
If your nose is in a place like this, it's OK.
You can lick it.
What are you thinking?
It doesn't matter where the smell is.
It doesn't matter.
If your nose is in a place like this and you lick it with your mouth, does it smell bad?
I don't know what you're doing.
What kind of woman are you with?
I don't need my nose here.
I like my nose here.
But what's here?
It's lonely here.
It's lonely here, so the balance is bad.
Where should I put my hair?
Is there anything here?
What's this?
Why are you putting your hair in a place like this?
It's lonely.
It's in the way.
Why?
It's in the way when you do something.
That's not true.
I want you to put something here when you wash your body.
If my nose is in a place like this?
That's what I think.
There's a nose here, but there's another nose.
When you take a bath, it's a different nose.
This nose doesn't function.
It's closed.
Where's the other nose?
This nose looks good on you when you wear a kimono.
Where did you go?
I went to the hospital.
Where do you want to go?
That's good.
I should go once.
But I'm scared.
What do you like?
Do you like CT scan?
You can see half of your face.
I'm scared.
If you call me,
I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do if there's something in my nose.
When I was a kid,
when I rode a bicycle,
there was a bee in my nose.
I went in, but I don't remember it coming out.
I know.
There was a bee or a bug.
I went in, but I don't remember it coming out.
Maybe it's somewhere.
I don't know if it's somewhere.
It's dead inside.
So it's definitely in my body.
As a difference.
It won't come out?
I didn't go in from here.
It won't come out.
It's somewhere around there.
For sure.
Let's say you went in from here.
I went in from here.
I went up once.
Is it decided?
It's decided.
When you go in, you go up.
I didn't know that.
Why?
I went up.
And then you go back.
I'm already there.
From here.
And then you go back.
It's different.
I'm going back.
And then you go back.
I'm already there.
I was thinking if I should make it shorter.
I see.
I should cut it here.
It's pretty funny.
I don't know where to start.
What are you doing at home?
What kind of woman are you?
What?
What do you mean by woman?
I have a wife.
That's enough.
Do you have a girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend right now.
I'm looking for a girlfriend right now.
What kind of woman are you?
I'm not married.
It's not funny at all.
It's funny, but it's funny.
I'm married, but when I do that...
It's funny.
Who is that?
I'm from Toshima.
I came to Tokyo from Osaka in April.
I have a question.
When I'm driving on the streets of Tokyo,
there are a lot of people who drive open cars.
Oh, there are.
The roads are more crowded than Osaka.
When I look at the open cars that are moving slowly in the parking lot,
people are staring at me.
I don't think it's cool at all.
Do you want to buy an open car?
I don't think so.
You don't think so?
Why?
It's like a toy.
What are you crazy about?
That kind of car.
Do you want an open car?
The other day, when I was driving with Nitta,
there was something a little old-fashioned in the open car.
Something like,
we don't have a tomorrow.
Something like that.
Right?
It's not a car like that,
but look at the back.
There's something like a basket in the back.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's like when you go on a picnic.
It's really like,
it's like you're driving on a park in America.
It's really tacky.
That's not it!
It's like you're in a mountain.
No,
I think that
if the driver gets in, it's fine.
What do you mean, if the driver gets in?
The guy I saw the other day was in an open car,
but he's bald.
Bald people don't get in an open car.
It's a part that you can hide.
If there's a roof, you can't tell if you're bald.
Why?
You're not wearing a hat.
I'm not wearing a hat.
You can't wear a hat in an open car.
The hat will fly.
You can't wear a hat.
You have to wear rubber.
There are bald people who are cool.
What?
Cool bald people?
What kind of bald people?
There are bald people like Takenaga-san.
Like Takenaga Nao-san.
There are bald people like that.
I think it suits you because you're that person.
Right?
You're really like that.
What kind of bald people?
You don't like people who are ugly, right?
That's right.
If you're like that, you should cut your hair.
You're so forceful.
You're like this.
That's strange.
I'm saying it's fine here.
It's fine. You're like this.
You're like this.
You're thinking about all kinds of things.
I've seen this before.
There's only this and this.
I'm folding this.
Like this.
It's really like a present.
What's worse is that...
You're folding it like a pie.
It's long.
It's like when you fold your pants.
There are people like that.
You only fold this part.
You don't fold this part.
It's fine.
There's that part earlier, but here...
You're like this.
I can't help it.
I'm going to extend it and fold it.
Like this.
I'm going to drill this part open.
I'm going to drill this part through and make a hole here.
I'm going to pull it out from here.
It's strange.
There's a bunch of hair in a place like this.
It looks strange.
Is it strange?
There's a lot of hair here.
There's a bunch of hair in your face.
I was watching TV the other day and thought of something.
At the end of the news, there's the Dao Heikin Kabuka.
Dao Heikin Kabuka.
What is that?
Let's think about it together.
Da...
I'm sorry.
What is Dao?
I don't know what Dao Heikin Kabuka is.
What is it?
So...
For a while...
My bubble burst.
Please explain what a bubble is.
The land was going up.
Do you understand?
I understand.
The land was going up.
Then the real estate company went to that direction.
What is that?
Japan is the real estate company's country.
At that time,
Wait!
That bubble burst.
Don't you think you're acting like a hero?
I think this is easier for you guys to understand.
Wait!
The bubble burst.
It hurts.
Who is it?
Wait!
Go ahead.
Who are you fighting with?
The real estate company.
That's it.
There are many schools nowadays.
For example, there is a school called Yumo-wa Wajitsu Koza.
It's a school that can capture people's hearts.
It's said that anything can be a school.
What kind of school do you think will be popular?
Did you go to school?
When I was little?
Solo class or calligraphy class?
That's not good.
What did you say?
You didn't say anything.
Everyone said that.
That's right.
That's why I didn't want to go.
What's that?
What did you do when everyone was drunk and went to the solo class after school?
I played with the marbles.
That's not cool.
That's sad.
What did you eat?
I ate tebasaki.
Everyone was going to the solo class, but you ate tebasaki.
That's not good.
It's a classroom.
It's a place to fix the marbles.
That's a lie.
It's a place where people from the countryside teach you the standard language.
The word standard language makes me angry.
What kind of standard language are you talking about?
What?
It's a way to treat people from Tokyo.
Everyone in Tokyo is a person from Tokyo.
That's right.
There are almost no people from Tokyo.
Most of them are from the countryside, right?
Yes.
They are all from Tokyo.
When they go home, they all say, zura.
It's true.
If you say, I'm from Tokyo, they'll think you're from the Philippines.
I'm proud of my Osaka dialect.
If you start a Osaka dialect class, you might be able to enter the class in Tokyo.
Because of the intonation.
If you don't want to say bad things, you should start a Osaka dialect class.
Right?
You'll be able to understand, right?
Yes, I'll understand.
It's cold.
It's not cold at all.
I can't understand.
It's really cold.
It looks really cold.
It looks cold.
I'm going to die.
You think so, right?
My stomach is not feeling well.
I have a cold.
It's not about the expression.
What is this?
It's good.
I don't want it.
It's good, right?
It's good.
You can buy the same one, right?
Where did they get the same one?
I'm still different.
I'm a bit different from Kappa's mother.
Good evening.
Right, we've finished today.
We did it, didn't we?
People who haven't been able to see it before should be able to see it now that the time has changed, so I'd like to ask you for your opinion on it.
Please let me know.
Other than that, well, I guess that's it.
Yesterday, my nose was clogged and it was hard to sleep.
If it's clogged here, it's clogged here too.
I'm not going to do it.
I'll take care of everything.
And I'm waiting for you to use my hall.
For free.
I'm waiting for you to use my hall.
So, what are you going to do?
For free.