Next, we will be giving away 1,000,000 yen!
The 1st KAKU RENBO tournament!
This is the 3rd time.
This is the 1st time.
The 1st time was during the winter.
The 2nd time was for various reasons.
We couldn't do it.
The 1st KAKU RENBO tournament was held in December last year.
We will be giving away 1,000,000 yen!
The 2nd KAKU RENBO tournament was held 3 months ago.
Who will get the 1,000,000 yen this time?
Today, we will be giving away 1,000,000 yen!
What?
What's wrong?
It's terrible.
A baby was caught during the Heisei era.
The microphone can't record the cry.
You can take it with you.
You were caught during the Heisei era, too.
What's wrong with that?
You were wearing a T-shirt.
You were caught during the Heisei era, too.
That's right.
Matsumoto-san really likes it.
You can like me, but don't come to my house and fold my pajamas.
Please don't do that.
It's a baby.
You can't hide it.
That's right.
What's wrong with that?
It's a baby.
You can't hide it.
He's crying.
It's hot!
It's cold.
Everyone, look at this.
You can look at this.
Wait for a while.
I've done many things, but I can't do this.
It's a baby.
Is it a baby?
I can't help it.
It's a baby.
If it's a baby...
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
This is a big problem.
You shouldn't be doing this. You should call the police.
Why are you doing this to a baby?
It's cold.
Why are you doing this to me?
You're the one who did this.
We're still single.
It's sad that you're crying.
Pocchan is so happy.
Pocchan!
He's getting closer.
Wait a minute.
I feel sorry for him.
He's getting older.
He's a Pikachu.
He must like Pikachu.
Pocchan, show us how you do it.
I'll do it.
Welcome.
It's scary.
You should look at the camera.
If he's embarrassed, he won't look at the camera.
Pocchan, one, two, three.
It's scary.
Pocchan.
Look at that.
It's scary.
He's just an old man.
What are the parents thinking?
It's terrible.
Such a cute child.
Excuse me.
What?
Did you leave your mom with my dad?
I don't know.
There's a lot in there.
What's in here?
I'm not sure.
I'm sure it will make them happy.
I think so too.
Pocchan.
I wonder if it'll make them cry.
Kou-chan, don't do it!
Kou-chan, your head will fall off.
He doesn't like it.
He doesn't like it at all.
This is really...
Let's change the diaper.
Ah, this is bad.
The poop is coming out.
It's coming out.
This is a diaper player.
Kou-chan, hang in there.
It's cute.
Kou-chan, it's cute.
It's cute, isn't it?
You're a fool.
What is this?
It's not even a toy.
I wonder if he's hungry.
You like this, don't you?
I like this.
Ah, yes, yes.
What is this?
Did you like this?
Everyone likes this.
Let's go, Kou-chan.
Ah, it's delicious.
Kou-chan, eat a lot.
It's scary.
It's really scary.
Kou-chan, this is delicious.
Kou-chan, today...
Thank you.
Kou-chan, Kou-chan, Kou-chan, Kou-chan.
It's scary.
Did you kick that?
Everyone likes this.
Ah, he's crying.
He's crying.
I understand.
He wants to go to the bathroom.
I see.
It's dirty.
Kou-chan, you can lie down here.
I'll put you in.
You can face this way.
Kou-chan, you can go in by yourself.
Kou-chan, what are you doing?
It's dangerous.
Kou-chan, Kou-chan, Kou-chan, Kou-chan.
Kou-chan.
Kou-chan, you move fast.
That's Kou-chan.
If you get scared, you can...
Kou-chan.
...you can get sick.
Here you go.
Kou-chan.
Here you go, Kou-chan.
It's a good chance.
You'll get well soon.
Kou-chan.
You're getting prettier.
Yes, you're getting prettier.
You're getting bigger.
Ko-chan, you're getting prettier.
Ko-chan, let's open the box.
Let's open the box.
What's wrong, Ko-chan?
After all, O-Numa is his father.
That's right.
O-Numa is cool.
Totally different.
Oh, it's good, isn't it?
Ko-chan, look!
This is no good!
Mama!
What is that?
That's the suspicious one.
Is that so?
We don't understand that!
You can't go with someone you don't know.
Po-chan went with someone he didn't know.
He's a very bad kid.
Mama is very worried.
But when Po-chan came back, Mama was relieved.
Mama and Po-chan were always together.
But it's the opening of the first one.
Po-chan and Mama
I've been thinking about this lately.
I don't want to say it now, but...
I used to do a lot of acting, didn't I?
I remember it well, but...
It would be interesting if there was a pearl like this.
There was something like that, right?
I remember the answer I wrote.
I wrote a panda.
It's a panda with a lot of heat.
It was pretty funny, so I remember it well.
Do you remember?
I don't remember.
Recently, there's a little bit of a boom on the streets.
Tare panda!
That's definitely my partner!
Is there such a thing as a Tare panda?
It's a Tare panda, but it's a little bit dirty.
That's definitely my partner!
Don't make your face so red!
Right?
That might be the case, but it's cool if it's a stone.
I was so skinny for a moment.
It's not the same panda!
It's not a giraffe or a deer.
It's a panda.
It's a stone.
I've told you everything.
It's okay.
I'm not angry.
Well, well.
I borrowed a little bit of your wisdom.
Come and say hello to me.
It's hard to say hello.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Hey, hey!
What is it?
I don't think so.
Well, that's right.
It all starts with a compliment.
Yo-san, you've been ripped off.
I'm angry.
But that's a character.
It's cute, so I don't think it's going to sell.
My bad Mickey Mouse picture.
There was a time when I printed it on a T-shirt and sold it.
No way!
I'm the only one who can print that.
I don't know.
I mean, in a good way.
It's dirty in the toy industry.
In the toy industry.
You know what?
Furby.
The one who talks.
That's definitely a lie.
What do you mean by a lie?
You know, if you stay at home and talk, you'll gradually learn the words.
It's definitely a lie.
You can't be fooled.
Why can't you say that?
Here it comes.
Well, then.
No, you win.
Yes, yes, yes.
Even for a month.
All right, all right.
If we live together, we'll do it.
Okay, okay.
That's a good assist.
Well, then.
Why is that a lie?
I'll tell you in a word.
Go ahead.
I'm not lying.
I see.
If you hear this.
You're really something.
Shut up.
Say it.
Why can't you say that?
Say it again.
And I'll tell you in a word.
I see.
I'll decide.
Okay, I understand.
Oh, you.
That man.
Why can't you say that?
If you say something, you'll say,
Machan is the best.
You don't have to say that no matter what the answer is.
It's obvious.
I'll say it.
If you hear Machan is the best, you're going to lose your mind.
And then.
And then you.
Are you still going to say that?
Please be my partner forever.
I can decide that easily.
You.
Yes.
I'll say it.
Harvey.
It's selling well.
It seems to be selling well recently.
What is that?
It's popular in America.
If you ask, they say it's a new toy.
They remember what they're talking about.
Harvey himself starts talking.
Yes, he does.
He went to America and was brought to Japan.
It's going to be a boom in Japan.
Everyone's going to buy it now.
They say it's sold out.
That's amazing.
Don't be fooled.
That's definitely a lie.
Why can't you say that?
Because it's true.
What is that?
Exhibition.
Why can't you say that?
You're the only one who doesn't understand that.
How am I supposed to follow that?
Exhibition.
You can't say it in one word.
If you don't like it, you can't say it.
Okay, okay.
I got it.
Please.
I'll definitely say it.
I'll definitely say it, but I'm a little worried.
What do you mean?
I'm worried if you can do it.
I can do it.
Can I practice?
Maybe if you can't do it, you have to buy a new one.
You have to buy it.
It's going to be a big deal, right?
Let's get this going.
The numbers are going to go boom.
Two Sugachans.
Let's practice.
Please let me practice.
What? What? What?
Yeah.
Is that what you want to say?
That's the way to say it, right?
What, what, what, what is it?
Right?
Mak-chan is the best!
I'm going to faint!
Hey, wait a minute!
After that, I'm not going anywhere!
What are you saying?
Until when are you going to be my friend?
I'm begging you, Sakai!
And then I'll be like, ah, ha, ha, ha!
What are you doing?
It's up to you.
No, it's...
If you bite this, it'll be the worst.
You'll be a comedian.
What?
Is it really that bad?
Okay, I got it!
Let's go!
I don't care about that!
And then we'll start.
Let's go!
It's called Furby, right?
It was a hit in America.
It's a stuffed animal.
When you talk to it, it gradually remembers those words.
And it starts to talk to itself.
That's right.
It sold a lot.
And then Japan did that again.
When it started selling in Japan, it sold out immediately.
That's right.
It's really popular.
You can't be fooled by that!
Why not?
You can't be fooled by the existence of a Japanese version of that!
I'll do it.
This is the only solution.
A
You're doing well.
I'm doing well.
It's like that.
What?
There are a lot of parts.
Furby is popular.
It's popular.
I want that, too.
This is a question for Mr. Matsumoto, who has read out a number of predictions from various animals.
That's true.
A live animal predicts the weather.
Yes.
What does a live animal predict?
Oh?
What?
It's a cry.
Oh?
That's what it predicts.
What does that mean?
Do you understand the meaning of prediction?
Prediction is something you understand before it happens.
That's right.
They predict the weather before they say it.
Why are you making such a frowning face?
Are you Fuji-san's sixth eye?
You can't do that.
What do you mean?
Everyone has a prediction ability.
Well, maybe.
Yes.
Do you know what psychokinesis is?
Do you know what pyrokinesis is?
I don't know, I don't know.
It's a fire flower.
Oh, I see.
It's an energy radiation ability.
If you think of it like that, for example, your head will burn.
That kind of power?
This is called pyrokinesis.
There are also psychokinesis and other types of nexus.
I also have a little bit of it.
What do you have?
But my ability is very simple.
It's not a very powerful ability.
It's an ability that's hard to believe.
You can just move it a little bit in front of your eyes, right?
For example, you have a stroller, right?
Please push this.
Like this.
Push the stroller.
I'll push it?
Please push it lightly and softly.
Really, don't move!
The truth is, with the power you just pushed, you can only move this much.
But what moved a little more was my...
...wagokinesis.
What's a wagokinesis?
Well, it's a wagon, right?
You don't have to get caught in a wagon.
This is my wagokinesis.
But you can't prove that, can you?
See?
If it was true, you could only move this much.
Ah, that was my wagokinesis!
Hey!
Look at me!
With that,
wagokinesis...
...is it normal to move like this?
Ah, it's still a wagokinesis!
You're too slow!
After you fall, you do this.
Before you fall, you do this.
What do you want to say?
Originally, there's this here, and you're here.
If you move like this,
everyone will say, oh!
If you push that, the power after that will be broken.
But isn't this important?
What do you mean?
Isn't this important?
Who are you?
Originally, you're pulling out your power by adding my power.
That's hard to understand.
What's easy to understand is that you can move it like this.
You can reverse it.
What are you talking about?
You push it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What are you doing?
You're pulling out your power.
Why are you making such a dirty face?
That's because,
right now,
I used reverse wagokinesis.
What do you mean?
If I didn't use that, I would have said more.
You stopped it?
I stopped it.
That's not good.
Move this!
Leave it like this.
It's stopped.
I'll protect you!