Ladies and gentlemen, Hizou the Kid. Unpublished talk show.
When your butt gets itchy in the city, how do you draw without being noticed by the people around you?
Or how do you draw your butt so it's not embarrassing to be noticed?
Have you ever had your butt itchy while walking around the city?
You have, right?
Why is it itchy in the city?
It's still itchy, right?
Is it itchy because it's still itchy?
Or is it not itchy?
If you put poop on your butt, it's itchy, right?
It's itchy, right?
So is your butt itchy?
Or is it the other way around?
I don't know if it's the other way around or not.
Don't people cheat and do that?
No one does that.
They do it across the chain.
Isn't that embarrassing?
Why is that?
The chain is like this, right?
In a circle.
Even if it's like this, it's not like that all over the place.
You have to look for it when you draw.
Women can't do it like this.
Why? You can do it, right?
The chain.
Please tell me a way that's not embarrassing.
Okay, I got it. I'll tell you.
This is pretty rough.
You're walking, right?
Where are you walking?
It's better to be in a crowded place.
Shinjuku?
Yes.
In Shinjuku or anywhere in the city.
Your butt got itchy in Shinjuku.
Please look for a alley somewhere.
Go into the alley.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What?
Why is it open again?
I'm just answering the questions.
I didn't mean it.
If you don't want to go into the alley, anyone can do it.
I'm just saying.
I didn't mean it.
Why is it open again?
I didn't mean to answer all the questions.
I have a question for Bruce's queen, Matsumoto-san.
How can you sing like Matsumoto-san?
Bruce is very difficult.
There's a lot of things.
There's a lot of things?
There's a lot of difficult things.
Isn't Bruce's queen a ***?
Well, that's what happened to him.
That's not what happened.
He's a genius.
He held my hand and said it with tears in his eyes.
And then he said he'd leave it to me.
What? He was saying something nice.
Well, well, well, well, it's you.
It was you.
Don't make a fool of yourself.
No, no.
Who is Bruce?
I'm sure there were a lot of people.
As a result, it was you.
It was you.
I said it twice.
Bruce is not a good singer.
That's one thing I can say.
He's just like he usually is.
Just like he usually is?
That's why...
When I pour hot water from the pot,
I think, oh, it's Bruce.
Even when I see a dog,
What kind of condition is that?
Bruce.
Bruce, here you go.
What do you mean by Bruce?
You don't even know what Bruce is.
And I've been talking about Bruce all this time.
No, I'm asking why you can sing like that.
If you can sing like that,
you know this is Bruce.
I'm sleepy.
Bruce...
Bruce, what kind of condition is that?
You don't even know what Bruce is.
Ladies and gentlemen.
When Hama-chan got injured
and was about to come back to life,
he gave an unrevealed talk.
Let's talk about an animal
that has a toilet in the Mutsugoro Kingdom of Hokkaido.
Recently, a stray cat in the neighborhood
is trying to poop in our garden.
Is there any good way to do that?
There's something you can do to keep it from getting drunk.
Is it a PET bottle?
It's a PET bottle, but it's something you can leave behind.
You don't have one?
What do you mean?
It's something you can leave behind if you don't want it.
The best thing is dog poop.
There's dog poop in the garden.
But why do you have to cover it up?
Think about it.
Imagine you're a cat.
You hate dogs.
If you go there, there's poop too.
You would never go there.
Do you really hate dogs?
Of course not.
They can poop in the garden.
And if you ask them, they'll say it's dog poop.
Who would go there?
That's what cats think.
There's something you can do to keep it from getting drunk.
It's something you can leave behind.
Really?
Yes.
Cats don't know what a PET bottle is.
Of course they don't.
What's that?
It's something you can leave behind if you don't want it.
Cats run away when they see light?
Then what about my star shine?
Toshi-chan.
Lastly, let's hear from the two people who couldn't show their stars last week.
There's a legend that the store you went to will definitely go bankrupt.
That's true.
I don't get it.
I'll tell you a small story.
If I go to a place where there aren't any people and eat there, I'll get drunk.
That's true.
Isn't it?
It's true.
But it's amazing.
It's completely different from you.
When you were sitting down, your seat was full, right?
When I was eating, it was amazing.
There were people lined up outside.
There weren't any people until a while ago, but there were people lined up outside.
Outside?
Where did they come from?
It was amazing.
There were people who wanted to work part-time.
They even saved the old man.
The old lady at the park was like,
The other day, I was beaten up by a bar.
I'm very sad about it.
Please tell me how to distinguish a bar from a bar.
If you see a bar and think it's bad, please tell me.
To be honest, even if I use my foresight,
I can't tell just by looking at the door.
You can't tell?
You can't tell just by looking at the door.
But if you go inside, you can tell right away.
But if I go inside, I can't tell.
It happens a lot.
People use their cell phones.
They go outside and say,
Hello?
Then they go out.
Outside.
But they can't go back inside.
So if you go inside...
There are a lot of people who run away.
Is that so?
If you go inside, how do you tell which one is bad?
Checkpoints.
First, on the counter,
there's an old woman who has a lot of meaning.
She's a fortune teller.
I'm not interested.
How many years has it been?
I'm not interested in that.
There's an old woman who has a lot of meaning.
When you need to pay,
if you say, I don't have that kind of money,
you'll be in trouble.
Just leave it like that.
That's what I'm talking about.
If you do that, you'll be in trouble.
Don't you leave before that happens?
Well, there are a lot of things...
Why are you so quiet?
Say it louder.
There are a lot of checkpoints.
You're kidding, right?
There are a lot of things, right?
There are.
Just say it.
Yes.
Seriously.
Seriously?
With your eyes.
When you first enter,
it'll be about 1 o'clock.
I see.
I understand that.
And then...
There are no checkpoints.
Everyone...
Everyone's close.
I don't care.
It looks fun.
What are you doing?
What?
Can you do it?
What kind of attitude is that?
How can you do that?
I apologize.
That was a bad way to say it.
I'm in a bad mood.
There are still a lot of things.
I apologize.
If you look at me like that,
I don't have the courage to say anything.
What kind of attitude was that?
I don't want to say that.
This program was brought to you
by the following sponsors.