Happy New Year!
Today, we have a special project for the New Year.
We will give you the best of the 2001 Gaki no Tsukai Omoshiro VTR.
This year, I have been selected as a member of the board of directors for four consecutive years.
I am the former downtown manager and the current producer of Lumineza Yoshimoto.
My name is Fujiwara Hiroshi.
Congratulations!
Why do you keep saying that this is the best of the 2002 Gaki no Tsukai Omoshiro VTR?
Who is the best of the 2002 Gaki no Tsukai Omoshiro VTR?
It is not the best of the 2002 Gaki no Tsukai Omoshiro VTR.
So, we have come to the end of the 2002 Gaki no Tsukai Omoshiro VTR.
How was last year?
It was a good year.
We had a drama called Ashi-ta ga Arisa.
It was really good.
We had a record time before that.
We had a record time with this member.
There was a special in the drama.
Please watch it.
It was a good year.
This program is sponsored by the following sponsors.
Let's start.
I will announce the best of the year in 2001.
First, we will announce the top 10 to the 7th place.
The winner is VTR Ruby.
The library is a place where you have to be quiet.
The person who pulls the skull card will be punished.
What will you drink?
What!
That's a book rod.
It's a good year.
It's a book rod.
He makes such a joke and buys any book rod.
Once again, he appeared in the recording of a kid.
I want to say hello to you.
What is that?
That is...
In the TV station in Africa,
there was a girl who said she wanted to be close to me.
In the TV station in Africa?
Hey!
What are you doing?
Look down there.
What is that?
This is a time bomb!
Time is running out!
The staff must have set it up.
As a single person...
I don't want to lose!
What?
As a single person...
I don't want to lose!
How many times have you said that?
As a single person...
I don't want to lose!
You are making a mistake.
As a single person...
I don't want to lose!
You are making a mistake.
Hey!
Kazumi, where are you?
What are you doing?
Hey!
Stop!
Why did you do that?
Kazumi!
No, no, no.
It's not Kazumi.
In addition, Itao started a death match with his wife against Yamazaki vs. Morima.
Itao!
And he even introduced this person.
What is this?
Well, I think I've been on American TV before this program.
The musical instrument is very popular here.
The president who made the goods is very popular.
Did you make it yourself?
I want to say something.
No, no, no.
I wrote it.
Let's take a look.
It's just a sticker.
It's amazing.
I can't catch up with it.
Why?
It doesn't matter.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
I made a mistake.
By the way, I'm sorry.
It's a combination of the two of us.
It's not a combination.
I'm making a lot of money.
You're good at manzai.
What?
The biggest event of the year, the entertainer fishing competition.
This time, a hot battle with gorgeous faces has been held.
I feel good.
It's a smart manzai.
I told you, didn't I?
It's just me.
Who will be the winner of the 7th round?
The winner is...
Matsumoto Matsumoto!
I did it!
Endo's delusion began when a new cute AD came into the program.
Endo's attitude is quite different.
Don't aim at me.
There is no such thing as a tape.
Endo.
Yes.
I was surprised.
Endo's delusion didn't stop even when he went out to the badminton tournament.
How was the referee?
Referee.
Were you in?
I was in because it was raining.
I wasn't in.
What are you talking about?
Let's go.
Matsumoto Matsumoto!
Endo.
Endo!
You are making me angry.
Endo.
Leave.
The director hasn't changed, has he?
No, I'm not. You're leaving it to me, right?
It's strange that Seita is above the director.
It's strange, right?
Why don't you believe me?
I'm doing it this way.
What are you filming?
Nothing at all.
I said it earlier.
Man, you're good.
I didn't do it.
Why are you wearing it?
In celebration of Hamada's 38th birthday, those two came.
Thank you.
Hurry up and give it to me.
Why are you so cool?
Hamada-san, I heard that today is your birthday.
I brought you a present.
No, I don't want it.
Please accept it.
Hamada-san, I don't want it.
It's my birthday after the show.
I don't want it.
Shut up.
Don't touch it.
Stop it.
Oshima wanted to date Hamada no matter what.
So he decided to become Hamada's type by Matsumoto's advice.
He said it many times.
I like a woman who doesn't get hurt even if I put her stomach in her nose.
I like strong women.
Really?
But you don't have a strong woman.
I don't have a strong woman.
What's wrong?
Oshima, I have a strong woman.
What?
I have a strong woman.
I can do it.
You have a strong woman.
I have a strong woman.
She will definitely turn around.
I can do it.
Go, go, go.
I will go.
Hamada-san.
Yes.
Please look at me.
What's wrong?
She is crying.
Are you stupid?
Go away.
It was close.
It wasn't close.
I have to go to the drama location.
I will go home.
Thank you.
It's not good.
Let's go.
I did it.
Please.
Oshima came to the location of the drama.
Hamada was surprised by the action of Oshima.
Please.
What are you wearing?
I don't know.
I like you.
It hurts.
Robocon.
Help me.
You.
The next day.
On this day, 18 Hamashos were divided into enemies and allies.
They fought in baseball.
The fourth is the second Hamashos.
The fifth is the sixth Hamashos.
The sixth is the seventh Hamashos.
The eighth is the eighth Hamashos.
The ninth is the eighth Hamashos.
I know that face.
It's the worst.
I think he was surprised once.
He stood up but didn't know what to do, so he did this again.
It was interesting.
Hamada's attack was amazing.
But he gave up, didn't he?
Yes.
I was beaten by my father and Aikazawa was beaten by my father.
It's the fifth Hamashos.
Is it me?
It's not me.
It's the sixth Hamashos.
Hamada-san.
This is blue, isn't it?
I don't know what you're talking about.
So when the red comes out here, cut it quickly.
There's no such thing.
He tried a lot, but it didn't work out.
The limited time is 6 hours.
And finally, he will challenge the last one.
Got it!
It works!
It doesn't work.
It farts.
Ahh...
I did it!
Amazing!
Seriously amazing!
2nd place
2nd place is the one who made Japan laugh
I did it!
I see
It's a punishment game
It's a serious punishment game
It went too well
We didn't know what to do
It's the 36th time
It's true
56 hours
It's a punishment game
I think it's 1st place
1st place?
I'm getting married
This is the first time Yamazaki has announced that he's getting married
Yamazaki
And Yamazaki went to say goodbye to the women he said was his girlfriend
I love you
Forget about me
It hurts
It hurts but you're really noisy
I want to jump
It hurts
And he said goodbye to Moriman
And it's the last game
I got in my pants
It's in my mouth
Yamazaki
He's a foreigner
But the situation was unexpected
Yamazaki
I don't want to play a game like this
It's like Mori no Ijima
Yamazaki
Mori no Ijima
This is real
You look really happy
I didn't do it
I didn't open my eyes
I'm happy
You're an idiot
Yamazaki finally went to the wedding
When he saw the video, he said he couldn't help but cry
But when he saw the video, he was shocked
He's the one who likes it
It's a lie
Where did you get this?
Last year, we worked really hard
And this is the first place
What?
We can't laugh
It's a terrible story
Everyone, I hope for the best for Gaki no Tsukai and Luminator Yoshimoto
I want to say goodbye
Finally, Mr. Yamada will close the show
How was it?
Thank you for watching