Good evening!
It's been a while.
Well, it's been a while.
Hong Kong has also been converted.
That's right.
You know, the other day...
What?
Well...
I always...
Well, there was a bit of it in the opening today.
You said, M is M, right?
Yes, yes.
I was wondering how far M would go.
The other day, I tried the Ojou-sama course.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's not Jou-sama course, though.
Ojou-sama course?
There's a Ojou-sama course.
It's a bit soft, isn't it?
Yes, it's a bit soft.
I tried that, though.
What do you think about this?
It was lacking.
Well, rather than lacking, it's a bit different, after all.
That's right.
You know, it's like this, right?
Well...
You said, I wonder if you could show me a lot of things.
What?
Well...
Stop it, Soso.
Stop it, Ega.
Well, well, Ega.
I wonder if you could show me a lot of things.
Are you really doing it like this?
It's true.
At that point, you were like, ah!
Ah, I see.
I get it.
And then...
I have to take a bath.
Then again, I have to, well...
What was up with you in that moment?
I was in a standing non-stable position.
What?
Out of the blue?
Yes, it was.
And then, I was told, please go to sleep.
Yes.
And then, I went to sleep.
At that time, the young lady came and pulled on me, and went,
What about it?
It's funny.
Miss, it's funny.
It was really fast.
It was like this.
At that time, I was really embarrassed and excited.
I thought I wanted to be like that.
Do you understand?
I understand.
But surprisingly, I didn't feel angry or embarrassed at all.
What do you mean?
No, it was normal.
Your legs were stretched, but it was normal.
It wasn't normal. I didn't feel anything.
I see.
That means I didn't feel anything.
What didn't you feel?
I didn't feel anything.
I don't think that's true.
You didn't feel anything.
I thought you wanted to show me something.
No, no, no, no.
What did you feel?
It was M.
S doesn't have that.
I don't know about that.
Miss, that's true.
Is that so?
S doesn't have that at all.
You're a little S, aren't you?
I'm a little S.
Either way, it's annoying to be in a situation like that.
What?
Do you want me to show you a lot of things?
Yes, yes, yes.
What I'm told comes to me.
So I'll never be in that situation.
Why does that come to me?
You're telling me a lot of good things.
That's why I don't like M at that stage.
He's a good person.
Why is he a good person?
I want you to show me a lot of things.
You're telling me.
No, no, no, no.
That's not true.
That's not true at all.
I thought he was a good person.
That's not true.
That's not true at all.
What else did you do?
I had a lot of things.
You have a lot of tools.
I can't use it.
You can't say that.
I can't say that.
I'm doing it, but I'm not excited at all.
You're a good person.
I always...
I want to thank the guardian spirit who protects me.
When can I see the guardian spirit?
He said he was behind me.
He said he was behind you.
You can see him if he's around here.
I can see him.
That's not true.
Where is he?
He's right behind me.
Right behind you?
How much distance do you keep?
I'm sticking close to him.
You're sticking close to him.
That means you can't see him even if you look back.
You can't see him.
Right?
When can I see him?
Can I tell you a serious story?
A serious story.
Go ahead.
The guardian spirit...
Actually, this is a lie.
It never comes with you to the toilet.
Why is that?
That's privacy.
Who said that?
I read it in a book.
I didn't say it was privacy.
So if you want to see the guardian spirit,
it's best to poop.
I see.
It's a lie.
It's a lie?
The guardian spirit.
What do you mean?
For example, you're pooping, right?
Then you're just waiting outside.
That's different.
You don't bite no matter what.
You don't smoke.
You're just waiting.
Where's the guardian spirit?
My guardian spirit is in the toilet.
You're just waiting, right?
It never comes with you to the toilet.
When you see the guardian spirit,
if you hear something flowing,
you'll stop smoking.
You don't have to do that.
You don't have to get caught.
It reacts to the sound of the toilet.
If you do this once,
Look at me.
I can already see it.
What's going on?
What does it look like?
It's better not to ask.
It looks good.
Well...
Not everyone is human.
That's all I can say.
You're human, aren't you?
I'm a regent.
You're a bad regent.
I'm not bad.
I'm just strong.
What does it look like?
What?
It looks good, right?
Well, let me tell you.
It's a squid.
Moreover, it's a mongo.
A mongo squid?
It depends on the person.
Among the squids, it's said to be the most evil.
It's a mongo squid.
Be careful.
Even though I've calmed down recently,
at one point,
all my cell phone memory
was filled with a girl's phone number.
I have a question for Mach-chan.
Yes, yes, yes.
I can't get rid of the girl's phone number
that I can't find anymore
from my cell phone memory.
What's Mach-chan's criteria
for getting rid of the memory?
Well, when a woman is gentle,
she'll get excited.
It's better to get rid of it instantly.
Instantly?
Instantly.
What do you mean instantly?
You shouldn't get too excited.
What are you talking about?
You're the one who gets excited, aren't you?
It's me.
What's your criteria for getting rid of the memory?
Well, when she calls me,
when she says she doesn't use it anymore,
You're the one who got killed!
The opposite, the opposite!
You're the one who got killed while crying.
Then where are you going to throw it away?
I don't know!
You're the one who got killed while crying.
You're really really scary!
It's delicious when you cook ramen.
Then, seriously,
if I call you twice and you still don't answer, will you hang up?
What are you talking about?
I'm serious right now.
I'm the type of person who gets chased rather than chased.
You're so cool!
I'm the jelly type.
What?
No, I don't think I can fit into that type.
No, no, no, you're the Tom type.
What kind of jelly do you think I am?
I'm Jelly Fujiwara.
I have a question for Matsumoto-san.
It became popular in some schools in Osaka.
It's called Ossan Tataki.
Who came up with this?
Do you know it?
I know it.
What is it?
It's written there, so I'll read it for you.
You know it, right? Ossan Tataki.
I don't know about that.
Even if you look at me like that...
Read it! Ossan Tataki!
The rules of Ossan Tataki.
Ossan can't do anything.
You draw a circle, and you put in a person who plays the role of Ossan.
Yes, Ossan.
And on top of the line of the circle, there's an old lady standing there.
This is the old lady.
The people around you call the old lady Ossan,
and kick and hit her.
The old lady blocks that.
I think it's the other way around.
The old lady on the circle is being attacked by people outside the circle,
and you're trying to block that?
The old lady goes like this.
Stop it! Stop it!
Ossan, what are you going to do?
I'll kick her from here.
What are you doing?
Let's give it a try.
Hey!
I'm going to do Ossan Tataki now!
Did you hear what I just said?
Did you understand the rules?
Should we decide on Ossan?
Let's decide on Ossan.
We're all Ossan.
Rock, paper, scissors.
I lost.
You're Ossan.
There's one old lady.
Let's decide on the old lady.
Rock, paper, scissors.
We'll decide on the other person.
The other person.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
I'm protecting you!
Everyone is looking at you!
He ran away!
I'm protecting you!
I'm going to do Ossan.
Ossan...
I don't like Ossan.
He's painful!
He's painful, right?
He doesn't think much about his seniors or juniors.
Should we change the old lady?
Let's change the old lady.
You can stay as Ossan.
I want to change the old lady.
The old lady should only be touched.
I know.
This is the battlefield.
Wait a minute.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!