The next day
He's a fool
Oh really?
What happened?
I'm going on a date with an Australian today
I was on the phone in the car
Hello? Hello?
Loretta?
Loretta? Me? Me?
Hosei-kun
He's a fool
What should we talk about?
You're not in a situation to ask me to sign
It happens
I was in the rehearsal of the drama
I was in the middle of the rehearsal
I was doing that look look
There were a lot of old ladies
Once again, Barbara was doing the rehearsal
It's dangerous
I came out of the bathroom
My daughter is a fan
This is the opposite side
The two of them were holding me like this
I was a little embarrassed
I was wondering if they would sign for me
It's impossible now
What are you doing?
You have to say something like that
I can't say it
If I were an amateur
I would probably go
When I was in middle school
When I came to the baseball field in my hometown
Right?
I was like
Please sign for me
Right?
I can't say it now
You're running away
I said it calmly
That's right
I would go when I was an amateur
I can't say it now
I can't say it
On the way to the field
I was walking on this sidewalk
Pei-san and Parko-san were walking
No one was looking at me
But
It's hard for anyone to walk
After the shoot today
When I came in the car
It was the car in front of you
I was waiting for the traffic light
I couldn't stand it
When I went down and went into the public toilet
Wow, it's a beach
I went into the public toilet
I came out and walked
I'm just an old man
I don't have a nose or a tongue
I don't have a tongue
I can't stand it
It's hard for anyone
That's right
I finally found a hobby
That's a good thing
I'll do this
A star-seeing party
What is a star-seeing party?
This is a star-seeing party
This party is a birthday party
It's a party
A star-seeing party?
It's a star-seeing party
I'm going to do this
With your bare hands?
No, with a telescope
Of course I want it with bare hands
What am I?
I'm a junkie
You think that's old
I'll look at a telescope
You're trying to do something with a telescope
You're trying to buy a telescope
No, no, no
I'm just looking at the stars
I'm looking at the stars
And the stars are being looked at by the stars
But it's strange that you're looking at the stars by yourself
No, no
I've been thinking about it
Not only looking at the stars
But also holding the stars against the shutter
Holding them against the shutter?
Are you taking pictures?
Yes, I'm taking pictures
I've been thinking about it
It's a lot of fun
When I take a picture
I take a picture with oil
You take a picture while looking at the stars
Yes, I take a picture with oil
Yes, I take a picture
And then I write an image song about it
That's a lot of work
We have a great system
We do it with a camera
We're almost always there
Making sounds
And when I'm done with this
I'm done with the sound
So I'll add salt to it
And make it into a song
And then my hobbies
They're all over the place
No, no, no
There are a lot of big differences between you and me
For example, looks
The length of your legs
There are a lot of differences
You're completely different
The length of my legs
Do you know the length of my legs?
This is a hidden part
My legs are really long
This is a serious story
A stylist asked me to measure my legs
I measured my legs
The next day I got a call
They asked me to measure them again
I said, that's not possible
You're Japanese, right?
I came back to measure them again
I said, ah, I knew it
I wasn't wrong
But looking at your legs
It doesn't look long
No matter how you look at it, you're normal
It's completely different
I'm more of a man than you think
Ah, ah, ah, ah
No, no, no
I'm more of a man than you think
So
I don't know much about this
But if I lift this up
It's about 1,000 yen
Really?
No, really
No way
It's over here
Even if I lift this up
Nothing will change
No, no, no
Touch it
What?
Wait, wait
Don't do it like this
What do you mean, touch it?
Then touch my a**
Why?
But I can tell
Then don't look
Look at it with your eyes
Don't trust your eyes
Look at my a**
Hurry
Hurry and look at my a**
That's what I'm saying
You shouldn't look for hobbies
You can't do this forever
Birdwatching or something
No
What's so funny?
You're an idiot
In the past
That's like a bird made by humans
It was born from humans
Wild birds are more
There's no difference
They look the same
They're rougher
I don't care if they're rougher
They have a rough personality
I can't tell
The birds in the past are rougher
I can understand that
The birds in the wild are rougher
I don't care
They're always rougher
Even if they talk to you?
I don't care if the world is rougher
I don't care
They're rougher
They kick you
I want to see that
Bang, bang, bang, bang
They kick you
But I don't care
Even if the birds kick me
I don't care
Last time, Mr. Matsumoto announced
The world's 3 most handsome men
This time, he's announcing
The world's 3 most sad things
For example
Of course you can't be in the top 3
But at home, you know
When you watch TV
When you're lying down
And there's an ass in front of you
What kind of probability is that?
If you're lying down in a dressing room
And there's an ass in front of you
What kind of probability is that?
Whose ass is that?
Whose teacher is that?
You know that
When you're at home
There's nothing but yourself
That must be sad
You're living alone
When you have a sore throat
You get a high fever
You're alone
You have to do everything by yourself
You know that
There's that
When you're cleaning
You're cleaning like this
When you're doing this
When you're doing that
You can't handle the vacuum cleaner
That's sad
Don't say that's sad
I feel responsible
That's your responsibility
What's the 3 most handsome men in the world?
The 3 most handsome men in the world
That's what everyone wants to know
That's right
This is not in the book
It's not in the 3rd book
It's the 3 most handsome men in the world
And the pizza chef
That's one thing
And the foie gras
That's the foie gras, right?
Are you crazy?
You're definitely crazy
Why did Mr. Matsumoto refuse to be a member of the Globes?
Please tell us
It seems like you've been waiting for a long time
Komuro-san's way of inviting me
He's so annoying
He's so arrogant
He's always asking for my phone number
What are you doing today?
He's always calling
He's always calling my phone
Komuro, Komuro
You're really here, right?
I wanted you to be in that picture
I don't want to refuse
I thought it was okay
I wanted him to come
Why?
I said okay
Komuro-san is okay
But Mark
He's so annoying
What are you doing?
I went to eat with Mark
With the Globes
Mark was sitting in front of me
He's amazing
I was surprised
When I looked at him
Mark was dropping the Coke
It was Mark
Mark dropped it
I picked it up
I looked at him
Mark wasn't wearing it
Mark was naked
He took it off
He took it all off
When did Mark become like that?
I don't know
He took it off
I thought he would come
Where is he?
In Komuro-san's office
He pretended to pour the tea
And came in
This program was brought to you by the sponsors