I'm sorry.
As always, thank you very much.
I received a rose that I hated in the hospital room.
It was a little annoying.
I received the rose! Thank you very much.
Huh?
I'm the master of the house, so I'm the AD Otomo!
Hello!
What's wrong?
Um...
Hey!
No one woke me up!
I was sleeping and I saw a bear under my eyes.
I had to fool him, so I made a bear in the middle of the night.
You fooled him?
That's fine. We'll talk about that later.
Today's opening is...
It's the AD Otomo battle.
This is the first time!
Actually, we have an AD Otomo in our staff.
He has a lot of letters.
First of all, this is...
By the way, I don't have a boyfriend, so I can't sleep well.
I'd be happy if someone could introduce him to me.
So I have a suggestion.
Why don't we have an AD Otomo battle for the first time?
I see.
We've got four of them.
Oh, really?
First of all, the four people who wrote this letter, come on out!
These are the people who said they liked Otomo.
What's your name?
I'm Yuki Naito, 23 years old.
I'm Keiko Serita, 18 years old.
I'm Michiko Sakai, 24 years old.
I'm Naoko Nishikawa, 18 years old.
You're all so quiet.
Who are these people?
Now, if you want Otomo, come on out.
And ask Otomo a lot of questions.
I'm sure some of you haven't seen Otomo yet.
I wonder what it's like to be called an old man by four women.
For now, we're the ED Otomo lotto.
This program is brought to you by the 4th and the sponsor of this program.
I will ask you 4 questions from now on. Please answer them correctly.
Are you number 1?
I think I am.
Number 1?
You are number 4, right?
Yes, I am.
It's easy to understand. Number 1, number 4, number 2, number 3.
It's complicated.
It's easy to answer with 1, 2, 3, 4.
It's interesting.
I can't say that.
I want you to answer honestly.
I want you to say it again.
When was your first experience?
With whom? How?
Are you asking me to tell you the answer?
Yes.
Are you saying yes?
When I was 18 years old, I was with my girlfriend.
You were dating at that time.
It's not like that.
That's true.
It was 7 years ago.
You were dating at that time.
Say it again.
You were dating at home.
Is that the first time?
Yes, it's the first time.
I see.
Did you two get along well at first?
No, we failed at first.
That's right.
I don't know.
I was like that, too.
You didn't listen to me.
It hurts.
I can't take it anymore.
I went to the hotel next door.
Are you kidding me?
Let's go.
Is it true that you are living together?
I often go to my friend's house.
We live together.
I see.
You go to your friend's house.
You don't live together.
You lied to me.
I was on the phone while editing.
You were on the phone while editing.
Why are you on the phone?
I was on the phone while editing.
You were on the phone while editing.
I'm sorry.
Let's take a picture.
One by one.
It's about 30 seconds, right?
Yes.
Hello.
One by one.
Where are you from?
I'm from Japan.
Continue.
Have you ever come to watch our program?
Not once.
Not once?
I'm a high school student.
Do you watch it every week?
Yes.
How old are you?
24 years old.
24 years old is your age.
That's right.
I was surprised.
It's funny.
I was frustrated.
Shut up.
Hello.
Have you ever seen me before?
What?
I saw you on TV.
On TV?
Your baseball is amazing.
What?
Your baseball technique.
My technique?
Yes.
Your batting was amazing.
I did it on purpose.
It was cool.
Really?
Yes.
You're lying.
You have the time to fool around.
That's why I called you.
Please open the chair.
Yes.
It doesn't matter what you say or hear.
Please put on the eye mask.
Okay?
I asked you a question.
And you talked to each other.
He is in front of you.
He is different from you.
If you think so, please go home.
Okay?
Please come closer.
Here.
Don't fall.
Please judge.
What will they do?
There is one person left.
I want to be with Otomo.
Otomo, please take off the eye mask.
Okay.
What is this?
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
Let's do our best.
Yes.
Hello.
What is this?
Why did you suddenly pay 2,000 yen?
It's the same amount as before.
I don't want to talk about this.
But I can't ignore it.
What?
It's something to celebrate.
It's black.
Thank you very much.
I will collect 1,000 yen each from here.
Why?
I have known him for a long time.
I can't believe that he has a child.
Why?
When I go back to my hometown, all my friends are like that.
Why don't you say that?
I have a lot to say.
You are amazing.
Thank you very much.
Let's talk about the program.
Did you see the program?
No.
I saw the program until the last minute.
You are cold.
I am scared.
What are you scared of?
You are scary.
What?
You have blood.
You are scary when you see blood.
I saw the program until the last minute.
I heard that you cut the grass here.
I have been cutting grass for a long time.
I can't cut grass.
You can't cut grass.
No, no, no.
So I do not cut grass.
I have to cut grass.
If I cut grass, I will have a lot of grass.
I do not cut grass.
So I cut grass.
If I cut it, it will be like an egg.
If you cut, it will be like an egg.
If you do not cut, it will be like an egg.
You have to do it well.
The grass will not be too thick.
I want you to see my face.
Why?
Which side is the face when it comes out from the head?
Huh?
It's facing this way, right?
This is the back of the head.
Why? It doesn't go in like this, right?
It goes in like this.
The earth comes out while rotating like this, right?
What!?
Rotating like this.
It's so weird!
So if I say, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
The earth comes out like this, so I'm like, what are you doing!?
It comes out like this.
At first, I immediately started crying.
Huh?
I immediately started crying.
I don't know about that, but I was outside and I heard a cry.
I was outside and I heard a cry.
Yeah.
What was that?
Really?
Yeah.
I heard a really loud cry.
I was really moved.
And it was like this.
It was like this, right?
Huh?
Why was it like this?
I opened the door and ran around.
And the name, what was it? I gave it a name.
What was it?
Ikumi.
Don't do that.
You gave it a name?
Yes.
I was like, what!?
You said you'd give it a name.
That's right! You can't ask me to do it!
Why can't I ask you to do it?
If you were a comedian, you should have given it a funny name.
Ikumi-kun?
What's with that Ikumi-kun?
What is it?
It's sake!
Bring me sake!
What's an interesting name?
That's...
Maeba-bon!
You should ask yourself.
If you were born as my child, would you give it a name like Matsumoto Maeba-bon?
That's right!
Think about it!
You don't want to give it a name? Bring me sake!
You're that young! You can't laugh!
You should give it a name.
What?
If you were born as my child, would you give it a name?
I'm a copy robot.
What's with the perm?
I'm thinking of names like Sato or Tanaka.
I'd give it a name like Suzuki.
I'd call it Matsumoto Sato.
You can't make me laugh!
Bring it on!
Like Matsumotoppe.
That's right.
You can't call it a sentence.
Like Matsumotokana.
Like Matsumotodayo.
Oh, it's a sentence.
If you keep calling it that...
If I wake up in the morning, I'll call it Matsumoto.
You can't call it a sentence.
I'll call it a sentence.
I'll call it a sentence too, but if you're born again, you can call it Saki.
I don't want to.
You're not manly.
I'm not manly.
Why didn't you ask me?
Why?
Did you ask Sanma?
Yes.
Did you ask her?
If it was me, I would have asked her.
You should have asked her on TV.
You're thinking of weird things.
You're only thinking of weird things.
You're not thinking of making it right, are you?
It's about people anyway.
You're so annoying!
It's like...
It's like the first day of the waiter,
It's like the first day of the waiter, Mr. Japayuki.
What is that?
I'm amazing.
I've been up for about 30 hours today.
You don't have to brag about it.
I'm going home early today.
I'm sleepy.
When I get home, I'll be like...
I'll be like...
That's funny.
I was given a job when I was in high school.
I'm an old lady in Osaka.
This is nothing.
I said,
I thought,
I'd wake up again at night.
I woke up, Mom!
I can't do that, okay?
I'll do it, okay?
In the middle of the day, in the middle of the winter...
You don't have to do that to wake me up.
Okay!
What are you doing?
I feel sorry for you.
I feel sorry for you, but I can't help it.
Stop it. Let me sleep.
Hitoshi, you should shake your butt and beg.
Who?
This guy is an idiot.
You said it today, right?
I'm going to get out of downtown.
I'm not in a band.
That's what you are.
You said you were going to get out of guitar and bass.
You said you were going to get out of downtown.
What are you going to do by getting out of downtown?
What are you going to do?
Well...
At this time, I'm going to start laughing.
I'm going to do something funny in front of the producer.
Don't laugh!
Come on out.
Are you a general today?
Yes.
What are you doing now?
From April, I decided to study for 35 minutes.
What do you study?
I want to be a musician.
I see.
You look funny.
What is the meaning of this word?
I don't know.
Really? Why?
I have an old man and an old woman.
You have an old woman and an old woman.
Don't say such a big thing.
Don't you usually say something like,
I have an injury, so I'm scared.
You are a civilized person.
I'm not a civilized person.
If you don't know,
If you ask about the disease of the anus,
I'll give you 25,000 questions.
Say it.
Well...
Anus...
Ressho.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Yukiko Abe.
Hello.
This is a popular game in my class.
I'll give you a quiz.
Is the Shinkansen a man or a woman?
I don't know, but it's a man.
Why is that?
I don't know.
Is the Shinkansen a man or a woman?
This is a man.
Why?
Because it flies the station.
I see.
It's an adult joke.
Is the umbrella a man or a woman?
Woman.
Why?
Because...
I got hit by the rain.
I'm wet.
Oh, my God.
If you get hit by the rain, you're wet.
I'm wet.
The answer is woman.
I got hit by the rain.
Men and women are in everything in this world.
Is that so?
That's right.
For example?
Men and women are in everything in this world.
What?
This table?
That's right.
Which one is this?
Don't you know this?
Tell me quickly.
I know gender and age.
Which one is it?
This is a man.
How old is he?
Thirty.
Why?
What's the reason?
I'll be thirty this year.
Why?
There's a reason for this.
Men and women are in everything in this world.
This is a child's play.
What's the reason?
There's a reason.
There's no reason.
How old are you?
Twenty-seven.
Is it a man or a woman?
It's a man.
Why?
I don't know.
Where is it?
Can you show me?
It's good.
I'm impressed.
What?
Can you give it to me?
Give it to me.
Why are you looking at me?
I made it.
This is a man and a woman.
I feel sorry for one of them.
I'll give it to you.
Hello.
As I said last week,
I have an announcement to make.
On Monday, April 8th,
from 7 to 9 pm,
we will have a special show
with the boys and girls
in the special program.
Let's surprise them.
We will be the surprise prank champion.
We are looking for surprise people
in this program.
We are looking for people
who can do this kind of special skills.
Please write a letter
about what you can do.
We are looking for assistants.
We have a lot of assistants
who can do this kind of special skills.
Please write a letter
about what you can do.
Anything else?
Let me see.
We should find assistants.
I see.
I'm looking forward to it.
We are going to surprise them.
On April 8th,
from 7 to 9 pm,
I'd like to ask you to do it through this on-air.
Is it okay, Otomo?
Yes.
I look forward to working with you.
He's got smoke coming out of his head.
That's all for this week's Dantan's Child's Play.
Until next week, goodbye!
This program is brought to you by Rion.
Thanks for watching!