You're so cute.
You're so popular.
You're so funny.
Well, there are many things.
There are many things.
Are there many things?
There aren't.
There was a letter in the mail the other day.
I wrote a lot of things.
To put it simply,
I asked him to lend me 3 million yen.
You can lend it to me.
Please lend me 3 million yen.
Why didn't you write that you have it?
I made a card.
When I made a card,
I felt like I had all my money,
so I used it up.
What?
It's normal.
It has nothing to do with me.
I thought it had something to do with me.
I was a fan of Mr. Matsumoto.
When I used up all of his money,
I had a lot of debt.
It's different.
It's personal.
I want a bag.
I want shoes.
I want a month's rent of 3 million yen.
And then I want him to lend it to me.
I'm going.
When I use it,
people ask me to lend money a lot.
Really?
Why?
I don't even have money to borrow.
Everyone has cell phones.
I do, too.
Why?
I'm so angry!
Well, I'm sorry.
It's good that you can get in touch with her.
But there are times when I can't get in touch with her.
It's really annoying.
I can call her, right?
And then...
I don't know if I keep calling her.
If you know, you can call her again.
If I call her again, I'll call her again.
And then...
I called her three times.
And when I called her again, she disappeared.
You've been fine until now, haven't you?
That's right.
Why are you suddenly getting sick?
I'm really angry.
But everyone's okay with that.
Harutatsu-kun has a cell phone in his bag, right?
I don't know if someone is pressing it inside, but it's ringing.
When I look at it, it's 8888.
What is it?
What kind of situation is this?
Well, that's true.
But when I look at it, it's 88828.
What are you talking about?
It's been 8 all the time.
Where did you go?
Sometimes I call her and it's ringing.
It's 88828, and no one's answering.
I'm so angry.
It's ringing, but it's not ringing.
I don't think it's time to sell cell phones yet.
It's not complete yet.
Even if you're talking to a car driver, sometimes the other person's voice suddenly sounds like a robot.
I'm scared.
Your voice sounds like a robot, too.
I'll tell you a little bit.
If you press it, this part will light up, right?
That's right.
It'll light up, so you can use it in the car.
But the time it lights up is short.
Do you understand?
So, for example, if it's a PokéBell, you press it twice.
It disappears while you're doing it.
I don't understand.
Wait until all the PokéBell are in.
What's wrong with you?
It'll be gone in a second.
It disappears.
You'll fall asleep.
You'll fall asleep, and when you look at it, there are three of them.
If you look at it like this, you'll fall asleep again.
I'm looking at him.
I don't even know where I'm looking at.
I don't know. I'm looking at an apple.
That's completely sick.
You were fine until now, weren't you?
I'm hungry.
That's something everyone can think of.
Please be careful.
What should I be careful about?
No, no, no.
The knitting.
What about the knitting?
So please be careful when you wash it.
You know, don't you?
I told you to put it in the net and wash it.
But don't say it.
I didn't expect you to be so careful.
Thank you very much.
The audience is so energetic.
Everyone is.
It's okay.
When you watch this kind of energetic audience on TV, your laughter sounds like a lie.
It sounds like you're stabbing someone.
Right?
I'll take it off.
I don't know anything about TV anymore.
Don't say it.
There's a lot of things I don't understand.
What the hell are you talking about?
What country are you talking about?
I don't know.
You're supporting the Titans, aren't you?
I'm supporting them.
Do the Titans win?
The Titans win.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Are you going to give up?
No.
I'm in a bad place right now.
Do something if you're going to win.
What?
Don't give up.
You'll get punished.
I'm not saying anything.
I'm not going to give up.
This is embarrassing.
This is hard.
I'm not going to give up no matter where I go.
Please, Hanako.
Okay.
I'm not going to give up no matter where I go.
When something sad happens, you spread your wings wide and fly in the night sky while crying.
Why are you so sad?
You almost got knocked down the other day.
Are you okay?
Well, that's...
Put your wings out before that.
It's a hand.
You can't fly with a hand.
What?
A hand becomes a wing.
I see.
You can only fly when something sad happens.
Yes.
You can't fly now.
I think it happened four times in the past.
What?
Death.
Someone died.
Yes.
Something sad.
It's death.
That's right.
Death is the saddest thing.
Right?
Yes.
Who died first?
When Pearl died.
That stupid dog.
It's called Gakushakenya.
You're lying.
It's not a dog.
It's called Gakushakenya.
It's completely Gakushakenya.
Who?
That person.
When Pearl died?
Yes, when Pearl died.
How did you fly?
How did I fly?
Do you have a posture when you fly?
Yes, I do.
I can fly from the second floor window.
You're old.
Old?
I can go down once.
It's like Choro-kyu.
That's right.
It's the principle of Choro-kyu.
I go down once and then go forward.
Do you understand?
What are you doing?
I'm going in.
What?
What are you going in?
I'm going in.
There's a crack in the air.
You're going in there?
Yes.
Please show me.
What?
Please show me your posture.
My posture?
Yes.
What?
I'm going in.
Yes, yes, yes.
From here on, you're like the head of the picture.
Stop it.
It's completely different.
The shape is the head of the picture.
Zen, I'm conscious of something.
If you taste the bottom of sadness, you can fly.
The bottom of sadness, the bottom of sadness, the bottom of sadness.
It's all about the bottom of sadness.
I want to go up because it's the bottom of sadness.
Please tell me that, too.
I'm going to be shot down soon.
This is a lie.
It's a lie.
It's all a lie.
What is harder and harder than bungee jumping?
In the end, there's a limit to what's scary.
That's why I have no choice but to add to the fear.
Hey.
You have a lot of guts.
That's scary.
Hey.
Where are you looking at?
Are you going to stay still?
Hey.
This is the scariest.
That's all I have.
Tiger, yakuza.
I only have a cutter knife.
Cutter?
Well, well, well.
That's why the yakuza rides on the tiger.
I'm scared if the tiger has a cutter.
The tiger is riding on it.
The yakuza is not riding on it.
The tiger has a cutter here.
Oh, I see.
I'd be scared if I had poison on me.
You're a kid.
That's my way of thinking.
What kind of gum should I throw away?
The person who invented the word gum is a genius.
Is that so?
Because there's no food like this.
It doesn't go away permanently.
It doesn't go away.
Don't you put gum in your mouth?
There are people who swallow gum.
But if you swallow gum, it's bad for your body.
That's right.
Well, I'll tell you the truth.
You're a troublemaker.
Don't you tell me when you throw away gum?
When I chew gum for a long time, I throw up.
That's not funny.
I don't think it's funny.
No, no, no.
I'm not talking about that.
Why?
I'll throw up.
It's not good for your taste.
If you keep complaining about it, it'll be disgusting.
That's right.
Some people say good things about it.
It's the same when you throw away the gum as it is when you throw away a woman.
Well, say it.
When you throw away a woman...
Love is all about excitement.
While you're excited, your love will always...
...grow into a hole.
It will blossom.
Right?
Love and...
I'm asking about when you throw away the gum.
Is it still going on?
It's still going on.
Excitement. You'll meet her today.
Wait till 10 o'clock.
You'll meet her today.
It's going to be a long time.
You'll get excited thinking about it.
I hope so.
During this time, love is alive.
Let's talk about the gum.
The gum and the woman are the same.
When you throw away the gum, you won't get excited.
What's that?
I'm sure you'll get excited when you throw away the gum.
I don't care if you cry all of a sudden.
It's like this.