Broken Thunder. How far is Broken Thunder?
How far is it? You already know, right?
We're going to buy some mountain climbing goods.
You're in high spirits again today.
I'm not in high spirits at all.
During the season, Machan discovered that there was a mountain climbing tour.
He couldn't be underestimated by the staff.
It seems that the way to buy mountain climbing goods that looks like a tour is the next street.
I want to go to Tateyama, but it's Tateyama at this time of the year.
That was strange.
Then...
Manager! Manager!
What kind of manager are you?
I'm going to climb from the front of the station.
It doesn't matter where you climb.
The mountain is nice.
This is about 15 seconds.
Tateyama.
Starting with the winter that melts the silver world on one side,
It is the longing of climbers through the seasons.
In order to reach Tateyama, Hama-chan arranges mountain climbing goods.
It's a list of things to buy, right?
Yes.
And what are the goods that Machan says are usually arranged?
There's nothing strange about it.
What are the goods that Machan arranges?
I'm angry.
Are you angry?
I'm very angry.
Why?
Jopper.
There is no such thing.
There are red and blue Jopper.
Please buy one by one.
This is Burikko.
It's dangerous when you fall from the mountain, so put it on your shoulder.
It's like a sponge.
But it's plastic, isn't it?
Yes, today is plastic.
What is it?
This is Catherine.
This is a dumpling.
If you say Catherine, you will be laughed at.
Is that so?
What are you talking about?
What is this person?
It's like a mountain climber.
Only in Yamada.
There is no such thing, right?
I wonder how to change it.
It was beautiful.
I'm angry.
I'm sorry.
You should apologize.
It's okay to apologize.
What kind of shame should I have?
I'm angry.
You should apologize.
What are you saying?
No, that's not true.
Really?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Shio.
I can't say it.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Welcome.
I want to go to Tateyama.
At this time, Tateyama is the best.
Tateyama is the best, isn't it?
Welcome.
I want to go to Tateyama.
At this time, Tateyama is the best.
I get off at the station.
I'll give it to you.
Yamaha is good.
What is this?
Jopper.
Red Jopper and...
Red Jopper and blue Jopper.
This is it.
And...
Jopper.
How many?
It's so small.
You can't even put it on a plate.
This is plastic.
Plastic.
There are two types.
And...
Dumplings.
I know the name.
Cassidy.
This is it.
This is the flow.
It's good like this.
Yes.
In the meantime, Yamaha is good.
Yamaha is really good.
Yes.
I understand.
It's like you're motivated to make a video.
I'm not motivated.
Are you a middle-aged man?
I'm the one who's cool.
I'm not a middle-aged man.
Hamada-san.
Yes.
If it's like that, I'll send you a message.
According to what I heard, this store only sells two.
That's right.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm the one who's going.
Then stay with me.
Let's go.
Nothing has changed.
Can you hear my voice?
I can hear it.
It's a good song.
Yes.
That's why I'm going up the mountain.
I'm going with these legs.
As a feeling.
Yes.
I understand.
Let's go.
Yamaha is good.
Yes.
It's a rock climbing store.
Yamaha is good.
It's the first time.
What?
I want to go to Tateyama.
Yes.
At this time, I want to go to Tateyama.
He's laughing.
I can't call the manager.
Manager.
Are you the manager?
No.
The manager is not here today.
He's at the exhibition.
You know Yamaha, right?
Yes.
I want to go to Tateyama station.
Tateyama station.
Yes.
It seems that Tateyama station is far away.
It's better to be away from Tateyama station.
Be away from Tateyama station.
Look at various things.
Yamaha is good.
Joppa.
Can you give me Joppa?
I want to get a dumpling.
I'll give you a dumpling.
Please give me a dumpling.
Excuse me.
A dumpling.
Please go to the store that sells dumplings.
Laugh.
It's a cushion.
It's a cushion that you can put on your shoulder when you fall.
That's right.
Yamaha is good.
Laugh.
It's a cushion.
Yamaha is good.
It's better to speak in a loud voice.
It's a cushion.
Yamaha is good.
It's a dumpling.
It's been a long time since I've been in Yamaha.
I hate it.
Laugh.
The general customer is laughing.
I'm sweating.
I don't like it.
Oh, I see.
I'm embarrassed.
Um...
Did one of you die?
Hey, why are you in such a good place?
Huh?
Did you take a bath?
Where did you go?
I left something in the vase.
Why are you dying here?
You imitated me.
I don't like it.
I'm sorry.
Will you apologize to me?
I'll apologize to you.
There are many things.
Did you watch the game last week?
I went climbing today.
Look at the result.
It's been a long time since I've been embarrassed.
Hey, your intonation is strange.
It's dirty.
You couldn't say such a thing in the previous simulation.
I can understand it.
I'm sorry.
Can you give me a dumpling?
What?
If you give me a dumpling, I'll eat it.
That was the opposite of my father.
Ask me anything.
If you want to do something new.
I've never said I didn't know when someone asked me something.
I'm serious.
You're pretending.
I can move the jumbo jet.
What?
What do you want to say?
Do you know this story?
There are three pilots.
They don't eat the same food before the flight.
Really?
Why?
If they eat the same food, who will control the plane?
It's not that easy to understand.
I don't know how to stand.
Everyone knows that.
Tell me something you don't know.
Ayami, stop it.
Everyone knows how to eat.
I have a lot of knowledge.
If you want to control the plane, tell me how to do it.
Okay.
Do you call it a cockpit?
We call it a cockpit.
It's just a name.
Cockpit.
How do you get into a cockpit?
I don't want to get in.
You can't get in when you're on the plane.
I can get in.
No, no, no.
There's another place you can get in.
No, I can't get in.
No, you can't get in.
There's a door in the back.
You can't get in from the same place.
I can get in.
You can't get in.
At that time, the cook cooks.
The captain eats.
The cook cooks.
When everyone finished eating, the captain said,
Everyone is ready.
Why are you talking like a master?
It's true.
Everyone finished eating.
Oh, really?
What are you doing?
Don't put it in.
Are you a keyboardist?
You put a line in such a place.
I'll be right there.
It's a big deal.
That's how it is.
If you came later and everyone was in the same place,
I don't know where you would be.
There's a door next to it.
When you say it at home,
There's a door like that.
And then...
It's like this.
It's the opposite of fame.
What am I doing?
Well, it's stupid.
Which one do you do first?
First, you have to start with the voice recorder.
You have to record it.
I'm recording it here.
That's right.
First of all, you have to operate the voice recorder.
You can't talk.
That's why, well...
Wait, wait, wait.
It's the same old story.
You have to push it.
It's a plane.
I don't have a gacha.
Shut up, shut up.
If you make a mistake, you won't be pushed.
It's just a plane.
You're being pushed at the same time.
It's like yesterday.
You turned on the switch, didn't you?
I turned on the switch.
What are you going to do with that?
Well, that's the inside of the plane.
Wait a minute.
That's right.
From the top.
It depends on the plane.
What kind of plane is that?
That's a 727.
It's so old.
Boeing 727.
That was when I was in elementary school.
It's still flying.
It's like this.
What's the weather like now?
Is the weather sunny?
It's like this.
Do you understand?
How do you start the engine?
What?
When you start the engine, you're already excited.
That's a very important job.
If you're in a car, you have to start the engine.
It's not as easy as driving a car.
That's right.
How do you start the engine?
First of all, there's a lever here.
There's a lever.
It's a wire-like lever.
You pull it like this.
There's a lever here, too.
What are you doing?
That makes the wings look good.
It's manual work to make the wings look good.
It's a little saggy.
It's saggy.
That's just a way to do it.
It's difficult.
You can't do it with wings.
Yes, yes.
There's a way to do it.
There are a lot of buttons.
You have to lower all of them.
It's a mixer.
I have to make the voice recorder on the B side.
You can do that until it works.
It's 60 minutes.
It's not flashy.
It's just moving.
You're going to make it on the B side?
If it doesn't work, it won't be flashy.
You can't erase everything.
The one you recorded before.
I want to leave the last song.
That's good.
I have a request for Mr. Matsumoto who won the National Nutrition Award.
Please dance a touching dance that will make the audience cry.
Did you win the National Nutrition Award with a touching dance?
Yes.
Every year, I'm invited to the award ceremony.
Do you go every year?
It's a marriage ceremony.
Do you go to dance a touching dance?
Yes, I do.
Do you cry when you see me?
I'm not the kind of person who only offers laughter.
I'm not like that.
I don't care. Just dance.
Open your mouth wide.
Open your heart.
What?
That's all I have to say.
This year, this season has come again.
That's a nonsense speech.
It's Komatsu-san's speech.
Who is Komatsu-san?
Komatsu Masao-san's speech.
No way.
This season has come again.
Every year, I'm invited to the award ceremony.
What?
I'm not the kind of person who only offers laughter.
What kind of costume are you wearing?
I'm wearing a short-sleeved shirt on my back.
Are you crying because of that?
I'm wearing a kimono.
That's right.
Are you hiding your face?
I'm hiding my face.
You're hiding your face.
Your face is creepy.
I can't cry.
You're fast.
What's the funniest movie you've ever seen?
What do you mean?
Tell me the funniest movie you've ever seen.
Why are you suddenly asking me that?
I'm suddenly angry.
Tell me the funniest movie you've ever seen.
A battle without justice.
Was it funny to watch a few movies?
I'm sorry.
Komatsu Masao.
That's all for today.
This season has come again.
What?
I'm going to cry.
That's great.
Hey!
I have a question for Matsumoto.
I was trying to get in a cab the other day, but I passed it by.
How can I get a taxi driver to notice me?
Is that possible?
It can't be that you don't notice.
It's a driver's license.
That's right.
There's no doubt about it.
I'm coming and I'm doing this.
That's right.
I don't like that.
If the road at Tokyo is a U-turn, you can't get in.
Is that so?
That's right.
I would have asked him to pick me up.
Really?
If it was Osaka, he would have told me.
He would have told me.
Tokyo is a place like that.
It is.
Let's go.
JR Inashimono's...
What? A radio?
What?
This is a good thing sometimes.
I was very excited.
I was about to sing a song.
JR Inashimono has 80% of the shares of the Japanese stock market.
If he had 80% of the shares...
What?
The other day, I was about to catch the Shinkansen.
The door closed in front of me and I had to leave.
Is there a way to catch the Shinkansen at that moment?
Of course.
Is there a way?
In what condition?
I was running.
You were running.
I was singing.
And?
I didn't know if I would make it in time or not.
The door closed in front of me.
The door closed.
I went inside.
It was terrible.
I wanted to get inside.
The Shinkansen started to move.
It was moving.
Even if the Shinkansen started to move, I could stop it.
Is that so?
Yes.
Please tell me.
First of all, I tickle the heart of the Shinkansen.
The pride of the Shinkansen is high.
I think I'm the best at everything.
I tickle it a little.
I see.
When the pride of the Shinkansen started to move, I didn't think it was that fast.
What?
I'm a Shinkansen.
I didn't think so.
The pride of the Shinkansen is high.
I was surprised.
I saw the round part.
When the round part of the Shinkansen started to move, the door opened.
Please stop it.
Is it that fast?
I was worried about my mother.
I got a call from my father this morning.
His wife passed away this morning.
I'll knock it down.
What did you bring?
Did you bring a car?
The round part of the Shinkansen is high.