It's going to rain now!
My sister is coming back from the hospital.
He's excited to play games with the cats.
It's big enough to play music.
You're cute.
Mom?
He's excited to see my mom.
Nevertheless, we managed to get in.
Happy New Year right?
Ah?!
You are보리 gamma
I don't know what you're talking about.
You're crazy.
I'm sorry.
You're late.
Good morning.
Hello.
I'm the guide, Akimi Nagayama.
Nice to meet you.
Is there anything you don't know?
I don't know.
What's your name?
I'll tell you.
I'm Akimi Nagayama.
You're angry, aren't you?
I'm back.
How was it?
We're going to have a picnic.
I think you all know about the picnic.
I'd like to sing a song.
One, two, three.
Let's go over the hill.
Let's blow into the earth.
Why are you all so shy?
Let's sing together.
Let's pierce the blue sky.
Let's go over the hill.
Put sunglasses on and melt the water.
When you put it on, it changes.
What?
I'm sorry.
It doesn't change anything.
I don't think it's funny, so I'll take a picture of it.
Let's all take a picture.
Let's start with Yamazaki.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19.
Are we two?
What?
What about Shoji?
Who's Shoji?
Everyone, let's go.
I hope you don't get in the way.
Sakamoto-kun.
Yes.
You're not in the picture.
You're not in the picture yet.
Everyone, let's go to the left.
I'm not going to lose.
Wait, I'm going to win.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19.
Try it.
I don't think it's funny.
Let's all have lunch.
Yeah.
Let's eat.
Everyone made lunch by their own strength.
To be honest, I've been wondering about the side dishes since a week ago.
First of all, this.
Who the hell is this?
It's hard.
What's on it?
This.
Put it on.
Who is this?
All right.
What is this?
Producer.
It's perfect.
I don't know this either.
Takasu?
Wow.
It's amazing.
Look at this.
If you take this money, it'll be 1,500 yen.
This is about 450 yen.
Wow.
It's hard.
I'm getting old.
What's this?
Is this a punch?
This is a punch.
This is a man's dish.
Who is this?
All right.
What's on it?
Wow.
This.
What is this?
Is this a crab?
I don't know this.
What is this?
I put it in the freezer.
You're not good at this.
What is this?
This is a lunch box.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
You're a fool.
This is no good.
I ordered a lunch box.
This is how it was made.
There's no food coloring.
This is a crab.
This is an Anpan.
This is delicious.
I'm scared.
Look at this egg.
This is wonderful.
I'm going to eat it.
You're eating it, aren't you?
Eat it.
It's okay.
What is this?
You'll know when you eat it.
It's a spinach.
There's no taste at all.
What is this?
I forgot to season it.
Yamazaki, eat all the spinach.
The source of energy.
You have to feed me that.
I'm going to eat it all.
You're a fool.
What is this?
There's no taste at all.
It's bitter.
I don't think there are many customers today.
Why is that?
I'm tired and I can't talk.
I don't know because you didn't watch the opening.
We were planning to make lunch by ourselves.
We went on a picnic.
We always think about what to do next week.
Let's make lunch.
Let's do our best.
I've been thinking about it for a week.
I want you to see that.
There was spinach.
What's this?
This is spinach.
That's right.
That's bad.
You won't understand it.
He's really good at it.
He's good at it.
In fact, I hated him when I first saw him.
I hated him when I first saw him.
But it's interesting.
No, no, no, no.
I don't care about that.
I'm talking about the taste of your Horanso.
You should season it.
That's what everyone says at first.
But as you eat it, you'll understand its taste.
When you eat natto at first, everyone is surprised.
At the current stage,
you should season it like this.
It's already done.
You should do it and add it.
Don't be afraid to be told off.
Why should I be told off so much?
It's bad, so I'll take it off.
That's why I'm apologizing.
That attitude is the attitude of apologizing.
Don't hit me anymore.
I'm not saying that.
This is a man.
The staff said,
I want you to have a match little by little.
Can I decide this time?
What are you talking about?
You decide every time.
If you lose to a person, it's a punishment game.
I can't move by myself.
If you lose to yourself, I can do it, too.
I didn't lose.
I just lost.
That's right.
White wins.
Don't say that.
That's it.
Just temporarily.
That's where I am.
You're next to me.
I chose...
Takatobi.
You've been saying that for a long time.
It's amazing.
To tell you the truth,
I didn't want to play Takatobi.
If you play it, you'll win.
That's right.
It's dirty.
I've thought about it many times.
I'm good at it.
It's a game.
It's already decided.
I didn't want to play it if I could.
But I won't come.
If I'm red-handed.
What do you say?
What am I to the public?
What am I?
You don't know?
I don't know.
What are you going to do?
What are you going to say?
Where are you coming from?
But if it's Takatobi,
I can win.
Right?
I can't play sports in the public.
I'm not good at cooking.
I know this today.
Right?
I'm too weak for women.
No one says that.
I don't earn more than Hamada.
I only earn 110,000 yen.
What kind of man are you?
I'm often told that.
Liar!
Anyway,
today,
or rather, this time,
Did you play the last one?
If I play this,
I'll be...
But if you play that,
I'll do my best.
If you're so good at it,
I won't refuse.
Really?
Yes.
You really won't play Takatobi with me?
Well,
It's a great honor to play Takatobi with me.
Only Akira Nishikino can play Takatobi with me in the entertainment world.
Do you want to play Takatobi with me?
If you refuse,
I'll be scolded again.
What kind of memory do you have?
What's the average?
About 140,000 yen.
You can fly with 140,000 yen.
I can fly with 140,000 yen.
I can fly with more than 140,000 yen.
What?
Can you fly with more than 140,000 yen?
Why are you so scared?
I can't help it.
What's the average?
100,000 yen?
I don't know.
For example,
how many times have you flown with your memory?
Hurry up and say it.
Well,
If you talk to me, I'll fly with you.
It's 145,000 yen.
That's not true.
You can fly with more than 145,000 yen.
I can't fly with more than 145,000 yen.
Well,
I can't fly with more than 140,000 yen.
Let's say it's high.
How much can you fly with?
Let me tell you.
When I was in the second year of junior high school,
I flew with 165,000 yen without lying.
Moreover, I flew with Rappa Zubon.
What kind of time was that?
You flew with Rappa Zubon.
So,
I don't know if I'll win or lose this time.
Next time,
I'll do it.
I can't do that.
Why?
I agree with you.
I'm the leader.
Who is the leader?
I'm the captain.
I've been pulling you all the time.
I'm the captain, too.
So, let's decide the punishment game.
Okay.
I know what you're going to do.
You're dirty.
You're dirty because of your double structure.
Why?
If you fall from a dirty place,
there's still something dirty.
Even if you fall down,
Why?
When I play a punishment game,
I'm not cool,
but when you play a punishment game,
you're so manly.
You should try skydiving.
What?
I've only done it once.
I was crying.
You're just a pigeon
and you're just sitting here.
A long time ago,
there was a crowbar.
That's all.
You can say anything about me.
But you can't say anything about a crowbar.
Why?
What's the meaning of a crowbar?
What is it?
You have a dirty crowbar.
No, it's not dirty.
I haven't used it for 30 years.
Why don't you take this and use it here?
Why?
That's a punishment game.
Give me a break.
Why?
I'm hesitating to take it,
but I have to use it here?
I look like a man who gets angry easily.
If you lose,
I'll take this,
so I'll use it somewhere.
Why do I have to use your crowbar?
Take the skin here.
Why?
Don't take it.
Then I'll cry.
I'll use your crowbar.
Here?
Use my crowbar here.
I'll use it when I'm angry.
But you want to use my crowbar, don't you?
I don't want to use it.
Have you ever been saved by this?
Don't say such a thing.
If I were you,
I'd use your crowbar here.
I'll use the round crowbar here.
I'll use the round crowbar here to eat you.
Do you have a magazine cover?
In your family?
I don't want to.
On TV?
With a lemon in your family?
I don't want to.
Why?
You don't have to have a lemon.
I don't want to.
I don't want to have a lemon.
I don't want to have everything.
If you say so,
I'll make you happy.
Is this show over?
Not yet.
After this show,
on June 10th,
Thursday at 7.30 p.m.
I'll be on the show on the 10th.
Please watch it.
Let's go to the newspaper.
I have a question.
When you close your eyes,
what is the meaning of the pattern on the back of your eyes?
Can you see the pattern?
Yes, I can.
See?
I can see it.
I can see the light.
For example, this girl can see this.
This girl can see it.
No way.
I can see it perfectly.
I can see the pattern.
What kind of pattern can you see?
I can see the letters.
What does it say?
I started to eat cold noodles.
Why does a cook wear a long hat?
Why?
It doesn't make any sense to work.
It depends on what kind of food the person is eating.
A great person wears a long hat.
That's right.
That's a mistake.
The highest you can see is a normal person.
What?
You can see the highest.
The person wearing a long hat is the greatest.
He is a fool.
No, he is not a fool.
He is not a person.
There is a person who is very tall behind him.
He doesn't go out of the restaurant.
He says it's not true.
He cannot go out.
There are many people who are tall.
He doesn't need a hat.
He can't work.
He doesn't move.
So, wait a minute, Matsumoto, are you going to run away like that?
There are people who say that, right?
But that doesn't make sense why it's expensive.
I understand why it's expensive, but I don't know why it's expensive.
There's a lot of umami in it.
I'm just fooling around and being mocked by my partner.
Umami?
What do you mean? Tell me in detail, Mammo-san.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about the umami.
Don't you understand?
Tell me.
I don't understand.
What do you mean?
There's umami in the hat.
I don't understand.
There's no reason why it's so long.
You're really eating me up.
It's okay to be horizontal, right?
Why didn't you make it vertical?
That's why I'm jealous.
For example, stir-fry vegetables.
I'm going to do it.
There's no umami in it.
There's a lot of umami in it.
It's expensive.
There's a hole in it.