High Tension The Best Ten!
Good evening!
It's been a while!
That's right!
It's been a year and a half!
A lot of good-looking comedians have come today as well!
Then let's go!
Let's quickly announce the Best Ten!
Yes!
This week's Best Ten is...
58 points!
The First in the Naibike, Kogoriko Tanaka Naoki!
Congratulations!
Tanaka-san is always in 10th place.
Every time he's in 10th place.
Excuse me, but it's just so-so.
Yes?
It's just so-so, but I feel like I'm going to slip.
It's just so-so.
No, no, no, no.
This is just my gut feeling.
No, no, no.
Really?
It's okay this time.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
Well, well, that's...
No matter what happens...
It's amazing that you're in the Best Ten.
Yes, that's true.
Yes.
This week's 10th place, Kogoriko Tanaka Naoki's Naibike, First!
First in the Naibike, Kogoriko Tanaka Naoki
Hey!
Tanaka, this is just...
Give it back!
Hey!
You idiot!
Oh, yes!
Thank you, Megumi!
What?
Okay, thank you very much!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Let's continue.
This week's 9th place is...
86 points!
Megumi, license, Fujiwara Kazuhiro
Congratulations!
Wow, this is your first appearance.
It's the 9th place.
It's your first appearance and you're 9th place.
Yes, thank you very much.
It's decided that your partner will be high-tensioned.
That's right.
Your eyebrows are like this.
It's a little strange, isn't it?
It came off a little.
Oh, that's the stress.
Did your eyebrows come off?
Yes.
Then let's go to the 3rd place.
Let's go!
This week's 9th place is...
License, Fujiwara Kazuhiro
Megumi, license, Fujiwara Kazuhiro
Hey!
If you have any complaints, come to me.
My family is a high-class family.
I grew up without knowing how hard it was.
If you come to me,
I'll beat you up.
Yes, you're a loser.
Thank you very much.
Well, that's how it is.
That's right.
Next, this week's 8th place is...
171 points, Haranishi Illusion, Fujiwara Haranishi Takayoshi
Congratulations!
We did it!
We did it, didn't we?
Yes, we did.
It's the 8th place all of a sudden.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Yes.
We're in the 10th place.
I want to sell a lot.
I'll do my best.
Yes.
I want to sell a lot.
It's rare to say that clearly.
Now, this week's 8th place.
Fujiwara Haranishi Takayuki and Haranishi Illusion
Yes, I'm Haranishi.
Haranishi has come out.
The most interesting man in the world.
I'm really funny, really, really funny.
Illusion, let's do it!
What kind of funny laugh is this?
This laugh is...
3, 2, 1...
It was a laugh! It was a laugh!
What kind of laugh is this?
Thank you very much.
I see.
What kind of laugh is this?
Let's do it!
This week's 7th place is...
239 points!
Yes!
Revolution!
Cream stew! Arita Teppei!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
There's information in here.
Arita-san, the VTR from the 7th place was burned into a DVD.
It was saved as an A-class and showed to the juniors.
There's information in here.
Huh?
Well...
Was it that complete?
You guys...
Even though you may have seen it live...
You can't do this in front of the downtown.
Even though you know how much it is.
I've done it up to here.
You've done it up to here.
I think it'll be saved as an A-class again today.
That's right.
What will it be?
The 3rd place...
Shall we move on?
Huh?
Yes.
This week's 7th place is...
Cream stew Arita Teppei's revolution!
Gannari ya gannsai
Onsare kaware nari
Hai hai hai
Okasama ai
Ei
Ne
Sato
Hajin
As expected, there are times when you just get excited.
Ah, hello!
Please come up here.
This week's 16th place is...
The best runner...
Penalty...
Wakitta Yasuhito
He's like a person who can keep his words for a long time.
He's wonderful.
He's got an incredible body.
He's almost at the top.
Let's go.
This week's 16th place is...
Penalty...
Wakitta Yasuhito's...
Best...
Huh?
Penalty...
Salute!
The nipples...
The nipples are misaligned, Policeman!
I'm glad that the requires two policeman.
Policeman who takes you everywhere.
That was pretty good.
I don't understand anything.
Now, let's go back to the rankings.
This week's 6th place is...
287 points.
Like King Kamehameha,
Hotohara Tohru.
Congratulations!
In the past year,
you've been the most nervous.
In the past year?
There's 365 days.
Please do it once.
If I get it,
I want to do my best.
Please do it once.
Are you going to do it?
Even if I do it here,
I don't think anything will come out.
That's true.
I'm going to do it.
Are you going to do it?
This week's 6th place.
Like King Kamehameha,
Hotohara Tohru.
In the season of Kiku,
the cherry blossoms are in full bloom.
What?
It's stuck.
Just one kiss!
Curry udon.
The best is King Kamehameha.
This is the best.
That's touching.
How are you?
Thank you very much.
What kind of ending is this?
What an abrupt ending.
Thank you very much.
Let's move on to this week's 5th place.
No. 308.
Noodle Philharmonie 2004.
It's here.
Thank you very much.
My eyes are closing.
They closed while we were waiting.
It's a little strange, isn't it?
My ears have been saying something.
It's like a Tatsunoko Pro Saku.
Tatsunoko Pro Saku.
It's Tatsunoko Pro Saku.
Don't accept it.
Stand by, please.
Let's go.
This week's 5th place.
Noodle Philharmonie 2004.
Udon is a hit in Japan.
I bet my life on udon.
I'm hungry.
Philharmonie.
Who are you talking to?
Calm down.
Thank you very much.
It's not thank you very much.
This week's 4th place.
370 points.
A man called a monkey.
Kokoriko Endo Shouzo.
Congratulations.
That was close, Endo-san.
That's right.
It's rare to get 1st place.
Why are you talking like that?
Endo-san calmed me down.
I got 2 songs at the same time.
I'm still...
You're still...
I'm going to turn red.
Hamada, I'm going to turn red.
That's why you quit.
It's not because it hurts or something.
It's because you're going to turn red.
It's because I'm going to turn red.
Unfortunately, you didn't get the 3rd place.
If there's a next chance.
I'll do my best.
Standby.
The expectations for Endo-san...
There's something amazing about Japan.
Let's go.
The man called a monkey.
What's this?
Tokyo, can you make a watermelon?
I...
This is bad.
I ate a watermelon.
But you...
Watermelon...
Don't you want to eat a watermelon?
What did you say?
I sometimes...
I sometimes want to eat a watermelon.
Surely, surely...
The same feeling as everyone else.
That's it.
That was good.
You've done that unfinished job so far.
This week, we've ranked 32nd.
This way, please.
You're dangerous.
It feels like Marlin Monroe.
That's right.
The prank of God.
This is a prank.
Stand by.
It's a spotlight.
What's your score?
This week, we've ranked 32nd.
Chiara Seiji vs. Chiara brothers.
Chiara Seiji vs. Chiara brothers
I got it!
Don't laugh.
I don't think this is right.
You're the one who's doing all the wrong things.
Is this really my fault?!
No it's not!
It's your fault!
You're the one who's doing all the wrong things!
If you take anything from me, I'm going to kill you!
You're the one who's making things up!
I'm going to kill you!
It's cold and I don't have anything fun to do, so I want to go home.
When I leave the house,
I don't want to bring anything from May because it's surprisingly cold!
I don't care!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
I'm looking forward to the next episode of this spotlight.
Let's go!
This week's third episode!
474 points!
Masked Ninja Man!
Dachou Club!
Ryuhei Ueshiba!
Congratulations!
This is...
As expected...
What is it?
A dignified aura!
This is the third episode!
Thank you very much.
This aura is something you can't really show.
The sense of stability is different.
I'm sorry, but let's move on to the third episode.
Let's go!
This week's third episode!
Dachou Club!
Ryuhei Ueshiba!
Masked Ninja Man!
Masked Ninja is here!
Huh?
I can't move my arms.
I can't bend my arms.
I can't do it! I can't do it!
I can't do it!
Alright, I did it!
Hmph!
Listen!
You guys!
I don't care where you hide!
Even if you disappear in one piece!
I, the Masked Ninja, will cut you to pieces!
Hey!
Where did you hide?!
You!
Come out!
I can see you!
What are you doing?!
Alright, I'll do it like this!
Eh?
Alright!
Pon pon no jutsu!
Yeah!
Pon pon!
Pon pon pon pon pon!
Thank you very much!
Isn't that person 1st place?
He's 3rd place.
Ah!
Such a high-level thing!
No, no, no.
2nd place is...
493 points!
The Masked Ninja, I want to erase the rain!
Miyasako Hiroyuki!
Congratulations!
8 yen for a woman?
That's too much, Miyasako-san!
That was close!
You missed 1st place!
Right?
I think we can expect a lot from today.
I think so too.
Eh?
Yeah?
There's a hole in the air.
It's hard.
Then we should do it quickly.
That's right.
Then, standby.
Really, what kind of order was that?
I don't know.
It wasn't an order you could say over the phone.
It wasn't.
Let's go.
2nd place this week.
The Masked Ninja, Miyasako Hiroyuki.
Stop it!
What are you doing?
No!
Ouch!
That was an accident!
Policeman!
You beat me there?
What?
It hurts!
The 2nd place is still in the top 10
Is that okay?
I mean...
Who is the 1st place?
That's how it is
Really
The 1st place is...
556 points
Com-sama help, Yamasaki Hose
It's scary
That's right
I put on makeup
I understand
That's amazing
It took a long time and money
It took a while
How long did it take to put on makeup?
About 30 minutes
That's faster
It took longer
It really did
Did it blur?
If it did, then it was blurred
If it didn't, then it wasn't blurred
It was a convenient talk
That's right, thank you
Thank you very much
Can we look forward to this?
It's the 1st place
With this much makeup
I feel like I can do it today
Really?
You look calm today
I can look forward to it
I think you can
Let's go
This week's 1st place, Yamasaki Hose
Com-sama help
Yamasaki Hose
It's Naomi
I don't like smoke
Com
I don't want to slip
Policeman
I don't understand
What should I say?
My nipples are coming out
Policeman
Stand up
That's amazing
I don't remember what I want to slip
Everyone, let's take a commemorative photo
Let's look at the camera
Let's take a commemorative photo
Thank you very much
It didn't mean much
That's right
I'm really sorry
I'm sorry to the staff
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors