Who was it last time?
License.
License. You've been talking about your license for a long time.
Ah, really?
I really thought you should get a license.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
What is it? Did something happen?
I don't want to watch TV anymore.
Why?
The World Cup is over.
I'm not interested at all.
I don't care.
I'm not interested in anything.
I'm not going to watch it.
I'm not going to watch it even if it's 1mm.
There aren't many people who are interested in it.
But...
It's just that time.
But you'll watch it anyway, right?
I can't watch it.
Your face is like a fool.
I don't care about my face.
But you won't watch it, right?
I won't watch it.
It can't be helped.
Goal!
What?
I don't care about that.
I don't care about that at all.
Ah, you scored a goal, right?
No, no, no.
Goal means the end.
Right?
No.
It's so difficult that no one watches it.
Goal!
Shut up!
I'll eat, sleep, and take a bath.
I don't care about the goal.
I don't care about the time.
I don't care.
I don't care about that.
If you really want to score a goal, you should have done it now.
You should have scored a goal now.
But then...
You'll score a lot of goals now.
Even if I do that, I'll just be a fool.
I'll talk about it after my opponent scores a goal.
It doesn't matter.
What do you mean?
Shouldn't the people who came from overseas accept that?
Well, since it's an international tournament, they should provide a practice room.
Is there any benefit in doing that?
What do you mean?
Doesn't that mean people will come?
But you've been to so many places, and you've been to so many places at the same time.
There's no way that the village itself will get excited.
No, it's just the village that gets excited.
What?
The radius...
How many meters?
Cameroon...
How many kilometers?
Cameroon, huh?
You're late.
Do you know why?
I saw it on the news.
It's about money, right?
It's like a joke.
You came on a cheap plane because you wanted money, so you were late, right?
Is that so?
That's what they say.
They say that direct flights cost a lot of money.
But you wanted to save money, so you went on a cheap tour.
You came from the outside.
You made a lot of money.
I didn't know that.
The villagers were making money, but you were late.
You're late, but you're not a good person either.
It's the same with you.
Slowly, slowly, something came up.
It's the opposite, isn't it?
It's the same with you.
You know how Cameroon feels, don't you?
I know exactly how Cameroon feels.
That's weird.
It's okay.
I won't see it.
How are you doing lately?
It's an old story, but there was another one.
What is it?
Choja Banzuke.
I looked into it in detail.
You have about 20 million yen more than me.
I think you've got a little bit of it, but you're going to get 10 million yen, aren't you?
You're not going to put it in the envelope when you get back to school, are you?
Wait a minute.
What is it?
It's not a ostrich club.
Ostriches are all the same.
What is it?
What are you talking about?
Is it weird?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Well, let me ask you.
Yeah.
Last year, you were higher than me.
Was that how it was?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
That's when I was a pretender.
I have my own way of thinking.
I don't do that kind of thing.
That's your style.
That's my style.
Then I won't do it either.
What style?
I won't do it either.
Why?
Then, what is it?
What are you talking about?
You see...
Yes, yes, yes.
The one who hasn't come out yet is Paul, right?
No, he's here.
Why hasn't he come out yet?
No, that's...
I don't know.
That's just...
Every day is the final answer.
I don't know what you mean.
But I'm sure you know what a combination is.
For example, when you were a rookie,
you won the rookie award,
or the celebrity award,
or the amateur celebrity award.
You did it properly.
Properly.
In the true sense, you two did it properly.
I won't forget it.
When I was an amateur celebrity,
I won a prize of 50,000 yen.
He gave me a trophy.
When you win a trophy or a medal,
when you win a rookie award,
you don't give a trophy.
I was like,
Oh, thank you.
And when I won a prize of hundreds of thousands of yen,
I was like,
Oh, thank you.
And then,
in the dressing room,
I was like,
Oh, thank you.
Why?
And I was like...
I was like this.
Like this and this.
Why?
I was like this.
I was like this,
and I was like this.
You're annoying.
I was like,
I don't want to blame you.
No, that's wrong.
What's wrong?
No, you're wrong.
No, that's...
So, what if you do that from this year?
What if next year...
It's from this year.
If it's a new song next year,
it's from this year.
What about the announcement from last year?
Oh, that's fine.
I'll do that from last year.
Why?
That's weird.
In exchange,
if something happens to me in the future,
and I go like this,
and you're really like this in the park,
if I only take the radio and the dog with me...
What is it?
What year is that?
Even if it's only the radio and the dog...
That means you're a dantai.
That's right.
That's why...
I'll go to that park.
What year is that?
How many years has it been since you took the radio and the dog with you?
Well, it's been two years.
Two years?
I won't be there in two years.
If I take the radio and the dog with me...
That's right.
I'll be an octopus by then.
But you'll be happy.
When you take the radio and the dog with you,
I'll fly from an airplane.
An airplane?
And then,
I'll say,
You're downtown.
And then,
I'll say,
I'm glad we made a promise back then.
I'm at the turning point right now.
If I give you 10 million yen here,
you'll have a lot of money in the future.
Do you understand?
What are you talking about?
You should definitely do that.
You're talking nonsense.
It's 10 million yen.
No, that's not it.
That's weird.
Why?
What's weird?
I mean,
I don't understand why you don't want to pay 10 million yen.
That's what I don't understand at all.
Why?
Because you have 20 million yen more than I do.
That's why I'm paying my taxes.
What do you mean?
Taxes?
It can't be helped.
It can't be helped if you pay more taxes than I do.
I have an idiotic family.
So,
I have to feed my kids.
I'm just getting in the way.
You're just getting in the way,
you're just getting in the way.
It's like you're polluting the Tetrapods.
Where do you get that from?
I don't know.
10 million yen?
You're saying I have 10 million yen here?
How many times do I have to tell you?
You'll get tired of hearing that.
When should I start sniffing the smell of the toilet paper?
There is, right? The one with the smell.
Yes.
Do you use that?
Certainly, there is no need to smell it.
That's right.
It's because it has a smell.
It's not a smell that you can fool with that smell.
Well, yes.
That's right.
So, there is no need to smell it, right?
What do you mean?
But you shouldn't smell it.
But the smell comes from smelling it, right?
It's not because you smell it.
You smell it because it has a smell, right?
Huh?
No, it's not huh.
So, when you use it, do you smell it like this?
You don't smell it, right?
Then, when should I smell it?
Huh?
No, it's not huh. You know it.
So, it's poop, right?
No, just throw it away.
Just throw it away.
Just throw it away. It's too late at that stage.
It's before it's too late.
No, it's not.
Don't say strange things even though you don't have 10 million yen.
It's not, right?
So, how should I say it?
For example, what is your favorite food?
Yakisoba.
There is one more, right?
Gyoza.
It's gyoza, right?
Since you like gyoza and yakisoba, do you want to eat gyoza and yakisoba?
If there is one, I will eat it.
Huh?
There is yakisoba inside the gyoza skin.
Don't say it like that.
It's not like that, right?
If you add what you like, it will be twice as delicious.
This is a stupid way of thinking.
But there are times when it's the opposite.
If you add two things you don't like, it will be surprisingly good.
I think this way of thinking is suitable for this.
What do you mean by that?
That toilet paper alone doesn't have a strong smell.
But when it's combined with the smell of poop...
It gives off a really good smell, right?
The smell of poop.
Don't you have the courage to do that?
Wipe my ass and bring it here.
You have a lot of courage.
That's why I don't like the smell.
Try it.
This is...
This is that girl?
Don't you think so?
That girl?
This is that girl who smells like the countryside?
What are you saying?
Why are you laughing?
No, that's a mania.
I'm happy about that.
Okay, then try it.
Really.
Try it.
That's just tied to my past memories.
I'm determined that the smell of poop is strong.
There are times when it smells strong.
Yes, there are.
I'm surprised.
What am I?
There are times when it smells strong.
Yes, there are.
I'm thinking about the side that smells strong.
When I think about that, I definitely know that it smells strong.
I can't bring it here.
Try it.
It smells so strong that it can be used as a diaper.
What do you mean a diaper?
It's the air purifier of the entertainment world.
I think I can use that.
Is that so?
Yes.
When you're inside the negative ion, how excited are you?
You're from Kyoto, right?
The negative ion is said to be very good.
You're talking about the momentum.
No, it's not like that.
I don't understand the meaning of being excited.
What do you mean?
It's said that the negative ion makes people excited.
Really?
Yes.
Don't you have a negative ion device at home?
I don't have one.
People who work like this should have one.
Really?
It's better to be excited than to be low.
That's right.
That's absolutely right.
Do you have one at home?
Yes, I do.
If you have one, you'll be very excited.
A lot of things change.
Please tell me the details.
How does it feel?
The negative ion spreads widely.
When I go into the living room, I feel the negative ion.
There's a lot of negative ion coming in.
It's coming in from the back of the room.
The negative ion is coming in through the gap.
The negative ion is coming in from the back of the room.
It's amazing.
It's coming in through the gap.
Does that make you excited?
It's easy to get excited.
The negative ion is coming in through the gap.
It's coming in through the gap.
I can feel the negative ion coming in.
That's how you get excited.
I see.
I think today's guest was too high-class.
I don't know.
I don't know if there's anyone here who has a machine.
Is there anyone?
I don't think there's anyone like you.
It's amazing.
There's a lot behind the TV.
There's a lot behind the curtains.
That's amazing.
It's really...
It's obvious.
There's a lot behind the curtains.
Hey!
It's scary.
There's a lot behind the curtains.
I don't like wearing that.
Really?
Even if I'm wearing it, it looks like it.
The negative ion.
Really?
Nearby?
Nearby.
Because the room is full of negative ions.
That's right.
Even when I'm screaming, the negative ion is coming in.
What's that?
Director.
Why is it like D?
The negative ion is coming in.
Grimdor is a man who plays the flute.
When he plays the flute, all the rats in town gather around him.
When he hums that song, all the old and young people in town gather and dance.
I heard that there's a magic trick in Matsumotsu-san's lyrics and music.
What kind of trick is that?
The staff of this show told me to change my phone number from time to time.
Really?
I told them not to say stupid things.
What?
You're just going to say that?
How about it?
But you've made a lot of them.
I've made a lot of them.
But how about it?
I think that's what we're going to do today.
What do you mean?
That's what we're going to do today.
I'm going to change my phone number.
Are you going to change it?
Are you going to do it?
You're the one who's going to do it.
When I look back on the past, I feel like it was a long time ago.
I see.
Can it be shorter?
Sure.
How do you want it to be?
Isn't it going to be fun?
Sure.
It's going to be fun.
Please.
Are you going to record it?
I'm going to record it.
That's better.
Let's change it from next week.
Everyone, be quiet when it starts.
Can I?
Sure.
Can you help me?
You're the only one who's going to do it.
Is this okay?
I told you to wrap the tape properly.
Why?
It's hard to breathe.
I can't sing with this mic.
What kind of image do you want?
It says it's going to be fun.
Everyone's going to dance.
I understand.
That's fine.
There's something like that.
Of course there is.
That's why I'm here right now.
You can sing it for a while.
I can't sing it for a while.
Let's go.
Yes, please.
Take it, Deshi.
It's a vegetable.
It's a fun feeling.
It's fun.
I told you it's a fun feeling.
You're going to disband.
If it's a vegetable, I can't throw it away.
I don't care.
How is it?
After that...
You should put the sound on the bass later, right?
That's right.
Then play the whole song.
I don't know what kind of song I want to sing.
You said you were going to join us.
What do you think this is?
I'll put the sound on later.
You can sing in a cappella.
Really?
I'll make it fun.
I don't know the atmosphere yet.
It's a sampling.