I don't want to see it in the kids' room.
Tsukitsugi Ogiri University!
Good evening, everyone.
I'm the head of the Kadakuchi Association, the Soviet Union.
Nice to meet you.
Let's call in our young girl.
Hanashika, please come in.
Let's introduce ourselves.
Let's play a game.
Let's start from here.
Okay.
You bet with me.
Carrot and rabbit.
What about that heart?
I have a name.
Moe!
Name!
Aozora Yohji.
What is it?
Okay, you.
I bet with you that I'll make a story.
Yes.
I'll solve it with Mr. Hamada's daily life.
What about that heart?
I won't do it in a place where there are no people.
What?
I bet with Aozora Yohji.
Carrot and rabbit!
Next!
I bet with my friend in AD.
I'll solve it with Hamada Masatoshi.
What about that heart?
I'll do my best, so you do your best, too.
Next!
I bet with...
I'll solve it with Maki.
What about that heart?
I'll do my best, so you do your best, too.
Okay, last one.
Let's go.
I bet with...
I'll solve it with Yoshinoya's beef bowl.
What about that heart?
I don't like women very much.
I bet with Katsura Utanda.
Okay, nice to meet you.
Next!
I bet with Ayu-e!
There are five characters in Ayu-e.
I'll fold them and let you talk about that person.
First of all...
Mr. Katsura.
Mr. Katsura. Let's go with A-gyo.
Okay?
I bet with Ayu-e.
Ah!
You always wear a red dress.
Let's talk about Nihon TV.
What is it?
Let's go with Sa-gyo.
Sa-gyo is the best company.
It's a TV show about UFOs and ghosts.
Su!
Mr. Su is a good producer, but...
What are you doing?
This is not a good place.
Se!
There are many sex-lovers.
That's not a good place.
Su!
There are many sex-lovers.
That's not a good place.
I bet with Nihon TV.
What is it?
There are many sex-lovers.
There are many sex-lovers in Nihon TV.
That's right.
Really?
It's true.
Let's go with this.
I'm sorry to say this, but...
It's a child.
Let's go with this.
Let's go with Sa-gyo.
Sa-gyo?
Yes.
Ki!
Catch the tight wife!
Ku!
Your lips are drooping down, but...
Don't say that!
Ke!
The more your pores open, the more...
Ku!
Don't say that!
The second one!
The second one! Read the Atatamo!
Now, are you ready?
Here it is.
It's a book about how to draw animals.
I haven't drawn anything yet.
I wonder if Atatamo is already drawn.
Let's read it.
What kind of drawing should I do?
What is it?
Hamster!
I can't believe it's a hamster.
Yohji-kun.
Yes.
From Yohji-kun.
The reason why I met this hamster Tsubochibo-kun
It's a book about how to draw!
It's a novel!
Who's drawing it?
I'm drawing it.
What?
It's really good!
Read it!
The real way to draw is...
What is it?
If you buy it at the aquarium...
It's a good thing.
It's different from before.
There's food!
Let's stop there.
It's different from before!
There's food!
What is it?
Food is...
I like small hippos.
But everyone, let's think about it here.
Let's draw three hamsters in Chinese.
Okay, stop there.
I see.
Let's draw three hamsters in Chinese.
Before I draw it in Chinese...
I said let's draw it!
I have to explain it.
I already drew it.
Before I draw it,
I have to talk about the history of the aquarium.
I'll talk about the history of the aquarium in the cross.
I see.
In the saying of Chaya Shirojirou...
In the saying?
In the saying...
I don't know the pace.
What kind of sound did the third hamster make?
What is it?
This is from a long time ago.
There was a fishmonger who went to the fishmonger's room.
Like this.
What kind of sound did it make?
It was like this.
Yes!
Let's start with Yohji, whose voice is hoarse.
The owner of the rice shop is worried.
Ah, I'm sorry.
What kind of sound did it make?
I'm sorry.
Hey, Hoka!
Yes?
You guys are hopeless.
Look at me.
Saejo Hideki is worried!
Oh!
Ladies and gentlemen.
It was really hard today.
Yes, it was really hard.
Let's go home shortly.
Let's go home.
It has nothing to do with you guys.
You guys should die.
You have to go home early and make your own time.
Is that so?
I really don't have my own time.
I used to be the head of a gang.
Are you kidding me?
I miss it.
You don't even have a gas station license.
You can't even ride a big car.
I really miss that time.
I did a lot of bad things.
I liked it more than Kenkawa-san's name.
I really did a lot of bad things.
I'm glad I did that.
Oh, against the enemy.
Yes.
Against the Black Jaguars.
When you're surrounded by 30 people.
Even as a good leader.
It's true that you can shake things up.
How did you handle it?
What do you mean?
30 people surrounded you.
Yes.
What did you do?
You should have been scared.
That's right.
What did you do?
Stop it!
I'm not going to stop at that.
I won't stop at that.
I'm going to turn my back on them.
But even if I think I should stop,
I can't stop because I'm the leader.
That's right.
The leader over there is strong.
The leader over there was strong too.
Do you know that guy?
Oh, Kawachi.
Ohkawachi!
Ohkawachi is also a big deal.
Ohkawachi?
You said, stop it!
Ohkawachi said, go!
I didn't expect that kind of attack.
That's why I said, fly!
I said, say that!
It started to spin.
30 people started to spin.
Oh!
Then?
I didn't expect that kind of attack.
I said, say that!
Say it now!
Say it right now!
I said, go!
I waited too long.
It's like this.
Why do you care about the camera?
I want to show it to you.
It's like this.
It's terrible.
Then?
It's terrible!
I said it.
But you didn't stop it.
I didn't stop it.
Why didn't you stop it?
I said it like that.
I was scared.
Really?
It was terrible.
Then?
I was there.
Leave it to me!
I said it!
But you know, in high school,
we were weak.
We were weak.
We had to go to the toilet.
We had to take the girls.
We didn't know what to do.
They were so strong.
We were so scared.
We were so weak.
We were walking with a girl.
It was like a department store.
There was a woman there.
She was so mean.
I had to cut her noodles.
I was cutting her noodles.
I had to cut her noodles too.
You were watching that.
Leave it to me.
She has to climb down the stairs.
I understand.
She had to climb up the stairs.
I was climbing down the stairs.
I was climbing up the stairs.
There was a lot ofifferences between us.
Leave it to me!
Put my head down.
We've already parted ways.
We'll never meet again.
I think it's okay to get a little drunk.
I think it's okay.
I think so too.
And when I got off the bus, there were a lot of electronic products.
And she was just lying there, looking at me like this.
She was looking at me.
And then that guy...
He came in, so I had to come in!
I couldn't stand it!
What do you mean, you came in?
You came in, you came in!
What kind of clothes was he wearing?
He was wearing a cardigan with a Ushite-ella-like collar.
Yeah.
He was wearing something red.
That was in vogue!
He wasn't wearing a belt.
He wore a pair of rubber-lipped panties.
Okay, okay.
And he looked like a short guy with long legs.
And he was wearing women's slippers.
Women's slippers?
He was wearing women's sandals.
It was gross.
And he asked me, what are you doing Kristoff?
Your girl is listening to you?
Yes, she is.
Oh, she is telling you?
What?
Well, she looks like a girl I know.
You're lying!
My girl is lying!
You're cute.
You're good at lying.
I'm telling the truth.
Who are you?
I'm in love with electrical appliances.
I'm scared of these things.
I don't want to get hit in front of a girl.
It's tough.
I'm already in love with you.
I don't want to get hit in front of a girl.
Well, let's talk over there.
Hey, come here.
You're so strong.
I told her to wait for me.
And I made her wait.
I was hoping that she wouldn't do anything until I got there.
I didn't care what she did.
I just wanted her to do something in front of a girl.
On the way.
I was walking ahead of her.
Oh, you're here.
I told her not to turn to that corner.
I told her to follow me safely.
When I was about to turn around,
She was kicking me in the ass.
Shut up.
She saw me, didn't she?
She was just looking at me.
What do you think of Hayashi?
You know, I have a lot of
I like to watch you.
I usually introduce things that are interesting.
Sometimes, you see, there are a few letters that say,
What is the purpose of this child?
I introduced about two today.
Who stands out the most among your family?
What made him do that?
I've never thought about that.
I wrote that with a pencil.
It's strange, isn't it?
It's strange.
It's really strange.
I think this is the same person.
Where is the place where you can relax at home?
It's strange, isn't it?
Why do you ask that?
Did you know that?
I don't know.
For example, if you say it's a living room,
Oh, there are amazing people in the world.
For some reason, even if you make friends in the same class,
Even if you pass each other in the hallway for a year,
It's like passing by a dead end.
I see.
Why have you two been friends for a long time?
Or do you hate each other?
Please answer.
Pen name, Ucchan Love.
Ask Ucchan.
I'm worried if I can understand this.
Really?
If you don't see each other for a while,
Even though you were so close,
It's hard to talk to each other.
Really?
You talk to anyone.
This is his strength and weakness.
That's right.
If I didn't have anyone, I would talk to Shoukaki.
I would talk to White.
I can't talk about this on TV anymore.
I couldn't stand it.
But I'll stop it.
I'll stop it.
Don't laugh.
It's true.
It's okay.
I'll laugh like this.
We weren't that close friends in high school.
At that time,
As it is now,
In the TV game center,
It was the time before the invasion of the invaders.
We weren't invaders, but I knew the game.
What?
There was something like that.
What is that?
It's okay.
It wasn't a sound.
What is that?
There was something like that.
Galaga.
Don't speak so loudly.
It was here.
It was there.
When I was doing Galaga,
My friend said,
Long time no see.
I sat on the chair.
Galaga.
It's not good to die now.
Long time no see.
How are you doing?
Well,
Where did you get a job?
The printing company?
Yes.
The company?
First of all,
I...
What should I do?
If Galaga dies now,
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to do.
What should I do?
Don't say anything weird.
Be careful.
So,
It's funny,
I want to talk about it.
You know what I mean?
Well,
Is it okay?
Yes.
Is it enough?
A little more?
Galaga was doing it.
Is it enough?
I want to broadcast it.
What?
Did something happen?
A lot of things happened.
I didn't have such a good friend.
Yes.
I...
I played a game.
I haven't seen you for a long time.
Well,
Invader is popular.
What is it?
Pyon, pyon, pyon, pyon.
I knew it by the sound.
What is it?
Invader...
Galaga!
Shut up!
I was there in the past.
I played it.
Yes.
I had a friend.
I said,
It's been a long time.
You shouldn't do that.
I said,
It's been a long time.
Pyon, pyon, pyon, pyon.
I said,
What are you doing?
Are you doing well?
Yes.
I'm doing well.
Did you have a job?
Yes.
Well,
I...
Matsumoto...
Pyon, pyon, pyon, pyon.
What are you doing?
I have such a good ear.