I don't want to see it too much.
Chikichiki! Naita Naita! Koraekirezu! Naitakkei! Grand Prix!
What is it today? Are you going to cry?
I think you've seen a lot of TV movies so far.
If you watch this, you'll start crying.
I asked them to put it out.
From now on, it's in the back box one by one.
It won't be all long.
I want you to watch it for a while.
And when it comes out, I wonder if you're really crying when you see it.
What about everyone?
Are you a person who cries a lot?
I am.
You cry a lot.
You cry really fast.
What about you, Yamazaki?
I cry a lot, too.
Me, too?
Yes, I cry a lot.
I cry really fast.
I'm a romanticist.
In Japan, it's called a romanticist tennis ball.
I'm going to play in order.
First of all, Yamazaki.
I'm a little...
Let's see what's going on with Yamazaki.
Yamazaki, please.
Really?
It's true.
Whose body is it?
It's the body of Pet Midler.
It's the mother's body.
Oh, your mother is Pet Midler.
That's right.
I'm going to be Nijiko from today.
Next is Takasu.
Takasu, please.
I don't know what Takasu chose.
Goodbye, mom.
I loved you, mom.
Don't forget me forever.
Goodbye.
Hakubi, Hakubi.
Maoh.
It hurts.
Goodbye.
I love you forever.
Maoh.
Hakubi.
It was good on the way.
I'm going to cry again.
I'm crying.
Takasu, please.
Something.
I'm getting goosebumps, but I'm not as high as I used to be.
You used to be high.
I've been here a lot on the way.
I'm tired.
Let's keep going.
Next, Sadachi.
Yes.
I want to go home.
Let's go home.
Let's go home together.
Current
Machine.
Mine!
They're dead!
Why are you crying?
Yamazaki's crying too.
It's so good!
Let's have Soga-chan come out too.
Soga-chan, go ahead.
She's crying a lot, right?
She's crying!
Soga-chan isn't crying.
She's crying.
She's crying a little.
Oh, really.
That's how it is.
When we first came out on Nomugi Pass, everyone was laughing.
Looking at it closely...
Chi-san is good, right?
Chi-ichi came out.
Chi-ichi.
Next, Otomo-kun.
Yes.
Otomo-kun was crying.
Hey, you!
Hurry up and come out!
I can't do it anymore.
Don't worry about me.
I can end up like this anyway.
But what about Otomo-kun?
Otomo-kun, please!
Okay.
Is it true?
So, it's a lie!
You're the one who said it.
The flies are...
There are no flies.
I don't know what to do.
Okay, next is Hamada-san.
Hamada-san.
What is it?
Let's go.
I don't really know.
Today, we have Nekota Katsutoshi-san, who has become the center of the Japanese men's volleyball world.
He's been practicing hard every day, thinking only about winning.
Sometimes I wonder why we have to do it.
But since I was born with a man, I want to do something big in my life.
That's what volleyball is now.
When this life is over, let's build an ordinary life anywhere.
Until then, there will be a lot of lonely and sad things, but I'll do my best.
At that time, imagine the figure of two people in the future, or the figure of a child going to see the cherry blossoms.
Nekota Katsutoshi
You're wearing high heels.
How about Hamada-san?
Please.
Are you crying?
We shouldn't have done it at the first letter.
I should have done it at that time.
I called my brother to come to my house.
I was watching it while doing it.
I wanted to cry.
I have a brother.
I have a brother, so I can't cry.
I remember holding back.
This is the last time.
I'm going.
I'm going to open it now.
Nekota Katsutoshi
Chibu, let's go home.
I don't want to go.
Chibu, Chibu, Chibu.
Dad.
That's right, that's right.
No matter what anyone says, Chibu will never do it.
All right, all right, all right.
Dad.
I don't know.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello, hello.
What is it?
I don't know.
Every season is a double course.
I feel a little cold.
I have a long entertainment life.
Everyone is laughing like this from now on.
It's annoying.
I thought it would be annoying if I could sell it.
I was on the Shinkansen the other day.
That's the first time.
I'm sleeping on the Shinkansen.
I'm pretty tired.
Shinkansen to Osaka.
I'm sleeping on the Shinkansen.
What happened?
I woke up and was asked to sign.
I have to turn around.
I'm turning around.
They are the same.
I'm sorry.
Sign.
I don't know what to pay attention to.
There are too many people.
Even before that, the president of the Shinkansen said,
I will take a private room.
I don't care.
I want to sit on a chair.
I want to sit normally.
I don't want anyone to come.
I don't want to let anyone come.
Why are you smiling?
I'm a good person.
I can't help it.
I went to the New Year's party the other day.
I'm reading a Shinkansen book.
I'm reading it with naked.
And this year again, a celebrity came to Hawaii.
Oh?
It's a surprise.
What is it?
The popular comedian D.T.H.M.
What?
There's no doubt about it.
This time, it seems like they went as a couple.
The one who came to the pub appeared alone.
He's waiting for you from here.
Other than that, he took a few staff members with him, and he seemed to be in a good mood, so he scattered a lot of chips.
He was like this.
He scattered a lot of chips.
And finally, he went out with a blonde woman in net tights.
Hey, who is M in the middle of studying abroad?
I don't know if I followed my partner, but I don't think it's because they went as a couple.
I don't think so.
What are you doing while you're married?
That's right.
Why do you write a weekly magazine like that?
Who says that?
I don't know.
Oh, there was this time.
Stop Always
You have to write the same thing as I do.
That punk stopped my bad comment.
I had to stay in the car.
You used to use someone else's bad words, but I had to use my own.
If I have an image that I am bad, Ilam always use my own bad words.
I don't really use anyone's bad words.
Look at this.
That's it.
Don't say that.
The bad words are...
You are talking more and more.
The bad words are to say something that doesn't exist.
That's what the bad words are.
I'm the most angry right now.
What are you talking about?
That guy.
Wait a minute.
It's the first day of the new year.
You can't say that.
He's the only one who's angry.
Everyone's angry.
I don't know.
I'll tell you.
I'll just tell you.
Shut up.
I'll tell you everything I think.
I'll tell you everything.
You judge.
He's selling it in a refreshing way.
It's refreshing.
It's not refreshing at all.
That's a bad word.
That's my guess.
But when I look at people and their faces,
I don't know.
I don't know if he's really like this.
I've been right up to now.
But you shouldn't judge that.
That woman is definitely a little different.
Well, that's fine.
It's refreshing.
It's selling.
It's selling in a refreshing way.
That's not it.
That's it.
He caught a man.
That's a refreshing image.
It's wrong for two men to go abroad.
They don't have anything private.
You can't say that.
Why not?
Everyone has a private.
But I don't want to say anything good.
I'm going abroad.
What did you say?
You can't go.
You denied it all.
I didn't say anything until then.
You can't go.
That's when you come back.
What?
It doesn't matter.
When you come back,
That's when you come back.
When you come back.
When you wear a hat,
It's like that.
I've been interviewed.
I've been ignored.
I can't imagine that.
I can't do that.
Why not?
If I say it more refreshingly,
I can say,
I had a good time.
But,
I can't answer
when I'm interviewed
with glasses on.
That's a bad attitude.
What are you doing?
Why don't you listen to me?
I can't go that far.
What?
You can't go that far.
That's the bad part.
Talk to me from there.
You're so long.
You can't go like this.
You can't go that far.
I can't connect with you.
You're so long.
And,
I don't know what happened to my parents.
They are angry.
My mother is also angry.
And,
my sponsor is also saying a lot of things.
My agency told me a lot.
They told you?
They told me.
But,
if I go to Hawaii,
what's wrong with that?
If I say it again,
I think,
she is funny.
She has guts.
I think like that.
But,
if I go there for three days,
I will shorten my hair.
I will put on make-up.
I will be fresh.
When you warm up your body,
why do you have a membrane?
What is it?
It's a barricade to protect.
It's not a barricade to protect.
But,
isn't it like that?
It's not like that.
It's not such a difficult problem.
What is it?
When you warm up your body,
why do you have a membrane?
Simply speaking,
it's a cow skin.
No, no, no.
Let me tell you one thing.
I'm also ready.
No, no, no.
What are you saying?
Why is it like that?
What is it?
It's a cow skin.
Right?
Everyone is saying yes.
No, no, no.
What is it?
It's because my hair is like this.
There are many useless things.
I don't need Anna.
I don't need a coin.
I don't need to spend millions of yen on a birthday party.
I don't need to buy a kimono.
Isn't it decreasing?
I don't even know what a tombstone is.
Why?
I don't need Anna.
If you die, I want you to put it in a tombstone.
Of course.
I want you to put it in a big stone.
I want you to wear it every day.
That's a good idea.
You are a more dynamic person.
Why?
If I were a dynamic person,
what would happen if I died?
What would happen to your bones?
I don't care about my bones.
What?
I don't care.
It's like a glass under the TV.
It's like that.
My family is not in a good mood.
I fell down once and fell.
I fell down many times.
What should I do?
My bones are broken.
I'm a year old.
I'm really like that.
Why are you talking like that?
I can't stand up while I'm alive.
I've been saving money since I couldn't sell it.
I'm not an oven toaster.
Then don't bake it.
If you put aluminum foil on it.
You have to fold it.