In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukaya, we'll be shooting with Reikan Caddy.
I'm scared today.
I'm a little worried.
What's scary is the traffic jam.
It took me 5 hours.
This time, we're going to a haunted spot. Let's see how many photos we can take.
So, the downtown team, the Kogoriko team, and Mr. Yamazaki.
As for the rules...
If you take a photo of the point you took and there's one ghost in it...
One ghost?
If there's one ghost in it...
You're treating me like I'm a ghost?
If there's one ghost in it, you get one point.
The team with the most points will receive...
A gift from Hawaii.
Are you kidding me?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
We won't be able to see the ghost course just by ourselves.
We'll have the caddies guide us through the course.
First, from the hellish Oyama amusement park, Sakura.
Please welcome Mr. Kinzo.
You're too excited.
He's so excited.
Mr. Kinzo.
Are you okay?
You're fooling around.
You have to follow my instructions.
You're serious, right?
It's dangerous.
You're packing good stuff.
What is this?
This is number 9.
Number 9.
There's a lot.
This is number 1.
You can't copy the good kids.
That's right.
Next, number 9.
The ghost guide boss, Oda Mudo.
It's Anomita.
Hello.
When a monk comes in, he says, good morning.
I thought you'd have to do your best.
You're wearing a mask.
I'll do my best to not forget that it's Anomita.
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
Last but not least, the best stair talent in Japan, Inagawa Junji.
No, no, no, no.
It's dangerous.
It's scary.
It's really scary.
I want to make everyone happy today.
I don't know what you want to see.
I want to show you what I can do.
It's a good day.
The location was delayed today.
I think it's better to stop.
I think so, too.
I think it was delayed in the sense that it might not come.
It usually happens that way, but it's not like this.
The ghost guide is on the wrong way.
I want to say.
When a monk is in a hurry, he steps on the floor.
Let's go.
Oh, my God.
Everyone, get in line.
Before shooting at a haunted spot, I had Mr. Kadi and his friends tell me scary stories.
The big bird is Junji Inagawa.
A very scary story has come up.
This is two years ago.
It was spring.
I have a friend.
My family is close to me.
My friend contacted me.
My daughter graduated from college and started a broadcasting company.
I don't know what to do because I don't know the industry.
I was wondering if there was a good place.
I happened to have a store in Suginami.
I took a train from my parents' house.
I was told to look for it.
I can't tell you the name of the station, but it's Suginami.
My daughter's apartment is 80 cm from the ground.
It's a two-story apartment on the ground.
My girlfriend is on the first floor.
It's spring, but I'm still a student at school.
I'm going to a company, so I asked my girlfriend to come out.
My girlfriend told me that she would do something like this again.
My girlfriend sent me to a place where I could live.
I was drunk and nervous.
I fell asleep.
I slept in the bathroom.
I don't know what time it is.
Yuki-chan
I woke up to a voice.
She woke up.
She said she was walking her dog at night.
I thought it was strange.
Yuki-chan
When I think in a calm way
Even nothing can be forced.
Do you see her?
I apologize.
It felt good, didn't it?
I fell asleep.
I don't know how much time passed.
Hey, Yuki-chan.
It was that voice again.
It was very close.
I was wearing a futon.
I heard a click.
I opened my eyes.
Hey, Yuki-chan.
What are we going to do tomorrow?
And...
Apparently,
she was in her own room.
She came into the room.
At that time, she thought,
I'm not a human.
I can't get into the room without a sound.
I thought the situation was different.
When I put my earphones on,
I heard a click.
And then I said,
Hey, Yuki-chan.
What are we going to do tomorrow?
When I heard a click,
I didn't know what was going on.
I was very happy.
I just heard a click.
And then I heard a click.
I was wearing a futon.
Hey, Yuki-chan.
What are we going to do tomorrow?
I was wearing a futon.
I was pushed.
I could see it moving.
She was pushing the futon with her face.
And then she whispered in her ear.
Hey, Yuki-chan.
What are we going to do tomorrow?
I could feel her breath.
Please come back.
I heard a click.
Hey, Yuki-chan.
What are we going to do tomorrow?
Please come back.
I heard a click.
I thought,
And then I left.
The next day, she left without her luggage.
But she still has her apartment.
I'm scared.
Let's stop.
And the next spiritual spot
will be explained by Oda.
It's the God's Tower.
It's a tunnel with a strong connection.
If you see the spirit,
You'll see something
A little beyond the middle.
I don't think you can
Get there.
Is there anything there?
It is a place
A long time ago.
A place where murderers
I killed him and dragged him into the room.
So, if you could get in from the other side, what would you do?
Mr. Yamazaki...
Wait a minute.
Thank you very much.
Why are you alone?
You said you could get in by yourself with a digital camera.
You said you couldn't get in at all.
You can get in by yourself with a digital camera.
I'll have you do it.
I can't do it.
I can't.
Thank you very much.
I couldn't do it.
I can't do it.
The place they're going to this time is a certain tunnel in the Kanto area.
Near that tunnel, various incidents have occurred.
It's a devil's tunnel where countless spirits come and go.
Will they really be able to take pictures of the ghosts?
At 11 o'clock in the afternoon, they finally set off for the devil's tunnel.
Hey, everyone.
We're on our way to the scene of the devil's tunnel.
It's like a 4 minute boat ride.
It's the first time we've had such a fun filming.
This is no good.
Don't you feel it yet?
As the filming bus went deeper and deeper into the mountains,
they couldn't hide their anxiety.
This is no good.
I can't do it.
At first, the spirit caddies started to look down at the tunnel.
I'm going to announce it.
It's coming out.
Wait a minute.
Inagawa-san.
Amazing.
What is it?
Inagawa-san.
Yes.
Please announce it.
This is...
It's coming out.
Yamazaki can't hide his anxiety with the words of Inagawa Junji.
It seems like there's a ghost inside.
It's not like there's a ghost.
There is, right?
There is.
It's not like there's a ghost.
All the caddies are looking down at us.
To be honest, this course is for beginners.
We're really beginners.
Especially today, we're against it.
We're really against it, right?
This is tough.
It's really tough.
It seems like we can't go on like we said at first.
For the sake of the fear, Young and Adalto changed the shooting of the two teams.
First, the young team led by Inagawa caddies went to the tunnel.
Yes.
I'm going.
Be careful.
It's okay.
Why are you doing that?
It's scary.
It's amazing.
We can't go in.
Why?
Hang in there.
How far are we going to go?
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
Won't it disappear?
Yes.
Why?
We can't go in any further.
It's okay.
Let's go.
What is it?
It's scary.
What are you doing?
What is it?
No, no, no.
It's not me.
What are you doing?
Manon was surprised.
He was surprised.
It's scary.
What is it?
I was scared.
Wait a minute.
I'm already out of breath.
What is this?
It's on the chair.
No, no, no.
The Young team is finally entering the tunnel.
This is amazing.
What is this?
This is incredible.
The top and the front.
It's calling.
It's incredible.
Wait a minute.
What is this?
Let's go.
The ceiling is incredible.
It's incredible.
Did you see that?
I didn't.
I saw it with my own eyes.
I'm sorry, but...
Why did you do that?
Let's go.
If you don't come closer,
the walls will turn black.
The person will be reflected,
but the scenery will be dark.
What should I do?
I want to be carried to the wall.
I want to be carried.
Can I take a picture here?
Take a picture.
Is there anyone behind you?
No.
What is this?
Behind you.
There's someone behind you.
Stop it.
There's someone in front of you.
Take a picture.
Where?
There.
Let's go back.
Let's go.
No, wait a minute.
Let's go back quickly.
No, no.
Ah, this is bad.
Isn't there anywhere to go?
I did my best.
Hey!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What?
This.
This is all black.
Look.
Everyone is black, look.
It's a white ball.
This black face is a symptom, isn't it?
This face is really scary.
It's scary.
Well, this is useless.
It's a summer project.
Hey!
What?
I won't open it.
Go away!
What are you closing?
Why are you silent?
You can't close it here and there.
Go and close it over there.
If you're going to close it.
Close it in the toilet.
Please.
There are 10 wheels.
Go up.
It's okay to close it, isn't it?
Yes.
After this, what happened in the tunnel of evil?
Why am I a bridge?
In a place like this.
Wait.
That's right.
There is a reaction on the right.
There is a reaction.
That's right.
On the right.
It's a little further.
What?
It's over.
What are you doing?
You have to get on the car.
Why?
About one.
What happened?
It's okay, Sakurai.
What is this?
It's okay.
Then, let's take one more.
Yes.
Shall we go?
One by one.
Because it's a big deal.
Please stick to the wall.
Is this okay?
It's a little strange.
There are two people in the car.
Go.
Yes.
Did you get on the car?
I got on.
I got on the car.
What?
I heard a voice.
What was it?
It was a big wind.
What is it?
I definitely heard the voice.
I heard it on this side too.
I see.
What should I do?
You heard a voice?
I didn't hear that.
I definitely heard it from this side.
Then, what should I do?
I think we should go back.
It's okay. Whatever happens, it's okay.
Let's be quiet for a bit.
Okay.
Look.
It's coming.
It's reacting.
Let's be quiet for a bit.
It's behind us.
It's definitely behind us.
What?
It's walking.
It's trying to walk.
This is bad.
What?
I think we should go back.
It's coming.
It's good.
Let's be quiet for a bit.
Let's go back.
This is bad.
There are only two lanterns.
It's hard.
It's different from here.
The air is heavy.
This is heavy.
What is this?
It's coming from behind.
My head hurts.
What is that?
It's making a perfect sound.
We should go back.
Let's be quiet for a bit.
Let's go back.
It's on both knees.
It's trying to cut.
Who is it?
It's the staff.
It's coming.
I don't understand.
What should we do?
It's coming from behind.
It's still there.
Really?
It's looking at us.
It's hard to see.
It's the one behind us.
Let's go back.
It's really fast.
Did it hit me?
What if it didn't?
It didn't hit you.
It hit my waist.
I don't understand.
Hello.
I'm really scared.
I didn't say anything.
Something hit my shoulder.
I was scared to say anything.
I didn't say anything.
Thank you for watching.