I'll tell you.
You're watching TV, right?
Even if you buy it from me, you won't be able to brag about it.
In the second episode of Gaki no Tsukaiya,
Which do you like more, Chikitsuki or Dochiyan?
Gaki no Tsukaiya
Let me explain.
There's a panel here.
The upper part is my panel,
and the lower part is yours.
I'll randomly put them on,
depending on whether I like them or not.
Then we'll go around each other.
Let's do that.
Now, let's put them on.
I can't help worrying about this.
There are a lot of problems.
It's just that this isn't our intention.
If you look at it, you'll understand.
Which one should I start with?
Let's start with the one you hate.
Let's see.
It's very popular.
Even on TV, it's definitely more than 20% white.
But...
I don't like it at all.
What do you hate about it?
I hate this tail.
Oh, really?
No, no, no.
It's not my intention.
Wait a minute.
Shimura-san watches it every week.
I don't really like my hair.
Shimura-san, that's it.
What?
If you were a man, you should have said it more clearly.
Why is it so thin?
Should I stretch it here?
This too...
Go, go!
But as a senior in this world,
I think there are a lot of things I should learn.
No, no, no.
I think so.
That's right, but...
What do you think about that?
I don't care about that.
I just don't like that part.
It's a matter of looks.
This guy!
It's the worst!
I don't like it when I can't say anything.
That's no good.
I'm not a comedian.
Sometimes I appear on Time TV.
But I have to say it more clearly.
It's disgusting to watch.
Agnes, I want you to say you like it.
Then I'll say,
Agnes, you've changed.
I don't think I've changed.
Applause!
I don't like the way he sings.
I don't like it!
Say what you like.
Mr. Chage...
Does Mr. Chage wear a hat often?
Yes, he does.
That's because...
He looks good in a hat.
Why does Mr. Chage always wear a hat?
Because he likes it.
As soon as I saw him,
I thought he was a bald man.
You don't like me, do you?
Here's a chicken.
Is that okay?
This guy just came out.
What's next?
No, no, no.
I don't like it at all.
What do you not like?
The one in the middle, Ryu-chan.
I don't know anyone who can sing a song of Dorikamu.
There aren't many people who can sing it.
What is it?
It's like God's E Kanji no Kinyoubi.
Don't sing such a lousy song!
The title is bad!
What is that God's E Kanji no Kinyoubi?
It's funny!
You're the one who's in trouble!
What kind of song is this?
There's not enough data.
It's always like that.
I have a lot of fans.
Seriously.
There's no airing here.
If you raise your hand,
I think you'll say,
I can't do that.
Seriously.
Let's be honest.
Do you have a fan?
I'm sorry!
I do have one.
You're doing something right now, right?
Your face when you're flying!
When you're flying.
Your face is like a raccoon.
When you're flying, you're like,
What the hell, you idiot!
You're going to get in trouble!
I'm going to get in trouble!
I'm scared!
I'm in trouble.
Shut up.
It's really hard.
What is?
I've been through a lot.
I have to do my best.
Why are you talking like that?
What's wrong?
I don't know.
It's still cold, isn't it?
It was cold today.
If you think about it,
It's almost cold in a year, isn't it?
That's not true.
Why are you talking like that?
It's almost cold in a year.
It's almost cold in a year, isn't it?
It's the end of the season.
When I was a kid,
There's a ceremony, right?
I thought it was divided into four.
It's not.
It's half cold.
It's been cold since October.
It's 11, 12, 1, 2, 3.
Look, it's been six months.
It's half cold in a year.
That's right.
It's different because it's cold all year round.
It's half cold in a year.
It's cold today.
What are you talking about?
You have to think about it again.
What do you mean?
About the audience.
How do you think about the audience?
I used to do it with only men.
You've done it once, haven't you?
Only young men.
I don't know if I can think about it a little more.
There are a lot of couples these days.
It's annoying.
I don't know what it is.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Do you think we're a bit of an outcast?
Do you think Michael Jackson is in it?
I came to see something on AVEC.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You used to do a project, didn't you?
A signing project.
Do you do it?
It's getting warmer.
I'm thinking about it.
Downtown Pure Land.
Pure Land.
That's a word.
You're lying.
Downtown Pure Land.
So, Machan, Hama-chan.
They're wearing stuffed animals.
There's something like Kitty.
Something like this.
We don't move like that.
There are a lot of things.
What about rides?
There's a magic carpet.
Oh.
You and I are holding a board.
Everyone's wearing a lot of things.
It's like this.
It's like a break.
No, no, no.
It's like an amateur's break.
There's that, too.
While looking at the screen.
Hey, hey, hey.
Star Tours.
I'll do that.
In Akichi?
No, there's usually a screen.
Yes, yes, yes.
What do you do in Akichi?
I'll do it as a child's user.
You'll see when you think about it.
So there are a lot of parts that have been cut.
I'll show you on the big screen.
I couldn't broadcast it.
The chair won't move.
I don't need that.
I don't feel good.
I'm not listening to you.
Is this it?
There's something called Machan experience and Hama-chan experience.
What kind of experience is that?
That's why.
You see it, don't you?
It's like a child's user.
I'm on the Machan experience.
There's a story.
If you get hit in the head by Hamada,
Something from above.
You can see it from Machan's point of view.
You can see it.
That's true, but...
It's better to be on my side.
If I'm on your side, I won't cry.
What do you mean?
That's my life.
Then you'll do something on your side.
I'll be on your side.
It's fun to watch it from a distance.
Everyone's on your side.
Then downtown stores.
It's common.
Downtown goods.
That's one more thing.
Downtown stores are like that.
Inexhaustible.
Vegetables?
Vegetables.
Inexhaustible vegetables.
That's how it is.
Do you want to do it?
This is a new project.
If you want to come, please come.
That's right.
I'll do it.
Just spin it?
Then you can enjoy it?
I can enjoy it.
You and I will hold it like this.
It's about three people.
No, no, it's different.
There's nothing like this down there.
There's no stick like that.
It's all mine.
It's huge.
Why?
I can put three people on it.
It's impossible.
I can't do it alone.
You don't have any strength.
That's not true.
You don't have any grip.
Try it.
It doesn't hurt at all.
Why is your face like this?
I'm angry.
It doesn't hurt at all.
You can't go to a sports club.
What is that?
You're angry because you don't have any strength.
I'm angry.
It doesn't hurt at all.
Something's wrong with your arm.
There's a story about Kaioka.
What?
A sports club.
Really?
Our soccer player, Takasu,
won a squash prize.
If I start playing squash,
do you want to play it
when we play against each other?
Sure.
Let's say I play squash for half a year
and I get better
and I become like Fujii Tatsuya.
That's
only for casters.
If you become like that,
do you want to play against me?
The punishment game this time is tough.
It's already decided.
This time,
I'm going to skydive
without a parachute.
If something happens to me,
I'll die.
Just in case.
I'll jump without a parachute.
If nothing happens to me,
I'll die.
Let's play against each other.
Really?
Are you going?
Let's play.
Let's play against each other.
I don't care.
Why are you so angry?
Just throw it to me.
If you don't do that,
you'll get in trouble.
I'll be kind to you.
Do you play tricks recently?
I changed my number.
Your phone number?
I don't care.
I'll throw it to you.
I want to go in.
If I go in,
I'll get in trouble.
I don't care.
I'll be kind to you.
In the past,
in the past,
I used to shout.
But now,
I can't do that.
You have to be there.
I don't have a place to go.
My voice is like this.
Like this.
When I come home,
there's something in front of the door.
There was an erotic video.
I'm happy.
I don't know if I'm happy or not.
What's the content?
Last erotic video of a girl.
There was something.
I saw it.
I can't help it.
That's why.
It's like this.
People who watch TV
have their own ideas.
It's weird.
I'm in trouble.
If so,
What will you do?
I add pressure to my back.
This is not the back.
Is this the back?
A pack that puts pressure on your back.
Put pressure on it.
Ah, this is a bit similar to what I said earlier.
Ah, is that so?
Why is the phone's cord not straight, but curved?
That's right, if you say it like that.
It's like an electric wire.
What do you mean, an electric wire?
To stop broadcasting.
That's not it!
It's an electric wire!
What do you mean, an electric wire?
That's not it!
It's an electric wire!
It's scary, an electric wire.
Why is that?
It's scary.
You call it an electric wire?
Put in a booo.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
An electric wire.
It's an electric wire!
Why is there a booo?
Why is there a vacuum cleaner?
If you press it, it goes like this.
That's weird.
But it's convenient, right?
It's convenient, but it's inconvenient.
Why?
You can't do it all at once.
If you use it for a year, it goes like this.
If you pull it a little more, it goes like this.
No way, I can't put it in like this.
That's...
That's the vacuum cleaner.
Well, that's fine.
Why is it spinning?
This is my plan for NTT.
What does that mean?
It's my plan to charge a little more for the phone bill.
If you charge it directly, it won't take long to charge the phone bill, right?
If you extend the distance like this,
the phone bill will go up a little.
Such a code...
Such a code will reduce the phone bill.
Yes, it will reduce it.
So, normally, when you say hello,
you say hello, right?
You say hello, right?
That's...
Hello?
At this point, it costs about 20 yen.
This is my plan for NTT.
You're the only one who can do this.
Idiot!
Even now, the phone's function is getting complicated.
I can't keep up with it.
What do you mean?
Like a transfer phone...
I thought about it.
A machine to prevent prank calls.
It's a little complicated.
You can use a transfer phone.
For example,
the Japanese NTT will rent an apartment in Brazil.
Wait a minute.
Say it again.
What?
The NTT...
The NTT will rent an apartment in Brazil?
Rent an apartment.
If the NTT goes to Brazil,
it won't be a problem for the hotel, right?
The employees, right?
What are you talking about?
Go anywhere!
Without a share.
I don't care.
To Brazil.
Even an apartment.
It's easy.
For example,
a prank call will be sent to my place.
I'll make it a transfer phone.
I'll send it to Brazil.
Then, the person who called me
will be in Brazil.
Amazing!
Even if I talk for 5 minutes,
it will cost thousands of yen.
With this, a prank call won't be a loss.
At that time,
I'll say,
what color are your pants?
What color are your pants?
It's 2800 yen.
It's more expensive than my pants.
After the wedding,
I often see you two
riding a car.
What is the empty can
behind the car?
Why?
Are you going to put an empty can behind the car?
I whisper to you.
You must be crazy.
I'm sure.
It's not me.
Someone is behind me.
I'm not that powerful.
What are you doing?
Why is it an empty can?
Do you know the saying,
if the wind blows,
you will go there.
You will go there.
Marriage is happiness.
Happiness is an empty can.
You laughed.
Why is happiness an empty can?
What are you talking about?
Why?
I'm not that powerful.
What are you talking about?
There are many people watching.
Right?
Happiness is an empty can.
Why?
Happiness is
a dream.
A dream is
a night.
As a government.
A night is
a dark night.
It sounds like a kid's idea.
A dark night is a ghost.
A ghost is scary.
Right?
Scary is an empty can.