This is the 5th episode of Gaki no Tsukai Arai, Tsukitsugi! World's Peaceful! Narikiri Omiya-I!
5th episode?
It's an unbelievable story today.
Well, let's do it.
I wonder what it is.
All the Japanese people are like this when it comes to peace.
World's Peaceful is running on the road of peace.
Saito Director 41 years old.
No one can stop the passion for marriage that rises as much as it is shaken.
What kind of peace will challenge a new match?
Well, today, Mr. Yamazaki.
Yes.
Please tell us about the progress.
Yes, I understand. Today, we have three wonderful guests.
Toppata!
What's going on?
It's fast.
I've told you before, but it's not a small story.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Please give us a little time.
Just a little.
Please.
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
Mr. Yamazaki.
Yes.
Please introduce the first person.
Yes, let me introduce the first person.
Yes.
Today, I ate something a little strong.
I ate fried chicken and rice balls.
What?
Saito.
What is that?
That's great.
Oh, hello.
Thank you very much.
It's very expensive.
Yes.
But you are a university student, aren't you?
Aren't there any people around you?
Well, I'm tired of it.
Yes.
It's amazing that there are so many young men these days.
I see.
Yes, yes, I understand.
Well, that doesn't mean it's new.
But you were born in the 29th year of the Showa era, weren't you?
Yes, I was born in the 29th year of the Showa era.
Well, since I was eight years old, I've been working in a barbershop.
It's hard.
Well, let's watch the video.
Yes.
Aoyama.
That's good.
Oh, it's really hard.
It's really hard.
Wait a minute.
It's really cool.
But your legs are short.
Your legs are short.
What's wrong with your legs?
It's light.
Your legs are short.
Wow.
This is awesome.
Their faces are like real ones.
They look like real ones.
That's right.
Wow, they look like real ones.
I forgot about the newspaper.
It's coming, it's coming.
It would have been better if it was wider.
It's like a sausage.
Ah, it's not that you can see it all the time.
Sometimes it's like this.
It's like a sausage in a convenience store.
Oh, that's nice.
Ah, it's coming, it's coming.
It's coming.
That, that, that.
That's right, that's right.
It's because it's in.
In my case, I can't use too much force.
I'm going to
after that, like this...
That's right, like that.
Wonderful.
That was wonderful.
This one's pretty good, though.
Hey.
Ah, sorry.
I think the audience,
are really surprised by the loss all of a sudden.
That's right.
There are theme songs.
Right.
I want to look cool today.
I see.
What do you think of me today?
Who are you asking?
My girlfriend.
Your girlfriend?
What do you think of me today?
You looked a bit like a monkey, but it was wonderful.
Right?
It was nice.
But out of all the ones I've done, you were the best.
Thank you very much.
All right. Please wait a moment.
Sayaka, what about you?
I like people who eat things clean.
Heipo failed.
Well...
How was it?
I'm sure you can tell by the tone of my voice.
Well...
I've been told by my parents a lot today.
No way.
How can you talk to your parents about this?
Next, I have a girlfriend.
I see.
I have ten Ashis now.
I didn't like one of them recently, so I cut off one of them.
You came looking for the tenth Ashis?
Yes, I came looking for the tenth Ashis.
You're not Ashis!
But I'm playing with Ashis, so I want to have a serious relationship with her.
Here you go!
Here you go.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
Please come over here.
Are you a fan of Anri?
Yes, I am.
Nice to meet you.
Miss!
No, I'm not.
But you have a girlfriend, don't you?
I have a lot of friends.
You have friends?
Yes, I have friends.
You have a lot of friends.
I have a lot of friends.
Ashis asked you about the tenth Ashis, didn't he?
Yes, he did.
How about you?
Well...
I don't really listen to him.
You have a girlfriend?
Yes, I have a lot of friends.
Then, please come over here.
This is great!
Heipo!
You're good!
This feels good!
This feels bad!
I don't know if I can do it or not.
He's looking at you!
He's looking at you very much!
You did it!
This is great!
This is amazing!
Hello, this is HEPPO.
HEPPO-SAN!
Yes?
Wonderful!
He liked it.
I got it!
Thank you very much.
This is more amazing than the first time.
Is the third time okay?
It's okay.
I have a question.
It's almost Christmas, isn't it?
Yes.
Are you thinking about something?
I'd like to be with you.
Yes.
Other than that?
Me?
I'd like to see my parents.
I'd like to go to my parents' home town.
Really?
That's unexpected.
I'd like to see them.
How long have you been single?
It's been about 20 years.
Yes, it's been about 20 years.
Really?
It's been a long time since I had a girlfriend.
I had a girlfriend about a year ago.
The other day, I officially became the vice president of an office company.
What an annoying man!
That's because I'm the wife of the vice president.
I think it's a privilege.
Let's go!
Please make your judgment!
You're lying!
I thought I could do it.
Why?
My nose is dirty from this distance.
I'm clean.
You're 41.
Yamazaki-san, please introduce your last girlfriend.
She recently broke up with her boyfriend.
Her boyfriend was three hours late for her date.
She waited for him for three hours.
She endured everything.
Please call her.
Chika Kihara!
Hello.
Are you a cameraman?
As a profession?
What do you do?
I take pictures of magazines.
Really?
Yes, I take pictures of musicians.
I'm looking for a company.
I want to make my own work.
Really?
Give me the gun!
Give it to me!
I'm scared.
I'm looking at you.
I don't want to die.
You're smoking, right?
That's right.
I don't smoke.
Don't forget to smoke.
I don't want to die.
You were so naive at the end.
Do you have a lighter?
You look like Mr. Slim.
I don't want to die.
You'll die before you realize it.
I'll be brave.
It was cold.
It was very cold.
It's not perfect.
Please wait for the result.
Please make a judgment.
Failure.
I'd like to ask you again.
As I said before, I became vice president.
I'm sorry, but I'd like to do it again.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Good evening.
I'm going to send it today.
I'll send it.
I'll send it every week.
I see.
What is it?
Let's get started.
My body?
I feel the same way these days.
That's terrible.
I'm not breathing as well as before.
That's no good.
I used to be able to do a lot of things when I was over 30.
I used to be able to get on the elevator when it was open, but these days I can't.
Even if I press the button three times, I can't get on the elevator.
I can't get on the elevator.
But that's my taste.
No one can understand that.
If you say that, it will get worse and worse.
That's right.
It can't be helped.
I haven't been to the fuzoku recently.
You used to be able to get on the elevator, but you haven't been there.
That's my word.
I haven't been there recently.
You haven't been to the fuzoku recently.
What do you mean by interesting fuzoku?
Let me tell you.
I'm getting tired of it.
I'm getting tired of it because I'm surrounded by women.
Then you should go to a different shop.
I went to a different shop.
When I went to a different shop, the system there was like,
I'm going to put something in this.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to say anything.
At that point, my M heart was shaking.
I didn't feel good when I was told to do this and that.
Who's coming?
That's M.
Do you understand?
No, I don't understand.
You don't understand, do you?
I'm a super high-class S.
I'm surrounded by women.
Stop it!
My face is like this.
Are you an idiot?
No, I don't know.
Because a comic duo is made up of S and M.
This is a fact.
Otherwise, you can't do it because it's a duo.
I've been doing it for 15 years.
I'm a super high-class M.
I'm a super high-class S.
What do you mean by super high-class?
What do you mean by high-class?
If it was a high-class high-class, it wouldn't be a big deal.
High-class high-class.
It means high-class high-class.
It's not a high-class high-class.
I want you to be emotional.
Let me tell you something good today.
A comic duo is made up of S and M.
I see.
I'm a super high-class M and you're a super high-class S.
It's very clear.
It's very obvious, isn't it?
If you hit me and see that I'm in pain, you won't be able to stop it.
Why?
Why can't you stop it?
I want you to be more stupid.
I want to hit you, so I want you to shake me more.
That's right.
I want you to shake me more to make me more stupid.
Stop it.
You might feel that way, but it's not like that.
I can't say things like this.
I see.
I'm so tired.
Stop it.
It's in your mind.
You should develop a new store.
You should be more aware of what you're doing.
That's right.
I understand what you're saying.
As you get older, you'll gradually understand what I'm saying.
What?
In the past, I used to say things like this.
I see.
But now, I say things like this because I have money.
Now, I say things like this because I don't know.
You can't say things like that.
I say things like this because I'm a C-class student.
You can't say things like this because you're a C-class student.
Matsumoto-san, you've fought against 999 kinds of beasts and won many times.
But you were surrounded by cows and broke their bones.
If you were surrounded by them, how would you escape?
First of all, you shouldn't be surrounded by them.
Of course, I shouldn't be surrounded by them.
But if you were surrounded by them...
I understand.
Come on, Anaconda.
Me?
Yes, because you're the only one who can fight against Anaconda.
Come on.
Anaconda isn't like that.
That's funny.
One by one.
I shouldn't say it first.
Come on, Anaconda.
It's like this, right?
Anaconda is more stiff.
More like this?
It's different.
But it's fine like that.
Come on, Anaconda.
You can't escape.
The speed is different.
If you don't fight against Anaconda, I can't teach you.
Come on, Anaconda.
I'm a little stupid.
I was scared to fall.
This summer, I was stung by the sun.
I couldn't stop stinging.
I was stung so much that I bled.
For next year, please tell me how to avoid being stung by a crab.
Me?
Yes.
Understood.
That's fine.
What is it?
Please tell me how to avoid being stung by a crab.
Did you get stung a lot this year?
It seems so.
I got stung so much.
And it's over this year.
Of course it's over.
Then, next year is impossible.
What do you mean?
When you get stung, you have to say,
I'll end it this year.
I'll let you get stung this year.
I got it.
I got it when I got stung.
Yes.
I'll let you get stung this year.
But you'll get stung if you get stung.
I'll let you get stung when I get stung.
I don't have to put up with it even though I got stung.
I don't know if I got stung when I was talking.
I got stung when I got stung.
If you get stung here and here, it doesn't matter.
There are times when you don't get stung.
When you don't know anything.
You don't get stung.
You can't understand that you got stung.
You don't get stung, do you?
I don't get stung.
If I get stung, I'll hit you and kill you.
Why did you get stung?
Oh, I remember.
It doesn't matter.
Do you know why I got stung?
What do you mean?
Please tell me.
I want to suck your blood.
No, no, no, no.
That's not it.
Why?
They say they're happy to make people happy.
That's why I'm going to suck your blood.
I'm going to look at you for a while.
Okay.
Okay?
Then I'm going to look at you like this.
I'm going to look at you like this.
Why?
Don't eat sushi.
If I get stung, they'll think I'm crazy.
Why?
Who?
I'm going to take your flesh.
This is the best way to get rid of stinging.
Oh, I see.
I'm going to do this.
If I get stung, they'll think I'm crazy.
Then until I get være, they're going to think I'm crazy.
I got you killed!
With all my hair.
Put on some hot water.
You shouldn't have said that!
It's really bad!
You don't want to see your partner like this until he dies?
You don't want to see him like you don't usually see him, right?
I don't want to see you doing it.
What is that?
Do you think you're doing it?
What are you doing?
You're so childish!
I'm winning!
Damn it!
You!
Did you see it?
I'm done with that.
Of course.
I don't want to show you what I do all day.
But remember this!
Hey!
You're about to cry!
Remember this!
My sex is amazing!
You shouldn't have said that!
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.