Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
Today, we're at the Shinjuku Gyoen.
That's right.
If we had another camera, I'd like to film these idiots.
In the middle of winter...
Let me introduce them to you.
You're idiots, right?
It's cold outside every time.
So the staff told us not to dress warmly.
They told us to wear T-shirts 24 hours a day.
Today, all the staff are wearing T-shirts 24 hours a day.
They're doing their best.
The staff around here...
We're...
It's really cold today.
It's about 9 degrees today.
Look at that.
What is that?
That's called a kit.
It's a painful thing.
What's a kit?
Theater Sun Mall.
They put a bottle of coke with a dollar in it on the table.
I see.
And they want you to sit here.
That's amazing.
If you do it in a hall like this, it's usually slippery.
It's slippery.
That's how it is.
It's like a revenge movie.
A big explosion.
I wonder if it's okay.
It's kind of nice.
The T-shirt is pretty.
It's colorful and nice.
Everyone looks like they're having fun.
Right?
Who designed this?
It's a hobby that I want to hit.
This program is brought to you by Sunluck, Oyama International Products, and the sponsor of this program.
Ah.
It's lonely to be alone.
Ah!
Thank you.
Mister.
Who are you?
I'm Rolling Thunder Man.
Rolling Thunder Man?
Yes.
I didn't know that.
It might be impossible on Earth.
Impossible?
What are you doing here?
Do you know Peggy Seijin?
Peggy Seijin?
Yes.
I heard that the evil Peggy Seijin is attacking the Earth.
If you leave it like this, the people on Earth will get hit by Peggy Seijin.
What?
I came here to protect this beautiful Earth.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Peggy Seijin is coming.
I don't know if Peggy Seijin is looking at you.
You can't do anything.
I'm still a child.
I see.
Be careful.
Thank you.
See you.
I'm Rolling Thunder Man.
You are a strange man.
This is from Isojima.
It won't open.
Uncle.
Yes.
What?
It won't open.
The lid from Isojima.
It's Peggy Seijin's doing.
Is it true?
What a terrible thing.
I'm okay.
Thank you, uncle.
What a terrible thing.
You can't do anything.
What?
I'm tired from M36.
I don't know that.
Be careful.
Thank you, uncle.
Yes.
Uncle.
What?
I'm scared of Peggy Seijin.
Shut up.
Rolling Thunder Man Mimi.
You can't do anything.
Mimi?
Peggy Seijin said something bad about you.
I didn't do anything.
You don't have to say something bad.
I heard that Peggy Seijin said something bad about you.
Really?
If you don't say anything, Peggy Seijin will pull your hair.
Do something, uncle.
I'm scared.
Where are you, Peggy Seijin?
Peggy Seijin.
Rolling Thunder Man Mimi.
You can't do anything.
Peggy Seijin is coming here.
Peggy Seijin.
What are you talking about?
What are you talking about, uncle?
If you don't say anything, Rolling Thunder Man...
Are you thinking about it?
Yes.
I have a good idea.
What is it?
Don't worry.
Even if Peggy Seijin attacks, I will defeat him with Rolling Thunder Man.
You can defeat him.
Yes.
Uncle, can you live with me?
I live alone.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Please live with me, uncle.
Let's do that.
Let's live together.
Yes.
Then three years passed.
I'm back.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Why are you taking off your pants?
What?
What are you doing?
You are alone.
Don't do that.
I'm not doing anything.
Something stinks.
What?
Clean up the room.
I feel sick recently.
Are you on the side of justice?
Only at the beginning.
Let's live together.
At the beginning, I was nervous.
What are you doing?
Why are you taking off your pants?
What?
Clean up the room.
I don't want to do that.
It's your job.
Don't touch me.
I've changed.
At the beginning, I was kind.
Why were you kind?
You don't do anything at home.
Do your job.
Stop it.
I hate you.
What?
Go home.
Go home?
Where are you going?
What?
When will the Peggy Seijin come?
I told you three years ago.
Rolling Thunder Gate.
It's coming soon.
When will it come?
It's been three years.
You lied.
That's not true.
The Peggy Seijin is not coming at all.
The Peggy Seijin is late.
What are you talking about?
Don't pull me.
Do your job.
What is this?
What is this shirt?
You're dressed up.
It's the Rolling Thunder Store.
What?
What is this?
I can beat you.
I can't stand it anymore.
If there is a Sadameshi in your house, it may be the Rolling Thunder Gate.
You reacted somehow.
Let's go.
It's been a long time since I did this.
This is the first time this year.
This is the second time.
This is the second time?
Yes.
You're lying.
Really?
This is the second time?
Yes.
This is the first time.
Really?
Yes.
You didn't have to do it today.
You didn't have to do it at this time.
You didn't have to go back to Osaka right after this.
Really?
Yes.
But Kohaku was amazing.
I can't believe it.
Which one was it?
What?
People who watch TV know it.
I can't believe that Tetsuya Takeda ran out of Pritin.
That was in Sendai.
I was surprised.
That's why it was a little late to mosaic.
But which one did you win?
What?
Which one did you win?
This year, you know.
Shirofumi won.
Let's bet.
What?
Which one did you win?
You're making fun of me.
Let's bet.
Okay.
What will you do if you lose?
You won't do the opening location alone.
I don't want to do that.
Today, you know.
The staff was wearing the T-shirt of Kiyoshi Ariyama.
The staff was wearing a T-shirt of Kiyoshi Ariyama.
And the bottom was like Gungnji Kawamata.
Like a brief.
And the back was like this.
You lost.
And you put your pants on.
You wore this big pants of Gungnji.
I was like Rolling Thunder Man.
I don't see the reason.
It was blue.
Shouka was wearing different pants.
One of them is called Nukui, and the other one is called Kawamada-kun.
I mean, it's rude to call them pants.
Why is it rude?
There must be some kind of problem.
What kind of problem do you have with white pants?
Are you that amazing?
What kind of problem do you have?
It doesn't mean anything like that.
It's a bit yellowish.
White pants are always beautiful.
Right?
That's not cool.
Can you do it if you lose?
I won't do it if I lose.
This is decided by Saito.
If you lose, you have to wear a suit like this in the back of Zoom-in Asa.
You have to wear a T-shirt and white pants.
You have to wear a suit like this in the back of Fukutome-san.
What do you think of this?
Do you think I'm crazy?
It's early in the morning and it's hard.
Oh, really?
If you lose...
You won't be able to get up in the morning.
Which one of us won?
Let's make it clear.
If you lose, you have to wear a suit like this in the back of Zoom-in Asa.
In the back of Zoom-in Asa?
Okay.
Then let me say it first.
Red pants.
If you say it so clearly, I want red pants, too.
This is Tuesday, right?
I think it's really funny.
Tuesday, right?
I'll laugh in front of the TV.
If you say it so clearly, I'll laugh in the back of Zoom-in Asa at 7 or 8 in the morning.
So...
You have to get up in the morning.
It's hard, though.
This broadcast is on Tuesday, so if you lose, the next day, Wednesday morning.
You have to do it on Wednesday morning.
This year, I've been thinking about my activities as a downtown.
It's good to be on an amateur program.
Is that so?
An amateur program, a viewer program...
But in the end, that's the only thing that makes sense.
If you lose, what are you going to do?
Is it okay to say Zoom-in Asa?
Or you can paint Mr. Wiki white.
There's something like that.
There is.
But I'm really thinking about it this year.
I'm going to be on an amateur program.
I'm not going to work at all.
I'm going to be on my own.
You're going to apply like an amateur?
I'm going to apply.
For example, what are you going to do?
What I'm thinking about right now is that...
I'm going to be on KIN-CHAN NO KASO TAISYO.
I'm going to apply.
That's right.
This is delicious.
You did it in the new year, didn't you?
There's still half a year to go.
I'm thinking about that.
What are you going to do?
I'm thinking about this.
I'm going to do KAMELEON.
You're going to apply on KASO TAISYO, aren't you?
Why do you do that in KAMELEON?
That's not what he's going to do.
I'm going to apply on KAMELEON.
And I'll do the big mouth.
Open your mouth wide.
You should apply on your tongue.
Should I?
Prepare a black and red cloth.
I wrap it around my body.
I wrap it around my tongue.
I hold a stick with my left hand and put a fake fly on it.
While I was doing the Camelot, the fly got stuck on the other side.
I grabbed the fly with the front of my hand and put it back with the back of my hand.
It's hard.
And I only have to say the line.
0.2 seconds.
Can you do it?
Where is this?
But I don't think I can do it until I pass the exam.
Is that so?
In that case, you are one of Kin-chan's students, right?
That's right.
I don't think a kid can get an A.
So, if you do the Camelot and say, please come out, I'll do it like a kid.
I'll do it like Yutako.
I'll do it like Adokena.
I'll do my best.
I think I can do it.
Oh, really?
I think I can do the Camelot.
But I don't have any special training.
I'm the only one who can do it.
Special training?
I don't have a fly.
The fly was stabbed by Natsumi Ogawa.
I asked, who grabbed the fly?
He said, Hamada.
I'll do it until I get older.
So, what happened to your white hair?
What?
I can't do it.
You can't do it?
You can't?
I'll tell you why.
If you lose.
What happens if you lose?
What are you doing?
Oh, I got it.
You should wear a furus.
I don't want to wear a furus.
What are you going to do?
I'll do the Shogun of China.
Oh, this is a different song.
I'll sing Garara Nyororo.
I'll sing Garara Nyororo at 10 in the morning.
I'll go to Fukutomo.
Bam!
The people who are watching this show,
they've been on this show for hours already.
It's hard, isn't it?
It's hard for the people who are watching this show.
But, well,
I don't know the result of 31 days,
so I'll do my best.
It's okay.
I understand.
I'll do it.
I'll do it when I lose.
Right?
Yes.
You're white, right?
It's red.
Give me the red one.
I don't want it.
Well, I can see it.
I'm doing it in the morning.
I don't care about the time.
I know what I'm doing.
I don't care about it.
Don't you have the same score as Kouhaku?
I don't?
I don't.
I wish I had.
It's okay.
I understand.
So, shall we go?
Yes.
Let's go to the post office.
Oh, really?
Don't kick the door.
I want to do it.
Do it properly.
Don't kick the door.
Even if I'm late for work,
I'll do it properly.
Don't do that.
Don't be late.
I'm counting on you.
Okay.
I'll do it properly in the ending.
Give me a minute.
He doesn't want to do it.
This is amazing.
Look at this.
Kouhaku has worn this much before.
After Kouhaku's marriage announcement,
he has worn only this much.
This is a new way of doing things.
Today, Kouhaku's girlfriend
came to the post office.
She came to the post office.
Oh, really?
Yes.
I think I know whether it's red or white.
Red.
See?
It's red.
Who do you think it is?
Wait a minute.
Let's ask the staff at the post office.
I think red is Kouhaku's favorite color.
White is Kouhaku's favorite color.
See?
I'll remember that it's white.
So, do it properly.
Why don't you do it?
You should do it.
Why don't you go out with her?
Don't say dangerous things.
Let me introduce her.
It's been a long time.
Why do you say such things?
Mariko Wada.
Don't say it.
I won't leave you alone.
I'm on TV.
Don't say it.
Harashi Sagami, Kanagawa Prefecture.
Where is it?
Oono Sagami.
I'll stop here.
You have a great academic record.
Are you a junior high school graduate?
I'm a junior high school graduate.
You don't have to aim for it.
Thank you for coming today.
Thank you very much.
Let me introduce Harashi.
Her pen name is Piko.
Good evening.
Congratulations, Harashi.
The other day, you made the ultimate choice.
I made the ultimate choice on this show.
Which do you like better, the name Nanashi or Piyopiyomaru?
At that time, you said Piyopiyomaru was better.
I don't like Hama-chan.
I like P-chan.
That's enough.
Don't be stubborn.
I'm not that stubborn.
I thought about it at that time.
What is Piyopiyomaru?
When you said Piyopiyomaru, which do you like better?
I thought about it in my head.
That's why I like P-chan.
I don't think so.
Don't say such things.
I'm looking forward to it.
In about 5 hours, the Shogun of Hamada-san will be here.
I don't know if you're a Shogun or not.
Why do I say such nonsense?
Is your schedule okay on Wednesday?
It's morning.
What?
I see.
I don't have work from 7 o'clock.
You don't have work from 7 o'clock.
I'll definitely do it.
If I buy this, I'll go back to Osaka.
I saw it in Osaka.
I'll go back to Osaka like Tamura Masakazu.
I don't mind looking at it from the side.
Please.
Everyone is looking forward to it.
This will end at 2 o'clock.
About 10 minutes.
2 o'clock and 10 minutes.
Well, about 5 hours later.
Let's meet again.
Well, let's meet 5 hours later behind Kutsume-san.
Thank you very much.
It's fun.
The first time.
Don't you feel like you've already won?
No, it's not like that.
5 hours later?
People who watch TV only know who has won and who has lost.
It's amazing.
I don't know why I said such a thing.
Let's go for now.
I'll go if I lose.
If I lose, I'm sorry.
What?
I'm thinking about the next new development.
I can't ride it.
Idiot.
I'll never ride it.
You have to decide which one to ride.
I see.
I have to pretend to be a foreigner passing by.
What kind of person are you?
I have to pass by when I go to the main subject.
I can't do that.
I have to ride a plane and chase.
Idiot.
Please think about it.
Let's think about something new.
I'm still in the hope of winning.
You saw it.
I have to write a letter.
Is that so?
Please don't do that.
I want to see it.
I have to write a letter.
And the place.
Please do it here.
Please come to my dorm.
I have to write a letter.
I'll do it here.
I'll do it.
Please look forward to it.
I'll write a letter here.
See you in 5 hours.