I'm Miyasubako, the staff member of Kira-Kira, a TV show about gangsters.
What's this?
Well, Miyasubako, you can say whatever you want to us.
I see. You've been on this show for a year and a half or two years.
There must be something you want to say.
I can't say it out loud.
I see.
I'm not going to say that I'm writing a name.
I don't know who wrote what.
We are the type of people who accept such things from the very beginning.
Yes, yes.
We admit mistakes.
Well, you seem to be proud of yourself.
So I think we can just say what we want to say.
Oh, really?
Well, it's hard to say it.
Well, well, well.
This is Miyasubako.
Why are you so rude?
What's this?
Isn't it something you can use?
Yes, I see.
Well, I don't know what you're going to buy.
I see.
Please put it in.
You're going to put it in?
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Let's see.
The second one, right?
No, the first one, the first one.
I wonder who this is.
Hamada, you're not funny.
Five years later, the comedy show will be this Team Zero Yamazaki.
Yamazaki!
Yamazaki, wait a minute!
Do you know what Miyasubako means?
How do you write a name?
Do you really think so?
No, I'm being honest.
Is it true that it's five years later?
Well, it's about five years later.
I see.
But I think it's a good thing that young people think like this.
I think it's a good thing.
I thought so, too.
I thought I was funny when I was young.
But I had talent.
This is from Matsumoto.
Don't call me Nakasone.
Remember my name.
That's all.
Well, who am I?
I'm that stylist, Chibiya.
Come here.
What's your real name?
I'm Uesugi.
I can't remember Uesugi.
What do you mean?
Uesugi is a little strange.
I always remember that name.
Why did you call me Matsumoto?
Well, Noriyasu...
He called you Hage?
Yes.
Is he your father?
You can't call me like this.
Let's go back.
What's this?
In Okinawa, in Roppongi,
I always bring delicious women.
Even if you give them to me once,
I won't be punished.
When I gave you this paper,
I wrote my name on the paper.
It says I don't know.
I don't want you to find out.
Really?
I wrote my name here.
Come on, Otomo.
Otomo!
What does this mean?
Well, sometimes...
What?
Sometimes I...
I like women.
You like women?
Yes.
Do you like women?
Yes, I like them.
You don't like them?
No, I don't like them.
Do you think I like them too much?
Somehow...
I don't give a shit!
Why?
To the director of Saito-Chief.
I've been with you for 10 years,
but I've never seen your girlfriend even for a second.
To be honest, if you don't have one, I don't have one.
This is interesting.
Wait a minute. Where is she?
Where? Where? Where?
Probably...
Yes?
Maybe she's doing the opening ceremony next week.
I think she's in the dressing room.
Saito!
You!
I was listening to the assistant's phone number!
I didn't know there was such a team director!
What the hell!
Did you see his face?
Did you see?
I bet you couldn't take his face.
He looked so sad and depressed.
Saito, what were you doing?
What did you ask?
Look at this!
You should have met her.
You shouldn't have sat next to her.
You should have talked to her.
This guy is the director.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay wearing such a skirt?
I don't know if I did it right.
Ladies and gentlemen.
I'm sorry.
You were late today.
You should have talked to her.
What were you doing before we started?
What?
Well, I'm often told that I'm a nice guy.
I was taking a shit.
You were told that you're a nice guy, but you were taking a shit.
You don't look like you're taking a shit.
Idiot!
By the way, you look like you're having a hard time.
You look like you're having a hard time.
How many times did you take a shit?
As I always say, I take a shit about once a month.
I take a shit about five times a day.
I take a shit about two hamsters a month.
You don't have to take a shit about two hamsters.
But today, I took a shit about two hamsters.
I took a shit about two hamsters.
You haven't finished yet.
You shouldn't do that.
That's true.
I take a shit once a month, and then I don't take a shit about two hamsters.
It's still the same.
You still have something to say.
You're right.
That's what I've been saying.
That's right.
Did you take a shit properly?
Yes, I did.
You can't take a shit about two hamsters.
I did take a shit about two hamsters.
Do you have poop on your pants?
So, I have.
You should have pooped properly.
Everyone has poop on their pants.
I don't have.
Everyone has.
What?
Everyone has poop on their pants.
I took the statistics.
8 out of 10 people have poop on their pants.
I don't have.
I can't stand it.
What do you mean you can't stand it?
We can't stand it.
Out of 10 people, for example,
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8,
up to that point,
we put in 10 people.
These two people.
Yes.
8 people already have poop on their pants.
Well, you have.
I have.
I don't have.
What do you mean?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6,
up to that point,
we put in 10 people.
You guys.
No.
You're the only one who doesn't have poop on their pants.
Aoi, why do you have poop on your pants?
I don't think it's dirty.
It's not about whether it's dirty or not.
You can't have poop on your pants properly.
When I finished,
everyone was like,
did you wash your hands?
I don't wash my hands even if I poop.
Why?
Well,
I don't do it when I'm small.
I don't think I should wash my hands.
I don't wash my hands either.
When I'm big,
I don't wash my hands.
Everyone, let's be honest.
I'm not a genius.
What's wrong?
I'll ask you.
Why don't you wash your hands even if you poop?
Why are your hands dirty?
I'll poke you in the head.
Then I'll wash my hands.
I see.
That's great.
I went to the batting center.
I thought you were a real sportsman.
The speed ball hit the batting center.
If I do more,
I'll be called out in the draft.
I quit because I thought I couldn't do it anymore.
Who's watching the batting center?
It's your job.
If you're going to bet,
quit golf and go to the batting center.
That's fine.
No, no, no.
I see.
You're good.
You're really good.
I came to the summer camp to get a note.
That's great.
Then I'll go to the batting center and bet.
Let's do it.
You're so strong.
It's fine.
Let's do it.
I go to the baseball class.
Only one day?
Yes, yes, yes.
I don't have gloves.
I'm poor at home.
You went home because you were about to cry, didn't you?
If you're going to learn baseball,
bring gloves.
I don't have money.
Everyone is wearing uniforms,
but you're wearing a jersey.
That's not true.
I'm Matsumoto.
Nice to meet you.
Let's get along.
Let's start the summer camp.
Matsumoto,
why don't you protect him from the outside world?
Matsumoto, where are your gloves?
I don't have gloves.
Be quiet.
Then, in my head,
I remember my mother.
Yes.
My mother when I was a child.
Yes, yes, yes.
When I was a child, yes.
In my head,
when I went to Awajishima with my family,
I said,
I love you.
My mother is like this.
When I think about running on the beach with my mother,
tears come out.
You came back without saying anything.
I came back without saying anything.
Why is that?
When I'm sad,
I don't think there are many girls.
There are.
When I was practicing taikwondo,
I was doing something in my lower body.
The gouda of taikwondo.
I was doing gouda.
Yes, yes, yes.
When I was in elementary school.
I was doing something in my lower body.
Here.
I was doing this.
Where did you dig it?
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Stop it.
If you have something sad,
your mother runs like this.
You were running when you were running away.
Your mother.
Why is your mother running when you are pooping?
It's scary.
It's not scary.
You don't do it.
What?
I'll do it.
It's about time to do something.
This year.
The first time.
What kind of rule?
Let's decide the rules.
Nothing.
That's why it's a winning-losing rule.
What?
Oh, that batting?
Yes.
What is it?
Oh, there is one more thing in the batting squad.
Prepare a professional player.
I'll have you throw it.
How many balls will you hit with 10 throws?
Oh, that's fine.
That's right.
It's better to have a different player.
Why?
If it's the same player, it's not good.
It's better to have a different player.
You should be a professional player.
I'll be a match player.
You're underestimating me.
I'm a professional player.
You're fast.
I'm not fast.
I don't think so.
I'm a professional player.
It's totally different.
What are you thinking?
A professional player?
Of course.
Ega.
Sure.
Isn't it?
Yes.
It's not that bad.
How many kilos does it throw?
About 100 kilos.
You can't throw it as you want.
That's right.
Yes.
Well, you know, you know, you know.
What?
What is it?
You don't have any HENKA-kyu?
What is that?
If you don't get straight, curve and shoot in 10-kyu, what will you be?
That's...
If you throw only big, weird balls only in my time, what will you do?
In your time, straight, boom...
So, you can decide how many-kyu each.
How many-kyu for HENKA-kyu.
That's right.
Oh, is that so?
Yes.
Is that so?
No, no, no.
If you throw big, weird balls only in my time, what will you be?
What is that?
What?
It's for curve.
Well, let's do it.
In the near future.
Oh, in the near future?
Then, let's play a punishment game.
I see.
Let's do it.
What kind of punishment game?
What?
Then, let's go to a human-like place.
Let's do it.
You said you don't want to do it in the past, so let's stop it.
I'll replace this tooth and this tooth.
Why do you have to replace this tooth?
Hey, why do you have to pull out the tooth in the punishment game?
I'll give you my tooth.
I don't need it.
I don't need it either.
You have teeth, but I don't have teeth.
I don't need it.
What are you talking about?
Well, you can think about it gradually.
What?
Gradually.
I see.
I'll do it.
The game will be decided by that.
Then, you can think about what to do.
The game will be decided by that, right?
What?
You said it.
Why?
You have a strange confidence.
I don't have confidence.
You have confidence that you can beat me in sports.
What?
Did you just say yes?
Yes.
I see.
Do you think you can beat me in sports?
You said it.
You underestimated me.
You should play a game instead of batting.
Don't say nice things.
What?
Your team and my team.
But you have to match with 8 players.
There are 16 players.
I don't care.
Do you think so?
Yes.
That's interesting.
Do you think so?
What?
I don't care about the game.
If I lose, I can do it alone.
But if there is something that the whole team can do,
we can accept the game.
Then, the whole team will be desperate.
If I lose, they will think I'm kidding.
The young people behind.
Right?
Let's do it together.
OK.
Let's do it.
In a game.
What if I lose?
That's not a problem.
I've always wanted to try it.
Do you want to try it?
Even if you ask me to try it,
I can't say yes.
I'll do it with saran wrap.
Do you want to try it?
If you lose,
don't tell the players.
Idiot.
I can't do that.
What will happen if you try it?
What if there is a big electronic game?
It's like heating meat.
It's like Sinatto.
My body is...
Stop it.
Let's do it.
Good evening.
You have long legs.
I don't have long legs.
You're still the same.
What's your name?
I'm Emiko Tanada.
How old are you?
I'm 19 years old.
19 years old.
Look at her.
It's me.
Look.
It's you.
It's amazing.
You have long legs.
I don't have long legs.
You're right.
Do you have long legs?
I don't have long legs.
What's wrong with you?
I think you're drunk.
Thank you very much.
It's amazing.
At the end of last year, Naoko Nozawa appeared on a radio program.
They talked about downtown.
Nozawa said,
Hama-chan, you look like Fumiya sometimes.
He was happy.
Listen.
Fumiya said,
I think I look like him.
He said something very happy to Hama-chan.
How was it?
Hama-chan was happy.
What's that voice?
I think I look like him.
Really?
You really look like him.
I feel sorry for him.
When he wears a hat like this,
he really looks like him.
So,
when Fumiya-san asks him what he looks like,
Nozawa-san said,
He looks like a lolicon.
He said,
He looks like a middle school student.
A lolicon or a lolicon?
Which one do you like?
I like both.
I like boys who are in the second grade of elementary school.
Don't say such a bad thing.
You don't believe in anything.
I don't believe in anything.
How can you say that I look like a lolicon?
Good evening.
I also look like Hama-chan.
Have you ever heard of me?
When I eat a sweet potato like Ritomazu Shikenshi,
it reacts immediately.
But I don't like it.
You are the worst.
When I write something like this,
I get angry again.
Who made you laugh?
Are you sick?
You are the worst.
My friend called me a lolicon.
Just like that?
I think so.
But I get angry again.
So I put a whistle on my butt.
A lolicon?
Good evening.
Let's play baseball.
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
I didn't intend to do that at all.
I just wanted to say that I'm good at baseball.
That's what happened.
But it's okay.
It's not funny.
Let's do it.
So next week,
let's play a draft.
Let's decide who will play with whom.
This is a big game.
The losing team will be punished.
So everyone watching TV,
let's think about a punishment game that 9 people can do.
It's a big game.
Please refer to it.
I'm angry.
I'm 20 years old.
I'll tear his face off.
50 thousand yen.
And a button.
That was a fart.
That's great.
Anyway, please send it.
And the assistant.
The mother.
All the assistants.
They're here.
That's it.
We're going to play a draft game.
See you next week.
I want to cut his reach if I need to be