Jiraiya!
Matsu!
Ichira!
Let's fight!
We are still beginners.
It's almost done.
I'm telling you to do your best, but you can't sell it to an entertainer.
You can't sell it.
That's right.
Mr. Akashiya, Mr. Akashiya.
Last year, he earned 300 million yen a year.
That's amazing.
Mr. Katsura earned 100 million yen a year.
Mr. Okue.
Last year's annual income was 50 pesos.
50 pesos?
That's Mexican currency.
Sorry, sorry.
No, no, no.
I think the entertainer can't sell it.
No matter what you say, the car he's driving is amazing.
It's amazing if it sells.
Oh, I see.
Do you know what Mr. Masao Sen is driving?
Rolls Royce.
Wow, this is amazing.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Do you know what Mr. Katsura is driving?
Ferrari.
Supercar.
You can't be surprised by that.
Mr. Botan of Chaos Botan.
The car you're driving is a fire truck.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
The air conditioner is on.
It's hot, hot, hot, hot, hot.
Hey, what's wrong with you today?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't be angry with me.
If I sell it, don't take it.
You're right.
After all, if you sell it.
What do you want to do?
I'm good at singing, so I want to release a record.
You're good at singing?
Can you sing?
I can sing, leave it to me.
What's your favorite number 18?
Mr. Nakajou's lie.
Then let's have the guests listen to it today.
Please listen to it.
Then, Hama-chan.
I'll play the accompaniment.
We'll play the accompaniment.
Please go to the back and get ready.
Thank you for waiting.
Jimmy Onishi will sing.
Mr. Nakajou's lie.
Jimmy Onishi's lie.
Where did you come in from?
What?
What did you say?
Where did you come in from?
It was a little hard to understand.
I don't understand.
I was confused because I did it alone.
I'll do it alone next time.
He's the only one who can dance.
I'll leave it to you.
Jimmy Onishi's lie.
It's me.
How can you sing?
How many times do I have to tell you?
I thought you were a singer and a singer-songwriter.
I'm sorry.
Let's get it right.
It won't work if we do more.
I'll do my best next time.
Let's get it right.
I'll show you next time.
眞
Jimmy Onishi's lie.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Happy birthday to you, happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday to Hitoshi.
Well, it's every year.
Thank you very much.
Well, I've been doing a lot of songs.
Compared to CX, it's pretty good.
It's pretty good.
Well, it's every year.
Can you say something?
Yes.
Well, it's the second time.
I don't have anything to say.
Thank you very much.
Well, it's getting cooler.
I have to work a little harder.
What's with your attitude?
What?
I hit my ass.
You hit your ass.
I'll do it a little more.
You're going to shave your beard.
Why do you shave your beard?
I can't help it if I don't shave my beard.
If you have time before the show, you can do that.
You can't decide the turn when you come out.
I'm 29 years old.
You're already old.
I don't know how long you've been doing this.
I've come to a difficult place.
Why?
I'll be 32 years old in two or three years.
Don't you think it's a little too much?
Is that so?
It's a little too much.
I'm glad you quit school at that time.
That's the right answer.
I think that's the right answer.
You're a ninja.
I'm not a ninja.
You're not.
You're a ninja.
You're still alive.
I'm flying.
I'm a ninja.
Ninjas don't show their faces.
You're showing your face.
It's hard, isn't it?
What do you call this?
Snap.
This is still the city.
I know.
Is that so?
Why do you keep pushing your mouth?
You're dirty.
There's a demon with a P, right?
If you move your mouth, you can see what it looks like.
I was told clearly.
That idiot.
I told you.
You were telling someone on TV today.
I wasn't telling anyone.
You were telling someone.
Don't say that.
I've never changed.
I'm not resting.
What are you going to do with me?
Did you run away when you woke up that morning?
I think about it when I'm moving.
Why?
For example, when I'm on TV.
When I was in Osaka.
I'm running all the time.
I suddenly think.
Where am I going?
At 3 o'clock.
Why?
Why do you do that?
What?
I saw your reaction in Kobe.
I can't go because I'm resting.
I have no choice but to run away.
I've been marked.
Marked?
My chief manager, Hiroshi Ozaki.
He said he wanted to rest.
I don't know if he went to Okayama or somewhere else.
I went to buy a cigarette.
Where are you going?
I'm going to buy a cigarette.
Don't sweat.
I'm in the same state.
That's good.
Everyone is fooling around.
Who are you talking about?
Him? Her?
No, no, no.
It's amazing.
I don't work.
Who?
No, no, no.
You're going somewhere.
I'm going to Canada.
I'm the most angry.
What?
Who?
Why?
I'm tired.
I can't sleep for a week or two.
I'm just asking for a break.
No, no, no.
I'm serious.
How many weeks is that period?
Why don't you rest?
You're doing a show on vacation.
When I see him, I'm sure he's doing a ballpoint pen like this.
That's when you're listening to people.
I'm talking to you.
That's like us.
That's hard.
They're always like this.
Don't talk about peace.
No, no, no.
It's hard.
I had to do something.
I have to find a healthier way.
A healthier way?
It's easy, isn't it?
We talk a lot like this.
I'm sure I'll have a stomachache when I get home.
It's not easy.
I have a bad throat.
How much do you talk in this hour?
When I went to the doctor, I was told that I had a weird migraine.
Migraine is twice as much as a person.
Why don't you cut it?
If you cut it, it's going to be a big deal.
How is it going to be a big deal?
If you cut it, you'll get a lot of heat.
This is one of the factors.
Is that so?
If you become an adult and cut a ballpoint pen, you'll get more than 40 degrees of heat.
That's right.
And when you beat that 40-degree heat, you'll never have to worry about a ballpoint pen again.
But the problem is when you lose.
What if I lose?
It's going to be a big deal.
So what's going to happen?
The 40-degree heat won't go down for a week or two.
What if it doesn't go down?
It's going to be a big deal.
So what's going to happen?
I know it's going to be a big deal, so what's going to happen?
The stars are beautiful.
What are you talking about?
You know what?
Crash!
Really?
And the other thing is...
You'll become a seedless bomber.
If you don't become a seedless, you'll become a bomber.
Explain that to me.
No, I'm sorry.
Seedless bomber.
What's a bomber?
Are you serious?
If you become an otaku, you'll become a seedless bomber.
You can't call me a bomber.
Are you serious?
If you become an otaku, you'll become a seedless bomber.
It's the same as that.
That's right.
You'll evaporate.
Evaporate?
That's right.
You'll evaporate.
The heat will go up.
Evaporate?
No, really.
What?
I'm serious.
You'll disappear.
That's a seedless.
What?
This is the most troublesome thing.
This is what I'm most afraid of.
That's why I don't do it.
You'll become a seedless bomber.
I thought it was different.
That's the most troublesome thing.
That's right.
This is...
You'll become an old man.
But I don't like it.
You won't be able to use it anymore.
No, no, no.
I want to be a seedless bomber for the rest of my life.
That's your age and physical strength.
If you keep doing that, you won't become a seedless bomber.
I'll definitely keep it.
I'm still a little worried that I won't be able to do it.
Is that so?
You won't be able to do it?
I won't.
You're really something.
You won't be able to do it.
Or maybe it's because your opponent is a man.
Why?
Don't say scary things!
You!
Really...
It's nothing.
You know, recently...
What?
It's getting cooler.
It's getting easier to live.
It's easier to live.
But you know, you keep saying that there's not enough water.
Yes, yes, yes.
How about this lack of water?
How about it?
You say that once every few years.
But I hear that when you use water in a rough way, it causes an air-raid.
You keep saying that there's not enough water.
Don't waste it.
Even when you appear on TV, there are idiots who call you.
If you say things like that, I'm going to call the police.
There are a lot of people who watch TV wondering if there's anything they can do.
That's why you keep saying things like that.
Why do you keep saying things like that?
If you abuse animals, you get a lot of calls.
But why don't you use monkeys?
You're forcing yourself to use them.
But I don't take care of them properly.
There's that guy.
He's a terrible guy.
He has a big mouth like a dragon.
He's got a nice voice.
That's why you're scaring me.
He smiles a lot when he's on television.
If he says things though about a lion, it's a mess.
That's why it's scary.
踩ろョネOut of the lion's mouth fixed.
jinX
You'll see later.
Your words are more annoying than your face!
Really!
In your mouth, you're so stubborn!
I'm so stubborn!
You know it!
You're so stubborn!
Don't cry!
I'll hold you!
What a quiet girl!
Idiot!
Really!
It's his fault!
What?
It's not like that!
Gah!
She scratches and goes gah!
She goes gah!
And I'm sitting on the floor, she goes gah!
Gah!
And she goes gah!
And I'm on the floor, she goes gah!
So she can't run away?
She smacks my face, she goes gah!
And she goes like this.
It really scared me.
When you say that,
I dyed my hair with dye.
I dyed my hair with dye!
I dyed it with dye!
With a string!
So that I wouldn't run away!
So that you wouldn't run away!
Don't do it together, Salto!
In my room, there's a French doll.
Oh, that's good.
It's not such a silly letter.
Are you bragging?
No, I'm not.
There's a French doll.
About two weeks ago, it wasn't a big deal.
But about three or four days ago,
when I went into my bed, the French doll moved.
When I looked at it, there was blood coming out of my head.
My hair was a little wet.
Stop it!
Isn't that just your way of saying things?
There's a ghost in my room.
What?
That's what I said.
That's not good.
It's not good?
It was written by someone I couldn't trust.
Really?
But even if I was sleeping alone,
I still couldn't see the doll blood.
Yeah.
You're scary!
Even if there's a doll,
what kind of doll do you have in your room?
What?
Do you have a doll in your room?
What are you doing?
It's not a doll.
It's something that swells.
Stop it!
Everyone's scared of that.
I'm not scared.
I'm not scared at all.
No.
There's something like a dog's fur coat.
Everyone's scared of that.
Don't you feel like you're going to move?
I don't think so.
What are you going to do at home?
Before you go to bed,
you suddenly go like this.
I don't think I can do that.
I was going to go to bed,
but I happened to see a doll.
Thank you for your hard work.
Are you scared?
What are you going to do if you're told that?
You can't tell anyone.
You're a hard person.
If you tell anyone, they'll think you're stupid.
I'm scared.
What are you talking about?
Really.
Do you want me to bring this French doll?
Bring it home.
What?
Why?
Don't say it.
I'm telling you I'm scared.
I've been telling you I'm scared all this time.
You don't believe me, do you?
Bring this French doll home.
Go to bed.
What?
You're scared, aren't you?
I'm scared?
That's not true.
Try it.
What?
But there's one thing I can say for sure.
This is a French doll.
What's so funny?
I often see Mr. Muzugoro's face on TV.
I see him licking Mr. Muzugoro's face without hesitation.
Why is that?
I'm scared.
I see.
But that's what everyone thinks.
If there's a chance like that,
animals will talk to dogs.
If you give a microphone to an animal from the Muzugoro Kingdom, they'll talk to you.
If you say, come here, they'll say, come here.
They'll call you again.
Please forgive me.
Don't laugh.