Today I came to a great place.
I'll go around from a great place.
Today I came to Jujyo station.
Behind that is Jujyo station.
Do you know that these two stations are in Saitama?
I see.
Everyone's cheeks are red.
Mr. Komewarashi.
I can laugh.
No, it's not.
It's good.
It's not good.
It's true.
It's not a joke.
I'll bring this.
It's true.
What is it?
Let's have a talk.
Please.
If you're buying rice,
Kunimatsu.
What?
Cut it out.
We're at Jujyo today.
Shinohara Engeijo.
The theater of Mr. Komewarashi was here a while ago.
The playground.
In fact, there are still people who are acting here all the time, but they can't go out for us now.
Because they are staying here.
Is that so?
I'm really sorry.
Well, let's do it here all year round.
What are you talking about?
There is no place to stay.
This is great, isn't it?
Great.
This is the most amazing thing I've ever seen.
Let's do it in front of the audience while sitting on the tatami mat.
I think it's the first time.
Let's go to the dressing room.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to wear it.
This program is a product of Toyo.
Ooyama International Product
Sponsored by Sanraku
This is the eighth time today.
Today is a great day.
You guys are laughing a lot.
You laugh in the theater before you see the story.
Today is worth working hard.
If you work hard, I think you'll get a twist.
I think you'll get a twist.
That's great.
Aren't you a little tired?
I don't know if I'm a little tired.
The atmosphere of the atmosphere is not enough.
But if you gather like this, there are people who have bad feet.
You have to be careful.
Today is the eighth time.
I've done it eight times.
I've already stopped doing it last week.
I've already stopped doing it.
I said I'd do it again on the sixth time.
But when I think about it, there's no joke.
I've already stopped doing it.
I'll do my best today.
I don't know what to do next week.
I've been to Tokyo and Osaka.
Osaka's power is still not enough for Tokyo people.
Osaka's fans are amazing.
I'm a little out of it.
So we're in Tokyo now.
I think I ran away from Osaka's fans.
I'm scared.
If I'm not good, I'll be in trouble.
I've been a little out of it.
Especially when I first started, I didn't know what to do.
You too, Mr. Rotarin.
The phone was terrible.
It was terrible.
I got a phone call at 3 o'clock in the morning.
I picked it up and saw a pipe organ on the other end of the phone.
I was surprised.
The phone was real.
I'm sure it was a rich girl.
I was surprised.
I bet you're playing it in a big house.
When I hung up the phone, I thought it was out.
But I didn't know it was playing.
I was surprised. I thought he was a death-ler.
You idiot.
Really.
He's a death-ler.
It was disgusting.
I was wondering what would come next.
I called him again.
It was even more disgusting.
What?
He was reading the holy book.
In the middle of the night?
Yes, he was reading the holy book.
It was disgusting, but I wanted to ask him.
But if I asked him, he would hit me with a bat.
What?
It doesn't matter.
I closed my eyes and asked him.
It was disgusting.
He was very serious.
I didn't mean to call him.
I asked my friend if he was serious.
I wanted to confirm it.
You didn't confirm it yet.
Yes.
I wanted to confirm it.
He said his name was good.
I asked him if he was a fan of Yamada.
If he was a fan of him.
I asked him if he was a fan of him.
He said no.
I asked him who he was.
I didn't know who he was.
I asked him if he was a fan of Yoko.
I wanted to confirm it.
He said he was a fan of Harada.
I see.
He was like this.
Wait.
You said it before, didn't you?
He said he was a fan of Harada.
I asked him what he was.
I was surprised.
I thought it was not true, so I asked him if he was a fan of Harada.
He said he was a fan of Yoko.
I asked him who he was.
He said he was a fan of him.
He said he was a fan of Yoko.
He said Yoko-san, but what you said was Yoko.
I changed my phone number.
What I did next was, I sold telephones.
You didn't have a phone number to contact.
On the contrary, you knew the address, so you sold telephones.
I sold telephones.
If I didn't have a phone number, I came to the telecommunications office.
I said that I received a message, and I changed it.
You received a telecommunications message.
Yes, so please call me when you come back.
I received a message.
I came back.
I left it there, so I called the telecommunications office.
Hello, I received a telecommunications message.
Oh, are you Matsumoto-san?
Yes, I will read it, so please wait a moment.
He is about 50 years old.
I waited a moment, and I came back.
Yes, I will read it now.
I love Matcha.
Ufufufu.
I read it.
Such a middle-aged man says,
I love Matcha.
Ufufufu.
I'll send it to you.
No, no, no.
And the one who takes things.
This is the worst.
It's called business in Tokyo.
We call it Yogyo.
Yes, yes.
We go to the countryside, right?
For example, we go to supermarkets like Daiei.
Yes, yes.
And we play games and go home in front of everyone.
If that happens, there will be people who are still standing.
We come to the station home, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
When we go home, we steal things that people are wearing.
Yes, yes.
For example, if you wear sunglasses on your chest,
we steal it.
Wow!
You are a thief.
Yes, I am.
And the one who takes things.
If you lose to a crowd,
you try to break your thumb.
What are you doing?
What do you mean by that?
What are you talking about?
When I was on TV,
you said,
I had a fracture.
I'm glad you said that.
I was there.
I don't want you to do that.
Last year, when I went to Himeji,
I took a new pair of sunglasses.
Yes, you took a new pair of sunglasses.
You said, this is only Kota.
Yes, I said that.
I took a new pair of sunglasses and ran away.
Normally, I would give up.
But they were expensive sunglasses.
I said, wait a minute.
I was embarrassed.
I took a new pair of sunglasses and ran away.
You are lying.
No, I'm serious.
You stopped like this.
Yes.
You said, this is only Kota.
I said, wait a minute.
You said, Mr. Balma fell.
There are such things.
Yes.
There are many people in Osaka.
I came to Tokyo.
When I see people in Tokyo,
they have a great sense of fashion.
They are different from us.
It's great.
Boys are thinking about fashion.
Yes.
They are fashionable.
When I was a student,
there were only three patterns.
There are three patterns of clothes.
Yes.
IB, Yankee, and Saffron.
There were only three.
I had to choose one.
But it was difficult at that time.
Yes.
I had to choose IB.
If you were in the middle, it would be cool.
Yes.
You could be looked down on.
I had to choose IB.
There was no such a time.
There was no such things as food.
No other things.
I had to mix home made ¡¬.
It was IB.
¿¬
It seems that the things we eat are массive.
I don't know why.
What?
It were not all IB.
I have to
Why are you eating it when it's cold?
You're eating it from the top to the bottom with the I.B.
That's not good!
That's not good, I.B. eating it from the bottom to the top!
It's delicious!
That's not good.
What do you drink?
What do you eat with I.B.?
Do you eat it from the bottom to the top?
I.B. eats popcorn.
You can't decide that!
What's popcorn?
What do you drink with I.B.?
You can't decide that!
Why do you drink cola?
Surfer is difficult.
What's difficult about surfer?
I don't know what to eat.
Surfer is amazing.
You look healthy.
You don't get sunburned.
If you have a weak body, you look cool when you're on the wave.
I'm working out.
I don't have thick arms.
I have muscular legs.
Muscular legs?
What are muscular legs?
When you see universities, you see catfish-like feet.
You see catfish-like feet.
I've heard this.
Catfish-like feet!
I have 컨tacted feet with catfish-like feet.
What are you talking about?
You're the one who said it!
You're the one who said it in the live stream!
You're an amazing guy!
You can't say it one by one, right?
You're like Kamoshika's foot!
I'm like a lizard in front of the town.
If you say that, I'm like a lizard's face.
You can't say that from here!
You can't say that one by one!
No one says Kamoshika's face from here!
You can't say that one by one.
Then what do you eat?
What do you eat?
Sea food.
Are you stupid?
What's sea food?
There's a lot of things like Korot.
Who doesn't know?
You don't know Korot, right?
It's the oil of a whale.
The top is black and the bottom is white.
It's like a sponge, don't you know?
You don't have to eat it.
What do you drink?
What do you drink on the surfboard?
Drink sea food.
It's called seawater.
What do you drink on the surfboard?
The most difficult thing is to be a Yankee.
Everything is difficult to be a Yankee.
You have to be a Yankee around you.
You have to be a Yankee from your family.
It's not good to be a Yankee.
You're usually alone with your family.
Why is your family like this?
My mother was a Yankee.
My mother was different from a Yankee.
She was short-tempered.
She was a Yankee.
I'm sorry.
Your mother was short-tempered.
She was a green aunt.
Her father was a green uncle.
I was a Yankee in elementary school.
I went to my mother after my father passed away.
I was scolded by my father.
My mother said,
This is strange.
Why is my mother a Yankee?
My mother was a Yankee.
I was scolded by my father.
My father was a kind man.
He was a Yankee.
My mother was a green aunt.
She was short-tempered.
My mother was a green uncle.
My mother was a green aunt.
She was short-tempered.
She was a green aunt.
What is your name?
Let me tell you something.
I cut my hair at first.
Then my bangs fall down.
My bangs fall down.
It's annoying.
It's a little annoying.
Then my bangs fall down.
I went to the hospital.
I became a sports person.
How long have you been doing this?
About 10 minutes.
You've been doing this for about 10 minutes?
What is this?
The fan letters that you get from fans in Osaka and Tokyo are cold.
Really?
Yes, yes, yes.
How is it?
The fan letters from fans in Osaka, for example, if you write a phone number,
they write, it's okay to call, so please do it.
In Tokyo, they write a phone number and say, you can do it.
That's great.
It's a bit of a high-profile type of fan letter.
Let's introduce the fan letters today.
Is there anyone here who has been in a relationship with Ashii-san?
Yes.
You're such an honor student.
Oh, you've been in a relationship?
Oh, is that so?
Are you studying or not?
Everyone knows that you have a girlfriend.
Oh, is that so?
You have a girlfriend, right?
I don't have one.
It was taken, but it doesn't matter.
Is there anyone in Mach-chan?
This is really...
How can I get a girlfriend?
I want a girlfriend.
Really.
That's great.
No, no, no.
What's great?
Really.
Really?
I don't have anything to say anymore.
I really want a girlfriend.
Why don't you have one?
I wonder why.
Huh?
After all...
I don't have a chance to know.
So I'm thinking of sleeping with her next time.
Oh, that's...
I'm thinking of sleeping with her next time.
I'm having a lonely night.
I heard from you.
Normally, when you go to a disco, you go dancing, right?
I don't dance well, so I can't go.
Well, for the time being, I'm dancing like this.
Can I really say that?
No one dances like this.
Well, well.
I'm dancing like this.
I usually dance.
No.
I'm sitting down.
I go back to the back.
I smoke while wearing glasses.
Really?
I'm Kinji Sawada.
I'm a back-up dancer.
Everyone is dancing in the middle.
I smoke while dancing.
I go to this place where I'm dancing.
And if I don't like it, I go to the next place.
Like this.
What?
Such a guy.
From bottom to top.
I never dance like this.
I don't like it.
I want to know человек abomen.
Let me teach you Osaka dialect.
Yes, please.
Everyone did it.
A person from Tokyo.
You put some words we use in our speech,
for example,
if you watch TV drama,
there are a lot of things we don't understand.
For example,
Torihada.
You have a sword in your hand!
What's so funny about Torihada?
Torihada, eh?
Osaka Torihada is...
Torihada...
I'll say it, but...
Don't say it too much.
Osaka is...
Sabuibo.
This is...
That's why...
Don't say zoku zoku zoku!
For example, if an old man touches you, you say zoku zoku zoku, right?
You say something like Sabu, right?
And then you say something like Sabuibo.
Just like that!
Sabuibo.
I don't say this.
Also, you see...
Osaka's Marudachi is...
That's it.
If a child goes waaaaah!
I don't know what to say about this, but...
You say, I-chibirina!
I-chibiru.
I-chibirina.
You say, I-chibirina.
If you're in the house, you say, I-chibirina!
I-chibirina, I-chibirina!
Tokyo's mothers are kind, right?
You say, I-chibirina.
Osaka is different, right?
Osaka is...
You say, I-chibirina!
You can't say it right away.
If you're angry, you go waaaaah!
You say, I-chibirina!
No, seriously.
Seriously, right?
You put out your hand, too.
You say, I-chibirina!
Osaka's mothers are easy to get excited.
Osaka's people.
You can't tell the difference on the way.
If you do that, I-chibirina!
Osaka's mothers are easy to get excited.
You can't tell the difference on the way.
If you're angry, you go, I-chibirina!
I-chibirina!
You say, I-chibirina.
You touch it, I-chibirina.
Osaka's mothers are easy to get excited.
If you're angry, you go, I-chibirina!
Also, what Matsumoto-kun often says is about poop.
It's in the middle of the night, so it's fine.
I didn't know about this at all.
I thought it would work here, too.
Is poop poop here?
Well, poop is poop.
You can't call it that.
No, it's different.
Osaka is, you know, baba.
Yes, yes, yes.
I was a kid before, and when I said baba, it didn't work.
Oh, I see, I see, I see.
It's called baba.
There's something called baba, right?
That's the name.
That's poop.
Osaka says baba, so I say, hello, I'm baba.
It's true.
No, seriously.
It's not that strange now, but when we were kids, we used to say giant baba.
It's a bit of a joke, though.
It's a bit of a joke, but it's true.
Giant baba, you know?
Everyone is holding their asses.
That's how it is.
Don't you have to sing together today?
One last word.
If you do that, again.
Let's drink and say goodbye.
Do you understand?
If you don't say yes, I won't be able to hide it.
I'll leave it to you.
Do you understand?
Do it like this.
I'm serious.
Osaka is serious.
If you do that, again.
Now, let's say goodbye.
Let's go.
One, two.
It's over.
To be honest, I wasn't sure if it was a good idea.
It was a good idea.
I've only done it once or twice.
I'm addicted to it.
It was about six years ago.
I don't know how the audience will react to this show.
I'm scared.
What will happen next week?
What are you going to do next week?
What?
You're going to say that right before the show.
I have six regular shows in Osaka.
It's the most painful show.
Even though the staff is free.
The staff says, today's assistant is cute.
When people are holding their heads.
They say, he was cute before he left.
I didn't see it.
I didn't have the courage.
I'm happy.
But it's been a while.
It's been a while.
Let's do our best for now.
Good-bye for now.
This program is brought to you by Toyo Suisan.
Oyama International University.
This program was brought to you by Toyo Suisan.