This is the Gaki no Tsukai Arai-hen!
The Gaki no Tsukai Arai-hen has reached 1 million yen!
That's great!
First of all, please explain.
This is...
This is the wig I've been wearing for the past 3 years.
You...
You've been wearing a wig like this for the past 3 years?
I've been wearing this for the past 3 years.
This is the one I've been using often.
Isn't there anyone who has grown fond of this?
Kondo Masao.
Kondo Masao, right?
Well, it's a certain pattern.
This is Hagimoto-san.
It's Kin-chan?
This is a...
You want to do a parody of that show itself?
Yes, yes, yes.
So, we'll do the special points.
So, there's this?
Yes, there's this.
Well, I'll wear this.
I'll wear this and go inside.
I'll go up like this.
So, you're wearing this?
Yes.
So, 15 points or more is a pass?
Yes, it's a pass.
For example, if I stop at the bottom of 15 points,
I'll make a sound like this.
So, I'll stop at the bottom of 15 points.
So, you won't stop?
I'll stop.
So, I'll make a sound like this.
What is this costume? I don't like it at all.
It's slippery, it's slippery.
The audience is making noise.
What is this, what is this?
If I go up to here, you have to do a cartwheel.
You're doing a cartwheel.
I'm doing a cartwheel.
I don't like this costume at all.
I hope I can get out of here.
Everyone is doing this.
You'll go around in a cartwheel.
When you come out,
I'll wear this wig,
and put on makeup,
and put on these clothes,
and I'll be wearing this mic,
and my eyes will be drooping,
and I'll come out like a goldfish.
I'll be like, I'm so glad.
And I'll come out like this.
I'll say, I want to go higher.
I want to go higher.
And then you'll be like...
Booboo booboo booboo booboo
Congratulations!
It's perfect.
You see, there's a camera right next to it.
I can use this to go up to the top.
Oh, I see.
Like this?
Yes. I can use this to go up to the top.
I can use this to go up to the top.
That's right.
Like this?
This is good.
So I'm wearing a suit like this.
Yes.
And I'm like,
I'm glad.
Yes.
I'm going to close my eyes.
I can do it.
I'm confident I'll get a million yen if I pass the audition.
Really?
The judges might not even know I'm Nozawa.
I heard you were like that before.
Right?
In that case, I'll say,
I'll say,
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ladies and gentlemen,
I really don't believe that.
Yes, that's true.
Yes, yes, yes.
Sorry to keep you waiting for so long.
It can't be helped.
It's not anyone's fault.
It's all Nikko's fault.
Yeah!
Really.
I waited for an hour and a half.
When I was on the plane at 3 o'clock, I was already on time.
It was like, bing, bong, bong, bong.
At the airport.
The 3 o'clock flight to Tokyo is at 4 o'clock.
You're lying.
It's like you're stuttering.
I'm not stuttering.
I was hungry.
Yeah.
In the end, I was late for an hour.
I waited for another 30 minutes.
I was late for an hour and a half.
When you get on the plane, you'll be late again, right?
That's right.
When I got on the plane, I got on the plane.
It was annoying again.
When I finally got on the plane, I was surrounded by kids.
Front, back, and side. It was annoying.
I was hungry.
I can't forgive kids.
Why?
It was annoying.
I couldn't help it.
You were happy.
Yeah.
You couldn't help it.
It was annoying on the side.
But it was annoying on the front, back, left, and right.
I couldn't help it.
On the seat?
Yeah.
I was surrounded by kids.
You were surrounded by kids.
Yeah.
I was surrounded by kids.
The old man behind me was angry because of the pig.
It was a serious situation.
It was hard for an hour.
Yeah.
It was a serious situation.
It was hard for an hour.
These days, parents don't care about their kids.
I see.
When I was a kid, my father was very strict.
He told me that I would lose if I played with him.
He told you that you couldn't win.
These days, parents don't care about their kids.
They tell me not to say things I don't want to say.
My father is laughing.
I see.
There was a shelf in front of me.
There was a juice.
He said, I'm thirsty. Take it.
I found it.
I was surprised.
What is that?
That kid was very mean.
If my father wasn't there, I would have dropped him.
That's right.
Really.
I whispered to him.
I said, ready, set, go.
It's hard to forgive.
These days, kids have a lot of money.
Kids have a lot of fashion.
That's right.
It's hard to forgive.
My father's watch.
The other day, he was like that.
Jiro.
He was on a TV show.
There was a pig boy.
He was in elementary school.
He lost weight by 18kg.
That's right.
Really?
He put a watch on him.
He was trying to be a diver.
It was hard.
Time doesn't matter to you.
No, no.
What is this?
That's right.
Time doesn't matter to you.
Really.
I said this when I was a kid.
Kids are young when they grow up.
How much did it cost us to grow up?
That's right.
Jiro.
Kids these days are growing up.
They are young.
They are amazing.
They are the president.
They are like a president.
The other day, he was really lazy.
He was like this.
He put a watch on him.
Sometimes, he was like this.
He was like a brother and a sister.
His little sister was so lazy.
So he put it on here instead of here.
That's annoying.
It's annoying to put it on here.
I look at adults.
Like this.
I don't think about that.
I was on a plane.
I had a question.
It's been a while since you've been on a plane.
Yeah.
There's a reclining.
You have to lower it.
When you land, you have to raise it.
Why do you do that?
It's dangerous.
Why is it dangerous?
It's like this.
What's dangerous about it?
What?
What if you get shocked?
If I get shocked,
I don't know if it's better or worse.
Why do you do that?
It's dangerous if you're about to be blown away.
Why do you smoke when you land?
You don't know that either, do you?
Why do you do that?
Either way,
when you fall, you get a little dizzy.
It doesn't matter if you smoke.
When you get dizzy, you fall.
You get a little dizzy.
It's like this.
When you smoke, you fall.
You hit the old man in the back.
The old man is on the back.
What are you doing?
It's long.
You get a little dizzy.
That's how it goes.
Why do you like Katsura?
Everyone in the world says that.
I can't help it.
I'm not saying anything.
But there are a lot of strange things.
Why?
Two people riding a bicycle.
It's been stopped a lot, hasn't it?
Why not?
Someone answer me.
You don't know, do you?
Well, if you say that,
it's because it's dangerous.
It's easy to clean up.
If that's the case,
it's more dangerous to ride two people in a single car.
You can wear a helmet over there.
Two people riding a bicycle with a helmet on.
But you're going to a country school.
You're wearing a helmet.
You can't ride two people in a single car.
That's what I'm saying.
That's why.
You can wear a helmet and ride a bicycle.
You can't ride two people in a single car with a helmet on.
What?
Damn it!
Then why do you ride a bicycle?
Why can't you ride two people on a bicycle?
That's what I'm saying.
That's why.
Why can't you ride two people on a bicycle?
You can't ride a bicycle.
What?
You can't ride two people in a single car.
But you can't ride a bicycle.
No matter how many times you wear a helmet.
Why?
I don't know.
By the way, you looked like a yakuza today.
Why are you saying such a bad thing?
I'm a yakuza.
I got on the plane.
I'm still moving.
I landed on the plane.
What?
I'm going to run for a while.
I have to fly.
I'm still moving.
Please wait for me at the seat belt.
I'm going to run for a while.
Excuse me.
The plane is still moving.
I'm still moving.
Please wait for me at the seat belt.
You looked like this.
What is this?
No.
I was stopped.
I was told to go.
I couldn't get out of the plane.
The seat belt was in the back.
So I went to the seat belt.
Then I got on the plane.
I couldn't make it to work.
That's not what I said.
Really?
I couldn't make it to work.
That's because I was late.
Let's go to Haragi.
Please.
Hello.
What about today?
What is that?
I don't have money.
Really?
You applied yourself, didn't you?
You didn't apply yourself.
You don't have money.
How much do you have?
22.
You smile a lot.
Why?
I don't know.
Do you have a bad head?
Don't say that.
This is against the rules.
Really?
Yes.
I only have this.
No, you can't wear this.
I'm sure of it.
If you wear this, you can't wear anything.
If you don't wear this, you can't wear anything.
This is strange.
You can't wear this.
This is not a problem.
This is...
Where are you pointing?
In the end, everyone will see this.
If you don't wear this, the shape will be the same.
No, I like the black color here.
You can see it from here.
I can't see it.
What are you talking about?
Thank you very much.
Let's introduce the postcards.
Good evening.
I heard that there is a new film crew called Black Keys in Osaka.
Is that true?
Yes.
I haven't seen it yet.
They have a bad attitude.
There are four of them.
They are all wearing black clothes.
I'm ugly.
I like that kind of person.
I used to be like that.
When I was a fairy, I liked an ugly woman.
What?
I liked an ugly woman.
I didn't like her, but I liked her.
Matsumoto-kun, Matsumoto-kun.
They always follow me.
At that time, there were only about 10 fans.
The fans gathered.
Matsumoto-kun said, but the ugly woman was a little far away.
Hitoshi.
It's really your style.
Let's go home.
Where are you going?
What do you want to do?
There is a woman who uses such a cowardly hand.
I have a request today.
I want you to give my grandfather a nickname.
My grandfather is 76 years old.
He is completely stupid.
As soon as he was stupid, he got better.
He took a dog and ran around the neighborhood.
And on the way, when there was a pole, he bit the pole and said,
I'm going to sell it.
Children in the neighborhood are called stupid in Iwasaki.
It's not funny, so please give me a good nickname.
By the way, stupid is not a joke, but a real stupid.
What kind of nickname do you have?
I can't follow such an old man.
Grandmother.
I'm old, so I can't understand it.
I'm very tall.
I'm 186 cm tall.
That's why I stand out more in school and on the train.
I'm a high school girl, so I'm fine in school.
But I'm seen a lot on the train.
It's embarrassing.
I hate it very much, but I can't do anything about it.
My grandmother in the neighborhood says,
I'm a girl and I can't marry you because I'm so tall.
How can I not stand out?
I'm 106 cm tall.
I'm the most famous person in the family.
I can't think of another nickname.
If I say that, I'll be cut off.
I'm the director's favorite.
What do you think?
I'm short.
But a girl like me is fine with a boy who is shorter than me.
I don't care if a man cares.
That's right.
There's no problem with girls.
But a girl who is taller than me is fine.
That kind of sex.
Is that so?
This is a man's desire, isn't it?
It's better than me.
Why are you always like that?
I'm glad you said yes.
But you're so simple.
What are you talking about?
I've never dated a girl taller than me.
I don't know.
Even if you say that, it's not good.
Men want to have sex with a girl taller than them.
They also want to have sex with a girl they don't like.
Do you go down?
Down and up.
It's like we're going back in time.
You...
If it's up, what are you?
What's up?
Meiji?
It's Taisho.
You're a fucking old woman.
But you have feelings.
You can say Heisei.
No.
You can think of Heisei.
But Taisho...
No, it's Taisho.
Taisho is a little...
That's right.
If it's Heisei, it's enough.
What's wrong with Heisei?
If it's Heisei, how old are you?
One year old.
You'll be okay in a dozen years.
Can you eat it?
It's yakiniku.
You'll be okay.
Yes, I can eat it.
Can you eat it?
Next...
Which one should I choose?
I have one, too.
When I went to Shinjuku the other day, I bought a down-down T-shirt for 500 yen.
500 yen?
But when I went home, it said down-down.
And below that, it said Hamada Hitoshi Matsumoto Masatoshi.
Have you ever bought a down-down T-shirt like this?
If you have, please tell me.
I'll be tricked. I have one.
A cassette.
You have it with me.
It's Kenji Sada, right?
Kenji Sada.
Kenji Sada, the best singer.
You two go buy it.
There are about 20 songs in the cassette.
If you look at it, it says,
Darling, Tokio.
Let's go to your house and listen to it together.
It's 1000 yen.
All the hit songs are in it.
It says, Kenji Sada, the best singer.
It's cheap.
I went to my house.
When I opened the cassette,
It said, I'm talking to you.
I'm talking to you.
I don't understand.
He's an old man.
He's talking to an old man.
If you look at it, it says,
Suzuki Ichiro.
Who are you?
It's true.
That was the worst.
It was the worst.
I won.
There's a trick.
Let's go to the last one.
Tokiotto.
Katsura-chan.
I've been going to the downtown every Monday since the summer vacation.
That's where I felt it.
When the fans of Hama-chan shout Hama-chan,
They shake their hands and say hello.
Mach-chan is a scoundrel.
Do you hate the fans of Mach-chan?
By the way, Nitta-san is also a scoundrel.
He's the manager.
There's a fool who's a scoundrel.
What's that like?
He's a scoundrel.
Mach-chan?
I'm not really Mach-chan.
I see.
Then who are you?
My real name is Ota Souichi.
What?
I'm not really Mach-chan.
Ota.
Ota, let's go to the next one.
Let's go to that one.
What do people call you?
What?
They call me Okkun.
I see.
I'll ask the people who are watching TV now.
Okkun?
That's right.
That's more like it.
The opening is like this.
We're going to do it like this.
I want you to see it.
If you suddenly see it, everyone will be shocked.
It's a very high probability that we'll win.
It's a strong impact.
In a sense, it's a super zone.
What are you talking about?
You don't know either.
What?
It's true.
Let's win for now.
I think it's better to think about how to use 1 million yen.
Do you use it on TV?
I used it on TV.
And the assistant.
It's really a little less now, isn't it?
That's right.
I don't think it's possible.
Really?
I think it's better to continue until now.
I haven't been recruiting recently.
I see.
I'm looking for more assistants.
Please send it to me.
Yes.
I don't have a lot of money now.
I think I can get a lot of money if I send it.
I'm looking for more assistants.
Please send it to me.
Bye bye!