June 1984, the rainy season that lasted until yesterday.
On this day, we are going to have a strange experience.
I'm bored without a job.
Yeah.
What should I do?
I can't get a job at all.
Yeah.
I don't have money.
I'm hungry.
I'm hungry when I don't have to do anything.
On the contrary.
I'm hungry when I don't have money.
I'm hungry.
Let's have lunch here.
Let's eat at my house.
Let's do that.
That's the best.
I don't need money.
I don't have money.
How much do you have?
1,000 yen.
What?
This is the last money.
Really?
Yeah.
What should I do?
I only have 1,000 yen.
You only have 1,000 yen.
This is a large bento.
If we eat together, I have two of these.
You can eat one at a time.
I can eat one at a time.
That's enough.
Is that enough?
This is a large bento.
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
This is 470 yen.
Yes.
This is 480 yen.
This is 1,000 yen.
Excuse me.
Can you microwave this for me?
I'm sorry.
The microwave is not working today.
I can't warm it up.
Where can I microwave this?
I don't know.
You always say that.
If you can't microwave it at home,
you can microwave it somewhere else.
I can't eat it.
This is a large bento.
I don't know.
Ouch.
Good morning.
What are you two doing here?
I can't microwave a bento.
I can't microwave it.
What?
It's a joke.
I want to microwave it somewhere.
Where should I microwave it?
I don't know.
Look at this.
What is this?
There's a map here.
Throw a dart.
Go where it hits.
Let's microwave it.
Okay.
Let's do that.
Here it is.
Itabashiku.
What?
I see.
This program is brought to you
by the sponsor of the program.
Looking for a place to microwave a large bento
with Yamazaki's suggestion,
they head to downtown Ichiro Itabashiku.
Itabashiku has a population of 520,000 people.
Where will they go?
Hello.
Look at this.
We came to Itabashiku.
Either way,
you have to microwave it.
Okay.
It's already rotten.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
It's a large bento.
Okay.
Let's microwave it again in Itabashiku.
Let's do that.
Okay.
Ouch.
What?
What a reaction.
I don't like it.
It's like you're lighting a cigarette.
It's cool.
Let's go.
What did you do?
What was that?
I drooled.
Okay.
Nakamaru-cho.
They are looking for otakus who are going to microwave the bento.
They are going to Nakamaru-cho in Itabashiku.
I got hit on my leg.
It hurts.
It hurts, right?
It's bleeding.
It's not bleeding.
It's like a black bug.
It's bleeding.
I have that kind of thing.
I don't have it.
The destination that Darts told us is Itabashiku Nakamaru-cho.
There are 4514 people.
Which otaku are they going to meet?
Hello.
We are here in Nakamaru-cho.
Where are we?
Number 17.
We are here.
It's getting close.
This is the last stop.
Thank you.
Where are we going?
Let's go.
We are here, right?
We are here.
It's an apartment.
Iwatani?
Iwatani apartment.
One of the houses in Nakamaru-cho is closed.
What should we do?
If we run, we will find it.
Hello.
We are here.
Thank you.
Where are we going?
They found the destination.
They visit the owner of the first floor.
Stop it.
It's scary.
But it was an apartment, so they are in a darts again.
It's an apartment again.
One house was chosen from the side of Nakamaru-cho.
I'm not good at riding a bicycle.
They are in a darts again.
We are here.
Saito.
Tetsuichiro.
This is the third time.
Will they be able to find it this time?
I wonder if Tetsuichiro is here.
Keiichiro.
Tetsuichiro.
This is Keiichiro.
That's wrong.
They found it.
Excuse me.
Hello.
I want you to clean the bento.
Is that so?
Is that okay?
You are a very honest person.
What do you mean?
This is Saito's house in Nakamaru-cho, which was chosen by a darts of 12 million people in Tokyo.
You are also beautiful.
Don't talk nonsense.
They found it.
It's hot.
Is it hot?
It's warm.
It's burnt.
Tetsuichiro.
Keiichiro.
It's very hot.
We have finished cleaning and eating.
I want to drink cold barley tea.
How about darts?
Let's do it.
Hello.
It's been two weeks since I thought about it.
Two weeks.
The players suddenly became friends.
What's the problem?
The darts are swollen.
If the darts are swollen, the heat will come out of the hole.
It's coming out.
The darts are amazing.
Don't be so desperate.
When I had a darts about 41 degrees a few years ago,
I also had a darts about 40 degrees.
Ultra 7 was flying all the time.
Are you serious?
I don't know why Ultra 7 was flying.
Because of the situation at that time.
I think it's natural.
Because the darts are more than 40 degrees.
It doesn't matter who is flying.
Even if Ultra 7 is flying, it's OK.
It's OK.
It's strange that it's OK.
It's strange.
When an adult man is flying more than 40 degrees, it's dangerous.
Is that so?
Yes.
There are no seeds.
Is that because of the heat?
Yes.
Isn't it because of the darts?
What's the problem?
If you have a darts, you'll be in trouble.
The darts are swollen.
No.
My eyes are black, so I can't draw darts on the stage.
But...
No, no, no.
What are you talking about?
You can't draw darts from the outside.
Don't draw darts from the inside.
No, no, no.
What are you talking about?
Stop it.
Don't draw darts from your heels.
It's the same for otaku.
When the temperature rises, it evaporates.
Simply put.
It seems to be in a very dangerous state.
But it's okay because two people can do it.
It's not a battle between the Japanese and the Japanese.
That's right.
The other day...
When was it?
The day before the war?
I told you that I gave power to the Iranians.
The one with the battery connected.
It's not something you can do from then on.
Why?
The car is in a very bad condition.
The power was sucked by the Iranians.
It's not like that.
When the engine starts, it goes like this.
Really.
That's because you didn't maintain it properly.
That's strange.
I did something good.
I told you to go home.
That's because you want something in return.
You shouldn't do that.
I don't want anything in return.
Wait, wait, wait.
Human beings are in return for everything.
What are you doing?
It's completely different from what you said last week.
Wait a minute.
Is there anything you don't want in return?
What do you want?
Everyone is in return for everything.
Is that so?
You want to be kind to women because you have a purpose, right?
Tell me what you want.
Wear glasses.
Let's think about it this way.
Why do you wear glasses?
Because my eyesight is bad.
Because your eyesight is bad?
My eyesight is bad, right?
Your eyesight is bad.
That's why you wear glasses.
You look better when you wear glasses.
You expect something in return.
It's normal for ordinary people to look good.
Ordinary people, right?
Yes.
It's just about wearing glasses and becoming an ordinary person, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
It's not about looking back.
Ordinary people.
It's hard to explain to you with glasses.
No, no, no.
Glasses are a little different.
It's your way of thinking now.
It wasn't glasses, was it?
How do you get in just by wearing glasses?
It's annoying.
That's a lie.
You guys try it.
What do you do when you say it to an amateur?
No.
I don't know.
It's the same with women, right?
They get married and wash dishes.
They wash dishes.
They do laundry.
Just do it normally.
That's what they say.
Right?
By doing that, they get money from their husbands.
I can't say that they get money from their husbands.
Why?
I don't know.
I don't know either.
But you don't do anything good.
I think it's strange.
Don't you think so?
Do you get paid the same amount of money as you do good things?
For example, the money you lost and the money you got.
Which one is more?
The money I lost is definitely more.
I've never done anything bad to the police.
But I've done a lot of bad things.
I see. That's what's strange.
When I was on this show the other day,
I said, this is the most effective,
and they sent me a box of salampas.
I see.
I said I didn't expect anything in return.
I said, this is the most effective.
And they sent me the next box of salampas.
I said, I didn't expect anything in return.
That's normal.
But you're doing this with two people.
What if one of them is sick?
What?
Can't you manage yourself?
If you say so.
If you don't do it right, I'm still doing it.
Did you show your strength?
I haven't shown it to anyone yet.
I'll do it like this.
There's nothing.
If I do this once, it'll be amazing.
But today...
Do it!
It's really amazing.
Do it.
Everyone will be happy.
I'll do it.
Try bending it.
It'll hurt if you do it like that.
It'll hurt.
I'm sorry.
Your bones aren't ready yet.
They are.
You'll be 31 tomorrow.
I'm ready.
What?
Not yet.
If you do that, you won't be able to show your face.
I'll do it like this.
That's fine.
I'm doing it for my partner.
I'll do it right behind you.
I'll do it.
What is this?
It's coming out.
Where?
I can't see it.
I'll stop here for today.
And this part here.
It's really like your stomach.
It's like ice cream.
It hurts.
I told you I have abs.
Why is Mr. Matsumoto's smile so cute?
When I see Mr. Matsumoto's smile...
Open it. Open it.
I want to smile with him.
Mr. Matsumoto, who made me look like this.
Please tell me the reason for his cute smile.
Actually, this is...
This is...
How should I say this?
Originally, there was a meaning to how I was raised.
Originally, there was a teaching that I shouldn't smile.
From whom?
From my father-in-law.
Isn't he your father?
I'll tell you.
I think humans have the most beautiful smiling faces.
Only humans are animals that smile.
What's that?
Is it because of your husband?
When you feed him.
You're laughing?
I'm in Kamogawa Sea World.
My husband was on TV the other day.
When I fed him, he was like this.
When I fed him, he was laughing like this.
That's definitely a lie.
It's true.
That's gross.
It's gross, but it's true.
It's true, right?
It's true.
Wait, wait, wait.
What's the next story?
In animals, only humans and a horse can smile.
I see.
A horse?
Is that a horse?
Is that a horse? I think it's because of my husband.
Because of your husband?
But I don't know if it's a horse.
It's a horse.
How do I say this?
It's like a raised horse.
It's not bad.
Let's keep it that way.
Right?
There are only two types of this.
And that smile is also a symbol of humans.
I see.
If I say something like this, you might feel uncomfortable.
To be clear, your smile is dirty.
Your painful smile is...
Don't say painful.
You say it's cute.
Right?
For me...
How many years have we been together?
It's been 13 or 14 years.
Your smile is disgusting.
So don't laugh.
Try to smile.
What does that mean?
That's how it is.
Humans don't do that.
No, no, no.
That's from the era of hunting.
Try to smile.
I've been thinking a lot lately.
I'm not good at driving.
Who?
I'm from Tokyo.
I don't know if I'm from Tokyo or not.
When I try to turn left,
I keep turning left.
Even though there are 3 or 4 lanes on the left,
there is only one lane to turn left.
This lane is like this.
Like this.
Wow.
I don't think I can do this once.
But I don't think you can fix it.
Why?
You've been like this since we came here.
No, the first lane on the left turns like this.
The second lane turns like this.
The next lane turns like this.
Like this.
Wow.
What's that wow?
It's a god's word.
It's yellow and tries to stop immediately.
Even though people in Osaka are driving,
they're like, don't turn red! Don't turn yellow!
But people in Tokyo are driving like,
won't it turn yellow?
I can understand that.
You can go like this anytime.
Even though you're going, you're pretending you don't know.
What makes me angry is that
there are cars that are going like this.
And there are cars that are parking here.
Do you know that they're trying to participate in this traffic?
If they participate, there's no movie.
Because they want to go home.
But they're going like this.
And I'm the ass.
In this traffic.
If I go, there won't be any cars for a while.
Get out of the back.
But you're in front of me!
That's true.
Why?
I want to go faster.
This is all you can do?
I can't hold it in.
You can wait in my ass.
You can go as far as you want in my ass.
You can go backwards too.
Ah, Hirakawa-san.
Forcibly...
Ah, why?
I don't know why!