The 6th Gaki no Tsukai Arai-n De Chichi-chichi Gainoujin Tsuri Senchiken!
Mr. Hatsukawa, would you like to introduce the next contestant?
What are you doing? Isn't it too early to be so impulsive?
Let's talk more slowly.
Well, I'm glad you came even in the rain.
Let's start with this person.
He has won the last two competitions with a dignified top.
He has already been a legend in the drama.
He is too busy to go to the Seikan and he doesn't have time to do the Friday.
Mr. Matsumoto!
I remember the face of the time.
If I don't get in here soon, the screen will be blown.
Because it's like a TV show.
Last year, I said I would catch all the black bass of Kawaguchi.
This year, I caught the one I caught last year.
Thank you.
By the way, he is the g Gangster Bastion Leader Hamada Matsushita!
Hello 34 years old!
аж
is the first female Fusionist.
Such a womener......
He doesn't want to lose.
Please visit BUS3!
This man is obsessed with the evil spirit of the devil.
This year, he will finally become a professional.
The father of the devil, Itoi Shigesato!
Good morning!
Today's news is...
Please hurry up and give me the microphone.
No, it's not that.
Ah, it's here.
Itoi-san, what's the weather like today?
It's the best.
Is it good?
It's like a sweet rain.
A sweet rain?
Sorry.
No, no, no.
I don't know that either.
Please give me a shot.
Congratulations!
2 years in a row, he has 3 things to be proud of.
He has a black belt in Fami and Mashimaru.
Okuda Tamiya!
I don't care about the past.
Do you have any plans today?
Today, I will get in the way of others.
That's a bad strategy.
If I do it at my own pace every year, I will be taken away.
Even in the future, you will win this year.
I will remember that.
Please do.
Right?
It's hard to get involved in the conversation.
Please do.
Please do your best.
The
In My Power
Egu-chan
Thank you.
What is the
defeat that you have not won?
What is it?
What do you think about it?
It's like the pressure of Shimano.
Sexy Monkey of Rock, bringing the guitar to the lua, has appeared!
He is the 21st member of the 3-legged Yellow Monkey, Yoshinikan!
Welcome!
Last year, the first member to appear won the award.
I think there are plenty of chances.
I don't think I'll be waiting for the camera.
I'm always around.
I'll do my best.
The last two episodes have been canceled in a row.
Will the program regular be lost this time?
Omey Yamazaki!
Yes!
That's right.
You can't just be excited.
Yes.
What?
I'm so excited.
Let's finish this quickly.
Please.
There's one more person.
He's here.
You're so good at ending.
Last time,
I was watching from the front and I thought that there was also a beginner's rack.
I said it earlier, but what I do is that I think about how close everyone is to me.
Did you hear that?
What? Yamagaki, say it!
Hey!
You are... do your best!
You bastard!
Yes, thank you!
It is the greeting of the meeting of Mr. Hanagata and Mr. Kiriwaza.
Listen carefully!
I'm going to tell you all about it.
A B-class comedian like you.
A B-class beauty like you.
And a B-class actor like you.
And a C-class copywriter.
I'm a C-class person after all.
I'm a C-class person this year too.
Every year, every year.
I'm a fish in a pond.
I don't know if it's new or not.
Hey, Mr. Horishige!
Think of a catch-coup!
I've made a short message with your hard work.
First of all, Mr. Matsumoto.
This year, you should marry that person.
Thank you very much.
I don't know what to do.
There's no one else.
Eguchi-san!
Yes, let's go.
Eguchi-san, even if you take a god, you don't take a bus.
Thank you very much.
Okuda-san!
Okuda-san, Eiji's wife is calling for her sister.
What's that?
Okuda Eiji-san?
Again, Okuda Eiji-san.
Yes.
That's all I can say.
I was not confident to sing.
This is the most difficult part.
Itoi-san,
Wadaben Guts and Yoko Nara Biji.
Thank you very much.
Sorenkan,
What?
Kengoro painted red.
Wonderful.
It's not good.
It's a good live.
Now, let's start the 3rd round of swimming competition!
Alright! Let's start!
Let's go!
Have a good day!
This is a sponsor.
In the past 5 competitions, Matsumoto won twice.
Tamada, Itoi, and Kato won once.
By the way, Okuda has been in the second place twice in a row since the first time.
He has never won a championship in a competition.
Who will win the golden trophy this time?
Hey!
Just 3 minutes before the start, Yamasaki who has never hit a single target before suddenly...
Here it comes! Here it comes!
Hey!
What?
What's that?
It's the first one!
I got the first one!
I'll get it this year.
Is it that big?
It's this one.
What's this?
But this year it's a little different.
If you get one, I'll tell you.
It's a big one.
It's small.
It's a big one?
It's coming.
What is it, Tamino?
Ah!
It's a bar!
I watch TV but I often get bar.
Again, Yamasaki-Kato's pair.
This time, Kato's hit is...
Yes!
It's not Kazuya, Kazuya.
It's not Kazuya!
This is the adult's calmness, Matsumoto Itoi's team.
Can you show us?
Excuse me.
Ah, you're here.
Before I knew it, Itoi had caught the first fish.
But when it comes to Itoi, it's quiet even if I catch it.
Is that so?
Then, this time...
Hey, hey, hey.
Oh, it's big, but it's small.
It's small, right?
There's a wheel area here.
Oh, oh, oh.
It's a little small.
It's big for me.
Oh, oh, oh.
I don't think I'll be able to fish this year.
I'll be cool.
I'm embarrassed to be so loud like Yamazaki.
Everyone's like that.
Ah, it's small.
On the other hand, there's no one fishing yet.
Hamada, Okuda, Yoshi team.
First, the yellow-faced Yoshi gets the first fish.
He got a ball.
And then, he got a big one.
Oh, no.
It's coming.
Yes!
Thank you!
Oh, no. He's so excited.
It's coming. The wave is coming.
This is how he feels.
It's so noisy.
Thank you!
And for some reason, the last of the year's Yamasaki is the best!
I caught it!
The second one!
Shut up!
Furthermore, the Okuda that was barely running away earlier...
...is also the third one!
After the rain, it seems that there are a lot of fish this time.
At the beginning of the 20th minute, 7 out of 8 people had already started fishing.
And only one person left is Mr. Matsumoto.
Maybe it's not just me.
Really?
Mr. Matsumoto!
Mr. Matsumoto, come in!
Yes, this is Mr. Matsumoto.
I've already become popular.
That's what I'm saying!
The only one who can't catch is Matsumoto-san, so please do your best!
I'm already catching! I'm not letting you escape!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
After this, the incredible speed of Kato Yamasaki's amazing pair!
The prey is a carp, but it's a
momentary
Here it comes!
Hey hey!
You can't stop laughing!
And 30 points from the start
After losing to Yamasaki Kato, Yen-Yoshi has finally caught a big fish
It's not long
Give it to me!
Yoshinon, give it to me!
No!
And this time, Hamada...
Here he comes!
Ah! I got caught!
He was almost caught and was disappointed.
Meanwhile, Matsumoto, who hasn't said anything yet, is silent.
Ah...
It's really small.
But, even if it's small, it's still good.
Matsumoto is weak.
From the start, the second place's score is getting bigger.
It's over!
This is bad.
It's long.
And Hamada, who let the big one escape earlier,
Ah, it's going to be found out again.
It's going to be found out again.
Ah, it's cute.
It's cute.
Can you show me the gentle side of it?
You're good.
This time, the bus trip was really fast.
But, Matsumoto was left behind.
Really?
And then, finally...
He's here.
Oh, he's here.
Ah, he ran away.
He was big, right?
He was really big.
It's a dead end.
That's it.
He's frustrated and in a state of shock.
But after this, Matsumoto is in a state of panic.
Grandpa!
In the best condition, Matsumoto is alone.
And then, he gets hit again.
He got away again!
What should I do?
Meanwhile, a large amount of Yamasaki is contacting Hamada
Hello
Yes
Yamasaki and Kato team, right now, there are 4-50 people
What are you doing?
I'm fishing
I'm going to change with Kato
Yes
Can I drink a cup of sake first?
I'm sorry, I can't read it.
If you have time.
Well, I'm watching from a distance.
Can I have a drink first?
Please, please.
1 hour and 15 minutes from the start.
This is completely here.
It's surprisingly big.
It's huge!
Matsumoto gets the first one and gets the big one that will be part of the battle!
I got it! It's huge!
I got it!
Who is that cute girl?
Excuse me!
Even if you cry, I can hear you.
Can you hear me?
I got it!
This time, we are going to do fortune-telling.
We are going to do fortune-telling for today's fortune.
Okada-san, you are the 4th in the last few years.
Really?
You have a great chance of winning.
Thank you.
Please keep quiet.
I'm happy, Okada-san.
Thank you.
Next, Hamada-san.
I will follow you from this year.
I will win.
Thank you.
Yoshio, you have no energy this year.
Sorry.
Okuda and Hamada, you don't get along with Yoshio.
This is the key to victory.
It's dangerous!
Matsumoto-san, Eomuchi-san, Itoi-san!
Let's do the fortune-telling time!
Itoi-san, unfortunately, next year you'll be a
fortune-teller.
And itoi san is like archer
Baron Blow-down
It's time for the usual!
Using a special downtown lure, the person who catches it first gets 100,000 yen.
Last year, Yosuke Eguchi caught two fish and was able to win the game.
Who will get 100,000 yen this time?
Let's go!
The downtown lure time to earn 100,000 yen, start!
What's that?
It's not coming!
It's not coming, it's not coming.
It's coming, it's coming.
It's coming!
It's not coming, it's not coming!
It's not coming!
The ship that was about to leave the port dies.
But, really?
The ship is coming!
No, no!
No, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Please don't tell a lie!
That ship is really the worst!
And then...
Here comes Eguchi!
Eguchi has won 100,000 yen!
Eguchi-san, you did it!
You did it!
After the luring time, the tournament is finally over.
Hamada, Okura, Yoshii are moving to the point.
Matsumoto, Itoi, Eguchi are also focused on the last spurt.
Yamasaki and Kato's perfect combination is a piece of cake.
Who will be the winner of this year's award?
And there is a surprising ending.
The miracle of 15 years has now become an album and has appeared here.
The final episode of Ecstasy.
Ecstasy Records.
The big announcement!
Mr. Hamada is drunk, isn't he?
His face is full of alcohol.
Really?
He drank a lot of alcohol.
Why are you so shy?
Let's start with Itoi
I'm 23cm
Itoi is 23cm
Look at me
I want you to look at my aura
rather than my length
But you did it before
24cm
Thank you
It's good, it's good.
Did you get it?
26 cm.
That's a lot.
Haruna, you don't have any aura.
That's right, 24.5 cm.
Let's go.
Mr. Yagami, look at this.
You got it too?
That's amazing.
Why did you get all of them?
You've put in this much!
I've put in all of it, but it's already amazing, right?
Ah, that's not good.
Ah, 25.
Let's go, Hamada-san.
You can do it, right?
Ah, 26.
26, right?
26 cm.
Ah, but it's high.
It's high.
Next, Tamiya-san!
Chakurete!
Wow!
30 seconds!
Wow, amazing!
His chin is sticking out!
He always comes up to here.
Always.
That's right.
M-san, over here!
Yes!
M is Shoma!
I don't even have to measure this.
What's the value?
24 or 4.5.
It's 4.5.
4.5 means...
It's the 30th anniversary of the show!
Congratulations!
It's the first time!
I'm sure there will be more.
As you can see, the final result is...
The battle legend, Itoi Shinsato, has been humiliated once again.
The second-largest fish shop in Okutatamiyo, where he won the first prize, is presented to one person.
In addition, 10 people have the original downtown lure, a mega-buzz character.
We will give the book of professional search, which served as a guide this time, to five people.
Please apply for the product of hope at the name of the name of the product.
I really didn't want to beat Okuda, but it was fun.
Aida-san said that I was a bait.
If possible, I want to aim for the championship and continue to work hard.
I want to aim for the 4th place.
What are you talking about?
I'm looking forward to your performance next year.
Well, I'm 4th place in the first place.
I'm thinking that there are various rankings.
This year, I was 4th place in the black bus.
Next year, I want to do better than that.
Thank you.
I'm laughing a lot.
I thought I might get hit.
Next is...
The winner!
When I was eating earlier, I saw the members.
I was worried about whether I could get out next year in terms of age and position.
I was told that if I worked hard, I would be selected again.
I will work hard for another year and challenge myself next year.
I will be able to win the Mahjong this year.
I'm scared.
I'm a champion.
I'm searching for a prize that will only be given to the 8th place.
I'm not sure if I can win this.
Next year I want to give this to someone.
As I said from the beginning, my goal today is not to win, but to show you my aura.
The aura of Tsurizao. The aura when he's making people laugh.
I want to be a developer, or a salesperson.
I want to think positively.
As a person from the dark side, I want to be a system...
What?
Bye bye.