Chikichiki Shinshun Daishinrenkai!
I'm the host of this program, Chikichiki Shinshun Daishinrenkai!
I'm Yomesaki Hosei!
I'm the producer of this program.
I'm Kenji Suga!
I'm here to give you a wink!
What do you mean by a wink?
Don't mess with me!
Today, we have a new year's party.
Unfortunately, it's not a break-up.
It's a break-up.
I hope you'll enjoy it.
Thank you.
I'd like to have a toast, a greeting, and a mirror break-up from the people of Downtown.
The atmosphere is still very bad.
If I say anything here, I'll end up like that.
I'll have to make it up to you.
As Mr. Suga said, it's not a break-up at all.
That's strange.
It's not a break-up at all.
That's very harsh.
Anyway, thank you all for coming.
Thank you for having us.
Thank you for coming.
Cheers!
Everyone, the food is in front of you.
Please take your time to judge.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
This year marks the 10th anniversary of the Gaki no Tsukai Korei.
The atmosphere is just as calm as usual.
Congratulations on the 10th anniversary.
Meanwhile, Tanaka greets Hamada.
I'm your junior.
Nice to meet you.
Don't cry.
I'm your junior.
It's Tanaka! Everyone, gather around!
Tanaka's prank from last week, which received a lot of feedback.
This is a prank that Tanaka does on his own, but Hamada can't stop crying.
Stop! Stop!
Tanaka was so scared of Hamada's acting that he started crying.
No way!
Did you think he was going to cry?
No, I didn't.
I talked to the young comedians.
They all said he was going to cry.
That was the first time I saw it on air.
It was so fast when I hit him.
Everyone was like, wow!
You were laughing when you came out, right?
I wasn't laughing.
Matsumoto was laughing.
I was laughing, but it didn't make sense.
I can't do a prank today.
I can't bring a prank from here.
I'm in!
I'll never forget Tanaka's face no matter how many times I see him.
The second episode!
We can't use the kids, so we're going to use them!
Shinshun Owarai New Wave Manzai Dairase!
From now on, we're going to draw lots with 20 staff members.
We're going to have a manzai game of 5 teams.
First, we're going to draw lots for the numbers.
The manzai game was popular last year.
Everyone drew lots while hoping that they would be eliminated.
If the number drawn here comes out in the next roulette,
we'll have to perform a manzai on stage.
First!
The first team!
It's one-twenty.
Number 6!
Who's number 6?
It's Aotani!
I'd like you to push your opponent.
If you push him, you'll get hit in the head.
Stop!
I'm counting on you.
Number 10!
But it looks like...
It's Ron Gaze!
The second team is...
I'm counting on you.
Number 11!
It's Tanaka!
If you get hit by a strong guy, you'll get hit here.
I'm counting on you.
Let's go!
Stop it!
It's Takasu!
It wasn't Aotani this year!
The third team!
I want to run away.
Number 13!
Who is it?
It's Uwabaki!
I'm counting on you.
Thank you.
It's me!
It's Uwabaki!
He's the best!
Then it's either Uwabaki or Motoi.
I'm counting on you.
I want that one.
Last year, you were pretty good.
Matsumoto, you didn't get hit in the head.
Will I get hit?
I'm counting on you.
Number 10!
It's Fujiwara!
Who is Nakamura's partner?
There's only one team left!
There's only one team left.
Who will be the first one?
Number 11!
And the last roulette!
Number 4!
That's the end of the fifth team!
Yes!
Thank you!
It's me this year!
You're crazy!
Let's go to the last one!
This is the end.
I'm sorry.
Let's go!
Number 18!
Yes.
It's Matsumoto!
Matsumoto!
The god of comedy is here!
I'm so excited!
It's Matsumoto's turn!
It's Irie!
It's Irie again!
Number 5!
That's it!
This is it!
The other six teams are exhausted.
Yamazaki will decide the topic.
First, Adachi Saito's long A's is distraught.
Next, Sanaka Takasu's handy honnit challenge.
And Hamada Sakamoto's diet movie Titanic.
Nakamura Fujiwara's health is on the rise.
Otomo Endo's challenge is to catch the most difficult fish.
And the last one, Sugawa Matsumoto, is determined to be in the digital society.
It's a big hit in the commercial industry!
They are moving to a different room.
Even though it's a party, they have their own sense of humor.
There will be a careful talk show.
There are four kinds of food.
Now, let's introduce the first team.
They are Hamada and Uwawaki from downtown.
Their team name is Titanic.
I'm Uwawaki.
I'm Misabaki.
We are...
Geta Mako!
Yeah!
That's how it is.
Nice to meet you.
Yesterday...
May I?
Of course.
What do you mean?
Yesterday...
I watched Titanic.
You watched Titanic yesterday?
That's too late.
It was a big hit last year.
It just came out in the video.
You shouldn't watch it in the video.
You should watch it in the cinema.
Why?
The cinema is close.
There are two or three cinemas next to the cinema.
You should watch it in the cinema!
What are you talking about?
You should watch it in the cinema.
There were a lot of famous scenes in Titanic.
There were a lot.
No matter what...
What kind of scenes were there?
First of all...
On the battlefield...
The scene where two people's love is gradually connected.
The scene of spitting.
There was a scene like that.
It's a little dirty.
What was it like?
Watch it.
What are you doing?
Why are you spitting in front of the audience?
No, there were other scenes.
There were more.
There were more, right?
What kind of scenes were there?
The scene of spitting on the battlefield.
What are you talking about?
It's dirty.
That was a while ago.
There were other scenes.
Famous scenes.
What other scenes were there?
There was a scene of spitting on the battlefield.
This is...
What is this?
Rose.
There was a scene where Rose and Rose dance together.
It was a scene that looked fun.
Let's try it.
Wait a minute.
Don't laugh.
Are you okay?
There were other scenes.
Speaking of Titanic.
Famous scenes that must not be forgotten.
What kind of scenes were there?
That's it.
This is Titanic.
This is it.
That was good.
Let's try it.
Close your eyes.
Believe in me.
I believe in you.
Don't drop it.
Thank you.
The second episode is...
Long Gaze.
The theme is restaurant.
Here you go.
Thank you.
I'm Adachi.
I'm Penpo.
Long Gaze with the two of us.
It's a bad time right now.
It's a bad time.
Salaries are being cut off.
There's a restaurant.
There's no way to make money in one shot.
That's good.
When it comes to money...
Bank coat.
That's good.
Let's go to this bank.
Let's go.
It seems to be a bank.
Wait a minute.
What?
I need to pee.
I need to go to the toilet.
We're going to the bank now.
Even if you go to the toilet, you'll be suspected.
I got it.
I'm going to pee.
Let's look forward to it.
Tanaka and Takasu.
The theme is handy-hand.
Thank you.
Hello.
I'm Tanaka.
I'm Takasu.
The two of us.
Tanaka and Takasu.
You stay there.
Go home.
What should I do?
I'm Tanaka.
I'm Takasu.
The two of us.
Tanaka and Takasu.
You're the opposite.
What should I do?
I don't care about the convenience store.
I think now.
Yes.
Many things are popular.
Do you know what's the most popular?
Cell phone.
What are you doing?
I have a cell phone.
Don't say that.
Cell phones are the most popular now.
Yes.
One, two, three, four.
Some people have it.
That's right.
Do you have a cell phone?
I have it.
That's right.
I have a cell phone.
Let's try it.
Yes.
You are slow.
Please do it faster.
You should have said that.
You should have done that.
Don't be so fast.
Okay.
You're too fast.
We haven't pressed the button yet.
It's not possible.
What is it?
You're always angry.
What a guy.
You always say that.
What is it?
You should have done it at a good timing.
We're too fast.
That's too much. Just do it normally.
Okay, I'll do it normally.
Are you a fax machine?
You're not a fax machine, are you?
Don't say I'm a fool!
Don't say I'm a fool in front of the audience.
I heard there's a song called Chakumelo.
Chakushin Melody will play it for you.
There's a song called Smapp.
There's a song called Amuro-chan.
Amuro-chan is in my song.
You're Amuro-chan and you're a Chakumelo.
Let's listen to it.
Sing it!
You can't sing it, can you?
You can't sing Chakumelo.
But it's a melody.
What should I do?
I don't know what to do.
It's a melody, so it's weird to sing it.
It's better to be more calm.
If you're Japanese, you can sing Enka.
Enka is fine.
Let's go with Enka.
Please.
It's good, isn't it?
It's good.
That's why you can't sing it.
You can't sing it.
What should I do?
It's Enka.
You can't sing Enka.
It's Chakumelo.
Please.
It's good.
You can't sing it.
That was a great ending.
The fourth group is Endo-san and Otomo-san.
The theme is Masu.
Please take care of them.
Hello.
It's time for physical education.
One, two.
Please.
Let's do our best.
It's been a year.
I'm thinking of finding a hobby this year.
My hobby is fishing.
Fishing.
Fishing is good.
I fished for a bus.
I caught a fish and threw it.
The moment I caught a fish, I felt good.
You should find a hobby.
I'm doing it too.
Fishing.
Do you have a hobby?
Please tell me what your hobby is.
Fishing for a bus.
It's different.
I'm not alone.
I'm moved.
I was really moved when I caught a fish.
I'm moved because of it.
You are not moved, right?
I feel moved.
This is the first time in a week.
Masu, please.
I'm moved because of it.
The most moving thing was the 38th win in Yokohama.
Sasaki, the great Sasaki, the hulk ball, this hulk ball is amazing.
No one can hit that hulk ball.
I've never returned that hulk.
What? Who is that hulk?
My mom throws a better hulk.
Why?
Don't call me mom. Don't talk to me like that.
Mom, can you throw a hulk?
What kind of hulk is it?
My dad's son stabbed me with this.
That hulk is dangerous. What are you going to do?
Don't make fun of me. You're really amazing.
But the other thing that moved me was the championship interview.
That was so moving. It's been 38 years.
Didn't that move you?
I can do that.
There's no way you can.
I'll make everyone moved.
You're going to make everyone moved?
I'm counting on you.
He's returned after 38 years.
He's a Yokohama-based star.
Please tell us how you feel right now.
Who do you want to tell how you feel right now?
How do you want to fight in the Japan Series?
You're the one who's going to be moved.
You shouldn't be the only one who's going to be moved.
I'm not talking about the championship interview.
The championship interview is like the catch ball in a conversation.
Catch the ball. Let's do the catch ball properly.
Just baseball.
That's enough. Thank you very much.
I was surprised.
Let's go to the 5th team.
I want you to do your best in the 5th team.
There are two newbies.
Bafun and Fujiwara.
Please take care of them.
I'm Fujiwara-kun.
I'm Nakamura-kun.
Please take care of them.
I'm Fujiwara-kun.
This year is fast.
Yes, it's fast.
It's like January.
I'm 36 years old this year.
36? 36 means...
What is it?
Don't lie to me.
I know.
I'm 36.
36 means...
I don't know. I'm 39.
Why?
What kind of calculation are you doing?
Let's go to the last team.
Matsumoto and Sugade.
This is a digital society.
Hello, everyone.
Happy New Year.
What is there to be happy about?
What are you doing?
Aren't you greeting the audience?
What are you angry about?
I'm very angry.
First of all, January 1st.
It's New Year's Day.
What's going on in New Year's Day?
The number of mobile phone calls has increased by 11 digits.
It has increased by 11 digits.
How about 090?
How about 070?
It's complicated.
I'm responsible for it.
I'm angry.
Speaking of which, Osaka where we live.
Osaka.
The number of phone calls has increased.
It's said that six numbers have increased.
It's said that seven numbers have increased.
I can't remember.
I understand, but I can't help it.
The number of postcards has increased.
Seven digits.
How about 104?
How about 105?
It's complicated.
I'm responsible for it.
I can't speak.
The number of postcards has increased.
What's increasing?
First, the number of hair.
The number of hair has increased.
It has increased by one or two digits.
It has increased by three digits.
It has increased by 11 digits.
It's dangerous.
And you.
Sports is the J-League.
There is J-League?
It's increased by 20 digits.
You mean 20 people?
What do you mean?
20 balls.
What the hell are you talking about?
The current popular talent, SMAP.
Don't make fun of me.
I'm sorry.
SMAP.
There will be more members.
There are five of us, but how many are there?
There are six of us.
Six?
Who will be added?
Mori will be added.
Don't make fun of me.
Is it okay to make fun of me?
Yes.
And you.
The most difficult thing is the number of signals.
What is the number of signals?
Three colors are four colors.
What color will increase?
Gray.
What should we do if the driver and the pedestrian become gray?
Do you want to go to Ishikawa-chika?
Go to Ishikawa-chika.
Don't say no.
What is it?
I've been telling you a lot of things that will increase.
There are things that will increase and things that will decrease.
There are things that will decrease.
What is it?
The number of people who can laugh has decreased.
You are so excited.
What the hell is this?
Make it as a painting.
This burnt tennis ball.
Grandma, I accept it.
I was deceived by Takas.
I should have said a little more.
But he said it was interesting.
I couldn't do anything.
It was interesting, wasn't it?
Aikata-san's voice isn't coming out.
No, Aikata-san is...
I was rehearsing at around 4 and a half o'clock.
My voice wasn't coming out.
The first time I spoke, my voice wasn't coming out.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.