Which one do you like more, Chikichiki or Tsukikirai?
Daiki!
Three times?
What?
Well, it depends on the person.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to do that.
I'm sorry.
Daiki-san!
Yes, yes.
I've done it once or twice so far.
The moment I saw this, I knew what you were going to do.
This is...
...a photo zone for celebrities.
Mr. Matsumoto, from A to D, from the bottom, you can put whatever you like or don't like.
I'll put it.
But it's not our intention!
That's all.
I'll talk about why I like you and why I don't like you.
Well, well, well.
Even if you hate someone you like, there are some things you don't like about them.
There aren't?
Which one should we go with?
Well, Hamada's...
You don't like him?
I don't like him.
It's not that I don't like him.
It's that I don't like him.
I don't like him.
Well, even if you say that...
...don't you feel like you're doing something behind his back?
Well, I feel like he's been researching everything and then talking about it.
If you say something, he'll hug you in the coffin.
That's right.
I feel sorry for you.
I heard a rumor about you.
Even if you say things like, I feel sorry for you, he'll hug you in the coffin.
He doesn't even look around.
You go first.
I'll go first because I don't like him.
You don't like him.
I don't like him.
You don't like him?
Why?
I'm a Zura researcher.
I can see through people on TV who aren't Zura.
I can see through people who aren't Zura.
His baldness is fake baldness.
This is really baldness.
That baldness is strange.
It's strange.
There are baldnesses like this.
That's probably because someone at home is eating.
I'm not eating.
When I'm eating at home, my baldness is very big.
That's a really big baldness.
A person who's eating can't even put a hairband on his head.
Hey, hey, hey!
That baldness is big.
It's a baldness a woman in her 40s did.
That's no good.
But you like it.
If you like it, then it's fine.
I don't think you can tell from this photo, but recently there's a lot of white stuff around here.
That's right.
That's making Dandy-sa even more powerful.
But doesn't it look like that on TV?
Doesn't it look like you like it?
No, not at all.
It kind of looks kind.
Even if you don't say it, I know it.
This photo was taken after plastic surgery.
That's not true!
What do you mean by plastic surgery?
It makes you look attractive.
That's right.
Normally, when you get married or become popular, people will try to protect you.
But he doesn't have that.
Is that so?
I heard that he has his own room in his house.
But here, he has his own AV.
It's like he has his own house.
Even after his wife goes to bed, he's watching the video with both hands.
That's amazing.
I want to watch it too.
That's right.
Is that so?
Do you like it?
Yes, I like it.
He's a good guy.
Really?
He's a good guy, but he's a bit dirty.
He keeps asking me to give him money.
Hello? Hello? Hello?
My house?
I want to buy a house.
I heard that if you spend 3 million yen on it, it will be really nice.
3 million yen...
Is that okay?
What's okay?
What are you talking about?
I'm a good guy, including that kind of cuteness.
Open it.
Rex the Dinosaur Man.
Are you Yumi Adachi?
Everyone says you're cute.
From what I see, this woman is probably 22 or 23 years old.
She's a child.
What do you think of this?
You said you liked it, but why are you worried?
But your smile is beautiful.
Your smile is beautiful.
I like this part.
His...
It's the same.
I call this part an electronic brain.
I've never done that before.
This kind of area.
Please think of something here.
Dora!
Do you like this?
I hate it.
Last year, we did it for 24 hours.
We did it.
We did it once, and then we went back to the stage.
The three of us did it.
We've been doing it for a long time.
The three of us sat down and looked at each other.
Why are you talking like that?
Hey, wait!
Stand up and say, good morning!
I thought so.
Look at each other and say, good morning!
You don't even say hello.
That's right.
He's doing a music show.
How long has it been?
It's been a long time.
I'm here.
I don't know.
Look at me.
Thank you very much.
There are a lot of people like that.
I don't know much about it.
Senior!
You don't feel that way when you watch TV, right?
There are reporters around you.
The scene is different.
There are a lot of them.
That's right.
What are you writing?
I'm not writing here.
I'm going to quit the show called Gaki no Tsukai.
I'm talking without saying anything.
I will say something.
I will say, it's open!
I'm going home and I said, it's open!
I think they cut it.
But when I look at the video, it's completely on air.
It's on air.
I don't know what will come out.
I don't want to call you because there's a photo in the fan letter.
I already did it!
What is it?
Wait, wait!
Wait!
I already did it!
What is it?
No, no, don't say it.
We're friends!
What is it?
Hey, do it!
But...
What is it?
I don't need your help.
I don't need your help!
I don't need you to call me because there's a photo in the fan letter.
We're friends.
Thank you.
I'll be your fan from now on.
You're lying!
If it's only that, it's fine.
Then I'll tell you.
And then we can talk and meet.
No, it's fine.
What you're saying is what I'm going to say next.
No, no, no, no, no.
I didn't do it.
But we can talk and meet.
And then we can come to your house.
That's fine.
No, no.
We can hold each other.
That's not it.
No, no, no, no.
Why are you holding me when we're not talking?
No, no, no, no, no.
If we're not talking, let's talk.
Why are you holding me?
What do you mean you're holding me?
It's funny that we're not talking.
There's something like that.
No, no.
Then what are you going to do after you hold me?
Then let's talk.
You can hold me and drop me on the bed.
Well, let's talk.
I dropped you on the bed.
I held you.
I dropped you.
It's going to happen.
What do you think of this?
I'll check it out.
It's fun.
I'll probably tell you.
I'll tell you.
I'll send you home.
What are you going to tell me?
Aoka?
What is this?
Kento 12-jou.
What is 12-jou?
I don't understand.
You're going to get caught in something.
Bonnyo-yoyo is no good.
I'm going to get caught by that person.
But!
I told you not to hold me.
I don't have it, but you can hold me.
That's not true.
I'm doing it with him.
I think so.
I don't think so.
You don't think so.
Why?
I think he's going to do it.
You think so, don't you?
You did Bonnyo-yoyo, didn't you?
But after Bonnyo-yoyo, you did something different, didn't you?
I think so.
What is Bonnyo-yoyo?
I can't think of anything.
I thought I was doing a lot of things that would lead to misunderstandings.
I don't know if it's really something that would lead to misunderstandings.
I quit recently, but there was a story a long time ago.
When I was not caught by a taxi, a girl was running around in a car.
I was noticed by her.
I told her to get in the car and I told her not to go anywhere.
You are a talent.
I was doing it well.
You're good, but you're not good at all.
What is it?
You're not good at martial arts.
I'm not good at martial arts.
Of course, it doesn't matter.
I said thank you.
She said she would let me do it.
I was doing it from time to time.
I thought I couldn't do it.
What hurts?
That hurts the most.
You can't do it anymore?
It doesn't matter.
I really don't like it.
You move too much.
Why do I move so much?
I know you're hungry.
You shouldn't walk around and eat.
I go out to eat as much as possible.
I go to family restaurants.
I'm not a woman.
I wear a hat and absorb the rumors that I hear from people around me.
I make a line with it.
Why?
I've never heard of it.
I think the number of fans has decreased.
I don't think so.
No, it's decreasing.
I heard it from someone.
You had a press conference today, didn't you?
What?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You had a press conference yesterday, didn't you?
In the morning and in the afternoon.
In the morning and in the afternoon, didn't you?
So the magazines and newspapers that came out yesterday, and the train...
Nakazuri?
Nakazuri came out yesterday, didn't it?
I think it's already out.
From yesterday morning, at least until this morning, I believe it.
When someone was on the train, I could hear the voice of a high school girl watching Nakazuri.
I see.
It was shocking.
Say it from the beginning.
Why are you making me say it?
That's what I thought.
I saw yesterday's magazine, for example, my fan saw a magazine or newspaper and was shocked.
But my mother said, Yuriko, hurry up.
I'm going.
Where are you going?
Fan, fan, fan.
What are you doing?
Where are you going, Yuriko?
What?
Venezuela.
I got it.
After my father's work, I have to go to Venezuela with my family.
I can't make it on time for the flight.
I saw the magazine when I was about to leave, but I didn't see the newspaper.
Fan, fan, fan.
I flew to Venezuela.
This Yuriko from Venezuela still thinks that I have a beard.
That's right.
How can I contact this Yuriko from Venezuela?
Are you stupid?
I was watching the weather forecast on NHK.
You look like a very serious man with glasses on.
The chance of rain tomorrow in Tokyo is 10%.
But I'm sorry if it rains.
I was shocked.
NHK did the same thing.
NHK is falling apart.
Really?
In the past, NHK used to do rock music.
I think they will do a commercial.
That's not true.
Sometimes I draw around here.
It depends on where I draw.
What?
There is something psychological.
I can do fortune-telling.
Really?
I draw here.
That's the same as the old girl in the aquarium.
That's ridiculous.
Why do humans blink?
If I open my eyes, my eyes will dry up.
Your eyes will dry up.
I close my eyes once.
That's not the answer.
If you die once, it's over.
You are doing it with your body.
How far do you want to go?
I'm suffering.
I'm sorry.
If you die once, it's over.
If you blink once, you are dead.
That's it.
I see.
I hope you understand.
The director always acts with a bird.
Why?
The other day I went to get an avian.
In Switzerland.
I don't know the reason.
I'm already like that.
I think the director is like that.
The bird in the basket is the director Sakamoto.
Who is the big guy in the basket?
He is the elevator.
It seems that there is a meeting.
This is the director Sakamoto.
But the director Sakamoto doesn't speak much even if there is a meeting.
What are you talking about?
I see.
The garbage collection will change from October 1st.
This is a social problem.
I want to see this in a commercial.
You have to write your name.
You have to write your phone number.
I think this system will disappear in 3 months.
This is a difficult thing.
Why is it difficult?
You are saying a good thing now.
What is difficult?
The house is full of garbage.
Even girls can't throw away their underwear because they think they can't take it off.
They throw their underwear into a bag and throw it into a transparent bag. It's the same thing!
It's meaningless.
It's meaningless, right?
I have a lot of black plastic bags.
Why don't you give me that?
I get angry, so I throw my black plastic bag into the trash and finally cover it with a transparent bag.
You know what I mean, right?
You don't know what a black condom is, do you?
It's black.
Unless it's transparent, it's useless, right?
That's not good!
Why not?
It's useless if you don't write your name on it.
Why do I have to write my name on it?
Even if it's Tanaka-kun, it's Sato-kun.
That's not good.
If it's Sato-san, it's not good.