Hichihenge, the useless boy choreography
And now, the second male sounds- contribute from the junior gym
Finally comes the ending
How many of them are there?
Next time on Gaki no Tsukai, Chikitsuki! Chiyono Junior's transformation!
That was fast!
It was fast, right?
Well, my brother was like that, so I wanted to make him forget about it
But you're in 3rd place
Yes, I'm in 3rd place
It's strange, but I have a different potential
You're different from others
Yes
My dad is the type to worry
Oh really?
He doesn't sleep that much
He's not as good as his face
Let's ask him
Here's today's star
Thank you!
My brother
Hello
Please do your best
This is what hell is
Why is that?
It's the power of the two of us
It's like a kikishu cream
From now on?
Yes
A little while ago
I had a dream where my nails were peeled off the day before
I saw it
Why?
Well, it's natural that my nails were peeled off
3rd place! 3rd place!
Look at this
3rd place!
Why is your style a little good?
It can't be helped
It can't be helped!
Shut up
When I'm saying things like that, my brother laughs
It's peeled off
What are you going to do?
What should we do?
Is this what Yama-chan said?
What?
That's right
What does that mean?
Kyon is so cool
What is that?
Yama-chan always says that
When I was watching TV, my brother-in-law said that I became cool
But I became cool
Endo?
Saguro
He was looking at me
I don't know what to do
Is that so?
From various angles
It's not that Endo became cool, but Yama-chan became too uncool
Again, again
That's a lot of respect
You're joking again
I'm joking again
When I go there, my brother's style is not half bad
I've never measured my weight
It's almost the same as the Beijing Duck
It's thin
I've earned a lot of money
Thank you
Why did you earn a lot of money?
I can't help it
Did you get a place for the fireworks?
Why is the best place a bar?
Think about it
I'm a junior
Don't be so excited
Make me feel good
It's cold at night, so I'm telling you to come up
Think about it
Who is an idiot?
Why did you bring me to a good soba restaurant?
Why didn't you ask for katsudon?
Think about it
I can't help it
I'm so excited
That was dangerous
I'm an idiot
Who is an idiot?
Seiji
Seiji is an idiot
The previous pattern is the opposite
Do you use HEPO?
I use HEPO
I have to stretch 1 meter
How tall are you?
I'm 181 cm
I didn't do anything
Did you eat cartamon?
I didn't eat anything
I ate a little more than expected
I think you ate cartamon
I'm a Kyoto person, so I eat cartamon
What are you talking about?
Are you a good person?
I'm a normal person
Thank you
Excuse me
I can't help it
Look at me
Don't invite me
I can't see
I see
It's completely different
I can't see
I didn't know that Hotei was doing this
I think it would be interesting to find the roots of Hotei
Did you see Meisa?
I saw her
Did you see her character?
Yes
Do you want to tell Mizumoto?
I'll tell him next month
Did you see Meisa?
I saw her
Did you see her character?
Yes
Do you want to tell Mizumoto?
I'll tell him next month
Did you really see Meisa?
Yes
Did you see her character?
Do you want to tell Mizumoto?
Did you see Meisa?
Yes
Did you see her character?
You were missing, weren't you?
Do you want to tell Hikisa?
I'm going to tell her
Who do you want to tell?
Hikisa
Hikisa is not in the game now
I found a new character
It's nice
It's a new character
Who is laughing?
I can't help it
He is a fool
His necktie is too short
What should I do?
Who is this?
Sorry
Let's go
It was dangerous
Sanma appears here
It's true
It was a little similar
But I really thought who this was
Who is this?
I don't know
That's right
He is the worst
What should I do?
Did you play DS?
Is it on sale?
I played it on the guide
Yu-chan, where are you?
I came to the capital of flowers
Recently, the vegetables
Shut up
I don't know what to do
I'm sick of money
Heipo-chan, can I have some coffee?
Shut up
No matter how much I beg
I'm not a woman
My daughter is
If you ask me
I'm imitating myself
Recently, the vegetables
Shut up
I can't see anything from this conference room
Yu-chan
I like Ryuji
Don't laugh
It's that
I am crazy about those two, right?
I want to speak Japanese with someone.
I am crazy about those two,right?
You say that a lot, right?
What? What? What?
What?
That was dangerous.
I lost.
You lost.
Number 23, who is it?
There was an accident on the bike.
Yeah.
When the accident happened, it hurt.
I don't want to see that pain again.
Yeah.
It was really hard.
I don't want to see that pain again.
Let's count.
Here it is.
How much is it?
I'll announce it.
It's 26,000 yen.
26,000 yen.
Number 11.
It's Miyasako.
Thank you.
I should have done it earlier.
Next is you.
I didn't do it today, but I made a lot of money.
I didn't do it today.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Good evening.
I'll do my best.
I'm Hama, in charge of the comments.
I'm Machan, in charge of the jokes.
You're not stupid.
Well, well, well.
I can't say anything good.
Well, yeah.
Yesterday, Mr. Takatanosu of Japanet.
I've been saying this for a long time.
This is too expensive.
I'm getting more expensive.
I've been saying this for a long time.
I haven't seen it recently.
I was sleeping while watching TV yesterday.
A man came out and said,
Cool body.
How is it?
This cool body.
He said,
I want to sell it.
What kind of product is it?
Well, well, well.
What is it?
Metallic.
This metallic.
How is it?
This cool body.
He said,
Well, well, well.
You know, the bees.
There's a health food.
Royal jelly.
Mr. Anosu does it again.
Well, well, well.
This royal jelly.
This color.
Royal.
I don't know what to say.
It's not that effective.
Why is it so easy to drink?
You can drink it if you have water.
Well, well, well.
I'll forgive you.
It's okay.
I can't sleep.
In the middle of the night?
It's in the middle of the night.
I think I know what I was saying.
I was saying Vega Vega.
I started to say Vega.
Really?
Yes.
But I said Sonino.
One more time.
Mr. Anosu, you recently bought a new car.
You, too.
I don't want to buy a new car.
What do you mean you don't want to buy a new car?
You're the same age as me.
If I'm driving, the parts will fall off.
I don't want to buy a new car because it's not rusty.
I've been driving a car for six years.
I've been driving for about six years.
That's not true.
You're the one who keeps changing.
Why are you angry with me?
It's been a long time since I've driven a car.
You keep changing.
You're going to buy a new car again, aren't you?
I have a new car.
That's not true.
You're too smart and stupid.
What?
You're going to buy a new car?
There's a lot of meaningless functions.
I told you before.
There are a lot of buttons that I don't understand.
When I press the button, even if the speed is more than 40 km per hour, the speed is too high.
I don't understand the meaning of the button.
When I was driving at night, the yellow light was shining.
I was wondering what it was.
I looked it up and found that the airbag was working fine.
It's working fine today.
I'm attracted to the wrong time.
The opposite.
It's shining again today.
It's strange.
Why is there such a function?
Didn't you know that it was working fine?
I don't know.
How did you buy it?
Did you buy it without looking at it?
I bought it without looking at it.
Did you hear that?
What is it?
You are a man.
Cool body.
What are you going to do with it?
I sell it.
I sell it and run away.
I buy shoes.
I buy it like this.
I will buy that.
I will follow you all the time.
If you give a car as a gift on TV, you will be given a big key.
What kind of car is the car with that key?
That is not a real key.
That is a fake key.
I know that.
Really.
What is that face?
Stop that face.
That is made of styrofoam.
Even if a real key is given, it is difficult to distinguish it on TV.
So I made a big key and got a car.
Really.
Everyone knows that.
Stop that face.
I am angry.
I make a big key.
I don't have money.
But I make a real key.
Stop that face.
What?
I completely forgot about your job.