There were a lot of letters sent to this boy by the viewers.
What kind of letters?
There was information that they saw a variety of talents at various places.
Did you see them?
Yes, I saw them.
There were a lot of them.
Really?
It's 100% fake news.
That's all.
That's right.
They introduced that.
But it's not fake news.
What is it?
Which one is it?
Shut up.
I want to make fun of your stupidity.
I understand.
Are you heading there first?
I'm heading there first.
Whose letter is it?
Is it the first one?
The first one is amazing.
It's the first one.
I like it.
Hello, everyone.
Recently, I often go to a ramen shop called Marunaka.
Surprisingly, the famous musician, Nagamushi Tsuyoshi, is lined up in a long line.
Really?
Nagamushi-san?
Is this real?
Yes.
Let's go.
Let's see if Nagamushi-san is there.
Yes, let's go.
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
It's around here.
Are you standing still?
I'm standing still.
I don't know.
You didn't change the time, did you?
Even if everyone goes, it's not a big deal.
If that's the case, Nagamushi-san will be mad today.
I'd like someone to come and see me.
Who?
Endo should go.
Me?
I've met Nagamushi-san a couple of times.
Let's negotiate.
I'll go.
I wonder if he's here today.
If no one is here, it'll be a mess.
That's true.
If no one is here.
He's late.
What's that?
It's been a while.
Should we go see him?
Let's go.
Can't we do something better than this?
I think he's right there.
There he is.
Huh?
There's Nagamushi-san.
It's you.
It's Nagamushi-san, right?
What?
No way.
He's here.
He's got a hammer gun.
I can't believe it.
There's no mistake.
We're almost there.
That's right.
Why?
If you wait like that, you'll stand out.
That's right.
What are you doing?
Who is it?
Hello.
Eat this.
It's amazing, isn't it?
If we keep going, we'll meet a lot of people, right?
We'll meet a lot of people today.
That's right.
Well, the filming is going to take a long time.
It's time to wait.
Let's go. Let's go.
Where did Endo go?
I was surprised. I was surprised.
I was surprised.
I was very surprised.
I was impressed.
I asked for a photo.
It's amazing.
It's precious.
It's written as a fool.
That's right.
The paper was torn and broken.
It's lucky.
It's a big deal if I don't turn over.
Let's move on.
It's really amazing.
Wow, that's amazing!
I'm actually wearing it right now
Like this
Yes
In my neighborhood, there's a confectionery shop called Tanaka Kuni
That's what it's called
A confectionery shop called Tanaka Kuni
What is he going to do?
It's a mystery
Where is it?
There's no one here
But isn't the house nearby?
If we do this, they might come
They might come from anywhere
Tanaka
Yes?
You're Tanaka, right?
I'm Tanaka
Can I take a look?
Yes
I'll go and find out the truth
I'm sorry
I can't do this
Right?
Tanaka Kuni
How can they come to a confectionery shop like this?
There's no way they'll come
This is totally fake
There's no sign of them
Huh?
Tanaka Kuni is this big?
He's really big
He's big
He looks cold
Huh? Are you Kuni-san?
Huh?
I think I found something
It's normal
He's not completely drunk
But it's Tanaka Kuni
It really is
Right?
Kuni-san comes here to do this
Does he come to do the mess in the confectionery shop?
There's no confectionery shop
Look
There it is
Isn't that Morning Musume?
Really?
Yes, Morning Musume
It's no good
What's going on?
It's not Nacchi
I finally found out
I want Nacchi
I came here yesterday, but there's no Nacchi
There's no Nacchi
Where did you stop yesterday?
Don't joke with me
It's amazing
It's on
I found it
It's here
It was amazing
It was
I like Morning Musume
It was like that
It's still here
What?
It's fine
I think so too.
Rocky has been down for a while.
Yes.
Mountain-san, I saw something incredible.
What is it?
What a surprise!
The field of Sharankyu...
has been robbed.
What?
This is not good.
What is this?
Even if you say that,
it doesn't mean that we will do it again.
However, the house of a friend has been targeted.
I see.
What will happen?
It's a field.
We can't let it happen.
It can't be.
Something is approaching.
Is that so?
You see,
if such a big car approaches,
the other side will be wary.
That's right.
That's why someone is going to see it.
Who is going to see it?
It's you.
Thank goodness.
What?
It's you.
Who is it?
I think it's me.
I think so too.
The field is...
It's useless.
Who is going to see it?
Is it Rocky?
Yes.
It's bad for the field.
Yes, it's bad.
Where is Hamada?
It's you.
It's okay.
I see.
I thought it was you.
Wait.
This is a lie.
It's not you.
No.
I'm not lying.
I have a guitar.
Are you sure?
It's not you.
Wait.
It's really you.
What?
You're lying!
I really wanted to see it.
Can I see it?
That's Mr. Hatake.
But, but, but...
You're just playing the guitar.
That's right.
What's wrong with playing the guitar?
It's not wrong at all.
Wait a minute.
This is an excuse.
It's an excuse.
It hurts.
It hurt.
With a guitar neck.
I found a small branch.
I want you to notice it.
I don't want you to notice it.
I wanted your slippers.
Oh, my God.
Hey, Micah!
I forgot the guitar.
You left the perfect game.
What's wrong?
I forgot the guitar.
Hatake.
You have to apologize to the owner of the post.
I almost broke it.
No, no.
It was a shocking video.
Did you see it?
I saw it, but I was saying something.
What did you say?
I said I had a bad tooth.
Did you say that?
But it's amazing.
It's 100% 100%.
I still have it.
Really?
It's hard, isn't it?
It's hard.
To be honest.
Both of you are looking at it.
I'm looking at it.
But I'm looking for it.
I can see it.
I want to see it when it comes out.
It's a fake, isn't it?
I don't know.
Listen to me seriously.
I'm talking to you seriously.
Actually, recently, in a nearby park,
the father of Ashtag Joe,
Yabuki Joe,
went out.
That's it.
I don't believe it.
I'm looking at it.
Are you looking for it again?
It's not coming back.
Yabuki Joe will never come back.
It's a fake.
It's a talent.
It's that park, isn't it?
What?
It's Yabuki Joe.
It doesn't move at all.
Wait a minute.
The fact that Joe is dressed like that,
does that mean he's dead?
The last scene.
That's right.
He was dead, wasn't he?
I can't believe it.
It's a fake.
And he forgot to write his name.
He wrote his name.
That's right.
It's not moving at all.
Really?
It's dead.
It's the last scene.
It's not standing up straight.
It's cold.
I was surprised.
But it's Yabuki Joe.
There's no doubt about it.
Why is his face like that?
It's true.
The position of his face is definitely different.
Yabuki-san.
He's dead, isn't he?
No, no, no.
That's not true.
Joe was there.
Did you see it?
I saw it.
Did you really see it?
But that's...
That's not true.
It was Joe.
The last scene.
It's not moving at all.
It's dead.
To be honest, when I change my clothes,
I look at the costumes in the car.
This is a surprise.
I saw Super Mario
having fun in the neighborhood.
Super Mario?
I didn't expect Mario to exist.
No, no, no.
I wonder if he's okay.
I don't know if he's there or not.
He's having fun.
I saw Super Mario
having fun.
He's having fun.
I don't know if he's there or not.
That's true.
Yamasaki is slow.
He's slow.
Let's go see it.
Is that Mario?
That's Mario.
He fell down.
That's amazing.
Mamma Mia!
Are you from Okinawa?
Mario!
I'm getting tired.
He's getting tired.
I'm losing my speed.
I think we are out of the frame.
We're out of the frame.
The end.
I'm tired.
Pan para pan para ara advantages
Momon
I know
Stop
Pan para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para para
I'm so excited.
You are excited, right?
You are completely facing me now.
I just happened to see it.
I'm sure you'll tell me.
Shall we change the song?
This one, right?
I've been saying this for 3 weeks now.
It's a new release.
We need a tempo.
We can't just say everything.
We don't have anything.
It's like you've been slipping before it came out.
Do you have a microphone?
I have to record it.
Next week,
That's right.
Can you record this?
Why?
I can't do this.
I'm going to record it.
I'll just do it.
What kind of feeling is this?
We don't need to laugh at the device.
Well, that's true.
But I'm looking forward to it.
People who come out with such a device.
I don't know how much fun it'll be.
It's a device that you can't help but laugh at.
Matsumoto is Hamada's...
Run and get out.
Listen to me!
You should have said that earlier.
Why are you here?
I want to run and get out.
Matsumoto is Hamada's medicine box.
Hamada is Matsumoto's medicine box.
Matsumoto's heart's medicine box.
When are you going to raise the tempo?
You should have raised the tempo from the beginning.
Don't start from the lowest part.
Matsumoto is Hamada's medicine box.
Good!
What is it?
Really?
It's easy to sing.
Matsumoto is Hamada's medicine box.
What is it?
This time the theme is unity.
Please do it.
Matsumoto is Hamada's medicine box.
I can't say it.
Make it more difficult.
You should have said it.
I can't think of it.
Can you do it now?
I can do it.
I think you can do it.
Let's try it.
This is it.
I can do it.
Matsumoto is Hamada's medicine box.
It's difficult to sing.
Can you sing a song?
That's better.
I will sing a song.
Matsumoto is Hamada's medicine box.
You change every time.
I will sing a song.
Matsumoto is Hamada's medicine box.
I don't know.
I sing a song.
Omanoena
De-he-he-he-he, Oman
Demen-men, Omanoena
Nakana-kana
Let's decide on that
De-he-he-he-he, Oman
Demen-men, Omanoena
Demen-men
Not yet!
You're taking too long
You don't even know the grammar
I'll start from here
De-men-men, Omanoena
Nakana-kana
That's a difficult one
I want you to do this
Can I?
Let's record it
Is everyone okay?
Are you okay?
I can't do that many times
De-he-he-he-he, Oman
Let's change the grammar
Demen-men, Omanoena
Nakana-kana
De-men-men, Omanoena
Nakana-kana is too fast
Nakana-kana reminds me of my school trip
I was there
You guys are so stupid
This is difficult
I got it, I'll do it in ad-lib
Follow me
Try it next time
Let's do it
De-he-he-he
De-ha-mo-ha
At the end of the ad-lib, you were clearly pinching your nipples
It's okay, it's recorded
It's okay to listen to it
Really?
Next week, we'll listen to it
I see