What are you doing?
It seems that there are no more customers today.
Let's make it a signboard.
I was busy today too.
It's been three months since she left this house.
There is no signboard.
What?
What makes her the best entertainer in Japan?
I hope that
she will be
the best
entertainer in Japan.
I feel like I'm going to die.
I don't like it.
You!
I kicked you just now.
What do you mean you kicked me just now?
You didn't even contact me.
It's been a long time since I drank.
Please give me a drink.
Are you drinking again?
I told you to give me a drink.
Give me a drink!
Shut up!
I got it.
Just one drink.
You!
Give me money again!
You idiot!
I don't want that money!
Shut up!
You!
Actually, I have something to tell you.
In my
stomach,
there is your baby.
At the corner of a nameless north street,
the falling snow is
tears.
There is no woman
who is happy,
but the cold night breeze is
blowing.
I want to live with a man
who is tired.
Even such a small dream
and this unreachable body
are painful.
Even for me,
I chase
my dreams.
When I'm by your side,
there is a man
who laughs at your thoughts.
What kind of you are you?
If I don't see you,
if my dreams don't bloom,
I'll die.
You are the only one who can guide me
to the end of this world.
Can you bring me the finish?
Oh, it's coming out!
How many times have we done this show today?
We've done more than 50 times.
Oh, really?
How many times have we done this show?
Please forgive us for today.
It's hard.
I'm going to faint.
I'm sorry for today.
When we talk,
we get excited.
It's strange.
Today is...
Please forgive us.
What time is it now?
It's 10 o'clock.
It's too early!
Too early!
Recently,
I don't know how and where
I made a mistake.
At home,
there is a drink.
Isn't it a drink?
It's not a drink. It's a drink.
What's the cause?
I don't know.
I don't know where it came from.
Isn't it around here?
It's not a drink.
I found it.
I don't know the difference.
I know what a drink is.
Do you know how much
my house is full of drinks?
It's amazing.
My cat,
Chosuke.
What's that?
My cat.
My cat, Chosuke,
was full of drinks.
It was called the Al-Taro.
That was the cause of the drinking at home.
It was the cause of the drinking at home.
I put water in the pot.
I told him not to put it all in.
I told him not to put water in his ears.
I told him not to put it in his ears.
I put it in my ears until here.
I was with my brother for a while.
I still can't forget it.
The drink in my body was in my face.
Gaa!
My brother and I
Stop it.
I put it in my ears.
If I put it in my ears,
I'll die.
If you put it in your ears,
you'll die, but it's not scary.
It's not scary at all.
Gaa!
Chosuke
It's not scary at all.
I've never been scared.
I've never been broken.
Really?
I've been broken many times.
Why? Is it because it's dirty?
My body?
If your body is dirty,
you're dirtier.
It's not about dirt.
It's about what I've done so far.
If you say that,
you're dirtier.
That's all.
I'm really sorry.
It's not like that.
No, no, no, no.
It's pretty good.
I didn't do anything.
Don't say that.
What are you?
The audience won't laugh.
You can't go down and hit the audience.
That's what you do as an angel.
That's right.
You can't go down and hit the audience.
I'm talking, but I'm talking.
I just said,
Shut up.
How much did you pay?
I paid 2,000 yen.
Do you have a wallet?
I'll do this.
Stop it.
That's what I do.
Don't say that.
Why are you making a fuss?
Because it's so bad.
I don't know what it is.
You did it, didn't you?
No.
I didn't do any money.
That's it.
I was playing a game.
Shut up.
I went back.
My hat flew off.
You hit him from behind.
Stop it.
That's why.
I don't care what you say.
You hit him with a bell.
Think about the person who appeared.
Me.
Old man.
You.
Money.
That's all I can say.
You are the worst.
I have been hit.
It's bad for hat.
It's nothing to you.
Really?
I'm not so bad even though I think.
I'm not bad. I'm the worst, right?
Well, yeah.
You're the worst.
No, I'm not bad.
Who's bad?
Old man.
Obviously, it's the old man.
You're the worst after the old man.
No.
Who's the worst after the old man?
It's not me.
2,000 yen?
Who's the worst after the old man?
I wanted to hit him a little more, but I stopped him.
That old man should have hit him one more time.
One more time?
No, I didn't hit him.
I hit him one more time.
No, I hit him like this.
I won.
Don't do that to me.
I've never done that.
First of all, I think I'll definitely be killed in that world.
There's no doubt that I'll be killed in that world.
When I'm killed in that world, I'll definitely be an angel.
I know that.
You'll be an angel.
I'll be an angel.
I know that I'll go to heaven.
I don't know if you'll go to hell, but you're wearing something weird.
My way of thinking is that when humans are born, they give birth to a few points.
If you do something bad, the points will be deducted.
It's like a license.
There's something like 5,000 points, right?
Where did you get 5,000 points from?
If you die without using these 5,000 points, you'll go to heaven.
You don't have any more than 900 points.
Me?
Yes.
Here.
Because when you stole the gasoline...
That's enough.
I don't know if I'm talking to you properly.
Why?
My feet stink, so I'll give you another 500 points.
No, it doesn't stink.
My feet stink.
I said so.
You said that you didn't want to get off the horse because of the polo socks.
My feet stink.
I can't ride it.
Let me get off.
I always watch the two of you on TV.
It's about my father. One day, I was walking on the street and I met a foreigner and I stepped on his foot.
I should apologize for that, but after that, my father said,
Thank you.
He is my father, what do you think?
What do you think?
Before that, I went to Los Angeles. When I went there, there was a coordinator there.
He said, It's okay if you can speak English, because you understand Japanese.
I was like, really?
So I went out and brought my luggage.
He was a very strong American.
He was wearing glasses, and he was the coordinator.
He came to me and said, Didn't you sell the plane?
Yes, I did.
Are you okay?
It's Osaka's plane.
Yes, it is.
Foreigners in Japan should think about mastering Japanese a little more.
You don't have to study Japanese.
No, I don't need it at all.
After a few years, I think the whole world should be in Japanese.
More than that,
What?
I think the whole world should be in Osaka dialect.
This is serious.
There is no word that can convey emotions as much as Osaka dialect.
Can you help me a little?
I don't want to help you.
Help me.
I'm telling you to help me.
I'm tired. Help me.
If you tell me that, I think I have to do something about it.
I think so, too.
I think the whole world should be in Osaka dialect.
Please listen to the fact that I saw when I was 18 years old.
I think it was about 10 years ago when Go Hiromi was still in the talent show.
When I was watching Go Hiromi on TV, Hiromi started swimming like a man.
When the underwater camera caught Hiromi, I saw it.
The water from Hiromi's nose was dripping.
He was swimming.
At that time, he was swimming with a smile as usual.
My childhood heart was deeply hurt.
And I thought that an idol's nose is water.
That's a big solution.
I see.
Hiromi is also a human being, so he doesn't have to show his nose.
But those people are good at their looks.
So it's okay to cry when you win an award.
But if an idol singer cries with a dirty face, it's a nose.
I have to stop crying.
When an idol singer's nose comes out, it gets cold.
If you have a dirty nose, your teeth will come out.
Half of your teeth are normal, and half of your teeth are gold.
Crying with a short nose.
All your noses are the same.
How many times have you had a nose like this?
It's not good to have a nose like this.
You have to be careful.
Where did I put my teeth?
I put my teeth like this.
I forgot where I put my teeth.
You have thick teeth.
Maybe it's because of that.
There was a story in the newspaper that a giant bought Masao.
I found something amazing.
Picky Kyoko.
I understand your feelings, but don't contact me.
Dad, Mom.
Is it a daughter?
It's a daughter, right?
Are you talking about Picky Kyoko?
I'm talking about Picky's parents.
I'm talking about Picky's house.
Are you talking about Kyoko?
I'm talking about Picky Kyoko.
Are you talking about Picky?
That's right.
It says Dad and Mom.
It says Picky in Katakana.
That's right.
What are you talking about?
If it's half, it's Picky Kyoko.
But there's something else before that.
Kimura Picky Kyoko?
Isn't that strange?
That's not it.
There's no Picky Kyoko.
Isn't that a comedian?
That's not it.
I think you were given the name Picky Kyoko.
While you were born.
Kyoko.
No, it's Picky Kyoko.
Okubo Picky Kyoko.
I'm glad I said that.
You're talking about Okubo Picky Kyoko.
I'm talking about Okubo Picky Kyoko.
We're friends.
That's the problem.
Picky Kyoko is my name.
Why did you write it like that?
I asked my mom and dad why I called her Picky Kyoko.
But that was to do my best.
Where?
To make me feel good.
That's Picky.
It's Picky.
I said I wanted to call her Picky.
But she jumped out of the room.
So I understood her feelings.
I called her.
I don't get it.
Why don't you get it?
But Picky Kyoko said she felt good.
So I called her.
That's all I can say.
At my grandfather's funeral,
I saw his nose hair in the coffin.
I pulled it out because I was curious.
Then I went home.
I'm going to kill you.
No way.
I pulled it out because I was curious.
I'm going to kill you.
This is a common thing.
My grandfather died.
My grandfather was killed.
He had a squid.
But his nose hair was longer than I thought.
His nose hair was longer than I thought.
He was usually full of cotton.
His cotton was so white that it was stuffed.
If there was a Grim Reaper,
When he died,
He was wrapped in a veil.
But if his nose hair was longer than I thought,
He couldn't be wrapped.
Do you understand?
There's a veil here.
There's a foreign object that's coming out of the veil.
When I pulled this out,
This is just my grandfather.
My grandfather who was killed in that world.
It was between heaven and the human world.
When I pulled this out,
My grandfather was naturally...
Look at me now.
Here, here.
He was naturally wrapped in a veil.
You're annoying.
That's what I said.
I'm sure there are people like this.
Even if you think you're dead, you should try it once.
That's right.
There's a lot of traffic accidents.
You hit something and hit your head.
It's already broken and it's coming out.
What? Your brain?
That's right.
If you hit your head and you're about to collapse,
Call me.
I'm desperate.
Even if your heart stops?
That's right.
You called me.
I was reading a book of someone who came back alive.
How did you read it?
When I woke up, I was walking in the dark.
There's a light in the front.
I was walking.
For example, if I was reading,
How should I call you?
That's not a problem.
Accidents don't collapse.