Last year, November.
The Yomiuri Giants won the Japan Series.
The biggest beer game was held in Japan.
However, after the game ended, Endo came up with a proposal.
Why don't we do the beer game next year?
We will definitely win next year.
Everyone, please look forward to it.
The members made a sudden proposal.
The following year, the Tigers won the beer game.
At that time, I thought it was just Endo's selfishness.
Our team won the game.
It was my dream to drink beer with these guys.
It was my dream.
HANSHIN TIGERS!
Congratulations on winning the Japan Series!
Get out of the way!
I did it!
No!
Get out of the way!
I told you not to get in there with a bottle!
We are here at Hanshin Tigers' ceremony.
As you can see, there is a lot of commotion.
Let's hear what the players have to say.
No!
It's amazing.
Arthur!
Yeah!
Thank you very much!
This is the best!
Everyone!
Maybe!
The owner of the Daiei is
It may not be!
Everyone from now on
I changed my Daiei uniform
After 5 minutes!
5 minutes?
5 minutes is fast!
I was going to jump into the beer bin
Mr. Heipo!
What happened!
Mr. Heipo, be careful!
I jumped into the beer bin
I jump into the beer bin
There are no glasses!
I panicked by myself
I have nothing to say
I didn't get out of the way
I have no glasses!
From the sign to the beer, the preparation for the Daiei version was done in a hurry.
And 10 minutes later...
Fukuoka Daiei Hawks, the best in Japan, congratulations!
Thank you very much! Thank you very much!
Thank you very much!
How many times have you done this this year?
About six times.
I don't know how many times, but everyone's movements are so good.
It's like you've been doing the same thing over and over again.
That's true.
Thank you very much! Thank you very much!
Thank you very much!
In this way, the two beers are safely over.
A visitor to the relaxing room.
What did you just do to your chest?
I did both my upper and lower body.
Oh, both?
I went to the hotel in New York and went to the pool.
I thought it was just around here.
I think I found it.
You should tell the manager.
What?
I'm waiting.
It's over.
It doesn't matter.
I'll have a beer tonight.
It's over.
I've been watching you play last year.
You played both Giants and Seibu.
And you were in our endo.
Our endo?
That's right.
This year, Hanshin was able to win the championship.
That was a coincidence.
It's not a coincidence.
It's a coincidence.
That's why the endo of 2003 is our Hiroshima Tohoku Cup.
Our?
I wanted to play with beer.
The endo was out of use.
I was in it, too.
You weren't in it.
You were in it only once.
You were in it twice.
That's why I prepared it.
I'm waiting.
I've been drinking about two cups.
I'm done with the staff.
I'm sorry, but I'm going home.
Endo.
I'm going home.
Say it.
I'll pay you back.
You don't know?
You won Hanshin last year and won Hanshin this year.
The next thing you want to win is the cup.
You want to win the cup, don't you?
What are you talking about?
I'm number eight.
You're a permanent loser.
Endo is a permanent loser.
I'm number three.
I'm a permanent loser.
We're friends, so I'll leave it to you two.
I've brought everything you need.
Please help me.
I'm begging you.
I won't ask you again and again.
I did it on a show somewhere in Yamamoto.
There's no show I'm a permanent loser.
I won't do it.
It's starting to look like a cup, isn't it?
It's obviously not.
This is when Mr. Kinuzashi was still active, so it's a little old-fashioned.
But I'll do the cup.
I know.
I was in a hurry, so I only have Endo's cup.
I've been collecting a lot of things while running around.
I'm tired.
I'll do it.
This is the original.
It hasn't changed at all.
It's changed today.
What's that?
It's red.
Isn't that Red Oshima?
Soccer?
But it's red.
It's transparent.
If you look at it from a distance, it looks like it's going to change.
No, it's Shizuoka.
It's Shizuoka.
I went to Shizuoka just now.
I got it from a player called Wada.
Excuse me.
I'm wearing a uniform right now.
Mr. Saki.
Wow, it's cold.
It's cold.
It's like Christmas Saki.
I'll put it in.
I'll never lose it.
Mr. Hamada.
Me?
Yes.
Mr. Hamada.
I came back from my partner.
What partner?
Kato.
This is bad.
This is hard.
Really?
Mr. Kato.
What is this?
I'm going to put on a red hat.
Mr. Baba?
Yes.
What did you just say?
Mr. Baba.
Oh, my God.
It's bad.
You're using red panties.
It's like Pink Panther.
Wait.
That's enough.
What's up with him?
It's hard.
I don't know myself.
I'm sure you're still preparing.
He's wearing
The worst.
If you go from Chatan, you have to do it in a different way.
You have to do the same thing twice.
With Baba and Baba.
At least let Baba go first.
It's after Baba.
I did it.
It was a little too big.
It's a little too big.
Producer Tsutsuga.
Excuse me.
Ah, the fan's part.
Yes, properly.
After all, that's...
Producer.
That's right.
Wow.
That's...
I don't like that.
This person doesn't hesitate at all.
It's his own eyes.
After this, Yamamoto asked the other staff to join the beer party.
He gave red things in turn for the uniform of the car.
If red wasn't enough, he took out red paint and applied it all over the staff's body.
There's a little more.
Yes, yes.
What is this?
What is that?
Salmon?
It's salmon.
Is it salmon?
It's Santa.
Santa, don't bring it this time.
It's salty, Yamamoto.
Thank you.