Special in Hong Kong
It's special, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Two hours?
Yes, 7 and 9.
7 and 9.
They say you can do anything if you can do 7 and 9.
Oh, on TV?
No.
On the whole.
Oh, on the whole?
I don't know the whole.
What about Jimmy?
I don't know.
I'm not busy.
Are there any other guests?
I don't have any guests.
Me and you?
No.
I've never heard of it.
It's called special.
It's two hours.
It would be nice if it was just the two of us.
If it was just the two of us, it would be...
It would be a minus.
But if we do it together, it would be a plus.
What can we do with two people?
We're doing a lot of things.
What do you mean?
From comedy to comedy.
Let's do comedy.
Shall we do comedy?
I'm Sakata-chan.
I'm Rin-chan.
I'm Yama-chan.
I'm Jimmy-chan.
Together, we are Jimmy-Yama.
We've been friends for a long time.
We're really close friends.
You know what I'm thinking.
I know.
I know what Jimmy-chan is thinking.
Yama is like this.
That's great.
Two is like this.
Two.
Yama-chan, try it.
It's New Year's Day.
I'll do it.
Put a thread on it.
Octopus, octopus, rise.
Rise to the sky.
You have to do it properly.
Stop it.
This is funny.
It's a waste of time.
This is a special.
Two hours.
Seven o'clock.
What's that?
Do it properly.
I've been doing this for two hours.
That's enough.
Stop it.
Why are you doing that?
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
Mr. Okamoto is calling me.
I'm pretty angry.
That's not the problem.
I'm calling you because it's a special.
I can't deal with the manager of the first floor.
Manager Okamoto Akihiko
I don't know when that happened.
A young man started his life as a manager of downtown.
His character started to run wild and one day he was cut off from the world.
What are you doing?
Are you angry?
All of us?
Yes, the cast and the staff.
Why are you angry?
Why are you angry with me?
I don't know.
I don't want to do it.
Start.
Manager Okamoto couldn't stop anyone.
He followed the escalator and went crazy.
He developed his own scary challenge.
Are you going to arrest me?
I'll do it.
What does God want from him?
I'm going to Okinawa.
I can't do this.
The devil's plan was spread out in Okinawa.
I'm going to cut the watermelon.
You're going to cut the watermelon with this.
What are you doing?
The ideal girl is too big.
You're so cool.
And now he's cut off again.
Where are you going?
Where are you calling me?
Hong Kong.
You'll know if you come to the airport in Hong Kong.
And now he's going to Hong Kong.
Matsumoto Hamada's grand adventure in Hong Kong begins now.
Hong Kong.
This country is full of unusual activities.
Various people, food, and goods are overflowing.
The mysterious atmosphere is overflowing.
What will be waiting for them?
The boy's first trip to Hong Kong is about to begin.
It's very far from here.
This is not Japan.
You're high.
It's been a year.
What are you doing?
Good job.
What do you mean good job?
You finally came to me.
I've been waiting for a long time.
What is it?
Hong Kong.
You'll know if you come to the airport in Hong Kong.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
It took four hours by plane.
You can't do that in Japan.
You're high.
What are you doing?
You can't fly.
You're not flying.
Which way are you flying?
I'm flying.
Mr. Okamoto, you're high.
What are you doing?
It's my show.
It's your show.
Stop fighting.
Let's go.
I'm gonna go to the mountain
What are you talking about?
Why did you come to Hong Kong?
Because I want to
Don't say that on TV
Are you stupid?
I'm going to Maesan Road
That's a pass
Excuse me
Cat
Are you stupid?
I don't know if you're stupid
You're wearing the pants we were talking about
I don't know if it's a tie
It's the pants we were talking about
What happened to your pants?
I don't want to see my pants from here
What are you talking about?
Brief
I don't know
I don't want to see my briefs like this
I've been walking like this all the time
I can't wear this
Excuse me
I can't smoke here
It's dirty
Don't say that
I don't want to see my briefs
What kind of country is this?
It's a mess
The second floor of the bank is like this
I'm scared
Let's eat this
This is Hong Kong
I wanted to eat Hong Kong-style food
I don't want to be full
What are you talking about?
He's happy
I don't want to be full
Are you an idiot?
Do you have chicken nuggets?
I don't know
Ohama-san, let's go for a walk
Let's go for a walk
How about going this way?
Let's go for a walk in Hong Kong
I don't want to go
Matsumoto Hamada has finally landed in Hong Kong
It's going to be a difficult journey
I'm on Neyzan Road
Neyzan Road
Hong Kong's main street is crowded with people and shops
I'm scared of signs
That's funny
It's different
It's the opposite
It's the worst
It's not funny
Don't say it's not funny
If you say it's not funny, everyone will laugh
You said it's not funny
What are you doing?
Stop it
I'm going to kill you
Don't fight
Hey
I only brought one pose
What is one pose?
Look at him
He's wearing a mask
What are you doing?
Everyone is laughing
Stop it
You have to be strong
I can't adjust
You can't be like this
That's right
It's your fault
Stop it
Stop hitting me
What?
Stop it
It's your fault
I'm going to die
Why am I going to die?
The trip to Hong Kong is called by the manager, Hokamoto
They finally arrive at their first destination
We're here
What are you doing?
I want to show you something
What?
Hokamoto's Happening New Year
This is going to be popular
It's going to be
I'm going to do it now
Let's enjoy the night in Hong Kong
They go to the roof of the building
I'm going to do it now
You'll know when you see it
What is this?
Hokamoto's Happening New Year
It's going to be popular
Really?
It's not going to be popular if you don't see it
It's going to be popular
I'll do it with the light
It's messed up
You can't mess it up
I'm going to do it now
Go over there
Hong Kong
It's better to do it in the back
The location
This one?
It's here
Tell me when you get there
I do that sometimes
Don't say that!
Say it properly!
Yes, I will.
Let's go.
The title is...
AOKAMOTO HAPPENING!
Here we are!
Touch it!
AOKAMOTO HAPPENING!
You did a great job!
It looks like a flower is falling.
I'm taking off my slippers.
You did a great job!
It's beautiful!
Let's go.
Why are you so pale?
I don't want to get off here.
They are taken to the best restaurant in Hong Kong.
Let's have a toast and eat what you like.
Cheers!
It's my first time.
Please enjoy the food.
AOKAMOTO HAPPENING!
I don't want to drink anymore.
Are you serious?
What are you doing?
Go home!
Can I go home now?
You can go home.
You can go home now.
We will do our best.
We are very young.
What is your way of thinking?
It's rare these days.
I feel bad.
Don't say that you feel bad coming to Hong Kong.
I don't want to go home.
I can't lose.
Thank you.
I don't want to drink anymore.
What's the problem?
What are you going to do with the ketchup?
I will wash my hands.
You don't have to do that.
It's so delicious.
It's delicious.
You should eat 5 pieces.
I don't want to eat anymore.
I'm worried about you.
I eat 5 pieces.
You will be hungry at night.
I eat 4 pieces.
Please eat 4 pieces.
I will eat 6 pieces.
I can't eat anymore.
Why?
This is the main dish today.
This is the most expensive dish in Hong Kong.
You eat almost all of this.
This is like a broadcast ban.
You should eat this dish.
You have changed.
You are surprised.
I can't eat it all at once.
I can only eat it like this.
This is a great dish, isn't it?
Since we're at a good restaurant, I can't ask you to look at it.
I'd like you to get on the boat and say,
I can't do it.
Absolutely.
If I say it again, will you tell me?
Of course.
Mr. Okamoto, you're late.
You're late.
Come and look at it.
I'll be back.
The tempo is bad.
When did you say that?
He didn't say anything.
Did you go somewhere, Okamoto?
Come and look at it.
Yes.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You're too fast.
I'm sorry about the meal.
Mr. Okamoto is angry again.
He's calling me.
I'm sorry.
Why?
We've been eating together for a while.
He called me and told me to bring it right away.
Mr. Okamoto left.
Where did he go?
I'm sorry.
You're in a good mood.
Did anyone say anything?
No.
It's only natural for Jimmy to be angry.
That's right.
He goes to the place that Okamoto has designated.
He's going to be fired if he goes to Japan.
That's a good thing.
I don't think he can manage it.
He's the only one.
He's doing his best for himself.
He wasn't like that when we first arrived.
He wasn't like that at all.
He was a good boy.
He couldn't do anything.
When did he start to behave like that?
He started to behave like that.
He started to behave like that when he said he picked up a kitten.
I knew it.
He started to behave like that when he said he didn't need clothes.
He said it was warm when he saw a kitten.
It's obviously strange.
Obviously.
Are we there yet?
We're almost there.
We're almost there?
We're on top of the mountain.
We're on top of the observatory.
Observatory.
Okamoto is waiting for Takadai to see the night view of Hong Kong worth 1 million dollars.
What's going to happen?
This way, please.
I don't understand.
What's wrong with you?
I'm going to kill you.
Why are you going to kill me?
I want to eat noodles.
Why don't you come back to the hotel?
Look at this.
The night view is beautiful.
It's beautiful.
Why is it beautiful?
What?
I don't understand why you're angry.
Why?
Is it beautiful?
It's beautiful.
Why is it beautiful?
I'll show you.
The real night view.
What is this?
It's cool.
Why are you laughing?
I'm sorry.
It's really cool.
I don't understand why you're laughing.
Why are you laughing?
Yes.
Okamoto is waiting for Takadai to see the night view of Hong Kong worth 1 million dollars.
It's a lie.
I'll show you.
Aoyama.
Don't say it's beautiful.
I finally understand the meaning.
Will this view change?
It will change.
I'll show you the real night view.
I think it's beautiful.
It's dirty.
It's not beautiful.
I'm angry.
I'll show you.
It's not dirty.
It's really beautiful.
I'm saying it's dirty.
You should check it out.
Hello.
I can't hear you.
Can I touch it?
You gave it to me.
Put a switch in it.
I'm touching it.
You're touching it.
Hello.
I can hear you.
I'll call you.
I got it.
Look at it.
What are you doing?
It's dirty.
Finally, Okamoto will show you the real night view.
He's waiting for manager Okamoto's night view setting.
I'm back.
Why are you here?
He doesn't like it.
I'm here to borrow it.
You go.
I'm here to borrow the car.
Okamoto, you can't be gone like this.
Why is it so dirty?
It's dirty.
No, it's not dirty.
It's not dirty.
I'm going to beat you!
No, no, no.
No.
I'm going to do it until you apologize.
I'm talking about the technique.
Technique?
This...
Jabu...
Jabu?
It's definitely not going to work.
I'm confident.
Jabu is amazing.
That's a great decision.
If Jabu comes to me,
I'll just go and hit him.
I'm not that small.
I'm going to beat you up.
That's funny.
He has to wait for an hour.
I'm going to beat you up.
That's too much.
What is it?
I'm going to beat you up.
What did you say at first?
I'm going to do it again.
Okay.
I'm going to beat you up.
That's stupid.
Where are you?
I'm here.
I don't know where you are.
Where?
I'm going to show you now.
You're still beautiful.
I hope you come.
I'm scared.
I'm going to beat you up.
What did you say at first?
That's stupid.
I'm going to beat you up.
What is it?
Something is shining.
Something is moving.
What is it?
It's hard to tell if it's on or off.
Can you tell?
Something is moving.
Can you tell if it's on or off?
It's off.
It's on.
I don't know what it is.
Mr. Okamoto.
I'm doing it.
What?
That's enough.
It's not enough.
You're talking too much.
Yes.
Don't talk too much.
What is it?
What should we do?
It's beautiful.
You should look at it closer.
Do you mean we should go there?
Come here quickly.
What do you mean?
It's annoying.
I'm going.
Please wait.
It's annoying.
I'm going.
Please wait.
They go to the high-rise building where Mr. Okamoto is waiting.
Let's do Magical Banana together.
Can I do it?
Yes.
Magical Banana.
If you say banana, it's yellow.
Let's start with banana.
If you say yellow, it's banana.
No.
I said banana once.
If you say banana once, it's no good.
Did you understand?
Yes.
It's really annoying.
Let's start with you.
Magical Banana.
If you say banana, it's long.
If you say long, it's string.
If you say string, it's string.
If you say string, it hurts.
If you say it hurts, it's SM.
If you say SM, it's scary.
If you say scary, it's ghost.
If you say ghost, it disappears.
If you say disappear, it's eraser.
If you say eraser, it's pencil.
If you say pencil, it's HB.
If you say HB, it's coffee.
If you say coffee, it's makeup.
If you say makeup, it's red.
If you say red, it's lipstick.
If you say lipstick, it breaks.
If you say break, it's chopstick.
If you say chopstick, it's eat.
If you say eat, it's satiety.
If you say satiety, it's sleep.
If you say satiety, it's nightmare.
It hurts.
It's funny.
I don't know how to say nightmare.
I was told it's funny.
What Okamoto is waiting for is a lively moment in Hong Kong.
Times Square is in the center of the city of young people.
Mr. Okamoto.
Yes.
I'm downstairs, so I'll go upstairs.
Call me.
I'm angry.
I'm being pulled around.
I'm tired.
I'm tired, so I'm going home.
What?
I'm tired.
I'm tired, so I'm going home.
I'm going up.
I'm going up?
I'm scared of climbing the ladder, so I'm going home.
Don't be scared.
I heard your name.
Really?
I'm going home.
Don't go home.
I don't like this.
No one's coming.
I'm going.
It's too slow to climb.
I'm scared.
This is tough.
There are a lot of people.
Take it easy.
Yamazaki, be careful.
I'm fine.
That's dangerous.
I'm scared.
Yamazaki.
I'm fine.
I'm scared.
What are you doing?
My head.
I don't do small things.
That's right.
I'm scared.
I'm scared because it's shining.
That's amazing.
You shouldn't climb any higher.
I want to be the most beautiful woman in Okamoto.
What are you doing?
Don't move.
If you get too close, it'll be hard to see.
Stop joking around.
You can see it, right?
I can see it.
It's completely different from that picture.
It's very similar to that picture.
Let's go home.
What are you doing?
I was holding back my laughter.
I can't hold back my laughter anymore.
I let go of the switch.
My heart cooled down.
I can't go home.
Leaving Okamoto behind,
Ichido heads to Hong Kong at night.
I don't know what's going on.
I'm scared.
Since we're in the north,
let's get something to drink in Hong Kong.
What is this?
Japanese sake?
Is it like sake?
I don't know what Japanese sake is.
What kind of sake is this?
It's so dark.
Try drinking it.
You can drink it, right?
What's wrong?
It's burnt.
I don't know.
You have no guts.
Can you drink it?
I can drink it.
I have no guts.
Can you drink it?
I can drink it.
Let me see.
Don't drink too much.
You can't run away.
What should I do?
It's burnt.
Tea, tea, tea.
Don't drink too much.
You have no guts.
Let me see.
Don't do that.
I don't know.
Demi, you're amazing.
You're amazing.
I'm not like you.
Drink it and go.
Stop it.
Let's have a match.
Here.
Demi, you're amazing.
Let's have a match next time.
Look at this.
60 degrees.
Let's go.
Stop it.
Don't say such a thing.
Demi, you're amazing.
Let me see.
Let's go.
You're amazing.
Why are you eating?
Don't drink too much.
Hello, friends.
The clams are good, aren't they?
This is a dried ginger.
It's delicious.
Have you ever eaten it?
Here you are.
It's delicious, isn't it?
I'll eat the scorpion first.
Here you are.
I'll eat the scorpion one by one.
I'll eat it.
Are you going to eat it or not?
Go away.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
Hey.
I got it.
It's hot.
Stop it.
Be careful.
It smells like poop.
Go away.
What are you saying?
Are you drunk?
Let's eat more.
Don't cry.
You shouldn't cry.
He is laughing.
I don't know if he is drunk.
I'll give you a chance.
Let's eat the scorpion.
Read it.
It's easy.
The scorpion.
I thought you would do that.
I can't broadcast it.
It's over.
What is this?
It's a scorpion.
It looks like this.
You can't eat this.
There is a tree in it.
It looks like a poster of the election.
Here you are.
It's cold.
I have to do Yamasaki.
You.
Smile.
It's delicious.
That's enough.
You can't do that.
I won.
You are not good at this.
The night in Hong Kong is getting darker.
The sun is rising.
The wind blows through the continent.
The morning in Hong Kong is early.
Good morning.
It's 7.30 in the morning.
I'm in room 732.
Who is sleeping?
Let's go.
Cameraman.
What is this?
I took off my underwear here.
I took a bath here.
What is this?
This is a pouch that I put on my shoulder before shooting.
It's thick.
What is this?
Good morning.
You are the best.
Ouch.
What is this?
It was a prank.
It's strange.
Why?
What is this?
It was a prank.
You are funny.
You look like a murderer.
This is half.
It's okay.
Let's take a bath together.
Come here.
I was surprised.
This is half.
This is nothing.
I think I will be bitten by a bug.
I got it.
Let's take a bath together.
You two look like new stars.
I will be bitten by a bug.
I think I will be bitten by a bug.
Please watch this video.
Why didn't you appear in the report?
You should have been bitten by a bug.
I think I will be bitten by a bug.
I want you to wake up.
What do you mean?
You are very vital.
I don't understand.
I want you to wake up.
Let's go.
He is in this room.
I want you to wake up.
Why is it messy?
Let's go to the bathroom.
It doesn't change much.
I didn't see the TV.
Did you sleep there?
Why don't you sleep like this?
Why don't you use the bed efficiently?
Old man.
What is this?
It's funny.
It was funny when I was sleeping.
You are not good at it.
Old man, why don't you sleep with me?
I want you to wake up.
Why don't you sleep with me?
It's messy.
I want you to wake up.
Both were funny.
Old man.
Old man, why don't you sleep with me?
Sorry, sorry
What do you mean?
What are you doing?
I'm telling you, it's not over yet
I have a scar on my belly
Look at him
You should stop
Look at him, he's stuck
It's rock climbing
You know what I want to do in Hong Kong
I don't know
What a big face
I'll do Kulon, Okamoto, Horoyoi and Hashigo
Kulon, Okamoto, Horoyoi and Hashigo
What's that?
I know
I'll do as you say
Okamoto goes to the blue sea to transform into a dragon
Okamoto, what are you doing?
Hi
Hello
I'll be back soon
Watch me
The bridge is narrow
I can go to the sky
You can go there
No way
Hey
He said so
Watch me
Where are you going?
To the sky
We can go home now
Let's get caught
Let's go
Watch me
Okamoto transforms into a dragon and dances to the sky
You are like a male
You scared me
You are cold
I'll do it now
Let's go
What are you doing?
Are you sleeping?
Studying
I'm not tired
I'm tired
No, I'm fine
You are like a baton
Let's go
What are you doing?
I don't know
Ready?
It's spicy
Don't say it's spicy
He is a fool
You are like a dragon
Let's go
Ouch
I hit your face
I hit your face with that bamboo
Your head is in the way
Try to swim without your head
Without my head?
I'll do it
Watch me
I'm going to die
Oh my god
That was scary
I climbed the sky
Let's do it again
Let's dive and swim
I think we can do it
You are right
I know you want to go from the top
I'm going to try
Where are you going?
I'm going to sink
You can't do that
It's so spicy
You should dive and hold the bamboo
What should I do?
You said you wanted to do it
I was listening to you
I can't do anything
You can do whatever you want
I can do anything
I'm going to go
What?
He's doing it
He's doing it in order
You are so annoying
Look at your dirty face
Let's go home
It's not good
I'm sad
I was watching you
I wanted to ask you what pose you want
I'm so sad
He's calculating
I want this pose
I want to show my sadness
I'm so sad
Don't make me laugh
Wan Chai
Wan Chai is a small town in Hong Kong
Manager Okamoto Kireru is done
Okamoto, let's go for a walk
Let's go for a walk
How about going this way?
Let's go for a walk in Hong Kong
I don't want to go
I don't want to go back to Japan
I was waiting for you
Let's go home
You have dirty feet
My towel is dirty
It's OK
I'm not good at acting
I can't use scissors
I'm sorry
The mirror is next to you
It's delicious
It's amazing
I don't have scissors
It's Hong Kong cut
I can't hold it
I can't experience it
It's delicious
I don't have scissors
How many years have you been doing this?
I've been doing this for a few years
57 years
I don't care
I have a dog-like reaction
I don't care if the chair is burnt
Do you want me to do it?
No, I'm already
What?
Let's drink a little
It's not over yet
Okay
Good
You are a man
Okay
Let's go
Thank you father