When I woke up this morning, I had a headache.
I'm wearing a sun mask.
But the staff called me.
What I'm going to do today is...
I'm going to use today's drawing.
If you look at this, you can see how the opening project is going to develop in the future.
That's what I'm going to show you today.
That's all I have to say.
Let's take a look at the development of the drawing.
Let's go!
Gaki no Tsukai Aki-Fuyu Opening Project Sagi-Dori Collection
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
While talking about the history of Gaki no Tsukai, we must never forget about the competition.
And this is the most recent competition.
This is the biggest game of this century.
Hamada vs. Matsumoto Hoka.
The dream golf competition!
Hamada has absolute confidence in his golf skills.
This is a golf competition against Matsumoto Hoka.
Hamada's first shot is as good as Matsumoto Hoka's four shots.
As everyone says, Hamada's first shot is a nice shot.
Matsumoto is afraid of his opponent's expression.
When I get punished, my shoulders get tired.
I want to relax my shoulders.
Are you okay?
Hey, you're going too high.
Matsumoto's first shot.
No, no, don't fall.
Next is Tanaka.
Okay, I flew.
Where did you go?
The course.
It's open.
Is it free space?
What is that?
What is free space?
On the other hand, Hamada has a long shot.
Three on.
Where did you go?
It's open.
No way.
Really?
He missed the par, but it's the fifth.
Nice, nice.
Amazing.
However,
Since he missed the par and it's the fifth, we're okay with 20, right?
Okay.
I'll hit it 12 more times.
12 times at this distance.
Okay, okay.
I'll hit it and I'll close it.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Team Matsumoto in the first hole wins easily.
Next is the second hole.
Hamada is the first to try to turn the tables.
However, he missed the par and it's the OB.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
A rematch tee shot.
Where did you go?
It's over there.
Team Matsumoto in the second hole wins.
Wait, wait.
It's a practice shot.
Really?
Really, really, really.
It's a practice shot, right?
I'll go.
Okay.
Yes.
Team Matsumoto in the second hole wins.
Thank you very much.
It's finally the final hole.
Team Matsumoto is mercilessly attacking Hamada.
Okay.
It's good.
I'm good, right?
Amazing.
And Hamada's pad is...
Wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
In the end, Hamada couldn't win even once.
After this, he started crying and added one more hole.
Go down there.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh.
Hamada's ball was hated by the cup.
It's a four-time loss.
Team Matsumoto has won.
So.
Yes.
Hamada, you're out.
Yeah.
Yes, yes.
Three months later.
It's Akiko.
What is it?
No, no, no, no.
Go to Okanto, Hollywood and play Titanic.
The penalty game is determined by the love scene of Titanic.
The sky and the machine are waiting for me in the sky.
Hamada finished the hard penalty game.
A bomb came out of his mouth.
Excuse me.
Yes.
How about doing it again?
No, it's okay.
It's okay.
It doesn't matter what time it is.
Yes.
Let's improve the rules again.
Are you going to improve the rules?
No, I have to improve that.
Who will win the next game?
And what is the penalty game of the trial?
Hamada VS Matsumoto vs Golf Reunion
The next episode is coming soon.
Please look forward to it.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Downtown is famous for its sound when it appears in the talk.
Looking back at the history of the Gaki no Tsukai 9 years,
various songs have been used so far.
And recently,
Matsumoto Hitoshi's song has been used.
It is Taxi Driver.
My heart is swaying.
My love is swaying.
I am a taxi driver.
Taxi Driver.
Hey, stop it.
After this, the program recruited an artist to sing the famous song Taxi Driver.
And then...
Finally, a musician.
I'm so happy.
Please come on stage.
This is the artist.
It's Sharankyu.
The name was given by the mega hit band Sharankyu.
Osaka is a comic band.
I'm so happy.
Your eyes are swimming today.
I'm going to play the drums today.
I thought I had to.
I'm so happy.
The members immediately joined the sound.
The field has been shaking its neck.
I wonder what happened to it.
That's funny.
Sharankyu-san.
Yes.
What's going on?
I'm checking the lyrics of the song.
I've never seen it before.
I'm a little confused.
I see.
It takes a lot of time.
I'm sorry.
Don't ruin my image.
It doesn't matter if it's messed up.
I'll show you what it's like.
It's hard to get in.
I'm a little confused.
Yes.
Show it to me.
I don't know at all.
Ina Homo.
This is it.
Which one?
This one.
Believe in yourself.
Yes.
This is how the taxi driver Sharankyu version was completed.
I'm a taxi driver.
I'm all right.
We're still looking for musicians to sing for us.
We're waiting for your call.
The most luxurious luxury project with a child's user.
A celebrity fishing competition where famous talents come together.
Are you ready?
We're going to start.
Don't be ashamed.
Let's do our best.
Let's go.
I'm glad I have a job.
The first time started four years ago in Kawaguchiko, Fumoto, Fujino.
Among the members, Matsumoto was the first hit.
It's coming.
I'm getting impatient.
I've been fishing for a long time.
But after this, no one gets a hit.
I'll get a hit.
Liar.
In the second half, Itoi finally got a hit.
It's over.
It's coming.
And Okuda got a hit.
This is good.
The game was narrowed down to the three of Okuda and Itoi Matsumoto.
27.
8.
28.
But it's 7.
I'm getting impatient.
It's just 7.
That means...
Matsumoto wins the first game.
The first game was a success for Matsumoto.
The second game was a success for Matsumoto.
This man won the first game.
That means...
Matsumoto wins the second game.
I got a hit.
In the third game, the guests get a hit.
Two people from downtown are left behind.
In the meantime, Itoi said something.
I know how scary they are, so I won't say anything.
And the next moment.
It's coming.
That's good.
It's big, isn't it?
As expected of a defending champion.
Will Matsumoto's hit three times in a row work?
It's 36.
36.
It's dangerous.
What does that mean?
37 centimeters.
Itoi wins.
I'm so happy
He won 3 times in a row
This is so frustrating
The 4th Fishing Championship was held this summer
Everyone except Hamada and Enuchi won the first half
It's over
I have a bad feeling about this
But in the second half, Hamada, who was aiming for a comeback, won
I did it
Second time
This is bad
Enuchi, who was in a hurry, won right before the end
He applauded the winning battle
And the results were announced
He won 3 times in a row
This time, the winner is Hamada
Thank you
A terrifying downturn
He won 3 times in a row
Is it okay to leave Hamada like this?
I'm a TV entertainer who likes fishing
Come anytime
We are waiting for all the entertainers who like fishing
Stop it
Until now, Gaki no Tsukai has been broadcasting the battle of rivals for many years
Among them, there are two people who are called the most passionate and eternal rivals
Yamazaki Hosei vs. Moriman
Their fate began two years ago with Yamazaki's humiliating defeat in the Panty Trigger Battle
After that, Yamazaki was completely defeated in the second match
Even in the third match, Yamazaki was defeated by Moriman until the end of the Panty Trigger Battle
Yamazaki collapsed into the ring with a scream and showed a miserable appearance
And again, Yamazaki challenged Moriman
The match was held in Korakuen Hall, the holy place of martial arts
Yamazaki met Moriman
Yamazaki vs. Moriman
Yamazaki-san! Yamazaki-san! Yamazaki-san! This is interesting!
Yamazaki, who couldn't be honest in the fourth match, ran away from the ring
Yamazaki vs. Moriman
And finally, the final match was decided
What kind of finale will the long battle be?
Yamazaki vs. Moriman
The last Final Revenge Match
The day when the gong rings is near
The comedians start with high tension and end with high tension
First, let's watch this
High tension is the greatest weapon of comedians
Yamazaki vs. Moriman
First, this week's 10th place is
50 points
Kogoriko Spartandi vs. Naoki Tanaka
Let's watch this week's 3rd place
Fujii Takashi vs. Otoko to Onna wa Chigau
Otoko to Onna wa Chigau
This week's 1st place
Kogoriko Endo Shouzou vs. Yoshi
From now on
I will
do it
I want to eat
corn
eat
I want to eat
Tackle
Rubble
Look at your voice
I'll eat
At Gaki's conversion
We're hiring a great comedian who will bring you tremendous high tension
Get ready
High Tension Game
Up until now, Gaki no Tsukai has filed a lawsuit for various suspicions
and has passed judgement under a fair trial.
This is it!
It's so natural!
And now, here is the lawsuit that is the biggest problem with Gaki.
High Tension Game
From Tadayama, we will now begin the High Tension Game with Akihiro Ohnuma.
Gaki, the famous director, Akihiro Ohnuma.
The trial began with the accusation that this man, who looks like he has two sides to him,
is actually a real high tension guy and is a nuisance to the people around him.
High Tension Game
From Tadayama, we will now begin the High Tension Game with Akihiro Ohnuma.
That was when we were filming in Yoshinoya.
Yes, I remember this.
After the filming, the producer received a beef bowl from someone at the restaurant.
Hey, you guys! I received a beef bowl!
Share it with everyone!
Yay! I did it!
Ohnuma, who was watching the scene, caught the AD.
Hey, what did you receive earlier?
It was a beef bowl from Yoshinoya.
Give it to me. Give it to me.
Surprisingly, the AD took the beef bowl from him.
That night...
Today, we are going to eat out. Hurry up and get ready.
Yay! I did it!
The destination they arrived at was Yoshinoya.
And of course, the payment will be...
Please pay with this Tadaken.
How many tickets will you take?
I will take all the tickets I received.
All of them? All of them?
All of them?
I have something else to tell you.
Ohnuma also received a beef bowl.
What? Wait a minute.
I can't accept this.
What do you mean?
This is too much.
What do you mean? How many tickets did you receive?
50,000 yen.
Please announce the verdict.
The defendant, Ohnuma, has caused a lot of trouble to the people.
Therefore, there is no room for defense.
The verdict is...
He will dance on the street.
Ohnuma was sentenced to one year in prison.
However, the program is still looking for a witness for Ohnuma.
If the director of Ohnuma has caused any damage, please let us know.
The program is still looking for Ohnuma.
And finally, this announcement.
I will come to see you again.
I will come to see the people of downtown again.
Thank you very much. It was fun.
The famous people who want to see the talk of downtown live.
Please come to play anytime.
So, Gakky will have a golf match.
And Yamazaki vs. Moriman match.
I want to do it more and more in the future.
I was suddenly called out by Yue.
Please look forward to it.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.