Ladies and gentlemen.
I have something to tell you.
Yes.
It seems like...
It's not working.
Did you meet someone special?
Yes, I met someone special the other day.
Oh, really?
Yes.
It's been a long time since I went to ***.
Well...
It's like this.
I don't get excited when I meet the same people.
You don't know that?
Who doesn't know that?
When I go to the same place, I meet the same people.
It's not interesting.
You went to a different place.
Yes, I went to a different place.
This is amazing.
You developed it.
There was a guy like this.
I like him.
My mother does it.
Well...
How should I say it?
God's hand.
Yes.
It looks good.
God's finger.
It looks really good.
I was wondering what kind of guy he was.
He was told that he was an old lady.
Well, he was an old lady.
But he had a lot of technique.
He must have been greedy.
I was excited.
But he came.
A Colombian came.
I can't speak Japanese.
You can't speak Japanese.
You can't speak Japanese at all.
I can't communicate with them.
You can't communicate with them at all.
Moreover, they bring a lot of tools.
Yes.
They have a lot of tools.
The tools for pleasure.
Yes.
But they are useless.
Colombians are useless.
Hello.
This is my first time.
I don't know anything.
Don't do that.
I don't know what's going on.
He came.
He told me that he came.
He brought something like baby oil from his pocket.
Baby oil is sold in convenience stores.
Yes.
He brought only one in his pocket.
He put two on the bed.
He brought baby oil and told me to go to bed.
He said, I don't need this for now.
I don't need clothes.
He took off everything.
You should go home.
Why do you want me to do that?
I went to bed.
I went to Colombia.
Bang!
I put baby oil on my chest.
It's not a persimmon.
Bang!
I was surprised.
I pushed it out.
It's not a persimmon.
I said, I don't know what's going on.
He put baby oil on my legs.
Bang!
I pushed it out.
It hurts!
I said that for the first time.
You should go home.
Did you go to Itao?
I went to Itao.
A woman came to me.
She was holding baby oil in her hand.
What woman?
A Japanese woman.
She was the mother of the child.
I don't play guitar.
Has anything happened to you?
Not much.
Well...
I have insomnia.
Really?
Yes.
Wow!
You didn't tell me the whole story.
You said you have insomnia.
Why?
I don't know.
I don't sleep well.
I'm like an old man.
I'm like this.
Why do you do that?
I don't know.
You're mean.
You're like this.
I have insomnia.
I don't know.
Why do you do that?
You read too fast.
I'm going to have a baby soon.
Why do you always clean the pot at night?
I want to clean myself more and more.
Please tell me, Mr. Matsumoto.
When you meet your friends in the morning, you say,
Good morning.
But when you meet your friends again in the afternoon,
How do you say hello?
You say, Hello.
I understand that.
I'll tell you one thing.
For example, I said good morning.
I took a class in a different class.
I happened to be in the hallway for a break.
I said, Good morning.
Why?
That's strange.
Don't say that.
It's strange.
Where are you going?
To the science room.
It's strange.
I don't like that kind of meaningless conversation.
I'm asking you where you're going.
I wanted to tell you this before.
For example, there's downtown deluxe.
There's a lot of people there.
I don't like talking to other celebrities.
That's why you don't have any friends.
In the entertainment world.
That's a relationship.
I don't want to answer that kind of question.
I don't know anything about giants.
That's why you're always looking at people from the outside.
That's not good.
Why do you look at me when I'm talking?
I'm not looking at you like this.
That's not good.
The taxi driver says,
I lost to a giant.
I'm not interested in baseball.
It doesn't matter if the giant loses.
You don't have to say that.
The air in the taxi is just like now.
That's true.
I can only hear the sound of the air.
The air is bad.
When I was a kid, my father had a reverse pattern.
I was in a taxi.
What happened to the driver's body today?
He ignored me.
That's not good.
Stop it!
Grab it from behind.
It depends on the driver's back.
That's not good.
My father has a reverse pattern.
Matsumoto has a secret pocket on his body.
He has a man's seven tools.
What is a man's seven tools?
I have a man's seven tools.
Do you have a secret pocket?
No, I don't have a secret pocket.
Really?
Where?
I don't have a secret pocket.
You don't have a secret pocket?
I have a secret pocket.
You think you know me, don't you?
You don't know 15% of me.
You don't know the other 85% of me.
What's in it?
First of all, a condom.
A man's seven tools.
And a brush.
A brush?
A thin brush.
Like a brush.
And...
A tissue.
And a candle.
A candle.
And...
A lotion.
What kind of shop are you in?
What's that?
That's not a man's seven tools.
It's a business's seven tools.
Is that bad?
That's scary.
You can't put that much powder in there.
You'll get caught.
I got it.
If a bat throws a towel, why does it cling to it and fall with it?
They live in telepathy.
If a bat comes, it'll cling to it.
Why?
It has to be a bat.
It'll cling to anything.
In the end, bats look like that.
They care about things.
So if you throw it, it's no good.
If you throw it, it's no good.
Maybe.
It's called a bat.
They're kind.
Just one bullet can reach them all.
But if you don't have one, scattered bats would come.
Before as well,
If you don't have one, scattered bats would come.
before as well,
In New York, there was a horse riding on the street.
It was an officer.
It 심ed like that as well.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Even in that situation,
the horse is walking on the asphalt.
And at that moment,
it's moving like this.
While walking,
it's not a round-shaped horse.
It's definitely a horse!
I don't know about that.
I don't think it's a horse.
Let's say I'm a horse.
This is my first day,
so please take care of me.
The asphalt is moving like this.
I'm a horse, so I'm stupid.
It's moving like this.
I'll do it.
I'll do it until the second day.
On the third day,
I'll be like,
what?
Everyone doesn't like it.
That's because,
I don't know if it's a horse or not.
But I can't go to the horse race
on my own will.
I have to endure it.
I don't want to do it.
It's a bother.
I'll keep on doing it.
I'll be like,
this is really painful.
I'm so angry,
but I can't do it.
The horse is on my back.
The horse is on your back.
I'll be like,
I'll do it here.
I can't do it there.
If you touch me like that,
then, it's smart.
That's right.
No matter what,
I'll be in the back.
I'll go.
The horse is in my back.
But I can't endure it.
I've been doing it for a long time, but it's getting slower and slower.
This guy is strange.
No, no, that's strange.
You should remove it by yourself.
If you can do it by yourself, you can put it on again.
That's it.
That's all you can do.
What?
It's a full-zone button.
That's strange.
I don't know.
You have to think about it.
I don't think you can do it.
I don't know if you're going to use exhaust gas.
I don't think so.
I don't think you can do it by yourself.
I don't think you can do it at home.
That's a bad thing.
That's why I'm telling you to stop.
What are you talking about?
That's why I'm telling you.
I'm going to take you.