I won the tournament and got 300,000 yen
2 hours of shocking live broadcast
The national tournament
Everyone is doing their best
Buy what you like
I see
I'm a poor guy
You don't have much
Buy what you like
Because it sucks
You are laughing
But I have a tip
You have to have something you can have
I'll ask you why you want this
You may be rejected
If you drop it once, it will be returned
Of course
I'll start now
You have 15 minutes
What?
No way
I'll tell you what's in the south
I'll go to the south
Only B1
The winner is
B1
Let's go to the south
Sugajyan is out
I'll return this ball
It may be Sugajyan again
Sugajyan is good
Tell me what you want
B1
What is it?
TV
There should be a TV at home
Why do you want a TV?
It's old
It's a box
It's big
Let's go
This is bigger
I can't hold it
It's 135,000 yen
Study more
I don't need it
It's 135,000 yen
B1
You should choose
Otomo
How many times do you want to go?
Let's go to the 4th floor
I'll go to the 1st floor
Are you okay?
B1
Sugai
Let's get closer
B1
Stop it
It's a matter of time
This one
B1
Why did you choose the suit?
I'm going to get married
Are you sure?
B1
You should go to your parents
You were married
If you say so
B1
I don't need it
This is the second time
B1
Otomo
Stop it
B1
Otomo will be happy
I'll go to the 1st floor
Who's next?
B1
What should I do?
Let's go to the 5th floor
B1
Are you tired?
I couldn't wait
Wait
Why did you choose the suit?
B1
Isn't this cool?
Why did you choose the watch?
I don't know
B1
Wait
Why did you choose the watch?
It's a watch for kids
B1
What are you doing?
Wait
Let's go to the 7th floor
I don't know
No way
B1
What do you want?
I want a carpet
B2
Do you have B3?
B2 is fine
Should I buy 5?
B3
B3?
B3 is fine too
B3
I'll buy you a carpet
I can do this
You should walk
B3
Do you understand?
I don't know
Did you wear it?
No
B3
No way
I want you to wear it
Try next
Sorry
What?
It has nothing to do with you
You are sweating
Please
What the hell is that?
Is that Akano?
That's enough. Let's move on to the next one.
Alright!
Come on!
Tsuttsun.
You call this Tsuttsun?
Six times.
Who's next? Tsuttsun?
Where are you going?
Six times.
Six times?
Hurry up!
What?
Umobuton?
I've never been in Umobuton.
Because it's Gimboni.
I can't take this home.
But it looks light.
It's a five-point set.
Umobuton?
It looks light.
I can't take this home.
I've never slept in Umobuton when I was a kid.
Umobuton, five-point set, 68,000 yen.
Kotaro.
Can one person take this home?
It looks light.
This is wrong.
The color is different.
I've never slept in Umobuton when I was a kid.
I came up with a new game.
What kind of game?
This is for work or for school.
Why do you do that for school?
It's for fun.
It's very popular in America.
That kind of fun.
Are you going to say it?
Say it.
I can't teach you for free.
You know, there was a game like tag.
We can do it easily.
Is that kind of game?
It doesn't cost money at all.
It's very popular.
Say it.
I can't teach you for free.
You're going to do it right away?
Yes.
Teach me the new game.
I can't teach you that way.
It makes me feel bad.
When you want to teach someone something,
you have to use a pinhole.
I'll stop you.
Well,
sing a song.
What?
Make a song with ad-libs.
The lyrics.
It's very popular in America.
Are you guys having fun?
Three minutes later.
It's coming.
Do you really think so?
You look like a fool.
You.
Why?
Why do you look like that?
May I?
I'll go first.
I like you.
You have to sing
the lyrics of
I like you.
You have to sing the lyrics of
Go ahead.
I like you.
From the day we met.
It's okay.
Be more strict.
Hit me.
From the beginning.
Let's go.
Shrimp.
Wait a minute.
From the beginning.
Forever.
Go, go.
I like you.
Hit me.
Forever.
Go, go.
I like you.
Forever.
Go, go.
I like you.
What are you doing?
This is an Apache baseball.
Go.
Teach me from the beginning.
You always forget the beginning.
Forever.
That's right.
Go, go.
I like you.
At that time, she wears a uniform.
I wear a uniform, too.
Forever.
Go, go.
Wait a minute. Is this funny?
No, it's very funny.
What happens after all?
If you forget something, you lose.
Your father loses.
I'll do it.
If it's you, I'll do it.
It's a very good family.
Even at night.
You.
Why?
Is it because of that?
I like you.
My mother says so, too.
Let's change the subject.
You're cool.
You're a man.
Hey, it's like Fujiko Fujio F wrote it.
You're not a man.
For example, if there's a girl like me in the car.
If there's a girl like me in the car.
You're in the car and you're looking at her?
I think she's a cute girl.
I'll do it.
I like you.
How do you get on?
Can you break up so easily?
Do you get off the car with a car?
Sometimes and sometimes not.
It's just that.
The fashion of women is popular these days.
Women are wearing these boots.
Really?
I don't like that.
I like it when I'm wearing it.
I'll give you a house.
My house is like this.
It's like a person's front door.
Any woman can get cold.
When I go to the bathroom, I have to go through the front door.
When I go through the front door, I look at her.
She's sleeping.
When I look at her, I pull her.
Is it just me?
Don't make a big deal out of it.
Sometimes it's like this.
That's not true.
You should definitely stop being a girl.
You're wearing those boots.
I'm taking you home.
What's the problem?
I'll take you home.
Your way of thinking is strange.
What should I wear if I wear those boots?
I can't help it if I have a ray gun.
It's definitely strange.
There's a car that looks like a future car.
What should I wear if I wear those boots?
Full-body tights.
I can't help it if I wear full-body tights.
That's the problem.
It's strange.
There's a woman's short cut.
There aren't any men who like short cuts.
Look at her short hair.
Poor thing.
I'm sorry, but that's how it is.
Why do you hate it?
It's a woman's short cut.
That's how it is.
I see.
It looks good on you.
If you cut your hair short, it means you're a woman.
If you cut your hair short, it means you're taking care of your father.
No, no, no.
It means you're doing the same thing.
You have to stop it.
There's no such thing as a short cut.
Let's be careful.
What? Boots?
Boots, boots.
I see.
Tell me what to do.
I'm hungry.
Why do you put a lid on the toilet?
I put a lid on the toilet after I pooped.
That's why it stinks.
But it's like this.
It's like a firefly.
But it's only a firefly.
There's no one who closes the lid.
I'll close it.
It's the principle of the lid.
That means it stinks when you open the lid.
That's not true.
After you pooped, the next person came in.
Hama-chan, it doesn't stink.
As expected of Hama-chan.
What do you mean?
Nice batting.
When you open the lid, the real Hama-chan comes in.
The real Hama-chan of the concert comes in.
It's a long concert.
How do you poop at that time?
What's the purpose?
I don't know.
Let's go to the next one.
Please tell me how to distinguish between a male and a female.
How do you distinguish?
First of all, it's wrong to distinguish.
I'm the only one.
Everyone knows.
I'm a female.
And I'm a female.
No, it's a male.
It's between male and female.
That's wrong.
There's a female.
It's between male and female.
It's a joke.
I got it.
Let's say it properly.
I don't think it's a joke.
Hey, don't think that your parents will be happy forever.
I'm sorry.
I'm wearing underwear.
We don't live together.
It suits you.
I should have worn more.
I want to ask Bakuzan-sensei's best friend, Masumoto-san.
Are you his best friend?
He said, Yokaichi, this is the only thing I have.
But at the end, he said, I have a demon soldier too.
Isn't it a lie that he only has this?
Please listen to me.
No, I'm just saying that I have a demon soldier too.
This is one of my life.
Even though you are married,
when you first get married, you think, this is the only thing I have.
When you get married, you think, I have a demon soldier too.
I see, I see.
I understand that.
That kind of man's stubbornness.
I don't think there's anything I can do about it.
Everyone is looking for a demon soldier somewhere.
Walking around the town.
Even me.
You are saying the best thing today.
That's true.
About this.
Yes, yes.
That's why a woman has to try to become Yokaichi.
Right?
But you have to think about which is happier.
That's Yokaichi.
You said, this is the only thing I have.
Even if you say Yokaichi is better,
there are people who dig up Yokaichi and go to a demon soldier.
But that's when Yokaichi digs up Yokaichi and goes to a demon soldier.
The demon soldier becomes Yokaichi.
That's right.
That's a good thing.
It's good in the end.
But Yokaichi will look for another demon soldier.
It can't be helped.
That's why a woman wants to become Yokaichi.
I want to be Yokaichi.
I don't want to be a demon soldier anymore.
You don't want to be a demon soldier anymore.
I don't want to.