On the day of the recording, there was a sudden change in the atmosphere.
Hama-chan got sick and collapsed.
So we decided not to record today.
We decided to make a short film.
It's hard to talk alone.
Yamazaki...
I'll do my best.
I was going to do the cleaning in Yamazaki.
It took only 7 minutes.
That's a lie.
It took 30 minutes.
Yamazaki is interesting.
I've been doing it for 7 years.
What are you talking about?
The part of the bat that was suddenly cut by the radio was removed.
The radio staff couldn't handle it.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
I'll do it properly in the new year.
It was on TV.
I was surprised.
Well...
We don't have time, so let's play.
Let's go play.
Let's go to Amani.
We don't have time.
Everyone is going to play.
Excuse me.
Hama-chan, are you okay?
Okamoto-san is calling me again.
Please come soon.
It's a lawful way of talking.
If it's about Hama-chan, I'll hear it on the phone, so it's okay.
I don't care about that.
Hama-san is lying down.
I know that.
It's important that Okamoto-san doesn't come.
Please come.
Please come quickly.
We don't have time.
I'm sorry.
Let's all work hard together.
That's what we're going to do today.
He's going crazy.
Let's go.
I don't care about that.
It's annoying.
An emergency.
Manager Okamoto is angry again.
Please come soon.
Okamoto suddenly calls out without any intention.
I'm tired of the picture.
I'll be there soon.
I'm tired of it.
What time is it?
I'm not going to ask you for anything.
I'm going to ask you to bring me there.
It's still bright.
I'm going to play.
Let's go to Joy Police.
No, no, no.
I'll be there soon.
Please.
No, no, no.
Let's go to Joy Police.
Please come soon.
I'm here.
Suddenly, they are chatting.
Okamoto is waiting for them.
They are in Odaiba, a trendy spot.
What will happen?
I'm in a good place.
It's beautiful.
I'm here.
Where are you?
What are you doing?
I went straight ahead.
I'm here.
You are late.
I'm going to stop recording today.
Why?
Hamada is not feeling well.
We are not together.
We will stop recording.
What are you doing?
I'm a manager.
I'm a child care worker.
What?
You are not a child care worker.
No, no.
You are just talking.
You can't do anything if I'm here.
We don't know what's going on.
You guys are doing too much.
No, no.
I see.
What is this?
This is funny.
You guys are doing too much.
Yes, yes.
Recently, Isomata.
People around me are asking me.
What?
Isomata is funny.
Are you stupid?
He is funny.
What?
Mr. Hamada.
Isomata.
Yes.
What is this?
This is funny.
He is funny.
You guys are doing too much.
Recently, Isomata.
People around me are asking me.
What?
Mr. Okamoto is funny.
Are you stupid?
Yes.
If I'm here, you guys are here too.
What?
No.
But.
Why are you here?
You don't need to be so serious.
What?
Don't you have any problems with your breath?
Why is this guy funny?
He was funny.
I'm going to drink this.
Wow!
Amazing!
Good, good, good!
Wow!
This is the best!
This is amazing!
Wow!
Ah!
Hey!
Are you drunk?
This is so boring.
It was good.
I'll show you.
What was good?
It was good.
What is this?
What?
Is this a iron bag?
I'm going to drink this.
I'm going home.
Is that Isomata?
Isomata.
What is this?
Mr. Okamoto is so cool.
This is as it is.
50,000 bottles.
50,000 bottles?
From now on.
But!
I don't drink like Isomata.
I can't help it.
I'm drinking.
The amount is different.
The way to drink is different.
I'll show you now.
50,000 bottles.
I'm going.
What is this?
This is amazing.
I'm drinking this all the time.
I'm going home.
Gakimitsu is lined up beautifully like the summit of Banri.
Okamoto's ambition to spread the dream bridge to the stage.
What is the challenge using Gakimitsu?
This is amazing.
I'll do this.
I don't know what to do.
I saw it.
I can't say anything.
Okamoto, are you ready?
Yes.
Start!
It's heavy.
I didn't drink all of it.
Did you understand in one shot?
I only drank a little.
My body hurts.
I want to dance.
I can't walk.
I'll dance.
It's spicy.
Don't say it's spicy.
I'll dance all the way.
I can't dance.
What is that?
Okamoto.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
Why?
I don't know what you're doing.
That's the face of the viewer.
I don't know.
I can't dance.
It's a triangle jump.
That's amazing.
Why do you think it's that?
I can't dance.
Take it off.
I'll wait for you at the goal.
Are you really waiting?
I'm waiting.
I'm waiting on the way.
You should go back 100 meters.
I ran a lot.
You ran a lot.
Around here?
From where the carabiner is.
I don't know.
It's cold.
I'm going home.
Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen.
The main squeeze of the airplane will be about to take off.
What kind of reaction should I make when I walk down the street and see my girlfriend naked?
What are you talking about?
Are you from Kanagawa prefecture?
I happened to walk down the street and saw my girlfriend naked.
What should I do?
I'm 17 years old.
I'm a sticker.
Have you ever done it?
I have.
I don't.
I'm kind to the earth.
Which is more serious, a cigarette or a cigarette butt?
I think it's a cigarette butt.
Why do you say that?
You don't have to think about the cigarette butt.
I don't need it.
If you throw it away.
I don't throw it away.
Where do you throw it?
I throw it on the street.
I've done it in the bathroom in the apartment.
Oh, my God.
I'm in the bathroom.
You're in the living room.
I'm in the living room.
I'm in the bathroom.
You don't go straight.
This is how it is in the 21st century.
It was broadcast on April 21, 1996.
The other day, I was about to sell my beloved car, and as soon as I started looking for a new car, it was a non-trouble car, but it broke down.
Is this a message from God telling me not to sell it? Or have my feelings been revealed to the car?
This is definitely a living thing, a car. This is strange.
You're making a strange face.
This is strange.
Why are you making a face?
Friends from middle school are nice.
Someone come here!
I think so, too.
Well, I'll help you with that.
Well, that's what I'm saying.
You know, cars are like lovers.
Really?
If you try to buy a new one, something will definitely happen.
Most people are like that.
Haven't you ever felt that?
For example, what do you mean? Everyone is like that.
For example, your hair is growing and you can't put it together.
I thought it was annoying, so I thought I'd go to the hair salon tomorrow, but when I woke up the next day, it was pretty clean.
Today, it's easy.
There is. There really is.
The hair is telling you not to cut it.
I see.
Don't sell the car.
Yamazaki said something.
Really?
He was in the car, and he was going to the hair salon tomorrow.
He was riding a dirty Rolls-Royce until then.
I said, I'm sorry.
I said, I'm sorry that I'm going to be your friend from tomorrow.
He suddenly got angry.
Really?
Yes.
That's a coincidence.
I had a lot of regrets.
What?
Really?
Yes.
Tell me.
What?
Tell me what happened.
What happened?
Three days ago, I was riding a car and I was about to turn around and try to wink.
That's a mistake.
I raised my hand.
The weather was so nice.
That's a bad habit.
I said, I'm sorry.
That's right.
That's a bad habit.
There is. There really is.
Even machines are living things.
Is that so?
There is. There really is.
I'm the one who says to take care of things.
Does this mean that your feelings have been conveyed?
Yes.
Even for women.
If you think about throwing it away, you'll see a good place.
You're saying a lot of good things right now.
But before that, I said, should I throw it away?
That's also a negative point.
A broadcast of April 28, 1996.
What's inside the sun tower designed by Okamoto Taro?
Do you know about the sun tower?
I think I climbed it.
What?
I climbed the sun tower with stairs.
Who told you to do that?
No, no, no.
I was doing it in elementary school.
There are stairs inside.
Did you climb the stairs?
I didn't.
Let me see.
You were just listening indirectly.
No, no, no.
There were things like the Mitsubishi Pavilion and the Fuji-Pan Robot Museum.
The inside was like this.
What?
It was designed to give children dreams.
The inside of the sun tower is internal organs.
What is that?
What is this?
I don't know what it is.
It's internal organs.
What?
It's not a living thing.
Why is it internal organs?
Why?
What?
It's not the inside. It's stairs.
It's not stairs. It's internal organs.
Why?
You were moving in the past, right?
I'm still moving. I'm not moving.
You were moving in the past.
When was it in the past?
It was in the past, so it was before the bombing started.
I built it because the bombing started.
It came because the bombing started.
Where did it come from? I built it.
I don't know where it came from.
If you don't know, you don't know where it came from.
You don't know where it came from.
This is alive.
It's alive.
It's not alive.
I didn't do it yesterday.
You said it was concrete.
No.
It came when the bombing started.
It's not alive. You don't have legs.
It's like this, right?
Originally, you walk like this.
Why are you wearing such long pants?
That's your hobby, isn't it?
I'll do it for you.
Because it's a pair of boots.
Boots are fine, but why are you wearing a pair of pants?