At last, tonight, the judges of Ojo and Matsumoto are here.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
I was taking my acquaintance to an izakaya because the food there was delicious.
I introduced him to a good izakaya, and we went there.
We went there, drank, ate, and made a fuss.
After a long time, when it was time to pay, Matsumoto came over and said,
Thank you for the meal.
But after that, he said to me,
I don't say this because I'm your acquaintance, but it's about 20,000 yen.
It's 20,000 yen. It's very cheap, isn't it?
But I don't say this because I'm your acquaintance, but it's a lot of money.
Really?
It's expensive.
It's cheap.
It's delicious.
I'm pretending to be old.
That's not true.
It's not what you guys say.
I'm not going to let you eat.
You have to act cool.
We are leaders.
You have nothing to do with us!
We are all Yoshimoto! You are Jinrikisha!
No, I'm not! I'm Yoshimoto!
You are Jinrikisha!
No, I'm Yoshimoto!
You are Yoshimoto!
I'm Yoshimoto!
You don't know?
What are you talking about?
When I go shopping, I buy things like Uniqlo and Jeans Maid. I spend about 3,000 yen on pants.
I don't know if I should buy it or not. I don't know if I should put it on the price list.
I can't buy it.
I don't have any designer clothes, so I asked my senior if I could buy it.
I looked at the price list and it was 8,000 yen.
I can't buy it.
I was surprised.
I can!
I can't buy it!
What are you talking about?
You have a big nose and a small nose.
It's not important.
You can choose between two noses.
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
Next is Endo.
It's not from me, but I have a witness.
May I come in?
Please come in.
This is Fujiwara, the manager of Matsumoto.
This is Kimotsu, the manager of Hamada.
How many years have you been working for Fujiwara?
It's been three and a half years.
It's been three and a half years, right?
He has been working with most of the managers.
It's been three and a half years.
Have you ever been offered anything in the three and a half years?
Well...
Don't lie to me!
He's lying!
I offered him coffee at the airport in Los Angeles.
What are you talking about?
What's wrong with you?
I don't think he has ever said that.
How long have you been working for Kimotsu?
It's been three and a half years.
Have you ever been offered anything in the three and a half years?
I've never been offered anything in the three and a half years.
He's lying!
What's in your pocket?
I've been offered something.
Have you ever been offered coffee?
I've never been offered coffee.
He's lying!
What do you mean?
I'll explain it later.
When was your birthday?
It was my birthday last month.
Congratulations.
I happened to meet two people in the dressing room.
I took out 50,000 yen from my pocket.
That's cool.
Wait, wait, wait.
You don't have to clap.
Is this a segment where you take out 50,000 yen?
No, it's not like that.
As the same manager, I took out 50,000 yen on my birthday.
It's better to buy something you like than to die.
It's cool, isn't it?
It's cool.
Fujiwara.
Say that.
There's something like that, isn't there?
There is.
For Matsumoto.
It wasn't my birthday.
On Matsumoto's birthday,
the staff prepared a huge cake and a lot of food.
They prepared a lot of food.
I ate the cake with everyone.
I gave the bouquet to Matsumoto on the way home.
He said, give it to your wife.
I gave it to him and went home.
That's a lot of money.
Fujiwara, that's not it.
It's from the other day.
Is there?
Say that.
Please say there is.
Say that, or make that.
Make that.
I don't have that kind of power.
However, Fujiwara gave a birthday present to Matsumoto as a gift.
Really?
Did you give it to him?
Yes.
I gave him a birthday pin.
Even though he gave him a pin,
Matsumoto didn't give anything to Fujiwara.
I think that's a problem.
To be honest, I don't need a neck tie pin.
I'm scared.
Take it off!
It won't come out.
Don't touch it.
I don't feel good touching it.
Sit down.
What?
He's flustered.
That was a few years ago.
When Matsumoto went to Ise with Kimura, Imada and Itao.
When we arrive at Ise, let's eat delicious food.
Ise?
Ise shrimp is really delicious.
The car is full of excitement and we finally arrive at Ise.
Yay!
Parque Espana!
First, the four of us enjoy the sightseeing.
And then Matsumoto...
I remember there was Nichi earlier.
Can I stop by before we eat?
Sure.
For Matsumoto, who likes cheap restaurants,
Nichi is an interesting existence.
He couldn't help but stop by.
What is this T-shirt?
It's really cheap.
I should buy it.
Matsumoto is excited like a fish in the water.
And when the shopping is over...
I'm hungry.
Let's eat something.
Let's go!
We can finally eat Ise shrimp.
You're such a nosy kid.
But...
I'm sure there's a restaurant in the basement.
Matsumoto!
The three of them were thinking the opposite.
Matsumoto went to the udon restaurant in the basement.
And when the food he ordered came out...
This isn't enough.
I'm sure there's a croquette there.
I'm sorry, but can you bring it here?
But if I bring it in, I'll get in trouble.
Why don't you ask the owner?
I'm the one in the car.
Excuse me, can I bring it in?
Normally, you're not allowed to bring it in.
But the owner accepted Matsumoto's request.
And when he added the croquette that Kimura bought to the side dish...
This is Taragosu.
The volume is different.
Matsumoto was very happy with the udon.
In the end, he came to Ise to eat udon.
I see.
The witness, please come forward.
What the hell is that?
That's harsh.
Is this true?
If I didn't have a chance like this, I would have brought this story to the coffin.
I see.
I would have brought this story to the coffin.
What I'm curious about is...
In the video, you said that you were supposed to eat fish.
What kind of meal is that?
It's dinner.
It's not lunch?
It's not lunch.
If it was lunch, I would have had udon.
Is that dinner?
It's dinner.
I can't even think about it.
Of course, when I was looking at the T-shirt and pants on Sunday...
I thought I would turn the car around.
I see.
So that you can go to Meji-kun as soon as you're done shopping.
I thought so.
I wanted to go to a restaurant in the basement.
I see.
There was a Tatchan croquette.
I was very interested in it.
I see.
Why?
I've never eaten it before.
I don't know if it's different from the one I ate in Ise.
I was wondering if Umehimeya-san was running away.
I was wondering why he was running away.
I see.
I understand that question.
I thought it would be bad if I ate it all.
I was hungry.
So I went to Ise and Awabi about an hour later.
That's a good idea.
That's what I planned.
That's another way of thinking.
That's right.
I want to say that it's better to have that way of thinking.
That's bad.
That's a bad way of thinking.
Why are you looking at me?
Don't open your eyes.
Is it okay for you to eat udon?
I usually eat a lot of healthy food.
Is that so?
No.
No?
It's healthy food.
I don't know if there was a lot of excitement in Parque Espana.
What kind of excitement?
It was like a river.
There were four people on a boat.
It was like a drift.
Eventually, the river broke.
The boat sank a little.
The boat sank about three meters.
I see.
I thought, is that so?
What is that?
You're an interesting person.
You're a person who can think of more interesting things.
That's what I thought.
What is that?
I want to apologize to Yamazaki and Pocorico after the rain.
I want to apologize.
It's been a while since I've been here.
It's been a while.
I couldn't stop being a man.
It's okay.
It's wonderful.
You know what? You guys are not funny.
I'm playing with you guys but you're not funny.
Go away.
When I went on a trip, what did you do when I asked you to stay with me?
You're a good-for-nothing.
Go away.
You guys are not funny. Go away.
I still have a lot to say but I can't say it in words so I wrote a letter.
Please read it.
When I went to Russia for the first time as a souvenir, thank you for the 40-yen pin.
In Russia, the prices are cheap.
In Russia, the price is about 40,000 yen.
In Russia, the prices are about 40,000 yen.
You guys are not funny.
Go away.
I can't say it in words so I wrote a letter.
Please read it.
Do you know him?
Kimura Yuichi.
I always carry 9 yen in my wallet for my brother who hates money.
Do you know him?
I pay for the video you borrowed.
I didn't have enough money for Kimura Yuichi last year.
Do you know him?
I went to a karaoke shop with 10 people.
I only had enough money for 3 people.
Do you know him?
I don't have a lot of money.
Thank you.
I feel bad.
After this, there will be an even more unbelievable event.
And the trial will be held in Kakyong.
Don't film me.
Can we watch the next video?
Let's watch the special testimony video.
The testimony I know is about Itao's wedding.
I want to celebrate his wedding.
I decided to give 100,000 yen for the wedding.
On the day of the wedding, I put 100,000 yen in a lucky bag.
I noticed that Matsumoto was paying 70,000 yen.
I was sad.
I wanted to celebrate his wedding, but I changed it to 50,000 yen.
200,000 yen or 300,000 yen is normal.
Please give us a little more money.
There was a team fight, so I asked him to give me a jersey I was wearing.
It was a jersey.
He probably earned it.
But why did you take one jersey home?
I felt sorry for you.
Please give me something.
It's been 15 years since I was loved.
The first thing I got was a Kitsune Udon for 170 yen.
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's been 15 years since I was loved.
When I go out to various places, I use a car.
I don't know why, but Matsumoto's habit is to go in one car.
It's more fun to go in one car with everyone.
I was convinced.
When I go out, I use one car.
One day, I suddenly realized that I was going somewhere far away.
I don't know what you're talking about.
The VTR show is over.
What did you think of the show?
Honestly, I was surprised by the last gasoline.
I've been wondering for a while.
What is Onuma?
It doesn't matter.
The suit is the most autumn-like.
I'm looking at you.
He's the one who set up the trial.
Judge, please give me the verdict.
I'll give you the verdict.
The defendant, Mr. Matsumoto, is a rich man.
It's hard to change the fact that he's been causing trouble to many people.
It's far beyond our expectations.
I can't help it.
So the verdict is a guilty verdict.
He will be fined 1 million yen from Matsumoto's savings.
It's strange.
It's strange, isn't it?
Why?
Is this a Japanese TV show?
You're going to have a stupid trial, too.
Hey!
Next week.
Matsumoto will be fined 1 million yen from Matsumoto's savings.