I caught a cold.
I'm on a preventive shot.
You're lying.
You really do things like that...
on your own, don't you?
Hamada will collapse from the cold.
Hamada's sick project.
A special to show the back of the back of Gaki no Tsukai.
The program will start.
On January 8th, Gaki no Tsukai will be broadcasted over 400 times.
Around downtown Gaki no Tsukai.
Up until now, there have been a number of special projects,
and personal projects,
that have created projects that remain in the memory, even if they don't remain in the memory.
The number has exceeded 40 in just one year.
However, this program seems to show the back of the back of the back of Gaki no Tsukai.
In reality, the real back of the back of the back of Gaki no Tsukai has not been shown.
Therefore, this time, from the front to the back of Gaki no Tsukai,
everything will be revealed.
Up until now, it has been shown to anyone, anywhere.
Starting with downtown,
Yamasaki, Horikohoka, Kisei-chan's true face,
and the backstage during the actual recording, etc.
The first reveal of this program, the return of the fans.
We will present you a new special,
which will be a combination of a pre-released VTR.
This program is brought to you by the sponsors you see.
First, the appearance of the stars.
This project is to invite a big guest to Gaki.
Rather than inviting a big guest,
it is better to invite someone who is good at it.
The person who is assigned to call the stars from downtown,
has to become that star and appear.
For the person who is assigned,
the time to make the role is short,
and he panics.
As a result of his panicking, he is asked to evolve.
Isn't it good to have Hiroko Yakushima?
That would be great.
I've never seen him.
I saw him earlier.
Go and invite him.
He was on the show.
Really?
Is he a comedian?
Why is he a comedian?
He is a comedian.
This is the first time.
Hiroko Yakushima is the best.
I couldn't stop at the first time.
I don't know what will happen at the first time.
I don't know the atmosphere.
The atmosphere is strange.
The atmosphere is different.
He is here.
Are you in a sailor suit?
If you don't mind, I'd like you to come out.
What is it?
Is it okay?
Hiroko Yakushima.
Can I go home?
What is it?
I'm sorry.
I'm in a hurry.
I'm going home in a hurry.
Please take care of him.
This is Inoki's video.
I saw this video.
This is Suwa.
This is Inoki.
I don't think Inoki is here.
I'm looking for him, but I'm sorry if he's not here.
I don't know what will happen at the first time.
I'm scared.
I'm sorry.
I'd like you to come out this time.
One, two, three.
I'm scared.
Are you called Shimura?
Takasu.
I'm an otaku.
I'd like you to come out this time.
I'm scared.
Good morning.
I'm Shimura.
What?
Did you find Ako-san?
Is it really Ako-san?
It's been a long time.
That's just like Matsumoto and me.
If it's Ako-san, tell us earlier.
Matsumoto is going to do it?
Akko-san
Is there a place to hold it?
Yes, there is
Akko-san
My story is already over
What do you mean?
What should I do?
What kind of make-up?
I don't have any weapon
Really?
Yes
It's okay
Akko-san, what are you doing?
I don't have any weapon
I want you to appear on the show
It's okay
And for the first time
Kokoriko Endo is playing the role of this star
Nijikawa-kun
I didn't do it
And for the second time, Kokoriko Tanaka is playing the role of this star
I want you to appear on the show
I don't have any weapon
Wajima-san
For the first time, let's make a calendar with all the staff members
And for the second time, we made a calendar with all the staff members
Today, we have Mr. Yamazaki
Hello
Please
What are your plans for next year?
Next year, I want to do my best
For example?
Something like this
For work?
It's a long story
I want to play the piano
Please tell me the truth
I'm not lying
I'm joking
Please don't tell a lie
I want to play the tofu
I can only think of it as a joke.
Why?
Because I don't fly that much.
Today, we have Mr. Oitoshi Matsumoto.
Hello, hello, hello.
Welcome.
No, no, no.
It's been 98 years since the war.
That's right.
How many years until the 21st century?
That's right. 4 years?
It's been 4 years.
When are you going to talk about it?
2 more years.
It's kind of hard.
What are your aspirations for next year?
My aspirations for next year?
I want to do a lot of things that will wipe out the world.
I see.
That's a good thing.
Yes.
Wipe out the world and wipe out the world.
I want to wipe out the world and wipe out the world.
You're going to wipe out the world and wipe out the world?
I don't want to be surprised.
I don't care what you think.
It's hard.
You have to tell me.
Do you want me to tell you?
Talk, talk.
How do you say it?
Laugh?
That's a good thing.
I want to hear more of that.
For you, Yamazaki,
Laugh?
Yes.
What is that?
It's a misalignment of the composition.
A misalignment of the composition?
It's a little easier to understand.
I think you can do it, too.
A misalignment of the composition?
It's going to fall.
Oh, really?
What do you mean by a misalignment of the composition?
A misalignment of the composition?
Yes.
I think I sold this.
Yes, yes, yes.
Thank you.
Good luck on the second round.
I'm going to talk to Yamazaki again.
Is this it?
It's a big deal.
Five seconds before.
Yes.
Five, four, three, two.
Hello.
Today, too.
It's a friendly atmosphere.
Today.
I'm here.
Today's guest is Hama-chan.
Hello.
Good evening.
What's wrong?
What is it?
You're very excited.
I'm usually like this.
No, it's not.
You're usually very cheerful.
Oh, really?
You're not on TV.
I'm usually like this.
How do you usually feel?
You're cheerful, so don't say it first.
I'm calling a lot of guests because it's a talk show.
First, Sudo-kun came back.
The second time was Tanaka Kokoriko.
It's the third time today.
It's the 21st century.
How many years do we have left?
Two years?
It's been two years, so I'm wondering how I'm going to do it.
The frame is very wide.
How was it?
Are you trying to do it again?
No, no, no.
If you don't have a story, don't talk to people.
That's right.
But we learned how to talk.
As expected, raw things are good.
It's a little different from TV.
We're going to do it together.
I had a lot of fun.
I look forward to it again.
Please let me study more.
Thank you very much.
It's cold.
It's not good.
The 9th Gagirochikai Alliance's New Year's New Year's Party.
Everyone is in a good mood after drinking.
There was such a conversation between Machan and Hama-chan that I rarely see.
What are you doing?
I'll drink it.
Why?
After such a party mood, the downtown was decided as a new comedy combination at 9 o'clock.
Before the performance, he had never shown his expression on the stage.
The first is Hamada and O-numa.
It's coming.
Why don't you drink it?
It's complicated.
I don't want you to drink it.
I'm a bird.
We were the most naked.
It's hot.
It's not easy to be caught and caught.
You did a good job.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was good.
It's hard to be caught.
It's easy to be caught.
I can't be caught.
What is the relationship between that and that?
It's amazing.
I'm not nervous.
What is this?
I'm not confident.
Thank you very much.
It's over.
I'm sorry.
It's the last one.
It's finally the last one.
We've seen a lot of four teams so far.
The first team, the second team, and the third team were very good.
I don't know if the fourth team will win.
The last team is...
Matsumoto and Irie.
Hello, I'm Matsumoto.
I'm Irie.
We are Hammers.
I'll hit you.
You're a weird guy.
Stop it.
It's over.
It's too early.
I'm nervous.
I've always wanted to come and see it.
I'm very satisfied.
It was fun.
It was very interesting to see the real comedy.
I hope you'll be in a powerful downtown.
It was fun.
I've loved it since I was a kid.
I've always been able to see it.
It was really fun to see it live today.
If you'd like to come again, please come to the game.
The downtown of Hong Kong, which belongs to Yoshimoto Industries.
The downtown is full of bad guys working against the junior Horiko.
Horiko's wish is to send this man back to Osaka.
I'm going to send him back.
You're going to send him back?
I'm going to send him back to Osaka.
He quickly entered the school building in Hong Kong.
Everyone in Hong Kong was in a hurry.
What are you doing?
Put it in your mouth.
It's hard.
He loaded the cardboard box in Hong Kong into the truck and sent it to Osaka.
I was the only one who could say that.
When I got out of the car, the staff said,
Thank you for your hard work.
I couldn't say anything.
But let's go to NGK.
I'm a little worried right now.
Are you serious?
What happened in Hong Kong after the recording?
Stop it.
I'm going to Osaka for a while.
I hate you.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm sorry.
What happened to your mouth?
I was thinking,
I'm addicted to the chopper in Hong Kong.
It was cut like this.
Where is it cut?
It's okay.
You did it yourself.
It's disgusting.
You put it in the cardboard box and cut it yourself.
I can't do that.
That's funny.
I can't do it anymore.
You can't do it alone.
I was really scared.
I can't take it with me.
It's about the two of us.
I can't do it.
As a student.
And when I do that,
I can't turn the camera.
I was going to quit on the way.
Because it hurts.
I really can't do it.
I'm a general sense.
I'm going to hit 50.
You can't hit it.
Because it's a closed-door beach.
50 people will receive a calendar.
The prize money will be given to the winner.
Everyone, please apply.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.