The goal is to conquer the entertainment world!
The men will fly to the battle stage!
Osu! Ikidomebu! Part 2!
Now, this is the second time!
Last time, we lost, so the Ikidomebu was supposed to be gone.
Why is that?
I didn't say I'd do it again, but the staff really liked it.
It was naturally put together.
Last time it was 4 seconds.
Yes, it was 4 seconds.
Last time, the opponents were the team from the office.
They were strong and had an overwhelming career.
Yamasaki had the best record of 1 minute and 33 seconds.
They had a close fight.
However, Hamada's time was unexpected, 9 seconds.
He lost in just 4 seconds.
Everyone did their best.
I didn't do my best!
Please do your best again.
You're an idiot!
He's been doing that a lot lately.
The Ikidomebu isn't aiming to win.
What is it for?
It's for Ozonso.
You're an idiot!
He wants to escape.
But this time, there's one more person.
That's right!
He's a big shot in Hoshimoto.
This time, it's this person!
Hello! Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you!
That was a close call.
Don't just say nice to meet you!
Hanako-neesan, how's the Ikidome?
I'm confident.
Really?
In terms of seconds?
Well...
1 minute.
The time is up.
After 1 minute, it's 1 minute.
You're starting to look like Hodo-chan.
Do I look like Hodo-san?
Leave it to me.
Leave it to you?
Now then, let's have our opponents appear!
Ozonso!
3...2...1...
What are you saying?
Aren't you embarrassed, Mame?
There's Mame in the word.
I understand the meaning of this appearance.
Igi-Mame!
Hey!
Mr. X!
Mame!
You're the leader.
That's enough, Yugo-chan.
Today's opponents are the Ota-pro team!
I see.
Toga-chan is here too.
He's been practicing a lot.
Just once.
He's a bit of a sportsman.
I see.
He's been practicing a lot.
You can't lose to him.
I don't understand why he's so hard to get along with.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
It's the same as last time.
Yes.
In terms of time, the Ota-pro team won.
I see.
The order is like this.
Yugo-chan, are you really okay?
I'm okay.
By the way, who's the leader of the Ota-pro team?
Leader?
I'm going to be the leader.
Look at this muscle!
That's amazing.
Who's going to be the leader?
I think I'm going to be the leader.
I'm going to be the leader.
What are you going to do?
Can you make me do it?
I can do it.
You should do it more than last time.
I'm really weak.
I'm going to be the leader.
Okay.
Take it off.
What's that?
You can't beat me with that muscle.
It's not a muscle match.
That's right.
Take it off.
The leader of the Ota-pro team is Jimon Terakado.
His built-up body shows his progress.
I don't know how far I can go.
That's right.
I don't know how to aim.
I'll let Jimon be the leader of the Ota-pro team.
Wait a minute.
This is very different.
It's different when you do it and look at it.
I haven't been confident for a while.
It's a little different when you get in.
The pace is strange.
I can't breathe when I get up.
Okay.
Jimon, I'll start when the water reaches here.
I'll start when the water reaches here.
Okay.
Okay?
Let's go.
Ready.
Start.
I think I can do it.
Jimon.
What?
What kind of face is that?
I can't see the front.
I'm happy.
I think I can do it.
Go.
Like a demon.
I can't go.
Jimon.
Wait a minute.
I can't go.
You're going.
Awesome.
Yes, go.
I think I can do it.
You can go.
Oh!
He has some room for improvement.
But it's not coming out of his nose yet.
Oh, wow!
14 mins!
Wow!
Will Yagoto be as proud as he is now?
Is this a shelf?
Let's get him to try after a minute.
After 1 minute,
Just get it in one try.
After 30 seconds,
Just one time.
You have to go up to the 3rd floor.
The first team is Kokoriko Tanaka.
From the last record of 41 seconds, how much time will he extend?
This is the second time.
I'm used to it.
How's the water temperature?
The water temperature is getting warmer because it's cold today.
Ah, that's right.
Can you do it?
Yes!
Let's go!
Ready!
Start!
I didn't make it.
It's okay.
This is dangerous.
The wind is blowing.
I'm counting on you.
It's really hot.
I'm gonna try it.
Okay.
He made it.
I'm counting on you.
I made it.
It's a piece of cake.
Sorry, I'm drunk.
You shouldn't have played with that.
Something came out.
Stop it!
I'm not done yet!
I forgot 30 seconds.
This is amazing.
I can do it!
I can't do it!
At this point, he started at 21 seconds.
This is amazing.
I don't know what's going to happen other than this.
I'm going.
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Higo-chan, you can stop now.
I'm not going to be able to pull you back.
Who's going next?
Next is Kannazuki.
You know it, right?
Ouch!
What's wrong with you?
Cheer up!
I don't know what's going to happen if I don't do this.
Who is this?
It's Hase.
Hase?
Hase!
He's like Gin-san.
Hase, look.
Look, look, look.
I can't do it anymore.
I don't know anything about this.
I wanted to see something else.
Okay, I'll do it like this.
Wait a minute.
I want to go next.
Who?
You.
You're going with Hama-chan?
I'm going.
Kota Pro-team.
Jihon imitates a lot of athletes.
How good is he?
I went too far.
Get ready.
Start!
I think that's how it's done.
Slowly.
He went in slowly.
I thought it was going to be a good shot.
It's true.
What is this?
I'm going to imitate something.
You're going to imitate something.
Wait, wait.
I'm going to imitate something.
I'm going to die.
He's looking at me, but can he see me?
You can't see him, can you?
I can't see him.
I'm going to die.
Look to your right.
I can't see you, can you?
What was that?
It's only hire.
I wanted to imitate Shin-chan, but...
Is that how it's done?
You're weeding!
I'm going to cut my public.....
Shin-chan! Shin-chan!
I'm going to die.
Look to your right.
I can't see you, can you?
I'm going to die.
It's a false hope.
That's a good feeling
The kids team, Jihou is Hamada
The previous record was only 9 seconds
Will this humiliating time continue?
I think I can do it
If my ears start to hurt, I'll come up
But don't think too much about it
But if my ears start to hurt, I'll come up
I won't go
Let's go, Mr. Hamada
Please
Do it at your own timing
At my own timing
I did it
It's morning
Okay, it's going
This is a lot
It's going
This is bad
It was long, 14 seconds
14 seconds, okay
This is
What time is it?
It's hard
You can only hold your breath for 14 seconds
But you're eating a lot of noodles
How many seconds did you hold the noodles?
If it's a long noodle, you can hold it
You can hold it
The other way
Who's going next?
Okay
Mr. X
Jihou
Wait
It's Jihou
The country is on your side
Jihou, it's okay
Auto Pro Team, the leader of the ostrich, Jihou Katsuhiro
His career is not to be underestimated
Jihou, did you forget the noodles?
I won the noodles
Okay
Jihou, it's okay
It's okay
It's not a problem
Auto Pro Team wants to spread the lead
Jihou opened 50 seconds with a relaxed expression
The time difference with the ostrich team is 1 minute 25 seconds
Look at this mayonnaise
The ostrich team cannot lose
Yamazaki Hosei, who broke the record of 1 minute 33 seconds last time
Let's go
Ready
Start
He looks like he's going to eat
I'll give you 2 minutes
It looked dangerous last time
I did my best
He looks like he's going to eat
I'm ready
He's crying
He did this last time
Yes
Really?
He's practicing
It's going well
He's coming
40 seconds
He was slow last time
It comes
What is this?
He looks strong
It's coming
It's coming again
I'm going to be called!
It's completely different from last time.
Why?
It's because of my ability.
You were good last time.
Last time was a fluke?
It's because of my ability now.
Then, let's copy Otaku's self.
I'll show you! I'll show you!
Nocchi Popon Nocchi Popon Nocchi
Nocchi Ha To Doke
Go! Go! Go!
Why did you start sleeping?
It will be 12 o'clock soon.
Okay!
It's exactly the same as my joke.
You're so annoying!
You're always talking!
Then, you're going to be the Park teacher.
Thank you!
Hanako, are you going to go?
Yes!
I'm going!
What?
What's the meaning of that?
Hanako, go!
Hanako, let's go!
You're dirty!
Let's go!
Ready!
Start!
Did it stop?
It stopped at the shallow part.
Well, it's small.
If you go down too much...
I'm scared.
What is it?
It's a little bit of a side-eye.
I see.
You're a woman.
I'm a woman.
No way.
But...
It's over!
But I took it off at this stage.
You took it off.
That's not good.
What did you take off?
I took it off.
The name of the water pro team is dangerous Notch.
The dangerous energy is an act of terror to the opponent.
Ready.
It's going, it's going, it's going.
Calm down, calm down, calm down.
It's going, it's going.
It's going, it's going, it's going.
It's going.
You can't do this to me.
Oh, it came out.
I think you're doing something.
That's not good.
Nice!
6 seconds lead for Oda Pro.
That's not good.
6 seconds is not good.
I want to make a difference here.
I see.
Ueshiba!
Really?
Ueshiba-san.
I want to go.
I don't want to be the last.
Endo, you can go.
I have nothing.
The target is Endo Kokoriko.
The record is 47 seconds.
The winner wants to lead here.
It's a big deal.
There are a lot of things floating.
I don't like it.
Don't say that.
I don't like this.
Something is floating.
Endo shows his manliness here.
The last record is far above.
The weather team is under pressure.
The weather team's target is the ostrich of the island.
Will he show the miracle he did on the rice?
There's a lot of floating.
Are you ready?
this is such learning
I got it
I'll be in a bit
a little bit more
Oh oh oh oh
It's still not good
Get down! Get down!
In the middle... oh, it's hard
10 seconds left!
Go down! Go down!
A little more! A little more!
It's too early!
Yuu-chan, what's wrong?
Totton, Totton!
Yuu-chan!
What?
I'm so happy!
I want to close the door myself!
Wait a minute, I...
What's wrong?
Hey, help me!
Wait a minute!
What's wrong?
The show has started!
I'm so happy!
Are you okay?
You're drowning!
What happened?
I'm drowning!
I was going to dive again to cover that up.
The worst day...
This is how it started.
My father bought a two-bedroom house.
Everyone in the family is going to live in it.
But...
Your dream broke out.
Enshop Takefuji
Toridori David's new favorite, A.M.E.
Use the optical camouflage to beat the streets.
Phantom Crash
Recently, I started to think that driving on a rainy day is not bad.
Why is that?
I am running with Legacy.
A.D.S.K.Limited
New release
Subaru
We are worried about the stain.
There, Heisei made a medicine to dilute the stain.
2 times a day, anti-stain
Heisei White 2
Born, Takeda
Hotel, Hotel, Hotel, Jack is Hotel.
Hotel for family
5 mail addresses, Wills check is free.
Our Broadband, Jack is Hotel.
Finally, the final match. The grand prize of the Gaki team is Matsumoto.
He is a man who is determined to survive.
Hey, what are you doing?
Why are you so bold?
Are you okay?
It was fun when I first started.
It was fun.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
I'm scared.
I'm waiting.
Ready, start!
Oh, it's hot.
Why are you looking at me?
It was dangerous.
Why?
Why are you looking at me?
Open your eyes.
Hey, a little foam is coming out of my nose.
Why don't you open your eyes?
Oh, it hurts.
No, no, no, no.
It hurts.
It's almost the end.
Oh no.
That was close!
Isn't the water in the pool weird?
It's really floating!
5 seconds in 1 minute.
This is bad.
He's the world champion.
I'm the Mongolian champion.
Will they be able to turn the tables around?
Huh?
In the end, they don't answer the question!
windshield wiper
Look, from the part where you blow
It's smooth
That's why it's Piore's smooth sheet
It's smooth with powder
Piore
I hate studying, but there's a way to meet people
I want you to be kinder, bigger, and weaker
What's wrong with you?
There's a bad girl over there
That's right, it's Kotoruki
I'm Johnny
When I get on the train, I run to the bathroom and open the door
Happy time
You can choose the taste
The taste of the sun
Mediterranean lemon
Peeled fruit
Asahi Super Sour
Drink and be convinced
I want you to relax as much as possible for the first time
First, create an atmosphere that's easy to talk to
That's my job
Thank you
First time
We're waiting for you at the ice cream shop
Bridgestone's Mr. Tire Man
Thank you very much
Bridgestone
Don't give up on your hair damage
Try it for 14 days
Pantene Conditioner
Miracles don't happen overnight
For 14 days
Your hair will be healthy and shiny
Pantene
Then
Ah
What's wrong!?
Why are you fighting so much?
Thank you
Calm down
Come here
It's real
Ota Pro-team's grand prize is Tokashiki Katsuo!
The original boxing world champion's fighting spirit is exploding!
Ready, start!
That way of entering is dangerous.
It opened.
I didn't know it would suddenly come.
It suddenly came.
It's stupid.
It's better to stop it this time.
It suddenly came.
Calm down, calm down.
It's running now.
I did it like this, so I got it.
It looks like a demon.
It's suffering.
Calm down, calm down.
1 minute, 1 minute.
It will definitely go in 1 minute and 5 seconds.
Half.
Half!
It's dangerous.
It's coming this way.
It's moving a little.
It's moving.
It's going down.
Go up!
It's cool.
4 minutes and 39 seconds vs 5 minutes and 15 seconds
Auto Pro Team
You're weak
I don't think I'm weak
It's because of Toga-chan
I'm sorry
I'm not Toga-chan, I'm Shouhei