It's cold and I'm not in a good mood.
Hama-chan, I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Even if you ask me why I'm here, there's only one reason.
He's angry.
Who?
Him.
Oshima! Oshima!
What are you talking about?
You're going to get beaten up again today.
Hey, Hama!
What is it?
Why didn't you come to pick me up?
What is she talking about?
I don't know.
Oshima is waiting for you.
What?
What are you waiting for?
What do you mean he's not coming to pick me up?
But he got married recently.
He got married recently?
Congratulations.
That's why I'm wearing a wedding dress.
I see.
That's not true!
My voice echoed.
It echoed.
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
I don't understand what you're saying.
Hama-chan is going to be like this because you're being so noisy.
What do you mean?
You sound like you're going to throw it away.
So...
What do you mean by being so noisy?
I don't know.
Come and get me.
No, no.
But...
But Hamada-san is already married.
Yes, you're already married.
Love and marriage are two different things!
A married woman shouldn't fall in love?
What are you talking about?
Murakami!
Who are you trying to play?
Why don't you call your teacher?
Oshima Miyuki in Morisan.
Since last year's Valentine's Day,
she has been attacking Hamada with her love for him.
But she was rejected and she cried.
This fall, she was happily married to the love of her life.
But she didn't get tired of it and appeared again.
Will she be able to steal Hamada's heart?
Tonight, just before Christmas,
we will show you the ultimate plan.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
I've told you many times that you're not Hamada's type.
You've been trying to make me like that.
Hamada likes women who smell dangerous.
What kind of scent is this? I don't know.
For example, the scent of a bomb in her underwear.
I don't know anything about that.
He only looks at women like that.
His wife is the only one who has ever done that.
That's why he married her.
A bomb is a good thing.
What's wrong?
Oh no!
It's a bomb!
It's on my clothes again!
Do it!
You're going to blow it up, right?
It's true. It's a bomb.
Don't do it. It's dangerous.
It's dangerous.
It's okay.
Do it with a straight face.
What should I do?
You shouldn't do that.
It's dangerous.
Hamada likes women like that.
You shouldn't do that.
You can't escape even if you're dirty.
What should I do?
Hamada likes women like that.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
It's a big bomb.
Go away!
It stinks!
Don't come here in the middle of the night!
Take it away!
Hey!
You shouldn't do that.
It stinks!
You're still burning.
Take him away.
Let's go home.
It stinks!
You shouldn't come here in the middle of the night.
Let's go home.
You did what I told you to do.
What's wrong with you?
Let's go home.
You shouldn't come here in the middle of the night.
I've heard this before.
He likes women who are black and white.
That's true.
I've heard that.
He likes women who are black and white.
It's impossible for him to do that.
Let's go home.
It's impossible.
I've never done that before.
Let's go home.
It's impossible.
What's wrong?
Come on.
Hey.
It's so bad.
Shut up.
I can't finish it.
You can do it.
It's a human pump.
There are both white and black, so you can drink one at a time.
19 points.
Let's do it.
19 points for the blue one.
Don't be silly.
Don't do that.
Really?
Did you drink it?
Yes, I did.
Don't be silly.
Let's make it clear.
Really?
Are you okay with this?
This is cool.
Can you do it?
Which one is white and black?
White.
Can you do it?
You can do it.
Stop it.
That's not how you do it.
Can you do it?
Stop it.
You're a demon.
Go home.
That's not how you do it.
You can't do it.
I can't do it.
I've never done it.
What should I do?
It's dirty.
It's a shame.
You can sing My Way with your heart.
That's how you do it.
It's impossible.
Let's go home.
Let's go.
It's 19 o'clock.
That's it.
I can do this.
Let's do it.
I got it.
I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
Are you going to sing?
It's okay.
Music, please.
I'll talk to you when I'm done.
I'm not young and easy
So I face the final curtain
I only did what I thought
I took my wish and I made
I know much more than me
I didn't mind my way
But still, I can't stop
I only have a dream to find
I see all of it
And that's the truth
And it goes my way
You know, I have to go
I have to shoot a commercial for Georgia
I know
I don't have time so I have to go
Thank you
See you
Hey, hey
That's not what I'm talking about
You're not looking back at all
What are we going to do?
Hama-chan left
We have to go to Oshima
If we go now, we can catch up with her
That's true
Hama-san, we have work to do
Stop it, Mori-san
Even if we catch up with her
There's no half-hearted acting
Hey
Stop it, Mori-san
Mori-san
Stop it
It hurts
You can't do that
What should we do?
Should we go?
We have to go
Is there anything?
No
There's nothing
You're the type, right?
You know
I'm not exactly the type
I'm more of a race queen
You're not exactly the type
I'm not exactly the type
Everyone likes it
You're not exactly the type
Hama-chan, really?
Yes
Hey, Oshima
Let's trust Hama-chan
Let's do that
Even if you say race queen
There's nothing we can do
It's a leotard
It's a leotard, so it's not a problem
It's a matter of morality
Really
What's wrong?
Hey, Oshima
It's loud
It's a race queen
What's wrong?
Let's take it off together
Let's do that
I think it's going to be fine
Hey
Come here
It's cold
Start
I always see you at the usual station
You're wearing a sailor uniform
It's time to send you off
I'm waiting for you today
Oshima
This is tough
There's tomorrow
What are you doing?
Here
What?
What's here?
Here
Go away
I'm working
It hurts
What are you doing?
Why?
What's wrong?
You can't breathe
I'm doing a commercial
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
Han-san, I'm sorry, I didn't mean it like that.
Wow, that's amazing!
Hey!
You're a bit too much.
Why do you always react like that?
Go home, you guys!
Okay.
Then I'll get back to work.
Sorry.
Apologize!
You like me, don't you?
That's it!
Go home!
What do you mean?
No, I really like Race Queen.
That's not what I'm saying!
I'm saying that you're not Race Queen.
What's wrong with you, Hara?
You're not even close to Anko.
Seriously.
Give me a break.
What are you going to do?
Go home and sleep.
Just one night.
I'm going to sleep.
Oh?
Hey!
What are you going to do?
Go home!
What should I do?
I'll go home.
You can't go home!
You're going to get scolded.
I have to go.
You're going to get scolded again.
Seriously.
Let's stop.
Let's go home.
There he is.
He's here.
I'm going to sleep.
What are you going to do next?
What are we going to do next?
What's next?
This world.
You just got scolded.
You just have to succeed next time.
That's right.
Why did you come all the way here?
What should I do?
Why are you trying so hard?
Let's hurry up.
Let's go next.
You're like a child of a dinosaur.
There's something, right?
There's this much.
Hurry up.
I don't know.
What I heard was...
I heard that there are women who like Hollywood.
For example, this year, the ring was made in Sagako.
That's not the story.
What should I do?
Let's use this.
This can be used as a dress.
That's true.
That's great.
What are you guys doing?
Let's stop.
It's really bad.
It's okay.
Start.
I'm Hamada, the head of the family.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Hamada.
What is it?
I don't know.
Stop it.
It's bad.
I'm Hamada.
It's over.
Hurry up.
What are you doing?
Aren't you Sadako?
I don't know.
Don't come.
I'm Hamada.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
Let's go home.
Let's go.
I told you during the show.
I was going to hit you.
Don't be silly.
That's not what I said.
Why are you wearing a black underwear?
It's underwear.
I don't understand.
That's not Sadako.
You're wearing a black underwear.
We're going home.
It's over.
I'm going home.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
Don't come.
Stop it.
Listen to me.
It hurts.
How many times do I have to tell you?
It's not a few times.
It's a lot.
I'm not angry because I want to be angry.
You'll do something, won't you?
If you ask me, it's Kanda.
That's right.
It's Kanda.
Hamada likes a fresh woman.
What should I do?
It's too much.
Let's go home.
What should I do?
What's going on?
What's that?
It's a sea bream.
It's alive.
Oshima.
I can't say a word in that situation.
Say something.
Oshima, it's a sea bream.
It's a sea bream.
It's scary.
It's nice.
Let's go home.
What's going on?
Kuro-san, you should talk.
Talk.
How many times have we done this?
It's the real thing.
It's starting.
Start.
Please look forward to it.
Today, I'll do it for you.
Please.
Let's drink.
Nakai-san.
Yes.
Please.
What are you doing?
Eat it.
It's fresh.
Hurry up.
Oshima.
Oshima, come here.
Say sorry.
It's a different story.
It's not a different story.
What should I do?
I'm asking you.
Say sorry.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I said I like fresh food.
It's not fresh at all.
I can't eat it.
I'll drink it.
It's dangerous.
What are you doing?
Don't get in my way.
Let's go home.
It's not over yet.
I'll go for a while.
Why?
It's okay.
I'll go for a while.
I have to go.
How are you going to go?
It's here.
Where is it?
It's dangerous.
Don't say things that you don't like.
You've been saying it for a while.
What are you doing?
It's true.
You've been saying it for a while.
You're not getting any of the answers right.
What are you going to do?
I'm saying it because the method is different.
What's different?
I was going to say this.
Yes.
Why?
To be honest, Hamada is a class S.
He's a pervert.
Yes.
You have to be a woman who fits that.
You have to be class M.
Even if I say class M, I'm not that class M.
It might be true.
No.
Do something.
How many years have you been doing this?
It would be nice if you could feel Hamada's class S.
I can't.
What are you going to do?
It's a class S, so I can't do it.
I can't do it.
You can't do it.
No.
What's wrong?
Look at this.
I'm going to be a woman who fits that.
You can do it.
I can be a class M.
You have to do it.
You're going to be a woman who fits that.
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
I'm hungry.
I'm shaking a little.
That's nice.
Let's start.
Okay.
Start.
I'm going to be a woman who fits that.
You have to do it.
Do it.
I'm going to be a woman who fits that.
I'm scared.
This is scary.
This is hell.
Are you wearing glasses?
I'm wearing glasses.
You're really scary.
This is much too much.
It's too much.
It's like you're doing everything.
It's really like you're doing everything.
It's like you don't understand the depth of the earth.
You don't understand.
I'm wearing glasses.
You are the worst.
You scared me.
No, no.
I don't know what to do.
Hey, hey, hey.
Stop it.
Murakami.
I'm going to push.
Go away.
You are a loser.
I'm going to push.
Go away.
What?
Shut up.
No, no.
I'm going to push.
Go away.
Shut up.
I'm going to push.
You are a loser.
Who is the father?
I don't know.
I don't get it.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.