Five men gather at the windmill in the middle of the city.
The men's battle is about to begin.
Here, in Yomiuri Land, it's about to begin.
Gakiwan Grand Prix
The first Gakiwan Grand Prix at Chikishiki Water Slider World Championship
97 Gakiwan Grand Prix
We're going to be the fastest skaters in the world.
That's right.
Let's introduce the machines.
Let's introduce them.
Here they are.
These are the machines that have been chosen.
These are the machines.
First of all, the fastest machine will be chosen from these five.
Downtown will modify the machine and challenge the fastest country in the world.
This is Ueda.
This is amazing.
This is how he looked like.
He has a nice body.
Show me your back.
He's walking.
He's walking like a bird.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
The course is 41.5 meters long.
It's a high speed water slider on the old track.
Let's start with Tanaka.
Let's call him.
No.1, Tanaka.
Are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready.
Start.
6.36.
6.36?
Is this a joke?
What's wrong with him?
That's right.
Do it again.
Ready.
Start.
He's fast.
Look at this.
4.79.
Wow.
Start.
He's fast.
He took it off.
4.78.
Ready.
Start.
You hit your elbow.
Did I?
Do it again.
I'm really fast.
Ready.
Start.
Am I too slow?
Wow.
Amazing.
4.22.
Hey.
My car is heavy.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Look, there's a genius.
That's right.
What are you doing?
He's doing it.
He's really doing it.
Start.
Amazing.
Wow.
New record.
3.88.
Ready.
Start.
4.68.
I did it.
I think I'll go with Onuma.
I think Tanaka can do it again.
Why?
Why do I have to do it again?
Onuma is challenging the record.
We'll make you the fastest machine in the world with our hands.
That's a bonus.
Your eyes are shining.
Let's go with sparkling eyes.
Hey.
You're jealous.
We'll make you a machine with our hands.
That's right.
I'm jealous.
Do you want to do it with me?
No, I'm fine.
I'm fine today.
We've prepared something that you can think of.
Let's try it.
That's right.
This is what I want to see first.
What is it?
I want to eat it.
I'm going to go to Harabayama.
I'll play the castella before that.
I want to eat this castella.
I want to eat it.
I like castella.
Isn't that great?
The reaction has changed.
Castella.
That's great.
I'm going.
Get ready.
Start.
Castella.
4.60 seconds
It's not good
Is this Jaguar?
I think this is good
I want to try this
It's Jaguar
I think this is good
You are the only special one
I'll put this on my hand
I think this is good
I'll put this on my leg
I can't do this
It's a big service
Run
Good luck
It's popular
5.01 seconds
What is that?
I don't know
It's an elephant
You are late
It looks good on you
I don't know if this is a TV
It doesn't look good on you
He is a fool
Ready
Start
I can't do this
I'm panicking
I can't see
I can't do this
I came here to buy cheese
Let's go
What are you talking about?
I'm fast
I have little resistance
Have you seen anyone doing this?
Thank you
You have a jet engine
Run
What are you doing?
I've never seen anyone doing this
This is a great service
Ready
Start
I can't do this
I'm fast
You were cool
You came to help me
Ladies and gentlemen
It's starting
You are very energetic
I heard that you were satisfied with the last episode
I don't know
The opening was long
I don't need much today
I'll do it quickly
Time is running out
Why are you so energetic?
I don't want to
What do you think of downtown?
Thank you
Where are you going?
I don't know if you want to join
It's a very attractive place
Where is it?
If you want to go, I can take you
I don't want to go
I want to know the place
Let's go
You are an elementary school student
I'm going on a school trip
You said something good
That's the theme I'm aiming for
Let's go back to the past
I want to go back to the past
I want to go back
I can't go back
That's the theme
I've been to Niigata, Hokkaido, Sendai
I've been to many places
I've been there, but it's safe
Let's stop
I don't like the dirty world
Do you understand?
Money and women
It's dirty
I want to throw it all away
I don't need it
Do you have a beard?
You're an adult
What do you have?
I want to throw it all away
I want to go back to my childhood
You said that when you were in elementary school
I want to go back to the inn
That's a good theme
I'll buy you a pen
I'll buy you a grave
Is that okay?
Don't you think it's okay?
There's nothing to see
I think you'll enjoy it
You want to go back to your childhood
You have dirty eyes
This is going back to my childhood
I have a lot of dirty eyes
Please go
I'll refresh and come back
How do you know that?
Why don't you call me Mattsun?
Why?
What?
Old man
Now?
You look like an old man
You look different when you came back
I'm different
I'm like a rice with a heart
You don't need rice with a heart this age
I have a heart
But even if you have a rice with a heart
It's a mess
I want to go back to my childhood
I don't want to look like an old man
I'm an old man
You're an old man
If you call me Mattsun
Mattsun
Sorry
If you call me Mattsun
I'll change everything
You want to go back to your childhood
I want to go back to my childhood
I don't know
It's different now
It's nostalgic
There are always arguments between schools
Do you remember the ferry in elementary school?
There are many things
We were on the ferry
We were on the stairs
We were talking
We were elementary school students
We bumped into an elementary school student
I was talking and he kicked me
I looked at him and he told me to move
That's scary
I moved right away
You didn't move
That's scary
I moved
But I don't remember anything
That's not good
I don't remember anything
Matsumoto has a history of being raised by a mackerel
He was separated from his mackerel
Now he's looking for his mackerel
What kind of separation did he have?
I don't want to talk about that
How old was he?
Stop it
I won't stop it
I'll leave it
He was raised by a mackerel
It's true that he was raised by a mackerel
It's hard to change
How long did he live in the mackerel?
From 8 to 10 years old
He was very strict
Did he beat you?
He beat me
Really?
Really
Hmm
You don't cry all the time
No
Why did you send me a letter?
You don't have to send it
It's fine
Matsumoto has met many cute guests
Many people want to meet Matsumoto
What would you do if you met a cute guest?
It's the same for everyone
You don't want to be treated as a special guest
Let's say you're a mackerel
What do you hate the most?
I hate that
That's the worst
I won't shout
I understand
Even if you're a mackerel, you shouldn't be afraid
You shouldn't say,
I don't feel good
I don't have time for that
You shouldn't say,
I don't feel good
That will open up the heart of a mackerel
Let's say I'm a fairy
Like this
Do fairies appear like that?
There are many types of fairies
I don't want to be treated like that
I can't stand it
Why are you so happy?
Peep-peep-boo?
Hello
No
You're an old man
What are you doing?
You're a bad fairy
You always say,
Peep-peep-boo
You're a bad fairy
Do it properly
Why do you have that right?
You're not cute at all
Why don't you cry?
Do it
I can't play a double role
I'm a fairy and I met a man
I'm a fool
I'm embarrassed
You know that
Your face is not good
Is that so?
You should say hello
I don't know how to smile
You're scary
You don't like animals
You should do it like this
Do you understand?
You're a villain
If you don't do that, he won't open his heart
For example, ghosts are the same
Ghosts are bad
If you don't do that, he will be surprised
He will be surprised
I'm serious when I'm sleeping
I'm cold
What do you think?
Since you're wearing a kimono, I think it's cold.
I'm not wearing a kimono.
What did you say?
What?
What are you going to do?
I didn't say anything.
I want to use my butt hole.
What are you talking about using your butt hole?
That's right.
Wait!
What is it?
Hey, let me do something too.
Where are you going?
Isn't it really delicious?
Is it delicious?
That's right. Fireworks are always on my feet.
It's really delicious, isn't it?
It's delicious, isn't it?
How about the three of us go together with that gesture?
Are we connected?
Yes, we are connected.
It's beautiful.
A man who is stronger and more beautiful than ever.
That is a treasure bestowed by God.
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.