Your guest почти never comes.
Your guest
It's an rare occasion.
It's rare for the host to come.
It's an increased sight.
Oh.
Oh no!
This!
Oh, it's good.
You are宅者?
Well, I'm here to raise the ratings.
Watch...
At at this rate,
it'll be
completely voted out.
It'll be so hot.
Even if they come in without a gun,
they'll come in without a handgun.
They'll hit storm from the middle.
Right.
Oh, I'd like to publicly announce this.
Sure.
From August 30th, the 26th, it will be shown on the screen.
It's the best show.
Everyone who is watching, please watch it on the theater.
Mr. Hakuto?
Yes.
The first show...
6 billion.
6 billion!
My character will be 5.3 billion.
12 billion?
I don't want to do it.
I'm sorry.
Then, do you want to go?
Where?
Shouji-san's place?
Yes.
We're going to Shouji-san's place.
It's been a while.
Everyone's here.
What's this?
This is the Maiko-han Classroom.
I don't like it every time, but if you call me, I can't help it.
You've come all the way, so let's go together.
Let's go now!
Once you get hooked, it's annoying.
So, Toshiaki Karasawa decided to participate in the class of Maiko-han.
It's a good day.
It's better than I thought.
I'm a little nervous.
No problem.
Wow, a shrine.
It says here.
The Maiko-han room is here.
Maiko-han room?
It's like I'm always being cursed.
I see.
Unless it's a tatami room, it's not organized.
Is there anything to do outside?
On the contrary.
Hey!
Wake up!
Oh, scary.
Scary.
I was told to come here by the god of the waterfall.
What a coincidence.
Good morning.
The one who appeared in the video was the famous Shochu Murakami.
feel free.
Would you like to page全  mechanic in the class?
Oh! Brother knows it himself!
He is the brother of the beginner teacher.
Oh! Yeah.
He is cool!
But he pays attention to the details Because there are many old shoes.
I understand.
What?
This time, you're the teacher for the second half of the class.
Yes.
Excuse me, miss.
What?
There's one more student today.
Yes.
Oh, really?
Eh?
Is it spicy?
Yes.
It's spicy.
I don't think you know me.
Thank you.
I'm Koinon.
Eh?
That's my name.
That's your name.
Oh, it's Onokaga-san.
Onokaga-san.
If you can sell it at a gachiki, you can name it like this.
This is the back.
It's white.
What is this?
This is the number 575 that the president would be happy with.
575?
Something like that.
I'll be in your care today.
Yes, please.
You're a
I don't treat you like a special person.
What should I do if I don't want to do it?
Go home!
Get out of the main office!
I don't have time for that.
I'm sorry, but Mr. Yamazaki asked me to come here.
Oh, Yamazaki-chan.
What?
Your father was arrested for life for this case.
And you didn't hear anything?
It's not organized at all.
The hair of Maiko is pulling.
The Kyoto vegetables are running away.
I was doing such a silly thing, so it became a permanent report.
Maiko's items are usually scents.
It's a tool to make it look colorful.
Oh, sorry.
Hama-yako?
En-yako?
Thank you.
Matsu-yako?
Matsu-yako.
And...
Tai-yako?
Tai-yako.
You're new here, so I didn't think you'd come.
Here.
Sorry I'm late.
Excuse me.
I don't have any.
What?
Hoshin-kun?
Yes?
Bring it on.
What?
Bring it on!
I'll give it to you.
Go away.
Don't you need it?
You should take it.
Go away.
The sense of the game is...
This must be for sure.
No doubt.
It's definitely for sure.
Think it's a plate number.
What did you say?
I think it's a plate number.
What plate number?
There is a drawer like this.
This is a lot of things.
They are stored here.
There's a drawer like this.
It's fun to have a story like that.
The basic of Maiko-han is to sing.
Finally, the practice at the ozashiki begins.
This time, we're going to do it at the ozashiki.
Actually, it's still early.
Matsuyako, what kind of Maiko do you want to be?
I want to be a Maiko who is loved by everyone.
No!
I want to be a Maiko who is good at singing.
I'm sorry.
I'm...
I'm not.
Mr. Toyokazu.
I'm going to be the president.
Yes.
I want to be a good guy.
Is this a joke?
I've never heard of Matsuyoko-san.
Enyakko.
I've never heard of it.
What's your name?
Enyakko.
Excuse me.
Look at this.
It's good.
It's good to drink it from the side.
It's not a bar.
You're a good painter.
You're even a teacher.
That's amazing.
Thank you.
Seriously.
Oh, you.
Here.
I'll drink it.
Good luck.
You're a good girl.
Can I have a drink?
Here.
What's with that funny way of eating?
Well, it's just a man's habit.
There are a lot of people who want to drink with this kind of thing.
Oh, really?
What are you talking about?
The president is doing this and that.
You guys say it, but don't say it.
This is a project.
Yamada Yuki.
Can you do it?
Yes, I can.
Alright.
You do this.
You stand up.
Stand up.
There are people who love this.
Wait a minute.
Have you finished your beer?
Gari!
Yes.
Yes, I'm sorry.
I'm...
Look.
This is totally different from the others.
You're just full of excuses!
Hot is hot!
Cold is cold!
The kids in the blue floor are all hot!
Exactly...
I wonder how many words of render...
are used by the Japaneseller...
OK???
Are you ready?
Funds are NTDs
It is expensive
The meal transports the dishes
It is an important job
This is the example of cooking.
This is the president's favorite.
It's quite a secret.
It's morning.
It's like breakfast.
Secret?
Can you say that to the phone?
I can't eat this.
The distance to the kitchen is 20 meters.
First, he quickly prepares the salad for the dish.
He quickly passes the average amount.
And before he arrives at the house, he does a simple dish-washing.
Finally, he cleans the slide and delivers it to the house.
The president is tired from work, so he's hungry.
He can't go to work early, he's like a demon.
I'm ready.
First, Hamayako will challenge.
She and the other members will aim for the house.
Ready, start!
Good luck, Hamayako!
Fast, fast!
He is waiting for you.
Be careful.
Stand in line.
Eat bread there.
Don't take the sword.
He is waiting for you.
He is ready.
Are you okay, Hamayako?
Ouch!
Oh!
It hurts!
Are you okay?
I'm fine!
I'm glad I saw it!
Next!
Do your best!
Take care of him!
Please!
Do your best!
Ready!
Start!
Do your best!
You're doing great!
This is not the kind of movie you make for this.
Do your best!
I'm going to get over the wall and run.
Come on, Kintou.
You're running and you're running.
Oh, that's good, Karayako.
That's good.
I'm hungry.
Karayako, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Amazing.
That's amazing.
I want to do a perfect jump!
That's amazing!
How much more do you want to jump?
I'm going to do it!
Are you okay?
Thank you for waiting.
You passed.
You're amazing, Hamayako.
What's wrong with you?
You're not going to get any more of that.
I'm sorry, I'll do my best.
What do you mean by that?
You're a punishment.
This.
I'll bet on it.
No, no, no.
If you do it properly, it will be the responsibility of everyone.
Yes, yes.
Next is the night training of Maiko who can't do it if her body is stiff.
I'm Maiko, so I'm a virgin.
I'll be the boss and you'll be called from the next room.
You'll refuse it.
If you refuse it, the boss will come to play in various places.
Snacks from the guard, cabaret club, and the last place to go is this showroom.
I know. If you refuse it, you'll be hugged.
Matsumoto, you are the best!
I'll do my best!
Matsuyako, you can do it!
Matsuyako, you're here!
How are you?
I'm getting used to it.
Really?
How are you?
I'm very happy, but I'm a little bit...
I don't care about you.
But I'm so embarrassed.
What are you embarrassed about?
Because I pulled your bath towel.
No, no, no.
I don't want to see your bath towel.
You're so annoying.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
What's that?
You're so rude.
I'll go to the car and come back.
What do you think is the best way?
You'll feel sorry for me if I do that.
Let's do it.
Yes.
I'll do it.
Please.
Please show me.
Excuse me.
Thank you for your help.
You're welcome.
What is it?
I want to sleep with you.
Please stop.
Actually, I have a broken rib.
A broken rib?
Yes, a broken rib.
I have a scar on my back.
What is that?
Don't lie to me.
My butt is dirty.
My back is really stiff.
Please stop.
Amazing!
The training is coming to an end, and the rest of the training is in the blink of an eye.
It seems that you don't need to add anything to this.
I'll practice it right away.
Look.
Try to follow me.
It's a revenge.
Where are you following me?
This is my first time, so I always bring my paper cup here.
Don't just come to the scene like that.
Do you understand?
No, I don't understand.
If...
Tanaka.
Yes.
Please tell me what I should do.
You did your best.
I don't understand, but...
So, you're trying to change the atmosphere?
What was that?
It sounded like a cross chop.
Really?
What about you, Mayuko?
A cross chop?
I just did a cross chop.
You're not going anywhere!
No, I'm not going anywhere.
Let's go to the next one.
In any situation, the lost person has to go to the house.
Today is a good day, and the summer is hot.
The season is very stormy.
It's a land like that.
No matter what happens, I will go to the president's house.
Today, I will set it up as a storm.
Who wants to do this?
Oh, right!
Kana-san, you're a newbie.
Come here.
Kanae-ko, do your best.
Do your best, Kanae-ko.
Kanae-ko, you're a newbie.
Shall we do it together?
Are we doing it together?
In short, we'll do this.
This time, let's do it like this.
Ready, set, go!
Men's match!
Okay.
Men's match.
You can choose 5 people.
You can't judge a person by a woman.
The man you judge is a man.
I think a man is good.
If you judge a woman, she is good.
The one who has more applause wins.
The one who has less applause loses.
The one who loses will do this.
First, I think that the manly one is better than the manly one.
That's enough.
I don't know.
With such a applause,
Now, the one who thinks the wind is better, please come forward.
I lost.
It was perfect.
I thought I could bring it to the end, but the last one, the clapping,
at least, there was something like,
I've already won twice.
Let's do the storm.
That's right.
I'll show you how much I'm always ready.
I can't do it with a wind.
Please look at the heart of the microphone.
Hey!
Stop there!
They've got laughter!
It's cold!
We've reached Odachi.
Just a little more.
Mom, I'm too hot!
Here it comes!
Lady, the roof is on fire!
It's amazing.
I'm glad to hear that.
I've been a member of the National Band for a long time.
Shall we go?
No, not yet.
I'm still thinking about my last mission.
Yes, yes.
President, do you know how many people are in the investigation team?
Thank you for watching!