First episode!
The Gaki no Tsukai Alliance, Chikichiki Yamazaki Produce
This is...
Tantan Keikaku!
You can't produce.
I can!
You can bite it?
You can also do a bang!
Like this.
That's not good.
Lately, I've been slacking off.
Well, I'm still the same as when I was a rookie.
That's not good.
What are you talking about?
You have to change it!
But that's not good.
I said that, but did you think it was bad?
I thought it was bad.
What do you usually do?
Do you make jokes?
No.
Don't talk to me again.
You only play games.
It's dark!
I'm sorry.
You can't do that.
This time, you have to go back to when you were a rookie.
You have to make a joke.
A comic?
A comic!
I wrote a joke.
Really.
Can you do it?
It's really your idea, isn't it?
Yes, it's really my idea.
I thought about it a lot.
The name Downtown is old.
It's called Grand Bazaar.
It's a combination of our names.
That's not good.
No, no, no.
I'm going to sell it.
What should I do with this?
Can I write it in my own way?
Or should I say it one by one?
As it is.
It's been calculated all the time.
Hello.
This is Grand Bazaar.
Merci.
It's not Merci.
It's Merci.
Do you want to destroy me?
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
At first.
Yes.
It comes out like this, right?
Come out.
Hello, this is Grand Bazaar.
Merci.
Yes.
This is Grand Bazaar.
Oh, it's bad.
I thought it was an interesting movement.
It was surprisingly normal.
This is Grand Bazaar.
Yes.
I went to the zoo the other day.
Why?
Is it wrong?
I'll do it a little more.
Why?
I'll pull it.
I'm sorry.
I went to the zoo the other day.
Why?
I'm surprised.
I don't know what to do.
I didn't say anything strange.
I was pulled here.
I don't know what to do.
I can't do it without shaking it.
I'm scared.
I'll do it.
Then the girl.
Yes.
I don't know what to do.
I'll say it.
He says his role.
He doesn't need a girl.
He says, I don't need a girl.
I understand.
Then the girl.
Yes.
I'll go this way.
This way.
I'll walk this way.
Wait a minute.
I walked.
I can't stop here.
Don't say such a stupid thing.
I'm stupid.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to do.
This is hard.
My face is red.
Where is Rori from Asia?
I can't do it.
I'm wearing a jump suit.
Did you know this?
Are you inside the car?
I'm walking!
Hey, you're hitting my shoulder.
What are you doing?
You're doing it!
This is the impersonation of a gorilla.
Osaka...
Here, here. Osaka's famous punch, punch, punch.
What the hell?
Yes, yes.
What is that?
What do you mean?
You can't get it.
Why is it called what the hell?
Osaka's famous punch, punch, punch.
What the hell is that?
Should I go forward?
Yes, yes, yes.
Is there anything to look at the hair?
Oh, this.
Are you okay?
At the end, just say, it's over.
It's over.
Should I say, it's over?
It's over!
Yes.
Be careful at the end.
Me too?
Yes.
Do you want to do it together?
I can't remember.
It's all over the place.
It's all the other way around.
You have to talk about it.
That's right.
Well, well, well.
Don't worry about the details.
The basics, the basics.
It's okay, it's okay.
I don't think I can do it.
You can do it.
Be confident.
More.
No, it's not.
Be confident.
It's not that I'm not confident.
Don't be nervous.
Don't laugh at all.
Be serious.
If you do your best, I think you can do it.
You guys are the ones who can do it.
No, it's okay.
No, no, no, no, no.
All right.
It's not organized at all.
I wrote a story for downtown.
I'd like you to see that story.
This is a grand buzzer.
Please.
I am an animal hider.
Healthy.
Merci.
Hon madam
I'm back!
I went to the zoo the other day.
What the hell?!
There are a lot of things to learn about animals.
What do you mean?
Animals are more colorful than humans.
Colorful?!
Even if you say it's colorful...
For example, when you go out to pick up girls,
it's like this, right?
Excuse me, would you like some tea?
Something like that.
Well, at first...
You can't do that.
After all, you have to learn about animals.
Animals are amazing.
How to pick up.
For example, you have to learn about the nine-legged qi.
That's going to be super!
That's something you should learn about.
But it's beautiful, but it's too flashy.
No, it's not like that.
Let's try it.
Then the girl, right?
Walk over here.
It's a short tongue, isn't it?
A person or a human?
And there's no chicken.
But you said the short tongue was pretty good.
Now keep walking.
Excuse me.
Long for me is the age-o
A woman is a sea
Judy Long! Why?
What? What do you mean what?
I'm surprised. Girls are troublesome.
I'm surprised too.
Yes.
After all, animals are amazing when it comes to food.
What do you mean?
It's amazing no matter what you eat.
The meat and vegetables are fresh.
Very healthy.
Very strong.
Grandfather!
What's wrong with you?
You fight too, right?
Well, there are many things that make me angry.
Yes. In that case, learn from Gorilla-san.
Gorilla?
Gorilla is amazing.
Yes.
Let's try it.
Oh, you hit me in the shoulder.
What?
What are you doing?
By the way, I'm Karate 8 dan.
What?
It's a communication karaoke.
What is that?
That's a fool of communication education.
Don't make a mistake.
Yes.
You do it properly.
Well, I'm walking.
Oh.
Hey, you hit me in the shoulder.
What?
What are you doing?
Do it!
Huh?
Oh, it looks strong.
Osaka specialty, Pachi Pachi Punch.
What?
After all, there are many things to learn.
This is amazing.
Well, there are times when you are busy and you can't eat, right?
Yes, there are.
It's hard.
It's not delicious even if I eat it.
Yes.
But I'll break my body if I don't eat it.
Yes, yes.
In that case, you should learn Rakuda.
Rakuda is taking nutrition from kelp.
No matter how busy Rakuda is, it doesn't do anything like eating while moving.
There is no time when Rakuda is busy.
Really, Rakuda.
It's a joke.
It's forbidden.
After all, you can't buy animals.
Well, I used to have a dog.
Oh, you have to buy it when you come to Tokyo, right?
No.
Oh, what?
Have you ever had a pet?
Of course I have.
What does it smell like?
Kijirami.
I don't like it.
It's broken.
It's messed up.
This is a strawberry.
I told you not to make a mistake.
It's strange, isn't it?
Because I suddenly went to the zoo the other day.
Why?
That's strange.
You don't have to go.
And it says pull here.
Why are you wearing this?
It's cold.
It's really funny.
Why?
You're not good at it.
I can't do it.
You can't do it all.
You did it properly.
I was sweating when I fell asleep.
I can't do it.
You're the one who can't do it.
Hey.
Wait a minute.
There's a sub.
Ladies and gentlemen.
That's great.
It was easy to get in today.
The toilet was good today.
I put a tag on it before I went in.
Because it's their names.
When I'm in, I flip it over.
I'm using it.
I've been waiting outside.
It's like a judo club.
I'm in now.
I have to do my best to talk today.
I have to take back the first half.
What do you mean by the first half?
I'm wondering if it's okay.
You'll know if you watch it from the beginning.
If you turn on the TV in the middle.
That's hard.
What kind of story are you talking about?
I told you to put it on the screen.
It's a threat.
Yamazaki's story.
It's a story.
It's really cold.
You've been waiting for a long time.
What did you do at the end of the story?
Did you go outside once?
Didn't you go out once?
I had to fix it again.
What do you all do at that time?
I smoke outside.
I smoke.
Do you feel good when you touch your genitals?
I feel good.
I've been touching my genitals for a long time.
Is that so?
I usually touch my genitals when I have a lot of time.
Time flies.
It's completely different from the five minutes I've been touching my genitals.
For me, it's golden time.
In a sense.
It seems that you're not feeling well.
I don't care.
Wait a minute.
You're weird.
You were like that before.
You said you were sick.
You said you had a fever.
I don't care.
Why are you angry?
I'm saying this as a caretaker.
It's okay.
It's just a cold.
Did you catch a cold at the end of the year?
No.
What?
This is a holiday.
Don't say that.
Why are you angry?
What is it?
I don't care about your height.
What kind of world is this?
Who do you want me to tell?
I don't know.
I went to Disneyland.
I don't care.
No matter how many times I go in, Cinderella Castle is fun.
Do you know?
I know.
But I don't care.
I'm scared.
You're the worst.
Please come here.
I like that kind of thing.
I don't care.
Do you like that kind of thing?
I like it very much.
What are you doing now?
I'm afraid of water.
I have a question for Matsumoto, who was chosen by the man who looks most like a cola in Japan.
Please tell me how to drink cool cola.
I don't know why I don't have a cola commercial.
What?
How to drink cool?
Please drink it.
Wow!
Old man!
I hit you twice.
Well, that's fine.
Bring a washing machine.
Put the washing machine on your face.
Like this.
The bottle is flying away.
No, no, no.
I'm holding it.
What?
How do you hold it?
Like this.
Put the washing machine here.
I see.
This movement is cool.
It doesn't matter if you open the bottle.
Let's go from there.
I'm a drinker.
You wake up in the morning and open the curtain.
I wake up in the morning and drink cola.
Of course.
You wake up in the morning and open the curtain.
And then...
What?
You wake up in the morning and open the curtain.
That's strange.
Either way.
And then...
Open the fridge.
I didn't see it.
One more time.
Open the fridge.
And then...
Why are you laughing?
Because I have cola.
Why do you look so sad?
No, no.
You look sad.
Wait a minute.
Action!
Like this.
Your face is different.
You have a refreshing face.
Yes, I have a refreshing face.
And then...
Like this.
You break it.
I'm not laughing.
What's funny?
You look cool and you take an egg.
It has nothing to do with the cola commercial.
It's a breakfast commercial.
And then...
You take it.
What's that?
This is cola.
Okay.
Like this.
And then...
You pull the string.
Yes, cola.
Someone come here!
What's yes, cola?
Yes, cola, yes.
It takes a lot of time.
Really?
You have a refreshing face.
Okay.
And then...
You wake up.
You have to do it from there.
You come back.
What?
And then...
You come back.
Hey, hey, hey.
Sakata Toshio.
Let's be cool.
You're a cute old man.
You open it.
Yes, cola, yes.
And then...
You cry.
What are you doing?
Who are you drinking it to?
There's someone behind you and you're drinking it.
Your shoulder is all wet.
What are you doing?
Drink it!
You're trapped in concrete.
Yes, yes.
You're thrown into the sea.
You're chained and the building explodes.
You always escape in five seconds.
The voice of the third generation of Hikita Tenko is also loud, Matsumoto-san.
I'm going to sing a song.
Yes, yes, yes.
A big tsunami is coming from the west sea.
A big eruption is coming from the east mountain and lava is coming.
A huge tornado is approaching from the southern land.
A huge snowstorm is coming from the northern snowy mountains.
When you're in danger, how do you get out of this situation?
To put it simply, when I'm in danger...
What?
You're mumbling.
I really want to say this to everyone.
You want to say it, don't you?
I really want to say this.
Why don't you say it twice?
Because I want to say it.
Do you understand?
You have a mekuso here.
I want to wear a mekuso.
You have a mekuso on your right.
I really want to wear it.
No, you don't.
It's hard for me.
Please remember this.
If you don't like it, for example, bullying.
When you're so involved, what I really want to say is...
When you're in danger, your mind goes, oh my god.
For example, when you're bullied, when you get milk on your head,
your mind goes, oh my god.
I want you to keep that in mind.
Like your jaw is broken.
Do you understand?
There's nothing you can't get away with.
It's not like that.
When you're so involved, when you get milk on your head,
your mind goes, oh my god.
I want you to keep that in mind.
I won't.
I'll do it.
Can you pour me some milk?
Oh my god.
That's enough.
Stop it!
As a sex counselor in the entertainment industry,
I've been consulted by various entertainers.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
It's like, I've been waiting for this.
Yes, that's fine.
When you go out for sex,
please tell me the most comfortable way to live in this world.
What are you talking about?
How to live?
How to live.
I don't know how to live.
For example, what about your face?
That's a lie.
You know,
you just killed yourself.
Why?
Like this.
I have to put up with it.
You have to put up with it.
Absolutely not.
I have to put up with it.
You have to completely let go of yourself.
Make a loud voice.
How?
It doesn't matter.
More!
No!
Can't you do it five times louder?
Ah!
I'm scared of women who have sex.
I'm not scared.
Women are the same.
What?
I can do it like that.
So,
are you ready?
You go to sleep.
Wait a minute.
Can you see it?
Like this, right?
What?
Well, well, well.
It's okay.
Do whatever you want.
Right?
When it comes,
Hey!
Don't leave me alone!
Everyone is too embarrassed.
No, you always say,
Ah!
You always say,
What else do you say?
You say,
Ah!
No, I mean,
You normally say,
Oh, sorry.
I'm sorry.
Normally?
You sound like a man!
I'm starting now.
What?
The high-pitched tone before going,
So,
You say,
Ah!
Right?
Is that okay?
If you say so!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.