Youkai
Unusual creatures living all over Japan since ancient times
No one has seen them even though they have always been in contact with the human world
Good evening
Today
Youkai
You can't see youkai in Japan
Some people have seen ghosts
We are going to do a ghost test soon
Youkai
Youkai are disappearing
There are 5.6 million youkai in Japan
That's a lot
Don't make me laugh
I brought you this
It's worth 300 million yen
He is strange
This is a water purifier
It's worth 500 million yen
How much is it?
I'm borrowing it
This T-shirt is worth 2 million yen
It's a normal decoder
It's a decoder
Today is a very hot day in Tokyo
This is my usual attitude
Youkai's happiness
I'm getting nervous
There is a youkai in this bus
Look at the back
Hey
Look at this
Youkai ghost
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching
What is that?
Look at that
What is that in the middle?
Is this a youkai?
Let's get off
Are you serious?
Come on
Is this a youkai?
Don't get too close
What is this?
This is a youkai cat girl
She is the richest girl in the youkai world
She is good at selling people's rice at a farmer's rice field
Youkai cat girl
Don't look back
Youkai is acting like a good boy
I'm going to hit you
What is this?
I'm scared
Let's go together
I'm really scared
I didn't think I would see a cat girl today
What is that?
It's shining from the outside
No
Are you okay?
Be careful
What is that?
What is this?
The young man's favorite
He is the most dangerous youkai
He has many tricks
Youkai cat girl
This is a bad guy
This is dirty
What is this?
Stop it
This is a dirty youkai
Who is dirty?
Osaka
This is Osaka's youkai
Get the water from the other side
He is a good guy
Get him
What are you doing?
I'm just wiping
This is dangerous
This is really dangerous
This is an interesting youkai
Where can you find such a beautiful youkai?
This is dirty
This is a youkai with a voice
I can hear your voice
Let's go again
This is dangerous
The average age is too high
Come here
Two or three people
What is this?
This is a youkai from Akita
Youkai from Akita
He is a young youkai
He is a youkai
He is still running
He is being scolded
He will make me laugh
I'm getting angry
He is being scolded
Gunshot
I can't laugh
This is dangerous
I'm going to smoke
What having from a cigarette
I'm getting embarrassed
This is not good
Look at this
You shouldn't be scared like this
There is a boss character
Really?
What? I can hear laughter
What?
Hard wheel?
He is a former comedian, but he is pursuing the beauty of men
He is a hard wheel
He likes women and alcohol
He is the number one bad guy
He is the night king
This eel
Eel?
Hamamatsu
What?
What are you doing?
Are you a youkai?
What is this?
This is fun
Do you have a barbell?
Yes
Try to make a joke with this
Ok
Can you beat this youkai?
Let's go
This barbell
Idiot
This youkai is good at attacking
Stop it
This is a professional skill
Harper nice day
Harper day?
Don't you know?
Harper nice day
Let's go
Can I die without reading this?
It won't break
I don't think it will break
The youkai that I know
They used to be tough
But this time it won't work
What do you mean?
What is that?
It's sliding
This is a barbell
What is this?
Can you sing a song?
Please
You are a youkai
Youkai
What youkai
What?
The Japanese youkai has 5.6 million followers
Because of this youkai the youkai can't do anything
The boss character youkai
My face is nervous
I'm nervous
You are nervous
You
If you hug me it's over
You won't say anything funny
Can I wear this?
It's a mino
This is a mino
I see
It's hard
Can you lower the zipper?
Lower the zipper
What do you think?
I lowered it
This is a zipper
What?
I'll wash it
I'm a bit fat
You are noisy
I lost
Where does it disappear?
Run to the other side
Youkai run to the other side
Yamada kun
This is the worst
It was scary
How did you deal with it?
I did a lot of things
This is the bottom
Let's go home
Thank you
There are still many youkai living in the human world
They might be next to you
It's hard to do a broadcast at this time
Why?
It's hot
I'm tired
It's really hot today
How many degrees?
30?
39?
Thank you
39 degrees
39 degrees is 80
80?
What?
Did you pass by the sun?
Anyone can pass by
Everyone can pass by
What is it?
I forgot to tell you
There is an event
What event?
An event for 24 hours
You?
No
It's on this show
I think you'll get a address
Send me a letter
I'll contact you personally
If I say I'll do it here
There will be people who don't care
I see
I can't contact you
Let's do it together
I don't want to do it
The audience is tired
You
People say I'm like Matsumoto
When the audience is tired
I can do it too
You're standing here
Don't get me wrong
I'm your grandmother
Really?
No
That's how it is
I'm old
You're old
You have to think about it
Why are you lecturing me?
You have to put your elbow on the side
On the elbow?
You can put it on the elbow
I can't put it on the elbow
Listen
I can't
I can't put it on the elbow
Everyone does this
Do it
I don't get fat
You suddenly got fat
No
You're talking and you're like
I'll put it on my eye
I don't care
But you're a bit more thin
Has it changed recently?
Did it rain?
Rain?
Rain
Is it okay?
It's okay
Tokyo is also bad now
No
It's going to rain
You can't trust the news 100%
They exaggerate
That's not true
There's no harm in exaggerating
The news is explained in the video
There's no water
There is
No
That's how it is
They exaggerate
They do?
That's not true
Something's wrong with you
You're talking while looking at me
That's not a lie
That's not true
You're a fool
You're a samurai
I'm a country boy but I'm not a samurai
I don't know
The capital of Tokyo is
The capital of Tokyo
What?
The capital of Tokyo is
Is it okay?
The capital of Tokyo isn't just one
There are several
They only show the part where the sun rises
That's all there is
There isn't
That's why
How many percent is there in Tokyo?
There are places where there isn't
Like Shikoku
They say there's no water
But the people of Tokyo
Why are you eating sushi?
I know there's no water
You can't eat sushi
It's not sushi
You can't even make Indian food
You think everything is sushi
If you do this it's sushi
I don't think so
What do you mean?
There is water
There isn't
There is
Why are you saying there isn't
There isn't
There is
I'll change the topic
High school students now say they're scared
They used to be scared
Really?
Yes
They used to be scared
Are you going to sing for us now?
Are you going to sing for us?
High school students didn't have a place to sell their underwear
They just couldn't sell it
If they had a place to sell it they would have sold it
Really?
Yes
That's what they say
Everyone believes that
Someone said it's 39 degrees
But it isn't
You can tell just by looking
You shouldn't be fooled
They say it's summer
But it's not that summer
It's summer
It's just that feeling
It's not
You can say it's downtown
But it's not that downtown
There are a lot of students today
There are too many I'm getting lost
Mom
I can't fly
The adults are looking at me
What should I say?
It doesn't matter
This is serious
I'm not being shy
You thought I was cute right?
You?
You can really say that
You thought I was cute right?
Really
No
What is that?
This?
No, I'm fine
Why do people turn into evil faces when they smell?
I can say this
I can't smell anything when I'm laughing
You are also a prince of a very erotic country
You've smelled women's underwear right?
Yes
I'm also like that
Can't you laugh at that time?
No, I can't laugh until here
When I can't laugh
You can't do anything about it
I can't do anything about it
I can't laugh until here
You can't laugh like that
Humans are like the car's change
It's a neutral situation
When you smell, you make it neutral
And you decide if it smells or not
And if it smells, you do it
It's a very erotic situation
If it smells, you go in 5th gear
What do you mean by a very erotic situation?
I don't understand
If it smells a lot
That's right
I said if it smells a lot
If it smells a lot
What is that?
There are many trucks behind my house
One of them turns to the left
The truck says something
What is the purpose of this truck?
The truck is a truck
It's dangerous because it turns to the left
If you say that, it will stop
That's right
The truck has a trick
A trick?
A trick
It's not a trick
It's a deadly trick
Kamen Rider
What is Kamen Rider's deadly trick?
Rider Kick
It's similar
Where is it?
Rider's deadly trick
Rider Kick
It's a deadly trick
Rider's deadly trick is Rider Kick
Truck's deadly trick is Rider Kick
That's strange
I understand
I understand what you said
Let's get to the point
When Kamen Rider does Rider Kick
He doesn't kick without saying anything
Before he kicks
What is that?
Rider Kick
The truck says
Let's go, Nailin
It turns to the left