You're underestimating me, aren't you?
Hey!
This is no good!
Up until now, the use of the kid was the Grand Prix for anger.
The Grand Prix for stomachache.
The Grand Prix for surprised faces.
There are various Grand Prixs that decide the king
And tonight, a new Grand Prix that decides the king opens the curtain
Chikubi Water King Grand Prix
This time, we will have a battle to decide the king of the new genre, Chikubi Water King
The judges are two people from Downtown.
Thank you very much.
I think we are the most of these members who are sucking their nipples.
Based on the experience.
I think it is better to judge the person who is sucking their nipples.
In the normal sense, Hamagawa-san is also...
He is sucking more than me.
He is sucking more than you.
No, no, well...
He is a bit of a poison.
He is not a poison.
I'm not scared at all!
This time, we will challenge the moon-like star, Kokoriko Endo Tanaka
And the first appearance of the child's world, Miki Kosei
Please explain the rules
This time, we will do something that the challenger doesn't know
We will ask you to go to the target mode and see if you can suck their nipples.
However, there is a possibility that the video of a man sucking a man's nipples will be unbearable to watch on TV.
We have prepared a button in front of the two of you.
If you two are judged that you can't show it, please press the button that you can't show.
If you press it, the video will stop and it will be said that it is only sound.
If you think it's good, press the button.
The video will be back.
It's like a compliance.
I thought it was bad.
We can't do that.
Well, it's good.
At first, I thought it was a woman.
But it's not good.
I agree.
The person who can show the most on TV is the champion of this water.
Of course, the way to suck is to follow after sucking.
There is no follow.
Of course.
That will be the subject of the judge, so I would like you to do your best.
Let's go. The first challenger is Endo.
Thank you.
Now, Mr. Endo's target is this person.
Mr. Yoshimura.
This is quite a high level.
Yes, it is.
After all, he has a unique sense of tension.
It's a bit embarrassing.
This is really, at that time, he was called the demon army.
The juniors below us were already shaking.
He is a strict senior.
However, once he started to suck, he could take it all.
Eh?
Really?
He's that type of person?
He's still this young?
Even in front of his juniors...
Kakariko Endo, let's go!
Yes, thank you.
Good morning.
I'm sorry.
He suddenly came out.
It's hard to do.
He's good.
I'll give you a little bit of a break.
When I say it, it feels like I'm starting to get a little bit of a break.
I'm going to talk about it a little more.
I'm scared.
It's a solid story.
If you do a push-up and do a squat, it's like you're doing a push-up.
I can't do it like I'm doing it.
I used to do this when I was tired.
I have to hold it.
Like this.
You can do it like this.
How about this?
This is good.
Why?
You can do it like this.
Do you understand?
This is the hard one.
If you put your right ankle on it, it's not like you are leaning your right arm.
It's like that.
It's real.
I've never heard of it.
WhKapo,
Can Mario pick music boxes or send them to the
This is for the left side.
Left side?
Yes, for the left side.
Let's go to the right side.
Then, the K is...
I don't think it's okay.
I'll pretend to be a spring.
The left side is...
For the left side...
Oh, I see. I have to go back once.
You have to go here.
What are you going to do here?
I'm scared.
I pulled it a little.
You have to go straight.
I'm scared.
It's not good.
Please watch here.
What is this?
I was wondering if I could see it.
It's easy to breathe.
It's from the bottom.
It's not blowing.
What kind of Korean do you do?
What are you doing?
I'm doing a swap.
Swap?
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, but I'll show you.
I'm going to show you how to do it.
I'll show you how to do it.
I brought him here.
Wow!
What?
Look at this.
It's definitely a costume.
Amazing.
You're the one who's coming out.
What?
Amazing.
We've already crossed the pass.
His face is...
Amazing.
He makes a lot of noise.
When Kimu crosses the pass, he is very noisy.
That's right.
This is exactly what Matsumoto-san said.
Exactly.
He is a M.
I see.
So, if the channel changes, I can accept all.
He is the last one who was chosen.
He couldn't accept it.
Matsumoto-san said that there was no after-haul.
I was blowing.
That's right.
If I blew, there was no problem at all.
I also asked for the contact information.
It's real.
You know it, right?
I'm not kidding
I know it
The next challenger is Tanaka-san
Please
Tanaka-san's target is this person
It's here
It's B. Orogon-san
This is quite a challenge
I have worked with him several times a year
I can't imagine how he would react to this.
He might be scared.
He might be a little scared.
So I'm trying to imagine that he might be a little scared.
How long has Tanaka been a chikubi-sui?
Two years.
I don't think he's been a chikubi-sui for two years.
The last time we knew was in May this year.
I'm married this May.
I don't want to see it now.
Of course, I want to see it.
Tokoriko Tanaka, let's go!
Yes.
Hello.
It's a little different.
It's a special night.
I want to go like this.
I'm sorry.
It's hard to take off my clothes.
I was surprised. I saw the same picture.
You didn't see it, did you?
No.
The same picture.
I heard that.
We were looking for people in trouble.
I was doing martial arts.
Do you still do it?
Yes, I like it.
I'm so tired.
My body is so strong.
I'm so strong.
My arms are thicker than before.
I'm 4'6".
I'm working out every day.
I want to do it.
I want to work out.
I want to do that.
It's like a big fish eating a big fish.
Oh, that one?
Can you do it?
I can.
Just a little bit.
I can do it.
Oh, you can?
Oh, that's great.
This is the body.
Move your left hand.
Move your left hand consciously.
You are not moving your hands now.
I'm not moving my hands.
Bobby, you can do it!
You can do it!
If you become a
What are you doing?
There's a lot of boobies.
Boobies.
Boobies' boobies...
If you touch them, they'll move.
What are you talking about?
I touched them, but the boobies got stiff.
When they got stiff, the boobies were moving.
If the boobies were more stiff,
the boobies would move.
If you do that, you'll fall down.
You're talking big.
And then...
The volume is amazing.
You'll be like...
He's definitely not happy.
Stop making a fuss.
You can live.
What are you talking about?
Everyone...
He's just laughing.
Wait a minute, what are you saying?
What are you saying?
There are people who are like that.
But I'm not alive anymore.
What are you talking about?
I can't see it.
Robin is scared.
Oh, this is bad.
What is this?
This is bad.
It's dangerous.
It's not good.
What is this?
I was surprised.
What does this mean?
What is this?
For example,
I'm going to do it.
You two are so cute.
What are you two doing?
It's like a gel.
I think the gel is sweet.
It's not sweet at all.
I'm going to do it.
It's a tiger stone.
OK, OK...
What?
Oh, I'm choked!
tired?
Like if we have to cry?
I water-throw bath so theleo will be better than soaked
What?
It was good to enter.
I wanted to show my muscles.
I was glad to be asked to do it.
His nipples are quite sensitive.
That's what it is.
It was good.
So if you sit down, I don't think Bobby will be funny.
If you get tired once.
I can't put it in with Bobby.
It's amazing.
I can't keep my sanity.
Let's turn to the next challenger.
Next is Kosei of Mickey.
Please.
Why him?
Well, I think I look like a nipple.
Do I?
I don't think so.
Which one is it?
Please stop.
Please look at it.
I heard that it's better to have a nipple with a little bit of a rough feeling.
That's why I chose this.
I think he will go to his senior.
Let's see.
The target of this year is this person.
Daigo.
I can't see him.
Daigo is also a bit of a
When I was auditioning in Osaka, I was very scared.
I was walking and I couldn't see his face.
And the person above him, so the number of times he has to do the chikubi is a big hurdle.
I wonder if this will work today.
Now, let's start the chikubi of Kosei.
Kosei Niki, let's go!
Yes.
Come in.
I'm home.
Kou?
Yes.
What's up?
I haven't heard from him at all.
He's not home yet.
It's still Osaka.
How long have you been in Tokyo?
I've been in Tokyo for two days.
Living in a hotel is really hard.
But it's not convenient.
I'm sorry.
What is this?
I see.
I'm sorry.
You are the worst.
You are bad.
I was scared.
I'm sorry.
I like Tsukubisu.
I love it.
I know it's strange to say this, but I want you to do it.
He said it clearly.
I'm a reliable brother.
What do you want from your brother in Tokyo who is only for your nipples?
Then, please let me do it.
If I think, I can't do it, I can do it.
Why do you come from above?
You are trying to deny me.
If I ask you to lick my buttocks, I can do it.
Why don't you understand?
I'm saying it's hard, but I'm really tired in Tokyo.
You know that I'm tired.
I've never heard of it.
It's a wall of Tokyo I've never heard of.
Please take it off.
But we are talking.
Please take this off.
No, it's not like that.
You are young.
That's why I'm saying that we should decide.
I'll take it off.
No, I'll take it off.
Don't look at me like that.
Why are you taking it off?
What did you do?
Yes, it was in the mountains near Shibuya, in the north of Tokyo.
More then that...
Each thing you entered,
You had entered,
Good, But,
It was in another way and you left it.
Yes, take it to another body,
and at that moment,
One nice woman Hol Yoshimoto
came up here,
and she asked,
Do I have a顔?
Then I explained the meaning.
Glue.
But,
I'm not sure.
I think you have to be more energetic.
I see.
More energetic.
What should I do?
Take a sip.
I can't do it.
Forget it.
Don't look at me like you're saying,
I took a sip.
What do you mean?
I'm doing it once.
I don't understand.
I don't get it even if I do it.
Look at me.
You're being greedy.
I said it twice.
I'll forget it today.
Excuse me.
One night.
What is this?
One night is long.
Which one do you want to forget?
I'll do it.
No, that's not it.
The opinion of the person who gave up is not important.
I'll forget it.
I'll do it once.
Don't make fun of me.
Thank you.
You'll get something out of it.
I was really scared.
I was scared. I didn't know what I was going to get.
But you did a lot.
I can't change it anymore.
How many seconds?
I've already decided.
10 seconds.
That's a long time.
10 seconds is long and scary.
10 seconds of silence.
I'm the one who's going to change it.
Please tell me your opinion.
It's not normal for you to do that.
You're sitting in the back and you're screaming.
Can you show us once?
The trick.
Can I?
I'll count.
I can't see.
I'll do it.
Thank you.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5...
It's like this.
Look at this! I really want you to see this.
I worked really hard on this.
I really want you to see this.
You're really working hard.
Yes, it's amazing.
I really worked hard on this.
I'm really scared.
Look at this.
It's terrible.
You did it.
You are so hot.
I'm standing here for 20 minutes.
It's so comfortable.
How do I feel when I go home?
I feel like I'm in the
Thank you very much.
Work hard...
I'm freshed out!
Daigo seemed a little off at the very beginning
I wonder if he went to lane him instead
Just hard problem
But you had so much nurf at the beginning
He even had me standing in my face
I was stepped on my face.
So it was good.
On the contrary.
But the distance was shortened a lot.
I thought it was shortened.
But Daigo-san became more gentle than I expected.
When I said hello, he said,
You are the one who sucked my nipples.
But he was completely conscious of it.
He was completely conscious of it.
I forgot it, but Daigo-san still remembers being sucked in the nipples.
It's a very attractive event.
That's right.
Next week!
The final episode of the Chikubesuiyo Grand Prix!
Who will challenge that veteran comedian?
This looks like fun!
It's like we're dating!
Who will win the championship?
Do you want to do an inertia?
I want to do an inertia.
I think it's like a racer.
I'll do a hot pop-punk.
You must not laugh at the 24 hours of the Science Fiction!
DVD & Blu-ray will be released on November 29th!