How many meals can you eat with this side dish?
This time it's the same as the title
The winner will receive a prize
Last time, Suzuki-kun won 100,000 yen
Let's do our best this time
I won't say anything interesting
When did he change his mind?
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
Here are the side dishes
You can choose whatever you like
Then you can eat
We don't know which one you will choose
Let's start with Suzuki-kun
Lucky Seven
This is interesting
I will choose No.3
I will choose No.6
No.6? I see
Let's see one by one
Gao from the soccer club
Next
This is good
What is this?
Let's see Suga-chan's
No way
This is really good
It's the same
Let's see Sago-chan
This is not good
It's not good
If you eat too much, you will get hungry
Everyone, sit down
Start
You have to eat it until you give up
Wait
That man
Eat it with mayonnaise
Gao, second
Eat it now, eat more
Sago-chan
Finally takoyaki
Takodake
You are learning
Right, Hamada?
When I was eating, a man dressed up as Tozan came
He ordered 3 curries
He ate while crying
What was that?
He ordered 3 curries
He ate while crying
What was that?
I don't know
It was Tozan's
Let's see
Leave it
It's enough
Saga-chan, what will you do?
I will stop
Saga-chan got 3
It's big
Please open it
It's the worst
Wait
It's really bad
What will you do, Saga-chan?
I don't want to eat it
Saga-chan got 3
Open
This is
It's not open
Shake it
That's how you do it
Get out
Suzuki got 4
Open
This is the worst
Jam bun and cream bun
I want this
It looks delicious
Saga-san's soup is gone
It's gone
It's all gone
He used it too much
Wait
What is this?
Your youth has just started
Why are you like that?
No
Gochisosama deshita
I'm going to hit you
Evo-kun
It's light
It's really heavy
This is good
The meat is not good
He said I can't eat meat
Evo 0
What should I do?
What number?
Number 8
It's heavy
Open
Please stop
Please
Anko
Koshi-an
It's koshi-an
It's sweet
At least give me 2-an
I don't want it
I said I can eat 8
What kind of harmony is this?
It's like rice
It's like Iwanori
Iwanori is good
This is the spirit of an entertainer
Otomo, open
Evo-san
It's heavy
Let's go with raw liver
This is good
Number 12
What is it?
Hama-chan, please open
Please
It's the worst
I don't want it
It's light
It's a good face
Eat
It's pineapple
It's not pineapple
It's interesting
It's good
The rice is good
It doesn't make a sound
It's special
It's talent
It doesn't make a sound
I chose it
Number 1
It's heavy
It's a big service
It's so sweet
It's good
How many times did you eat?
4 times
He is doing something
I don't need a phone
You can put a pineapple
It looks good
Is it for a party?
Yes
No
You can put it on the table
Where are you going?
You can eat it quickly
I will put it on the table
It's a tie
Why?
It may not be on the air
It's a lot
I prepared something good
My stomach hurts
Start
It's not good
It's good
What is that?
It's a cat toy
It's starting
Please forgive me
It's called a combo
It's good
It's a good combo
You had a good break
I have nothing to do
I was wondering what to do
I went to the car shop
I went there
You went to play sometimes
I didn't have fun at all
I went to a haunted house
I spent 500 yen
No, it's not that
No, no, no
There is only this stage
No, no
It's like this
What's next?
I don't know
That was the scariest
In a different way
What is that?
You don't ride a normal roller coaster
So
Yes, yes
This
What?
You didn't go to a party?
I thought I had to ride
No, no
Let me say
Why couldn't I ride a roller coaster?
There was a reason
In the past, roller coasters
You were told that you only ride roller coasters
You are a fool
Yes
Why? What was the reason?
A roller coaster
I was a roller coaster
It's fine
Why?
What is fine?
From now on, I will become a warrior
I don't care
Tell me the reason
There is a reason
It's you
I can't say it
Have you ever been to a roller coaster?
There is a roller coaster called Jet Star 2
There is
The two of us
In front and behind
Like this
I'm not scared
Push
On my back
I'm not scared
Let's go
Who wants to go to an amusement park with you?
I don't want to go to an amusement park
Let's go
You are disgusting
Don't spit it out
What?
Let's go
I don't want to
Don't spit it out
Don't eat sushi
I don't want to
No
Don't eat sushi
I don't want to
I don't want to go to an amusement park
I want to go
I don't want to go with you
I don't want to
It's not like that
Where do you want to go?
There's a place where you can bungee jump
What's the point of going there?
Wait a minute
Even though we were together
You were beaten
Why do you exist?
I don't care
Anna is scary too
Aren't you scared?
What are you scared of?
What are you saying?
You and I are different
What are you scared of?
What are you scared of bungee jumping?
If you keep going
Keep going
What are you scared of?
First of all, it's high
When you fall, you don't know if you're going to cut yourself
I see
For me
The bottom
What do you call it?
There's something like a mat
At the amusement park
That big one
I'm scared of that
I can't stand that feeling
That's why
I can't do it
If you take it off
If you move it
Well
Why?
I need to take a break
Talent
It's better not to show it in private
If you show it
It's better to have a mystery
Yes
You like to talk
I'm full of mysteries
I only do this when I'm on TV
Basically
I'm a kimono
I ride a car
But
I can't do it
Like this
When are you wearing a kimono?
What is this?
Why are you kissing me?
That's why
On my day off
I'm wearing a kimono
That's a lie
Why don't you know
If I'm wearing a kimono or not?
I'm not wearing it
That's gross
Right?
What do you want to do?
I don't know
Aren't humans annoying?
I don't have pockets
Even if you cut your nails
You know you have to cut it again
It grows
That's annoying
I don't want to cut it
I don't want to cut my fingers
I don't want to cut my feet
If I cut my feet
If I cut my little finger
My posture won't be like this
When I cut it
I don't want to cut my fingers
I want to cut my toes
I don't want to cut my toes
Why?
You're talking about my fingers
I'm talking about my toes
That's poop
Do you want to do it one last time?
Do it for an hour
I don't want to
But sometimes you have to put up with it
You have to put up with it
It's not good
I don't want to
I've failed so many times
You're a grown up
Don't you know?
I've failed
The elevator
I was totally fine until then, but when I got out of the elevator, I suddenly went like this.
I went like this.
And then I went like this.
I couldn't take it anymore.
I was like a superman.
While I was running.
And then I went like this.
I could fly.
You were disqualified.
I couldn't take it anymore.
I went like this.
And then I went like this.
I said, Hau.
What kind of reaction do you take when you see your parents' sexiness?
What kind of reaction did you take?
To be honest, this is the end of the world.
If you are a kid watching TV, you should never show your sexiness.
It depends on how you look at it.
Every time you look at it, your attitude changes?
That's right.
You shouldn't look at it like that.
Go! Go!
Your father doesn't like it either.
Say something!
That's enough!
I think I've said this many times, but when I forgot to blow my whistle and went home to get it...
You didn't do it.
That's right. I was scared.
I can't believe I forgot to blow my whistle.
You were blowing your own whistle.
I was blowing my own whistle.
Wait a minute! I'm going to sue you!
I'm going to sue you!
Why?
Pay for your sex!
I didn't do anything to you.
Family harassment!
You said you were going to sue me.
Please praise each other in English.
Cute or beautiful.
By the way, this is the same.
Please praise each other.
Sweet!
Delicious!
Wait a minute.
What?
Delicious?
That was close.
That was close. That's good.
Juicy!
Juicy?
Pumpkin!
You...
What do you mean?
That sounds good.
Is that okay?
I don't know anything about that.
Miso soup!
That's not good.
What? Miso soup?
Soy sauce!
That's not good.
Soy sauce?
You mean soy sauce?
Damn, it's delicious!
What are you talking about?
That's not good.
It's okay.
My value.
500 pounds.
You said pounds?
I said pounds.
500 points.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.