Who will be the winner?
Today we made a board like this
This time we spent a lot of money
That's right
It's interesting to look at it like this
For example, this is DREAMS CAM
DREAMS CAM
Right?
This will be a red group
It will be a red group
And Mika will be a white group
That's fine
Wadawaki is a red group
This is a mistake
He is a man
By the way
In the 40th episode of 1989
When Mita Yusuko and Takeda Tetsuya were in the lead
This is the first shot
We went to the ZOOM
In the year 1942, when Yusako and Sakai were in the lead
You lost this too
This is Karaba
Based on this
Now, look at this board
I didn't watch the show last week
I said it was a white group
I said it was a white group before
I will look at this card again
You will look at it again
Wait
It doesn't matter if it's red
I can see that
What is it?
There are too many meaningless people in the white group
Yes
It can't be helped
I don't need SMAP
This
I don't need it as a white group
These guys
It's broken
I don't think this is right
That's what I mean
But last time, I said that the Checkers would be disbanded
This is the last time
I thought it would be fine
In the end, it's about how hard Torii will do
Who is the red Torii?
Akiko did it last year
She probably didn't do it for 2 years
You don't know
If you think about it like that
I think the white group is Torii
It doesn't seem like it
Torii?
Then who is Torii?
I don't think so
I don't think it's Sabu-chan
I don't think it's here
I'm sorry
But it's the first time
I understand
Then
What will you do?
For now, you decide
Say it
Why?
Well, well, well
Say it
Say which one
I think it's the white group
You think it's the white group?
Where did you come from?
Why did you come here?
I want to stand next to them
You want to stand next to them
I understand
So you and I think the white group will win
That's how it is
Right?
Yes
This time's punishment game
It's this
Ta-da! It's Hatonina broadcasted after Nyan TV broadcast
You have to do that
By the way, do you do it live?
That means on Nyan TV
At 4 o'clock?
At 4 o'clock
Why me?
A-chan is waiting for you in the cloak
A-chan
At the color bar?
At 5 o'clock?
If you lose, you will become a pigeon
It will be at 4 o'clock
For now, the red group and the white group
To get the right to say it first
Let's go to the match
We went to Yotsuya's pachinko
What will the game be like?
From now on
Each person will take 3000 yen
You have 20 minutes
If I lose in 10 minutes
What if you lose in 15 minutes?
That's my win
Of course
Then you should do it slowly
But you have the number of balls
When you have it left
Got it
Let's go
A-chan
I might lose
Matsumoto was sitting before
I'll lose here
Did you get it?
No, I changed it to this
I'll pay before I go home
I got nothing
I have 1600 yen and this much left
So you have nothing
So for now
I'll decide who gets the right to say it
I have the right
So I don't have to say red
The match will be
White group and Matsumoto
White group
I'll do it again after this
Ladies and gentlemen
It's Nacchan
Sorry
What are you wearing today?
Is it cute?
Cute?
Who are you asking?
Cute
You're close
What is it?
You're a bit sluggish
Who's sluggish?
Don't get excited
I'm not
It's Nacchan
You can't be sluggish
Is something wrong?
It's not like that
Really?
C2
I don't know
What?
It's Machan
It's fine
Don't make it look like a jingle
It's stuck
Look at it
It's round
Let's go to the post
It's decided
Kouhaku, who will win?
Yes
I'll do it
White
Why are you saying that?
We had a match
We lost
If you lose
I'll say it in the opening
On Nittere, on a black and white screen, a pigeon will fly
A pigeon will fly out of the cage
The picture will come out and the show will end
It will become a pigeon
Moreover, it will be broadcast live
It will be on Nittere at 4 o'clock
That's right
In the morning
You will
You will be a pigeon at 4 o'clock
But what do you think?
What do you think about the real thing?
There is a rumor that Checkers is not a bird
It's not a bird
It's a bird
Is it you who will ring the bell?
That's right
It's a good excuse
But that is
As you said earlier, the white bird is a bird
Kitashima Saburo came out
I just said it's a bird
You can't say it's a bird
But I didn't say the name
That's right
Sabu-chan came out
As you said, if you say it's a bird
The white bird will win
But it's not
It's a bird that looks like a bird
It's just a guess
It's not a bird
But it's red
I chose white
But if it's red, it's blue
But that bird will appear 2 or 3 times
That's right
Is that okay?
What?
It will appear 2 or 3 times
So you don't have to do it alone
Even if I lose to him, it's a friendly match
Why?
Why is it a friendly match?
It's a competition
It's a friendly match
I don't need it
It's because you put it in
It's a friendly match
I don't need it
What if I lose?
What if white loses?
Will you come out?
I don't know if I'll come out
You'll definitely come out
I'm always thinking about you
Really
I wonder if my hand will be okay
I wonder if your hand will be okay
I don't care about my fingers
Stop it
There's a story about whether to stop or not
Whether it's red or white
It's either red or white
Last year it was red
If it's white, it's white
So stop betting on white or red
Will you cry or not?
I see
So which will you choose?
If it's white, maybe I'll come out
It doesn't matter
That's right
Why are you making such a loud voice?
I'm right next to you
You can't cry on TV
You can't cry in front of the lights
That's an excuse for 24 hours
You're persistent
You said it 24 hours ago
It's hard to say whether you cried or not
That's why I think red or white is better
I always say this every year
It's a tie
Is that possible?
There's no such thing as a draw
Really?
There's no such thing
Which is it?
How many episodes do you have with that person?
Two?
Three?
You have three
One person is not enough
If it's a draw, the producer will join
Right?
The people who are watching this
Just look at the results
I can't help it
Who will win in the end?
Where did your strength come from?
You want to turn even Kouhaku into an enemy
What's your strength?
There's no such thing as a draw
But I don't think there's a draw
Why?
Kouhaku
I'll have you say it now
I was aiming for Kouhaku this year
Why did you aim for him?
Not with you
But now I'm aiming for YangYangYangYang
I think I can do it
It's a bit short
It's too short
I was wondering if I could win
It's okay if it's red
There's a lot of white
Somehow Masa
Toshimasa? Masatoshi?
This Masatoshi
Who is it?
What are you singing?
Is it a drama?
Yoshida Heizaku
Yoshida Heizaku?
Who is Yoshida Heizaku?
Do you know Kenji Noriwaki?
You're crazy
Is that so? I don't know
There's a lot of white
You're going to lose
I can't help it when I cry
That's right
I thought so
Kei Unsuk will cry too
Kei Unsuk doesn't cry
Kei Unsuk is the one with the beard
He sings with BeiYan
I don't know BeiYan
Do you know BeiYan?
Thank you
You don't know BeiYan?
There aren't many Japanese people who don't know BeiYan
People who know BeiYan
People who don't know BeiYan
It's hard
Wait a minute
People who drink iced coffee
What did you say?
I said that when I was Alice
Really?
Kei Unsuk
If there's a happening
It will be this
It depends on the happening
But I've said the happening
Ladies and gentlemen
I've waited
Today has started
Don't say unnecessary things
If there's a happening
I don't know what will happen
You can think of other things
Ah
Where is it?
It's here
Ladies and gentlemen
It's Batchan
Actually I'm not sure if I should go to university or become a nurse
You two are not worried about the future?
I'm worried
Sometimes I have to say things like this
I can't say bad things
That's right
I can't say things like this
You're not sure?
Do what you like
It's easy
It's hard to be a nurse
It's hard
I don't know
A great person will come
What is that?
Injury?
Yes
That's right
Just looking at the blood is scary
It's a hard job
I think it's hard to be a nurse
What else is there?
There are hard jobs
It's hard to be an AD
In the program
I think so
That's right
Is that so?
It's hard
The money is...
That's what I'm saying
It's hard work
I can't do good things
I can't say good things
I can't find a woman
I can't do anything
That's right
I've done that many times
In the program
What do you mean?
After it's over
I like to talk a lot
What are you talking about?
I don't want to do this forever
That's what I like to say
That's why
When I talk
I often hear that I was invited by an AD
Is that so?
That's right
If you don't have a job
Please do your best
Quiz corner
Ballpoint pen and mechanical pencil took the sumo
Which one did you win?
Thinking time
The answer is
Ballpoint pen and mechanical pencil took the sumo
The mechanical pencil won by pushing
Oh yeah
You called me
That's hard
Why is Osaru's butt red?
It's not a quiz
Everyone thought about it
Osaru's butt is creepy
When he was born
I don't know
His butt is like a rose
It's not because it's white
It's because it's that season
I've seen it
His butt is creepy
It's amazing
I wonder if he has a rose
I can't say it
It's sincere
His butt is like a rose
It's like a rose
Why is everyone's butt like a rose?
It's not good if everyone's butt is like a rose
It's okay if everyone's butt is like a rose
All monkeys are like a rose
That's not true
I'm excited
Why is Osaru's butt red?
Are you stupid?
Why is a human's butt blue?
There is no blue butt
It's an example
No, it's blue
You have a yellow beak
Is your beak yellow?
Is it yellow?
I don't know
It's blue
It's an example
I often say that the monkey's butt is red
It's not red
It's red no matter how you look at it
The monkey's butt is blue
It's not blue
It's blue
It's a little blue
What are you saying?
It's not blue at all
It's not a monkey
The monkey's butt is red
It's not red
It's a monkey
It doesn't matter how you look at it
There are times when you try to say the monkey's butt is red
I don't care
What?
It's true
The monkey's butt is red
There is no monkey with a red butt
There is
I found out today
Your TV is strange
Your TV
It's like that
It's true
The monkey's butt is red