In the early of the new year, the staff gathered at Sugano Mege.
What's going on?
You know, a while ago...
Iai...
It's not Iai.
Shiragatori?
I got a phone call from a client.
He said my sword is a toy.
Don't say such a thing.
Don't go that far.
This will be a problem.
This will be the last challenge.
Komomi thinks this sword is a toy.
The other day, Machan asked me for this sword.
He said it's a lie.
Even if it's not a hand, it's a toy.
So I talked to Machan the other day.
He didn't ask me to do it.
He said he would do it if I asked him to do it again.
He said he would do it?
I prepared a sword for you.
I said something good, so it's fine.
Here you go.
Thank you.
That's bad.
That's the end.
It's the end.
It's really bad.
Thank you.
Shogun Shogun
This.
I've done this before.
But this is the most dangerous sword in the industry.
This is a good sword.
If I had been told before, I wouldn't have been able to do it.
But you don't have to do it twice.
If you do it twice, the rating will go up.
I'm sorry.
I succeeded in Masamune, but you don't understand it.
That's why I'm going to do it.
I'm going to do it with Catherine.
Is this Catherine?
I'm writing a picture of Mr. Fuji.
This is also that.
I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
I hope the rating goes up.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to write a picture of me being mentally united.
Are you going to do it?
Let's do it.
It's better to quit.
Are you okay?
It's been an hour.
Has the balance changed?
Is your bangs okay?
I can't see it.
The program will be closed at this time of the year, right?
Congratulations on the opening of the program.
What day is it?
It's the second day.
It's the second day of April.
You don't have to do this program on the second day.
Why don't you do it properly?
I don't think there's anything to do.
Nittere?
Nittere itself.
It's stupid.
The drama is also slippery.
It's a double line.
What is it?
I can't say that at all.
It's a double drama.
I can't say that.
I can't say that at all.
Why!
Don't pull it out.
No, no, it's not like that.
But this year, I wonder what kind of year it will be.
Ninety-four years.
That's right.
Are you out of your mind?
Why?
Why would I do that?
That's why the yakuza are being threatened with money.
They're being forced into it.
No, what I'm saying is...
As for myself, I have a lot of work to do.
I'm doing five books right now.
I sing five songs.
Each one of them is a pretty intense one, right?
And then, I hear that you're doing some kind of drama.
I'll have you say it again.
You're out of your mind!
That's how it's connected.
That you're out of your mind.
Are you in a lot of trouble?
Then, if that's the case, tell me.
I'll do something about it.
Do you need money?
That's strange.
No, it's not like that.
There's no way I'm waiting for 2,000 yen.
That's strange.
If you're going to do that,
people will think that Matsumoto is having a lot of fun.
But I'm having a lot of trouble.
No, I'm doing it because I'm on vacation.
I don't like what you're saying right now.
No, it's downtown.
That's too cool.
It's a commando.
Why is it a commando?
I'll crush your legs.
Why are you silent?
No, I've heard it before.
It seems that the drama is good in many ways.
Wait a minute.
What's good?
When you're doing variety shows, you don't meet people.
But there's a lot of drama.
It's not like that.
Talk to me more.
This is a liar.
If you lie, you'll look like this.
It's normal.
The waiting time is long.
Everyone, listen and go home.
What do you mean listen and go home?
I think it's a lie today.
Listen and go home.
I don't like it if it's a lie.
There's a lot of waiting time in the drama.
If you say it's waiting for the sun,
the actress who cries until the next day...
What are you talking about?
I'm touching your nipples right now.
Actresses don't do that.
You're right.
When you watch a drama,
the actress is touching your nipples.
Why?
Don't think about it.
Idiot!
It's strange.
After the drama, they date and get married.
Right?
That's different.
What are you talking about?
What do you call that?
Actors and actresses are the same.
I don't understand the difference between actors and actresses.
Do you have a partner?
I definitely have a partner.
What do you mean you have a partner?
What are you doing?
I'm a man of body type.
I'll tell you later.
I'm not telling you.
I'm just saying.
I've been telling you.
I'm not telling you.
Whose nipples are you touching?
How many times have you done it?
About four times.
Four times.
At least four times.
I've only done it once in a drama.
Did you hear that?
Then do it more.
Do it more.
If you're really doing it, then do it more.
How many times have you done it?
If you keep doing it, you can't stop.
As a man.
So you're holding it back?
So I can't do it.
I can't have a partner.
When it comes to acting as a couple,
actresses tend to get involved.
They don't know the real world and the drama world.
You know it well.
Yeah.
You're lucky.
If I was doing my job now,
I wouldn't end up with such a beautiful place.
No.
I would have a good time with you.
I would.
I wouldn't have a good time with you.
I'm serious.
I would have a good time with you.
You're definitely going to come back here.
It's hard to talk here.
Let's do it here.
But...
But what?
It's okay.
What?
I want to change something this year.
What do you want to change?
We were just chatting in the dressing room.
You know,
Ryuichi Sakamoto came here the other day.
Right here.
He said he likes this drama.
He's the world's Sakamoto.
He wrote a song for the world's Sakamoto.
You go wrong?
Badly...
It's bad.
They lose to Japan.
They aim for the hit charts all over America.
Then they win by themselves.
It'd be great if it sold in America, you know.
downtown doesn't work, so change your name when we go to America,
and you'll be called Countdown.
That'll be cool, and in Japan nothing's going to sell.
On the songs.
Let's do it.
Ryuichi Sakamoto's PRODUCE.
Geisha Girl!
Hey, look for a new partner only when you're singing
It's Geisha Girl, what are you going to do?
What's Geisha Girl? It's our name
Is that so?
Why is it Girl?
Old man!
On the contrary, it's En!
I'm sure you can do it
I don't know
It's Geisha Girl's song, sing it!
Why do you like that old lady's food so much?
Like pufferfish, pork
If you can't find a new partner, I can try
I really don't think about it
It depends on the type of fish
That's right
If that person can do it, I'll do it
First of all, I can listen to it
Can you write it for me?
You know, you've been to a lot of Japanese artists
But you can't do it, right?
Takadaka
That's our Geisha Girl
It's not decided yet!
I'm still in downtown
Geisha Girl is dangerous
No, no, no
Oh my god
You didn't get it right
The market is different over there
Market?
That's right
What is that?
Do you sing in English?
Yes, yes, yes
Somehow, somehow, Nutae
No, that
You can't leave Nutae here
The title is Nutae, isn't it?
This is...
Let's do it with rap
Hey!
I don't have a thin skin
You're biting me
I can't do it
Hey, you there
What is that?
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
Once, Miho-kun
He asked me to come over to play
He asked you to come over to play?
He asked me how far is it
How many square meters
How many blocks is it?
1.5 square meters
How far is it?
That...
Say it right away
If you say it by color, it's green
No, no, no
By width
If you say it by area
The color doesn't matter
If you say it by color, it's green
I understand that
How wide is it?
If you say it by animal...
You say it by animal
If you say it by color, it's green
In the alphabet, it's Z
Z, right?
How wide is it?
Hey, you
What is it?
You're so noisy
Say it right away
It's a curry flavor
No, no, no
It's not a flavor
If you say it by color, it's green
If you say it by area, it's curry
It's a curry flavor
Of course
Let's think of it as the biggest event of this year
I see
Everyone, I'll start writing
I'll start writing
Do ants get full when they eat ants?
Of course
But it's like this
After eating one
If we see it, we'll know it's like this
The appearance is the same as the ants
In the end, I think
There is a habit of animals
Basically, animals want to be sold
They want to become big
They think about eating ants
Right?
Yes
Kirin's stupid joke
His neck is long
Did he eat ants?
So he eats ants
But he doesn't really eat ants
He puts it in his mouth and eats it
After that, he eats it smoothly
He eats it smoothly
This is the most
So what I want to say is
Everyone doesn't become happy
It's annoying
The postcard
There is nothing good
If you open the fridge, there is only green onions and ginger
What do you want to do?
I'm hungry, I'm hungry
What should I make?
I don't know what to put out
In winter
I often see people with red noses
What is a copy robot?
No
I have a cold
I have a cold, so my nose is red
My nose is itchy
What does a copy robot mean?
Wait a minute
Am I mistaken?
Of course
Of course, Hama-chan
Then what is it?
Is there really a copy robot?
It's not like that
The reason why my nose is red is
That is
Laser
It's one step ahead
I don't know what it is
I'm happy 20 years ago
I understand more and more
If you get a laser, you will be happy
In a sense, you will be happy
Are you unhappy?
I am happy
When you are entangled with someone
When you think it would be nice if you got a laser
Everyone has one or two
There are times when I am entangled
I am happy that I get a laser
Does it have any power?
Of course
It's not just coming out, is it?
It's not just coming out, it melts things
It erases things
It melts things?
It erases things?
Yes
Please let me hear more stories
And then
When this area was still in the middle of the night
Do you know?
Well, it's okay
You are happy, right?
When the laser comes out
Isn't that 20 years ago?
Yes
20 years is a long time
It's my adolescence
Your adolescence
Your acne has finally disappeared
That's right
In terms of society
I was finally recognized as an adult
You were recognized
You smoke
You drink
You shake your hands
You are recognized
Yes
That 20 years
Happiness
20 years ago
Yes
Okay, you graduated
Thank you very much