The
Thank you!
I've been through a lot of things like crook, but I've never been accepted.
You've never been accepted?
I'm 54 years old, but I've never been accepted.
I've never been accepted.
But...
I've been accepted a little.
Well, today is your birthday.
Thank you very much!
Happy Birthday
Happy Birthday to you
Happy Birthday...
Sorry?
He is out...
I sang too much
You spirits must have erased it
He erased that
You are so naughty
You should have erased that
Yes
Sorry, I'm a mess.
And it's already...
It's melting.
It's not 5.
It's not that much.
It's both OK.
It's not 5 or anything.
It's not enough?
I'm really curious about this.
That's true.
There's more.
There's 4.
There's no 4.
Just 5!
I don't know anymore
You can do it!
Happy birthday to you!
Thank you!
Cheers!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
It was good.
They are so popular among the members.
Really.
They are popular 30 times.
This program has been on air for 29 years.
He's 55 years old, and he's 30 years old.
30 years old is amazing.
It's amazing.
That program is...
Because the members haven't changed.
There are many stories about going home in the water.
But...
There's no such story.
The company will tell you.
Yoshimoto will tell you.
The members will tell you.
They won't change the members soon.
I thought Yama would stop when he went to Osaka.
I think so.
Will you stop?
I will.
Wait, wait, wait.
I didn't mean to come here on purpose.
Well, you take the Shinkansen every time.
It's not a good way to communicate.
The Shinkansen's president also said that.
JR JR.
JR is the one who bought it.
He said, you shouldn't put this on.
Where do you live?
Where are you going?
You're in Tokyo, right?
The president also said, there's no point in going.
There's no point?
Thanks.
Love Trumpet!
Wait for it...
This mast be mischievous.
vocalist
He is J.Dinah炫 flips.
that's so strange
Are you J.Dinah?
I am J.Dinah.
21 years have passed since I became a kid
Every time we meet, you are always kind
It's hard to make a smile, but it's wonderful to make a smile
I always learned those two things close to me
Matsumoto-san, Matsumoto-san, thank you always
When I don't know why I can't explain it well
At times like that, you always change my smile
Thank you for being born
It's simple and the most...
It's a bit difficult to sing it.
It's not easy to sing it.
That's right.
Today we had a station show.
What do you think?
Everyone is celebrating my birthday.
Yes.
They are saying that they are happy.
Singing is good.
It makes you do things you can't usually do.
That's true.
What about the lyrics?
Did you write it?
Tanaka is not a professional singer, so he has a great singing ability.
That's true.
But he is a good singer.
He is doing his best in the atmosphere of the song.
I felt that he was doing his best in the atmosphere.
I don't care about the evaluation of the song.
The fact that the content came in is a good thing.
I said that the content came in.
What?
Let's be friends.
It's your birthday!
It's fine if you're happy for a little bit.
That's right. That's enough.
That's enough.
There's no way I wouldn't be happy.
That's good.
I'm happy for that.
It's good.
It's worth it.
Tanaka thought about this.
Of course.
How many years have you been a kid?
We've been a kid for 4 years.
You've been a kid for 4 years?
I was 25 years old.
That's fast.
But in other words, there is no time when I was only out for 4 years.
I'm really grateful.
Since the last season.
I was doing it.
I started doing it when I was a bomber.
I quit the bomber in the middle.
I was only a bomber.
I introduced you to Matsumoto-san.
Tanakao.
He came to pick me up in Tokyo.
When I first finished it.
When I arrived in Tokyo on the last Shinkansen, the taxi stop was so crowded.
I see.
I couldn't get in.
I said, sorry, but could you please stand in line?
I was sitting in the back seat.
I was lonely, but Tanaka was there.
Oh, really?
I was so serious.
Yamaguchi and I were in the back, and Tanaka was next to the driver.
I didn't say a word until we arrived.
You were nervous.
You're still nervous.
Nice to meet you.
I could tell from behind that you were a bit down.
I was down and looked like a clown.
You didn't move at all.
If you think it's funny, then it's not a problem.
I was nervous.
After that, I'll do it again.
Ah, this is what you wanted.
That's right.
Do you remember?
For the first time.
That's right.
It's these bands, you know?
With a bashful moment outside a first-time In- attendant's
A woman has been picked up
On the first-ever society reineletide
I was the one who wanted to take you with me
I was the one who was greedy and had no money
He said,
I'm going to borrow your card
He gave me light
The one who gave me the passport of a comedian I met was you, Mr. Matsumoto.
I will run this path desperately from now on
I am grateful
Wonderful!
You sang it!
I sang it
It was good
It was really good.
What?
I thought, maybe there was such an episode.
There was a video called Dan.
Yes, Nakameguro. It's gone now.
It's gone.
I've been here for a long time.
I was riding a Jaguar when I was riding a Mazumoto.
I didn't have any money, so I borrowed it.
What video?
A little bit of a scab.
Both of you?
You didn't rent a single movie?
We didn't rent a single movie, we rented all the movie tickets.
How many movies did you rent?
We rented about 7 movies.
In Matsumoto's car,
Matsumoto divided the movies into two parts.
This is the end, this is the end.
This is the end.
I really remembered that.
I thought it was nostalgic.
It's not like DVDs now.
You can't tell by looking at this.
I have to keep it.
Sometimes I make mistakes.
That's a good thing.
After I finish, I get a massage.
What kind of massage?
I feel good.
Shoulder or neck?
No, I feel like a sukebe.
I don't know what sukebe is.
I don't know.
The name of the shop is called the magic hand.
I don't know either.
I wonder what kind of magic it is.
I see.
A very small woman brought a mysterious bag.
I tried to look at it, but I couldn't see it.
The light was dim.
I don't remember much from then on.
I've been doing a lot of things.
I call him Eli.
I've heard of him.
I'm not a benefactor, but I'm saying that you should never see it.
What's inside?
What are you doing?
I'm a girl.
Your imagination?
Your imagination is a girl?
I'm a girl.
At that time, I was a four-legged bike.
I was in this shape, and I was doing a lot of things.
I don't think I'm a girl.
I'm not a woman.
Oh, really?
I'm not sure if I can say this in this costume.
You're a girl.
I'm a girl.
I'm going to record it today.
It's going to be a long day.
I'm going to write a Hamashou.
Well,
I like it.
It's a little different from Hamashou.
Matsumoto-san, I'll keep on wishing for you, Matsumoto-san
I'm stoic about comedy, I can't do it, I say it right away, it's really funny
I really admire that kind of thing, the most interesting is the most important
The most extreme of the wicked ideas
The front line of the world of laughter
There are no people who don't laugh
There are no people who don't admire
H.I.T.O.S.H.I
People are your heart
Light shines on the dark world
Thank you Matsumoto-san for laughing with me
I will keep on asking you, Matsumoto-san, please
Happy Birthday!
It was a surprising song.
There was a bit of rap in it.
It's a young song.
It's the youngest song.
It's a new song.
It's different from the others.
It's different.
We're not good at it.
I wanted to convey my feelings,
and the lyrics of the rap came out immediately.
It came out.
I think it's because of my sister.
I've been a kid for 18 years, but I still think of her as my sister.
No.
I can't remember anything else but Nori Yoshio and Matsuno-san.
You mean your sister?
No, I mean Inomoto.
Oh, I see.
It's complicated.
I thought it was just me.
Fujiwara is cool, too.
He's like a Hanyu star.
He's a three-shot.
Yoshimoto is like Chang Gung Sok.
It's close to the Korean star, but it's not the Chang-Gun style.
Oh, that's right.
Do you remember?
After the recording
You treated me to dinner
You always said
That you would go home
After shopping at the store near your house
You mutter, I get off, and disappear into the shop
Good work, I bow my head and go home
Since then, the moon has been flowing, and you have taught me
At that time, I didn't always have anything to buy
I sent it to you so you wouldn't notice
It was like that, but it was getting worse and worse.
What?
It was like a impersonation.
Was it?
No, no, no.
Really, this is being said strictly.
What?
Who are you talking to?
It's a little Hamashou-ish.
Well, I'm really sorry about this, but it's similar to Jigoe.
Do you remember the content now?
I think everyone has that.
I think Hamagawa-san has that too.
He's a junior.
He's surprisingly considerate of his seniors.
He tells them to go home and pays for the taxi.
That's a problem too.
If you suddenly get a few thousand yen from your senior.
But it's better to send them close.
I don't have much to do, but I go there sometimes.
I see.
I don't really...
Well, I think everyone does that.
No, no, no.
But I was grateful.
That's right.
At that time, we went together about 4 or 5 times a week.
Oh, yeah.
That's almost all.
I didn't have anyone, to be honest.
Actually, you're the first in Tokyo.
That's right.
And then six months later, Downtown came to see me.
Matsumoto was really all alone.
I was really all alone.
We were together every day.
There was also that end of the show, right?
Going to the store and stuff.
In the video store on the hillside,
I borrowed Matsumoto's card.
I borrowed 6 of them.
I forgot to return them.
I didn't get married at that time.
I was a man who couldn't clean up.
I was in a mess at home.
Did you retire?
I don't know because I'm lost.
I was really pissed off.
I was thought I retired.
I went to borrow it, but I couldn't lend it.
I haven't been returned yet.
I see.
And then, for about an hour, he was wearing a very funny, very funny, very funny outfit.
Very funny, very funny, very funny.
I thought, if I hadn't returned the video, I wouldn't be so angry.
But I'm the one who's at fault.
That's not true!
I can't return it.
From that time, when I got angry, Yamaaki started drawing Doraemon.
He wanted me to help him.
It's like the Doraemon from the Dragon Ball.
If it was the Doraemon, wouldn't it save me?
I don't know. I don't have any intention.
Did you write it without getting angry?
No, I wrote it.
You wrote it without getting angry?
I'm a little mad.
You're really angry?
Well, I'm asking you.
What are you doing?
You won't get angry if you see it.
I can't get angry.
I'm a little of a giant.
This is not good
After this, the person we never expected will come to celebrate
Hello
Welcome
The legend is here
I feel a little nervous to be here longer than Tommy
A talk show without a host
We have to do the show together
How is it?
On the 24th, 11pm
There are many things
I see.
I played with girls a lot.
We played together.
We got along and we broke up.
We broke up and we met again.
I met a girl for the first time.
Matsumoto asked her,
He asked me,
Do you want to drink something?
He called me, Jean.
Jean?
What does that mean?
What kind of Jean?
He is a man of one year.
He asked me,
Do you want to drink anything?
I think it was the first time.
It was the first time.
That's good.
So, I think it was that.
When she became one with him,
I think she overcame him.
It's a good thing that you're a member of the committee.
You're saying it from a distance.
What are you saying?
It's dangerous.
This is a committee.
It's a time when it's sharp.
I thought it was a little bit,
but it's not smiling at all.
I thought, he's a person who accepts.
I didn't know that.
It was so amazing.
I have a lot of memories.
We've been friends for a long time.
That's true.
Please come in.
Welcome.
Oh, hello.
Happy birthday, Mr. Hashimoto.
Thank you very much, Momiji.
Momiji too.
Wow, it's so beautiful!
Thank you very much!
Next week...
Matsumoto's Birthday Party
That person who we never expected to see
And his partner Hamada too