Well...
I'm in trouble.
What is it?
I don't know...
when I'll be able to take a break.
You're not cold?
Excuse me.
Good morning.
Can I talk to you?
Why?
What is it?
What's wrong?
I got some information yesterday.
Aki-chi is in love with a great Shina.
What?
You should have told me.
I was wondering if you could tell me today.
That's right.
What's wrong?
A great Shina is in love with a great Shina.
What's great about a great Shina?
Anyway, everyone...
Well, that's what Tajima says.
Why?
You're a great trustee.
Let's go see.
How many times have you been fooled?
Yes, please.
You're a great trustee.
Let's go.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Excuse me, this is the place.
Really?
I don't trust you.
We'll be out soon.
Really?
Tajima is right.
What's going on?
What's going on between you two?
I don't get it.
This is the place?
This is the place.
Why are we the only ones here?
Really?
Let's dig.
I've never done this before.
It's true.
It's an excavation.
I wonder if something historical will come out.
Nothing's coming out.
What is this?
If this doesn't come out, it's the worst.
It's the worst.
You have to dig that much.
I'll dig around here.
Oh!
Did you find something?
I found something.
What is it?
What is this?
It's in a shallow place.
What is that?
Oh!
What is it?
And this.
This is here.
It's a takuto.
And it's a sashimi.
It's nostalgic.
What generation is takuto?
Takuto?
No, I rode it.
Really?
You rode it?
Yamazaki and I didn't ride it at all.
Ran was promoting this.
That's right.
Ito Ran?
Ran's something.
Something will come out.
Something may come out.
It's nostalgic.
Let's dig hard.
Isn't there anything here?
Something got caught again.
Let's go there.
What is it?
What is this?
It's different from the plan.
It's a Troy curtain.
It's nostalgic.
Why is it in a box?
This is nostalgic.
It's nostalgic.
But Yankee was here.
That's right.
It's Yankee.
It's a white high-neck.
This is delicious.
What?
What's wrong?
There is something.
Something is coming out.
What is it?
It's a Tominaga Ichiro.
It's nostalgic.
This is amazing.
It's a Tennis Tournament Pro.
It's nostalgic.
It's amazing.
Don't you know the Tennis Tournament Pro?
Really?
I don't know.
This is nostalgic.
He is the first famous tennis player in Japan.
It's the famous Tennis Tournament Pro.
I know.
It's a video.
It's a video tape.
What is this?
There is nothing in it.
Let's take a look.
There is a TV.
It's a TV.
What is this?
It's a playback.
It's okay.
It's finished.
It's a Lamborghini.
It's nostalgic.
It's for editing.
It's popular.
What is this project?
What is this?
It's amazing.
It's nostalgic.
How many years ago was this?
It was 15 years ago.
It was in the 80s.
It was in Osaka.
It was 10 years ago.
It's nostalgic.
I'm looking forward to it.
What is this?
I was prepared.
It's full.
It's not full.
What is this?
It's a flower box.
Is this a flower box?
If it was a flower box, I would have worked part-time here.
Really?
Yes.
What time is it?
It's 3 minutes and 8 minutes.
It's a flower box.
It's nostalgic.
I worked part-time here.
Really?
Yes.
I organized traffic.
It's nostalgic.
I've never been there.
It's very nostalgic.
It's amazing.
I want to take this home.
What kind of scene is this?
It's nostalgic.
I told you it's nostalgic.
It's hot.
I told you it's 100 yen at a 100 yen shop.
What is this?
I'm a gorilla.
It's nostalgic.
I had this doll.
What is this?
I'm a gorilla.
It's a good one.
It's a gorilla.
It's small.
I didn't know that.
I was so close.
I was close.
I'll give you this.
I don't know at all.
The next day
It's here again.
I don't know at all.
Good luck, Matsumoto.
It's here again.
What is it?
It's a Romeshi.
It's nostalgic.
I know it.
It's a Romeshi.
I don't know.
It's nostalgic.
What is this?
It's a change.
Ponce.
It's nostalgic.
I know that.
It's very famous.
The next day
It's here again.
Something came out.
What is that?
It's a game software.
It's a Famicom.
What is that?
Star Soldier.
I don't know.
I play games, but...
I have more.
The next day
It's here.
Matsumoto.
There's something big.
I know this.
Madame Yann
Madame Yann is my ramen
I know Madame Yann
I know
It's a high-class name
It's our time
We were making a joke
Madame Yann
You can't make a joke out of a person's stuff
Madame Yann is my ramen
Hey
Tanaka, something's coming out
I have something
Here it comes
Hey
It's big
What is it?
It's not big
It's not big at all
Tanaka
It's a morer
I knew it
There was a morer
As if it were alive
I was like this
But I can't do it at all
Tajima, this place is amazing
Hey
Yes
Look at this
Oh
Wow
It's a morer
What is it?
I've never seen it
It's a morer
You'll know when you see it
Wait, the video
It's still coming out
Let's take a look
What is this?
Look at your shadow
What is it?
Chocobay
Look at the sky
I don't know
Is it Chocobay?
It's amazing
I don't know
It's Chocobay
I want to drink it
Chocobay
What is this?
I don't know
Morinaga Chocobay
It's Chocobay
It's cheap
Why don't you know Chocobay?
What is Chocobay?
It was a huge boom
There was a bay seal
I can't collect it
I took a picture of the name
Hitobay
I was looking for my name
I wanted Yamabay
Yamabay
Chocobay
What is it?
Did you get it?
This is amazing
What is it?
Mataro
I know this
This is amazing
It's a dummy Oscar
I don't know
Are you stupid?
You are a serial killer
Don't you have anything?
Something came out
Something came out?
This is
How about this?
Eat
I love this
There was ice cream
It was like a sports bag
It was delicious
This is so nostalgic
Matsumoto is coming
Really?
What is it?
This is good
This is so nostalgic
There was a container like this
Tower
This is Eroica
There was Eroica
There was Eroica Old Toilet
This is so nostalgic
The smell
Eroica
This is so nostalgic
There is nothing
It came out
It came out again
Matsumoto will be happy
Robotacchi
This is so nostalgic
If you are a human
Be a friend
If you are a robot, be a robotacchi
Time goes by
Even if the times change
In the corner of their memories
Nostalgic things that have continued to remain
When I was a child
That toy that everyone collected
Youth
That cartoon that I enjoyed with my friends
The good old days of Showa
The number of such memories
It is a proof that they have lived
I don't know if I can be buried
I'm sorry
I'm angry
I am a child
Gaki Gaki-kun
Gari Gari-kun
I understand
What did you understand?
It was a little weak
It was about 48 points
What are you talking about?
48 points
I'm sorry
32 points of talent
It's below this
But I wasn't afraid
What do you mean?
Among the regular users
I am the only one
The only one
That's right
Tanaka is married
I was surprised
Seriously
That kid
That thin beard
I was surprised
Overall
If you think about it
You and Imada
Me and Imada
And
How far can you go?
Okama no Fuji
That's Okama
I don't know
It can't be helped
How far can you go?
I don't know how to use Gaki
Everyone has Gaki
That's right
What do you think?
It's like this
You can't draw
No
No one will introduce me
Right?
Why?
Can you introduce Kozuki Maya?
What?
Can you introduce someone like Kozuki Maya?
Who is Kozuki Maya?
I don't know
I don't know either
There's no one like Kozuki Maya
Who is Kozuki Maya?
I don't know
The atmosphere looks good
It looks like it's tight
Is there someone like Takarazuka?
There's no one like that
Don't you know?
Kozuki Maya
I don't know
What is that?
It's like Misaki Kyouka
There's no one like that
Someone who says I know
Someone told me
What kind of image is that?
What kind of image is Misaki Kyouka?
I don't know
I don't know either
I think it would be nice if there was someone like that
It's a difficult story
If that happens, when you and Imada get married
What kind of woman will you be?
That's right
I'll tell you this
Imada wants to get married
She doesn't have a girlfriend
Even now, she's asking if there's someone like that
If you ask her, she'll do it right away
Really?
It's a little different from me
There's another one
Yamamoto from Gokuraku is also single
But I don't want him to be in the same group
It's different
The way he thinks is different
The way he walks is different
Everyone has their own circumstances
What kind of circumstances do you have?
This is Kiza's story
I want to take everyone to Paris for a moment
I'm sorry
A trip to Paris for a moment
That's fine
A trip to Petit Paris
What?
What do you call it?
Marriage is...
Fun?
No
That's no
Marriage is...
A trip to Petit Paris
What?
That was a trip to Petit Paris?
Please come back
Did you take a picture?
That was too fast
I didn't notice
I've never been to Paris
Maybe I'm thinking more lightly
On the contrary
You can do it anytime
When I finished drawing
When I got married
I went to Paris
Today
We were on the bus
There was a moment
Yamazaki and Endo were at Hamada
The three of them were talking about kindergarten
I thought it was scary
I was here
Tanaka was here
Tanaka too
This is bad
Miyasako too
They were talking about school
It's scary
They moved
To the area where the children went to school
Even now, Miyasako is looking for Fudo
For the children
The entertainers have changed too
But
My wife
Who is your wife?
I'm trying to live in a good family
It's not a good family
What is it?
I don't know if it will happen
It will never happen
You're just saying it now
Logan
It's close
You're just saying it now
It will happen
I won't let you go to school
That's not it
I understand
What will you do if you don't let me go to school?
I'll stay at home
That's strange
You can't make friends
What is a friend?
Think about it
How many people cry when they die?
I see
Have you seen it?
No
At the very least, your family will cry
Oh my
Hama-chan
Your family won't cry
For a moment
I thought I was going to die
But when I said I was going to die
I'll go to the sky
I'll lose to curry
If you don't have an ant, you're an ant Matsumoto-san
Is that okay?
That's right
In this world, what do you think is an ant?
Please tell me everything
Where should I start?
It doesn't matter if it's an object
Let's see
A little drool
No
I don't know what you mean
I don't know which is a little drool
On the contrary, there is a little drool
Of course there is
Don't ask me in such an embarrassing way
That's your point of view
Because you
Why are you laughing?
Be honest
Like this
You're an idiot
On the contrary
Sorry, I'll go back to the story
Do you know what's here?
Do you know this is drooling?
That's not it
For example, there is a guy with a face like HG
I know
It's drooling
When I looked at it, it was a little drool
This guy
I know this guy
What is it?
There is such a thing
I know you don't say
On the contrary, there is a little drool
I know
Don't you know?
I know that
I know
I didn't say
That's right
I know
An old lady in her 50s
Why is that?
It's an old lady in her 50s
It's funny to say that
Is it a real problem?
An old lady in her 50s
It's an old lady in her 50s
20s woman
30s woman
40s woman
50s old lady
That's why I'm just saying that it's different.
You're a 60's old lady.
That's completely different.
No, it's not.
You're a 50's old lady.
That's why I'm just saying that it's different.
What are you doing?
Don't you get surprised?
Don't you think, whoa?
I do.
I don't like that.
A 50's old lady won't come to my house today.
Who?
There's a lady with relatives.
What would you do if I told you?
Hamada, Hamada, Hamada, wait a minute.
On purpose?
With the stage's sleeves.
Right?
Today...
A 50's old lady won't come to my house.
What would you do if I told you?
I see, I see.
I don't care if it's underwear or anything.
Hamada, Hamada, wait a minute.
You're a 50's old lady's forgotten item.