Ladies and gentlemen
Hello
No, really
No, no, no
Well, I think more than half of you have noticed
Hamada-kun is off today
What?
It can't be helped
Well, I know that
Since yesterday, the wind has gotten worse
It can't be helped
It's not like I'm taking a break for him
I'll do it alone today
I thought I'd get more booing
But it wasn't like that
Today's good friend was amazing
He's so annoying
And he's off
Really
It's hard to do it alone
But I have an opportunity to see Hamada-kun today
I'm shooting a VTR
Let's watch it together
I've been saying this for 3 or 4 weeks
I did a baseball tournament
I want you to see the results and the atmosphere of the game
Good luck
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
We divided into the Towns team
We played 5 games in total
The result of the game was that one of us had to be punished by 9 people
You'll see the results today
I haven't told you the results yet
If you see this, you'll know that Hamada-kun has a black stomach
Let's watch it together
Chikitsuki All-Star Dream Q&A
Let's go
The teams that won each game are all here
Downs
5 games
No goal
There are a lot of people who are not good at shooting
I don't know
But you're good
You can't see the goal from there
It's dangerous to look at it in a different way
I finally got a bandage off my head
There's a punishment game
If you lose, we have a terrible punishment game
I won't say it here
Let's do our best
Let's start the game
Let's do it
Let's start the All-Star Dream Q&A
Matsumoto Toshu threw a big ball
It's a drive
Hamada is the second batter
It's a catch
Yoshimoto Kogyo is the next batter
It's a high shot
But it's a batter
Hamada is the second batter
It's a home in like a ninja
I didn't remember that
This time, the Town's attack continues
How will the Down's team fight?
The first batter is Kobayashi
Hamada's fast ball
Hamada throws five balls
Matsumoto Toshu's cool expression
The second ball is Matsumoto
It's a third ball
But it's a batter
Will they win?
Matsumoto Toshu is the second batter
It's a home in like a ninja
The first batter is Noriyasu
Tsuga is the second batter
Noriyasu throws five balls
The Down's team is in the lead
It's a home in like a ninja
The third batter is Hamada
Next, Ikeagaru Matsumoto.
He shoots!
He's so careful, he's a Naira-frider.
But, this time, it's a last play for the producer, who's a genius.
He's not even aware of his position.
Next, Occhan Kawano.
It's a third goal.
He's going to score a third parry.
He's going to score a goal again.
Matsumoto's team is in the lead.
It's a 4-1.
Sakamoto is in the lead.
He's going left, left, left.
And the runner is in the lead.
The left-hander is in the lead.
The team's mode is on.
It's a tense game with a two-point return with an explosion at the end of the first quarter.
Now, is it a counterattack of the Hamada team on the 4th floor?
The runner who came out in the middle of the error was hit by the batter Onkomuro.
It's a left-over hit.
Left Tsuchiya, whose legs are wrinkled.
The runner is a home in. The fifth run of the Hamada team.
Matsumoto, who is anxious about the second half.
The Hamada team is alive.
The batter is also a right-handed hitter.
And the batter, Takasu, is also a center over.
This time, the Hamada team beats Noriasu, who is in the middle of the error.
The batter, Ichiyun, is leading by 7 to 3 with 3 points.
And the 5th run of the Kaihatsu team.
The Hamada team's attack on the strange batter, Matsumoto, has not stopped.
It's a home run of the camera Sakanishi.
It's a home run of Dameushi.
The camera Sakanishi is in a relaxed pose.
It's a 3 to 9 home in.
The next batter, Takasu, is also a counterattack of the Hamada team.
It's a home run.
What?
Really?
It's a home run.
It's a ball run.
Why did you hit the ball?
And finally, the final 11 to 3.
Will the 8 points difference be able to return to the team?
The 5th run of the Hamada team, the battle batter, Hashin.
You're not impressed, are you?
What are you laughing at?
It's a home run.
Now, Matsuyama, Shiratsuki, Hajime, and Jigoku batters are also out due to the dangerous play of the 2nd baseman.
And the last batter, Sugata, also has a three-point game set.
I lost.
What is that?
11 to 3.
Time's up.
The Towns won.
As promised, it's a penalty game.
The Towns.
The whole team.
The 10 of us.
Takatsu.
That's how it is.
I'm going to say this now.
Takatsu hit it.
I don't know if it was a home run.
No, no, no.
It was completely a home run.
It was totally...
It was completely...
I knew it was a home run.
And that's it.
That's it for the baseball game.
Matsuyama, Shiratsuki, Hajime, and Jigoku batters.
The penalty game is yours.
But the game is not a result.
Don't say anything about losing.
Your hard work, determination, and sweat.
It's more wonderful than winning.
Oh, Towns.
The Hall of Fame doesn't shine on you.
That's it.
I lost.
The penalty game is coming soon.
I'd like you to watch it.
My team.
Team Zero.
Where?
These guys.
They said it was a high school baseball game.
No, no.
What are you doing?
No, it's not.
I was disappointed before the game.
Matsumoto's long-distance practice.
Why?
Matsumoto was so good.
He was a good hitter.
He ran like this.
Like a mother.
Like a baby.
The director.
I'm disappointed.
I'm not good at running.
But I'm fast.
Are you fast?
I've caught the tail of a running cheater.
I was surprised.
Actually, I want to complain.
Noriyasu was injured.
I was hiding it.
I had a fracture in my ribs.
That's a good part.
Let's call the winning team.
What?
Talk to me.
You don't talk much.
Are you from the Philippines?
This is the winning team.
This guy.
He played a lot of Asian games.
I was surprised.
I caught the liner.
You were doing it in practice.
I saw it.
I heard it from the person who caught the liner.
Why did you win?
I was strong.
You didn't lose.
I didn't have a good shot.
My shot was faster than I thought.
You thought.
I thought you were strong.
My shot was faster than I thought.
I was doing my best.
I was unlucky.
I will play a penalty game.
I will never play baseball again.
What are you going to do?
I will play soccer.
That's bad.
You will play in this team.
What are you going to do?
Soccer.
You will play in the down team.
You will do it.
That's right.
Don't hit me.
It's already decided.
You are a silver-field killer.
I will do it.
Let's do it in another sport.
I want to do something other than baseball.
Thank you.
What did you say?
I don't think I can win.
Everyone in my team runs fast.
How fast are you?
I'm 6.6 meters.
What are you doing?
I rarely appear on TV.
I'm getting better.
I'm 6.6 meters.
I'm 7 seconds flat.
You are fast.
I'm 2.9 seconds flat.
I will write a letter.
Please bring a letter.
Hello.
There is a man in the team.
I will introduce him.
His name is Asako Imachi.
When she played baseball, she got a scoreboard.
A scoreboard?
I have a scorebook.
Is your boyfriend here?
No.
No?
Who will you choose?
I will choose you.
No.
Everyone knows it.
If you put me in the team, people will say that we are the same age.
What should I do?
I will get a scoreboard tomorrow.
Thank you very much.
Goodbye.
We always do it together.
Today, we will say whatever we want to say.
I will do whatever I want to do.
I am excited.
This person is angry.
This is a girl who is 15 years old.
I am Matsumoto.
Don't bully Otomo.
I am a girl who likes Matsumoto.
But I like Otomo more than Matsumoto.
Matsumoto, please let Otomo play with a girl.
Otomo is amazing.
I saw his letter.
There were about 10 letters.
Otomo is good.
Otomo, do you have a girlfriend?
Yes.
If she is my friend, I will do it with her.
Do you have a girlfriend?
I don't like it.
Good evening, Matsumoto.
I always enjoy watching your show.
Actually, I was watching your show on January 30th.
I was watching the draft meeting with my girlfriend.
And I decided to write a letter.
He wrote to Hama-chan.
She is a big fan of Matsumoto.
While we were talking to each other,
I wrote a letter with a diamond.
Hama-chan, please help me.
Matsumoto, I will definitely ask you for a diamond.
I wrote this letter while watching the TV.
Diamond.
Women say it easily these days.
Change the diamond.
Have you ever bought something expensive?
I bought a silver ring.
For your girlfriend?
Yes.
How much was it?
Well, it was 10,000 yen.
10,000 yen?
I bought a silver ring for her.
But when I met her a year later,
it became a gold ring.
The next man bought it.
Yes.
Matsumoto, what kind of ring do you give her?
Something expensive.
Really expensive.
Well, for me...
Well, if it's something expensive,
I give her a Rolex.
What kind of ring do you give her now?
Do you give her such an expensive thing?
Isn't it a pair watch ring?
Isn't it?
I think it's a Rolex.
What?
Look!
It's a Rolex!
I'm wearing a Rolex,
so what's the big deal?
It's a Rolex!
You probably don't know Team Zero,
but it's better not to get involved with them.
Both of them are crazy.
The other day,
I went to a cafe in Roppongi.
There's a cafe cappuccino.
Look, there's a piece of dough.
You mix it with a spoon.
As soon as it's done,
this guy says,
I'm so lucky.
I got some sweets.
This guy says,
Really?
What do I do with this?
You mix it,
you mix it with this,
and you eat it.
I went to Disneyland with him before.
He was having so much fun,
because he was an idiot.
He was like,
Peter Pan!
This is a story
about a friend who had an accident.
His friend was riding a bike,
and he was about to pass next to the car.
Suddenly, the door of the car opened,
and his friend fell down
as if he were being pushed by the door.
The first thing the woman said
when she got in the car was,
I did it!
I saw it!
She didn't even apologize.
When her friend came to her head
and asked her for her name,
she said,
I'm Taihei, nice to meet you.
She said she went somewhere.
Have you ever had an accident like this?
You've had an accident in your car, haven't you?
It wasn't a truck.
It was a six-ton truck.
A six-ton truck
was riding on your leg!
What happened?
I got off the bus,
and I thought I'd go to the side
and hit the order board.
Then, the truck tried to overtake the bus,
and it got out of the bus.
What?
It got out of the bus?
What do you mean
the moment it got out of the bus?
The bus stopped,
and the truck tried to overtake it,
and it tried to get in front of the bus,
and it got out of the bus.
Oh, I see.
The six-ton truck was riding on your leg.
It was just for a moment.
Did you get hurt?
It hurt.
It doesn't hurt at all!
So, today,
I'd like to end it here.
But since Hamada-kun isn't here,
it can't be helped.
Let's end it here for today.
What?
Sappu?
Sappu,
you can't get along with him anymore.
Someone said,
There's no one who can get along with him.
It's important to get along with him
when he's stupid.
Do it again.
I can't get along with him even if I do it again.
I can't get along with Sappu anymore.
You idiot!
Today's musical instrument was amazing.
It's been a year and a half.
It's been a long time since I've been this sweaty.
I can't believe that everyone can't talk this much.
Well, that's fine.
Next week,
a wonderful punishment game will be delivered to everyone.
Please look forward to it.
What else?
I'm looking for a talent like Mr. Ishii.
I'm looking for an assistant.
I'm looking forward to writing a fun story
that can be spread even in the city.
I'm looking forward to it.
Next week,
Hamada-kun will definitely come.
I'm looking forward to it.
When Hamada-kun comes,
I want to take a break once.
I'm looking forward to it like this.
That's all for today.
I'm not a playwright.
See you next week.
Goodbye.
I'm not a playwright.