Last week and two weeks ago, the comedians who were damaged by Matsumoto's money-spending were held in a funeral.
O-choko Matsumoto, Seko Seko trial!
You should say that, not that!
This!
This is you!
Wake up!
Matsumoto, the defendant, was forced to file a lawsuit, but the result was a crime.
He was fined 1,000,000 yen for using his money.
And later, a hearing was held on how to use the 1,000,000 yen.
We were told to have fun with the 1,000,000 yen.
I think people who watch TV can expect that.
I will prepare both the audience and the car.
The audience will be included?
But if you say that, having a guest is like having an event.
If I participate in that event, it would be strange if there was a gala.
In fact, I have to receive it.
If you look at Matsumoto's request at the school festival, it won't work.
This is a crime.
It's a crime.
I don't know how to use the 1,000,000 yen.
I don't know why there was a fine of 1,000,000 yen.
But the verdict is 1,000,000 yen.
What about you?
I didn't win the trial.
Then I'm the one who lost the trial.
It's okay.
Isn't it a crime?
You pushed me so much.
I see.
You pushed me.
You messed up my personality.
What is your responsibility?
Why are you responsible for me?
You are you, and I will definitely do the trial someday.
What trial?
End is end.
You are a complete asshole.
I'm not an asshole.
You chose this jersey yourself.
It's a papillon.
That's a complete asshole.
I'm not an asshole.
Please think about it this time.
It's a miracle that you can become one with the people on the scene.
How will Matsumoto use the 1,000,000 yen that Matsumoto entrusted to himself?
1,000,000 yen.
Thank you.
This program is sponsored by the sponsor you see.
And finally, on the day of the execution.
We are heading to Tokyo Summerland.
We have prepared a place and 500 people today.
500 people in this cold weather.
If you're not a leader of the Yopponobo tribe, you can't win.
That's right.
If you don't have that much power, you can't win.
Shut up. What are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
You're thinking about how to use the 1,000,000 yen.
Of course I'm thinking about it.
Really?
Yes.
I've been thinking about what kind of character I'm going to be as a comedian.
My comedy style is healing.
What?
Wait a minute.
You're not being healed.
I'm not being healed at all.
You came all the way here to heal.
I see.
I don't think so.
I've never been healed.
It's the opposite.
So I thought I'd like to heal the 500 people.
So I thought I'd like to show everyone a 1,000,000 yen fireworks show.
Shut up.
Fireworks?
Fireworks.
1,000,000 yen?
Yes.
Normally you can see it in the summer.
You can see it if you go somewhere.
But you said you wanted to see fireworks in the winter. Can you see it?
I've never seen it.
So I thought I'd like to show fireworks in this cold weather.
But it's worth 1,000,000 yen.
That's right.
That's amazing.
It's worth 1,000,000 yen.
I thought about it a lot.
I see.
Do you have 1,000,000 yen now?
No, I don't have 1,000,000 yen.
I'm not a person who carries 1,000,000 yen.
I have 2,000,000 yen.
That's not true.
I don't have 1,000,000 yen.
Do you have 1,000,000 yen?
Yes.
That's right.
It's healing.
But if you have a bank, show me.
I have 1,000,000 yen.
Really?
You have 1,000,000 yen.
Is that true?
Look at it from behind.
I don't know what it is.
I'll go first.
Ah, there's a normal person behind you.
I'm sure you've seen a lot of things.
That's right.
It's suspicious that it's a child.
That's strange.
You've seen too much.
You've definitely seen too much.
I don't remember how many times I've seen it.
I don't know.
Now, it's your turn.
What is it?
It's a big one.
Run away.
Hurry up and get on the bus.
Why are you coming back?
What is it?
Wow, amazing.
If you've seen this much fireworks, it's a good time.
I can enjoy it.
What did you see?
I can't see anything.
I didn't want to see that.
What was that face?
It was like this.
The bus arrived at Tokyo Summerland, a venue where you can enjoy a million-yen fireworks.
We're almost at the venue.
It's getting dark.
I'm looking forward to it.
We've been preparing for this for days.
There's a lot of people here.
It's a little cold.
They're all ready.
Sit here.
Here?
You're mistaken.
It's getting dark.
It's almost 10 minutes to go.
Meanwhile, the fireworks were almost ready.
On the other hand, the audience who came to enjoy the fireworks at Matsumoto was happy.
All that's left is to wait for the members to show up.
There's something I want to show you.
You're not going to do it yet?
I'm not going to do it.
The audience isn't completely out of breath yet.
Wait a minute.
You can't be completely out of breath.
I'll leave it until my mouth turns into a paste.
You know what I mean, right?
I want to tell you what fireworks are.
I know what fireworks are.
I've seen fireworks before.
But when you're asked what fireworks are,
For example, when a child is born,
What do you explain when your father asks you what fireworks are?
What do you mean?
You can't even explain it.
Are you going to blow it up now?
Think about it.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Look carefully.
Go.
The Japanese fireworks are divided into three parts by their structure.
Fireworks that create large, round fireworks.
Pokamono, which is often used in sports events.
And the small firework in the middle.
Speaking of fireworks, it's a firework.
I've been doing it since I made it.
How many minutes does this take?
When a firework opens in the night sky,
It spreads like a round stick and fights.
That's a firework.
The Japanese fireworks are divided into stars and parts.
It's called the representative firework.
That's a big feature.
The firework changes every time.
What?
It's all over the place.
It's too loud to hear the sound.
The assembly of the firework begins with the inner core.
The stars and parts are placed alternately in the paper.
When the parts are put in and the lower half of the firework is assembled,
The inner core is put in and the rest is finished.
It will be completed soon.
It's almost done.
Where did you cry?
I didn't cry.
I didn't think of anything.
There's nothing around the firework.
Firework?
That's a name.
That's right.
It looks like a firework.
Let's go see it.
Let's go.
Let's look at the history of fireworks.
The history of fireworks?
The history of fireworks.
When did the fireworks spread to Japan?
How did it become a firework?
I want you to see it.
Do you understand?
The history is good.
It's good.
I'll show you the time.
I haven't been able to prepare for today's event yet.
Really?
I'm wearing makeup right now.
We don't have to worry about that.
Let's look back.
The history of fireworks.
Where did you get it from?
This VTR.
Where did you find it?
The original firework of fireworks was invented in ancient China about 1700 years ago.
It was the birth of the so-called black-colored firework.
This black-colored firework, which is made by mixing wood, oil, and small stones,
will eventually spread to all over the world from China to the Middle East and Europe.
It came to Japan in 1543.
It came to Tanegashima with the Hinagajū.
The beginning of Japan's fireworks.
I don't know how long ago it was.
I don't know.
Finally, it was banned from manufacturing, selling, and using fireworks in the middle of the city.
It seems that fireworks became popular until the firework came out.
Hey, how was it?
Did you see it well?
It would have been better if you had seen it before.
I saw it.
Hey, how was it?
Where did you suck your nose?
I sucked my nose.
After all, there is no such thing as crying.
There is no such thing as crying.
What are you guys?
Oh, what are you guys?
I'm angry.
It can't be helped.
I'm angry. I'm angry.
You should get on the bus. We spent a lot of money on it.
Are you ready?
What's the matter?
Shut up.
Wait.
Well...
It's your turn.
You guys are also funny.
Fireworks in the world.
Please be patient.
It doesn't matter.
Do you think so?
I'll give you a hint.
Do you know English?
You don't know?
You don't know English?
Here you go.
Fireworks.
Fireworks is a firework.
You are terrible.
What?
I came to see you again.
That's not the point.
Please give me an A.
Please enjoy it more.
German.
Firebear.
Say it.
Italian.
Forky-darty-future.
Say it.
Say it like this.
Forky-darty-future.
Can't you say it louder?
French.
Rue-fou-darty-fus.
Say it.
Say it again.
Say it again?
Forky-darty-future.
Say it again from the top.
Really?
Fireworks.
Firebear.
Forky-darty-future.
With that being said,
Alright, finally
It's so dark
Finally, for everyone
Are you ready?
The fireworks you're about to see
How much does it cost?
1, 2
1 million yen
That's right, the 1 million yen fireworks
From now on
Let's go see it
Wow
This is amazing
This isn't just for 7 or 8 people
No, no, no
From the start
This is amazing
Matsumoto's 1 million yen
Let's use the 1 million yen
Thank you
Thank you for coming
Everyone
Thank you
Finally
Matsumoto's trial
The day has come
This is
This is a lot of expectations
That's right
It's a lot of expectations
It's been a while since we've gathered
And done something like this
For this program
I'm a little happy
I'm a little excited
Today's star
O-choko Matsumoto
O-choko
Matsumoto
1 million yen
What will you use it for?
I'll give you a 1 million yen fireworks
1 million yen
This is amazing
I'll say it again
I didn't do anything wrong
I still think that the trial was strange
But they
They are the parasites of the comedy world
They
What are you talking about?
Let's do it
I'll do it
Before that
The history of fireworks
I said it earlier
We were told
Everyone was waiting
We were told to show a video of the history of fireworks
I'm sorry
Everyone, the fireworks will go up from this side
It's going up
I'm really going to give out 1 million yen
It's a 1 million yen fireworks
I really want to give it out
You've seen it in many places
I'm doing it with my own money
You can see it with your own money
It's probably the first time I've seen fireworks with my own money
That's right
Really
Let's go
Everyone
Is it okay?
Let's count from 10 seconds ago
Okay
Let's go
Fire
Wow
Thank you very much
What?
Is it over?
You've been raising your head all the time
What?
It's over
1 million yen is that much
Really?
No
It's over
You guys are very expensive
That's 1 million yen
Wait a minute
It's okay
It's over
I'm sorry
Is it 1 million yen in one shot?
Is it over?
No
That's a lie
It's 1 million yen in one shot
It costs 570,000 yen
That's right
It's 1 million yen in one shot
It's 1 million yen
It's 1 million yen in total
Wait a minute
Why is it 1 million yen?
I can't imagine
I've never been told that much
What is that?
I can't imagine
What is this people's voice?
What is this?
I'm scared of the people
The fireworks that everyone is watching at the summer festival
It costs tens of millions
It's amazing
1 million yen is that much
And I'm the one who gave out the 1 million yen
I'm the one who gave out the 1 million yen
Thank you
You were the one who gave out the 1 million yen
Go home
He's saying it in English
Everyone, go home
You'll catch a cold
Wait a minute
I'm scared of the people
Are you listening?
1 million yen
The people are angry
What do you want to say?
You're a weak man
A weak man
I gave out the 1 million yen
I showed the fireworks
I'm scared
There's nothing I can do
That's right
That's the end of the 1 million yen
That's why
I'll close my eyes again
I'll close my eyes
Thank you
What we did in the end was to make their anger into a video call.
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.