Chikichiki Yoshimoto High School's unique bowling tournament
It's a bowling tournament
It's unique
What does it mean?
I don't know
Look over there
It's a pin
It's a unique bowling tournament
We throw the ball while saying something
They are the ones who are the pins
They are right about what we said
That's right
I thought so too
Only those people are left
If you say something like this, I can't be in the frame
Even though I have a lot of work to do
But there are people who did their best
They are always in the frame
What is this guy?
We will give away 16 types of natural hot springs
We will give away Tatsura Parkland hot spring
Thank you
Let's take a look at the pin
Do you want to touch it?
I thought so
There's a small one in the back
Why is he in the back?
Let's go, Yamasaki Gomi
Let's go
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
It's their decision
We think so
I think the people at home think so
I'm just saying
What are you doing?
Let's go
Basically, Hamada is ugly
What does this mean?
It means he's ugly
I see
No way
He's not alone
If you think so, you can break it
Next is a light one
I don't know why he's so popular
It's impossible for a normal bowling
Ah
He has a bitter face
Please
What is that?
What is this?
You almost lost
I was wondering until the end
He's amazing
He's standing diagonally
He's so diagonal
I couldn't go
What are you doing?
Ah
I see
You're trying to make fun of him
It's not what I think
Let's go
Izumi doesn't have love for talent
Mano-san
That was a good fight
I know
He didn't fall
His fight was the best
The pin was shaking
I see
Can I go?
Please
Let's go
Go back to Osaka
What are you doing?
I did it, but I don't like it
He's a piece of shit
Stop it
I have more talent than Yamazaki
Ah
What are you doing?
Why are you standing?
What talent do you have?
You
Who is he?
He's a veteran
What is that?
Mano-san
Yes
It was interesting to see everyone's cut
I think so
It was only 2 minutes
Please choose the MVP
Really?
Yamamoto-kun from Gokuraku
Let's give it to him
Congratulations
He dodged it
Thank you
Everyone did their best
Was it hard?
I wonder
Why don't you talk?
This kid didn't have a normal air
It's been 2 weeks
2 weeks is refreshing
Really?
Yes
There is a time for change
You can change your mind
You can show a different me
I've been saying that
It's not because of the change
Last year, I think it was last year
Matsumoto is going to be 2 times more Matsumoto
I've been saying that
It's 3 times more
3 times more
That's why Hanage is like that
Hanage is like that?
Yes
Really?
That's why
I agree
That's different
Hanage is like that
I said that
I used to be weaker
Hanage used to beat me
I see
Hanage used to beat you
Hanage used to beat me
From now on, it's different
Are you saying that?
I'm saying that
Now it's your will
Don't make fun of me
Now it's my turn
I remember telling you that
Tokyo is slow to deliver
I see
I found a really slow place
I was surprised
It's the same place as before
It's really bad
If you look back at what happened before
I used to order Tendon
I waited for an hour and it didn't come
I called
If I call and it doesn't come
I would say, it's here
I would lie
I thought he would apologize
I waited for an hour
He said, it's here
It wasn't here yet
It was here
And I said, you idiot
I remember that
It's been 2 years since then
You didn't ask for it
I didn't
I called him yesterday
I can't forget
It was 11.45
Which one?
11.45
I came at about 15
I thought I would eat while watching the show
I watched it
It was here
Even if it was 12.30
It didn't come
What do you think?
What do you think of your ex-wife?
I don't care
45 minutes
It's a bit strange
I thought it was lunch
No
It was lunch
The restaurant was busy
There was a lot of delivery
Let's wait 45 minutes
I'm angry
The problem is that the delivery was delayed
You don't usually wait 45 minutes at the table
Well
So they
The result is 45 minutes
I don't know if it's true
45 minutes
What happened?
It was almost over
I wanted to eat while watching the show
I just watched it
I waited another 10 minutes
I can't eat anymore
I'm very hungry
That's right
Boo! Boo!
It's a warning
I can't eat anymore
Do you want to eat again?
I'm angry
You are different from me before
I'm an adult
I'm not used to it
I'm sorry
What about Matsumoto who had a rice bowl?
That's right
Something like that
What about this?
I waited almost an hour
I can't go out
At work
I asked him to come in less than 10 minutes
My wife answered
Please wait a minute
The old man said something
Yes, there was a call
Could you come in 10 minutes?
I can't
What?
No way!
That's...
You should say that.
In short!
No way!
I refused.
It's coming out.
It's strange, isn't it?
I refused.
That's...
You didn't eat anything yesterday.
I was told that I can't eat anything.
I can't eat anything in Edo.
I'm counting on you.
Is it okay to allow such a thing?
But Tokyo is such a place.
The sushi restaurant I mentioned before is the same.
In the end, I don't know the restaurant, so I went back to the restaurant.
I went back to the restaurant.
That's strange, isn't it?
Because I didn't know the restaurant.
What?
Did you burn the restaurant?
It's a sushi restaurant, so I can't burn it.
I'm thinking about it.
But...
You're going to the fire.
But it's true.
I ate it in the neighborhood the other day and it was delicious.
I'm sorry, but the menu will be closer from now on.
In that sense.
I'm counting on you.
I'm shaking my hand.
It's not a menu.
It's not.
It's going to explode.
I can't let you cut it now.
But it's me.
Who?
Wait a minute.
I think I did it on the show.
How many minutes?
The slowest delivery in Japan.
I was right there.
I'm doing a lot of research right now.
What is it?
Genetic engineering.
I'm going to say something difficult again.
For example.
Brothers.
Women's brothers.
If there's a sister and a sister.
The older sister is cuter.
But that's the other way around.
No.
There's no doubt about that.
Is that so?
But the two brothers are cuter.
Right?
What's that?
You're talking about yourself.
No, no, no.
I think I did it wrong.
No, no.
But that's how it is.
It's not about the face.
It's a little bit of a jab instead of a greeting.
That's right.
Let me tell you a serious story.
For example.
If the older sister is really bad.
The next one will be really serious.
That's your house.
That's not true.
You should think about your family.
How can your sister be bad and your brother be serious?
That's the same thing.
That's not true.
You're a fool.
Why is that?
Everyone, think about it in your head.
That's not true.
It's true.
I know you, so I can say it.
That's not true.
You're the only one.
That's right.
What are you doing?
You can't just come in like this.
It's funny.
It's the same thing with sweets.
Sweets?
Yes, yes, yes.
Happy turn.
That's right.
One of them is really salty.
What is this?
Yes, yes, yes.
You put salt on it nicely.
If you eat another one.
That's right.
That's it.
That's exactly it.
In the end, we got to this point.
It doesn't have anything to do with what you said at the beginning.
No.
Banetan.
Do you know this?
What?
It depends on the couple.
Yes.
The woman who looks like her father is cuter.
Is that so?
Yes.
The woman who looks like her father is cuter.
This is definitely the rule.
Is that so?
Yes.
You look like your father.
I look like my father.
That's right.
Why am I not hugging you?
I look like my father.
I look like my father a lot.
My father tried to do it with me.
Akiko, too.
Stop it.
It's me.
We are the same age.
That's how much my father looks like his father.
That's right.
I had long hair.
That's not true.
Let's move on.
Yes.
When I was young,
I was told to work hard without paying much.
Where can I get that?
Stupid!
You should work hard.
Yes.
You haven't worked hard.
Why?
You haven't.
Am I?
What work do you have?
What do you have?
What do you work hard for?
I have worked hard on a lot of things.
What kind of trouble do you have in your head?
I ate spicy curry.
You ate it when you were young, didn't you?
What kind of trouble did you have?
I don't even have money for the subway.
Shut up.
Did you go through the same thing?
You walked from the south to the south and didn't have enough money to buy curry.
Is that what you mean by trouble?
You don't even have money for transportation.
If you have money, spicy curry is more trouble.
You ate it because you liked it, didn't you?
That's not trouble.
What I want to say is...
What kind of trouble do you have in your head?
That's why...
You walked from the south to the south and didn't have money for the subway.
What kind of trouble do you have in your head?
If I have money, I can take a taxi home.
I'll save money.
I'll do my best to make money.
That's what you think, isn't it?
Well, it's better than thinking about it all of a sudden.
No, no, no, no.
That's what we usually talk about.
I'll do my best to make spicy curry.
What are you going to do?
I want water.
That's right. I know.
This is the entertainment world.
What?
What? Don't say that.
That's not trouble.
Is it coming out?
What?
That's...
Why do you sneeze when you look at the sun?
I don't know.
No, no, no. If you sneeze, you look at the sun.
That's right.
You look at the light.
Don't you see it?
I don't see it.
How do you sneeze when it's about to come out?
Do you leave it to nature?
I leave it to nature.
Is that so?
If you don't do it, you don't know why.
No, I know.
You don't know.
I know.
I don't do it, but when I look at this document and understand that it's true,
I know that this will be like this, so it will be like this.
Let me hear it.
You see the sun, right?
The sun is very hot.
You think it looks hot.
I feel different at that point.
Compared to that hot sun, I'm cold.
Yekki!
When it comes to dead balls, it often becomes a mess.
A professional baseball game.
Why doesn't the pitcher run away when the batter hits the ball?
It's not cool to run away because you've been running.
You seem to like baseball.
You say baseball, baseball.
I like it.
I don't know much about baseball rules.
Why?
I just found out.
I don't know.
Is there a rule?
Yes, there is.
Why don't you run away after running?
If you catch a black man running, you're completely out.
It's not a ball.
If you catch the person.
If you catch the person, it's a change.
I've never seen this.
All change.
I don't understand the meaning.
I know it's a change, but if it's all change, it doesn't make sense.
Everything is a change.
I don't know how much it means.
Everything in his life is a change.
That's too much to say.
But you're running from the bench and stopping it.
That's why it's a problem if it's all change.
It's over on the first floor.
If you catch that.
I see.
It's all change.
Who said that?
The owner.
If you say all change, it's over.
You can't go back to the country.
All change means you can't go back to the country.
But when you're running, the owner is prepared to some extent.
Of course, of course.
It's been a long time since I've seen all change.
You didn't see the change.
It's going to be a big deal.
Don't you have a past?
I don't have a past.
Really?
Pacific Ocean?
It's not Pacific Ocean at all.
Pacific Ocean.
There's no Pacific Ocean now, is there?
It's in the west now.
The Pacific Ocean is all change.
It's like, what should I do?
It's in the west now.
It's called Pacific Ocean Club Lions.
That's right.
Before that, it was Crown Rider Lions.
I've done it twice.
Before that, it was Nishitetsu Lions.
I've done it three times.
I've done all change.
You've done it three times in the west.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't use the name of the west anymore.
That's what it means.
Tohato.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter if it's in the west or in Tohato.
It's called Tohato All Lions.