The next day
Hey, Masato-kun
Yes, yes
You're outside today as well
That's right
Do you know where we are?
What is it?
This is
Look at this
This is where the Tamagotchi is
You can't go there
Japanese people don't have this kind of respect
I'll teach you
Let's go to the hall today
Let's do it!
Just for the time being
We're in Mitaka right now
We're in Mitaka
This is
There are quite a few famous people
Oh really?
Yes, they're alive
They're alive?
No, they're dead
Look
The grave of Dazai Osamu
Oh, there's something like this
This old man
This Tamagotchi
He committed suicide in this area
This is Moriogai
Moriogai is that
The one who looks like he's going to die
That's right
Ah
Three people died in a car accident
Three people
In a car
This is
When the car is running
If we go out and get pulled
There will be four people here
There will be
I'll make it a grave right away
I'll make it four people right away
I like to do various things
I've never been here
But it's okay
No, that's what the soldiers say
The soldiers are walking
I couldn't accept it
But it's okay
I've never been here
Today is quite
This beautiful
Musashi's
In the entertainment theater
In downtown Gaki Natsukai
I'm asking for your opinion
That's right
Then
I'll do my best
Then I'll go
Boo
Today
Yes
I'll do it this time
That's right
I said it last week
I'll do it
I have to say that too
Yeah
What kind of content
Let's use the body
I don't use my body much
This program
Because it's a mouth
So use your body
Try it
Where are you going
When you're done
Something is noisy
Kirara
What
Today is the final
That's right
I'll do my best
Let's do our best
Boo
We've come this far
That's right
This year was particularly difficult
In the previous tournament
That's right
If you think of it
It was a tough fight
The first round was certainly
Obonko Obonko
That's right
I was defeated by that attack
I don't have any meaning
I stepped out
That's right
I was defeated by that
Then next
What is that
The University of Ethiopia
Hopeco Pisco
I was defeated by that attack too
We were also defeated by that rubber attack
That's right
Today is the final
I can't lose
Who is today's opponent
Today
Uchanko Nanchanko
The most
I can't lose to such dirty guys
I'll do my best
I understand
Your face is a little scary
Are you okay
What
Your face is scary
But they are also poor
That's right
There is no way we can win
Your serve is the best in this fight
That's right
It's noisy
I can't concentrate
I'll do my best
Then let's go
It's a serve from the other side
It's coming
Don't finish it now
I did it
I finished it
Idiot
What are you doing
You are hiding things from me
What are you talking about
I just said it
I said it
But you are hiding things from me
What are you talking about
I thought you were slow
On that day
Don't do it here
You are here
I told you to apply a lot of blood
You also did it during the fight
It's 5 minutes
I can't lose
The next serve is from the other side
Don't get angry
It's our serve
It's my serve
That's right
I haven't done this for a long time
I'll do my best
Take it
I'll do it
What are you doing
Your serve is a bad joko serve
A bad joko serve
It's your serve
I'll do my best
I'll do it
What are you doing
I'm sorry
Please take it
I'll do it
What are you doing
It's my serve
That's right
Please take it
I got it
It's a bad joko serve
It's your serve
Please do your best
I got it
I'll do my best
I'll do it
It's a bad joko serve
It was a bit traditional
Even so, I'll take it
It's okay
Hirara
What
At this rate, we might lose
Oh my
What are you saying
It's okay
We have to use that
Are you talking about that?
That's right
No, that's too dangerous
It's okay
Do you want to do it?
I'll do it
It's a bad joko serve
Combine
Let's combine!
Okay I will!
I'll go!
The weak point of this, is that you lose always,
Aaaaahh! If you keep it that way you lose.
I have no choice but to attack then!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Is that you, by any chance...?
You mean that one?
Yes!
That's no good!
But, if we do that one, those kids might die!
It's fine if they die!
No good!
We will win!
It'll be killing people! Let's stop it!
Alright!
We're going to do it!
If you say we're doing it...
We'll unite!
Alright!
Huna, huna, huna, huna, huna, huna, huna, huna, kii!
Now, then, if you can sell it, sell it!
Thin girl's receipt!
Hang on now
That's not Could!
You said just Countple!
Please erase this
That's not cool at all. What the hell is that?
Stop it!
It's been a long time since I've done this.
I'll do it while remembering.
Come on, do it!
We don't have time to waste.
Let's just go with it.
Hey, yesterday...
What is it?
I really like Katsura.
Yesterday, there was a radio show in Osaka.
You went back to Osaka, right?
I hurried back, right?
At the station in Shin-Osaka, there was a guy with a bad attitude.
Two guys with a bad attitude followed me.
Yankees, right?
Yankees, Yankees, Yankees.
Rather than a Yankee, there was another guy in a higher class.
He was a gangster, right?
That's right.
They followed me.
There was a guy in a taxi.
He was so heavy.
Hey, hey.
Don't pretend to be nice.
I'm not.
I'm not pretending to be nice.
I'm really bad at pretending to be nice, right?
Yankees.
I'm not pretending to be nice right now.
I don't usually pretend to be like this.
I don't know if it's true or not.
That's why I can't say that I'm bad at pretending to be nice.
On TV, they say,
Fuyumann is a good-looking guy.
I'm not good-looking.
I've never pretended to be good-looking.
Is there anything else you want to say?
Well, you know...
If they say that, I'll say it too.
No, no.
What are you talking about?
Well, you know...
When I'm in this world,
I can't use the strength I'm proud of.
If I get into a fight or something...
What are you talking about?
No, no.
I'm strong.
I'm really strong.
Right?
When I was in high school, I had a band.
What are you talking about?
I was living my life with a band.
What do you mean with a band?
I was interested in young people, so I had a band.
That's what happened.
Something scary happened.
But I couldn't help it.
I thought I could hit him.
When I went out in the morning,
I opened one door.
There was a hallway and an entrance door.
Yes, yes, yes.
I changed my clothes and opened the first door in the morning.
He came in like this.
What are you talking about?
Inside the room?
Inside the room.
Just like this.
I asked him,
What are you talking about?
He said,
At that time,
we had a lot of fans on this program.
We were like that.
He said something like,
What are you talking about?
I chased him to the bottom.
I was scared.
In the end, I had to let go.
No, you're not.
I didn't do anything.
I went to the wall.
You didn't go?
What I was scared about was
I forgot to close the entrance door.
It's your fault.
It's my fault,
but when I woke up in the morning,
I was sitting like this next to the futon.
Were you looking at me?
I don't know.
You were like this.
I said,
What are you talking about?
He said,
I'm a fan.
This is...
You shouldn't do that.
I've never been so angry.
That's not true.
I feel sorry for you.
You've done a lot of things.
What?
When I came home,
mayonnaise was applied to the door.
That's what I thought.
Mayonnaise is applied to the door.
Why don't you know what mayonnaise is?
I was trying to make you jealous.
I brought a broom and wiped it like this.
It's beautiful.
You did a good thing.
The door was shiny.
I can't break it.
I'm glad I saw it on TV.
If I had wiped the door with mayonnaise, it would have been beautiful.
I can't paint it for a while.
Please bring me a postcard.
There are a lot of postcards this week.
It's like a radio show.
I'm grateful.
Let me introduce you today.
There are many people who want to see the postcards.
I'm going to introduce you to those people.
What?
I was going to say that.
I'm going to look at it.
I sometimes look at my partner's face.
I want it.
This person's pen name is Chibi Maruko.
He has experience in UFOs.
What do you mean experience in UFOs?
I've told you many times that I've seen UFOs.
Do you think that experience will be trusted by everyone?
I think so.
You saw it and came to the station, didn't you?
Who will trust you?
I told you this story before.
There are many UFO researchers in Japan.
That person is going to do a UFO special.
Please come to the studio to talk about it.
It's a joke.
I don't know what a comedian can say.
I have a lot of things.
What is this?
This person is from Saitama Prefecture.
Is Mach-chan a homo?
My friends say that Mach-chan is definitely a homo.
Even if Mach-chan is a homo, I will be a fan of Mach-chan for the rest of my life.
That's right.
Am I a homo?
This is a homo.
I'm not a homo at all.
But there are times when I'm embarrassed.
For example, when I'm in a car.
A man is in the passenger seat.
I sometimes see a man putting his hand on the side brake.
I stop at the traffic light and pull the side brake.
That's true.
But it has nothing to do with being a homo.
I think it's a little embarrassing in my heart.
What about you?
After all, for a moment...
What is this hand?
I'm sorry.
Something like this.
You go to a bookstore, right?
There's something like a sub.
Like the Barazoku.
If there's a Barazoku while looking at a book like this,
There's something like that, right?
I'd like to see it a little.
Is this a homo?
But you can't see it all the time, can you?
Do you have to bring it all the way here and look at it like this?
Look at the A part.
Why?
Are you going to buy it?
When I went to a disco in Kyoto, there was one.
Really?
Invite me.
What did you say?
Come on.
Why are you so arrogant?
What?
Come on, come on.
I'll take you to the bathroom.
I'll put you in the bathroom.
You're gone.
It's usually scary at that point.
If that man calls you to the bathroom.
It's either torn or killed.
Come on, come on.
I'll put you in the bathroom.
I'll take off my belt and do it.
It was really scary.
What happened?
What?
Nothing at all.
At this point, it's all weird.
I'm already at the end of my clothes.
I ran away.
Really.
If you're going to Osaka, you should study in Osaka.
That's why I said goodbye.
That's right.
We don't have much time today.
Let's go to Kyoto.
What?
What kind of thing do you have?
There's no end to it.
What is it?
Well,
Ketsukatto.
Ketsukatto, right?
Everyone says this later.
It's not cool.
We're used to saying it.
Ketsukatto.
If you say this here,
Osaka people say, what kind of thing do you use?
What kind of thing do you use?
Ketsukatto.
If you say this here,
What are you doing?
What kind of usage is that?
That's a good one.
What are you doing?
That's what I'm saying.
What kind of thing does he do?
What kind of thing do you do?
Don't bite your butt.
Are you biting your butt?
Bite your butt.
It's hard.
What?
It's been a long time since I've been here.
What are you doing?
Ketsukatto.
What else?
What I was saying earlier.
When you're tired.
In Osaka dialect.
What do you say?
When you're tired?
Today.
Great.
Today was great.
Do you say it?
Which one are you?
You don't say it?
You say it.
You don't say it.
The person who raised his hand is a local.
It's a country book.
Where are you from?
Gifu.
Gifu?
That's cool.
That's the worst.
Gifu?
I don't understand what you're saying.
That's right.
When you're tired, today was great.
Today's point.
For example, if this person does this.
It's ticklish.
Osaka dialect is different.
Don't make fun of me.
Don't say it.
It's ticklish.
This is today's point.
Don't make fun of me.
That's great.
Where would you like to go today?
Kojubai.
Really?
Are you ready?
What else should we do?
The person next to me will make fun of the person next to me.
The person next to me...
If you make fun of me.
Goodbye.
You're not really cool.
We all are.
Let's do it.
Let's go.
You can just say,
Kocho kocho kocho!
If I say, yes,
Three times!
Kocho kocho kocho!
Next to you,
Ah, Kocho!
Do you understand?
Kocho kocho kocho!
Ah, Kocho!
Good bye, Konami!
That's the end.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Let's go!
Ah, one, two, three!
Yes!
That's the end!
But,
As soon as you say it,
You can't decide right away.
Well, well, well.
It doesn't matter if you're a soldier or not.
That's impossible.
Now, let's do the last one.
The last one.
Let's decide right away.
It's good to say goodbye.
Now, let's go!
One, two!
Ah, Kocho!
That's good!
Now, let's go.
Let's learn how to say,
Tsuruttai, Hachobai.
That's all for today.
Goodbye, everyone.
Thank you very much.
Well,
Yes.
It's over.
How was your first skit?
Ah, today?
Yes.
Ah,
I couldn't even sleep.
Well,
It's been a while.
Yes.
Well,
That's all.
That's right.
Yes.
The opening is no good.
That's strange.
What?
What do you mean?
It's already December.
That's strange.
It was cold today.
There's no way it's cold.
Yes.
That's strange.
I should have told you the day before yesterday.
That's right.
What do you think?
Well,
I don't know.
Next week is also a skit.
Yes.
Next week,
Well,
What do you mean?
It's a series of researchers.
I see.
Yes.
There's a thing called a researcher.
It's like that.
Well,
I want everyone to study it.
That's right.
Yes.
I want you to think about the meaning.
That's right.
What do you mean?
It's beautiful.
It's beautiful, so it's good to be beautiful.
The dressing room is.
Yes.
Well,
It's not a place.
People's offerings are there.
Children are crying.
Yes.
Well,
It's getting blue here.
Yes.
The tension is getting lower.
It's getting blue here.
Yes.
I've been there every day.
I'm talking about it now.
Yes.
Well,
Thank you for your time.
We'll get in touch.
Good.
Yes.
I'm sure it'll be okay.
Thank you.
This program was brought to you by Oyama International Products, Sunlux, and Toyosui.