For example, as a man, if you only show your face, you'll get 30 points.
You think you'll get 30 points, but you'll still get 50 points, right?
That's what makes you angry!
You said you'd get 30 points.
I've seen the players, but they're still low.
Everyone's bad.
What do you think, Tabas?
I think Yotsukato-san and Hatsumoto are better.
If you get 30 points, you'll get 55 points.
Why can't I get 30 points?
That's about 30.
That's the basics.
If I don't get 20 points, I'll get 30 points.
That's sad.
Is 20 points okay?
20 points is hard.
It's pretty hard.
You can go, right?
But who's going to play with me?
Don't get angry.
I can't get angry.
If you get angry because of that, you'll be an adult.
What do you think?
I think Hama-chan is better.
You think Hama-chan is better than me?
That's right.
What do you think?
There are various opinions.
What's wrong with you?
What do you think?
I think Matsumoto-san will get 30 points.
Are you sure?
Matsumoto-san is better.
Don't look down on me.
I think so.
What do you think?
The program was interesting.
I think it's a good thing.
Is that so?
Do you think I'm bad?
I don't think you're bad, but you're not an adult.
I think you're a bad person.
I don't like you at all.
I don't think you're bad.
I think you're a bad person.
I think Matsumoto-san will get 30 points.
I think Matsumoto-san is better.
I think Hama-chan is better.
What do you think?
No, I don't have a boyfriend.
You don't have a boyfriend?
Why do you have to do that?
You have to be calm.
I have a bad feeling about that.
Okamoto, you are in the nose.
Okamoto, you are a farmer's grandmother.
Suzuki, which side are you in?
I've been watching you since I saw you.
Okamoto, you are a farmer's grandmother.
I'm angry.
You are a farmer's grandmother.
Don't say the same thing.
I can't hear you.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You think it will be fun?
Don't say anything.
I know why...
They don't get benefits of course.
Alright...
Come here girl.
Hold on Motoyachi and Takasu are the worst.
Motoi-Chan is very funny.
I'm sorry, but as a producer...
I'll have to close this.
I'll go home.
What are you doing?
That's right, Tsukasa-san.
You don't say anything funny, so I'm going to...
Shut up!
You're fighting, aren't you?
Who are you, a producer?
You're going home.
Shut up!
Hey, hey, hey.
But if you think about it...
I'm still pretty manly, aren't I?
I'll think about it.
Let's go eat.
That's right, everyone.
I'm sorry.
Don't fall, don't fall.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Um... I overslept.
You overslept?
I overslept.
Oh, really?
I slept at 5 in the morning.
When I woke up, it was 5 o'clock.
I didn't wake up once.
Doesn't your head hurt?
No, it hurts a little.
Right?
I didn't wake up for 10 hours.
Oh, right.
I woke up because the prince kissed me.
Where?
Oh, really.
I woke up because it was 5 o'clock in the morning.
I told you so many times.
I can't sleep like that.
No, no.
There's a reason for this.
I thought I'd go home after work yesterday.
I was about to turn off my cell phone.
It was the moment I was about to turn it off.
I see.
I said yes.
You're from Matsumoto, aren't you?
I said, I'm definitely from Yakuza.
You're from Koi, aren't you?
I saw that.
I said, what's that?
You were imitating me.
I'm from Wada Akiyo.
You're from Wada Akiyo?
That's right.
Oh, really?
Hey, come over here.
You're quite drunk.
I was almost finished.
You were imitating Ako-san.
During the showdown.
I thought he was a muscle man.
He was...
He was like this.
He is doing something incredible.
Come here.
You're like an old man.
He was in a good mood.
You're really doing this kind of stuff.
One thing that's bothering me is...
Why are you fighting with your rival, Koji Matoba?
I was很 close to him.
Yes.
Why are you fighting with Koji Matoba?
I said, I don't know what you mean by that, but can you tell me?
Oh, there you go.
I gave him a character that seemed to have a lot of guts.
And he said, why me?
Akiyo doesn't know.
If that's the case, then there must be many more like Eikichi Yaza.
He's talking, but he's saying things about the earth.
He's got a good sense of humor.
I don't know what you mean by that, but can you tell me?
I said, I don't know what you mean by that, but can you tell me?
I'm acting like a fool.
I'm scared.
You were amazing.
What kind of tone is that?
You were on TV before, right?
I asked some ladies.
Who do you think is the most likely to lose?
I happened to be watching that.
I was watching that, and I was laughing.
I was laughing too.
What's so funny?
I cried watching that.
I was acting like a fool.
I was like, oh, I see.
You were acting like a drunk.
I'm scared.
Who do you think is the most likely to lose?
I said that before.
What did you say?
You said that.
I said that.
I can't say that.
You're acting like a salaryman.
You're acting like a salesman.
I said that.
I said, it would be fun if I had one.
I said, this is just a bet.
I said, if I had one, it would be pretty big.
Then...
Okay, let's go home today.
What was that?
I wanted to make a decision.
You wanted to make a decision.
A decision to go home.
I came to the store.
I said, thank you very much for today.
I was like this.
I said, that's right.
That's amazing.
When I did this, I looked like this.
I didn't like it.
What?
I said, that's right.
But it's okay.
It's better to say it.
The manager is a good person.
He always has a chain.
Mentally.
He doesn't really have a chain.
But he has a chain.
He has a chain.
I was alone yesterday.
I didn't know I had a chain.
I was dragged.
I was screaming.
I was about to go up the building.
I'm a real monster.
But it's okay.
I'm a senior.
And...
I'm sorry to say this.
I don't want to do it.
But this season is coming.
I'm going to sing.
Which one?
It's been a long time.
I have to do a showdown.
Come on.
We're going to do it on Kōhaku.
Kōhaku, red or white?
We're doing a Kōhaku program on TV.
We can watch TV together.
Is that so?
When Kōhaku is off from work,
We watch Kōhaku together.
We watch together.
We're going to watch it in the studio.
That's good.
And then, when we decide whether the red is white or not, I always say something like,
You decide.
You decide whether it's white or red.
You're playing rock-paper-scissors, aren't you?
Rock-paper-scissors is unfair.
Why?
And this time, we have to decide whether the red is white or red before that.
Why do you say that twice?
And this time...
No, no, no.
What do you think?
Can't you just run?
What?
Run?
What do you mean, run?
100 meters.
And then, the winner gets to decide who gets the right?
You can't blame the staff here.
I'm not blaming them.
Really.
You run 100 meters, and the winner decides.
The worst thing is, even though you won at 100 meters,
the worst thing is if the red is white.
That's the worst.
That's the worst, too.
See?
Then, there's nothing left for you to eat.
No, it's not like that.
If I play rock-paper-scissors, it's easier to decide.
I'm confident that you'll win at 100 meters.
I can win.
I can win enough.
What did you say?
I can win easily.
100 meters.
How fast can you run?
I don't know.
How fast can you run at 50 meters?
I think I can run at 7 meters.
And then, the winner gets to decide who gets the right?
Well, that's...
Why?
I can't talk anymore.
Really?
It's really fast.
How fast can you run?
It's there.
I went to the emergency exit.
You went and came back.
I went and came back.
Then, go again.
If you have it, you'll go.
Why?
It's there.
I don't have it because I have it.
I'm sorry.
It's here.
I said it twice.
I let you win.
It's really fast.
How many seconds?
I think it's really...
Really?
I think it's really 11 or 12 seconds.
No, no, no.
I can't stop it.
What are you talking about?
What can't you stop?
I can't stop it because it's fast.
Your words are funny.
If you have a member, you'll know.
I'll know if I win.
While you're talking like that, I may be in the Geisha Girls.
That's not good.
What will you do if you win?
I don't think I'll win.
I don't like it.
I hate it.
I didn't really go to swimming competitions.
Why?
When the kibasen started, I went to the toilet a lot.
Because your father was going out?
Yes, because my father was going out.
I was looking at my mother in a really bad way.
I don't know what kind of face I should make.
When the kibasen started, I was looking at my mother in a really bad way.
I don't really care about that.
I really don't care about that.
I don't care about the drama.
I don't care about the love scene.
I don't care about the bed scene.
I don't care about that.
When the kibasen started, I was looking at my mother in a really bad way.
I can watch that.
You said it was funny, but when you started watching it, it was very funny.
You are making fun of me.
I don't make fun of you.
I don't like the bed scene.
You know, the bed scenes.
That's a little tough.
That's tough.
It's so hard to watch the bed scenes on TV.
It was really hard for me to watch the bed scenes of my father and mother.
You can't do anything about that.
You can't say, stop it today.
To your father and mother.
You can't do anything about that.
So you try not to get caught on TV, right?
Yes, I do.
I can't help but watch them.
Yes, you just watch them.
You can't say, stop it today.
Stop!
I just know your mother.
You can't say, stop it today.
I'm wearing a fur coat outside!
At the end of the year, Japanese people are the ones who want to go overseas.
Where are you going this year, Matsumoto-san?
You're not going anywhere?
You always say, you're not going anywhere in the New Year.
I don't understand why you think that way.
Why?
I mean, I'm already in Japan!
You're in Japan, too.
I'm speaking with my senses.
I'm speaking with my soul.
With your soul?
Why Osaka dialect?
I'm speaking with my soul.
Where are you originally from?
I'm originally from the closest island to heaven.
Where?
Papua New Guinea.
New Caledonia?
Papua New Guinea?
You don't even know your own country!
It's Papua New Guinea.
Papua New Guinea.
It's Papua New Guinea!
It's New Caledonia.
Oh, I see.
That's why it's Papua New Guinea.
That's why it's telecom.
Papua New Guinea is no good.
You sound like a real Japanese.
Who are you talking to?
Are you talking to me?
No, no.
I have a question.
What is the X mark of shiitake mushroom for?
It's to make it easier for the soup to soak in.
What?
Why do you only use shiitake mushrooms?
Why don't you use carrots or Chinese cabbage?
Chinese cabbage doesn't die in one shot.
It dies in one shot?
That's amazing.
How many shiitake mushrooms do you have in total?
Why?
Why do you have a X mark?
It's already in there.
It's not in there.
It's just that there are shiitake mushrooms that aren't in there.
There aren't any.
No, no.
I'm serious.
There aren't any.
I'm not joking.
When?
When did you say that?
I'm sorry.
I'm serious.
I can't laugh at your attitude right now.
I'm sorry.
That's it.
I'm serious.
No, no. Don't worry about it.
I watch the Invention Army every week.
Thank you.
I always think about this.
Why do you always close your eyes when you announce the results?
No way.
Why did you say that?
I don't close my eyes.
No, no.
Put your hand in your pocket.
Announce the results.
Your voice isn't the atmosphere.
Say it in the atmosphere.
Announce the results.
You always close your eyes when you announce the results.
You don't know even though you don't watch me.
I always watch you.
Don't worry about it.
I'm not worried.
I'm worried.
You have a bad attitude.
You always announce the results.
You always close your eyes when you announce the results.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.