The first episode of the Gaki no Tsukai Arai, the next is Endo vs Jinnai, the real daikon actor, Cho Jiro's strategy!
It's a close battle.
It doesn't matter if it's a strategy or not.
What do you want me to do?
Today, we're going to decide the top of the daikon actor.
That's right. Well, I got the word from Jiro Sato.
Oh, I see.
The other day, we broadcasted a quiz about the 100 of Jiro Sato
Who do you think is the most daikon among the 5?
I'll say it bluntly
Endo-san
I did it!
I can remember his anger
Endo's daikon acting is a masterpiece
From now on, I will be the bassist of this bus.
The bassist of the movie, which was starring Shouzo Endo, has returned.
That means...
Alright, we don't have time. Let's hurry.
His smelly acting is worthy of the top of the list of great actors.
No way!
Shouzo knows it.
I'm Jinnai...
Ah, this is...
I've been paying attention to Jinnai.
Really?
Before Nagoya, I was in a drama about Nagoya.
It was a long time ago.
It was a serious drama.
But every time, I was like a gay.
You were like a gay in the drama?
I was like I was going to throw up something I didn't eat.
Here it is.
I can't go home today.
The drama played by Tomonori Jinnai as the main cast, Cinderella Date
This is my favorite shop in the world
I came here after I submitted my application to the district office
The second year was right after I opened my own office
I slipped into the home and fell down with a catcher
The doctor said it's not good yet, but I left immediately
I couldn't help it because I wanted to eat the beef tail red wine here
A splendid daikon acting that reads lines without a break
I look forward to the next 10 years
This is Asia 1 and 2
It's amazing
It's amazing that two people are gathered in Japan
And they are from the same company
They are from the same company
It's a miracle
Let's have the two main characters appear
Please
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Excuse me, Jinna-san.
You look like you're in a deep sea.
What do you mean by gay?
I've done it before.
It's a serious role of Cinderella date.
It's about the role of the third.
Do you know about it?
I don't know about it.
I saw the play with my ex-wife.
I was gay.
You were.
I see.
Really?
I think it's a commercial, but I saw the commercial and I got goose bumps.
Everyone got goose bumps.
Everyone.
When you come out, you act like you're not on the stage.
That's not good.
You're already doing it.
I don't agree with that! You should act!
I'm doing it! I'm doing it!
You shouldn't say that!
Endo-senpai is also acting like he's in trouble
If you say that, you won't be able to do anything
It's hard to do!
Why are you wearing a
I'll do it!
You can't say that!
Endo-senpai is also worried about that.
If you say that, you can't do anything.
It's hard to do.
The next episode
Why are you wearing a mask today?
We're going to shoot a performance for you two.
This time, the theme is the period drama.
The video is black and white.
It's black.
It's a little like that.
Endo and Jinnai filmed the same scene in advance.
The acting was re-enacted by the members.
The one with the lowest total score will be the unknown King of Daikon.
I'm sorry.
I did it seriously.
Are you confident?
Of course I am.
Let's watch it seriously.
The first scene is the revenge scene.
The revenge scene...
It's a period drama.
It's a classic.
It means that he's going to die.
Let's see the performance from Yen-提香 played by Seppo.
Look at his face.
оз
Seppo
Joined under the
income from winning the war
sunny
I am doing it.
was
If you are saved,
I will be happy and cut off my belly.
What kind of face is that?
That's not the face.
I will cut off my belly.
What kind of face is that?
Is he going to come out of the forest?
Lastly,
I want to read the book of the next life.
I will do it.
Do you want to do it?
Is that right?
Yes.
Very well.
Like a thorn in my side,
even if my body is to die,
I will be a flower
that will never wither.
That's strange.
He's doing it seriously.
Why is he laughing?
Really.
Finally...
Too much emotion...
Ah, I see.
It's going to be like this.
Too much emotion makes it smelly?
It's going in.
It's like a
It doesn't matter.
It's a body type.
It's like a golf club.
Can you stop looking at me like that?
This is a period drama.
I will stop it.
Hurry up and say it.
It's a curse.
I will stop it.
I don't know what you're saying.
Eh?
Please look at it.
What do you mean by look at it?
Let me do it.
I'm hesitating.
This is bad.
What is this?
I'm going home.
This is what happens.
Do it seriously.
I'm seriously serious.
I'm not laughing. I'm serious.
This is amazing.
This is terrible.
What are you saying?
No!
I don't regret it.
I don't regret it in my life.
When you're in that kind of situation, do you get angry?
Because you're angry.
You get angry, right?
I've been doing the drift all the time.
I can hear the laughter.
The laughter of the old ladies.
I don't do the drift in the set-up scene.
Everyone, it's a little judgment.
It's difficult.
How about this?
Everyone, please put your cards together.
Total minus 4.
Minus 4.
I'm suddenly feeling a bit...
Is this a debt start?
How do you feel now, Jinnai-san?
I think I made a mistake in my expression
I see
I thought I was like this when I was hungry
I was able to come up with a good acting plan
Why did you come up with this?
It's so funny.
Jinnai Tomonoshi.
I hereby appeal to you, Supreme Ministers...
I,ríSeph
Seph
You will be something very blessed
And by you death...
If the Kashi's slimseed were to survive...
I'd like to allocated the flesh, my lord.
Now, for the sake of Jinnai's lordship,
perdu pursuance!
skys stroke sate I'll
residents have made Mayor to read the places for emergent system toppings.
You haven't bit on his finger yet, have ya.
It's good.
It's like a movie.
For the country,
the heart that is devoted to the country is a water bowl.
Don't get lost,
leave it to the wind.
He has a good face.
Not bad.
I'll catch you!
From here on out, right?
That's the face of a real man.
This life...
And now, I will end this!
Go-Shōran!
What?
This is bad.
What is this?
Waaaaa!
Waaa!
That is so funny!
You didn't have to laugh.
I didn't laugh at all.
The one who said, waaaaa!
It was like an elementary school student.
Waaaaa!
It was like that.
The sports day has started.
What is it?
Let's judge
It's a lie, right?
It's a lie
This is a lie
I'll take it
It's a lie
Why did you laugh at the end?
What did you laugh at?
What are you doing?
That's dangerous
That's not true
It's a lie
Next is the scene of the poison
It was a scene of poison.
Poison?
Poison was poured into a very fun place and he drank it.
He died in pain.
It's hard.
It's a tension from the inside of the body.
That's right.
Hahaha!
It's time for the Lord.
I see.
Thanks to the great command of the Lord, we have won this battle.
Now our country is safe.
Listen, our country's
The war has just begun.
The Tengadori is just beginning.
I will crush those who hinder my progress.
That's a bit of a slur.
Come on, let's drink.
Sorry.
Let's drink tonight!
Here you go!
Drink it! Drink it!
This is a break-up!
He's holding it!
This is crazy!
Wow, Yuki!
Don't fool around!
Scary! Scary! Scary!
Scary, scary, scary.
You've gone too far!
It's like a one-eye again.
You're so mean.
You've been destroyed by the Jinnai family.
This is the grudge of our clan!
Wait!
You bastard!
I'm not going to die!
I can't die like this!
You're a fool.
I'm not going to die!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Ah, it stopped.
His acting is amazing, and his actions are also amazing.
He was poisoned, but why did he drink it again?
It's like a holy soup.
He should have checked it again.
No, no!
Because when you say, um, it makes you go, um, right?
What?
Where?
Even more so, you can't do it.
So what did you do?
What?
It's not strange, so I went twice.
The second time of poison is a problem, and the score is a minus 17 points.
Endo, can you break away from them at once?
Thanks to your excellent command, we have won this battle.
Now this country is safe.
Alright, the trouble in our country has just begun.
It stinks.
It's starting now.
It's the smell of heaven.
It stinks.
You're blocking my way.
It's not coming.
You're being merciless.
It's a
You're a liar.
The way you act stinks.
It stinks?
Well, well, well, I'll let you drink tonight.
What?
He yes...
Your order surely
from here
That kind of guy
It's regular
It's fun
What the heck was that?
Revenge successful!
Why isn't he arriving in the walls?
He fell for it.
What the hell?!
You!
You're stinking.
You...
You know that, right?
You're the one who's been destroyed by the Edo family, and you're the one who's been against our family!
I'm going to take off my sword and...
Stop!
You're so annoying.
You...
I'll cut you into pieces.
That's too serious.
There's no hole.
It's too much.
There's a lot of them.
There's a lot.
You must have seen a lot of things.
I did all of it.
All of it?
The scene where the old man dies.
It was smelly.
I don't like the smell.
What do you think?
That was just a skit.
It was just a skit.
But you were a grown man, you were a bit mean.
You could tell.
You could tell, right?
I was looking for contact lenses
You were looking for it
You were looking for the camera
I dodged it
I didn't do it like this
The acting was too much
It was negative 12 points and low rating
Jin-san is outstanding
That's right
It's a bit...
I don't have a taste
And it's not a VTR
It's a fire show
It's a live-action show
It's scary
Next is a live-action show battle with only facial expressions
He can't be defeated by a period drama.
He will continue to act with a big smile, a mischievous smile, and a angry face for 10 seconds.
Endo-san, how is it?
I'm thinking about which one to give him.
Let's go. First, Endo-san's big smile.
Action!
You bastard!
I will never let you live!
Let's go to the judgement, everyone.
I'm sorry, but you're the bad guy.
I hate you!
Next is Jinnai. First is his big smile.
Action!
Hahaha
You bastard!
I won't forgive you!
This is Yama-chan.
He's gone crazy.
Do it properly!
You're being called!
Let's see the judgement.
Ready, go!
It's not enough.
What do you mean it's not enough?
The one who got 51 points is Jinnai!
Jinnai is not a good opponent.
I want to see him fight again.
What do you think about this result?
I think it's a natural result.
I think it's about 20 points.
Jinnai's 32 points.
It's a minus. Both of them are minus points.
It's not fair to say that it's the result of the competition.
I'm so nervous.
E.B.C.
This face.
Is that so?
This is a really good face.
I'm sleepy.
Sleepy.
This face is sleepy.
It's sleepy.
I'm sleepy.
He's glaring at me.
I should move my eyebrows.
That's right.
It's like this.
This is strange.
Can you take it?
What is it?
Kato Cha-san.
Cha-san.
Really.
I haven't played Drill Daibakutou.
His face is similar to Chaa-san's.
He looks like Da-Funda.
Chaa-san's face is similar to Endo's.
He was Kato Chaa-san at the end.
Mori-san and Chaa-san.
They are just changing their faces.
The way he stands before he gets cut is like Takeshi-san.
There are many people.
Ah!
Ahhhh!
Why startled me?
The previous bout is now broadcasted zww by Hulu.