In the first episode, let's clean up Chikitsuki!
This is an educational program.
We want you to understand that it's dangerous to do this.
We have a lot of things prepared.
We use a microwave.
This is dangerous. This is OK.
This is the set.
Please sing a song of the microwave.
It will start soon.
It came suddenly.
I thought it would come suddenly.
There may be times when you don't use it.
You can use it until winter.
That's the worst.
That's no good.
There may be a second one next time.
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
Let's start with the first shot.
Are you ready?
Anything is fine.
I don't know.
Do you want to put it in?
Let's put it in.
I don't like it.
I don't like it moving.
It's hot.
I don't like it.
I'm scared of the sound in front of me.
Something is coming.
Everyone is getting bigger.
It's coming.
What is that?
What is that faint sound?
It's getting bigger.
It's true.
It's coming.
It stopped.
What is that?
A yo-yo is made of a balloon.
There is water in it.
If you turn on the microwave, the water will expand.
The water expanded and the balloon came out.
Take it off.
Are you okay with the oxygen?
I'm fine.
I'm scared.
It's coming.
What is that?
Look at the balloon.
I'm scared.
The balloon is going to float.
Let's eat.
Is this a ginkgo nut?
It's delicious.
Is it salty?
What is this?
What is this smell?
It smells like a yo-yo player.
It's fast.
It's amazing.
What's next?
Let's eat this.
It's interesting.
This is the one with brown rice.
I don't know.
It's over.
It's beautiful.
It's about to catch fire.
It's a bad guy.
I see.
What's next?
Let's eat this.
Start.
I'm scared.
It's leaking.
It's not warm.
How was it?
It's interesting.
It's amazing.
It's rice cake.
It's a clam.
It's cute.
Let's go to Keiko-do.
How many seconds is Keiko-do on the menu?
It's not on the menu.
Let's go.
Start.
Do I press here?
You can't stop it.
It's on.
Stop it.
Keiko-do has two lights.
The light is on by the electrician.
Let's eat the boss's egg.
It looks like a desk.
Let's go to work.
I want to eat the boss's egg.
I can ride on it.
Really?
Why do you hit my head?
I'm a professional bowler.
I'll start.
It's heavy.
It's really amazing.
I'm sweating.
It looks like a dinosaur egg.
The outside of the egg is empty.
The inside of the egg is full of water.
The pressure inside the egg is increasing.
If the egg is empty, it will burst.
You need to be careful.
It's important to read the instructions.
Put it on your head.
What?
Are you all right?
The other day, I was drunk at the sea.
I did a Christmas special.
The guests came with a bowl.
Because it's Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
The first group was good.
The second group was good.
Let's toast.
Merry Christmas.
I was drunk at the sea.
The sea was moving.
I ate rice properly.
I drank a lot.
The other day, I drank a lot.
I had 12 bottles of alcohol.
I jumped into the head of 10 people.
I've been recording the whole time, and you didn't show up.
I'm not lying.
Your face was all red, and you didn't show up.
That's not good.
You didn't say a word in the last part of the glove.
Actually, this is the first time I've heard about the glove.
This is the first time I've heard about the glove.
Really?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Right?
It's not fun to watch.
You announced the glove, right?
The other day, right?
Yes.
How is it?
This year.
How is it this year?
I wonder how it will be this year.
Who did you become?
Matsutaka.
You don't know, right?
Why is that your face?
I don't know.
Your invisible power is working.
Why is that?
If you say your invisible power is working, you're an a**hole, right?
It's like Norio Yoshio.
What is it?
Don't you really think so?
If you say you're an a**hole and you want to retire,
they'll treat you well in the newspaper.
No one cares.
What is an a**hole?
No one knows that.
That world is limited.
Right?
If you say you're an a**hole and you want to retire,
they'll treat you well in the sports newspaper, right?
If that's the case,
you shouldn't be treated as a bigger a**hole than Okahachiro.
Right?
But Okahachiro is in a small place.
If you say your invisible power is working,
Okahachiro is a bigger a**hole.
Why are you pushing Okahachiro?
Okahachiro is a bigger a**hole than Okahachiro.
Everyone knows that.
It's totally different.
The name value.
Out of 100 million people,
how many people are fans of Okahachiro?
Right?
That's right.
It's about 10,000 people.
Okahachiro's fans are 40,000 people.
Wait a minute.
My book has 40,000 people.
Okahachiro's fans are the same.
Wait a minute.
You're a bigger a**hole than Okahachiro.
I'm a bigger a**hole than Okahachiro.
Do you know Okahachiro?
I don't.
You don't?
I'm a bigger a**hole than Okahachiro.
You're just an old man.
No no no.
A big old man.
You're underestimating Okahachiro.
Old man.
If Okahachiro appears, you'll be surprised.
What are you talking about?
You've gotten old.
I don't know that much.
Do you know Okahachiro?
Yes.
You do know?
Even Okume no Hacchyan.
That's right!
She even says Okume no Hacchan.
This girl is from the Kansai area, isn't she?
See?
That's right, or else she wouldn't even know Okume no Hacchan.
That's not it.
I'm starting to want to call Okahachi.
I just want to say it.
Huh?
What?
Ah!
What's this?
Eh, what's this?
Ah, it's George.
What was it again?
Ah, there it is!
I'll do my best!
Ah...
I just want to say it.
From now on, from now on...
It's warm.
Is that so?
Thank you very much.
It's something to say, isn't it?
It's true.
It's hot.
It's hot, but it means it's warm.
Masumoto-san, you've been protecting Hamada-san for 15 years in every way.
If Hamada-san and Masumoto-san were walking outside together, the wind would always blow, and Hamada-san's back would fly off.
It would be a mess.
Masumoto-san, what would you do first?
This is...
It's a very good letter, isn't it?
Well, it's a if.
It's not a letter.
It's a story of what would happen if it happened.
It's a very difficult thing, isn't it?
No, it would fly off.
It doesn't matter what you say.
I'm the type of person who can't forgive things that have happened to Hamada.
At first, when the two of them were walking, I thought, oh, the wind is strong.
After all...
He always pulls out the string that he always puts inside.
And he pulls it tight like this.
It's like a straw hat.
He pulls the string tight like this.
He doesn't want the string to get caught in the string.
That's impossible, but...
I have some money, too.
If I really didn't pull it out, I wouldn't pull it out.
That's right.
You wouldn't pull it out like that.
That's why when the wind was strong, I pulled it out like this.
That's why it's not a team fight.
It's not a win-win situation.
It's not like that.
I was walking, and the wind blew.
When it flew off, I was facing the wind.
I was like, what the hell?
Let's say it.
Thank you.
I was angry with the wind.
I was angry with the wind, and then...
No, I was chasing you.
What?
You're already...
I'm not saying you should be angry, but I'm chasing you right now.
You have to come back as soon as possible.
When the wind blew, I was like, what the hell?
When I looked at you, you were already chasing me.
I was like this.
This is a question for Mr. Matsumoto, who is looking for a part-time job to be a part-timer.
I'm working part-time now, but I'm in trouble because the hourly wage is low.
That's why I'd like to ask Mr. Matsumoto.
Mr. Matsumoto used to do it, and he still does it sometimes when he's in trouble with money.
Please tell me about the part-time job for 86,000 yen.
You were doing it?
I was already doing it.
Oh, really?
Yes.
The hourly wage was 86,000 yen, and I ended up paying 86,800 yen.
I started with 85,000 yen at first.
What kind of job is it?
It's a part-time job.
That's too much.
If you had a little more talk, you could have said,
Let's say, let's go through the eyeballs.
First of all, you'll be told that in an interview.
Are you a person who can go through?
Go through?
I can't go through.
First of all, give me a pencil.
What are you writing?
Q.
Is it written?
Can you go through the eyes?
Q.
Can you go through?
Can't you go through?
Q.
If you write that you can go through, do you go through the right or the left?
I go through the right.
Ah, the right.
Left.
Go through.
Then you can come from tomorrow.
Wait a minute.
What?
What do you do when you go through the left eye?
I go through the left eye.
That's the right eye.
No, I go through the right eye first and then the left eye.
Sorry, I didn't know.
Go through the left eye.
Shut up!
What are you doing?
First of all, throw it.
First of all, you have to press the time card.
Don't press it.
What kind of part-time job is that?
Well, I'll tell you.
If you don't put the time card in before you go through the left eye, you won't understand unless you go through the left eye.
I know that.
I'm sure those who go through the left eye will know that.
Be careful.
I put a poster on the top of the time card.
I'll go through the left eye after I do this.
I'll say, I'm in Matsumoto.
Then I'll throw it hard.
I have a meter to measure, so I'll have you measure how many meters I've thrown.
I can throw 15 meters.
If it's long, you can throw it as much as you want.
Well, my eyes are quite attached to it.
From the morning to about 5 o'clock in the evening.
To put it simply, it's a repetition of that.
Why do you have 86,000 frames?
That's why you're a bad guy.
There's a mirror.
This is a magic mirror.
There's a rich man eating while looking at the mirror.
He's throwing again.
I'm starting to understand.
Well, how he throws.
The other day, Matsumoto-san was ranked second in the ranking of the best adults in Japan selected by elementary school students.
Is that true?
I have a question for Matsumoto-san.
When do you think it was good to be an adult?
Well, when I see myself standing naked like this.
After all, this is the behavior of an adult.
After all, this is an adult.
I'll definitely catch it.
Don't do it again next year.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
What is it?
I'll ask you instead.
You don't have to look at the behavior of an adult.
You can do it next year.
Why are you doing this?
It's different.
I don't know.
You and I are in the same team, aren't we?
What?
You're an adult, aren't you?
You may be an adult, but listen to this story.
We are a team, Matsumoto.
We are a pair.
We are a pair, and we are also a pair.
I said too much just now.
That's not true.
It's a pair.
As Matsumoto, this guy is doing his best.
He's doing his best.
You can't do it if you don't do it.
It's still funny.
I'm happy about that.
I'm happy about that feeling.
Everyone is happy about it.
We're all the same.
People say that everyone is alone.
No matter how many partners you have, you're always alone.
But this guy...
Even if I go to the end of the world, this guy will come to me.
He's always there.
What do you think?
What do you think about this?