Ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you very much.
Today we have a special for the kids.
We usually have 30 minutes, but how many minutes do we have today?
2 hours.
2 hours?
Normally we would have a special.
Right?
Right, right, right.
With the guests behind us.
It's not like that at all.
It's the same as usual.
The guests are all dirty.
It's 1.5 times dirtier than usual.
It's dirtier than usual?
You can see the moment when they come out, right?
The way they scream.
Right?
I can feel it.
How was it today?
Well, well, well.
The guests that came out today were
more than we expected.
We were 190 and 180.
More than we expected?
It's bigger than what we see on TV.
That's what they said.
That's what they thought.
Well, well, well.
They were surprised.
That's right.
I see.
Today is a special.
Yes, yes.
Today we have a punishment game.
Before I came here, I put on a red and white mask and lost.
You thought you wouldn't be able to do it, right?
Yes, yes.
Because it was last year's Kure.
I thought the people who were watching wouldn't be able to do it.
Yes, yes.
Well, today is a special.
I was surprised by that punishment game.
I was.
You dressed up as a dog from Hokuto.
Why?
You went to that place and said you were already dead.
Gaki no Tsukai Ara Endo Special Chikizuki Gouhou Matsumoto Ahohagaku Aomada Oekaki Dojo Bunkajin-hen
I did it once.
Everyone was so angry that they didn't like your poor painting.
Today, we have guests.
Today is a Bunkajin-hen.
Bunkajin.
But usually, I think that person is smart.
It's wonderful.
I think smart people have all sides.
Well, let's see how it goes.
Let's go.
Please welcome tonight's guests.
It's amazing.
Shizu, Shizu.
Wajima-san, you came in nicely.
Well, let's introduce them.
First, from this side, the political commentator, Shota Mano-san.
Next, the talent commentator, Yamaguchi Mie-san.
Next, the former Japanese TV announcer, Kobayashi Kawako-san.
Next, the professor of Waseda University, Otsuki Yoshiko-san.
Next, the student actor, Nakajima Keigo-san.
Next, the professor of Waseda University, the Egyptian researcher, Yoshimura Sakuji-san.
Next, the research scientist, Ichida Hiromi-san.
Lastly, the former boxing world champion, Koichi Wajima-san.
Wajima-san, can I come in?
What is it?
Wajima-san, how is your drawing?
It's a square, isn't it?
Yes, yes, yes.
A square?
I like to see it.
How about Maruo?
Do you draw?
Do you usually draw?
I draw a lot, but I haven't drawn much.
Everyone, you have your sketchbooks at home.
Yes, yes.
First, the first topic, please.
Doraemon.
Everyone, please draw Doraemon.
I'm pretty confident.
Huh? Something is missing.
No, I can definitely do this.
I don't know at all.
No, seriously, seriously.
Everyone, I'm sorry to disappoint you.
It's perfect.
Really, really, really.
Doraemon is perfect.
This is OK.
Then, let's see from this side.
Otsuki-san.
Otsuki, Otsuki.
What is this?
Isn't that a monster?
The nose is like this.
I have the impression that it's coming out.
The end is getting interesting.
Now, Kango-chan.
Is this an overkill?
No.
Please take it out.
Yes, Miya-san.
This is the closest I've ever drawn.
Why does it look like Fuji?
Now, Mano-chan.
No, I don't know.
What is that?
I've heard of an overkill.
That's all an overkill.
Doraemon.
Doraemon?
What do you do at a sweets festival?
Now, Wajima-san.
What is this?
Wajima-san, isn't that a condom?
As expected, there's a reason why it's called Gouko Matsumoto.
This is it.
Then, it's Bakagawa-kun.
No, it's not Bakagawa-kun.
It looks exactly like him.
Doraemon.
It's got vinegar on it.
It's got a thread on it.
Now, it's called warming up.
What's the next subject?
Over here.
Cow.
Now, everyone, please draw a cow.
First, let's take a look at the cow in the picture.
It's still big.
Is it okay?
It's cool.
Is it cool?
The face is like this.
Is it okay?
Yes.
It's okay, isn't it?
I can't tell if it's good weather or not.
Now, Yoshima-san.
It's good.
Where?
Here.
It looks like a sick cow.
It's close.
It looks like a cow.
It doesn't look like a cow.
The color is...
It's not good.
I got it.
Yes.
Now, Kyo-jun.
You make me laugh.
It's a cow.
It's not a cow.
It's a chimp.
Kamo-san.
Now, Mie-san.
I can't say anything.
The idea is poor.
Everyone thinks it's a standing cow.
I can say that.
Now, Bakagawa-kun.
Are you serious?
If you paint it black, it won't look good.
I forgot to paint it.
What kind of old man is this?
This is...
Is this Maro-chan?
Yes.
Shota-san, let's go.
This is a high point.
It's good.
I got it.
Please show me the answer.
Angel.
Angel?
I'm really embarrassed.
But...
Maro-chan, show me.
Is that so?
It's beautiful.
It's not bad.
I see.
It's calm.
I think it's okay.
Mie-san.
Did you add something?
I didn't add anything.
Mie-san.
It's not an angel.
Yes.
Why did you draw a cloud?
It's hard to draw a cloud.
So I drew a cloud.
The sun is shining.
I drew the whole picture.
But the face is messy.
It's an old picture.
I drew both.
An adult and a child.
This is good.
I see.
I drew this before.
It's really bad.
It's worse than this.
That's a bug.
What is yours?
Yours.
Marimo-san, who drew a small statue?
It's completely different, isn't it?
It's similar to mine.
Only the plate is similar.
It's the same.
I'm good at this.
Let's see your stupid drawing.
This is good.
Who drew a college student?
What is it?
But it's better than this.
Why did you draw a student?
What is it?
It's not like this.
You're good.
It's cute.
It's better than before.
It's messy.
Where did you draw me?
I made a mistake.
But the plate is good.
It's great.
It's glowing.
Please give me the last one.
Sphinx.
Yoshimura-san, if you don't draw well, it won't be funny.
Please give me the last one.
Yoshimura-san is crying.
Are you ready?
It seems that the stupid drawing is not over yet.
It's useless to continue.
It's okay.
Let's see your drawing.
I don't understand.
It's messy.
Sphinx is in the middle.
Let's see your drawing.
I don't remember.
I don't know.
Don't say it.
I know.
It's okay.
Kawago-san.
I understand.
Sphinx.
It's a break.
I don't want to show it.
What is it?
This is difficult.
It's difficult to understand.
Nakajima-san.
This is it.
Ichida-san.
It's embarrassing.
It's okay.
It's messy next to you.
It's scary.
I was surprised.
It's messy.
It's Sphinx.
Welcome.
Let's see your drawing.
How is it?
This is a world-famous drawing.
This is a low school student.
Let's see your drawing.
I'm a junior high school student.
You are not good at drawing.
I'm not good at drawing.
I have a personality.
My hair is messy.
I can't express it.
Let's see your drawing.
I have no comment.
Your drawing.
Who is Koshino Junko?
What is it?
You are amazing.
What are you talking about?
You are the winner of the first prize.
Thank you very much.
I can't reach my hand.
When I went to the store, the staff told me that it was sold out.
You can't say that.
I checked it myself.
I went to Okinawa for a drama special.
Are you doing a drama?
I can't do it.
Listen to me.
I went to Okinawa.
Okinawa?
I can't hear you.
I went to Okinawa.
Why can't I kiss my partner?
There was a record store.
I visited the record store.
I didn't understand it.
Do you have an H-Jungle CD?
I don't have it now.
Really?
I don't know when he'll come in.
Oh, really?
I don't know why that song is selling so well.
But that's a good thing.
The young clerk's brother was cleaning up the CD over here.
When he heard that, he looked at me and said,
Oh!
My brother was half-laughing.
I was being scolded by the old man.
The old man doesn't know why that song is selling so well.
But that's a good thing.
That's why I felt it when I saw it.
I didn't go to Okinawa.
As a member of H-Jun...
That's true.
But really, Moukyo,
I'm not kidding.
Please make this into an episode.
This is really serious.
That's not for me to decide.
No, no.
That's for Komuro to decide.
Hey, wait.
You're the only one who can say that.
Hey, I'm begging you.
Say it.
This is a serious matter.
I'm trying my best.
B.
Hey.
Don't talk about money.
Don't talk about money in that sense.
Lend me some money.
I'll pay you every week.
What are you talking about?
I want you to give me some money.
Why should I give you money?
You said you'd give me money for the record.
That's true.
I want you to give me money for the record.
It's all for Komuro.
It's not for me to decide.
You're right.
I'll do my best.
This is a serious matter.
I'm sorry for your stupid song.
But it's a little difficult.
It's easy to remember.
I'm really sorry.
I didn't know you could do that.
I'm sorry for the musicians.
Do you have a girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
Let's buy a girlfriend.
I'm sorry.
I don't like that.
It doesn't matter.
You're mean.
It's hot.
It's really hot.
I can't sleep well.
Is that so?
My body is especially hot.
I couldn't sleep because of the election.
Is that so?
Can you sleep?
I can't sleep because of the election.
I don't think so.
That's a phenomenon.
It's not a big phenomenon.
It's a phenomenon.
I can't sleep until the morning.
Your voice won't cross my ears.
I can't sleep because of the election.
That's a phenomenon.
I've heard it.
3 minutes.
Just once in a while.
Do you think 3 minutes will come just once in a while?
Time goes faster as the election is in progress.
Even if I'm scared, I can't sleep.
I want to go to bed.
You're still saying it...
I'm sorry.
Why don't you assume someone is a member of your team?!
You're a ignored member.
You have a lot of money.
I'm not asking you to give me money.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't care about the money in the CD.
I don't care about it.
It's strange at this point.
No, it's not.
That's the kind of hand you have.
No, I don't have money.
I don't have money, but I hate your money.
Why don't you give me some money?
I don't care about it!
I'm going to make you a lot of money.
You have a lot of money.
I'll take it.
That's the pattern.
What is it?
You don't have money.
Why do you have money?
I don't have money.
What? What do you mean?
What do you mean?
I said I have money.
Don't say that.
I don't have money.
Do you want money that much?
That's why.
No, really, really.
Look at that.
You want a lot of money.
I saw it because you told me to look at it.
You said it was 1,000 yen.
You want a lot of money.
Why?
You're so mean.
Do you want to look at it?
You can't do that.
I'm really in trouble.
It's not that bad.
It's really bad.
What's bad?
I'm in trouble this month.
What kind of life are you living?
How much do you spend a month?
I don't use it.
I don't have much money.
I've been scraped.
Don't say that.
Why?
That's enough.
What do you use it for?
No.
You're doing a lot of dirty things.
You're snacking.
I'm not snacking.
Wait a minute.
Don't say that I'm dirty.
You're dyeing your hair.
I'm not dirty.
You're spitting.
Why would I spit?
I'm not spitting.
You're holding an accordion.
Don't say that.
I've been scraped.
I've been scraped 16 times.
You're lying.
You've been scraped 16 times?
That's what it is.
Are you stupid?
I don't feel good.
How many times have you been scraped?
I don't know what to do if I get sick.
What if you end up in the hospital?
Promise me in front of the TV that you won't sell the CD.
I don't care.
You don't care.
You're holding an accordion.
No.
Don't say that.
I'm desperate.
I'm desperate for money.
I don't need that.
I don't need it.
You're stupid.
Why are you quiet?
You've done this CD money downtown.
Don't say that this is spitting.
Then the people around you will cry.
Why?
The people around you will cry.
Then the people around you will cry.
Hama-chan, your partner is heavy.
What?
Why are you so depressed?
I'm saying you shouldn't do that.
I'm not persuasive.
Please do that.
You signed the contract in March, didn't you?
What's a contract?
It's a new song.
I don't care if you get angry.
The new song is over.
Ah, the new song.
When will the new song come out?
Wow.
What?
Which one is it?
I'm talking about April.
You're talking about June.
Say it clearly, you idiot.
Wow.
Say it came out around May.
Let's say it came out.
It's number one.
What?
It's number one so there's no way it would be left.
My underwear is torn.
No matter how hard I try, the torn underwear doesn't work.
So I have underwear that I can't even take a shit with.
It happens.
It happens even when I'm crying.
I can't get it.
You can throw it away.
I can't throw it away.
Why?
I think everyone is living a great life.
You can say,
I don't care.
You can say that.
CQCQ.
I don't know.
You can say that.
When I get home, I'll wear this.
Why?
When I get home, I'll calm down.
I'm really depressed.
There's nothing in the fridge.
You can't buy that.
Thank you for the meal.
That's what you say.
What did you eat?
Thank you for the meal.
It's like this.
I want you to laugh.
I can't laugh.
I want you to give me a privilege.
I don't want to get caught in traffic.
I want you to let me go first.
Do you have a wife?
I can't go for them.
It's a poor family.
Get out of the way.
I'm going to get a lot of money.
I'm going to make the audience go crazy.
Finally, the long-awaited Hama-chan's worst punishment game.
Instead of the usual postcard, we have a lot of questions from the talent.
I want the talent to answer the questions.
That's right.
It seems that they are asking us to do that.
Before that, let's have them come out for a moment.
What?
Please.
There is a guest who wants to come out no matter what.
Please come out.
It's Yuta Yoshiko.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
When I passed the part A, my grandmother came out again.
Akiko is definitely behind this.
Thank you.
Thank you for calling me.
I didn't know at all. I didn't hear anything.
I'm getting hot when it's my turn.
Really?
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
I have something I want to give you today.
It looks like a handkerchief, doesn't it?
Where is it?
I can see it.
I can see it right away, so please turn it over.
This is good.
I don't need it anymore, so I'll give it to you.
It's 1993, so Mita-san doesn't wear it.
Is that so?
I think you were born in 1994.
I don't know that.
Is that so?
This is a gift.
I'll give it to you soon.
Thank you very much.
If you could give me a handkerchief.
That's right.
But you've made a lot of money this year, haven't you?
That's not true.
Did you drink so much that your head would explode?
I'm looking forward to it.
That's right.
That's all I'm looking forward to this year.
Mita-san, please give it to me as soon as possible.
That's right.
If I do that, I'll grow.
I won't be told anything again.
If you win first place, give me some money.
Why?
I won first place, so I don't need it.
No, no, no.
I'm also preparing to win the lottery.
That's great.
Please win the lottery.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
But Mita-san is making more money.
That's not true.
Mita-san has less money than us.
But she has a lot of money.
That's right.
You're lying.
If you win this one, how much will you take?
That's a lot.
That's a lie.
That's why the set is like this.
That's right.
If you win this one, you'll probably have millions or tens of millions of yen.
If that's the case, I don't have anything to do.
No, no, no.
If we win here, we'll be in trouble.
It's different every time.
Today, I'm proud to win this.
I'm very proud.
I'll cut everything here.
Why?
What's the time for such a strange program?
It's great that I'm in between the two of you and I'm on the show.
That's great.
That's why at home, too.
What's this?
It's a kid's soap.
That's right.
I don't know.
Look, there's a kid.
I'm proud of myself.
Do you watch it with your child at home?
Yes, sometimes.
Is that so?
But...
What is it?
Aren't you a little bit tired?
I'm tired.
I'm not tired at all today.
Is that so?
Why?
You're very tired.
I'm always tired.
I'm very anxious.
Is that so?
I'm calm.
I'm sweating.
It's too hot.
You're sweating a lot today.
It's unusual.
It's hot.
Are you surprised?
I'm surprised.
I was talking about money in my head today.
It happened by chance.
I didn't say anything bad about me.
Really?
You're funny.
I was talking about money.
I was so surprised that I was surprised.
You were surprised to see me after I did something bad, right?
What?
You're not surprised at all.
Why are you fighting?
What are you talking about?
Are you going to do it?
You're very motivated.
Do something.
What are you talking about?
I'm here to do something.
You're like an amateur.
I was told to do something.
How old is your daughter?
I was surprised.
I thought you asked about my age.
What are you talking about?
How old is your daughter?
She's not my daughter.
Is she your daughter?
She's 20 years old.
She's 15 years old.
She's cute.
I didn't know that.
We went somewhere far away before.
We did it in the rain together.
We did it.
24 hours.
We said we would participate in that.
You said you wanted to see it.
That's what I said.
You're not very smart.
That's rude.
I quit.
We watched it together on TV.
We danced at that time.
I was surprised.
Why do you remember that?
That's right.
I was young at that time.
It was a few months ago.
Do you want to dance with me?
I'm weak.
Let's think of something new.
I'm really weak.
Really?
I can't dance.
This is a rare opportunity.
I can't use this.
I'm sorry.
Well...
Like this.
What is this?
Like this?
You have to lower your waist.
I can't do this.
Why?
Like this?
I can't.
You have to raise your nose.
This is different.
Let's stop.
I can't do this.
What is this?
Didn't you dance?
I like this.
I often do this.
What is this?
Why is your hand behind you?
Did you dance in the past?
I'm really weak.
Everyone is amazing.
The audience is amazing, too.
We dance together at the end.
You are great.
I want to dance with you.
Do you want to dance?
Yes.
I want to dance with you.
I'm lonely.
Thank you very much.
What kind of dance did you do?
I didn't dance at all.
Like this.
I can do that.
You are great.
I often did that.
Goodbye.
Thank you very much.
Everyone, the middle of the stage is empty.
I thought it was empty.
I bumped into the middle of the stage.
Don't say that.
I don't know what this is.
This is so funny.
I'm tired.
I think you did a good job.
I thought you would win.
I thought so, too.
Do you read the flow of the times?
I didn't think that much.
If you have any problems, please contact me.
I'll tell you the number of the office.
Because my work is bad.
My work is bad.
I'll tell you the number of the office.
What's wrong?
I don't have a pen.
I can't write.
I can write.
I know.
I lent it to Sakamoto.
I don't have a pen.
I want to take it.
I went to New York.
I want to take a pen.
He is going to New York to take a pen.
What are you doing?
Do you have a day off today?
Yes.
I went to New York for a week.
I went to Bahama for a week.
What are you doing?
It's a punishment game.
I heard that.
You know that, don't you?
It's not cool.
The trip to New York begins.
Where do you live?
I don't have a pen.
I want to take a pen.
He can't do anything.
He arrives at JFK International Airport.
He is looking for a pen.
He arrives in America.
This is the worst.
He is in a hurry to go to his house in Sakamoto.
How many years have I been waiting for this?
Are you reading the flow of the world?
He finally arrives at the center of the world's economy and culture.
He is looking for a house in Sakamoto.
I'm in a hurry.
Where are you going?
Where are you?
This is the Empire State Building, the symbol of Manhattan.
It's cold.
It's cold, but it's beautiful.
Let's take a picture.
A picture?
Why?
It's very cool.
In addition, he has a lot of coins that he doesn't want.
This is the last time.
Next time I want to go skating.
Rockfeller Center, a famous skating rink in New York.
He is in a hurry to go to his house in Sakamoto.
He is attracted to sightseeing.
Next is Times Square.
I have to go home.
You can go home tomorrow.
I don't have time.
I don't like hot dogs.
Let's eat.
This is not the time to eat hot dogs.
He is frustrated.
Hamada.
Don't take pictures of me.
Eat this.
This is the city where many artists live.
It's been 21 hours since he left Tokyo.
He finally arrives at the apartment where Ryuichi Sakamoto lives.
This is where I live.
I don't know.
It's been a while since I met Ryuichi Sakamoto.
Ryuichi Sakamoto.
Professor.
Thank you.
I forgot something.
What is that title?
What is that?
That's it.
He draws a line from the professor's hand.
This is a warm pen.
The first game is a success.
Hey, Sakamoto.
Ryuichi.
Let's go.
I don't have that attitude.
I have to go home.
I'm not like you in Japan.
I'm a fighter.
It's cold.
You should go to the airport.
I have to go to the airport.
You're good.
I'm on a vacation.
You can say that at first.
That's it.
It's the worst.
See you later.
And Matsumoto goes to Japan.
The second time.
Did you do it once?
Yes.
You have to say it.
It's a meeting.
That's it.
Finally.
What's wrong?
You're like Matsumoto.
You always get in the way.
But now it's over.
It was very cold.
That's true.
It was cold at night.
It's an eraser.
What?
Wait a minute. What are you talking about?
I don't care. I want to bring it to you.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
It's Sakamoto-san's call.
I don't care.
It's a bad game for what you said.
It's really annoying.
Hello?
Are you in the classroom?
Yes.
Good morning.
I'm Matsumoto.
Oh, hello.
Hello, hello.
I just realized.
I don't have an eraser.
Oh, you left it there.
No, I didn't.
You left it there.
Do you have it?
No, I don't.
I have it here.
Do you have it?
I'll go get it.
Hama-chan is going to New York to get an eraser.
New York Manhattan, a nostalgic town, welcomes Hamada.
I want you to welcome me.
This is weird.
Stop, stop, stop.
Is that Suga-chan?
I don't want to go home.
Hey!
Why are you here?
I'm going to get an eraser.
I'm going to the
Why are you hiding it?
I'm going to get an eraser.
The nostalgic reunion with producer Suga.
Times Square is here after two days.
Why are you here?
Why are you hiding it?
I'm going to get an eraser.
I don't want to go home.
It's been a while since I came to New York.
It's been a while.
It's not the time to eat anymore.
Hey.
What?
I want to shop.
Shopping?
I don't buy anything.
We should shop.
Why?
I want to shop.
New York's fifth district.
The world-class boutique shopping mall.
He's being dragged around again by Suga's interference.
And he's carrying a lot of luggage.
It's been two days since East Village.
It's been 59 hours since he left Japan for the first time.
The grand punishment game is finally coming to an end.
This is a punishment game, right?
I lost, so I don't know what to do.
What is this?
This is annoying.
I don't know what to do.
It's so cold.
It's finally the reunion of Ryuichi Sakamoto and the 38th time in a row.
I'm done.
I'm tired.
Oh, it's 90 minutes.
I'm sorry.
You're late.
What do you mean I'm late?
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did you come here on purpose?
What are you doing?
He draws a line from the professor's hand.
The eraser is warmly handed to him.
The punishment game is complete.
I got the eraser.
This is what happens when you win the grand prize.
I'm going to write a song from tomorrow.
I'm going to challenge you.
I'm going to write a song and meet you at the grand prize venue.
See you.
And Matsumoto goes to Japan.
This is a pen.
I'm going to use this pen.
This is the pen.
You should have checked this pen from the beginning.
I'm going to use this pen.
I don't need a pencil.
That's a pen, isn't it?
No, it's not this.
I'm sorry.
Go, go.
What?
I want to play Evian.
That's great!
It's been a long time, hasn't it?
We have to play Evian.
Why?
That's how the audience reacts.
You're going to play Evian again?
Come on!
It's hard to play in New York.
I heard it's really hard.
It's really, really hard.
I haven't slept much.
You haven't slept?
It's daytime!
Well, I've done something similar to that.
What is it?
No, no, no.
Your punishment has already been decided.
Oh, really?
What is it?
Go to the North Pole and become a cool mint gum.
A penguin?
I'll sell it after I get off the plane.
You'll sell it?
It's a limited production.
When we were on the plane,
Mr. Abe was sitting in the back.
The woman said,
Please sign it.
It's okay.
It's a long trip.
I'll take it off now, so please wait a minute.
I said, what?
She took off her bra.
In the plane.
She took off her bra and said,
Here you go.
She's crazy.
It's really warm.
I signed another bra.
Don't smell it.
I see.
I didn't eat anything on the way home.
I was so tired.
You couldn't eat?
I didn't care about the in-flight meal.
I wanted to sleep.
I slept for a long time.
In the second half of the flight,
There was a foreign man with a bad Japanese.
He came to me and said,
You didn't eat anything, did you?
I said yes.
If you don't eat anything on your way home from abroad,
You can be mistaken for a drug carrier.
I said, I didn't eat anything.
I went home and left.
If I ate something, it would be digested.
All the medicine would go wrong.
I put some medicine in a plastic bag and drank it.
Then I went back to Japan.
I didn't eat anything.
I was sleeping all the time.
The other foreigners
looked at me like this to pass me by.
That person said,
You didn't eat anything, did you?
Of course I did.
But I carried it.
Let's ask questions.
Really?
Let's do it.
How are you, Hama-chan and Mach-chan in downtown?
It's been a long time.
I always enjoy watching this program.
I'm one of the fans of this program.
I want you to continue to do this program for a long time.
When you touch something,
There is a static electricity that flashes.
I've been wondering how to prevent that static electricity.
I want to prevent it.
How can I do it?
Why are you acting like a fool?
Do you always do this?
I can't prevent it.
It's the logic of putting a lid on something that stinks.
Stop it, you idiot.
But I can't do it right away.
You can't do it, but you can do it right away.
No, I can't do it right away.
I'm sorry for hitting you.
It's too nostalgic.
What does static electricity taste like?
It's a quiet electricity.
Really?
You didn't know that, did you?
I knew it, you idiot.
Don't say yes now.
Say yes.
Are you ready?
Static heat.
Yes.
Then what is yes?
Static heat.
Yes.
Say it.
No.1 static heat.
I'll sing it as hard as I can.
Yutemi.
Yes.
Say it. Static heat.
Static heat.
This is the culprit of static electricity.
By preventing this static heat,
we can get rid of static electricity from this world.
Yes, yes, yes.
Are you ready?
Try walking.
You should be able to walk.
Now,
there is a way to avoid static heat.
There is a way to avoid static heat.
Please tell me.
That's it. You know it, right?
If I walk like that?
If you walk like this,
it might be fun.
No one walks like that.
You might look like an idiot.
No, I don't.
But,
there is a lot of static electricity.
Yes, yes.
You have to do something about it.
Is there a way to walk?
Walk without touching the floor.
What?
Yes, yes, yes.
Come here.
There are sweets, too.
I don't know.
Walk without touching the floor.
You look like an idiot.
You are an idiot.
Walk without touching the floor.
Are you ready?
What is this?
This has nothing to do with it.
You can't walk without touching the floor.
What?
I can't walk without touching the floor?
What do you mean?
Do you mean the same movement?
Yes, yes.
If you do this,
static electricity will never be generated.
You can't hurry.
Yes.
But you don't like walking like this.
So, let's stop.
Are you going to stop?
Up to this point, we have introduced the products of trust, Tiger Magic, Asahi Beer, Noelia, Nipro, Lion Po, and our sponsor in Tokyo.
Let's go to the next one.
Hello, everyone in downtown Tokyo.
Long time no see.
I'm Koike from Kenjunkai.
There are a lot of problems with various countries around Japan.
There is a problem with Japan-US trade and China.
There is also a problem with refugees in Africa.
The hottest topic in Japan right now is KEDO.
Let me hear your thoughts on KEDO.
What is KEDO?
KEDO.
K-E-D-O.
Do you know what it is?
It's a Chinese character.
No, no.
What is it?
It's a story about me.
It's a Chinese character.
That's right. It's KEDO.
What does KEDO mean?
You are a fool.
Why don't you cut off your nipples?
Cut off my nipples?
I have to do a lot of things.
That's right.
Do you know KEDO?
Yes.
Is that so?
OZONSO.
Again?
What did you write?
What is OZONSO?
What is it?
I'm asking you.
I don't know. Please tell me.
OZONSO is...
Please leave.
It's nothing to do with OZONSO.
It's nothing?
Yes.
What are you thinking?
What?
At that time.
Why are you angry at me now?
It's KEDO.
I'm talking about KEDO.
Please tell me.
I know.
You.
Yes.
You shouldn't do that.
You.
Yes.
Don't do that weird thing.
It's KEDO.
KEDO.
Everyone can do this.
If you think about it, you'll understand.
Do you understand?
I don't know.
What does K stand for?
That's what I'm asking you.
What is it?
North America.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
England.
Are you okay?
What is D?
Germany.
I know.
It's Germany.
Leave it to me.
Okay.
The last one.
Australia.
It's Australia.
Okay.
Giraffe.
Why did you say giraffe?
Yes.
What is E?
It's a dolphin.
That's good.
I'm starting to understand.
What is D?
It's a dog.
That's all you can say?
Wait a minute.
Everyone, be quiet.
I have something I want to ask you all.
What is CHOKODAKE?
What?
Is CHOKODAKE English?
I didn't say that.
I didn't say CHOKODAKE.
What?
K is a giraffe, right?
K is a giraffe.
E is a dolphin, right?
It's a dolphin.
I'm starting to understand.
What is D?
It's a dog.
That's all you can say?
That's right.
The last one is O.
It's OCHI.
It's O.
Leave it to me.
What is O?
Australia.
I wanted to do that first.
You had to do it before that.
All right.
Let's do it properly.
The cake is bad.
It's like a line.
K is.
The cake is bad.
Nice.
It's better than I thought!
That's good.
D.
What's going on?
That's good.
O.
O?
You're always wrong.
You can't even write it.
But I don't know Hamada-kun.
Jimin, Jimin.
Stop it.
Even if you ask me a lot, I don't know.
That's enough.
Let's go to the next one.
Good evening.
I'm Azuma Chizuru.
I have hay fever.
I'm having a hard time today.
Recently, I've become an adult woman.
I've been calling myself an adult for a long time.
When do you think of me as an old woman?
I think of you as an old man.
See you later.
What are you talking about?
When do you think of me as an old woman?
Men go through a certain stage.
Little by little.
It comes suddenly.
At once.
It was normal until last week's Friday.
There was something like that.
Is that so?
What do you think of me as an adult woman?
When do you think of me as an adult woman?
What is that?
This is okay.
Why is it okay?
It's starting to smell.
What is that?
Does it smell?
When you get older, it starts to smell.
I'm 35 years old.
This is strange.
What does it smell like?
It smells like an animal.
That's the same as before.
That's right.
It always smells like an animal.
I'm really okay.
My body doesn't smell.
What?
Do you have a lot of curry powder?
What are you talking about?
It smells here and here.
Your back smells.
Why?
Wait a minute.
You can't say that.
Your back smells.
Your back doesn't smell like that.
It smells like an elephant.
What kind of smell is that?
My legs don't smell.
My armpits don't smell.
I don't smell at all.
It feels good.
I feel the same way.
I feel better.
I don't know.
I don't feel good.
I feel really good right now.
I know.
The adventure of Matsumoto.
Explosive explosion.
One day in March.
Hamada and the staff were called to Matsumoto.
At that time, they hadn't heard Matsumoto's decision yet.
He told us to come here.
He came early in the morning.
He came.
Matsumoto came there.
He made me feel like I was missing him.
Everyone's here.
What?
There's no water.
It's cold.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry to say this in front of you.
Recently, I feel like I'm very lazy.
That's in front of you.
I'm not inspired at all.
Inspired.
What do you mean?
Of course, that's what I mean.
I think it's very bad because it's becoming a very raw Matsumoto.
In the old days, I think it was more like a state of emergency.
I think it's coming to an end.
I think it's very dangerous.
I'm going to do some action.
I want you to see it.
It's different.
He's different.
Minotake is different.
That's what I want you to think.
Let me explain the situation.
I have a car ready.
I'm going to get in there.
I think you can see the helicopter on the side.
I'm going to pull up that car with that.
I'm going to go to a pretty high height.
I can't do anything with that alone.
I don't like it.
So I'm going to lift it up from the helicopter and drop it down.
I'm going to knock down the car.
It's still hard to do that alone.
As you can see over there, I have a tank ready.
I want you to thank me.
I think I'm going to be beaten up pretty hard.
But I don't think that's enough.
That's me.
That's what I've been thinking since the other day.
I want you to know that Matsumoto is crazy.
By doing that, my sleeping man instinct...
Your sleeping man instinct?
That's ridiculous!
What's the point of this?
You can watch it.
Are you stupid?
Which university did you go to?
I went to Kyoto.
I don't know.
He is Matsumoto Hitoshi.
He is a man who has overcome many obstacles as a weak 31 year old.
His trained body and sharpened mental strength...
It's only when you're in a state of extreme smoke that you're 100% sure.
Today, Matsumoto will take on the biggest challenge of this century.
I'll do it.
I don't want to run away.
It's okay to wind it up with a chain.
And welding.
I can't get out.
Have you ever done this?
This is the first time.
When I did it before, the car was black.
Who was watching at that time?
Who did you think was welding?
Who was around you?
Speak louder.
What?
What did you say?
Who was around you?
I don't know.
Finally, Matsumoto gets in the car.
What should I do?
I don't know.
I don't want to do it anymore.
I want to take a picture at 8mm.
I don't have a frame.
The car is chained and the escape is completely impossible.
It is even more carefully welded to the gap in the door of the car.
Matsumoto's expression changes.
Is it anxiety?
Or is his face scared?
What is it?
Are you going to raise the helicopter?
I'm sorry, but please give me a helicopter.
The sound of the helicopter engine echoes in the quiet place.
The car weighs 1.5 tons.
It's a very dangerous job just to lift it up.
At this time, Matsumoto's tension had reached its limit.
The helicopter that jumped continues hovering in the super low air.
It approaches the car that Matsumoto rode.
And the helicopter firmly connects the car with wires.
The helicopter slowly rises.
Will Matsumoto succeed?
This is the start of the ultimate challenge by Matsumoto.
Matsumoto is very excited.
Are you okay?
I'm shocked when I see that.
It's very high.
Look at that.
Are you okay?
It's very high.
How high is it?
It's amazing.
Can I drop this?
Everyone, let's go.
It's going.
This is amazing.
Are you okay?
Is it over?
Should we go see it?
The car is very high.
I shouldn't have done that.
If I get hurt, will I be responsible for it?
He said that.
Let's go see it.
Are you okay?
It's over.
I did it.
It was longer than I thought.
How did you feel when you fell?
I was surprised.
I did it.
Is it true?
Are you inspired?
I'm glad I didn't get hurt.
My face is a little dirty.
What did you do?
I was surprised.
Are you serious?
I thought there was still time.
Down Power.
Tell a surprising dream.
Good evening.
I'm the president of Joron Electric.
My name is Shio Miyagi.
My dream is to go to space.
Tell me your dream.
I don't have a dream.
What month is this?
I think it's out now.
I want to go to space.
This is the same as me.
Why?
You said you wanted to go to space.
I want to go to space again.
Have you been to space before?
Yes.
I want to go to space like that time.
When was that?
That was when I was in the first year of high school.
When you were in the first year of high school?
Yes.
Did you go to space alone?
Alone?
When I was in the first year of high school, I was in my prime.
You were in your prime?
What do you mean by prime?
Don't you know what a prime is?
I'm talking about my prime.
You said you were in your prime.
Don't you know what a prime is?
I don't know.
You really don't know what a prime is?
That's enough.
Why?
I don't know.
You can tell me.
I'm talking about space.
That's after that.
I'm talking about my prime.
You don't know what a prime is?
You're stupid.
I'm sorry.
Be careful.
Don't you know what a prime is?
I don't know.
I'm talking about space.
Okay.
When I was in my prime.
You have a lot of things at home.
Have you ever left the house because you didn't like it?
Not at home.
You haven't?
I have.
Have you ever been there?
Where?
To space.
You went to space at home?
I went to space at home.
How did you get there?
How did I get there?
There's a way to get there.
With a lens.
Come on.
Do you have two hours to get there?
Are you ready?
Look up.
I want to go to space.
I can go.
That's for sure.
Your mouth is open.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I haven't been to space.
What do you want me to do?
What are you talking about?
That's what I want to say.
Do you have a drawer at home?
I have a drawer.
You have a drawer, right?
I'll give you a drawer.
I'll close it once.
I'll go inside.
I'll come out.
That's space.
Finally, he reveals Matsumoto's hidden secret.
You never wave your hand at the end of a child's talk.
I told you, didn't I?
I told you.
You often say goodbye to the end of a TV show.
I'll do it until this time next week.
Why do you do that?
Do you want a fan?
Why are you trying to sell a fan?
I'm not selling a fan.
I'm just saying goodbye.
That's not good.
I'm not that kind of man.
Do you sometimes do that?
No.
I've been on TV once before.
Do you have a reason to do that?
No.
I'm saying this.
Really?
No.
That's strange.
When I'm working on TV, I'm the only one who watches it.
Please watch the VTR next time.
Tenshou Bukiya.
Please look forward to the next part 5.
Please give him a round of applause.
Hey, hey, hey.
What's this?
You're shaking it too much.
The last one was a baseball game.
Right?
That was last year's play.
Do I have to tell you the reason?
There's no reason.
I just said goodbye consciously.
If you say goodbye naturally, your body will be like this.
When the alcohol runs out, I can't help it.
A woman's confession.
Where do you feel the sex appeal of a woman?
I'm still in my 50s and 60s.
I'm always aware that there are only women in my head who want to be popular with that girl.
I don't know if I can be young.
I'm attracted to a woman's blue charm.
Where do you feel the sex appeal of a woman?
Can I be honest with you?
You might think I'm a pervert.
I want you to feel it.
That's clear.
I get excited when there's something beautiful about a beautiful woman.
For example?
For example, a beautiful woman has a snot.
It's snot.
That's right.
Even if I say it, it's in the middle of my face.
I get very excited.
I want you to feel it.
I think that's why I don't like it.
I get very excited.
For example, I'm eating somewhere.
When I see a woman with a snot, I think it's funny.
I understand that.
I'm sorry.
I get very excited.
I'm just a stupid woman.
I go to the bathroom.
I see a woman with a snot.
I got a snot.
Damn it.
Why?
It's very beautiful, but when I do this, it looks like a snot.
It's a very good excuse.
I don't like that.
Why?
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's coming out.
I wonder if I can control it like this.
I wonder if I can run.
That part.
I wonder if it catches the radio waves there.
It's a problem if you fix it.
It's hard if you cut it.
I really want you to cut it.
I'm a woman.
I understand.
I want you to cut it, but I don't know if you cut it.
But I want you to cut it.
I'm most excited about the beautiful things with scars.
But it was different in the past.
Did you hate it just because you had a snot?
If I had a snot, I would have called it a poop.
If you had a snot?
Did you hate it because you had a snot?
It's easy.
If I had a snot, I would have called it a poop.
I understand that.
That's why I treat it like a poop.
It's good to be on top of a poop.
When you go on a trip, you should go to a poop.
Matsumoto, the president of the country, is a student.
You are different when you have money.
Nice to meet you. I'm Sato Punch.
I have a question.
I got a nickname Sato Punch because I used to wear a punch perm.
The reason why I wore a punch perm was because I was in my 20s at that time.
I used to go out for a drink or go to a pink-related store.
I was often teased by the hostess that students should come to such a place.
That's why I wore a punch perm.
What do you think?
Please tell me what you did to avoid being teased.
This is a common thing.
Anyone can think of it.
I was never teased.
I was always teased.
I was called the left and right eye of the press.
I'm not afraid of it.
I don't feel bad about it.
No, no, no. I don't feel bad about it.
No, no, no.
Everyone was looking at me with great eyes.
I don't feel bad about it.
I didn't feel bad about it.
Everyone was looking at me with great eyes.
Are you stupid?
Even in high school, I was teased by the student uniform.
My chest was open and my chest was sticking out.
What?
I was teased like this.
You were teased like that.
Yes, I was teased like this.
Now, I'd like to give you a wonderful present.
This time, I went to New York for a punishment game.
I'd like to give you a few things I used at that time.
First of all, this ugly cap that says I love New York.
And I put it on my head.
I don't know what it is.
It's shining.
It's shining because the world is shining.
And this bra.
And when I climbed this Empire State Building, I made it.
It stinks.
But I have four of these.
And look at this.
No one will buy it.
The person at the store told me to close it.
This necktie is the best.
I'm going to show this to everyone on TV.
And I'd like to give this cap to the world's Sakamoto Ryuichi.
I'd like to give this cap to everyone.
Please write what you want on the postcard and send it to me.
I'll be waiting.
It's me.
Does anyone know?
Thank you very much.