Let's play dodge ball.
I see.
Before that, let's play dodge ball.
Yes.
This rule is difficult.
For example, when you cross this line,
Cover me, cover me, cover me, cover me.
Cover me.
While holding your breath.
Let's play dodge ball.
Yes.
With our team.
With Garakuta.
With Garakuta and Ponkrat.
Today is a great day.
Look at the camera.
Who are these people?
They are the handball team of Sanyo Shokai.
Oh.
They are here.
I heard it earlier.
Yes.
They throw the ball, right?
They are supposed to hop.
Do you call it hop?
Oh, here it comes.
Will it hit?
Yes.
This is a little...
But I don't want you to go out because it's a TV show.
I'll do my best.
But I want to say one thing.
We are stars.
That's all I want to say.
As you said earlier,
Rule.
We need a referee.
Yes.
The referee of the Japanese Dodgeball Association.
Mr. Tomioka will do it.
Please.
You don't look like our referee.
I'm worried about Mr. Tomioka.
How many people will go out?
How many?
Four people.
Then I'll go out with four people.
Yes.
You are the one who will go out first.
Four people.
I don't know who will go out first.
But I want to do it with a 10-year combination.
It's the same no matter what you do.
I'm always with you at home.
OK.
No problem.
OK, OK.
simplesmente
бо
possibility
OK.
That's the rule.
It's OK.
OK.
finding
It's OK.
Ouch!
I'm scared.
It's hard to take.
Look at the side.
I'm scared.
What is this?
7 to 0.
Team Sanyo wins.
Ladies and gentlemen.
It's noisy.
Are you all doing well?
We're doing well on time.
Really?
On time?
That's right.
Why?
Because we have a lot of days off.
We don't get angry as much as Golden Week.
That's right.
It's really annoying.
We work until the morning when people are off.
That's right.
What?
We don't have a day off that's so hard.
We don't.
Right?
Even if we do, we get told off.
We get told off and we're in a bad condition.
That's right.
And we end up sleeping at home.
We get a day off and when we wake up we have a lot of things to fold.
Why?
It's like that.
You're so mean.
I'll say this in my head.
We've decided.
What?
Which ball?
We've decided which ball.
On Saturday the 18th.
Yes.
We'll do it at Yomiuri Land.
Yomiuri Land.
We'll do it at Yomiuri Land on the second round.
We'll do it.
So everyone, we'll do it at Bulma.
The girls will do it at Bulma.
Yes.
The order of the first and the second is important.
It's not important at all.
What is it?
It's the order of the first and the second.
So we'll do it in the order of the first and the second?
Yes.
So we'll do it for the first 500 people.
I don't know if we'll cut this part out, but please bring a lot of money.
I don't understand.
You know, last year in September or October I went to Okinawa.
As a child.
Yes.
It's almost the 100th anniversary.
It's not the time to celebrate the 100th anniversary.
So I thought I'd go overseas with everyone.
The fee?
It will cost a little.
Well, if 1000 people come.
So I won't ask you to come.
It can't be helped if you drop your wallet.
That's right.
It can't be helped.
If you don't write your name on it, you can't keep it.
So let's go to Hawaii.
You can go with everyone to Hawaii.
That's good.
Let's go on a tour.
Let's take everyone.
You don't have to go on tours.
Don't say only you.
You must go to your girlfriend.
I'll go on a tour with Saigo Hideki.
We'll go to the airport and have a dinner show.
We'll go home and have a great time.
I hate those tours.
We are always the same.
Always the same.
Hey, you...
What is it?
What are you thinking about?
We are always the same. How much are we the same?
We are always the same when we go somewhere.
You take me with you to a lot of places.
I always hear this, but the people who come today...
They are usually...
One more thing.
Why do you treat them like this?
I don't trust them at all.
Really?
But you always tell them to treat you better.
You tell them to treat you with a warm heart.
I have a warm personality.
So I treat them warmly.
But they only treat 30 people.
What kind of fans are they?
That's right.
For example, the girl with glasses.
If she dies, will she cry?
Why does she have to cry?
Right?
That's terrible!
She won't cry?
What about you?
I won't cry.
That's right.
Why does she have to cry when she's dead?
But I don't hate her.
I don't hate her.
That's why I was shocked when I was the president.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you laughing?
You don't have to be serious about it.
I did feel sad when she died.
Really?
I did feel sad.
But it doesn't matter if you turn blue.
I was the president about half a year ago.
What do you call it?
It's called a pacemaker.
I had a machine in my heart.
I was like, I'm moving with a machine.
What are you talking about?
I touched it and there was a machine in my heart.
That's right.
At that time, she had a weak memory.
You can't do it all at once.
Does a pacemaker have such a strong effect?
Yes, it does.
After that, the president's movements suddenly changed.
It's true.
He was walking like this because he was so strong.
He?
It's okay.
Be careful.
But it's different.
What is it?
I said it earlier.
I think you'll like it if you press something.
I'll definitely do it.
The other day, I said something in the program.
When I was doing this to the girl in front of me,
I fell down trying to rub my face.
The other day, I was doing make-up for Fuji TV.
A girl in make-up came up to me.
Matsumoto-san, that's terrible.
You dropped the girl in make-up, didn't you?
Why do you think so?
Do you want me to rub my face?
I've never rubbed my face.
You've been lying all day.
You've rubbed your face so many times.
I've never rubbed my face.
I've rubbed my face three times in a row.
I've rubbed my face in the changing room.
I've rubbed my face in the bathroom.
It's been a long time.
What?
What did you do yesterday?
I was at home.
You had a day off yesterday.
Yes.
What did you do yesterday?
I was at home.
What did you do?
What?
I was playing outside.
What did you do?
I was playing.
With whom?
What?
With a friend.
A friend with long hair?
I think so.
Do you have short hair?
No.
Do you have a skirt?
I don't have a skirt.
What?
A pants?
Yes.
I can't see anyone around me when I walk.
It's not good.
Well, I can see you.
You look good.
We are not a man.
What?
I don't care.
How long did you stay?
About an hour?
No, 2 or 3 hours.
You stayed that long?
It's daytime!
You stayed in the park for 2 or 3 hours?
Yes.
What did you do in the park for 3 hours?
I played badminton.
And?
You played badminton?
You are not a man.
Everyone thinks so.
We are both men.
Why don't you understand?
You don't like to move your body outside.
Why do you go out with a man?
That's because you are a woman.
You played baseball?
Where did you throw it?
You said, Hii-kun, sorry.
You said, the wind is strong.
I call you Hii-kun.
What do you call me?
I don't like it.
Why is your face red?
Your face is red.
I was silent until now.
Actually, I am a bright man.
You stayed that long?
Yes.
You stayed in the park for 2 or 3 hours?
You are from Awamori in Akita?
Yes.
What do you mean?
Is your father the leader of the circus?
What's going on?
I am not the leader.
You are not the reason of death.
Don't make promises.
Thank you very much.
There may be such a thing.
He is a man with a knack.
A knack?
Wait a minute.
What is a knack?
It is clear in this program.
What is it?
We can make mistakes.
Don't take advantage of others.
I can't say that.
Let's stop it.
It's a habit.
Even if you watch TV,
even if the announcer bites you,
even if the announcer says,
this is Kenpatesu,
you can't say that.
Even if you watch TV,
You can't say that.
Let's stop it.
Okay.
Hello, everyone.
There was a program called Best Ten,
which I don't want to use as a commercial.
There was a downtown in 9th place.
I think so.
This is what I heard
from the head of the advertising department
of a big company, 350 companies.
It's a solid data.
There are only good companies, right?
That's right.
I don't want to be in a commercial.
It's a lie to make a delicious
sweets that are not delicious.
It's a lie to make a delicious sweets that are not delicious.
But this is the case.
That's right.
This is...
This is the problem.
I'm sad, so I won't say it.
I'm wearing it.
I'm wearing it,
but it's really bad.
That's right.
I don't know what I heard.
It's a destroyer's commercial in Kagoshima.
I don't know what kind of route
I came on.
What's sad?
It's a destroyer's commercial.
I don't say it's a car,
a cigarette, or a whiskey.
Destroyer's commercial...
What are you going to do with that?
Namu...
I'm sure you're going to do something in front of Takahashi.
But I'll say it little by little.
There's a song I've heard.
It's a trouble.
Especially the food.
Where do you choose?
It's the mouth.
Really?
If you go from there,
the problem is...
Why?
This weirdo mouth
is destroying everything.
It's eating our dreams.
This weirdo mouth
is eating our characters.
You are bad.
I've had this mouth for 27 years.
It's not weird.
Sometimes,
I think,
what?
That's not good.
That's why the food is bad.
That's not true.
The food is bad.
You are bad.
I'm not bad.
You are purple, too.
I hear the mouth.
Your mouth...
And you are purple.
It has an old feeling.
Go home.
I heard too.
He jumped out of the car and was about to go home.
He went into the book and stopped it.
He said, I'm going home.
He wouldn't have done that.
You said you were going to go home.
Did I say I was going home?
You said you were going to go home in an hour.
I didn't say that.
If I said that, I wouldn't be in the commercial.
I'll admit one thing.
When I did the commercial for Honda's Dio.
That was the only time I complained.
There was a Honda's Dio.
It was a motorcycle.
He said,
Can you speak a little louder?
Honda's Dio!
He said,
Can you speak a little louder?
Honda's Dio!
He said,
Can you speak a little louder?
Which one is it?
He said,
Everyone was surprised.
The person who brought the tea was surprised.
He said,
The tea was good.
I said,
He said he was sorry at the time.
Can you speak a little louder?
He said,
He wouldn't come.
I said,
He came for his voice.
He said that again.
What did your mother say?
It's my birthday.
It's your birthday.
Oh, it's the 53rd.
What are you doing?
Today, you...
Ucchan said he was going somewhere, so you said you were going to Omiyage High School, right?
And Ucchan came to see you today, right?
That's what you did in the rehearsal for Shikufuji TV, right?
I don't know!
Really? You forgot?
Did you bring it?
I brought it!
You came here and left it here, and you said,
Good work!
This box is for Ucchan.
No, this is...
This is my fault.
Ucchan watches this every week, so I'm sorry.
Why do I...
Why do I have to go through that place, too?
Which one?
And finally, the location of the dodgeball tournament has been decided.
That's right.
On Saturday, May 18th,
Come to the second round of Yomiuri Land at 11 a.m.
The reception will begin at 11 a.m.
And on the second round,
The match team and the Hama-chan team will be received.
You can choose which team you want to do it with.
That's how it works.
Everyone wears a burma.
Come to the second round of Yomiuri Land
on Saturday, May 18th at 11 a.m.
Yes.
We'll prepare the Hachimaki.
1000 Hachimaki, so it's 8000.
No, no, no.
And...
The assistant.
The postcard.
We're recruiting.
The address is the same for all of them.
At this place.
No, no, no.
The postcard is...
Next week's address.
See you.
Come to the 11 a.m.
Good job.
Mr. Mazo.
Mr. Mazo, let's play today.
This program was provided by the following sponsors.