Next, we have Naoki Shousaku and Kageki Tatate!
Last time it was Kouyou, right?
Are you still Ben?
Yes
This time, Kageki-chan
Shimoda Kageki
And Kamata Shigeki
I'm Kageki Shimoda
You're wearing a lot of fashion
Today, I'm going to talk about fashion
I see
Can you hit me on the forehead?
On the forehead?
On the forehead, right?
I'll grab your elbow
I'll give you 30 points
I'll go to your hip
I see
And...
Put your finger in your nose
Oh, this
What do I do with this?
Let's raise it a little
That's right
Let's make it 30-30
Let's make it double-60
What about this bang on the butt?
That's fine
I'll give you 50 points
What if I grab your tongue?
Can you do it?
What about a punch in the eye?
A punch in the eye
20 points
I'll give you 40 points
What if I break my finger?
I'll give you 50 points
What if I take off my high heels and throw them away?
That's a lot of points
I'll give you 200 points
This time, Mr. Matsumoto
Yes
We have Mr. Kageki Shimoda, the author of Naoki
As the kanji says, Kageki Fashion Talk
I'll try to get closer to Kageki's fashion
Let's have him on the stage
Mr. Kageki Shimoda, please come on the stage
Hello
This is the first time I'm wearing these
That's right
You're wearing them again today
This is the summer version
This is the summer version?
Please sit down and talk
You're wearing amazing shoes again
I don't have any shoes
Isn't this a stroller?
Do you normally do this?
Of course you can do it like this
You can do it like this, but you have to do it like this
It's a little different
I see
You change the color every day
This is a moniker
I wear it once every three weeks
I don't have time to go
This is the fourth week
What about the nose piercings?
The nose piercings
Do you have them open?
No, I don't
I don't like to make holes
I see
So I wear earrings
I think the nipple piercings are popular around here
Please show me
I was going to do it
Sometimes I don't wear contact lenses
I don't have long or gold eyeglasses
If I wear long eyeglasses, I don't wear contact lenses
Is that so?
I want to do what I like
What is this material?
This is like leather
This is what you have at home, right?
No, I don't like it
I'm sorry
It's getting bigger
Is that so?
Can you turn it around?
Turn it around
Please turn it around
Turn it this way
You did a good job
But you can't tell the number of piercings, right?
I can't imitate the piercings that I have
How many kinds of shoes do you have?
I think I have 70 or 80 pairs of shoes
Is that so?
What are you doing?
I'm going to make you naked
I'm not going to do that
If you're going to do that, don't do it
Are you healthy?
I think I'm healthy and strong
I can tell by looking down
Do you always tease me?
Only today
What are you talking about?
I thought about it
You two didn't tease each other
Is that so?
I'm interested in you
I like you
Let's start
I'll go first
Last time I lost
805 points
Even if you're slow, you can still get 805 points
I think it was more expensive to throw the shoes
I think so too
I'm going to start
This is actually 1208 points
I only have 3 pairs
1208?
1208 points
In the second round, Mazumoto won
Thank you
I'm going to try to catch up
Please show us
I put it in the contact
Really?
Thank you
Who will be the guest of the third round?
Today was a good day
It was hot
It's a good day
I'm not a summer person
I'm not either
I'm a person who eats yakiniku from the morning
If you think so
It's okay
I warm the hot plate
I put raw meat on it
I eat it
I eat it when I wake up
I don't smoke when I wake up
Why?
When you wake up, your nose will swell
What do you mean?
It swells
You're doing it
Rolling strategy
Don't do it
The fish is rolling
It's not a strategy
I've been doing it for a long time
After taking a bath
My head and body are clean
This is the only place that remains
You do it when you take a bath
There is dirt that cannot be removed
If you do it, it will be black
It swells and becomes beautiful
I feel bad when I wake up
I feel refreshed
I'm not a person who does it
I do it like a demon
It's a great strategy
I watch TV at home
I don't do it at home
I don't do it at all
When I forget it, it comes out
That's a bad memory
What is it?
I don't know what it is
It swells
There is such a thing
I don't know anything
Suddenly it became hot
Does it continue?
I often say that it is abnormal
When I hear that, I get angry
It's abnormal
It's only been a few decades since I observed it
This is normal
I don't know if it was different until now
There are various things now
Earthquake
I wonder if there is something in the world
The weather is summer now
It's raining
It's all frozen
Suddenly
I don't know
There was nothing until now
I was living normally
It's abnormal until now
It's true now
What are you talking about?
I was living normally until now
You are like Ken Shimura
I don't know
The weather until last year was abnormal
You don't know if it's true now
Are you listening to me?
I'm listening
The weather until last year was abnormal
The weather now is normal
There is no one
The Shinkansen was annoying the other day
That's right
What?
I can say that I was riding
Shinkansen is really annoying
I have to think about this
The rice in the Shinkansen
Why is it so expensive?
I don't know the price
That's unforgivable
You can buy it at the station
I have to think about it
You can buy it
I can't eat it outside
It's expensive
I have to think about it
I was hungry
I saw the price
Really?
It's expensive
Why?
Are you showing me a trumpet?
It's a black man's father
That's enough
Do you want it?
It's true
What are you doing?
It's too expensive
It's expensive
Explain it to me
It's business
I want to make money
It's business to show movies
It's not business to sell
If you want to drink, you can bring it
If you want to go on a date, you can bring it
It's a long-distance trip
If you want to drink, you can bring it
Young people don't want to go on a date
You are still drinking
I want to drink
I don't want to drink
If I were a politician, I would drink
You are frozen
You have juice inside
No
You are frozen
I don't want to drink
I can't hear you
You are frozen
I went to see a movie
It's expensive, but you are frozen
You are frozen
You don't want to drink
I don't want to say it
It's a courage to say that expensive things are expensive
Everyone can say that
It's embarrassing to say that expensive things are expensive
Everyone can't say that
Who said that?
How do you count the katsura?
It's not that difficult
It's katsura
It's a thing, so it's easy
The salaryman of the katsura company
He is selling a lot this month
3 miles per person
What do you mean by miles?
It's not a promotion
I don't know if he is saying it
He is saying it
What do you think?
Is it an umbrella?
It's an umbrella
It's just one
You are saying it in a strange way
It's a typhoon
How do you say it?
It's a big storm
Don't say it
It's a hectopascal
Really?
I'm sorry
Don't say it in a strange way
I know how you feel
You are saying it in a strange way
Like this?
It's a 100 hectopascal
It's a 200
What if you raise it to 100?
It's not scary
It's scarier
It's a big storm
I know that
What if you raise it to 100?
What do you want me to do?
It's difficult
Let's check it
What is it?
It's in a cardboard
I don't know
I don't like it
I put it in a paper bag
I want to see the toilet
When you buy a washing machine, it comes with this
If it says don't use a thinner, the fridge will...
The fridge will cry
The thinner will be removed
There must be a box like that
It's hard
It's like a dryer
There must be a box like that
You have to put it away
I've been wondering
I don't like it
Why do you leave the top part when you sell melon?
It must have a meaning
Why do you make it a T?
I don't know
That's why you cut it like this
If you cut it like this, it will be a T
It will be, but you should leave the top part
Why do you cut it like this?
Cut the top part like this
Cut it like this
No, the melon is like this
If you cut it like a T, you have to cut it like this
But you should cut it like this
Then it will be like this
It doesn't matter
It's easy to cut
No, you can't take it out
You can put it in the box like this
Then it will be like a vinyl house
If you cut it like this, you can cut it like this
It's the same as cutting like this
That's not true
You just have to do it like this
Why?
That's right
You have to do it like this
You can't do it like this
You have to do it slowly
You have to put it in the box quickly
That's why you have to cut it like this
That's not true
What?
That's...
What are you talking about?
Why do you have to do it like that?
That's why you have to do it quickly
You have to do it quickly
Why do you have to do it quickly to put it in the box?
There are so many melons
When I'm done with this, I'll go to the other side
I'll put it in the truck like this
But there are also melons over there
The melons are waiting in the truck
That's not true
What is it?
Why did you leave it like that?
It's easier to hold if it's like this