Nankan no Gaki no Tsukai Arahen de
Daikai Gaki no Tsukai Arahen de
Chikitsuki Flash Oogiri Daisakusei
It's been a long time since I came out of the opening.
This is in front of the Fuji TV entrance.
From here, a car will appear.
I'm going to have you do what you like.
Let's introduce the main characters of the day.
The car and the story teller.
Let's go!
Nankan no Gaki no Tsukai Arahen de
Hello!
I'm the main character of the day.
I'm drunk.
Nankan no Gaki no Tsukai Arahen de
Ready!
The tools are here.
You can use it as much as you like.
Yes!
Mr. Haritoko!
I can ride a tire!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What are you doing?
Yes!
Mr. Haritoko!
Mr. Haritoko, here you go!
Next!
Mr. Noriyoshi!
I'm scared!
Mr. Noriyoshi, are you okay?
I'm okay!
Mr. Noriyoshi, please!
Kissa-matto-pon-netto!
Mr. Noriyoshi!
You're in danger!
Next!
Screw!
Yes, please!
Screw-wide-shon-parappa!
What's this?
Um...
Mr. Asumoto!
I wrote this!
No, you wrote it!
I wrote it in the book!
No, you wrote it in the book!
Mr. Yamazaki, would you like to say something before this course is over?
I'm worried.
Where's the spare tire if you don't have a tire?
What?
Where's the spare tire?
Oh, hey!
Here it is!
Do you have a tire?
Yes!
Mr. Yamazaki, please come this far.
I have a tire!
Yes!
Noriyoshi!
Don't break it even though it's meaningless!
This is funny!
What's this?
That's a bumper, isn't it?
Yeah.
I wish I could get it, but I can't get anything.
Bum-bum!
Run away!
Bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum!
What are you doing?
I didn't think of this.
The original position is...
Don't say the original position!
It's a song at the door.
It's a song, right?
Yes, please!
Let's go over the hill.
While blowing the whistle, the mountain passes through the blue sky.
Let's sing a song with the leaves pointing at us.
The door! The door!
It's a long song!
It's getting hot!
Yeah.
What are you doing?
I picked up 452 yen.
Who is it? Who is it? Who is it?
The shadow that sinks beyond the darkness.
It's too high.
The white wings...
Gashama!
I'm scared! I'm nervous!
Thank you for your hard work, everyone.
Thank you very much!
We did our best!
Now, please get on this and go home.
Thank you very much!
Let's go!
Yes!
Get on!
Take care!
I'll call you at night!
Tomorrow?
Yes, tomorrow!
Thank you!
Take care!
See you!
Thank you!
Smile!
I'll call you at night!
Thank you!
Good evening!
It's not interesting at all.
That's right.
Well...
Yesterday was a little fun.
That's right.
No, no.
Yesterday...
Well...
Let's go hook up with a girl.
I don't know.
No matter how many times it takes, I'll do it.
It's not like I'm going to do it.
I thought it was too much in the last century, but I'm still doing it.
Well, then...
My car...
It's a medium-sized car.
Well...
I'll make it the headquarters.
And now...
Well...
Team Zero's Yamazaki.
I'll send you a lot of things.
I see, I see.
And...
Let's buy a transceiver.
Oh, for that.
I'll send you the information as soon as possible.
As soon as possible.
I'll send it to the headquarters.
And I'm going to wait here with a transceiver.
You too...
And when he finds a good woman with a transceiver,
I'll go and ask her for her phone number.
In some cases, there are times when she doesn't tell me anything.
I'll go to the headquarters and ask for her support.
That means you're going out, right?
Boom, boom.
I'll ask for your support.
And I'll catch it and get out of the car.
Here you go, Matsumoto.
Oh, no.
That's too much.
Come on.
What to do.
Well, that's...
It's too much.
It's really noisy.
Well, I did that.
It's too much.
It's too stupid.
It's not stupid.
The last transceiver.
The transceiver is expensive.
Do you want to buy it?
That's right.
Is it expensive?
If you buy it properly, it's not a pair right now.
They only sell one.
I see.
Right?
That's why one is so expensive.
That one is...
It's almost 30,000 yen.
Your salary is too high.
What are you talking about?
If I could, I'd like to split it into three.
Do you want that much?
I'd like to split it into three.
It's a half and a half.
I don't know.
I need 100,000 yen.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry I'm doing what I'm doing.
My crew is the headquarters.
What are you talking about?
No, it's not.
If you get 100,000 yen for that, you'll be scolded by your mother.
Let's stop that.
I'm already giving up.
Our staff.
It's the staff.
I was about to go home, but at that time I saw something on the window.
Instant camera.
Polaroid camera.
I bought it.
What is this?
Are you going to take a picture of the captain?
I'm waiting at the headquarters.
They take the polaroid camera and go to various places.
It's very common.
Even if you ask for a lot of phone numbers, you don't know who is who.
This is the face and this is the phone number.
That's right.
I asked for the phone number and took a picture.
I collected some of them and separated them later.
This is Maachan.
This is what you want to do.
You're having fun.
I didn't have much fun.
There are many things.
I'm doing it.
I was a little sad when I was doing it.
That's right.
I'm 29 years old.
I wanted three transceivers.
I want to play too.
Let's change the story.
The only sport I like is boxing.
I don't know. I lost.
Who? Yuji Watanabe?
I lost.
If this happens, Japanese boxing is a little painful.
If this happens, there will be Tyson.
Japan will issue bail.
I'll get it out.
I'll get Tyson out of jail and make him a Japanese nationality.
What?
Taizo Sakakibara.
Where is Sakakibara from?
There are many Japanese names.
Why did you choose Sakakibara?
It's more Japanese.
Sakakibara and Tyson.
I think the Japanese boxing world will improve considerably.
But this guy will come with me.
Don King.
Don King?
He looks like a guy at Tokyo Station.
His hair is like this.
Is that so?
Yes.
Does he look like me?
He looks like you a lot.
But he doesn't appear on TV.
Why does he have such a head?
If he didn't have such a head, he wouldn't be able to do it.
It will harden and harden.
And eventually.
It will be like this.
You should wash your head.
What are you doing?
I don't know what you're doing.
I was dancing, so I didn't know what you were doing.
I see.
I'm sorry.
This is what happens when you wash your hair.
I don't know if I should do boxing.
What is this?
It's scary.
Idiot.
If you do this, you won't get hit.
But if you do this, you'll get hit.
It's scary.
Why are you like this?
You're the one who gets hit.
There was a time when I didn't know what to do.
I was invited by you, so I joined this world.
I really wanted to do it in the world of boxing.
Really?
Really.
What do you want to be?
I want to be a police officer.
You've been watching that kind of drama, haven't you?
There's a narration at the end of the drama.
It's an announcement at the end.
That's right.
It's about the next sun.
Gori runs.
Why did Gori run?
Next time, Gori.
That's it.
Please tell me.
No matter how many times I say it, everyone says it's a lie.
There was one.
It's the ear that was suddenly sent to the Nanamagari book.
You're really doing it.
I'm not saying it's bad.
I know it's an ear, but I'm not saying it's bad.
You're really doing it.
The ear of Holmarin was sent to the Nanamagari book.
No matter who you explain it to, everyone says it's a lie.
Really?
Yeah.
I don't remember either.
It was suddenly sent to the Nanamagari book.
That's not the voice.
It's a bad ear.
Whose ear is this?
Is it a nuisance?
I'm not saying that.
You're saying a lot of things.
Listen to the title.
What is it?
It was suddenly sent to the Nanamagari book.
I don't like it.
Tell me the title.
It's a bad ear.
I heard it.
Is it a nuisance?
I'm not saying it's bad.
Next time.
It's a story I heard from my fencing friends.
Fencing.
About 10 years ago, there was a genius fencer called Inazuma from Amagasaki.
That man won the world fencing championship at the age of 19.
After that, no one saw him.
Rumor has it that he was very similar to Mr. Matsumoto.
Mr. Matsumoto, you are the Inazuma of Amagasaki.
I'm a fencer.
You're a fencer.
Why are you a fencer?
Are you the Inazuma of Amagasaki?
No, no.
At the time I read this, as you all know.
It's the first time I've heard of it.
No, no.
I've been doing it a lot.
If you're going to do it,
What is it?
What kind of shape is it?
What do you mean by shape?
There's something like this.
Something like a stance.
It doesn't matter how you do it.
I've been doing it for a long time.
You can do it.
Tell me, what do you do?
What do you do?
How do you do it at first?
It's like this at first.
Oh, it's like this.
And then?
And then from here.
That's what I'm talking about.
What do you do?
Well, basically, it's like this.
What do you do with this hand?
This is Kojiko-sama's hand.
You're wearing it.
You're wearing a net.
What is this?
It's annoying when it's dripping.
It's like this, isn't it?
No, no, no.
It's not at all.
I'm doing what I said.
Do it.
You couldn't say anything.
Can't you do that?
No, no, no.
It's like this.
That's really a fencing.
You're making fun of me, aren't you?
Because I can catch your hand.
I can see your hand.
I can see it.
Take it!
Can I take it?
You can't take it, can you?
Okay, come on.
What is this?
You're a little fast.
Really?
Anyone can do this.
Are you that fast?
Well, I can't take it.
Well, well, well.
Give it a try.
I can't talk to you.
Well, Inazuma...
There's no one left alive after Inazuma Zuki.
What?
What's that?
Inazuma Zuki.
Is it Inazuma Zuki?
Well, this is really dangerous.
Don't imitate it too much.
Don't imitate it.
People who watch TV can't do this.
Follow me.
Go!
I can't do this.
It's the season for red peppers to die.
How are the downtown staff doing?
By the way, Kin-chan.
Kin-chan is the general.
Takeshi-san is the lord.
Sanma-san is called a young man.
What do you think the two of you want to be called by the young people?
What do you want to be called?
There's not much left.
What's left?
Eikichi Yaza is called the boss.
Oh, the commercial one?
Yes, the boss.
What else is there to express?
The emperor.
That's a little tough.
Is it tough?
It's tough.
Man!
Man?
What man?
It's not a man.
What are they called?
Hamada-man.
If you say it, it would be bad.
Looks like you're being made fun of.
I'm a woman with a mask.
Masumoto mask.
Masumoto mask!
This is absurd.
No!
No.
I'm not going to do that kind of stuff anymore.
I'm going to talk about it in a more cool way.
Like, a story or something like that.
A story or something like that.
A legend or something like that would be good.
A legend about Matsumoto.
A legend! Good morning!
Matsumoto Matsudanaka or something like that.
Hello, I'm Matsumoto Matsudanaka.
Oh, yes, Matsumoto Matsudanaka!
I'm Matsumoto Matsudanaka!
My name has changed!
Good morning!
Call me!
It's called Blue Jean.
I don't know anything about that.
Matsumoto Blue Jean.
I'm not going to do that kind of stuff anymore.
I like that kind of stuff.
Pansheron? Sakuron? Paburon?
There are a lot of things that end in the name of Kusumi.
Is this some kind of code? Please tell me.
Is that so? Pansheron? Sakuron?
That's your field.
Is this a code?
Kaigen.
What else is there?
Noshin.
Noshin?
Pansheron?
What's this?
Kerolin.
Oh, Kerolin.
It just came out. Bafferin.
Bafferin.
That's right.
Is this a code?
Kusumi is basically a German word.
Is that all you've got?
It's a German word.
If you say Seirogan, it's a German word.
Well, you know...
The word for full moon is a circle.
German people pass each other, right?
Well, um...
Where are you going?
No, well, that's it.
It's called Seirogan.
That's bad.
What's a German word?
What's wrong with you?
No, no, I'm wrong.
It's a German word.
That's not a German word. It's Seirogan.
That's right.
I mean, it sounds like it.
The one with luck.
Pansheron.
Right?
Kabejin.
It sounds like it.
It's called Guru.
It's a German word.
You're making me angry.
What's wrong with you?
I'm asking you.
I don't know anything about medicine.
Even two or three children.
When I say Pansheron,
That's what I think.
That's what I'm afraid of.
If you say Pansheron all of a sudden, that's a German word.
It's a problem with your personality.
Pansheron, Kabejin.
If you say that, the children will be excited.
If you say it out loud, it's a German word.
I don't know.
What are you guys doing?
I hate this postcard.
Hello, everyone.