As usual, there was a gloomy atmosphere in the dressing room.
I'm the one who bought it.
Good morning.
Tanaka and Endo are calling you.
Right now?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Are you coming?
Yes.
Everyone...
Sorry.
Good morning.
Excuse me.
I have something to talk to you about.
Have you been working hard lately?
Yes, I've been working hard.
Have you been eating well?
Yes, I've been eating well.
You've been eating well.
You were talking on the phone yesterday.
I know you're having a hard time.
Yes.
Your father and mother are...
You fell in love, so it can't be helped.
Don't talk about love anymore.
It's different.
I was talking to Hamada yesterday.
I want to leave the name Downtown.
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
Why are you writing it?
Downtown.
That's right.
I'm writing it.
Can I give you the name Downtown?
What?
The second Downtown life-threatening ceremony.
We decided it.
Yes, I decided it.
My name is Downtown.
What do you want to do?
What kind of feeling?
Well, I'm Kokoriko now.
But how much power does Kokoriko have?
I don't know.
I'm not sure if I can entrust the name Downtown to them.
I'll see.
It's the second one.
Can we get the second Downtown?
If you do your best.
Really?
Yes.
We can do it.
Are you sure?
Yes, we can do it.
We can do it.
I can't react to it.
This is impossible.
We came all the way here because we took our pants.
Pants?
We took the pants of many people.
So you can't stop us.
We used our power to stop them.
With our pants?
Are you kidding me?
Let's show them.
This is the first time on TV.
We took our pants.
Excuse me.
You took something dirty.
This is from the old days.
This is from the 9th year of Heisei.
This is the war.
The war?
This is from my grandmother.
That's why I can't stop them.
That's what the master said.
That's how it is in this world.
There's nothing you can do about it.
This is terrible.
Take a look at this.
It's a red bread.
Red bread.
Asuka is huge.
Asuka watches it every week.
This is terrible.
Are you going to be okay?
At the last episode.
At the last episode's opening.
You went to that?
We only have this.
We went.
But this is the worst.
This is terrible.
This is like the return of Night in Night.
This is also a bad thing.
This is a rampage.
Stop it.
You're going to be in trouble.
Their war goods don't stop at this.
First, Wadaaki.
They were suppressed by the two of them.
Kin-chan.
When he went out to the enemy, he aimed.
His high heels are useless.
Ryusuke Shinsuke.
They suddenly disbanded.
They were attacked by a group of people in Kyoto.
Yasukiyo had to face a lot of difficulties.
We took it like this.
It's your turn.
Leave it to us.
We'll take it.
We'll take the second Downtown.
You only say the same thing.
I don't have any more.
We have more.
Please show us.
Let's go.
That's right.
When we were young, it was okay to take off our underwear.
But now the times are different.
It's a problem after you take it off.
After you take it off,
on your butt,
you have to blow your breath.
Your breath?
Can I do that?
That's how you finally win.
I'll do it.
Please.
The five-year-old duo, Kokoriko.
They are fighting against the popular comedy duo.
And they are fighting against the popular comedy duo.
Can they defeat the second generation of downtown?
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Yoshimoto Kogyo.
Kokoriko decided to defeat the popular comedy duo.
At first, I went to the Tokyo office.
Yes.
They said there were a lot of young people there.
I wanted to go.
Gokuraku.
Gokuraku Tonbo.
They have been a duo for 8 years.
They are active as a regular of Mecha-ike.
I'm going to do it with my life.
I'm going to get in your way.
Hey.
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
It's like you're on TV.
Are you on TV these days?
Are you on TV?
Wait a minute.
Are you a celebrity?
Take off your underwear.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
Sit down.
Take off your underwear.
I'll make you win.
Hey.
Who is the most powerful?
Huh?
That's not true.
Who is the most powerful?
It's me.
What's wrong with you?
Hey!
I think you all know this, but...
...you know that the entertainment industry...
...is being robbed of their underwear, right?
What's wrong with you?
I know that!
I'm your senior, but...
...without you guys...
...we can do better in Tokyo!
It's our duty!
So, I'm sorry, but...
...I came to take your underwear!
What did you say?
I didn't say anything.
For now...
...get ready!
Get ready!
Take off your underwear!
It's funny if you take off your underwear!
What are you talking about?
And at the end...
...it's funny if you hit your butt!
Get ready!
Let's go!
I'll go.
What about you, Gokuraku?
Yamamoto!
I'll go.
It's so simple!
One punch!
You're crazy, Tanaka.
You're like Yatsume Unagi.
This is a different class.
I'll go.
Hagi!
Don't lose, Tanaka!
I'll definitely win!
Don't get in my way!
I'll go.
From the bottom!
I'll go from here.
I'll definitely win!
From the bottom!
Hey, you!
Hey!
Hey, Ibuki!
You guys, don't underestimate us.
We're not the kind of people who climb up the stairs.
We're the ones who climb up the stairs!
You're not the kind of people I'm looking for!
Let's go.
Sorry, I was just looking around.
I was looking for the other guy that was not doing very well.
If it was someone from the other side, I would have caught him.
Yes, if it was someone from the other side,
I would have caught him.
He was really bad.
You're young.
I'm fine with the next one.
He's not the type to be jealous of.
I don't have anything to say to them.
I don't have anything bad to say to them.
Thank you very much.
Let's go.
Please watch the first episode.
Thank you very much.
Let's go.
Good morning, good morning, good morning.
Good morning.
What are you doing?
Norio Yoshio, who supported the comic boom.
A super veteran of the comedy world.
Do you know what comedy is?
This industry, this industry.
What are you talking about?
Do you know what it is?
It was really bad.
Hey, hey.
What are you talking about?
It was really bad.
Sit down.
This industry is a fight with panties.
It's a fight with panties.
It was really bad.
What are you talking about?
Your face is small.
Don't think like that.
What are you talking about?
What is this?
It's a fight with panties.
This industry is a fight with panties.
What is this?
It's a fight with panties.
It was really bad.
What are you talking about?
This industry is a fight with panties.
Sit down.
Get changed immediately.
A fight with panties.
Komoriko?
Go.
Yoshio?
Let me go!
What's going on?
What?
Go!
That's amazing!
Amazing!
Go!
Wait!
You're an a**hole!
You're just an a**hole!
That's the end!
So it's 1 win, 1 draw?
1 loss, 1 draw?
Yes, 1 loss, 1 draw.
We haven't won yet.
So you guys can't beat us.
In the next match,
we'll play 2 games in a row.
So 2 wins in a row?
Yes, 2 wins.
Next.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Look at me.
What?
Look at me?
I'm telling you!
I'm sorry.
There was no other way?
There must be something.
Well, let's see.
That's suspicious.
We'll see.
Yes.
Good luck.
Excuse me.
Good morning.
Hey!
Line up!
Good morning.
Hey!
What are you guys doing?
We're having a meeting.
It's an event!
It's an event.
What kind of event is this?
Hey!
Do you know what an event is?
What?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Do you know what an event is?
You don't, do you?
An event is a show of your underwear.
Do you know what an event is?
Hey!
It's a comedy show.
You're getting closer.
You said it was a comedy show.
Get changed.
You're getting closer.
I think I'm your junior.
What?
What do you mean?
That's me.
I'm the center of attention.
What do you guys think?
What?
What are you guys?
What are your glasses?
You idiot!
Are you drunk?
I'm the center of attention.
Why are you shouting?
You guys.
You guys are going to lose.
You're talking like a pig.
Shut up!
I'm not going to lose.
Get changed.
What are you doing?
Stop.
Brother.
You have to stop.
I'll do it.
Punch and Punch!
Come here!
Yes!
You!
I wonder if it's a good idea to punch Mano.
But I don't want to be a fool.
I don't think it's a co-op prize.
If you punch him now, you'll get another one.
It's impossible to hold it for a long time.
I'll hold it for a long time.
That was a waste of time.
Punch and Punch!
Yes!
One more time!
Everyone, get ready!
Go!
It's going to be fine.
Come toweight
Punch and Punch!
Yes!
It's okay if it suddenly stops.
Stop it! Stop it!
Start!
Miyasako!
Nice! Nice!
He's sleeping.
Miyasako!
Let's go!
End!
Kimura!
One point difference!
Ready! Start!
Go! Go!
End!
He's fast!
3...2...
Let him be!
We are super businesses...
Fight!
Hey, hey, hey, don't cut it!
That's enough!
You excited, seguir?
S... S... S...
Cook...
I don't want to, cook me some more!
I'm not asking you to cook!
I'm sorry!
What are you doing?
Okay! Okay!
I'm sorry!
End!
What's with this picture?
It's 1 to 1.
1 to 1.
But we did the ending until the end.
That's right. I think we won somehow.
But Tanaka lost.
So it's a tie.
It's a draw.
So it's 1 win, 2 losses, 1 draw.
At this point, we don't have to do the downtown show anymore.
What?
We still have time, so we'll do our best.
Wait a minute!
There's still a lot of young people left.
It's okay to do that.
It's a long story.
Hey!
You guys are telling me this early.
What should we do?
Nothing.
You're in a lot of trouble.
What are you going to do?
What should we do?
Just do it yourself.
But we still have to do the downtown show.
That's right. We've been fighting for a long time.
Please do it one more time.
Please.
We'll do it for real.
We'll do it properly.
Please.
What do you think?
I'm serious.
Let's do it separately.
Is that okay?
It's light.
Thank you very much.