Tonight's Gaki no Tsukai is decided by the two downtown guests who are currently active in the entertainment world while taking a questionnaire to the audience.
Otokomae Best 10 and Busaiku Best 10
The first time Gaki no Tsukai, Chikitiki
Tonight's Gaki no Tsukai is decided by the two downtown guests who are currently active in the entertainment world while taking a questionnaire to the audience.
The first time Gaki no Tsukai is decided by the two downtown guests who are currently active in the entertainment world while taking a questionnaire to the audience.
Otokomae Best 10 and Busaiku Best 10
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
First of all, Busaiku Best 10
From the photos that Machan and Hama-chan entered,
Chihara brothers, Riton Mizuno, 130R Hong Kong
Shimada Shinsuke in his 40s
Pick up comedians who you think are Busaiku
From there, it was decided to decide the ranking of the best 10.
What do you think of this?
This is difficult.
But this is a little similar to the red Hidekazu.
That's really a little.
Well, let's put it in.
Come on.
This is the second place.
And then.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'll think a little more!
Are you desperate?
Well, let's put it in.
So that's it.
Why is it you?
What are you doing?
I can't play.
I beg you.
It comes back.
Well then, what should we do?
What do you want to write?
The order. Let's decide the order.
Let's decide the order.
Okay.
Hey, wait wait wait wait wait wait!
Let's decide together!
Why are you doing this to me?
Hey!
I'm sleepy.
I'm the best.
Ah, I see.
For me, no matter what I say,
Hong Kong is not loose.
The boy's face is rotten.
Let's compete with this and this.
Let's do that.
I think it's this.
Okay, let's listen.
First, which one?
This one?
Yes.
If you think this is the first place, please press the switch.
Huh?
If you think Hong Kong is the first place, please press the switch.
Yes!
60?
That's because you guys have been telling Hong Kong that it's the last place.
Look at the real thing.
How about this one?
Well...
Let's listen to this one.
This one is called the ugly one.
I don't know if it's Hong Kong or Hong Kong.
Second place.
I think it's Mizuno.
It's Mizuno.
What does that mean?
Does that mean Mizuno is higher?
Huh?
Let's listen to this one.
Look at this one. It looks exactly like you.
I think it's Mizuno.
Which one should I choose?
This is amazing.
You guys are so weak.
Next, Shinsuke, the only one in his 40s, asked for a survey.
There are surprisingly few people who think it's ugly.
With 37 votes, he didn't make it to the top ranking.
Kimura Yuichi...
Let's put him in the 10th place.
What?
Please talk to me.
And then...
Like this?
That's enough.
I'll put you in the 10th place.
Thank you.
I don't know what you're thanking me for.
The 10th place said it's ugly.
What do you think?
I'm not good at saying it's ugly.
Let's listen to Hamada.
Switch on!
The one with the shoe laces wins, right?
Bring me a first aid kit!
A first aid kit!
Let's decide on this one.
There will be some changes later.
Let's decide on the best one.
The best 10 is the same as the last time.
First, from the photos of Matsu-chan and Hama-chan,
Higashino Koji, Yamasaki, Ronbu, Gokuraku Kato,
Nai Nai Yabe, Takusanju R Itao,
Ameagari Kesshidai Miyasako, Kokoriko's Endo, and Tanaka.
They all picked the ones they thought were the best.
They will decide on the best 10.
Who will be the best one among the actors?
Ah! I forgot the best one!
That's right!
This is it!
This is the best!
Let's decide later.
There's only one left?
Really?
Matsu-chan!
This is the last one.
There's no photo.
It's a foreign one.
I'll put it in.
Thank you very much.
Let's compete with this one.
First, this one.
Amazing.
I have to listen to this.
How do I listen to this?
The shirt looks good on you.
The handwriting is not wrong.
What are you talking about?
Are you going to compete with this one?
Are you going to go with this one?
It's obvious that you're going to compete with this one.
This one!
Amazing.
It's a half-hearted number.
Let's applaud.
I'll move this one.
Let's go.
It's a half-hearted number.
Where is this one?
It's not good, right?
That's right.
You just have to move this one.
Why do I get cold?
If I had a bag like this, it would be the worst.
If you don't have it, don't clap until the end.
That's it.
It's a little cold.
Matsumoto-san, your butt...
I don't care.
Don't say that.
I can't go up anyway.
I don't care.
I got it.
It's a half-hearted number.
You have to decide.
I'm going to be busy.
It's like this.
I don't know what to do.
How is it?
Hama-chan, go up.
I can hear Seron's voice.
Gokuraku and Downtown are the same.
Otokomae has to close it properly.
The partner has to close it properly.
This is the Otokomae's best 10.
Donbu was chosen as a combination.
Matsumoto was a little stubborn, but he ranked in.
The best 10 is Shinsuke Shimada, a veteran of Rakuten Hoshino.
Hamada ended up in the top 10.
Don't you feel uncomfortable that I'm here?
You guys...
You guys don't know that.
Really.
You have a terrible face.
I don't know if I should say this.
Here.
It's normal.
Like this.
The beard is like this.
It's amazing.
If you don't shave three times a day, your beard will be black.
It's like a guy from the Shounen Bakurozoku.
The skin is round.
I can't shave this much.