In the first episode of Yaki no Tsukai, Chikichiki Yama-chan presents
Summer Vacation! Nittere Jamboree Exhibition!
I heard that you stepped on your partner's foot for the first time in a few years
Really?
He stepped on it all of a sudden
And it was a fake, so please don't do it
I don't want to do it anymore
What are you doing today, Yama-chan?
Oh!
Nittere Jamboree is doing a lot of things here
We're not doing it
We're doing it
What are you doing?
We're doing it like we're doing it in Odaiba
It's completely different from that
This T-shirt too
It's amazing
I'll give it to everyone later
Please give it to everyone
There are a lot of event booths here, so let's go
Are you here to see this?
We were doing a stage
It's Enta no Kami-sama
That's why it's not for us
I see
But we're doing Enta no Kami-sama too
There's a return
The return
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors
Nippon TV is holding an event this summer
Nittere Jamboree
There are a lot of stage events
Including the booths of the popular program
Today, along with the booths for the kids
The DVD advertising director, Yama-chan
Will show you around Nittere Jamboree
What is this?
Do you want to try?
You can play with it
It's definitely fun
Let's go
I wonder if you can get it
You can get it
Do it
It's Nittere Jamboree
I'm sorry, Endo
Everyone is watching
You did something bad to Endo
Endo, you can't do that
Can you listen to me?
It's my first time
I'll show you how to do it
It was a great fight
After this, they will go around the venue
And enjoy the Jamboree
This is really Yamazaki
It's true
Yamazaki is the main
And the booth for the kids
Which is on the second floor of Nippon TV
The roof character festival
Here
Welcome
Please wear the helmet
It looks fun
Are you okay?
I'm excited
It's not
It's Heipo
You're Ko-chan
Ko-chan
Welcome to Heipo
It's Heipo zone
Next
Please stand
Here
Tonight is Yamada
It's so fun
Is this the end?
It's the end
Look
It's so nostalgic
It's the second time
Yes
This is
It's the 100th time
It's the name
It's so nostalgic
What's this?
It's Yamada
Tanaka
You can't touch it
You should put your hand in it
This is
It's dangerous
I don't like it
What's wrong?
What's this?
Please try
It's dangerous
It's not hygienic
There's something
What's this?
Everyone
Look at this
It's like
It's like playing
There's something
Can you see this?
What's this?
Look at this
You were standing on the stage
You mean on the roof?
We were looking at you
We were watching you
I was doing it from the 2nd floor
Did you start to wear the costumes?
The famous character that appears in Gaki no Tsukai appears in a powerful 3D video!
Wow, his butt, his butt!
His head, his head, his head!
Wow, amazing!
Ah, this guy.
He came out.
He has a lot of spirit.
Please look forward to the next episode at the venue!
Tanaka's hand is the most amazing.
It was light, right?
His glasses are fine.
This is amazing.
What is this? There are only Heipo.
Heipo is falling down.
This is Toshin-dai.
Ah, really?
Toshin-dai.
I can meet Toshin-dai Po-chan.
I've only seen him on TV, so this is the first time I've seen him.
Ah, Heipo is like this.
This is the Kusami Championship.
Koyori is also in Japan.
Ah, really?
Why don't you try Yamagaki?
Ah, I...
I...
Should I do it?
I want to take a picture of this.
It's a bit different.
Hanakoyori.
Ah, amazing.
This is the best.
This is the one.
This is the Kusami.
The Kusami.
This guy will never be able to do the Kusami.
He can't.
It's impossible.
It's the Po-chan Championship.
That's not true.
You'll be able to do it if you try it yourself.
I'll try it.
I can't do it if I try it myself.
Really?
You too?
This is the type that can do the Kusami.
Ah, the Kusami.
It's like Kato-chan.
The type that can do the Kusami.
The type that can't do it.
The last one is the sign on the panel as proof for today.
This is 2800 yen.
No, no, no.
The money is free.
It's free.
Really?
What is this?
At the exit of the booth, we received the DVD that will be released this month.
In addition, the original goods used by the kids are also on sale.
What is this?
It's an old lady's memo.
An old lady's memo.
The members will also challenge the lottery that will be given to those who have reserved the DVD.
Ah, Promide.
Promide.
What, what, what?
Show me, show me.
What is it?
It looks interesting.
This is...
There is no missing piece.
That's right.
I don't know what it is.
It's missing.
I also want to go.
How many are there?
Three, three.
There are three capes.
This is missing.
I want it.
Ah, it's Promide.
It's out.
Who's next? Who's next?
Who's next?
It's a hit.
Seriously, damn it.
It's a live photo.
I like Nakamura.
Who?
Who is it?
It's missing.
Is it this kind of box?
That's right.
It's all white.
I see.
What happened today?
It's like Takaki Boo.
Isn't it good?
Also, if there's an ukulele...
Don't make fun of Takaki Boo.
I'm not making fun of him.
Also, it's just an ukulele.
I hope it's popular.
You know,
I didn't want to talk about this,
but I heard a good story.
It's about Tanaka.
I see.
I happened to hear it from the staff.
A while ago,
on a show called Kokoriko,
he went to a location.
One of the staff went to the location.
The location lasted from morning to night.
After that,
he said,
Good job.
At that time,
I looked at Tanaka,
and he said,
His knees are dirty.
There's dirt on them.
There's mud on them.
I wondered why.
When I thought about it,
the location on that day was
a location where I heard a lot of stories
from old people.
I see.
When I talked to old people,
Tanaka was kind,
so he put his knees on his knees
and listened to old people.
There was mud on his knees.
Of course,
Tanaka was very happy.
He said,
Tanaka is a good boy.
I see.
I heard that story.
He said,
Can you tell me about this?
Are you an idiot?
Tell me about Tanaka.
I didn't tell him about this story.
I see.
Cut here.
He came out and said,
We came out.
I see.
He said,
Can you tell me that you heard a story?
Then,
He said,
What is it?
I said,
He said,
What is it?
I said,
I don't know.
What is the story of this person?
He said,
It's my first experience.
I said,
What is it?
I don't know.
He said,
What is the story of this person?
I said,
I don't know.
I don't have any idea.
I said,
Don't do it.
Let's go to Hakaki.
Why am I such a strong person?
I think it's good.
No, no, I've already heard all of this. It's not good to lie.
But I think there should be a lot of good stories about me.
No, I don't think so.
No one says that when I'm silent.
A little while ago, maybe half a year or a year ago,
when I was driving in the middle of the night,
there was a person who got drunk and fell down.
I asked him, are you okay?
He said, if there's anything, I'll take you to the hospital.
I did it. I really did it.
But to be honest, I was thinking,
send me to Deluxe in the middle of the night.
I was thinking, send me, you guys.
There was another person who was drunk.
I said, it's okay, it's okay.
He said, are you really okay?
I'll go, but it's like Deluxe.
Thank you.
When I got home, I thought, this is crazy.
He didn't come at all.
Why is that?
I can't see the bottom of my heart.
If you go to the hospital and go to the end,
it's not just the bottom of your heart, it changes into kindness.
That's true.
I just said something good, didn't I?
The audience is screaming on the roof.
It doesn't matter.
I do this kind of thing quite often.
I pat children's heads.
If there's a child who's been watching at the game center for a long time,
I give them 100 yen.
I do that kind of thing.
It's definitely a lie.
Why do you give 100 yen to a child who's been watching at the game center?
It's really weird.
I don't do that kind of thing.
What exactly is a melancholic night?
Tell me.
I'm already 40 years old.
I've only thought of melancholic nights about 8 times.
Actually, I don't know what melancholic night means.
That's right.
If you haven't received proper education, you wouldn't know.
I think everyone knows.
That's why you've never had a melancholic night.
Are you sad?
I don't think so.
I don't care about that.
It's my way of life.
It's embarrassing to say that you've never had a melancholic night.
I see.
I think it's embarrassing.
I'm from Osaka.
Tell me what a melancholic night means.
You're really a fool.
Don't think that you can teach me everything in words.
There are things that are sensual.
I'm going to steal that from you.
Come on, steal it.
Then I'll give it to you as a gift.
It's a three-digit number. Open it.
I didn't say anything.
It's 229.
Open it.
I got it.
At times like this...
Right, right, left.
Shut up.
Tell me what a melancholic night means.
That's right.
There are melancholic nights when you just watch TV at home.
And, for example, when you party and make a lot of noise.
There are also nights that aren't melancholic.
Isn't there something?
Isn't there something sensual?
Then I'll tell you.
When you have three items,
it's a melancholic night.
That's a sudden increase.
It's a sudden increase.
Then tell me what those three items are.
Even if you don't tell me, I want you to know.
I don't know, so tell me.
Tell me what those three items are.
First, a deep kiss.
What is that?
Have you ever had a deep kiss?
I have had a deep kiss.
You idiot.
First, a deep kiss.
I've heard of a deep kiss.
Next, a fist bump.
I've heard of it.
Hey, after a deep kiss, a fist bump.
It's funny.
Let's laugh a little more.
A fist bump.
Here, a lot of human beings are dropped.
That's not going to happen.
Here, the gas is scraped off.
That's not going to be melancholic.
Why did you say a fist bump?
After a deep kiss.
But I think it's more like a deep kiss than you think.
It's between craftsmen.
That's a bit too much.
That's because you have a pickaxe like this.
And you have a sword like this.
That's a bit too much.
This is more melancholic than a fist bump.
A little more.
Just a little more.
I didn't even get close.
Really?
In that sense.
You have to hold a fist bump.
That's right.
I think a fist bump is really amazing.
Everyone says it's a fist bump.
Because the dropped fist bump is in the right hand or the left hand.
That's right.
I want you to bite that part.
I want you to grab that part.
Well...
I think I went too far.
Can't you tell me one last thing?
Stop it.
If you say that, everyone will spend the night melancholic from tomorrow.
I will.
I can't forgive you for that.
Do you have it at home?
I think there are people who have it at home.
Is that so?
But that's impossible.
You can't be melancholic.
You still don't understand.
You don't understand everything.
Why are you giving up?
No!
If you give up...
You can't!
Never!
Why are you so serious?
It's just one more thing.
If you can do that, the melancholic night will be complete.
I'll do it.
Can I say it?
I'm sorry.
It's a military base.
That's where everyone gets caught.
I went to the military base with Deep Kiss.
I'm looking for a different place.
That's right.
It was under my feet.
That's why I went to the military base with Deep Kiss.
It's not a big deal.
I don't want to say this, but it's a super melancholic night.
Can I ask you one thing?
Are both the military base and the military base?
Of course.
The fingers of the military base are like this.
Deep Kiss.
Which one is the upper one?
If you want to be a super, you have to give me a plus.
Yes.
Then...
What do you mean?
I think some people want to have a melancholic night.
If there's an upper one...
Of course there is.
Then I'll tell you one more thing.
This is not a big deal.
Is that so?
Yes.
It's a mechanical pencil.
While doing this, with Deep Kiss, the military base, and the military base...
Click, click, click, click, click.
This is a super melancholic night.
Which one is it?
I don't know. I can't hear you. What?
It's 0.9.
Which one is it?
What? I can't hear you.
Both of them.
Yes, both of them.
You usually use 0.5, right?
It's a little thicker than usual.
Both of them.
What?
I can't hear you.
Both of them.
This is like that.
If you put 0.9 in a 0.5 mechanical pencil, it won't open.
There will definitely be no melancholy.
You should have listened to the details.
Of course.
Melancholy won't come out even if you want it to.
Melancholy will be stuck in there.
That's why I put melancholy in a 0.5 pen.
You put melancholy in a 0.5 pen?
What do you mean?
You put 0.9 melancholy in a 0.5 pen?
That's strange. I don't get it.
You put melancholy in a 0.5 pen?
I don't get it. What's a melancholy pen?
I've never heard of it.
There's a melancholy pen.
0.9, right?
You should have said that.
You should have bought a normal 0.9 pen.
It won't open.
No matter how many times you pull the string, it won't open.
That's strange.
You put melancholy in a 0.5 pen?
You should have said that.
I don't get it.
But...
If you don't want to talk, you can use a ballpoint pen.
You keep saying 0.9 all the time.
If I say it in detail, it can't be helped.
You put melancholy in a 0.5 pen?
I think it's sold in a melancholy shop.
You should have said that.
That's strange.
There are two in Tokyo.
You should have said that.
Kamen Rider.
That's strange.
You should have said that.
There are two in Kamen Rider.
That's strange.