I can't do it because I'm a kid!
Search for the correct answer in the shopping district!
This is a team from Shibuya.
I'm scared.
I can't do it, I can't do it.
I'm going to walk over there.
There are shops on both sides of the shopping district.
Each person will make a mistake one by one.
One person will search for it.
First of all, there should be no mistakes.
I'm going to walk all the way over there.
I'm scared.
I'm going to ask you to guess how different it is from before.
There are two choices.
I want you to guess correctly.
What?
What are you doing?
I'm asking you how it's different from before.
What is this?
There's one more.
There's one more?
What is this?
This is a new work from this fall.
You're lying!
What is this?
I'm walking with a pig!
This is different!
That's right!
It's getting cooler, isn't it?
It's cold, isn't it?
Why are you wearing red?
That's correct!
I'll give you a hint.
The person...
It's normal.
How is it?
Let's go with the correct answer.
Please come out.
This lady is the scarecrow.
The first one I saw was the lady over there.
Don't you get it?
This time, I set it up.
I'll go right away.
My Hamachan?
This is my Hamachan?
What is this?
You have to look carefully.
It's hard!
This person is Yuji Hirano.
As an extra, I have one more thing.
He's a real man.
He's the best in his field.
What's wrong?
What?
What kind of person is this?
It's normal, isn't it?
It's not normal.
It's hard!
It's amazing.
It's hard to say something like this.
Welcome, welcome.
Where are you from?
I'm from Eihime.
It's interesting.
Did you fall down?
I fell down. I fell down somewhere.
This old lady.
It's been a long time.
The set has changed.
It's new.
The design is still the same.
That's right.
It's Hibino's design.
It's still the same.
It's amazing that the set has poop.
What should we talk about?
There were a lot of things this time.
The most memorable thing was...
I was embarrassed.
What?
There's a time when I was tired and sleeping on the Shinkansen.
I was really tired.
I was dreaming while sleeping.
I was dreaming.
I was dreaming when I was in elementary school.
You had a great dream.
I was dreaming while sleeping.
I see.
My brother was sleeping next to me.
I felt like I was going to faint.
Who?
Me.
I felt like I was going to faint.
I fainted in front of my brother.
In front of your brother.
When I woke up, it was really peaceful.
You were on the Shinkansen at that time.
I was the only one who felt peaceful.
When I passed through the room, I woke up.
I was surprised.
I thought it was the Shinkansen.
I looked to the side and I was sitting next to it.
I was surprised.
I thought I was going to faint.
The person next to me laughed at me.
I thought it was uncool.
Was the sound loud?
It was loud.
I woke up by myself.
You woke up by your own sound?
I woke up by my own sound.
It was loud.
You woke up by your own sound?
I woke up by my own sound.
I woke up by my own sound when I was dreaming.
I woke up by my own sound when I was sleeping.
Why?
I don't know.
Are you sick?
I woke up by my own sound.
That's right.
Is that right?
I woke up by my own sound.
I think it's embarrassing to wake up by your own sound.
Women should wake up by their own sound.
Why?
Women have a lot of constipation.
They can't poop.
So they wake up by their own sound.
Is that so?
They have been doing this for a long time.
They are very depressed.
I do it three or four times a day.
You do it more.
I really do it.
I told you before.
How many times do you do it?
About two hamsters.
I can't say it's easy to understand.
You are such an idiot.
I don't know how many times you do it.
Why can't you do it at once?
That's true.
I can poop whenever I want.
Bring me a newspaper.
Here it is.
I can do it.
That's true.
I will stab you.
I can do it.
I can control the number of times and the amount.
You can control it.
I can poop as much as that.
That's too much.
I can poop in the same shape and color as that.
I can poop as much as that.
You can do it by turning your waist.
I can do it.
I wonder if you can do it.
It's difficult to do it at the end.
I can do it.
You can't do it.
Have you ever done it?
Yes, I have.
At home?
Yes.
You poop at home.
You poop like this?
I can do it.
I can poop in a round place like a cake.
I can't write congratulations.
Who are you congratulating?
You just poop at my house.
I can do it.
Don't you have any special skills?
People can't do this.
I don't have any special skills.
Can you do this?
I can do it.
You are a girl.
I'm a man.
You can't do it.
You can't do it if you turn your waist more.
I can do it.
What do you do when you poop?
You have to be careful not to poop.
That's right.
But you can't do it here.
In the last special edition of Shobai Shobai,
Yoshiko Nakada was next to me.
You pooped at first, didn't you?
I thought it was dangerous, so I pooped.
But your face was like this.
I'm sorry.
I was laughing at the beginning.
But when I came to the back, Yoshiko Nakada was next to me again.
I pooped at that time.
I thought it was rude, so I pooped.
So I pooped here.
I pooped again, and I pooped again.
Please forgive me.
You haven't pooped a lot, have you?
That's right.
I've never been pooped in front of me.
Everyone is a little too cool.
I think you should be a little more calm.
I'm showing my shame.
Really?
I'm fine.
What kind of shame did you show?
When I went to the hospital,
the doctor gave me a big finger on my butt.
When I said my intestines were strange,
he gave me a big finger and raised my leg.
He gave me a big finger.
You were so happy.
You're a fool.
I can't go to the hospital at all.
Everyone was happy when I said,
Give me a big finger.
I will never do that again.
I was so embarrassed.
I thought it was a rude doctor.
It's my job.
When I pooped, my face turned red.
Really?
Did you poop face-to-face?
So I went to bed.
My pants were shifted.
It was like this.
The pen name is a long-necked person.
I love it.
It's amazing.
Good evening.
I have a question.
What is Chanchara Okashi's Chanchara?
You're good at that.
Don't you know that?
I don't know that.
It's famous.
Chanchara Okashi.
I don't know.
What is Chanchara?
This is a long time ago.
It's a comic book.
It's called Chanchara.
By the way, Chanchara.
This comic book is so funny.
When was that?
When I was still in the gym.
When I was still in the gym,
there was a comic book called Chanchara.
It's so funny now.
I don't know about that.
Chanchara is really funny.
Chanchara Okashi is funny.
You're as funny as Chanchara.
I'm convinced.
Is that so?
If there's anything I don't know,
I'll tell you.
What are you doing now?
I'm drawing a lot now.
Drawing a lot?
You're still alive?
I'm still alive.
Really?
How old are you?
I'm about 98 years old now.
You're both alive?
Yes, I'm both alive.
But I'm doing well now.
You're doing well at 98?
I'm doing well.
Chanchara is quite expensive.
I'll invite you as a guest.
Really?
It's quite expensive.
What kind of comic book did you do at that time?
Chanchara.
Hello, Chanchara.
What's wrong, Chara?
It's hot, isn't it?
Yes.
What?
I don't know.
It's hot.
Yes.
I knew it.
It's hot, isn't it?
What are you saying?
I see.
When I was driving with my girlfriend,
we were at the pedestrian bridge.
When I was reading the quote,
the courage that doesn't give you the speed to be safe,
I bumped into the car in front of me and got into an accident.
Why is that quote written so that the driver can read it?
If you have anything to think about in the middle of the night,
please let me know.
That's what I think.
There's a long sign, isn't it?
I want you to read it, so I put it up.
But if you read it, it's dangerous, isn't it?
But what is that?
It's not that close, is it?
Well, yes.
It's self-defeating.
There was a lot of traffic on the road.
It was a little jammed, so I looked away.
When I saw it, I bumped into it.
Is there such a thing usually?
Yes, there are a lot of contradictions.
Even on a bicycle.
There's a thing that glows on the saddle of a bicycle.
Is that so?
In a dark place because it's dangerous.
At night?
Yes, at night.
When I ran, it was shining.
There was a car.
What's that?
It's shining.
Let's go.
Don't go.
There may be times when I pull it out.
There may be such a thing.
There are contradictions, aren't there?
Such a thing.
There is no such thing.
No, the world is full of contradictions.
What is full of contradictions?
There are a lot.
Tell me, if there are a lot.
There are two hundred and five.
Then, today is the fifth of that number.
There are five.
For example, this button of yours.
This is strange.
I don't need it.
First one.
Second one.
This microphone.
It's strange.
Second one.
Third one.
This skin.
It's all about me, isn't it?
Such a thing.
There are contradictions.
That's why I'm telling you to listen to that.
I'm angry.
I'm angry about that.
What?
The road sign is also the same.
The sign.
What?
For example?
That.
It's a pun.
I see.
Like, stop.
That kind of thing.
Stop?
Who are you talking to?
What does it say?
Please stop.
If it's not that, what are you talking to people?
It doesn't matter.
It's strange.
Stop and get angry.
You're angry.
Don't you get angry?
If you're told to stop.
It doesn't matter.
I'm the most angry.
I'm going to say it on TV.
I will never stop in front of the crossing.
It's okay to broadcast this.
I will never do this.
What did you say?
Who are you talking to?
I will never do this.
It doesn't make sense.
Why?
I will never stop in front of the crossing.
It's a confirmation.
Confirm what?
That the train is not coming.
It's not coming.
It's not closed.
That's right.
But maybe.
What?
Maybe.
Yes.
I don't know if it's a mistake.
I don't know if it's coming from the other side.
You can tell by the sound.
I'm not stupid.
I can tell if the train is coming.
No.
That's why.
I know now.
I know that you have to stop early.
It's not good if you stop.
If you do, you have to go.
If you do, you can't stop.
That's why I don't recognize the train.
The car is lined up at the crossing.
At the crossing.
When the train finally came.
Only about 5 people are on it.
What for?
I don't think they wait that long.
That's strange.
That's why I won't stop if you push me. I'll just keep going.
Is that so?
Yes, yes.
Even if I get hit by a train, I won't die, right?
Eh?
No, even if I get hit by a train, I won't die.
For real.
I'll write a letter and say, for real.
No, for real.
No, you see...
You've never been hit, right?
I'm not a guy.
I'm not a guy, I'm a guy.
That's enough.
I love you, Hama-chan.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to go get some sweets for my head.
The other day, when I was reading Men's Nonno,
Hama-chan was chosen as the 2nd best-looking man in the world.
Ah, really?
By the way, the 1st place was Yoshida Eizaku, and the 3rd place was Tawara Toshihiko.
What do you think about this result?
Hama-chan, you're certainly swinging your hips on TV, so please answer.
Please?
That's completely wrong.
Is that so?
Yes.
That's completely wrong.
You're a woman.
For me, you're a chick.
I can't do it at all.
First, just with your fingers...
Stop it.
And then, you use my tools.
I wrote it as 〇〇〇 and read it as 〇〇〇.
Hama-chan, 〇〇〇 is 〇〇〇.
You're such a troublemaker.
Let's go home.
It's so hot.
The other day, when I was riding the Shinkansen,
I was riding alone.
There were a lot of people.
When there were a lot of people,
when I was riding from Shin-Osaka, my fan...
There was nothing there.
He was just a fan.
He came in like this on the Shinkansen.
He handed me a letter.
Hama-chan, why didn't you call me?
Hey, call me.
He's angry.
He's scared.
The people around him were like,
Hey, there's Matsumoto.
There's Matsumoto.
The people around him were like, Hey, there's Matsumoto.
So the girl wrote in the letter.
She wrote it.
Please call me.
I'll ignore it.
Why don't you do it?
So why don't you do it?
I don't know, but I won't do it.
Don't make fun of me.
Ignore it.
I won't.
I won't do it either.
You do it sometimes.
Sorry.
So,
How's your time?
It's fine.
Let's go back to the basics next week.
What's that?
Time limit?
You just shot it.
There's a show called Yoshimoto's natural stupidity.
Actually,
This is...
You have it, right?
Yes.
This is me.
Is this me?
It's like this.
Yes.
This is a set of two.
Hudson.
I'm going to buy a game called Road Runner.
It will come with it.
I don't care.
Today is a gift.
For those who are watching today,
100 people.
This.
Please write to me.
I'm waiting for you.
And also write to me.
You do it as usual.
I do.
Please write to me.
I'm waiting for you.
So,
I won't do it again.
Goodbye.
Wait a minute.