Let's go!
Excuse me.
You are not alone. You are not alone.
It's dangerous. Please walk on the sidewalk.
I want to play dodgeball 500 to 500.
Tetsu wins!
It's finally starting.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
It's starting!
I am not going to lose to you!
Matsumoto is the one who is going to be punished!
Don't lose to that rotten Hamada!
Don't lose to that womanizer!
He's a homo!
I'm a homo!
Good job, guys.
That's right.
I'm the one who should be thanking you!
That's right!
That guy was a little bit bad.
He was a little bit like a scarecrow.
Now, the game has started.
30 minutes, Nagachoban.
First, he passes the ball to Keikai.
First, Matsumoto's turn.
Matsumoto is shaking.
Now, how is it?
Hamada's turn.
500 against 500.
Both teams have 100 players.
The losing team is waiting for the punishment game.
Now, Matsumoto's turn.
Hamada's team hasn't lost yet.
Now, Hamada's team hasn't lost yet.
Where is Matsumoto?
He passes the ball to Miyoko.
Go, Hamada!
Out!
100 points for Matsumoto.
Hamada passes the ball.
Nice catch!
Now, Matsumoto's turn.
Nice catch, Hamada!
Matsumoto passes the ball to go back inside.
He's running!
Who is he going to hit?
He crosses the line.
He's going!
Matsumoto!
This is no good.
Hamada is relaxed.
Matsumoto from Kishu Kaisei makes a goal!
Now he goes back inside.
Go Hamada! Go Hamada!
Let's go!
Hamada is out!
It's almost the end of the game.
The current number of players is almost the same.
The game is about to begin!
Hamada is running away!
Out! Out!
Hamada is out!
Kishu Kaisei makes a goal!
Now he goes back inside.
Hamada is relaxed.
Out!
Now Kishu Kaisei makes a goal!
Where is the goal?
Out!
Nice catch!
Hamada is relaxed.
It's almost the end of the game.
The current number of players is almost the same.
The game is about to begin!
Go Hamada!
Did he score?
This is the short bound.
You can't go back.
You scored directly.
Hamada is saying he scored.
It's almost the end of the game.
Out!
Matsumoto is out!
It's almost the end of the game.
Hamada is relaxed.
The game is about to begin!
The current number of players is almost the same.
It's almost the end of the game.
Good!
How many members are there in your team?
We won! Congratulations, Hama-chan team!
There is a graduation album, right?
We will take a picture.
And we will send it to each otaku.
We won! Congratulations, Hama-chan team!
Please
Congratulations, Hama-chan team!
We'll all be wearing a hangezura and ride on a roller coaster!
Everyone will be wearing a hangezura, and I will take off my hangezura!
We're finally going to reveal our identities!
Cheese!
A thousand young people gathered in Yomiyuri Land.
A day of youth, sweating with two downtown people,
and the memories of playing with the ball must have left something in you.
You too, from now on, are our friends. Let's jump out, under the blue sky.
Congratulations to the Hamada team that won!
The Matsumoto team is not in their right mind.
Please look forward to the punishment game.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Recently, you know...
Many of you are new here.
Oh, really?
I don't know if that's the case.
But it doesn't matter.
You know...
I'm going to be reborn from today.
Is that why your eyebrows are so thick?
Yes, that's why my eyebrows are so thick, and I look like a man.
But it's kind of gross to have such thick eyebrows.
Is that so?
That's too much.
You look like a man.
I'm going to be reborn.
It's thick, but it's more beautiful.
It's rough.
That's what a man's cooking is like.
I don't cook.
Well, you do cook.
Well, I'm going to stop here.
What are you talking about?
I'm a comedian, so I'm going to tell a lie.
I'm going to tell a lie.
You're laughing a lot.
Even if I'm told a little, people don't believe in the world of TV.
There are people who really believe in it.
No, there are.
I'll tell you why.
Last week, after the show, I got a lot of letters from the stars.
There was one, and there was a heart sticker on it.
When I opened it, there was a picture of a man.
It's coming from him.
How old is he?
He's 28 years old.
He's the same age as you.
He's really chubby.
His skin is smooth.
I can't stand you anymore.
My hobby is making sweets.
It's disgusting.
Please be my friend.
I'm waiting for your call.
You crushed it.
Let's go to Disneyland or drive.
Go, go, go.
Don't go, it's a loss.
It's a loss?
I'm begging you.
I'll make his wish come true.
Make it come true?
I'll make it come true.
Really?
It's not going to happen.
But I've been told that if I go to play in Osaka, I'll be taken to the toilet.
Is it true?
I went to the disco, and the man took me to the toilet.
Of course, I'll do it.
Are you serious?
I went home, took a shower, and cried.
Did you get hit?
Did you get hit when you took a shower and cried?
You're lying.
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
But as a comedian, I want to laugh.
I don't know if I'm going to laugh or not.
I'll make it clear.
I'm facing the camera.
What camera are you looking at now?
Here.
I'll make it clear.
I think.
You can't say such a thing.
You're lying.
I'm going to cut here and make a commercial.
I'm going to stop here.
I'm going to make it clear.
If it ends here, that's what happens.
That's right.
I'm absolutely wrong.
I can't write a letter like that.
I don't know.
I can't do that.
It's not fun to go on a drive with a man.
That's right.
But what if you touch me like this?
Wait a minute.
You can't touch your father.
I don't know.
That's not true.
I'm sorry I made a mistake.
I don't know either.
Everyone says it's funny on TV.
Amateurs say things that we can't think of.
What?
So you can't say it.
Even if you're playing alone, you can't say,
Today, Mr. Aikada.
That's true.
It's not the same.
It's true.
I used to say,
I don't usually hang out with my friends.
That's annoying.
When I asked him, he said,
I'll be back soon.
He said,
I killed him.
I still have a long way to go.
I'm going to bury him.
But still.
What?
I'm worried about him.
That's right.
He said,
Thank you for the meal today.
The other day,
He said,
I'm really close to you.
I see.
So,
I know you're married.
But he said,
I think you and I live together.
So what am I?
That's a lie.
You're married and you have kids.
But I'm eating with you.
Today's meal is...
I talked to you a lot today.
That's right.
I'm tired.
What are you doing today?
Are you in somewhere?
No.
That's right.
The other day,
I went to the dodgeball game.
Oh,
You went to the game?
Yes.
Really?
What are you?
The princess of the kingdom without a father?
No, no.
I want to go to a country like that.
Oh,
You're a princess.
You should say that.
You should praise her.
Thank you very much.
Did you come to the dodgeball game?
No.
Well,
Hamada bought it.
He bought it, right?
So,
After I got home,
I couldn't sleep at all.
What's wrong?
I can't drink well.
You can't drink well?
There's something going on.
What is it?
I was 24 years old.
I was 18 years old.
You were 18 years old.
Yes, yes.
So,
Hamada's team won.
Oh,
I lost.
When I got home,
There was no evidence.
Did you see it?
No,
I didn't see it.
The staff told me that.
I had no choice but to believe it.
All the staff are crazy.
I know that.
My best friend came out of here.
Are you stupid?
You're not stupid, either.
Let's hear it.
I started going to the dormitory in July.
The dormitory teacher,
There's a dormitory teacher, right?
Yes.
The dormitory teacher is Matsumoto.
The vice-director is Hamada.
Really?
That's all.
Please keep up the good work.
Is that so?
It's funny, isn't it?
I told you a funny story the other day.
That's right.
That's amazing.
You know,
B21 Hiromi Ono, right?
Hiromi's father and my father are classmates.
I found that out the other day.
I found it out.
We had a reunion after 30 years.
That's where I slept.
B's father said,
My son is B21 Hiromi.
My father said,
My son is Hamada Dantan.
We were like, what?
That's right.
That's an amazing story.
I was really surprised.
My father said,
Why don't you apply to Marukome, the eighth generation?
Can I get in?
If I can't get in, that's fine.
That's true.
If you can't get in, that's true.
Don't be upset later.
I'll send you two times a month.
If you say okay, I'll do it.
What should I do?
Hello.
Today, you watched the match of dodgeball.
This is the result.
Next week, I'll show you the penalty game.
It was exciting, wasn't it?
That's right.
Especially Takasu and the staff were excited.
Really?
They were desperate to remember the number of the ball.
If it wasn't that kind of thing,
I see.
I was very angry.
You have the number of the person who came to you.
Yes.
You remembered that, didn't you?
I think I remembered.
What number is good?
I was told later.
I was surprised.
Oh, Takasu.
Is that so?
Yes, really.
I was going to ask you after the show.
But you seem to be shy.
Is that so?
Don't be shy.
I was wondering if I should ask you.
I'll see you next week.
Next week is the penalty game.
This program was provided by the following sponsors.