Which one of you is the popular guy?
It's been a while since I've seen this hall.
But what are you going to do now?
Are you going to steal a painting?
Thieves don't dress up like this.
Then what is it? What is it?
Well, I dressed up like this.
Is that so? That's rare.
Thank you very much.
Let's have an opening today.
Today, I took a survey of everyone at the venue.
Oh.
Can you give me a little bit?
But this is not something to say now.
Do you really know that this program has no money?
I don't want to be a child.
But today, let me tell you what kind of survey I took.
What kind of guy is the popular guy now?
I'm sure both men and women are interested in this.
That's right.
The answers are written here.
This is the most popular among all of us.
There is such a thing.
What is your hobby?
My hobby?
This is it.
What does this mean?
Is it something to do?
What is it?
Is it a compliment?
Oh, I got it.
Onani.
Yes.
I'm sure there are many popular men.
I also play golf.
Is that so?
I'm a golfer.
Is this your opinion?
Yes.
I'm a golfer now.
I also play onani.
It's okay to write onani.
The most popular is golf.
Do you play golf or onani?
I play golf and so on.
Let's talk about your strengths.
Well...
My smile.
Wait a minute.
No, no.
Does it make you feel bad?
No, it doesn't make me feel bad.
My dream is to be in a commercial for Pocky.
Your smile after eating.
This is my dream.
Is that so?
My smile.
My strength is kindness.
What?
What kind of kindness?
I'm getting irritated.
I'm kind to everyone.
I'm kind to you, too.
Is that so?
Why are you staring at me?
I was counting how many times you hit me on the head.
Then I fell asleep.
Don't fall asleep like that.
You don't have kindness.
Everyone doesn't know that.
Is that so?
That's right.
What else do you know?
This kind of person is popular.
That's right.
Kindness.
This is...
I've done a lot of things.
I'm not as angry as a woman who wants to be kind to a man.
Even if I do something bad, she wants me to forgive her.
It's natural to be hit when you do something bad.
I do that.
But she wants me to forgive her.
But she likes men who forgive her.
Is that so?
That's right.
That's your girl.
She's waiting for you.
That's a bad thing.
You can break your nose.
That's right.
I do it to break my nose.
How about this?
Do I look like a man?
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
It's really...
I think this is a strange business.
This job?
Yes.
There's no other business that you two are doing together.
Is that so?
If you think about it.
That's right.
That means you two have to get along with each other.
What I want to say today is...
Why do you say such bad things about me?
You should say that at the academy.
It's not like that.
What is it?
It's the night of the dream red.
Did I say something rude to you on the night of the dream red?
Don't you tell me?
Like a fashion massage or something.
I'm very angry.
How angry I am?
I'm as angry as when I see the speed limit sign in a traffic jam car.
If you say something like that, I will...
You got hit again.
That's just one of the comments.
That's right.
Ma-chan, put your shoes on.
That's...
You're kind.
That's what you should never do.
You should get along with each other.
It's not like I'm angry because you said that.
If you say something like that, I know a lot of bad things about you.
I know your past that you don't want to be touched.
What are you talking about?
I've never said that.
I've always said that there are good and bad things on TV.
People have good and bad things to say.
I know that.
Right?
I know that your father was imprisoned.
You're saying anything in a different place.
You two are like eyes and ears.
You're like batteries.
Yes, yes, yes.
Right?
If you don't get along with each other, you can't win.
The opponent team.
Baseball.
You're getting along with each other, aren't you?
That's why you shouldn't pull people's legs.
That's all.
If you say something like that,
you'll only get caught.
I made a mistake.
It's not you.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
I thought you were getting along with each other, too.
That's right.
But there's a reason why you shouldn't get along.
As expected.
You want to get along with me.
That's right.
Think about me, too.
Hamada's father wasn't imprisoned?
That's right.
I think I should get along with you, too.
Hamada...
That's Mr. Tabata's place.
That's right.
But I can't make a mistake.
Let's get along with each other.
That's right.
But you don't have any friends, do you?
There's something in marriage.
You get divorced on your honeymoon.
That's right.
When you get home.
You can't stay together forever.
That's right.
There's a lot of things that make me angry.
I get angry.
I don't want to be with him forever.
When I go on a honeymoon, I get angry.
I get angry when I'm told to get out of here.
That's right.
When I get married.
In a different sense, I don't want to get married to a guy like that.
That's right.
You're talking about the Narita divorce.
Didn't you both have a hard time until the end?
That's right.
When I go out with him, I don't get angry.
You don't get angry, do you?
No, I get angry.
What?
You get angry?
I get angry.
Since when do you get angry?
What?
I've been angry since the beginning.
Oh, you got angry from the beginning?
Is that so?
No, but it's different for men and women who date normally.
But there are a lot of girls who can't stand it.
You can't get angry with a girl until you get married.
Is that so?
That's right.
But there are times when you get angry on the cover of something.
When you don't even have the courage to get angry, you get angry.
If you do that, I'm sorry, but it's better to get angry.
If you get angry when you don't even have the courage to get angry, it's really cool.
That's true.
It's not cool even for men.
If you get angry, you say, I'll do it.
But girls can't do that.
Do you have a girl you want to get angry with?
No, I don't.
I don't.
But if I get angry, I get angry.
I think it's a big deal.
I think so, too.
But there are times when you don't even have the courage to get angry.
If you get angry, you can't get angry with a girl until you get married.
You can't get angry when you don't even have the courage to get angry.
It's the same for me.
When I do something, I can tell if it stinks or not by the smell of my room.
I smell it by the sound and the way it comes out.
I think it stinks, so I look at the face and enjoy it.
There are times when I speak in a cool way.
I don't get angry with that.
You don't get angry.
This kind of man doesn't say it stinks.
That's true.
That's like a karaoke man telling me not to get angry.
That's what I'm saying.
That's true.
If you do something, it's not worth it to react to it.
I see.
Where do they usually get angry?
Do they get angry?
Usually?
They get angry.
Because there are so many people.
At this moment, someone is definitely angry.
They definitely get angry.
Is that so?
That's right.
Japan is such a strange country.
That's true.
Please take out your papers.
Hello.
Are you an amateur today?
Yes.
I see.
Are you angry?
No, I'm not. I'm just nervous.
What did you just say?
Work?
What do you mean work?
I said work.
It's amazing that an amateur can't speak properly.
What?
Do you understand?
I was about to ask you.
If an amateur can't speak clearly, it's the same as a doctor failing a surgery.
It's killing you.
Why are you repeating it?
I'm listening.
Really.
How old are you?
21.
You're 21.
You should get married.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I have one.
What?
What does your boyfriend do?
He works.
Does he look down on you?
This is strange.
My tongue is spinning.
I wanted to ask you.
I wanted to ask if you looked down on me.
Do you look down on me?
Thank you very much.
I'm glad that you look down on me.
Let me introduce her.
Her name is Hiromi Kozaira. She's 23 years old.
I've been watching her since the first episode.
By the way, there was something like this in the article of FromA on July 16th.
It was about a late-night show.
In the article, she was asked what her favorite show was.
She said she liked Gaki no Tsukai.
The first place was Kanossa.
It's over, isn't it?
It's over.
Now, Gaki is the king of late-night shows.
It's about Gaki no Tsukai.
It's written in the introduction.
Downtown is in season now.
Anyway, it's a big explosion.
It's about to be dangerous.
What do you mean?
A man named Pedro, who is 24 years old, wrote this.
It's Pedro's opinion, isn't it?
It's Pedro's opinion.
But you don't know if it's dangerous, do you?
Is that so?
That's right.
I don't know what's going to happen tomorrow.
I really don't know what's going to happen in this entertainment world.
I know what's going to happen.
I don't know what's going to happen.
I'm going to join the late-night show.
What?
I'm telling you.
You're not telling me.
Your ears are weird.
Did you find out?
I told you I was going to join the late-night show.
If you want to know more about the late-night show, please send it to the address below.
If you want to join the late-night show, please send it to the address below.
Tokyo, Shibuya, 1-1-4.
Aoyama, Flowerville, 5th floor.
The late-night show in Japan.
If you send it this far, you can join the late-night show.
Do you want to join us?
No.
You don't know how many benefits you'll get if you join the late-night show.
What are the benefits?
If I hear that, I'll join the show again.
The late-night show key holder.
If you become a member, you'll get all the benefits.
It's shaped like a bird.
It's shaped like a key holder.
And then?
The late-night show ballpoint pen.
What is this?
I don't know.
The late-night show ballpoint pen.
If you become a late-night show, you'll get a ballpoint pen.
What?
You're not allowed to say such things in the late-night show.
Well...
Read it yourself.
I'll help you.
What is this?
Read it, Aomodara.
Don't look down on me.
Good evening.
I'm a friend of Masumoto-san's cousin's wife's cousin.
What?
That's why we have a little connection.
I may bother you at some point, but please take care of me at that time.
His cousin is probably...
Makoto?
Liar!
Wasn't it Makoto?
I don't know.
His wife?
I was told that it wasn't Makoto.
Yoshie-san's cousin's...
Satake-san's...
That's enough!
Kuwabara-san's...
Liar!
This one.
How to go home.
The ending.
I've thought of a way to go home.
How about Parma No. 2 dressed up as Booby and come out to save them and leave?
That person...
If you dress like that, you'll really look like him.
I'll try.
I'll try to come out in Booby next week.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
It's the black screen of the Prime Minister.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
The other day, I was sitting in the toilet next to Kiyosu-kun at Shinjuku Station with my friend.
Then an aunt came out of Kiyosu-kun.
I was wondering what to do, and when I looked at her, she suddenly took out a trash can.
And she took out some magazines from them and read them out.
After that, I took out a couple of new, clean-looking weekly magazines.
And I put them on top of the magazine I was selling at Kiyosu-kun.
And I saw an old man buying the magazine from the trash can.
I couldn't stop crying.
You're lying!
Have you been crying all this time?
No, I haven't.
I don't know.
There's a thing called a manga spirit.
Oh, the last word of the day is a manga spirit.
I'll put this in the book and ask.
A manga spirit?
A manga spirit.
There's a thing called a manga spirit in the book you bought.
And after reading it...
There's a manga spirit in all the manga.
There's a manga spirit.
You're reading it, aren't you?
What's the manga spirit doing during that time?
There's a manga spirit when I open it.
There's a manga spirit when you open it?
Yes, there is.
And then?
When I turn the page, the manga spirit runs like this.
The manga spirit has to be on every page.
That's why it runs.
In the middle...
Oh, it's a station.
What's the manga spirit doing during that time?
I see.
When I read the next page, the manga spirit opens.
You're annoying.
The manga spirit is scary.
Shut up.
There was a girl called Aiko Gibo.
I don't know.
She's an amazing...
Old lady.
I know her.
She's Haguki Bon.
Yes.
Haguki Bon.
There was a younger brother who passed away.
She was crying.
Yes.
She's amazing.
Haguki Bon.
I want you to see Haguki Bon.
Why?
Watanabe of Akashin-Go saw it and said,
I'll tell you later.
Right?
That kind of person...
He said, what are you doing here?
He said, hey, hey, hey.
I asked him later.
He said, there's a manga spirit behind you.
What do you say?
He didn't die.
You did something terrible to a woman and broke up.
The manga spirit of that person is behind you.
I think you'll definitely be told.
The manga spirit is annoying.
Call him next time, Gibo-san.
If I tell him...
The manga spirit is behind you.
The manga spirit!
You're an old lady.
I admit that she's Haguki Bon.
But she's not an old lady.
You should call her sensei.
The one behind that sensei is Haguki-chan.
I don't know her!
If you have a chance next time, please do it.
It's good, isn't it?
Is that all?
Yes, that's all.
I have to go home.
I have to clean this up.
So, what do you want to do?
I want you to stand here today.
I'm going to leave in a cool way today.
Like a Kabuki actor.
Really.
Is that okay?
Yes.
Everyone, please come again.
Goodbye.
It seems like it's going up and down from the back.
Up and down.
Amazing.
That's all?
Good evening.
I'm the editor.
Yes.
So, this week, we went down and came back.
Next week, they'll come to help us.
Is that decided?
Yes, it's decided.
No. 2 will come to help us.
We'll ask No. 2 to help us.
I thought about it today.
Tsu-chi looks like No. 4, doesn't he?
He's a pa, isn't he?
So, we'll ask No. 2 and No. 4 to help us.
No. 2 will come to help us.
Please look forward to the next season's ending.
And, we'll use the postcards.
100th anniversary.
I see.
It's already here.
But, we don't have this yet.
You don't have it?
Yes.
Let's ask for it.
That's it.
We'll use the postcards until the next season.
Bye.
Thank you.
That's good.
Let's ask for it.
Are you happy?