Pigs, also known as the Gu-Temoku boar, are a species of wild boar.
Their origin dates back to the Paleolithic period, when European, Chinese, and Indian boars evolved into wild boars.
In Central and Western Europe, pigs were an important food source for the common people.
However, the influence of their religious beliefs made them a popular term for evil spirits.
Also, in Japan, in the early days of Japan, pigs were bred and their history is old.
In the course of time, the influence of Buddhism brought them down, but they were also popularized along with civilization.
There are more than 300 species of pigs.
Approximately 800 million of them are sold worldwide.
Their weight ranges from 80kg to 200kg.
They give birth to 6 to 16 pigs at a time.
Pigs are often misunderstood as having a lot of fat,
but they are actually the most nutritious and balanced protein food for the Japanese.
This is proven by the fact that Okinawan people eat about 1.7 times the amount of pork per day and are ranked as the best in the country.
And today, we are going to eat these wonderful pigs.
Today, we are going to give you more and more presents.
Thank you.
It's all about presents.
These guys are really...
Today, they are all wearing summer clothes.
This year's summer was hot.
That's right.
We are here to solve the summer heat.
Over here.
Thank you.
This is the best-known pork in Maruyaki.
It's called Yorkshire.
It's a good one.
It's a good-looking pig.
That's right.
It's Maruyaki.
It's wonderful.
You've never seen it, have you?
I've never seen it.
It's a good dish, isn't it?
A good dish?
Yes.
It's a high-class dish, isn't it?
Why is it so small?
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Wow.
What is this?
Salt and pepper, right?
We have to do this by hand, right?
What?
It's hot.
Everyone is angry.
The smell is from here.
Yamazaki.
It's hot.
He gets angry very quickly.
What?
Is it inside?
Yes.
It's inside.
What?
If you don't taste it, it's bad.
You should rub it.
Yes.
He's fast.
He gets angry very quickly.
It's hot.
You have to rub the salt because there's only the salt.
The salt won't come clean.
And you have to rub.
I can't drink in this attire.
Some softness than usual.
Now you're really enjoying it.
Good, good.
Here it goes
sudah
Today as well.
You're not kidding, are you?
It's enough.
You've gone mad.
Have you?
It's good, isn't it?
Look at this fat
It's good
It reminds me of Hamabe
Is there anything else I should put on?
The butt
Wow
That's a big one
The butt
Oh, this nice part
What is this?
You have to turn it slowly
Slowly
It's a nice
color
The butt shrank
Turn it
It's amazing
It looks good, doesn't it?
It looks like Shimura Ken
The tail got longer
Why?
Because of the fire
The tail broke
Isn't it soft?
The fat
It looks good
The juice
It looks really good
The way you cut it
I don't know
You look like you're happy
Here you go
Is this salt and pepper?
Can I cut it?
Here you go
I'm not a regular, so eat it
I'm not a regular
It's good
It's really good
Is everyone having a good time?
Yes
Don't die in the summer
It's the end of the summer
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you
It's good
Did everyone have a good meal?
Yes
Thank you
We ate well
Please do your best for the second half of the year
I'll do my best
Ladies and gentlemen
When did you come back to the ladies and gentlemen?
About 3 or 4 weeks ago
Today is good
This is cool
This is popular
It's not popular
It's like the prince of the lake
I don't laugh
We are the only ones who laugh
It's really quiet
I don't know if it's S
It's better when it's hot
It's good
I was surprised
Yoshimoto Kogyo is dirty
It's really dirty
Really?
Yoshimoto doesn't put in a lot of gyala
It used to be a month late
If you work this month, it will be in the next month
That's right
About half a year ago, it was two months late
Matsumoto thinks it's strange
I was surprised when I heard it
Why?
There was a reason for this one month
It would have been better if it was in the next month
But he put it in the bank and increased the interest
I was surprised
Really?
What is this company?
Normally it's like that
Really?
I was surprised
The president of Yoshimoto said in a magazine
Matsumoto put in 600 million this year
I don't have 600 million
It's a lie
He said he put in 600 million
But I earned it
I earned it
I ran
Matsumoto said it's a lie
It's a lie
I said it's a lie
Why are you angry?
It's a dirty company
But I can't help it
I always think
For example, I live in Tokyo
I have an apartment
But I can't help thinking
For example, from the program
I have to pay for accommodation and taxi
You don't live here?
But I have to pay
I take all the money
It's a bad luck
I thought you would say that
I'm not talking about this
You're not
You've been talking about that
Wait
I don't care about this
I'm talking about this
I know it's easy to take
I'm not talking about money
I'm talking about my feelings
A while ago
I went back to Osaka
I heard you were snoring
Why?
I don't want to talk about this
I heard you were snoring
Are you stupid?
No
When I talk about this
I get angry
You want to talk, right?
Go ahead
I live in Tokyo
I don't know what you're talking about
What are you doing?
What are you talking about?
I live in Tokyo
To be honest
I don't know what you're talking about
I'm a snorer
I'm sorry
I'm angry
I'm not talking about this
Really
Why did you snore?
I don't know
I'm a snorer
I was walking normally
It's normal
It's been a week
It's been a long time
You look cute
To be honest
I have a lot of gold
Don't brag
Let me talk
I have 4 gold
I have 5 gold
To be honest
I don't have many talents
It's okay
You don't have many talents
You have 31 talents
It's okay
Tell me why you were walking
Right now
I'm a snorer
I don't like it
I looked back
on Osaka
I want to be a snorer
Why were you walking?
Tell me
I want to be a snorer
like I was back then
It's dangerous
I understand
You're a snorer
You know people come to you
I wanted to be a snorer
I was a snorer
I sometimes
Where?
I was walking
Like this
Why are you wearing a basket?
I'm not wearing a basket
Why did we talk about this?
I went back to Osaka
Of course
I asked my parents
to get me a Shinkansen
I stayed at a hotel
I asked my parents
to pay me
You went there in private
Pay me
Why?
You went there for fun
Pay me
Why are you standing there?
What do you mean?
You're living in Tokyo for work
You're not going to Osaka
You're going home
You don't live here
But
I can pay you
No
You have to pay
I'm not paying
I'm talking about this
You're not paying
Pay me
It's not 10,000 yen
You're saying mean things
Is it mean?
Am I dirty?
It's cold
What are you doing?
Why are you so angry?
Don't say that
I said it because I knew
What is that?
Come with me
Let's do something
Let's do a concert
I want you to pay me
I'll get paid
I'll pay you
That's against the company
You can't do that
I want to do it
It's cold
You're saying it's cold
It hurts
Where are you going?
I noticed that
You use animal characters
Black cat, pelican, kangaroo, duck
Is there anything in common?
I don't know
I don't know what you mean
Is there anything in common?
Let me ask
I'm saying
Black cat, pelican, kangaroo, duck
What is it?
It's an animal
You use animal characters
You know animals
First
It's full of hair
Full of hair?
It's not just black cat
Kangaroo is full of hair
It's not full of hair
It's not smooth
Why are you saying that?
It's my job
It's full of hair
It's not just black cat
Why do you close your eyes when you cry?
It's a face
This is a good thing
No
Everyone has an item
There is a kangaroo
There is a pelican
There is a black cat
It's not an item
It's forcibly
You can put it inside
That depends on which side can put it
No
This black cat is my parent
So what? It doesn't hurt that much.
No, no, no.
The ones who can put it in are all individuals.
But the pain is separate.
Stupid!
Stupid?
Your mother can put a stand in it, but she's holding it in.
Your mother can put a stand in her butt, but she's holding it in.
So I can't wear a yohane.
I'll think of you as a kitten.
That's enough!
Fueru wakame becomes wakame if you put it back in water.
But what happens if you put Matsumoto-san back in water?
That's right.
What happens?
I don't think that's the right way to say it.
What do you mean by putting him back in water?
No, it's not like that.
If you put him in a pool or something, something will happen.
That won't happen.
What?
It won't happen.
If you put him in water, something will happen.
That's why I said it would happen.
You can't say that.
You did it with Itoi-san before, right?
Fishing, right?
Black bass.
Why didn't you run away then?
You had a chance.
No, I didn't.
You had to hold my yohane and put it in like this.
You can't run away like that.
Who told you to run away like that?
Why did you have to hold my yohane and put it in like that?
Then I would have gone like this.
No, no, no, no.
That's a temporary form.
What are you?
If you do this, you can run away, right?
You're changing your position.
I'm your partner.
I was killed by the river.
What is this?
What are you at this time?
I'm your partner.
No, no, no, no.
If you were my partner, you wouldn't have run away like this.
Why?
What are you at this time?
That's why I'm your partner.
I'm your classmate, your friend, and your partner.
That's why you're my partner up to this point.
Right?
What are you when I talk to you?
I'm your partner.
Why?
That's strange.
You run away like this.
Wait a minute.
Don't you need a partner who runs away like this?
It's okay to have such a partner.
You're an idiot.
There's no way.
I'll tell you something.
You don't have to do this for the rest of your life.
Then I won't run away.
That's why.
Maybe.
Someone doesn't know that.
Wait.
Wait for me.
Well, well, well.
I was smoking here.
When I looked at it, someone was like this.
What are you going to do if you don't make it in time?
I'm all alone.
But I'm sure you'll come back.
With a lot of eggs.
Don't come back.
I feel bad.
With eggs?
Don't you feel bad?