The famous prodigy is Hamada, who was called by the name of Sugano.
You know, we did the 4th episode of Shihadori.
I got a complaint that I was doing it slowly.
This is the challenge of the previous episode, which became a problem.
The wheat of Hayamagashi, which is said to have died because of the suffering of Hayate of Matsumoto, is gone.
That was a good rating.
So what are you going to do?
The 5th episode.
That's enough.
I'm sick of it.
No, that's not it.
I'm telling you it's dangerous. What if you get hurt?
I haven't been hurt 4 times so far.
I haven't been hurt so far, but I think I can do it.
Don't get angry.
Masato, wait a minute.
Listen to Shihadori.
You have to listen carefully.
I did Shihadori 4 times.
I did it.
That's the project you gave me.
You were a talent before you won the first place in Shihadori, right?
I did Shihadori.
I got a complaint that I was doing it slowly.
What's your answer?
I don't know.
I admit that.
That's enough.
I don't like the talent video I'm doing now.
I'm like a TV show.
I'm going to call you a teacher from now on.
Who are you?
I'm going to bring it.
Don't go.
If you don't want to do it, don't do it.
If he takes this attitude, I'll be angry.
Who are you talking to?
Maa-kun.
I told you I'd do it.
Matsumoto Shitoji appeared in Shibotoshita Shiro Shibozoku.
What are you doing?
I'm going to do it.
I'll buy you.
After all,
after all,
In short,
I have to do it.
I'm going to do it.
I'll get hurt.
I'm going to die.
I'm going to get hurt.
Listen to me seriously!
Stop it!
What is it?
It's not a fast turn.
It's not a reverse turn.
I'm not going to use any tools.
I'm going to do it with all my heart.
If you don't do it with me, we'll do it together.
That's right.
I don't know.
I don't know either.
Let's go.
What are you talking about?
I'm not going to use any tools.
I'm going to do it with all my heart.
Let's go.
What are you talking about?
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Let's go.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Come on!
Okay.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Don't touch me.
It's my fault.
I'll call the electrician.
Yama.
It's dangerous.
It hurts.
Don't step on me.
I'm going to get hurt.
I'm going to do it.
Why are you hitting me?
Are you an electrician?
I'm an electrician.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Don't think about it.
I'm sorry.
I told the electrician.
I can light up four bulbs.
It's okay.
Let's go.
It's okay if it's this bright.
If there's another one, I'll light it up.
It's okay.
It's bright enough.
I'll light it up.
It's okay.
I'll do it.
What is this?
What are you doing?
Yamazaki, call the electrician.
Okay.
It's okay if it's this bright.
If there's another one, I'll light it up.
You do it.
I'll do it.
It's okay if it's this bright.
Can you do it?
I'm sorry.
I'll do it next time.
I can't do it with just one bulb.
It's okay if it's this bright.
Can I light it up?
It's okay.
You can try it.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Please be careful.
I'm sorry.
That's all for today.
I went too far.
What is it today?
I want to say that I made a wish.
I didn't say it yet.
You won't say it yet?
What if I say it?
I'll say it again.
I heard it last time 5 or 6 years ago.
It's hard to make jokes with a laugh.
So I...
The lines here are really thick, you know?
So when I'm at home, I buy a TV and I can only watch that kind of stuff.
What are you talking about?
It's funny!
I was watching it, but I couldn't draw the lines at all.
Like this.
Why are you looking at it like that?
I was looking at it like this.
This is one of the 7 mysteries of the entertainment world.
The 9th one is...
What are the 8th ones before that?
The 8th one before that is...
Why is Tama running around?
Leave me alone! I've been doing this for years!
There are a lot of mysteries.
I have a hard time with my nerves.
I'm an old man. I'm 30 years old.
I've lost a lot of strength.
Really?
In the past, I was amazing, but I've lost a lot of strength.
In the past, I shot guns every night.
Where did you shoot them?
Where did you shoot the guns?
There was a mark on the carpet.
You shot guns on the carpet?
At that time, you were caught by a cheetah's tail.
I ran and got caught by a cheetah's tail.
Where were you?
I didn't care where I was.
It has nothing to do with me!
I don't remember where I was.
So, where were you?
I don't remember.
It was really hard.
I know that I'm going to die soon.
I think it's going to be 2 or 3 years later.
I'm going to do scuba diving with my eyes full.
I'm going to dive where I usually don't.
You've never done scuba diving, have you?
No, I've never done it.
You're lying.
Let's do it today.
Can you teach me how to do scuba diving?
I want to do scuba diving.
I've never done it.
Teach me how to do it.
You look like Yasukyo.
This is a tank.
I'm going to carry this.
You're going to carry this?
I'm going to carry this, too.
I'm going to put this in.
If I put this in, I can breathe.
Don't put it in.
Let's go over there.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
It's been a while.
I have to do it.
I'm very fast.
I know that.
I'll die in three years.
I can do what I want to do.
I'm just wondering how I'm going to die.
You're going to be stabbed.
Damn it.
What are you talking about?
I'm a woman.
You're a woman?
Let's do it.
Who's going to be in the condo?
Why?
There's a lot of things.
Someone's going to come.
With this.
That's not going to happen.
But you can't tell me that there's a woman here, can you?
I'll tell you that you're not alone.
That's why I don't feel like I've been deceived by that woman.
What about me?
I don't do a lot of presents, but I don't do it here.
That's right.
I was talking to Shinsuke Shimada the other day.
I don't think I should have said that.
What are you talking about?
No, no.
I don't do presents.
After we broke up, we hit 1 million.
How many times did I say that?
300,000?
We hit 300,000.
I didn't do anything that would hit 300,000.
Why did you keep your face red at that time?
I'll do it.
Why didn't you come out?
I admit that my face was a little red, but...
Was it red?
The studio was hot, and I'm originally from Akita.
What are you talking about?
I'm from Akita, so I can't come.
No, you can't.
I don't think there's anything like that.
What are you talking about?
How do you die?
I'll die.
Why are you telling me to die?
You'll be alone until you die.
What are you talking about?
There's a time when I want to have a child.
You can't make a name for yourself.
I want to raise a child like me.
It's different from you guys.
Did you see it?
I'm doing this.
Did you see me doing this?
That's how I was raised.
I was raised really well.
For example?
First of all, I'll give you money when you're in elementary school.
If it's 10 million yen, I'll give you 10 million yen.
From now on, I'll give you 10 million yen.
You can do everything with this.
I'll pay for your school lunch from there.
I'll give you money for your school trip from there.
If you want to eat only sweets, you can buy sweets with 10 million yen.
But you can't go on a school trip.
You can't go to high school either.
I tried it.
But if you say something good, you'll get a good one.
You're an old man in elementary school.
On the contrary, you'll lose your cuteness and crap.
In a sense.
I don't like your voice.
Do you want to increase the tempo?
Why does Yumi Shirakawa often appear in the drama where Hama-chan appears?
I don't know.
That's what the casting is like.
What are you laughing at?
What kind of laugh is that?
It depends on how you do it.
But that's strange.
That's strange.
It's not like the old Momoe-chan and Tomokazu Miura.
He appears in everything.
That's strange.
There must be something.
That's not something I can do.
If it's Shirakawa-san, I'll say, yeah!
You're not saying that?
I'm saying it!
I'm sure there are people who think you're saying that on TV.
That's strange.
What is Shirakawa Yumi?
Is it Downtown?
Why is it always the same?
It's strange.
I'm going to go to court again this evening.
Why?
Is there such a thing?
I'll look it up.
I've been to Meiji-kun.
Wait a minute.
No one said it was just the two of you.
It's not a co-star.
It's not a common excuse.
It's true.
What is this?
It's like a rice field.
Have you ever seen a rice field?
Why do your eyebrows grow longer as you get older?
It doesn't make any sense to take it to another place for nutrition.
What is it?
The lines are strange.
You're a machia.
For example, there are three grooves in the middle of the head.
There are three lines.
Normally, there are three lines in the middle of the head, but this line is in the middle of the head.
That's why...
I feel like I'm going to get better.
I don't really care.
You're like Osamu-san.
I do it sometimes, but I don't care.
Osamu-chan.
Why do your eyebrows grow longer?
I don't know.
There's a shoulder hair.
Really?
Around here?
My brother has a back hair.
A back hair?
It's like a sofa.
What is this?
Is a bird staying here?
It's not.
It's like a bird's head.
Who is the bird?
Well...
The reason why there are two lines is...
Why are there two lines?
Is that true?
Is it wrong to have one line?
That's right.
You're standing like this.
I'm not standing.
You're standing.
There are times when I stand.
I'm standing like this.
Have you ever seen it in the mirror?
Yes, I have.
You're moving like this.
Are you serious?
I was surprised when you made it clear at first.
And then, in the end, you fall down.
What is this?
What are the two lines?
You're making two lines, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
You can't make it with two people.
That was funny.
It's usually two people.
Why are there two lines?
In the past, there were 12 lines.
There were 12 lines?
There were 10 more?
It's said that there were 100 lines of instinct.
I like that.
There are 12 lines.
There are 12 lines?
Yes, there are.
Really?
What?
These two lines are the remaining ones.
These are love and courage.
What is this?
We're holding love and courage.
We do this every day.
Hello.
Love and courage.
That's right.
It's connected to what I said earlier.
It's about whether love wins or courage wins.
What are you talking about?
Everyone does that.
What's in the remaining 10 lines?
Everyone has their own story.
What is it?
When humans are born and live,
they lie when they have to do bad things.
They make their parents cry.
They fall one by one.
You should follow them.
When you collect all 12 of them, your wish will come true.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.