Today, we're going to lift our heavy back and challenge ourselves to move.
It's a difficult song, but it's called Memories of Love.
Here it is.
Normally, when you go to karaoke, when you play this song, this kind of image comes out.
I can't do it.
Here are the lyrics.
I think this is the point.
Yes, it's the joy of a beautiful life.
This part is going to change.
Happy, happy.
From here.
The beginning of the change is like this.
It's like a dead tree.
When it comes to actors, it's this person.
Here you go.
Good morning.
I'm so excited.
This is the best scene in the producer world.
You're an idiot.
The theme is...
I've been listening to Memories of Love for a long time.
The theme that comes to mind is...
Thank you very much.
It's a mixture of men and women.
This isn't funny.
It's hard.
The other person hasn't decided yet.
I'm holding the camera right now.
It's hard.
I'll keep shooting.
Let's start with the bed scene.
Let's take a look at the first cut.
This is the first cut.
I'm looking at the night view from the hotel window.
There's a back shot.
You can't see it at first.
It's like this.
A new partner.
This is good.
It's good.
Suga, take a picture of Gaon.
Okay.
It doesn't change much.
It's good.
I can't do it if I'm doing it as a partner.
I'm looking forward to the bed scene.
It's like this.
I'm the only one in Shinjuku.
This town is mine.
I see.
You should open your legs more.
I'm sorry, but I can't see anything from the hospital.
If you hit this, you'll sell it.
I'll do my best.
Let's do it a little bit.
Put your fingers up.
It's good.
Let's do this.
Ready.
Start.
Suga, don't move.
Cut.
I don't know.
What do you want to do?
Next is the shower scene.
Ready.
Start.
Cut.
Put your buttocks on your shoulders.
Tell the pig to do it.
I was told by Katsushi.
Let's do a funny scene.
Ready.
Start.
I want to kick you.
I kicked him a lot.
There was an ad-lib.
That ad-lib was good.
Let's do a scene where blood flows from the hip.
Blood flows from the hip.
What's that?
I've never used it before.
I can't use it.
Let's do it.
Ready.
Start.
Cut.
That was good.
I was stabbed.
Let's do the last scene.
It's a pet scene.
Look at me.
Look at you.
You are not welcome.
It's difficult to decide.
What do you want to do?
I want to go to Yonaoka.
Let's start with Kameya.
I don't like it.
I don't like the lower mouth.
Let's do it.
Let's start from the feet.
Ready.
Cut.
That was good.
I changed the scene.
I see.
I got it.
It's a little different.
Let's do it.
Let's start from the feet.
I don't like it.
I don't like the lower mouth.
Ready.
Start.
Let's start from the feet.
I don't like the lower mouth.
Cut.
I changed the scene.
I see.
I got it.
It's a little different.
Let's do it.
Let's start from the feet.
I don't like it.
I don't like the lower mouth.
Cut.
I changed the scene.
I see.
It's a little different.
Let's do it one more time.
Horive.
Really good.
Really good that.
Mr. Mado, this is awesome.
Horive, your mistake is serious, right?
In the end, it was like this.
Usada-chan was like this.
Okay, okay.
Good, good, good.
Takao Yamaoka didn't like it a little, but this time...
I'm serious.
Both of them are low.
It's better to be manly.
It's the same as usual.
Is it normal?
Yes, yes, yes.
This is wood and gold.
That's how I feel.
Ready...
Go!
A beautiful life...
Ah, I'm getting into the refrain.
He's an idiot.
愛の甘い名残にあなたは微睡む 天使のようなその微笑み 時は立ち止まる
窓に朝の光が優しく揺れ動き 貴方の髪をためらいがちに染めてゆく
美しい人生よ 限りない喜びを この胸のときめきを貴方に
この世に大切なのは 愛し合う事だってと 貴方を教えてくる
二人に視野を訪れて 星になる日が来ても 貴方と離れはしない
Translated by Releska