Which one of you is a fan of Tsukishiki?
Hey!
Sorry, sorry.
Today, we have a monitor.
We'll put in the audience.
The people who came to see us today.
They'll come in.
While we're watching.
This is your fan, right?
They came in!
This is my fan.
We'll decide on 3 people.
Then we'll go to the stage again.
And we'll give it to them.
Wait a minute.
You're my fan.
What kind of image do you have of my fans?
That's...
It's tough?
It's tough.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
This is your fan.
There's no mistaking it.
This isn't anyone's fan.
No, it's definitely yours.
Someone brought it.
Even if someone brought it.
I'm wearing it because I want to see someone.
I want to see you.
I'll check this out.
This isn't me.
This is Bu-chan.
Pink Bu-chan.
I'm really into Bu-chan rice.
Rice?
This is your fan.
It's tough.
It's your fan.
This is your fan.
This?
Really?
This kind of thing...
It's tough.
It's like a comedian's jacket.
It's cool.
I definitely want to draw you.
You mean me?
Yeah.
Is that so?
This young man is definitely like that.
What is this?
It looks like an old man.
Whose jacket is this?
It's a matchmaker.
It's tough.
This guy looks like a country bumpkin.
It looks like an old man.
It's definitely you.
The second one is an actor.
I don't know. Stop.
It's definitely this guy.
It's my fan.
It's like a daughter-in-law.
Thank you.
Everyone.
We were looking at you from above.
On the monitor.
We were looking at each of your faces from above.
There were some people who laughed at the camera.
There were a lot of people.
Today, as the title says, which book is it?
We made a guess.
The person you think is different from Hamada's fan is...
3 of C.
It's you.
5 of E.
It's that guy.
2 of H.
It's you.
That's right.
It's Hamada's fan.
I expected it to be Hamada's fan.
19 of D.
The girl with glasses.
It's her.
6 of B.
You are definitely Hamada's fan.
That's right.
11 of D.
That girl.
What's your name?
Manjoto.
My name is Manjoto.
Manjoto?
That was close.
Whose fan are you?
I'm Hamada's fan.
What part of Hamada is this?
The lips.
What?
Sit down!
What's your name?
Inagaki.
Who are you?
I'm Hamachan.
So you want Hamada to do this?
A little.
What?
A woman?
Are you kidding me?
That's cool.
Do you really have breasts?
Of course I do.
Touch her.
From here.
What?
That's cool.
That's rude.
I thought it was a fan of Matsumoto, but it was Hamada.
I thought it was a fan of Matsumoto, but it was a woman.
That's a big mistake.
What's your name?
I'm Bekehame.
How old are you?
I'm 21.
This girl is definitely your fan.
There's one more thing.
My heart is not here.
Which one is your fan?
Hamada.
It's the other way around.
That's a big mistake.
Is that so?
She was Hamada's number one fan, right?
That's right.
She said,
I'm definitely a fan of Matsumoto.
That's what she said when she came in.
What's your name?
Yoshida.
How old are you?
I'm 22.
I'm 21.
How old are you?
I'm 22.
You're so noisy.
Who are you?
I'm Matsumoto.
Matsumoto?
That's right.
I have a lot of things I want to ask you.
What's your name?
I'm Nishida.
How old are you?
I'm 24.
I'm Matsumoto.
See?
You forgot again.
What is this about?
I thought I wanted to be beaten up.
This is terrible.
I'm so hot.
My body is shivering.
But Rupan-kun...
Rupan-kun!
What are you doing here?
I didn't expect you to come here today.
I'm not Rupan-kun.
That's a bit harsh.
I'm not used to this kind of thing.
Really?
If you squeeze it a bit, it becomes Rupan-kun.
That's a bit too much.
I have a lot of things I want to ask you.
I'm working on a video right now.
This is going to be released soon.
This is interesting.
You have to buy this for rent.
This is going to be a long-term storage.
This is interesting.
I think everyone doesn't know this.
We debuted and did a lot of manzai.
We've been putting in a lot of manzai since then.
Yes.
And between that and that, this is interesting.
I can't stop.
Just remembering doing that is interesting.
I'm crying.
I got a dog-man.
It's a dog, but it's a robot.
You're the doctor who made the dog-man?
Yes, I'm Dr. Dog God.
That's the name.
It's a dog robot.
It's just a normal dog.
I got a request from the show.
I wanted to make a dog robot.
They said it was better to have a dirty dog.
I put on a wig and a cape.
I ran away with a cape on.
It says V on my forehead.
I'm an alien.
I'm a one-handed bug.
I ran away with a wig and a cape.
I said, go home.
I looked for a dog for an hour.
I was surprised to see someone walking like that.
To get on their back.
This is close to finished, so I want you to buy it.
I'm thinking of doing this animal series for a while.
We'll do a great show.
Mr. Gorilla
You're Mr. Gorilla?
He's a gorilla.
I've been admiring that teacher for a long time.
But since I was a wild child...
It would be interesting if I said something good.
I can't say, teacher.
But I want to do this as an animal series.
I'm a little tired now.
It's about time to stop talking.
But this is Tsuyuya, so...
I'm not talking.
Please come out.
Wow! You scared me!
Why?
Are you hungry?
What is this?
It's a gift for someone who won the quiz.
Oh, really?
It's a prize for me to be on a popular TV show.
Oh!
Did you happen to win this show?
How was your time with Sanma?
It was fun.
Oh, really?
You did comedy, right?
That's right.
Oh, I see.
Amemaman!
With Kanpei, right?
Yes, with Kanpei.
Oh, I see.
What do you think of Kanpei?
He's a wonderful person.
Do you really think so?
Yes.
Don't Jimmy and Kanpei have something in common?
Oh, really?
Don't they?
Jimmy is cute, but Kanpei...
Is he cute?
But he really likes sex.
When he went to Korea, he was doing it for 24 hours.
The other person was angry.
Let me at least eat something.
You're a bit too much.
Oh, really?
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I was surprised.
Now, let me introduce him.
This is Takada-san from Itabayashi-ku.
The other day, I saw him do the Kin-chan run.
What are you talking about?
Don't say things like that.
I've never seen it before.
I've never seen it either.
On the show, there was a request for people who are good at doing the Kin-chan run.
Hama-chan, please come out.
Hey!
I'll put this in.
This is going to be interesting for the first time in a while, isn't it?
No, it can't be.
It's like this.
Taisho is nervous, so it can't be.
This is a corner for you.
He even wrote his address.
If you can do the Kin-chan run, please come out.
Right?
Please come out.
Before that, you have to do the round rice.
You can do this right away.
I'll wait for you to do the round rice.
You don't have to wait.
I'll wait for you.
Don't do that.
The Kin-chan run, you're good at it.
I'm not good at it.
You're good at it.
Hang in there.
Are you talking to a stupid kid?
It's true.
You're good at it.
I don't need to do the round rice.
You can't do it.
You can definitely win.
I'm an amateur.
What are you talking about?
Are you a pro at the Kin-chan run?
All the people in front of the Kin-chan run are amateurs.
In front of the Kin-chan run?
That's not true.
I want an amateur to do it.
Do it now.
Do it.
You can do it.
Run.
Come on.
You can't do it.
What are you going to do?
Do it.
You can't do it.
There's no way you can't do it.
I don't really trust Nostradamus.
I don't know about that.
I don't think he'll quit.
Nostradamus is stubborn.
He thinks the moon is pointing at something.
Who's pointing at something?
He lines up the alphabet and reads it upside down.
Why would he read it upside down?
That's a long story.
I don't think that's true.
Really?
How many years until Earth?
How many years until now?
1,910 years.
1 year.
8 years until then.
What are we going to do?
We're going to blow it up.
You know what?
The big Earth is going to explode.
It's going to be a mess.
I want you to ride on it.
Are you sure you want to ride on it?
Of course I am.
I've never seen a place this small.
You're the only one who's excited.
There's no one else.
You want to ride on it.
You're wrong.
You're making me angry.
What's wrong with you?
You're wrong.
It might be small.
But I don't know if it's big enough for me to ride on it.
I'm going to be alone.
I don't know what to do.
But there's someone over there who's excited.
There's no one else who can do that.
What's wrong with you?
When it explodes,
who would want to ride on it?
I want to ride on it.
But I don't know if it's big enough for me to ride on it.
If it's big enough for you to ride on it,
how are you going to move forward when you're excited?
I don't know.
Can you move forward when you're excited?
I can move forward when I'm excited.
You're going to move forward on your own will.
You don't study the air resistance at all, do you?
I'm asking because I don't know.
When you go this way, it's like this.
It's true.
It's like this in the direction you want to go.
That's right.
What don't you know?
When you want to move forward, you know how to move sideways.
What do you do when you want to move forward?
I can't move forward.
I can move sideways, but I can't move forward.
So if you move forward, you can move forward.
What do you mean?
This is sideways, isn't it?
That's how you do it.
If you move forward like this,
if you move a little to the side,
it's like this.
Don't make it so complicated.
There's something like this.
This isn't right.
What do you do when you want to go backwards?
That's why.
That's why it's the same as before.
What should I do?
Try it.
Next time, do it like this.
Don't lie!
Are you kidding me?
What are you talking about?
Don't say it.
No one says it's going to explode.
Because in 1999,
something was falling from the sky.
What was falling?
That's why you look like an alien.
Are you laughing?
I'm laughing.
It's hard.
It's falling from a completely different place.
I'm laughing.
It's falling down.
It's falling down like this.
I don't know what it is.
Are you laughing?
I'm laughing.
There's nothing wrong with that.
I'm laughing, but what do you say?
I got this land.
I'm laughing.
But humans are all going to be killed.
Maybe.
I'm sure it's like that.
It's not my sense.
I'm an alien.
I want to draw with my imagination.
I think I have an eye.
I don't think I have an eye.
I have an eye.
It's a completely selfish human way of thinking.
I don't have an eye.
What kind of shape is that?
I have two hands and two legs.
I have an eye.
It's a completely human way of thinking.
I don't think it's like that.
I can't walk like this.
I can't walk.
It doesn't even look like a shape.
What kind of shape is that?
What?
It doesn't look like this.
It doesn't look like this at all.
It's a lump.
But it's a lump, but there's something.
What is something?
Something like this.
I don't know that.
What is something like this?
Is that a substitute for a hand?
I don't have a hand.
What is something like this?
What?
Where does it come from?
Something like this.
What is this?
What?
It's around here.
For an alien, it's a big bone.
What is it?
It's a man's bone.
It's a shape that I don't know.
It's scary.
When I first saw it.
It's scary over there, too.
When I saw it.
It's like this.
That's right.
It's scary.
When I saw it for the first time.
But there was something before.
An alien that came down from the UFO.
There was a picture of an alien that was captured like this.
That's why there aren't a single kind of aliens.
There are many kinds of them.
That's why the stock is close to humans.
Maybe.
I think my sense is this much.
It's my sense.
I think to myself,
If there are any living things, it's about this size.
Nothing serious.
There are about 50 million people here right now.
Such a small alien.
I don't know if there are about 50 million of them already.
How the hell are they doing, right now.
I don't know if they have already been here.
You're so tiny. Even if you had 50 million yen, it would still be scattered all over the place.
So, I don't think you're going to stick it to someone's ear.
I don't think so.
You mean, inside your ears?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Eh?
Scary.
You're so tiny.
I'm sure that such a tiny guy is very shocked right now.
Because he knows it's me.
I don't know if you have something inside your ears.
I don't know.
So, for example, if you have something under your ear, you would take it off right away, right?
Then, you might have something underneath your ear.
I would hide it quickly.
You would hide it quickly.
So, from now on, when you take off your earring, you'll look like a
No, no, no, no.
You'll be like a faint.
So, from now on, when you take off your earring, you'll look like a
You'll be relieved.
Ah, you'll take it off again.
So, you take it off once and take it off again.
Wow!
You should do that from now on.
Don't say that!
That was a coincidence.
I'm here!
Hello.
Well, Kin-chan, are you going to run?
Are you leaving already?
What is that all of a sudden?
What are you going to do at the end of the show and say, Kin-chan, are you going to run?
No, no, that's not something I should say today.
What is it?
Do your best.
No, I'm not going to go to the studio.
Why?
Why are you doing that?
Well, it's not that I'm going to the studio.
I'm going to be quiet in front of the TV.
Is that so?
Well, this is a new thing for you.
Wait a minute.
The new event is your rice ball, isn't it?
That's why I'm trying my best.
I heard that you got the rice ball, too.
Really?
Can I get it?
It's a rice ball.
What do you think? Do you have it?
I'll do my best.
No, no.
And I'm going to go to the studio.
You're going to run, aren't you?
All right, let's practice.
Next week's opening.
Hold the ground somewhere.
What are you going to do at the opening next week?
That's why you're going to run all the way on the ground.
I'll take you to the city.
Are you serious?
Yes, yes, yes.
With a tire on your waist.
I'm looking for a postcard and an assistant.
Everything is the same.
I'll be waiting for you.
Don't forget it.
Goodbye.
Theã£
sorry.
Oh, boy.
If you have thelogland, you can go to the set.
Come come come
That's probably what you think.