I don't want to go to court for being a Tare Panda
But it's embarrassing for you to go to court with such a serious face
I don't care about that!
Idiot!
It's completely different
What is it?
Hamada
You can't do this!
You can't do it right away
Have you ever done it right away after coming here for 10 years?
I haven't
There was Shigonchi
Shigonchi is short
It's been a long time
The reason why you can't do it right away is because
I've been thinking about it for the past 2-3 weeks
I found out one thing
What is it?
There is no gag
Don't say such a big thing
There is no need for a gag
So today
Even if Hamada thinks about it
It's a simple story
If you look over there, you can see
Today there is a god of gags
It's a thank you from the god of gags
Let's get it
Yamada-kun has a gag, right?
I have a lot
What is it?
Yay, yay, yay
I have a lot
Like this
For example, if you're walking on the street
You'll be told to smile
If you don't smile, you won't be able to do it
You won't be able to do it
I have a lot
You still have a lot
You have a lot
I have a lot too
Alice's Bikkuri Mankai
That was amazing
Matsumoto doesn't have a gag
You have a lot
I have a lot
Hoyo Hoyo's Pao
Please look forward to the second episode
This program is brought to you by the sponsor you are watching
Do you have any data from the past?
We have data
Are you ready?
First, let's see Tsukami's gag
This is definitely important
There are many
Dachou Club
I don't think this is interesting
But if you say no, it's Dachou
And this
Welcome
1, 2, 3
Is this a gag?
This is a gag
I'm just saying it to make you feel better
But at the end of the game, let's all do it together
That's right
Matsumoto
It's not a gag
I didn't hear it, but I just made it a gag
I'll do it
If you don't put it back in
It's bad
Let's put it back in
It's 36 yen
It's bad to say it's a gag
Daimyojin
Please
For your mother
Edo River, Tamagawa, Chinchin River
Wait, wait
Thank you
Where did you get that?
Edo River, Tamagawa, Chinchin River
That's not a gag
You don't want to do it, right?
It's not for us
Yamaguchi, how much did you put in?
36 yen
That's
If it was that little, you wouldn't be able to do it
It's 36 yen
You don't have money?
It's weird if I put it in
You put it in
Should we put in 500 yen?
Let's put in 500 yen
Let's put in 550 yen
Thank you
Edo River, Tamagawa, Chinchin River
You're skipping your nails
That was funny
I kept it
It's a different pattern
It's not a gag
I think Tsukami is like that
It's a gag using things
Kami-san
You just said it's like that
It was like that
It's a gag using things
For example, there's this
It's from a YouTuber
This is
If there's something like this, it's a joke
Is this a gag?
Worldwide
With this, Yuri Geller can eat for the rest of his life
That's right
Actually, we've prepared a lot of things
Really?
We've prepared a lot of things
Is it like this?
Don't pretend to be good
If it's Yamazaki, what will happen?
We can do it right away
Really?
Please tell us Yamazaki's gag
This is a prank
It's like this
It's a joke
If it's Kami-san
What will happen?
Is it okay if I don't do it?
I'm sorry
Is it okay if it's just Kami-san?
Please take care of Kami-san
Kami-san, it's wrong
It's completely wrong
Why did you do that?
I don't like this handbag
Kami-san, I'm sorry
Kami-san, it's wrong
It's not like Kami-san is thinking in advance
That's right
It's a gag
If you give it to him, Kami-san can do it right away
That's right
It's Kami-san
Kami-san, it's okay
Is it okay if I don't say his name?
It's okay
It's Kami-san's show
Please
He's not here
Kami-san
Wait a minute
Kami-san, please
He's here
Please take care of Kami-san
This is embarrassing
Kami-san, I'm sorry
As expected
Kami-san is amazing
Is it okay to say that?
I was waiting for him
Let's do this for the last time
I'll leave it to you
Please
Let's do this for the last time
I got hooked
Am I that?
Kami-san
I'm in trouble
I'm sorry
I didn't bring my ero today
I'm not good at talking
Kami-san
Kami-san's face is really bad
Kami-san, can I change it?
Is it okay?
That's right
Don't use it
I'll change it at the end
Kami-san will change it at the end
It's a good sentence
Don't throw it
I'm sorry
I didn't bring my ero today
Was it hard?
I'm coming to save you
Kami-san
I'm sorry
I'm lonely
He's trying to do everything
Kami-san
It's difficult to use things
Where is Kami-san from?
I'm Kami-san from Machiavelli
Is there a way to end it?
Yes
For example
That's right
I said it before
You can use it either way
Goodbye
That's right
Let's go
Let's get it
Kami-san is still here
Let's end it
I have to go back and take a bath
Kami-san
I don't know
So
Today
Will we meet again in 20 years?
I don't know
That was good
I'm happy
I'm really happy
Well
I'm crying
Please do it again
What did you say?
So
Tonight
In 30 years
I can't do it in 30 years
I can't do it in 20 years
The way you say it is totally different
I laughed at the end
Have a good day
That was good
Should we do the last one?
Let's do the last one
Today's talk is over
I'm going home
Why are you going home alone?
You're the only one left
Let's end it here
See you in 20 years