You're always doing these
stuff.
Besides Hamada, there's be a man who don't know anything but just a little of something.
He have been the most bad among all.
If others find it, I think he'll famous.
Thank you very much.
What is going to happen to Tomojo Matsumoto?
No, I haven't heard anything yet.
Well, I'm going to try it today.
Try what?
Well, I don't know if I can say it to an amateur, but it's serious shiragadori.
Matsumoto Shidoshi seriously challenges shiragadori.
It's a real Japanese sword.
Well, I'll take it.
Well, I don't think I should do that.
Well, it's serious.
I've been thinking about it for about two months.
Well, there's a guy called P-kun in Katanauchi.
Oh, P-kun.
Well, I'll ask him.
Well, it's dangerous.
I've been doing it seriously for 10 years.
I've never taken it seriously at all.
Are you all right?
No, I'm pretty excited.
If you can get the rating, you'll get it again.
No, there's no problem with the rating.
I don't know if it's one or two.
No, it's two.
Oh, it's two.
P-kun.
Masamune Mendo.
It's heavy.
How is it?
Well, I don't think everyone has seen it.
Well, it's a little small.
I don't like it very much.
Well, it's good.
It's nothing.
What?
It's two or three million yen.
That's amazing.
Ouch!
Are you all right?
It's dangerous, really.
The green one is better.
Oh, it's green.
I can't use this one today.
Whoa!
It's scary, it's scary.
It's scary.
Let's put that away for a moment.
Yeah?
What's this?
What do you want me to say?
I don't know.
Well, this is it.
Wow.
It's amazing.
There's Masamune-san.
He's a famous swordsman.
It's shining.
It's heavy.
This is heavy.
It's scary.
I'll turn it around.
I can't do this.
I'm in danger.
Don't do it.
I can't hold it like this.
What's that?
They don't make things like this anymore.
Yeah.
They can only be made in the mountains.
There are only two people who can make this in Japan.
P-kun and A-kun.
What?
I can't hold it like this.
Why are you crying?
That's it.
Who makes it like this?
You do it?
Yes.
I think I'll ask Hamada to do it.
What?
I don't think so.
I'll ask my partner to do it.
Hamada-san.
Hamada.
What?
I got it.
Try it.
I can't hold it like this.
He's more...
concentrated than I am.
I checked the speed.
That's right.
How fast?
Like this?
No, faster.
Anyone can do it.
Like this?
Faster.
Are you okay?
Amazing.
It was so fast.
Are you okay?
Do you want to talk today?
Yes.
What's so funny?
It's cold, so I'm happy to be inside today.
Him and her.
It's hard to wait outside.
The bath.
It's cold these days.
Do you take a bath in the spring?
I usually take a bath in the spring.
In winter.
I want to ask Dr. Matsumoto.
Ask me anything.
You can ask me anything.
I'm not a bad guy.
You can come if you want.
I'll send you a drink this year.
I've never thought of that.
You know, when you don't put bath salts in, you can't go in with normal water.
When you go in,
you can't go up.
There are a lot of children.
What's that?
That's the movie.
Did you watch the movie, Abyss?
No, I didn't.
There are a lot of creatures at the bottom of the sea.
There are a lot of creatures like that.
There are a lot of fairy-like creatures.
Why are you a fairy?
You're protecting the animals.
There are a lot of them.
It's like a stick in the mud.
What's wrong with that?
When you go in, you run away.
Why do you run away?
You're protecting them.
Water is weak.
You're weak.
You're protecting them, but you're weak against water.
What's wrong with you?
The enemy is too strong.
There are a lot of strange things.
Including you?
There are a lot of questions.
I went to a pet shop.
Do you know what happens at a pet shop at night?
I don't know.
There are only cats and dogs.
When that happen,
The pool will begin.
Gyo-san, you have a cat, right?
Yes.
I hear it go, meow meow meow meow.
First, the cat. The cat. The cat.
First, it starts.
After that, it goes,
woooow.
The tone is completely different.
The cat goes, meow meow meow meow.
So, the dog doesn't cover it.
The dog doesn't cover it.
Why?
It's like a dress with a tanned chest.
A female dog starts with a long hair.
That's a good one.
Animals speak, basically.
I don't know.
I don't know if they talk.
That's the same in the electric shop.
Everyone comes in at night.
Gyo-san, you have a stereo, refrigerator, and an iron, right?
Yes, I do.
If you have all of them, the party will start again.
How will it be?
It will disappear, right?
It will look like an interior.
Everyone will go home.
It will be dark, right?
Who's in charge of the speech?
It's Tansu.
Tansu?
Tell him to go to the refrigerator.
Tansu is in charge of the speech.
I went to the interior.
Sorry.
I went to the electric shop.
Who's in charge of the speech?
The iron is in charge of the speech.
It will disappear.
It will disappear, right?
Five iron will be gathered.
What's it like?
Nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan!
This year is already over.
It was good.
No, no, it's not over yet.
It's not over yet, is it?
Are you going home this New Year?
Home.
You're not going home?
Why?
Well, it's not like...
You're not going to see your dad or grandma, are you?
You're not going home, are you?
I'm not going home either.
You should go home!
You're just hanging around all by yourself.
What the hell is this?
You're just hanging around all by yourself on New Year's Day.
No, I'm going home.
You should go home!
You're so annoying!
Why?
My mom sometimes goes home at New Year's Eve.
It's the day before New Year's Eve.
Mom?
You don't have a man at all.
You have a slight beard.
When you're an old woman.
I have one.
You're not going home, are you?
I'm not going home.
It's New Year's Eve. You should go home.
You should go home!
No, I'm not going home!
You should go home. You should go home all by yourself.
No, I'm not going home.
You should go home.
I'm not going home.
Who told you that?
You're so stupid!
I'm going to go home.
I'm not going home.
You're such a pervert.
Don't lie to me!
Who are you talking about?
Just a shoe box is enough to make you go woooow!
You can't say that!
Why does that person have such a great house?
The toilet is also a great place.
Just the toilet.
It's really great, isn't it?
It's a toilet, so it's got a lot of dust.
Shut up!
But you don't take it either.
Don't mess with me.
I'm jealous.
What's that?
It's the toilet.
I've never seen it.
What are you talking about?
There's only one toilet in Japan.
It's great, isn't it?
What?
You're always like this.
If you say it's great, it's great.
But I don't think we're the same kind of couple.
I don't have anyone when I go home at night.
I'm hungry at night, right?
When I go home, I usually eat gombutoku.
I don't eat gombutoku.
By that time, you're already a Vivaldi.
Why?
I'm not eating anything like this, and I'm not listening to Vivaldi.
The pork is like this.
I'm not doing it.
Stop it.
I'm not eating pork.
Where are you?
I'm in the house.
I know.
If you open the oven, it's going to be like this.
It's going to be like this?
It's going to be like a silver-haired man in boots.
I'm not crying.
That's great.
I'm popular.
Where are you?
Where are you looking at?
But I'll think about it next year.
What are you talking about?
Next year, I'm going to buy land.
Buy it.
What are you talking about?
Get on more.
I'm going to buy land.
What are you talking about?
This is the front door, right?
Go-kun, come here.
What's wrong?
What?
It's okay.
How?
Is the front door there?
This is the front door, right?
Here?
It's going to be like this, right?
This is Hama-chan's room.
Why?
Why am I with Aikata-san?
I have a question about dogs.
My dog, Gon, died around 3 p.m. on March 15th this year.
That's fine.
You guys died at 3 p.m.
Don't laugh at me.
It's nothing.
He died at 3 p.m. on March 15th.
That's fine.
I have a question about dogs.
How long do dogs live?
I don't know.
How long have your dogs lived?
Dogs live longer if you buy them.
About 15 years.
Really?
They live longer.
They get attracted to cars.
How did your dogs get dirty?
What?
What's wrong with my dog, Per-chan?
I don't know.
Didn't your dog get dirty?
Don't say that.
The last one.
What?
My dog, Per-chan, was wearing a dress.
I told you.
It was moving.
My dog, Per-chan, was eating.
He ate all of them.
He ate them all.
What are you doing?
You ate them all.
I don't need your food.
I'm just waiting.
You're annoying.
The other day, I went to a bookstore and found a book written in 1994.
I took a look at the book.
On January 0, a foreigner might come to stay over.
That's good.
Will a foreigner come to my house?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Wait, wait.
Accept it.
I'm sure he'll come.
Do you have to write it like that?
A foreigner will come to stay over.
If it's correct, it's great.
It's great.
He'll come to stay over.
That's right.
I'll give him a room to sleep.
He'll eat breakfast.
I'll give him a bath.
He'll watch TV.
Scary.
You're scary.
Good morning.
Say that.
It's a nice night.
Mama.
What would you like to eat?
It's the next night.
Thank you for watching!