Hello.
What are you doing here?
It's really cold.
Today is the first time I came to Shinjuku.
Look at this.
This is a book store.
It's being sold very well.
Really?
The person who was wearing the clothes is also...
No, no, no.
It's the person who was wearing the clothes.
I see.
Take a look at this.
Last New Car.
The story of the sea in the month of the 15th.
The cameraman's hands are shaking.
It's amazing.
It's the first time I've been here.
What are you doing?
Doesn't this look a bit like Hamada?
Look at this.
There's a store all the time.
The cameraman is amazing.
Look over there.
What?
Boys Massage Plaza.
Oh, oh, oh.
If you listen to the story earlier,
It's a male version of Souplan.
When you go there, there are beautiful boys' pictures.
You can choose this.
Masato-kun, I brought you today.
I brought it.
Thank you very much.
Go.
Yeah.
I want you to put it on again.
But the book store is the most surprising.
That's how...
Now, now.
It's like this.
Really?
It's definitely dangerous.
I finally got away from that creepy, scary place.
Now.
This is the Bifran Theater.
This is today's venue.
Yes.
This program is Ooyama International Products.
Toyosui-san and.
Sponsored by the sponsor you are watching.
I'm surprised you came out suddenly.
There's usually a question.
It's a little weird.
You opened the curtain yourself.
It's unusual.
Yeah.
But let's do our best for 30 minutes today.
Is this the fourth time today?
That's right.
I'm going to do my best on the comedy show.
It's not a good show in the world.
There's no show.
There's a lot of dark news lately.
It's all about really bad cases.
Yes, yes.
Recently, there was an incident where I could laugh.
Inoki was added.
Stupid.
I can't laugh.
It seems that he held back his tears and talked for the rest of the time.
That's right.
It's scary.
I want that power.
That's true.
There's no funny show on TV these days.
Oh.
I hate Sazae-san in the anime.
That's a little stupid.
You're the most funny man in Japan.
But it's just one pattern.
Next week, Katsuo and Hanazawa-san will be done.
Stupid.
I can't watch it.
You did a good job like a child.
It would have been hard if Nakajima hadn't come out.
What kind of way does Nakajima come out suddenly?
He only plays baseball every day.
I can't stop thinking about manga.
Is that so?
It's cute.
When we were kids, we used to watch BEM.
That was interesting.
Three people come out.
BEM, BEM, BEM.
Yes, yes.
A family or someone I don't know.
They've been traveling all the time.
It's BEM.
BEM, BEM, BEM.
The child's voice.
Yes, yes.
He becomes friends with a local child.
He's very friendly.
Yes, he becomes friends.
When an incident happens, BEM transforms in front of his friend.
He's a monster.
When he transforms, his head looks like a butt.
And his body looks like Nika-Poka.
He puts his butt in here.
Yes, yes.
He goes wild.
Then he goes back to the child.
He's a scary guy.
Yes, he's a scary guy.
Then he goes back to the child.
Then he says to the child,
I'm sorry.
I lied to you.
Yes.
I'm not a human.
I can see that.
You've been a butt all this time.
He's joking.
He's joking even more with BEM.
BEM?
lesothia
I'm not a human being.
You know you are.
You're inside the butt.
Yes.
You think you're a human being,
but you're not.
BEM?
You're wearing tights and you're so skinny!
I was so angry.
You know, there are a lot of machines.
Like the neck-gel-ge, the brain-gel-ge, the yago-gel-ge.
And there are a lot of other machines that can be eliminated.
The most pitiful one was the neck-gel-ge.
When the neck-gel-ge came out, the title was pitiful.
The machine neck-gel-ge peeked out of the window.
It's not a big deal.
I don't think it's a big deal to get hit by a Barum-1 all the time.
It's just peeking.
The Barum-1's song.
It's a joke.
You're even talking about the song?
The song is a joke.
There are a lot of songs in the world, but it's a rare song that doesn't have that much content.
The super-human Barum-1.
It's not a big deal.
It's like the engine sound of a Barum-1 car.
I don't know the meaning of this.
You're running fast.
The machine neck-gel-ge.
I'm sorry about that.
You're running fast.
I don't know.
When I was a kid, I thought it was fun to be fooled like that.
I don't know anything because I'm a kid.
You asked your parents something you didn't know.
When I was a kid, I wondered how babies were born.
I can't help it.
You should ask your parents.
Parents should not destroy children's dreams.
Listen to me.
I'm not going to tell you.
A rooster flew in from the north sky.
If you do it with your mother, you'll be born.
You're lying.
It's midnight.
I don't think it's going to happen.
What's wrong with you?
Your mother and the rooster went into a love hotel after a meal.
I'm going to be born?
Yes.
After that, your mother was combing her hair in front of the three-faced bird.
She said, when can I see you?
What kind of world is that?
A white rooster?
It's a blue rooster.
Everyone has a dream when they're little.
That's true.
There's a lot of things.
That's right.
I want to be a baseball player.
There are many baseball boys.
There are many, but it's too much.
I'm a baseball player, but I'm a professional baseball player.
I don't like playing baseball.
I'm just throwing a ball.
There are a lot of people who want to do it.
It's the same for professional baseball, but it's amazing that it doesn't go up to one.
Especially in national baseball.
It's because the ball is wide.
There are a lot of players who quit in the middle.
Coach, I'm going to quit baseball.
All right, stop it.
Wait, hey!
Hey!
That's not it.
I quit baseball.
All right, stop it.
It's a race.
If it's the coach, I won't stop it.
I quit baseball.
What are you talking about?
All right, stop it.
I quit baseball.
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
What is this?
That's why you have to be more aggressive.
I can't do that.
What's that?
Gak!
Hahaha!
Where does it come from?
You're going to do it.
I'll do it.
Gak!
What did you say?
Coach, I'm going to quit baseball.
Gak!
What are you doing?
This is the name of the guy.
Convince him.
What?
What's wrong with the engine?
Stop it.
Then, my father's pyjamas...
I told you to stop!
Why should I stop at your place and wear my father's pyjamas?
I didn't tell you to stop at my house!
That's why I'm persuading you.
Tell me!
Huh? Tell me!
I don't get it.
Hey, what are you talking about?
Hey, you!
I see.
You're the supervisor, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
Look at that. What's that?
That's...
These are my pyjamas I've been wearing for the past three years,
whether it's raining or windy.
If you take them off, they'll get wet.
That's not the problem!
Wait!
It doesn't matter if you take them off!
I'm telling you to stop!
Let's go!
Stop properly!
What?
I got it.
There's a lot of ways to stop.
What are you talking about?
Huh?
What are you going to do about this?
It's sad and painful.
It happens to anyone.
In that case, take off your shoes.
Here?
Take off your shoes!
No, I quit.
I want to quit baseball, so...
Take off your shoes!
You're forcing yourself.
What do you mean, take off your shoes?
Take off your shoes!
You're forcing yourself.
What do you mean, take off your shoes?
Huh?
Okay, now you can...
What are you talking about?
I don't care who takes them off!
Who?
Huh?
There's a way!
If you watch TV, you can persuade them!
There is.
It's like a youth drama.
Yeah.
Okay.
Hamada, what are you saying?
I'm not saying anything.
Look at the sun.
That's right.
I'm telling you to do that.
What are you saying?
Look at the sun.
That's right.
What?
Hey, say it louder.
Hamada!
Yes!
Look at the sun.
Look at it better.
Okay.
My head hurt.
It's been a while since I heard this.
It's been a while.
How long have you been doing this?
About 10 minutes?
You haven't done it for 10 minutes?
Well, before I went to baseball,
I did it for 5 minutes.
What?
What are you doing?
I'm cleaning the mic.
Oh, really?
That's weird.
I didn't hear you at all.
I was surprised.
Hey, are you going to spill it on the staff?
Say it.
I'm going to do it.
Hey, we didn't know that either.
It came out suddenly from the side.
This is the staff's thing, right?
Someone.
They say they're on TV.
What?
It doesn't make sense.
Well, this...
Well, it did rain last week.
The assistant,
I said,
the guy who came to the country,
and it really came out.
I was deceived.
I've been sitting with the makeup artist for a long time.
Oh, really?
I'm a makeup artist.
I'm a makeup artist with a very exotic face.
Let's go with this.
This person is
This person is amazing.
He's from Matsudo.
Kamizawa Misako.
23 years old.
Do you remember?
Thank you.
Please put in about three people.
What does that mean?
I don't think it's a mean thing.
Please put in about three people.
I like Hama-chan.
That's what it is.
What kind of comment is that?
What is that?
That's good.
I like the cute lower lip of Hitomi Tsuburana.
I love it.
Let's play together next time.
This is also
Hamada's
this harsh comment.
I don't know if this is right.
Why?
I want you to soften it a little more.
The other day, when the show was on air,
towards Mr. Koutaro Satomi,
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to Mr. Koutaro Satomi of the country.
That's not it.
No.
I'm nervous when I'm next to you.
Why?
Stop it.
I want you to be more like an amateur.
Oh, me?
I want you to be a little more professional.
When Mr. Morio Kazama came from the other side,
he said to me,
There's a reason for the Super Cup.
That's right.
Let's hear the reason.
Stop it.
Please.
Mr. Koutaro Satomi.
Stop it.
When Mr. Koutaro Satomi was on the other side of the show,
he couldn't make it to the final.
The other people on the other show
were left with about four sets of finals.
They said they'd cheer for the winner.
We went to the 800th night.
We cheered for the show.
Koutaro satomi made a mistake three times in a row.
Koutaro satomi.
He made a mistake.
He was on the other side of the show.
It was a fast-forward quiz.
It's good to press the button.
When Koutaro satomi was reading the question,
he was like this.
Then he was like this from the side.
When I was reading the question,
I put my hand on the button.
He was like this.
Koutaro satomi was scared.
He was in a hurry.
I had to press the button.
When I pressed the button,
he was like this.
I didn't understand.
Then he was like this.
Stop it.
I want you to think about it.
I'll ask Mr. Kanagawa later.
Please be more gentle with him.
I was told that
he was a very good actor.
He often did a good job.
He hit the head of an amateur.
He was very good.
He didn't do it in a painful way.
He said something I didn't understand.
It's not common for an amateur to say that.
I didn't do it.
He is very good at
the Osaka TV program.
He is very good.
He was angry at the Osaka TV program.
I wanted to do it to Matsumoto.
But he was scared.
I was scared.
He hit my neck.
He was angry.
He was angry even if I didn't do it.
He hit my neck.
He was angry.
He hit my head.
I don't care.
I can't do that if I was angry at the Osaka TV program.
I'm very angry.
Wait a minute.
There are many people who get angry.
I'm angry because I'm angry
because I'm angry.
It's okay to be angry.
But you can't be angry at the Osaka TV program.
There are people who get angry at the Osaka TV program.
There is a place called Minestrone in front of the entrance.
I don't know if you can say it or not.
Minestrone.
Minestrone?
There is a hot soup.
I want to eat it.
When they came in, they hit me.
Minestrone hit my hand.
It's hot.
This is not good if it doesn't happen.
It's hot even in the middle of the airport.
Minestrone's melted onion was on the pan.
Look, it's hot! Half of it is hot!
And the feeling of an Italian who made the Minestrone!
What are you talking about?
I was also surprised by that.
There are a lot of them in Harada.
There aren't many in Tokyo.
I've been to Tokyo many times.
Really?
I've been on the train.
I know that there are a lot of them.
What are they doing?
When I got off at the station,
I wanted to leave the station as soon as possible.
There were a lot of people.
One of them hit me.
He said,
What the hell is this?
I looked at him and said,
You're a really bad guy.
I remember.
When I made my debut.
Don't tell me to get out of the way.
When I made my debut,
I was riding a car with him in Osaka.
When I started to appear on TV,
I didn't know if 100 people would notice me or not.
I was driving in the middle lane.
When I stopped at the traffic light,
a kind-looking man who looked like a salaryman
looked at me and smiled at me.
He pointed at my face.
He was smiling at me.
He was looking at me with a salaryman's eyes.
I was looking at him 3 times.
I was looking at him 5 times.
I was looking at him 4 times.
Are you a Kabuki?
I really don't want to do that.
I want to be more warm-hearted like Kin-chan.
What would you do if you were angry at me?
I was angry the other day.
I was in Osaka.
I was in a hurry.
I was fooled by a fool.
That's angry.
I have to put up with it.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
I don't want to talk about downtown on TV.
I released a record.
I see.
You idiot.
You released a 5-song CD before.
I did.
In October...
Stop it.
If I was asked if I had a record,
if I was asked if I had a record,
I would say,
I don't have one.
I don't have a good record.
It's over.
As you said,
I want to hear this kind of story.
I think it's okay to ask questions.
That's right.
It's my first time.
I heard this happened.
Please tell me in detail.
That's good.
A girl appeared today.
I was surprised.
That's amazing.
I was really surprised.
That's right.
The other day,
you didn't say the age limit.
That's right.
What is the age limit?
From what age to what age?
Yes.
What do you do?
Isn't this live?
Yes.
I don't care about the age.
That's not good.
What are you?
How old are you?
What is your strike zone?
What kind of strike zone is this?
I'm the assistant of the program.
The strike zone is about 15 years old.
Is that so?
It's not that.
What kind of strike zone is this?
I'm over 18 years old.
Over 18 years old.
20 years old.
Well...
8 years old?
I think so.
Are you over 8 years old?
I don't think you're over 18 years old.
There's a change here.
I don't know much about people over 18 years old.
I don't care if you know or not.
I'm the assistant of the program.
That's right.
Let's say you're 18 years old.
That's not good.
Let's say you're 30 years old.
I don't care if I'm 30 years old.
Let's say you're over 18 years old.
I'm the assistant of the program.
From 18 years old to 30 years old.
30 years old.
That's a lot.
From 18 years old to 30 years old.
Let's say you're over 45 years old.
Let's say you're over 50 years old.
I'll introduce you next week.
Thank you.
This program is Ooyama International Products.
Ooyama International Products.
Sponsored by the sponsor you see.