Please look forward to it.
We're going to have a punishment game.
Kouhaku, who's going to win?
This is strange, isn't it?
I'm going to get angry at Osaka.
There's no such word.
Who's going to win?
Who wrote this?
I don't know. Raise your hand.
It looks like Mr. Tamao.
What?
Idiot.
This is the 42nd NHK Kouhaku Song Contest.
We have all the participants.
I'm writing it down.
There are a lot of first-time participants.
Who are they?
I heard about them a while ago.
Who is Smokey Mountain?
I don't know him at all.
There's something strange in the red.
Who is it?
Who is Sarah Brightman?
Who knows Sarah Brightman?
I don't know.
Who is Sarah Brightman?
The song is Love is Over.
Why now?
This became a topic.
What song is this?
Iruzuku Machikado.
The town's colouring.
That's it.
Who is Sawada Chikako?
Let's go to the sea of this year.
This guy is not going to wake up, is he?
I don't know if he's going to wake up on the same day.
He's going to!
You idiot!
If you're this old, you should have gone to bed early.
You should have gone to bed the day before.
Is that so?
Of course.
I've been watching this for a long time.
There's no basis for this.
But as a winner,
I think the white one is a bit more advantageous.
But the order is not clear yet.
That's true.
So it's very hard to predict.
It's lined up in that order.
That's right.
So it's not a big deal who's going to win the first round.
That's true.
If you can do this, I want you to set it up for me.
The order.
If I were to set it up,
I'd have to grab the first round.
That's right.
Smokey Mountain.
Why?
I don't know.
I'm going to say it's a big deal.
The big bird is Andy.
I don't know why, so I'll just say it's hard.
I think it's red.
Red.
I think this is the problem.
The red group.
Wada Akiko.
You did the 6th round, right?
I didn't know if I could get out.
I think Akiko will cry after he's won.
He said he would.
I did it this far, and I wanted to go, but I can't sing.
I'm going to cry.
And then everyone will cry.
I don't know about that.
I'm going to cry.
I have a brother.
Jin, Jin, Jin.
Yes.
I have a brother.
I see.
Wada Akiko comes out when he's going to cry, and when he says,
Jin, Jin, Jin, it's going to make everyone cry.
That's true.
I've seen it many times.
You're red.
Red.
You got it right.
I got it right.
There was no problem at all.
Yes, yes, yes.
I got it.
Now, what are we going to do if we lose?
It's a penalty game.
It's been a while.
I can't decide.
I've been thinking about a lot of things.
We've decided.
Let's get rid of the other programs.
That's how it started.
One more thing.
Bad reaction.
I've been thinking about a lot of things.
Color bar.
Yes.
Challenge the color bar.
What time does the TV show end on Sunday?
It ends at half past two.
And the next reunion is probably about five o'clock.
About five o'clock.
About five o'clock?
Yes.
In the meantime, we have two and a half hours.
That's right.
In the meantime, part of it, about five minutes.
Whichever way you bend it, it turns into a color bar.
Beep.
We're still negotiating.
We haven't gotten permission yet.
We don't know yet.
If it doesn't work, the TV show will end on Sunday.
Then, in the picture.
A pigeon will come out.
Let's run away.
Whichever way you bend it, it turns into a color bar.
It's early in the morning, though.
Yes.
What time does it end?
About four o'clock.
In the world of three o'clock or four o'clock.
If I lose, what will you do?
I'm fine.
Don't come.
You're coming home again?
Of course not.
That's right.
I'll go even if you lose.
Absolutely not.
That's not possible.
I think that's what the show is about.
What kind of punishment game is that?
One hand in the same place.
Why are you crying?
Ladies and gentlemen.
It's different from usual, isn't it?
Well, it's the first time I've done something like this in a proper studio.
It's the first time.
It's disgusting.
It's disgusting, isn't it?
Let's go home early.
It's too far.
The other day.
Yes.
What are you doing?
I'm not being looked down on as a character.
I'm being looked down on a little by little.
You know, I feel like a woman.
What are you talking about?
I feel warm.
Idiot!
I'm being looked down on.
You're like a murderer.
What are you talking about?
I went into a convenience store.
There was a middle school girl.
She was wearing a hat.
I didn't know what she was wearing.
There was a girl in her first or second year of junior high school.
She was looking at me.
I thought she was looking down on me.
She was looking down on you.
She was looking for you.
She was touching my skin and leaving me.
She was looking at me.
I thought she was looking down on me.
I was wondering what would happen next.
She took off my hat.
She took off my hat and hit me on the head.
You're a weakling.
I'm a weakling.
She hit me on the head.
I couldn't take it anymore.
She was a girl.
I couldn't get angry at her.
She came to me.
She took off my hat.
I went home.
I was in a taxi.
I thought I couldn't get angry at her.
I thought so.
Hamada is amazing.
Why?
You don't have to go fast.
What are you doing?
It's hot.
Wait a minute.
She was laughing at me.
I was wondering what would happen to Hamada.
Nitta, me and the taxi driver were thinking about it.
You're a liar.
The driver has nothing to do with it.
She is amazing.
It's your specialty.
What kind of actress is she?
For example,
Hamada, I'm always watching you.
It's not like that.
I'm a weakling.
A weakling?
What kind of situation is this?
I'm a weakling and a weakling.
I'm a big fan of yours.
Really?
If you say so, it's okay.
It's okay.
Hey, motor!
Don't play with me!
I'll be angry.
Hamada came to me.
She said,
Hamada, let's go.
I said,
Ha ha ha ha.
Come here.
It's hard to talk.
It's okay to talk.
But if you are beaten up,
Normally, when humans come to us,
we don't get angry immediately.
If we don't get angry on the spot,
we go home, calm down,
think about it,
and get angry.
That's true.
You're a little different.
In that sense, you're just a foreigner.
Why?
I'm you.
I'm not a big fan of you,
but I hate you very much.
I said too much.
I'm sorry.
You're a little different.
In that sense, you're just a foreigner.
I'm sure.
I met you in Osaka a long time ago.
You had a fight with a taxi driver.
I stopped you at first.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I was angry.
I'm sure.
What?
I'm still angry.
I'm sure.
It was nine years ago.
What?
When I was still living in Osaka,
I was treated like a child.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
I asked you to get in the taxi.
I went to the station.
I thought it was bad because it was a one-meter distance,
but I asked you to do it.
What?
Can I get on the bus from there?
I came here.
After the customer left, the customer came out,
so I can't get on the bus with him.
That's not cool.
I said I'm sorry.
Get on the bus.
I'm sure.
Are you angry?
Why are you angry?
Then you got on the bus.
You came to stop the bus, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
You came to stop the bus.
Stop the bus.
I asked you what you meant by getting on the bus.
Why are you angry?
The two of us were angry.
But when you're angry,
you feel scared.
What?
You look like a child,
but you're really strong.
That's not true.
That's right.
It doesn't matter.
You're a scaredy-cat.
You're still a kid.
You were on the JR train from Osaka Station.
Give me a hand.
I know that.
What are you talking about?
You can't do that.
I said, let me do it.
We were in the middle of the train.
I said, let's get off at the next station.
He ran away at the next station.
No, you got off.
Don't say that.
You ran away, didn't you?
You're mistaken.
I got off and hit here.
Don't say that.
I don't care about your life, Hamada.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to get killed.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
Do you know what happened yesterday?
There was an announcement.
The wife of the vice-principal said,
When was the last time you kissed?
I'm going to get killed.
You're going to get killed.
I don't care.
There were complaints from the Iranians.
What?
They were like this.
What are you talking about?
The Iranians?
Yes!
They were watching TV like that.
Is that so?
If I say that here, my wife will call me.
Well, it was not before that.
My dick is so small that I can cut it.
There's no way you can make a mosaic like this.
My dick is so long and wide.
Stop it!
Setagaya-kun, Nakayama-kun, good evening.
I have a question for you.
Bun-yo-yo-yo-yo-yon, Bin-yo-yo-yo-yo-yon, Bun-yo-yo-yo-yo-yon.
Which one do you think is the most pleasant?
Bin-yo-yo-yo-yon.
It doesn't look interesting at all.
You're still not satisfied.
Which one is the most interesting out of these three?
Which one is interesting?
Bun-yo-yo-yo-yo-yon.
You're still not satisfied.
I can't make a mosaic like this.
Bun-yo-yo-yo-yon.
It doesn't look interesting at all.
Bin-yo-yo-yo-yon.
Do you want to try this?
It doesn't look interesting at all.
Bun-yo-yo-yo-yon, Bun-yo-yo-yo-yon.
You're still not satisfied.
Which one is the most interesting out of these three?
It doesn't look interesting at all.
Bun-yo-yo-yo-yon.
Bun-yo-yo-yo-yon, Bun-yo-yo-yo-yon.
It doesn't look interesting at all.
She's a bit...
Hey!
You there!
What was that?
I just had a sensei like that.
Oh, you did?
She's like...
She's like a hated...
Like a pig.
If she's like that,
everyone will hate her.
I'm sorry for this guy.
His parents will hate him too.
Everything will be over.
It'll be hot.
First of all,
it's best to
make her look like a pig.
That's the best.
Right?
It's too much to make her look like a pig.
I think it's best to make her look like a different person.
I see.
Like changing her hobbies.
Don't show off.
Let's make her look like a different person.
Let's decide the time and place for the date.
We can go to Shibuya or Hachiko-mae.
Let's go to a place like that.
Before everyone is watching.
Don't dress like that.
It'll be embarrassing if you're with her.
If you're with her,
you'll be embarrassed.
That's the best.
What do you think is best?
First of all,
she's like...
She's like...
She's like a woman.
You're overreacting.
Why?
It's strange.
She has a big body.
She has a big sword.
She has a big shield.
She has a big chest.
First of all,
she has high heels.
She looks like a woman.
She's like a woman.
If she's with you,
you'll probably never see her again.
Definitely.
You should say that.
I don't know if it's right to say she's lame.
Right?
Cut.
When does this happen?
Doesn't it happen when you do something bad?
When a little child...
What?
When a child does something bad.
Didn't you use it?
Don't ask me that.
Don't you know?
I know.
How do you usually use it?
I don't usually use it.
Why do you use it in the New Year's party?
When it's all excited,
it's about time
to have a Takeda-kun
do a Tsumuten-ten.
to have a Takeda-kun do a Tsumuten-ten.
Look, this year
there is a child called Ohirachi.
You called Takeda-kun.
So go ahead.
I don't want to see that.
You don't want to make fun of me again, do you?
No, no, no.
I don't know.
I don't know how to do a Tsumuten-ten in the New Year's party.
You've seen it before, haven't you?
No, I haven't heard of it.
Just try it.
Is this how you do a Tsumuten-ten?
It's not funny at all.
I don't know how to do it.
When you said you'd do a Tsumuten-ten
in the New Year's party,
I couldn't see your stupidity.
You couldn't see it?
Can't you see my stupidity even if I'm doing a Tsumuten-ten in the New Year's party?
So do it.
What are you going to do with a Tsumuten-ten?
I can't make a stupidity that you can't see.
Cut this letter.
Look,
it's going to be a long talk.
This is it.
This is going to spread.
When I was in kindergarten,
I was playing in the playground
and I fell from my head
when I got on the car's hood.
At that time,
there was a dog poop and I was saved.
My friend saw me with dog poop on my head
and I ran away.
When I went home crying,
my grandmother put water on my organs and wiped it for me.
It's a long story.
Before I go to this school,
I want to make a complaint.
Yesterday, you said,
Oh, this guy is stepping on dog poop.
Who is the dog?
I decided.
In that area,
there are only dogs and cats.
Is that so?
What is there?
Who is doing it on the street?
There are also insects.
You know dog poop.
If you do dog poop,
I don't know.
If you look at the dog poop,
it's all mine.
But you don't poop that big.
I don't know.
What kind of insect?
Do you poop bigger than your body?
I don't know.
Where were these small insects?
There are a lot of insects.
They all come together
and get together.
I don't know.
The small insects are
the same as the big insects.
What kind of man are you?
Are you human?
You poop on the street.
I don't know if there are such insects.
I don't know if you are a dog.
You are a dog.
It's a dog poop that fell
from the car bonnet.
You poop in such a place.
I don't know if you are a woman.
You can't be a woman.
I said that to you
to check who is a man
You can't be a woman.
There are many animals that poop.
There are a tiger, a hyena, a rhino, a elephant, a giraffe...
There are many animals.
That's not true.
There are no animals in the park.
Why?
I don't know.
No, I didn't.
I'm coming.
I've seen it before.
It started again.
So, please don't decide with dog poop.
I want to talk about that first.
Well, it's dog poop, but...
What? That's what you're thinking?
That...
I've never said,
I've never said I've never Θve to say it.
I've never said I'll never show my feelings.
He said it's too cold.
So I said,
You're too cold.
And he
That was nothing.
I had nothing.
He really is short of information.
The carrier is covered with skin.
I was with the carrier.
I had nothing.
I had nothing at all.
Dude,
If you don't don't don't
Don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't