Please get along with me
I can't get along with you
I'm sweating so much
The most important event of the new year is the comic contest
Number 9
Matsumoto?
Yes
Congratulations
No matter if you win or lose, it's important to win the competition
Number 1
Okamanya! Okamanya!
This is how the 6 teams were decided
Hamada and Endo's team
Matsumoto and Okamasa and Shishio's team
Yamazaki's Trio and Tanaka's Pinguet
A fun face-off
Endo!
And the top batter is this duo
The two of them went to look for their father's child
And ended up finding Endo's a**
How did this cowardly skit come about?
Let's take a look
This year has come again
It's the year of the new king
Look at this, there's a lot of stuff
What should we do?
Should we do it alternately?
For the two of them to do a skit, they will do it alternately
But the problem is, what kind of skit will they do for the new year?
That's the biggest problem
This is the one that looks like a dog
Probably
What is this?
Hamada's idea was to use Endo's a**
Endo's a**
Endo, are you okay with that?
I'm fine
I think it's funny
The front is a bit unnatural
It's open
Should I wear the jersey on the front?
You can wear it like this
I took it out earlier
How is it?
The training went smoothly, and the snake year skit is complete
Don't move
The theme is snake year
It's finally time for the two of them to appear
Hello
It's the 21st century
I was thinking of doing my best
But everyone is saying 2001
Please come to Shibuya
Everyone is saying 2001
What? Who is saying that?
Endo, don't move
Endo
What's wrong?
There's a moon
Hamada-san, this is a**
Thank you
What is this?
You guys are the worst
With the dirty strategy of the top batter
It became difficult to do it
Other combinations with amateur staff
This year, more than 0 years
Many combinations have slipped
Tanaka, who decorated the bird, is also in this situation
After all, you couldn't win
Among them, Yamazaki was the worst
There was such a reason behind that cold and broken skit
While other combinations were doing well
Yamazaki Toh
He doesn't want to do it at all
I can keep it
That's right, I know that
I'm frustrated with that
As expected, Heipo is also in a hurry
He can't hide his frustration
What is that?
Saigo-san, what are you doing?
Don't be serious
That's it
Master, please
What is the suggestion that Yamazaki made?
To be honest, ad-lib
All of them?
Yes
This is the result
You bastard
This is the first time in the 21st century
It slipped
Only once in 4 years
Among them, Matsumoto and Okama characters
The combination of the broadcast writer Shiono, who was noticed
Shiono, who represented the Shidoni Olympics
Shiono made a lot of jokes and invited the audience to laugh
What was behind the scenes?
I wiped the salt
The meeting with Matsumoto began
Shiono is confused
In the name of a foreigner
I only say the kanji of the Shimo
I can't say such a thing
I can't say the name of the curry
Curry Lewis
Shiono made a mistake
I wiped the salt
The joke of Shiono was completed
Matsumoto
Shiono
Together
Together?
I didn't turn off the lights and put on the gloves
I wiped the salt
Can you speak louder?
You are so real
You are a technician
You are a fool
What are you doing?
But that was completely one
Shiono, who hasn't shown it yet
What kind of combination will be born next year?
Don't fall in love with me
Hamada's
Hamada's ears
Don't fall in love with me
It's like an influenza
You have a hoarse voice
I also have a hoarse voice
I don't know the difference between an influenza and a cold
I have a hoarse voice
At that time, I will continue to wear gloves
Please accept it
I want you to be my companion
I don't have a hoarse voice
I still have a hoarse voice
I'm almost healed
I will be a great master
I don't know which is the master
There is always a master
After this, I will be a great master
You are bigger than that
I have a hoarse voice
Do you have something?
I have something
I was investigating the
What?
I don't care
I don't care if you have a hoarse voice
It's not something that can be improved
It's not
What is NHK?
This is a big problem
This is a difficult thing
The more we appear, the lower the hoarse voice
It can't be helped
People often think
Are you okay?
What is that?
It can't be helped
What is it now?
I want to improve
Do you want to improve?
I want you to do a real exchange
Who is the most beautiful?
Everyone is kind
But the kind is justice
The courage to fight is also justice
You have to fight when you fight
I don't care
It's the talent's courage
You have to fight when you fight
It's easy to get hated
You don't have to be poisonous
You're angry
You don't give up
It's not like that
I don't know what you're talking about
We have to move forward
I really want to show my heart
It's pure
I don't know
I cry when I see a puppy
I don't know if you understand that
I'm sad that the people don't have the power to see that
Who do you ask to do the NHK exchange?
The people who watch NHK
They're old
But the young people do it
But the young people don't do it
Even if you want to be hugged
At the time of posting
You will be the label as an ordinary woman
If you don't want to be hugged
You will be called a pervert
You are the woman whose chilli applicants don't want to be hugged
That's forgetful
There's the consideration problem
You're not going to say you are angry
No
Why do you like Takuya Kimura so much?
That's true.
You can't help but want to see him!
Do you want to see him that much?
That's not in the numbers.
I said I want to see him!
Get out of here!
If you put up the internet at 9pm...
It looks hot.
It looks really hot.
What do you like about him?
That's not in the numbers.
It's in the 30s.
I think I'm more refreshing.
I think he's more refreshing.
Do you like him that much?
If he's here, I don't think so.
He's next door.
It's true.
When I said I wanted to see him...
It's a little strange.
I understand that.
He doesn't do anything on Wednesdays at this time.
I didn't think I needed that kind of technology.
But I found out that I can do the magic trick.
Wait a minute.
You can't win against Ikkoku-do.
I was watching Ikkoku-do the other day.
I thought he was amazing.
I thought I'd give it a try.
I can't do it.
I'm surprised.
To be honest, I can do it, so I can't laugh.
I can't move my mouth.
What do you want me to say?
I'll do it.
Stop it.
You're amazing today.
You're not moving your mouth.
I'm not moving my mouth.
Close your mouth.
I can't move my mouth.
You can't move your mouth.
You do it.
Like this?
You're amazing today.
I can't move my mouth.
You're not moving your mouth.
You're amazing today.
I did it, right?
You're not moving your mouth.
I'm not moving my mouth.
I can't move my mouth.
It's not open.
This is how you talk.
I can't do that because I'll only look at my mouth.
If you close your mouth like that, it'll close.
The one with the time difference
I love you
No, but...
No, it's done
I'm fashionable, so it's done
Today too, with Matsuki's card, you can buy things
It's finally here
With 7 special benefits, Matsumoto Kyoshi member card
You can get the card for free
You have to enter
Hey, don't they look like they have a fever?
Hey, look, they have a fever
Look, they're coughing
Listen to me for a moment
Let's talk about it when we catch a cold
The wind is so persistent
At that time, Perak's cold medicine
Only Matsukiyo
Gold chip star
Do you know this?
This time the gold is...
Super hot
Hot and spicy
Spicy chili
Wow
Nabisco chip star
New flavor on sale
Gorgeous
I'll take this
Can you fight for 24 hours?
Literally
From noon to midnight
From dawn to noon
I'll hit you without a break
This is Amdes Fighting Festival
Tomorrow's Marumiere
It seems to be similar
Hey, is it expensive?
Various
I want to, I want to, I want to
Room, room
Looking for a room
Hey
Household information
Humanity
From Dekrute
Change the destination of the car
A completely new way of thinking
131 people died in an accident
The man survived unscathed
What do you think it means?
Are you ready to know the truth?
Unbreakable
I have a question for the vice president of the World Bowling Association
Yes
It is said that there were four holes in the bowling ball
At that time, what were you putting in the fourth hole?
After all, what you don't need will disappear
Right?
Before the bowling was so popular, it was necessary at first
Four?
Yes
Now it's like this
It's like this
Right?
Now it's like this
In the old days
In the old days, there was another small one here
There was a small one around here
Why is it so far away?
What?
It was under here
It was to put your fingers in, right?
No, it was to put your fingers in
It was for different purposes
No, it was for different purposes
What was it for?
I put some soy sauce
And
The rain was sticky
No matter what kind of food you make, you must never compromise
That's true
Please tell us three important tips to make the best ramen in Japan
Can I say this?
Why?
To be honest, it's the best business
I'll tell you
This is a big problem in the world
Is that so?
Yes
I don't know if it's better to turn off the sound
Ramen Jiro
Do you have it?
I've been here a few times
It's thick
But I want to eat it again
What kind of soup is it?
Do you have some?
Ramen Jiro is fine
But I don't know what it tastes like
When I was eating it, it was so big
But when I looked at it, Jiro was hiding
No
Really
Jiro was hiding?
Yes
Jiro was hiding
I couldn't see it for a second
What do you mean by Jiro was hiding?
It was in my head
Think about it
The name of the ramen shop is the name of most people
What does that mean?
I want to catch the person who makes the best soup
It's not fair
You can't just use that person's name
The name of the shop is not important
This is really true
If you want to make ramen, please consult
But you don't know who makes the best soup
That's right
That's why the best soup is ***
That's why
Catch it
You might make a mistake
It might be spicy
Wash it
Wash it before you put it in
If you wash it, it will be soaked in the soup
That's right
You have to make it delicious
You should have looked at it while you were running the shop
Jiro was hiding
He was trying to run away
That's right
I think that's why people say it's a ***
You say that you can't say this
This is a corporate secret
You can't say that
Because it's a person
The name of the store is correct
It's covered with ***
This is the goal
No.7
Designed, now on sale
Apex Tracks
Onizawa Onizawa
There are so many good cars
Which one are you talking about?
No, it's not a Nano Road
If you choose a car, it's a habit
Car Sensor Recruit
Water shine that the lips have dreamed of
New appearance in Maybelline Water Shiny
Finally 80% water shine
Slippery stretch, look at the water flowing and shining
Don't you want to burst with the sparkle of water?
From Water Shiny Maybelline New York
Maybelline
Hello Swiss
What should I do with the car insurance?
40% off?
Until the accident?
It's not just an accident
From now on, car insurance
This is it
Hello?
Hello Swiss
Yes, it is a utility fee
Oh, it's not a utility fee
I changed it to a cheap one
It's completely different
I don't know what it tastes like
It's better to be delicious
The middle high of the high
After all it's here
The realm of possibility exists here
It's a lifetime of excitement and shock
Give her another chance
For me
Sixth Sense's Harley Joel Osmond
Pay Forward The Kingdom of Possible
Question
Why is the A-class donut less effective?
Answer
It's because it's a double-layered structure
Is this the image?
That's right
I see, I see
A-class donut
Evolving in an instant
Bridgestone
People who repair cars often lie down and lie under the car
What are you doing?
If I had to say
After all, there's no way you can do that much
I've asked for car repair
Those people work really hard
That's because they like cars
For a living
For work
Of course they have that kind of pride
But even so, they work too hard
Is that so?
Yes
I've thought about it a lot
I looked at it
That thing
It's sucking in car juice
It has a story
It's supposed to be sweet
You've never tasted it
Apparently it's sweet
It's the sweet smell of Tokonatsu's coconut
What's with the car juice?
If you ask me what car juice is
The story is over
It's there
You turn on the engine
What's so good about it?
It doesn't matter if it's a parking lot
You turn on the engine for a while and leave it alone
You move it and look at it
The car juice is coming out
It's that
If you leave it alone
The car juice is coming out
Is that car juice?
It's amazing
It's sweet
Is that sweet?
It's not sweet
You've never drunk it, right?
I have
What are you talking about?
There's a lot of azuki
I don't think many people know that it's sweet
Really?
But there's no way sweet juice comes out of the car
Why?
Where's the sweet juice?
Where's the sweet juice in the car?
You really don't know anything
I don't know
I'll tell you
Where does the sweet juice come from?
It's raining
There's a bit of sugar in the rain
There's no sugar in it
The power of the wiper is amazing
From the tip of the wiper
While doing this
It comes out
Sugar
There's something wrong
You put gasoline in it, right?
Yes
It's that time
There's usually something sweet in it
It's like a tank
You open the lid and do it
While doing that
You put something sweet in it
What is this?
Have you ever been angry?
What did you put in it?
You didn't put on your glasses
Please don't say this on TV
Aoyama
If you look at it, it's sweet
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching
Weekly Gaten
From Recruit
X-Trail Jam in Tokyo Dome
On February 3rd and 4th, the snow falls on the Tokyo Dome
Charismatic snowboarder Tery Han Kosei's appearance is decided
X-Trail Jam, a collaboration of sports and music
Tickets are on sale
The realm of possibility exists here
It's a lifetime of emotion and shock
Give her another chance
For me
This is a performance by Harley Joel Osment of X-Sense
Pay Forward, the realm of possibility
Every scene has a reason
Every scene has a trap
Do you know the truth?