Thank you very much!
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
I'll think of something new.
Can you make a big movement of a new game from this program?
Sure.
What kind of game do you want?
Let's start with rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
I can only say rock-paper-scissors.
No one can do that.
You want to win, don't you?
I can't think of anything.
It's hot.
It's strange that I can only say rock-paper-scissors.
So I have to turn the game around, right?
Turn the game around.
Why do I have to turn the game around?
Rock-paper-scissors.
You win.
I win.
Sorry, can I say the broadcast code?
What?
It's not funny at all.
What is this?
If you don't change the game from there, nothing will change.
That's right.
I'm in trouble.
You play rock-paper-scissors, right?
If you lose, you lose.
If I lose, it's your fault.
I can't say I won here.
If I say I won, I have to say the broadcast code.
Do you understand?
If I can't say it, the broadcast code will continue.
What does that mean?
Rock-paper-scissors.
Let's do it.
You win.
I won.
You can't sell this.
What if I do it over and over again?
Let's do it over and over again.
But there are times when you can't say it, right?
Let's decide that.
Why can't I say it?
You can't say it?
I don't want to say it.
Let's do it like this.
Let's do it.
Wait.
What is this?
I did it like this.
I don't think so.
Let's do it.
Okay.
Rock-paper-scissors.
You win!
Take this!
Rock-paper-scissors.
You can't say it.
When you can't say it, you can't say it.
Let's do it.
Rock-paper-scissors.
You can't say it!
You can't say it.
Rock-paper-scissors!
Can you see it?
What do you think?
It's better than I expected.
I'm surprised.
Let's play with faces.
What kind of face?
The face of the theme I said.
This shop is...
I thought this shop was bad.
I couldn't go in because it was a neighborhood.
I happened to be there.
I went in and ate it.
It was delicious.
That's your special face.
No.
You did that before.
I said, do it.
That face.
Please.
Are you going to do everything from the beginning?
Just the face?
You did it from the beginning, so I'll do it from the beginning.
Just the face.
Here we go.
I'll just have that face.
It's totally different.
It's a big face.
That's the face of a regular customer.
The regular customer is always delicious.
The regular customer eats like this.
It's always delicious.
It's a face that says, it's delicious.
It's totally different.
I'm sorry.
I'll just have the face.
Me?
5 seconds.
That's the face when you see something.
It's totally different.
Hey!
It's 100 points to you!
That's not the face when you eat it.
No.
That's the face when you see your parent's sex.
You're an experienced person.
Don't have to act.
I don't need it. I don't need it. I don't need it anymore.
Let me do it with acting.
I don't need it. I don't need it anymore.
Okay, let's go.
I don't need it. I don't need it.
I don't need it when I say aah.
I don't need aah either.
Please.
Okay, 5 seconds. 4, 3, 2, 1. Cut.
I'm sorry.
Don't look at your parents' sex and accept it.
On the round part of the tip of the nose...
Ah, Matsumoto-san said that he's putting 100 million yen's insurance on it.
The other day, I thought there was no one there, so I was playing with my nose.
Suddenly, a person came in and I thought it was cool.
I was playing with my nose, and Matsumoto-san told me how to play with a cool nose that can be easily fooled by people.
You play with your nose, right?
I play with it.
There are times when I put it in like this, right?
I'm getting angry.
I put my finger in like this.
What is this round thing inside?
There's something round.
I've never put my finger in like this.
It's like it's spinning.
It's scary.
It's supposed to come off, but it's like this.
It's like this.
It's a little stuck on my nose.
There are times when it comes out like this.
Why?
Why did you do that?
I thought I shouldn't make my partner look stupid.
How do you fool people?
With a cool nose.
How do you fool people with a cool nose?
Do you want me to teach you how to fool people with a cool nose?
Yes, please.
For example, in a car, like I said earlier.
Let's say the traffic light is waiting for a signal.
If you look at it, the guy next to you is looking at you.
This is bad.
It's bad.
At that time, let's open the window.
It makes it easier to see.
Let's open it.
Let's be clear.
I didn't cheat on you.
Don't bite me.
It's a cool way to fool people.
That's right.
I didn't cheat on you.
I'm telling you clearly.
Then...
I was cheating on you.
Don't talk to me.
Don't make me think I didn't do it.
I understand.
Don't talk to me.
Open the window.
What is this?
Is this your first experience?
No, no.
I put it in here.
I put it in here on my own will.
What is this?
Is that so?
That's the most...
This person...
The person who was told that.
This person doesn't even know that his nose is smelly.
That's why.
He's a strong person.
Strong.
That's no good.
He's like a prince.
I don't want to be called a prince.
I have a question for your mother, Matsumoto.
How hard is it to give birth to a child?
What is it like?
Please tell me in detail.
I think...
Giving birth to a child is a terrible thing.
Terrible?
Do you understand?
And the child has a lot of hard and painful things in his life.
His mother is getting that pain to soften it even a little bit.
I don't want to hear such a beautiful thing.
Please tell me how hard it is.
There's a little something.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
A little something.
There's a little something like this.
I've been told such a little something.
A little something.
A monkey?
It's a monkey.
It's a little something like this.
For example...
I got it.
When I was camping, I was walking on the mountain road and a little something came down.
And I got hit.
It's a little something like this.
It hurts.
My face hurts.
It's a little something like this.
It hurts.
And why are you laughing?
Why do you hit people like this?
That's not the point of the story.
That's just a little something.
That's a little something.
It doesn't hurt much.
I don't understand.
This is the easiest way to understand.
Is that so?
That's difficult.
What are you talking about?
Do you have a cutter?
This is good.
What is a cutter?
A cutter knife.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's something like this.
That's good.
Something that's more common.
That's easy to understand.
That's right.
Do you have a cutter?
Yes, yes, yes.
A cutter knife.
It's all out.
Yes, yes, yes.
Right?
Your nose is...
scary.
That's...
It doesn't hurt.
That's scary.
So...
How did you feel the day before?
What do you mean?
Are you scared?
I'm scared.
Because you went all out,
when you were doing this.
Are you talking about the pain you felt while doing it?
Okay, let's try it.
Ah, this is painful.
Tell him about it.
Tell him about it!
Ah, this hurts.
It hurts.
This hurts.
But it especially hurts me.
What do you mean by that?
You're the worst!
You're a monster!
You're a monster.
In a way, I'm a monster.
What's so hard about that?
You're a middle schooler.
That pain...
To an old man at the iron mill...
To an old man at the iron mill?
That's really easy.
You're the one who's noisy, right?
That's my job!