The usual scene of the school night
But for some reason I couldn't see that man
Good morning
I'm sorry
Okamoto-san is still here
He left
I'll call him right back
Yes, I'm sorry
I knew he would leave
I knew it
All the staff told me to call him
They told me to call him right back
I'm sorry
You always do that
I can't do that
Usually when you get angry you don't say it
Right
I'm sorry, anyway I'm sorry
I'm sorry
Junko house, Junko store
Wait a minute
What are you memorizing?
Junko house, Junko store
It's ok
It's ok, let's go home
Let's go home
What?
What is he doing?
He's not angry today?
He's not angry
He's sleeping
What?
Be quiet
What are you doing?
He's not sleeping
That's it
I can't see
There's a mirror in front of you
I saw it
I'm so angry
I'm so tired
Let's not talk about it
Your partner is angry
Is that so?
I didn't say that
What?
I don't want to walk here
I'm really sorry
I'm your partner
I'm sorry
You guys are acting strange
What is that?
I'm sorry
This
Don't fight
Okay
Express your love
Look at this
When I came out the other day
Isn't it good?
It's good
You ran for 21 seconds
How many?
You ran for 15 seconds
Why are you so behind?
That's because
You're running behind
You're still far
I'm sure you edited it
What?
This is my opening
I think you edited it a little
Why are you editing this?
Editing?
We'll have no time to talk
Isn't that good?
Why do you need to talk?
No, no
I'm just a simple boy
Is that so?
That's good
It's good that I'm the manager
Are you going to do something?
What?
Human arrest
I'm going to do it
Be careful
Get ready
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
Kodama-san
Yes?
I've prepared
Human arrest
Are you okay?
I'm okay
It looks scary
It's scary
We can't do it
Let's go
What are you going to do?
I don't want to do it
This guy is annoying
Take care of it
Yamagaki-san
I can't do it
You have to catch it
It's a talent
Excuse me
It's scary
Just one more time
Okamoto-san, I'm going to raise the angle
You should be able to see the banana
Catch the banana
Raise it
It's high tech
Let's see Okamoto-san
Okamoto-san, are you okay?
I can't do it anymore
Let's do it like this
I'm sure you can do it
I can't do it
Please
Okamoto-san
Let's go
Fire in 5 seconds
4, 3, 2, 1
It's stuck in my head
Okamoto-san, you can't catch it
Okamoto-san, the banana
I can't do it anymore
It's too scary
Okamoto-san, come over here
I can't do it anymore
Okamoto-san, you can't do it anymore
Let's go
Okamoto-san, please raise the camera
Thank you for your hard work
Okamoto-san, you can't do it anymore
What?
You're doing it again
I did it again
Why?
Everyone is disappointed
Is that so?
I did it again
It's fine
You have to buy that
I don't want to sell it
I'll sell it
I just did it in the corner
You don't have to sell it
I can't do it anymore
Good evening
It's getting hot
Can you do it?
I can't do it anymore
I forgot
You can't change it
Don't touch it
I can't do it anymore
It's not like that
That's right
You have a good face
The other day
What?
When we were shooting Gotts
Wada Akio came
He left a message
He said he'll call back
I thought it was a car accident
Suddenly after Gotts
I got a message
I said I'm sorry
I said I have something to talk about
I said I don't have anything
You were like a talker
I was like that for 2 hours
I thought it would be fine
I called him
I thought it was a party
I knew my purpose
I knew why he couldn't drink anymore
Really?
He was trying to get me
Scary
He got angry
He touched
You're lying
It's scary!
Damn it
It's true
It's so cool, it makes you want to puke
What do you mean?
The guy who got killed by a wada
But if you take a picture of him
It would be amazing
Wada Akiho Matsumoto
Three times
I'll take a picture of him like this
It's scary
It's so cool
I can't fit such a fat guy
Can you fit him?
You can't?
You can fit him
Me?
That's not true
You can fit him
I'm really sorry
That's not true
What's wrong with you?
If you don't stand up, you'll get hit
If I don't stand up, I'll get hit
Are you underestimating me?
If I don't stand up, I'll be told to stand up
Then I'll get hit
First, I'll be told to stand up
Then you'll be told to stand up
I'm like Hanaka
I want to see it
I'm sorry, I'll bring a tissue
I really want to invite Hamada
But he has a family
Thank you
I don't want to invite him
I really wanted to get married at that time
You wanted to get away from that?
I wanted to get away from that organization
I thought I had to get married
You should have read the organization
I'm really sorry
I really wanted to avoid that
I can't do anything about it
What are you doing?
I really wanted to avoid that
I'm sorry
I was really scared
Take this too
But I really...
I think everyone is waiting for that
You'll get hit
I think I'll fight in court
You'll go to jail?
I'll go to jail
I can't do anything about it
So it's better to get hit
Do it
I can't do it
I need a
There was a guy who annoyed me
Who?
He's not a celebrity
What?
He's a celebrity
He went to eat
It's like a family restaurant
You can see the parking lot while eating
He's brushing his teeth
At the parking lot?
At the parking lot
I was drinking wine
You're drinking wine at a family restaurant?
I've been eating for 70 years
I've been eating
I've been drinking
Okay
Don't look at me like that
I'm not stupid
I forgive you
It's okay
I've been eating
At first I ignored it
When someone tells you not to brush your car
I'm brushing it
I'm brushing it first
And then I look at it
I can't see
I'm panicking
This is this
That's that
And then, he finally finished brushing his teeth
Right?
Next time, he'll bring out a handkerchief or tissue and brush his teeth with an antenna
How cute!
He'll blow on the round part of the antenna like this
Are you serious?
I'm not lying
I don't know if he's going to pick up his girlfriend
He didn't plan to do that. He was doing it the whole time
Even though he was brushing his antenna, he couldn't get any messages
What are you waiting for?
When he opens the door, he opens it like this
He doesn't put on his shoelaces
That's right. This is where he closes the door
When he touches the handkerchief, he looks at it like this
I'm going to brush you!
Why do cats stand up even if they fall from high places?
Why do they stand up?
Let's say this
They stand up even if they're not cats
They don't stand up
Even if they're horses
Let's try to make a horse stand up
At the opening of the show
It's not that high
Let's try to make a horse fall from a really high place
That's impossible
You've never seen a horse fall from a shelf, right?
No
I've seen it many times
Have you ever eaten while watching it?
Where can I watch it?
In a small pub
I want to go to a small pub
Why is the cord of the phone spinning?
But it's not spinning
If we put it in a straight line, isn't it pretty long?
It's an old man's idea
Well, it's an old man
Isn't it?
He's not that young
NTT guys
They only think about extending the story
That's right
If it's a straight line phone
Hello?
By doing that
Next
That's right
How many of Hamada's CDs did Yasashiki Matsumoto, who is called the mirror of Japanese people, buy?
He bought a lot
How many CDs did he sell?
I don't know how many he sold
He sold about 200,000 CDs
I don't think he sold 200,000
He sold about 200,000
He sold about 1.9 million
That's right
But that
There's no one who said, I bought a CD
Then why did you sell 1.9 million?
Wait a minute
Don't say something that makes me cry
That's right
What?
Matsumoto-san, why can't you smile like that?
How is it?
Hey
What kind of smile?
It's disgusting
Disgusting?
Smile more normally
Disgusting
Smile normally
Most people, for example
If a person with a face of 50 points smiles, the 5 points will decrease
Do you understand?
Is that so?
If you smile, it will be more disgusting, but if you smile, it will be 45 points
You already have a 40 points face
Don't hide your 40 points face
Wow, 40 points
You already have 40 points
Everyone said that
What kind of answer is that?
Everyone in Fuji's family said that
But
That's the story
Everyone said that only Matsumoto will smile and become even more disgusting
Who said that?
Everyone said that
My family said that
Your family said that?
My family said that only Matsumoto will smile and become even more disgusting
You guys are Matsumoto too
Only us
Only our family
I can understand that
Everyone said that
Everyone said that only Matsumoto will smile and become even more disgusting
Is that so?
It's like you're planning something
That's not true
You're the only one who said that
Well, you're like that too
You said it as a joke
That's not true
Why did you say it as a joke?
You're overreacting
I'm not overreacting, it's natural
You're always like that
I'm sorry
Do you say that?
It's disgusting if you're like that
I'm sorry for that time
That's why I said it
Hey, smile
Show us a smile that will increase your score
There are many ways to smile
Is that so?
Smile
It's natural
It's not natural
Why can't I see it?
It's not the best
Is that so?
It's the best
Okay, I got it
There's nothing more than this
This is a smile that will increase your score
Yes, a smile that will increase your score
A smile that will make everyone happy
Yes
Please
It's a smile that will make everyone happy
This is the best
If you smile that much, you can't see your teeth
If I smile that much?
Yes
When you smile, your teeth will show
Why can't I see it?