We're going to do a little boy's play.
Sarai-
I don't know what's going on.
It's my first time doing this.
Thank you very much.
This kid is the best.
The yellow is glittering in my eyes.
The staff's t-shirt is cool.
Thank you very much.
Good evening.
It's already started.
I'm sleepy.
All of a sudden?
It's already started.
If I get tired on the way, I think I'll eat gum and change to the wind.
It's finally starting.
It's a 24-hour TV show, but it's actually a 25-hour show.
If you put in the rehearsal, it'll be about 32 hours.
It's nice to sing in a big way.
I'm going to cry.
Thank you very much.
Did you sleep?
I'm a little sleepy.
Why?
Who? Your friend?
Who?
Your friend?
I'm a little sleepy.
My friend, take only half of it.
I don't think there's any more.
Thank you very much.
I just went to Osaka.
I'm going to cry.
Thank you very much.
Those who are watching this TV, you can think of the previous story, but this is yesterday's today, right?
Normally, we rest. Normally, we rest.
Nittere, too.
It was Okada-san.
It's true.
Well, there is a musical instrument tomorrow, but let's stop it.
Let's stop it.
It's like a famous scene.
It's like a famous scene of a musical instrument until now.
Please!
It's like an end-of-life story.
Hey!
Normally, we do it.
We do, we do, we do.
Then, I'll be waiting for you tomorrow.
No, but, Hamada-kun.
What?
You are a touching father, aren't you?
Well, I usually do it with a needle and a needle, but in the end, it's just the face on the outside, and the inside is a gentle voice.
Really? What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
It's not coming out.
That's right.
When I was reading the text, it was coming out.
No, it's not that it's coming out.
Well, I didn't have anything, did I?
You were like a sparkling thing.
Hey!
Ah! Don't lie to me!
Ah!
You were a dirty person.
What are you talking about? You were crying.
What are you talking about?
You were crying.
Ah!
Don't lie to me!
Well, you can put it in the editing room while I'm talking.
This 24-hour crying scene.
Let's take a look.
Why?
A Cambodian child is chasing a paper airplane.
Right?
What are you talking about?
Ah!
Finally, I found love.
What are you talking about?
I didn't want to see you.
I probably knew you were crying.
I was doing this, but I thought I should take a look at it.
When I looked at it, you were wearing it.
It's not coming out.
Really?
What are you talking about?
That's why Fax is wearing it.
I was impressed when Fax was wearing it and Mr. Kusada was calling him.
It's called downtown tears.
At that time, I was surprised.
What?
Hitoshi?
Hitoshi wasn't crying.
You're asking yourself.
Hitoshi was crying?
Hitoshi wasn't crying.
But it's related to downtown tears.
Ah!
Masatoshi.
There were a lot of moving VTRs.
Tokumitsu and Mr. Kusada and me.
It's okay to sit down and rest.
But I was looking at the monitor.
You were the only one who said,
Tenmusu!
Two minutes ago, you said,
Ah!
Even if you didn't watch the VTRs, you said,
Tenmusu!
You were crying in the end.
It's okay to eat something in between.
That's because you're going to fall.
That's right.
You were sleeping.
In the back.
Don't say bad things about people.
When everyone stood up and said,
You were like this in the back.
Ah!
Tenmusu!
How many times did you come before?
I just went into energy while watching the VTR.
I don't know anything about other programs.
Really?
It's true.
Why?
Didn't you take a break once?
One hour.
About an hour.
When I went to the broadcast.
That's right.
There was about an hour at that time.
I took a shower here.
That's right.
I can't.
I have to change my pants.
Did you poop in your pants?
I don't want to poop in my pants.
Are you stupid?
You woke up 24 hours ago.
You were wearing your pants like that.
How many people did you poop in your pants?
I can't.
I didn't poop once that day.
Why didn't you poop?
Toku-san said,
I can't poop at all.
I'm hungry.
I feel bad.
Did you poop in the meantime?
I pooped twice.
What?
Is that so?
That's right.
I don't know if it's because of that.
I didn't poop.
I took a shower.
I sat on the chair.
What do you call it?
I had my eyes closed.
You pooped a lot.
You pooped so much that the ectoplasm came out.
Why?
The white one.
I pooped.
I closed my eyes.
I looked back from the opening quietly.
Liar!
Godne-chan called me again.
After that?
Alien called me yesterday.
I was doing it.
Alien called me.
That's right.
It's true.
I was in the middle of it.
Good evening.
I had a question.
Why do you call an ant an ant and make it poop?
It's just an ant.
It's okay to be an ant.
Do you have an attachment to ants?
Even if you have an attachment, why are you pooping?
I don't have an attachment to ants.
Is that so?
Didn't you poop when you were walking?
Why are you walking?
You didn't poop, did you?
I didn't.
You're just walking an ant.
I didn't do that.
When you were a kid, you played with ants and pooped.
I've never done that.
You did when you were a kid.
I feel sorry for you.
There was a sparrow in front of my house.
The sparrow caught the sparrow and hurt its leg.
The sparrow was able to fly for a few days at home.
The sparrow returned the sparrow to the sparrow.
You're noisy.
I'm a bad guy.
I think you two are famous entertainers.
I have a question.
There is a drug called FINISH.
Why are you laughing?
Are you really a singer?
I'm a singer.
Please tell me what you're singing with your name.
That's true.
I don't know what you're singing.
My name is Koganezawa-kun.
Why don't you have to be Koganezawa-kun for the promotion of FINISH?
Why don't you have to be Koganezawa-kun?
Why are you Koganezawa-kun?
It's a business that uses the throat.
It's not an excuse for anyone.
I want to know how old you are and what you're singing.
That's right.
Do you have a trust relationship with Machan and Amachan?
My school teacher said that if you trust each other, you should be able to say the shortcomings of each other.
In a sense, the fact that you can say that much means that you have a trust relationship.
Is that so?
That's what it means.
In that sense, you can say it because you trust each other, and the person who says it will not be angry.
Is that so?
Do you have such a broad mind?
I don't know that.
You won't know until you try it.
I don't think I have 10 shortcomings.
For example, let's do it one by one.
My lips are thick and disgusting.
Wait a minute.
That's a shortcoming.
Do you have such a thing?
My lips are thick and disgusting.
I've been with you for more than 10 years, and I've had a lot of feelings for you.
What kind of shortcomings do you have?
That's a shortcoming.
You have to say it.
I don't like this part.
Are you angry?
That's not true.
You won't know until you say it.
Your lips are disgusting.
I don't like this part.
What is this?
It's disgusting.
It's disgusting compared to Akira.
What is this?
That's a shortcoming.