Everyone!
I have a letter for you.
What is it?
It's from a mother in elementary school.
I'll read it to you.
Nice to meet you, downtown kids.
I am a mother with a son who is in the second grade.
My son is playing baseball in the Little League.
But he had a fracture before his first official game.
He is very depressed because he lost his regular seat.
My son's name is Minoru Okada.
Minoru is a big fan of Gaki no Tsukai.
I watch his videos every week.
Would you please cheer for him?
Thank you very much.
It's from a mother named Kiyoko.
I'm moved.
He is a fan of Gaki no Tsukai.
I hope we can cheer him up so that he can play baseball again.
I'm moved.
I've never been so moved.
The hospital is nearby.
Let's go to the hospital.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Thank you very much.
This is a hospital.
Hello.
Thank you for coming.
My mother gave me a letter.
Thank you very much.
It's from Edo, isn't it?
Yes, it's from Edo.
I hope we can cheer him up so that he can play baseball again.
He is a big fan of Edo.
Is that so?
I watch his videos every week.
Here are some flowers.
Thank you very much.
This is amazing.
It's beautiful.
Thank you very much.
I heard that you are playing baseball.
Yes, we are.
Really?
Yes.
Good luck.
Thank you very much.
Can I open it?
Yes, please.
Open it.
I wonder what it is.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's a globe.
It's done.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
I'm glad.
The end.
Can you sign it for me?
Of course.
Can I?
I'm sorry.
You are a big fan of Edo, aren't you?
I'd like to ask you for this.
It's a treasure of Minoru.
This is from a long time ago.
How did you get it?
Did you buy it on TV?
No, I bought it.
Are you selling it now?
Yes.
It's called Dynamite Shikoku.
I see.
Thank you.
Wow, it's Edo's signature.
It's my Edo's signature.
It's Edo's signature, isn't it?
No, it's not.
I'm glad.
He's getting better.
Are you so happy that you bought it?
Yes.
What should I do?
Can I ask you something?
This is Edo's favorite character, Hohohoin.
Is that so?
It's enough that you bought it.
If you can, can you cheer him up with your Hohohoin?
No, it's okay.
Please.
Are you okay?
It's been a long time.
Please do it in your usual outfit.
I can't do it in this outfit, can I?
You look good in your usual outfit.
Do you want to see Emi-no-roko?
Yes, I do.
Really?
Well, then...
I have this, too.
Please use it if you like.
You're actually wearing it, aren't you?
Yes, please.
Please.
I can't help it.
I'll take this and use it.
Then, I'll get ready.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm a big fan of Edo.
I'm glad.
I like Edo.
It's rare.
That's right.
I'm glad.
Today is a good day, isn't it?
Are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready.
I'll be around here.
Minoru-kun, please get well soon.
Please get well and do your best in baseball.
Please get a regular.
Please.
Please do it.
Yes.
Minoru-kun, please get well soon.
Minoru's smile is amazing.
I'm glad.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
It's about time.
Thank you.
Please do your best.
I'm sorry.
Actually, I wrote a letter to you.
Yes.
Actually, Minoru has been depressed since she had a fracture.
Because of that, she couldn't sleep well.
I see.
At the Hollywood audition of Mr. Endo,
you imitated Takeshi, didn't you?
If you show that in the video,
you'll sleep better.
I'll sleep better?
Yes.
Since Mr. Endo came here today,
can you imitate Takeshi in front of Minoru's eyes?
What should I do?
The doctor said that if you don't sleep well,
you'll get better late.
That may be true.
Please do it.
After this, I'll record it.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Please do it.
I'm glad that you'll do it, Minoru.
I did it.
I can see Takeshi today.
I can see him.
What's the matter with Takeshi and Minoru?
You're going to sleep soon, aren't you?
That's right.
Thank you for always supporting me.
I'm going to sleep now.
I'm going to sleep.
Please do it.
Dan-kun!
Dan-kun, you bastard!
Get out of the car, Dan-kun!
Why aren't you turning?
Are you sleeping again?
Get out!
You're going to sleep naked.
Stop it!
Turn the car, Rakkyo!
Which one do you want?
Turn the car, you bastard!
Why are you like that?
What?
I told you to turn the car, Rakkyo.
Turn the car, Dan-kun!
Why aren't you turning?
You're sleeping, you bastard!
Why are you like that?
Turn the car!
Tell me why you're sleeping.
Turn the car,
rottenunno!
You're sleeping, this爛爛爛爛爛爛爛爛爛爛爛爛爛爛爛爛爛爛爛爛爛爛爛爛爛爛
Come on! Come on!
Come on!
Hurry up and put your pants on!
What the hell are you doing?
What's with that look in your eyes?
If you're going to run away, then don't do that!
You idiot!
What the hell are you doing?
What are you doing?
I'm always here!
Hurry up!
Aren't you?
I'm always here!
Taka!
Taka, come on
Hurry up and get out of here!
Come on, Taka!
Tell me something, you idiot!
You can't say anything, you idiot!
What the hell are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you here?
What's wrong?
Tell me, Rakkyo.
What are you doing?
Rakkyo!
Rakkyo, what's wrong?
What's wrong, Duncan?
What the hell are you talking about?
Mori! Mori!
Mori, come here!
You're the one who made me angry!
Why do you want me to turn the car?
Why don't you turn it?
Hey!
Don't do it!
I said don't do it!
What the hell are you doing?
Hey!
Someone turn the car!
Why do you want me to do this?
I said turn the car!
Don't do it!
What the hell are you doing?
Hurry up and turn the car!
I said turn the car!
What the hell are you doing?
Taka! Taka!
I said come here!
Turn the car with Taka Drusher!
Hurry up and turn the car with Taka Drusher!
I said turn the car with Taka Drusher!
Why don't you turn the car?
What the hell are you doing?
I said turn the car!
Turn the car!
What the hell are you doing?
Are you a witness?
I said turn the car!
Hurry up and turn the car!
What are you doing there?
Turn the car!
There is a big car!
Hurry up and turn the car!
What the hell are you doing?
Turn the car!
I said turn the car!
Hurry up and turn the car!
Why don't you turn the car?
What the hell are you doing?
What are you looking at?
Why don't you turn the car?
Why don't you look at me?
Why are you looking at me?
Tell me!
Why don't you look at me?
Why are you acting like that?
Why are you like that?
Turn the car!
Let's go!
The band that Mr. Matsumoto used to work with, the blood-soaked handsome boy, was one of the members.
What kind of member was he?
For example, if you ask for his name, there was someone who said, there was that person?
What?
If you ask for his name, there was someone who said, there was that person?
Of course, of course.
Really?
Well, the members were active separately, so I don't really want them to say it.
Ah, I see.
Yes.
It was a bad past, wasn't it?
Well, it was a bad past, so I don't know.
I see.
Then, tell me.
Well, there was a boy from L'Arc-en-Ciel who was a vocalist.
You did it together, didn't you?
I did.
Say his name.
What's a vocalist's son?
You don't know even if I say it, do you?
Why don't you just say his name?
Well, I called him by his real name.
Ah, then you can say his real name.
Sasada.
Ah, so Sasada was the vocalist?
No, Sasada was the vocalist.
I was the vocalist.
Because he was the most handsome boy.
He had a voice like a peeled egg.
That's not funny.
What was Sasada doing?
Sasada was a guitarist.
A guitarist?
Which one?
He was a bassist and a guitarist.
Say it.
I'm a bassist and a guitarist.
You're the vocalist.
I'm the vocalist.
What about the others?
Eh?
I was the most handsome boy.
What about the others?
Amamiya Ryo.
That's old.
No, no, no.
I was an electric guitarist.
I was a synthesizer.
Which one?
I was an electric guitarist and a synthesizer.
I can't say it.
What was it?
Amamiya Ryo.
I was an electric guitarist and a synthesizer.
Everyone is different.
Then what?
Even if I'm lying, I have to say what everyone knows about the members.
My memories have to be changed into what you all know.
Please tell me the others.
Who was the singer?
Amachi Shigeru.
I was an electric guitarist.
That's old.
Then what?
Even if I'm lying, I have to say what everyone knows about the members.
My memories have to be changed into what you all know.
That's what I have to say.
I'm sorry.
Vocal, bass, guitar.
Who was the drummer?
The drummer was Kato Go.
The tambourine was Tani Hayato.
That's right.
Right?
You're always in front of guys.
You should definitely put Kato Go in front of guys.
Matsumoto-san has done a scene-stealing game three times before.
Where did he do that?
He was standing in front of a ramen shop with a long line of people.
That's when I finished my scene-stealing game.
That's it for today.
That's when I did my first scene-stealing game.
What kind of situation was that?
Who did you do that to?
That was the ramen shop owner.
To the owner.
That's it for today.
He apologized to me.
That's when I did my scene-stealing game.
What does that mean?
I don't know what that means.
Can you do it again?
What happened to your father when you did that scene-stealing game?
The scene-stealing game...
was terrifying!
I think that's it.
I still have two more scenes to do.
You did three scenes?
That's right. I didn't forget.
Then I'll do two more.
What did you say?
The scene-stealing game...
If you say it like that, I'll do the fourth scene today.
No, no, no.
You can't do it for me.
You can't do the scene-stealing game.
I can't do the scene-stealing game for my partner.
I can't see the picture of your scene-stealing game.
Where did you do the second scene?
It's an old story.
The first scene was when I was in the second grade of elementary school.
I did the scene-stealing game for an old lady at a restaurant.
Why did you do the scene-stealing game for an old lady?
I took the leftovers to the restaurant.
I was told that I left a lot of money.
I see.
I didn't leave the money.
I took the leftovers to the restaurant.
At that time, I was very angry.
I was very angry.
What?
What did you say?
I was very angry.
That's dangerous.
You shouldn't be angry.
I was scared.
I didn't say I was scared.
But I was angry.
That scene has already been shown.
Where?
When I went to the violence room.
I don't know.
How old were you?
I was 19 years old.
And?
I drank two glasses of water.
I was told that I had 500,000 yen.
I was paid 500,000 yen.
That's right.
After that, I got angry.
I got angry.
I was told to pay 500,000 yen.
I took out a piece of paper from my wallet.
I took it out.
Can I tell you the truth?
Yes.
I had a lot of fun until the end.
Why is it like this?
Why?
I don't think it's a good idea to write a letter.
Why did you take out a piece of paper from your wallet?
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
I couldn't see what it was.
It was just an old man and an old woman's reaction.
After that, I took out a piece of paper from my wallet.
Everyone was surprised.
I was eating in front of my eyes.
After that, I took out a piece of paper from my wallet.
I see.
My reaction was different from everyone's reaction.
It was different.
Do you think it's a good idea to write a letter?
I think it's a good idea.
I think it's a good idea to write a letter.
I'm sorry.
What?
I see.
I can't write a letter now.
I've been asked to write a letter.
What do you want me to write?
I want you to write a letter.
I have a letter.
You don't have a letter.
You can't write a letter now.
I have a letter.
I didn't expect you to write a letter on the stage.
So I always leave it to you.
You can write a letter now.
I don't think you can buy sesame dumplings while we're talking.
It's not sesame dumplings.
What is this name?
It's a letter.
There was no Japanese confectionery shop nearby.
What?
There's a letter here.
I have a letter.
I don't care.
You ate it again.