Atami Indy's secret mission!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hello!
What's up?
Let's just say it for today.
We're here at Atami today.
We're here at Atami Indy's secret mission.
We're here at Atami, but it's a little cold today.
It's cold!
It's been raining a little.
Today, at Atami,
as you can see from our clothes,
we're going to be Indy Jones.
I don't get it at all.
A helicopter!
Our helicopter is going to teach us how to fly a kite.
It's going to fly from the top.
Here we go!
It's heavy!
Do you have a flashlight?
I'll use it.
Do you have one?
I don't have one.
Did you find it?
I found it!
What does it say?
What?
Tomaru Hotel, Blover Station.
This is the same!
Yeah.
But if we don't look at it,
and if we get it wrong,
we'll get chased away.
I don't get it!
This program is brought to you by Sunlux.
Can we search for treasure
by following the instructions?
What?
This is it.
This is the man's room.
There's a man's room and a woman's room.
Hello.
Where is it?
Dad, I need you to put a mosaic on this.
Oh, really.
What's on your dad's towel?
It's like...
It's like I got a piece of Kentucky.
It's on the screen.
Please show it to the towel.
It's a big party.
Wow.
Hello.
This is amazing.
What's this?
It's a big party.
I didn't know they prepared something like this.
If you win,
I'll give you instructions.
Really?
Yes.
I got it.
Get on.
I'm used to playing in a tea house.
Please teach me how to do it.
I'm not a dancer.
You're not?
This is the bedroom.
I'm not a dancer.
Miss Sugoroku.
Yes.
You look like you used to be a comedian.
Nice to meet you.
With this lady.
Miss Atami.
That's right.
I'll do it.
Yes.
I lost.
I should have lost.
I should have won.
Yes.
Are you ready?
I'll start.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Out.
Safe.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
I got it.
Wow.
You're dirty.
What are you doing?
It's okay.
From Tasuki?
One, two, three, four.
I want to be hugged.
Idiot.
I see.
That's it?
Today is a service, right?
Yes.
That's it.
Are you ready?
I'll start.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, nine, ten.
Out.
Safe.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
I got it.
You're so bad.
You should have lost.
I lost.
I should have lost.
I should have won.
I got it.
It's okay.
You did it.
Will you show us the kind of fight again?
Where is it?
I don't know.
Here it is.
What?
It's my turn.
You have to do this.
You should hit like this.
You're bad.
I should have seen.
Ah! That's it!
Let's go to Atami Castle.
I can't do anything else.
For whom is this for?
Let's go to Atami Castle by this.
I hate Atami the most in Japan.
I don't think so.
Let's go to Atami Castle by this.
There is a command post.
Really?
I can't go there.
Please.
Please, find the sea that said,
Let's go to Atami Castle by this.
I don't want to do it anymore.
It's a beautiful place.
Thank you very much.
Look at yourself. I'll look at the other side.
I'm looking for the sea.
Found it?
Found it!
I found it!
Atami Castle.
It's a castle that can defeat enemies.
Let's go to Atami Castle.
To defeat the enemies.
Yes.
What are you looking at?
Look at this kid's face.
This kid is amazing.
He looks like he's having fun.
But in a observatory like this,
when a child is put on something like this,
it's before he can throw it away.
You can't throw it away in a few minutes.
I'm sorry.
I'm really bad at this.
I'm going to live alone.
Do you understand?
When I grow up, I want to be a professional wrestler like Oninichan.
It's not that rough.
It's not rough.
It's crisp.
It's good, isn't it?
If you can hit it every time, it's hard to hit it this way.
I want to be an all-star.
A match between Shizuki Combat and Yuero.
Who's going to be the all-star and the star?
Sorry.
I have a gun like this, so don't turn around behind me.
People will fly.
What is that sensei's attitude?
Is that attitude right?
Who are these guys?
Who are they?
Wait a minute.
These guys are pretty good.
Don't come near me.
What is this?
Don't come near me. You'll regret it.
It hurts.
What hurts?
Run away.
Are you still coming?
Everyone, let's have a fight.
Behind you.
There, there, there.
I did it.
What is this?
There, there, there.
There.
What are these guys?
They're not cool.
There.
I'm scared.
There, there, there.
Alright, we did it.
I can't take it anymore.
So, we beat them up.
Of course.
But this scene is scary.
This dinosaur?
Running in the car at night and falling like this.
It's unbearable.
It's scary.
Ah, it was scary.
What is this?
Ah, there, there, there.
There, there, there.
Everyone.
There.
There, there, there.
Why did you come back?
It's scary, isn't it?
Yes.
It's different, isn't it?
Ah.
Don't do something like Ajiro Okawa.
Why did you come back and rest?
It's a bit...
I've been working out lately.
It's different, isn't it?
That's a good thing.
I've been working out.
The color of your body is the same as the color of the rock at the starting point.
Hey, George.
You said you were going to run.
That's right.
Ah.
Look at the rock.
There.
Ah, I was surprised.
I was surprised.
This is the secret.
What are you wearing?
Let me see.
It's a vinyl.
There is sand in my neck.
Put more sand in.
I'll eat this.
It's cold.
You are like the opening of the movie.
It's not.
Put more sand in.
I'll make you a turtle neck.
Big mouth mould...
Just like Satoro.
It's so much fun.
Right, Hamada! Keep only this!
Oh, indeed!
I can't take it anymore.
Help me.
What do you mean, help me?
It's not funny at all.
What's that?
That's CX.
What?
Go away.
How did you like it?
Yes.
Today, we tried to do the best version.
This is the best version?
Yes.
We came to Atami.
We spent a lot of money.
That's right.
Are you selling this?
Yes.
Really?
Where?
Helicopters and such.
That's not it.
Helicopters to give orders from above.
That's right.
The balance is strange from the side.
Then, shall we introduce the postcards?
Yes.
There are no customers.
Are you introducing without customers?
I'm introducing without customers.
Right?
I'll send you the result of the survey.
What is it?
The person you want to be a lover with.
Number one.
Mr. Nitta.
No comments below.
The person you want to be kind with.
Mr. Nitta.
No comments below.
The person you want to be a brother with.
Mr. Nitta.
No comments below.
The person you want to be the father of your child.
Mr. Matsumoto.
No comments below.
Please don't tease Mr. Nitta too much.
I'll accept the prize.
I'll accept it.
Mr. Nitta is very popular these days.
Don't tease Mr. Nitta too much.
Why?
I think.
Yes.
From now on, I'm going to do more and more.
I've been thinking about what I'm missing.
What?
What do you think is missing?
Warmth.
I have it.
I don't have it.
I don't have it today.
Are you stupid?
Let's be a little warmer.
It's warmer when we're in contact with each other.
Where did you go?
Really?
Even if you go to work.
Yes.
I did something rude the other day.
What did you do?
No, it's okay.
If I tell you, I'll talk like this again.
You can say that.
Yes.
I'm a little stupid.
This guy.
That's why.
It's okay.
I was surprised.
I was surprised and I thought it was parallel.
That's right.
It's on the show.
After the show.
The next story.
No, I'm going to talk about that.
At that time.
Nozawa passed in front of us.
I hit Nozawa's head.
That's fine.
It's the same office.
I thought I was a senior.
I'm a senior, too.
That's fine.
Behind him.
Who was it?
I don't know.
There's a reason for the super cup.
Kazama Morio.
Nozawa passed in front of me.
I hit Nozawa's head.
Kazama Morio came behind him.
He hit Kazama Morio's head.
There's a reason for the super cup.
He's like this.
I saw him.
He didn't break.
I said,
I'm sorry.
I want you to stop.
I can't do that.
What's next?
Next.
I'll talk about this.
A survey again?
No, it's not a survey.
Please compare which one is better.
What?
Popularity.
There's a big difference, isn't there?
My target is from the wider part.
From the bottom to the top.
Is that so?
You're only from the bottom.
You look like you can do it.
I look like I can do it?
Your eyes are wide open.
How old do you think I look like I can do it?
You're about 12 years younger than me.
Yes, I have 12 kids at home.
What are you talking about?
I don't have any savings.
Really?
Yes.
How much do you have?
I don't have any money.
You only have a few hundred thousand yen.
How much would it cost if I told you to prepare 10 million by tomorrow?
You have to wait until next month's salary.
I don't have any money.
You only have a few hundred thousand yen.
How much would it cost if I told you to prepare 10 million by tomorrow?
I have the same amount of money as you.
Compared to that, you only have a few hundred thousand yen.
How much would it cost?
I don't have any money.
That's not what I'm talking about.
Are you kidding me?
Idiot!
I was going to say the same thing.
You're late.
That's true.
I've been working for years.
But I'm late.
You're late.
You're not good at work.
Why?
Why aren't you working?
I'm not late.
That's why I'm working.
I don't know if you think I'm late for work,
but I'm always late for work.
I see.
That's why I'm late.
What about you?
What?
Me?
Yes.
What about you?
Are you having a hard time?
Are you crying?
What's that?
You look like you're having a hard time.
I think I'm going to sleep.
This is a quiz.
Think about it together.
There's a refrigerator.
I want to put an elephant in there.
There are three conditions.
What are they?
First of all, you have to wake up.
And?
There are three conditions.
Let's see.
Open the refrigerator.
Put an elephant in.
Close the refrigerator door.
That's amazing.
There's another one.
Let's do another one.
Put a giraffe in there this time.
And there are four conditions.
What are they?
Open the refrigerator door.
Open.
Put a giraffe in.
Close the lid.
What's that?
There's another one.
Put a outlet.
That's it.
It's going to be a big one.
What are the conditions?
Open the front door.
Close it.
Open the refrigerator door.
Put an elephant in.
It's connected to the previous story.
That's the old man's fault.
Put an elephant in.
Close the lid.
It's funny.
That's it.
This is the Atami version.
And then, as I say every week,
I'm going to show you how to coordinate with Nitta.
Next week, I'd like to do an opening related to that.
I'll show you everything.
I'll see you next week.
Bye.