The night's Kuchipaku hit studio, the second half of the show!
The members of the second half have gathered together to perform a performance of incredible synchrony!
Good, good, good!
Over-reacting!
The mouth pack's monster has appeared again tonight!
Who will be the winner?
Tonight, the winner will be decided!
Let's move on to the next mouth pack singer.
Let's hear it! The hit song that was a huge hit by chance, the masterpiece that became a social phenomenon, tonight, the first time to reveal it, Mr. Shimon Masato's, Swim, Taiyaki-kun!
Well, it's because it's sold.
CEO vanity
carrier
He doesn't Multi-use
Hello
What a surprise
Just like this?!
Your V-shape just happens to look like this.
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
You are a very popular kid, Taikichi.
I think there are many businesses where children are in.
What was the hardest business you did?
Children are surprisingly big.
You're not a 5th grader?
Well...
You know...
I know
What's wrong?
Middle school?
I'm just starting
What?
You're only 15 or 16?
15 or 16...
I wait everyday
You wait everyday?
Everyday
The hairstyle is a little impressive.
Do you have any manners?
This is...
Zack Baran.
Zack Baran?
The sound is different.
Zack Baran.
Thank you very much.
Let's move on to the next one.
The Date men who have been time-slipping since the 3rd year of Genroku are coming to Edo tonight.
Kuroizaki with rock, Oedo with kabuki rock.
Oh
What a poem
Yep, it's a true story.
mówn
It's like that guy's song.
wow
It's so cool.
So cool.
I'm notlla
A fair ranked hero
Oh, eh, no!
A town where a girl sleeps
The moe-do flies into the night
Even though I have a bad back
Thank you very much
You have been a time-slip since the year of the dog, but do you have any problems in your current life?
At first, if I say that I had a problem, it would be a lie, but now I'm used to it.
If you say that you didn't have a problem, it would be a lie.
Speaking of Mr. Rokus, you are from Ikaten, but which band did you think was the most rival at that time?
Ah, it's from Begin.
Ah, that's true.
I was also like Begin at first.
Eh?
But when Ikaten came out, it wasn't like this anymore?
I thought it was different.
Ah, is that so?
Everyone was interested in the Genroku era, so I think that's why it became like this.
So, you've been time-slipping for three years?
Yes.
Sorry, what's going on now?
What is going on? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. What's going on?
I'm sorry.
It was a wonderful performance.
Thank you very much.
It was wonderful.
Let's move on to the next mouth-to-mouth singer.
A big star of the group sounds era.
He appeared with a polished look.
Kenji Sawada's Slipper
It's a little similar
Why is it always like this?
I'm the winner!
I'll show you everything
I want to see everything of you
Oh, that's good
What's that?
Thank you very much
That was wonderful
When you were working as Kouhaku's bird, you said you refused to be a bird at first.
I basically hate birds.
Oh, really? Why?
The last one is sad.
How far has your voice reached now?
Not at all.
How about you, Shibata?
It's so close.
It's not close. I can't hear it at all from my side.
You can't hear it at all?
I can't hear it at all.
You covered Tokyo, and you were on Kabuki Rocks. How was it?
I've never met him before.
Oh, really?
So you didn't say anything about it?
I didn't get permission.
You didn't get permission?
Is it okay for me to sing?
Well, then...
What's that?
Thank you Sasuke-san!
Thank you!
Let's move on to the next mouth-to-mouth singer.
The national big brother, sorry to keep you waiting.
The ideal sister of the Japanese people will sing a song with a sweet voice.
Matsumoto Yuya's Sentimental Journey.
It's definitely him.
See? It's definitely him.
Cute.
I'm hungry...
I've been practicing this so much!
Like a magazine that's thrown away
Every time my page turns, you dig it out
I wonder if you know? I want to know
I'm traveling deep into your eyes
My sentimental journey
I want to dream as I am
I want to be with you
Yama-chan, you're serious this time?
I want to tell you
Because I'm still 16
I was invited by something, I was taken by you, It's not a sentiment
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
I was a little nervous.
Everyone is laughing.
Speaking of Iho, you were scouted in Harajuku.
What did you do in Harajuku?
I loved to see the bamboo family in Harajuku.
You went to see it.
Yes.
And then...
And then?
Was he from Kansai?
I was very close to Madoka-san.
You're a bit different.
I'm different.
I've always been from Kansai.
When did you first meet Hiromi-san?
I'll get scolded by Hiromi-san.
It's been decades. Please stop that.
No, no, no.
You'll get scolded.
What's the word for Hirobis' proposal?
Ah, that's right.
That is...
Yun Kai.
In Osaka, at Nakano-shima...
Nakano-shima?
At the festival hall.
At Madoka-san's concert...
He did it.
At that time.
When I went to greet him...
And then Madoka-san said,
I don't want to propose to you.
And she said to me,
No, that's not right.
It's not me.
It's Kiyomi-san's.
There was such a thing.
And we got married.
No, no.
There was such a thing in the dressing room.
Oh, my God.
After this, the winner of the contest will continue to appear!
Now, let's move on to the next mouth-closing singer.
The son of the Fouke family has appeared in the mouth-closing hit studio.
Masashi Sada will announce his retirement.
Eh, Sada-san?
This is bad.
If you let him do this, he'll...
I want to tell you before I get married.
Don't make a voice.
I'll talk to you, but listen to my voice.
You can't sleep before me.
You can't wake up after me.
Make a good meal.
You're always beautiful and colorful.
If you can laugh at me,
Don't forget me.
The woman I love.
You are the only one in my life
Thank you very much
You are called by your fans and staffs, but what is your real name?
I don't know
You don't know?
You are close with Mr. Kuramoto, do you go somewhere together?
Yes, I go to Kagoshima recently.
Kagoshima?
Kagoshima and my hometown, Shimai-doshi.
What is your hometown?
I think you don't know, but it's Napoli.
It's not Napoli.
Your wife was a former CA. How did you get along with her?
There is a very good hotel in Kagoshima.
There is a good hotel?
Yes, on the hill.
And I asked her if I could kiss her there.
You could kiss her?
Yes.
And she refused.
She refused?
Yes.
It may be boring, but it is a very deep memory for me.
I was not able to get a kiss in my life for the first time.
So the first time you were not able to kiss her was when you were a man.
I see.
And then we got married.
Oh, I see.
It was a very loose marriage, but she was the only one who was hard.
There were many things.
Thank you, Masashi Sada.
Please go to the next corner.
Thank you.
Let's move on to the next mouth-to-mouth scene.
A popular kid in elementary school.
A one-shot gag full of humor.
A great success with a bad character.
In Yamazaki Hosei, Yamazaki Ichiban.
Yamazaki Ichiban!
Good morning!
Looking at the sun, the stars of Yamazaki
Go, Yamazaki, for your own sake
Dreams are big, they are the world's most beautiful
Aim, Yamazaki, for your own sake
Yamada Kikishima!
It's getting more and more interesting.
Thank you very much.
This is the main character of the anime, Gakkyou Yamazaki.
What kind of story is this?
Yamazaki. I'm Yamazaki.
I'm Yamazaki, but...
I'm the school principal.
Why did you say that?
You're the one who got dragged.
How was it, Natsukima-san?
Well, I think it was good.
I got to show my energy in the second half.
The first half wasn't interesting at all.
I think it would be good to show a little bit of my speciality in the end.
That's right.
Of course, we are waiting for the little one.
Lastly, please.
The new one?
Oh, no, no.
Any one is fine.
Please.
We've been doing that recently.
Of course, we've been doing something more appropriate.
He came here and then turned around
Give me your face
What are you doing?
Let's move on to the next scene
A man who is not trapped in the circle of enka
and always challenges himself to the new music field
Shinichi Mori's Kitano Hotaru
Morita is definitely a good singer.
He is definitely a good singer.
He always comes to see me.
Good, good!
That's better, I think.
Good, good, good, good.
It's still a bit off-key.
The chorus is coming.
Nice.
Good, good.
Let's do a little bit.
There are parts that we want a little bit more.
Give us a little bit of your face.
A little more.
Good, good.
Good.
Good face, good face.
What kind of face is that?
Thank you very much!
No, no, Mori-san, you're the first one I've seen.
You have a different style.
It was wonderful. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
It seems that Mori-san was scouted by Charlie Ishiguro-san.
What kind of person is Charlie Ishiguro-san?
Charlie is a half.
Is it a half?
I'm a half.
What is this?
When I was walking down the street, Charlie said,
Yes, he is half English,
and he said things in English, so I can speak a little English.
So I said, OK.
So you are a good singer.
What is the content?
Walking down the street.
Now all the performance of the mouth-closing singer is over.
The winner is...
Who will win the victory?
Now, the winner is...
The winner is...
Masashi Sada!
I'm so happy
Congratulations
A reward for the winner of the mouth-clap festival, a live performance
The song is Sada Masashi's song of gratitude.
Before I get married, I have something to tell you.
It's a pretty tough story.
Listen to my true feelings, and wake up
I'm not a river
Don't forget me
The woman who loves me
Loving women is when you love your own life.
Don't forget that.
Loving women is when you love...
Loving women is when you...
...love one person, just one person...
Thank you.
Thank you very much.