Gaki no Tsukai's famous show, Hichihenge
Up until now, there have been 19 heroes who have challenged
Despite being under a lot of pressure, their sense of humor, acting ability, and courage have been tested
Some have cried, some have cried
And tonight, this man will challenge Hichihenge
Who will it be?
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai, Chikichiki, Chihara Yasushi, Hichihenge!
Chihara!
Eh?
Seiji!
Come here!
Wow!
Now, this time
That's amazing
You're acting weird!
I am!
I'm not!
I just came from home!
There's nothing weird about it!
What is this?
Good style!
This time, it's the 20th person
Ah, the 20th person
Bob Sapp is a bit...
Well, I'll do it so I'll aim for it
Really?
But!
Even though it's low, it doesn't mean that I'm not funny
Why?
The result
Of course
Even if it works, the next one is Junior
Ah, I see
Sorry, in a few months
Yes, please
Junior has already changed three times with the power of medicine
That's true
What will it be like?
I don't know if everyone will laugh or not
That's true
Really
It's like an occult movie
It's not funny at all
When I was filming
The cursed dog came and looked at me twice
He looked at me and said, what?
What should we do?
It's amazing that we're facing each other
What does that mean?
Dauntaro-san will show his face
And he will choose between the younger or the older
Ah, I see
He will choose
Yes, yes, yes
Well, I'm fine with it
He will definitely be chosen
How many people will be chosen?
How many?
What should we do?
Tanaka, do you want to try it?
Ochi musha, wakahage, erogappa, suichu
What are you going to do with this?
I used to do it with Jin-san
Yes, yes, yes
You almost died
I don't want to do it
Really?
Yes
Thank you
Really
What should I do?
Is this for real?
I haven't been to the gym lately
I can't do it
I can't fit in here
I've been to the gym for a while, but I don't know much about it
So, what should I do?
If I don't do it right, it won't end
What should I do?
When I was making the second one, I did it with a roll
That's right
It took too much time
If you don't give me an opinion, I'll let someone else do it
I'll do it at that meeting
That's right
I can't do it
Should I call him a human dog?
It's good, isn't it?
I can't stand up on my own as an old man
I'll give you a piggyback ride
Excuse me
Please give me a piggyback ride
Are you crying?
Are you crying now?
I'm not crying
Are you crying?
You're not crying
Let's go over there
Excuse me
Please
Are you crying?
I'm not crying
I have to do my best
The first impact was a big explosion
I thought it was bad
I felt it
That face
There's no place to throw it away
But it's true, isn't it?
It's definitely my fault
You'll be surprised
Why is it my fault?
What should I do?
It's definitely my fault
What is it?
I can only imagine
It's definitely my fault
I endured it
I don't know
It's obviously coming out of the water
It's coming out of the water
What is it?
That hat
So, this is the way
Is that so?
It's the way
Subi Subi-chan!
Hey, hey, hey! Wait, stop! Don't move!
Stay right there!
Subi Subi-chan!
Subi Subi-chan?
Subi Subi-chan!?
What's up, Arotea?
Damn, you're here.
When you're hanging on the wall, you look like Marco from Agnese Bay.
There's a door next to the hallway.
Yes, that's right.
You did well.
It's still dark.
Hello? Akira?
Yeah.
Are you here now?
No way, everyone's here.
Okay, I got it.
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
Are you watching now?
Yeah.
I'm watching.
I'm being watched.
I'm doing it.
I'm doing what you told me to do.
Yeah, I'm doing it.
Yeah, I'm watching.
I got it.
This is pretty good.
Did you get it?
I got it.
40,000 yen and 3,000 yen.
Wow, that's amazing.
Thank you very much.
That's amazing.
But...
What is it?
I don't want to do this.
I'm serious.
What?
Ladies and gentlemen.
Are you dreaming lately?
I don't dream.
Once in a while, I have a really big dream, but when I woke up the other day, I laughed so hard.
The moment I woke up, I was like, hahahaha!
Was it that fun?
It was amazing!
You were in it too!
What?
It was a dream, so I was a bit dazed.
But that was probably in middle school.
It felt like middle school.
Everyone was like, get together!
It was me, Hamada, Ito, and Wada.
And I was gathered with 5 people I'd never seen before.
And there was this scary person who said, get together!
I think it was Adachi-sensei.
Ah, I see. I'm really sorry.
I get it, I get it.
I think it was that model.
And they said, you guys are too messy.
You guys are messing up the atmosphere.
So you have to choose one of you guys, and you have to die today.
That was sudden.
That's right.
Normally, I'd be like, well, whatever.
But it was a dream, so I was like, I see.
Right?
And then they told me to announce the winner.
And I was like, first of all,
Say!
That's how you decide?
I was like, yeah!
Yeah!
You're going to get killed.
The other 4 didn't care.
Yeah!
And in the end, Ito and you were going to die.
Why?
Really?
And then, this is where it gets interesting.
Why did you say there was only one?
Ito and you.
Just the two of us?
I don't know why, but it was just you and Ito.
And then we decided to go to the infirmary.
So the guy who was going to get killed was going to the infirmary?
Yeah, and then they gave us an injection.
They gave us an injection, and 30 minutes later, we were super sleepy.
So they told us to go to sleep, and that was it.
And then Ito and you were like, what?
They gave us an injection.
And we were like, don't be so depressed.
And then we went to the park.
We still had time.
So the 5 of us went to the park.
And out of nowhere, 5 guys from Kusamura showed up.
And they were like, who the hell are you guys going to kill?
And we were like, whoa!
And then we looked at Ito and you, and this is what happened.
We were about to die!
And unfortunately, I woke up.
And I was like, whoa!
Isn't this dream amazing?
You didn't watch it until you died, did you?
It was really funny.
I mean, why are you guys fighting?
We were about to die!
We were doing this, but...
So you're pushing this?
I can imitate Taketsu-san.
Taketsu-san!
Why are you pushing the staff?
I want to do it!
What's the difference between Careless Smith and Aerosmith?
They're exactly the same.
Doesn't that make any difference?
They're completely different.
Aerosmith?
Do you know Aerosmith?
Who is Aerosmith?
He's in a band, right?
That's right.
Careless Smith?
It's Careless Miss.
The leader of Careless Miss.
You don't know Gaitare, do you?
I don't.
That's rude.
I've heard of Aerosmith.
The name, Aerosmith.
I don't know.
I've heard of Careless Miss.
They're exactly the same.
It's a different name.
It's not a different name.
Back in the days of the Indies, it was Careless Miss.
It became a major name?
It became a major name, Aerosmith.
Then it's Kaenri!
I used to do it in front of a department store.
Gaitare, right?
I used to do it in front of a shop.
Then it's Gaitare, right?
I used to do it in front of a shop!
I used to come and do my best.
I stayed in front of Teichiku's eyes.
Teichiku?
You're only going to Teichiku's eyes?
Don't say that!
You're going to Teichiku's eyes!
You're going to get in trouble!
I was going to debut.
But I didn't have the punch.
So I went with Aerosmith.
The leader, Careless Smith, didn't like it until the end.
The name, Kaenri.
We've always done it like this.
Gaitare, right?
I've been to Tohoku!
You've never been in Tohoku, though?
I've never been to Tohoku, though?
I'm traveling here these days.
Let's go and see Careless Smith, shall we?
Ok, if it's not real, we're going to see it.
Really.
What if it's not real, then—
There's definitely going to be someone.
A strong challenger.
He's going to give you electric gender事情.
Is that right?
Rock.
Me?
Why are you calling your partner rock?
Careless Miss is rock?
Careless Miss is not rock
It's not rock? Then what is it?
Acapella
Then it's not a band
It's not a band
Why?
It's a cappella
It's not a band
What do you want to know?
You're going to see Careless Miss, aren't you?
Aren't you going?
I'm going, so what is this?
It's Two Days
What do you know?
I don't know
You're saying something I've never heard before
It's Three Days
Which is it?
If you say something good, it's Three Days
For the time being, it's Two Days. Try it
I was listening to what you were saying
Then your cell phone rang
Careless Miss
I was wearing it
Your cell phone rang and you said, I'm sorry
Why did you sit down?
It's not like you're with a woman
I'm a caretaker, so I said, I'm sorry
Then I went to the front door
Well, try it on the second day
DVD 4th edition is about to be released
The last of the four months of release
It's a masterpiece talk that includes an unpublished scene that couldn't be broadcast on TV
In addition, the 15-year confrontation and punishment game will be released
Please look forward to it