I'm not a kid, so I'm Yamazaki Otaku Omon Prank Camera!
Well, you've seen Yamazaki-kun.
I've seen him.
Actually, it's his second time.
Let's trick him.
I'm a little worried if I'm going to say something good.
What are we going to do today?
Well, to the people who set it up.
Please come in.
First of all, I've been doing terrible things on Telekura before.
In the past, I played the role of being deceived.
I'm Takasu-kun of Telekura.
Please come in.
Actually, today, Takasu-kun asked me to lend him a room.
Yamazaki-kun's room.
He asked me to lend him a room.
He asked me to stay with his girlfriend.
Actually, his girlfriend was this woman.
Yamazaki-kun came back and this appeared there.
I've been a Yankee for a long time.
I was very strong.
You say a lot.
I'm in the class of the boss.
You're a small boss, aren't you?
I'm a small boss.
Was I really the boss?
Well, let's prank him.
First of all, please come in as his girlfriend.
What's your name?
I'm Asaki Misato.
Misato-san.
Actually, Takasu-kun is called Yamazaki.
To her.
To borrow a room.
It's better to call her Yamazaki.
It's my room.
To her.
So I'm Yamazaki.
Yamazaki-kun came back while I was in the warehouse.
And she's gone.
Then this man will appear.
Please come in.
No matter how you look at it, you don't look like an elementary school student.
I'm Murakami-san, who introduced the villain.
I'm Misato-chan.
When I was told that I couldn't do anything to my Misato,
I wondered if Yamazaki would blow out the panchowkaze.
I'm still in a good mood.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
He's here.
Run.
Hello.
It's cold.
I'm fine.
What?
I'm going camping.
Yamazaki-san, what are you doing?
Nothing.
Go, go, go.
Don't move.
Hello.
Is Yamazaki there?
It's me.
It's me?
Hey.
You.
Misato.
I'll kick you out.
Misato?
Yeah.
Hey.
Don't mess with me.
Who is Misato?
Don't talk to me like that.
Don't think about it.
Hey.
Say something.
Wait a minute.
What are you talking about?
I'll be there soon.
Wait a minute.
Who are you?
Murakami.
Wait a minute.
Come here.
I'll wait for you.
Hey.
Say something.
Who is Misato?
This?
I just got a call.
From Murakami.
Wait a minute.
I'll be there soon.
Say something.
What is it?
I'll wait for you.
No way.
My voice is shaking.
I can't stand it.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What did you say?
I just got a call.
I'll be there soon.
Hey.
What is it?
I just got a call.
Misato.
Misato?
Who is it?
Don't lie to me.
Murakami.
I'll be there soon.
Is she a Yakuza woman?
This is the worst.
I'll be there soon.
What is it?
It's like this.
Hello?
I'm in Yamazaki.
Yes.
Are you Yamazaki?
No, I'm in Takasu.
Get out of here.
Yamazaki?
What do you mean?
I'll be there soon.
Wait for me.
Yamazaki is somewhere else.
What is it?
I'm scared.
I'm in trouble.
I don't know the number.
I know the number.
By phone?
I don't know the number by phone.
I'm scared.
It's okay.
I don't know the number by phone.
I'm here.
What are you going to do?
I'll ask.
Who is it?
It's me.
I'll go from there.
Are you going to run away?
Let go of me.
I can't run away.
Excuse me.
I'm Yamazaki.
What are you?
Yamazaki is over here.
I'm Yamazaki.
I'm sorry.
I'm not Yamazaki.
I'm not.
I'm sorry.
You need to spend more time in your home.
I have my brother with me.
I'm not Yamazaki.
He's the leader.
I'm sorry.
My brother's not alive.
I'm not Yamazaki.
Hello.
Let me go.
Ouch!
I'm sorry!
Hello, I'm Murakami.
Ouch!
I'm sorry!
I thought I was going to die.
Let's get out of here.
When I called you, you said you were fine.
You're really bad at this.
Yamada, let me introduce you.
He's a villain.
I did it at any time.
You're crying.
I'm about to cry.
I was deceived again.
I'm gonna cry.
I'm gonna grind my teeth.
I will do what I can.
I'm going to run.
I'll talk to you later.
Please wait a minute.
You've beenаний.
enough
Stop it!
You've been khácly!
Ladies and Gentlemen
Hello!
Let's have a good time today.
Although I'm a little bit tired.
Let's talk a little bit and go home.
Talk a little bit and go home.
I've been saying this for a long time, but I can't reach your hands anymore.
I've been saying that I'm a star.
But in the end, I'm just a twinkle little star.
What are you talking about?
What's a twinkle little star?
I'm just a little star.
I'm not that big of a star.
But...
Hey, wait a minute.
What?
Why are you talking while looking at me?
But we're three times bigger than you think we are.
Is that what you wanted to say?
That's right.
The next one?
There's one in Yoshimoto Kogyo.
Well, specifically, there are two.
The medal has arrived.
Masamotoshi Toshi, Hamada Masatoshi.
I wrote it down.
Who sent it?
I took a quick look.
Kaifu Toshiki
The Prime Minister of Japan.
What does this mean?
This is us.
We are the people of Takane no Hana.
He's just saying it.
Well, next up is the Prime Minister.
It's a confederation with a culture person.
A confederation.
Miyazawa Rie was here last year, wasn't she?
That's right.
Next time.
We're next to Kaifu-chan.
Well, really.
He wants to touch our skin, doesn't he?
He wants to...
He wants to grab this fortune.
That's what he thought.
Well, I understand how he feels.
That's right.
This is us.
Well, there are people who can't go.
Well, this is us.
Let's go.
Right?
By all means.
Let's go by all means.
What should we wear?
Right?
By all means, we'll go to a place like that.
It says, please come to the confederation in your daily clothes.
But to be honest, there's no one who dresses up like that.
T-shirts and jeans.
That's a bit rude.
So, we'll go in matching party dresses.
You're wearing a party dress.
And matching.
You're opening your chest a bit boldly.
Yes, yes, yes.
Wearing a flower.
Wearing a net.
I think there was a misfortune.
It's like this.
I don't know if I can talk to them.
I don't know who they are.
Who are these two?
But I'll talk to them in order.
I don't think it's about who they are.
I'm sorry.
The Prime Minister.
When we went before,
Who are these two?
Why do you want to talk to them?
How are you doing recently?
That's all you can say.
You can only say something abstract.
I can't say anything.
What should we do at that time?
I don't know if we should be serious.
That's fine as usual, isn't it?
It's up to you.
When we went before,
What do you think of the song?
Maybe if you do that,
The SP will come and say,
Yes, wait a minute.
No way.
There's a guy like this next to the Prime Minister.
People will think you're crazy.
Foreign exile.
It's not that far.
But I wonder how far you'll go.
I'd like to hear something about Nepal Pearl.
If you make a suspicious move,
The SP will make a mysterious move.
When it goes like this,
People will think you're crazy.
When the hand goes like this,
When it goes like this,
You're a karate master.
I think you're going to do something.
I don't want it to be like this.
You have to keep it tight.
For the time being,
Just do something.
Make a strange face.
Is that allowed?
That's about it.
When I pass by,
I'll make a normal face.
Where do you do your makeup?
If there's a pencil,
I'm a magician.
I can do anything.
I'll go to the bathroom.
I can be a strong tiger.
You don't look like a tiger.
I can be a dog or anything.
Do it properly.
I'll stand up with my face.
What are you going to do when I do that?
Let's keep a distance.
Why don't you do it with me?
Why?
I don't want to be dragged.
Let's wear a costume.
What kind of costume?
I don't know.
When I saw the costume,
I thought you were laughing.
Let's write Down Town on the T-shirt.
It's not B&B.
Why?
I used to wear B&B.
I used to wear a T-shirt with Pionkichi's picture on it.
You?
Yes.
You should wear that.
With Pionkichi's picture on it?
Yes.
It's just a shirt.
It's a running shirt.
It's not naked.
I think I can do it.
Or you can dress up as a TV character.
What do you have now?
Something that has an impact.
Is it Hideki?
But if it's Hideki,
people will think it's really Hideki.
People will think it's really Hideki.
Hello.
This person is...
Mr. Yamada.
It's a very ordinary name.
It's nothing.
If it's Yamada Mari,
there are probably tens of thousands of people in Japan right now.
There are?
Mr. Yamada is at the venue today.
Is he here?
Yes.
Hey!
You're a man no matter where you're from.
Yamada Mari is the only one who says,
shut up to you.
Thank you very much.
Now...
What?
Let's move on to the postcards.
I'm a very cute middle school girl.
By the way,
have you ever thought that Machan and Amachan are so scary that you could die?
When I was in elementary school,
I was waiting for my friends in front of the school gate.
A strange old man came up to me and pointed at the poster on the wall.
He said,
this is me.
So I looked at it half-heartedly.
I was surprised again.
As the old man said,
this old man was a criminal who was on the verge of death.
The old man laughed at me.
I was so scared that I had no choice but to run and run and run back home.
This is scary.
I wonder if he really did that.
Is such a guy walking around?
In front of the school gate?
There are really many things.
You know,
a long time ago,
I told you about my brother.
He was running in a single car in the middle of the night.
Then,
the old man was covered in blood and was lying down.
I stopped the single car and asked him what happened.
He was in a state where he couldn't speak.
He was covered in blood.
He was spitting blood out of his mouth.
I wish I had left him alone.
That's not a good thing.
But you can't just leave him alone.
What's wrong with you going that far?
It's not true.
If you go that far, you'll be fine.
I felt sorry for him.
I went to the pharmacy.
I bought disinfectant and gauze.
I went back to the pharmacy.
The old man was covered in blood.
I wish I had left him alone.
Someone called the police.
The police came.
What happened?
When I told him about my brother,
the blood-soaked old man suddenly stood up
and pointed at my brother.
He said,
He did it!
My brother was in a state of shock.
I can't believe it.
It's love-sody.
His eyes were like this.
His nose was like this.
I think you should help people.
Help people.
Can you do emergency treatment?
For example, if you have blood coming out of your nose.
Yes, I can.
I've said this before,
but I've never fixed my gauze.
Really?
When?
Two years ago.
Why did you cut it?
Why did you cut here?
Because it hurt.
It hurt? Okay.
Why did you cut it?
I cut it.
You cut it?
Pull out the gauze.
What are you going to do?
What?
How do you fix your gauze?
Pull out the gauze.
I pulled out the gauze and cut it.
Why?
Why did you cut here?
If you do this, it will stick.
You don't know anything.
If you cut it like this, it will stick.
Let's cut it.
What?
It's okay.
I got it.
Wait a minute.
It's okay.
It hurts.
What?
It's okay, but I'll sue you.
You should sue me.
But I don't like it because you cut it.
I want to see it.
What do you want to see?
How long does it take to stick?
Two and a half minutes.
Let's go home.
It's enough.
I can't decide when to go home.
I'm always surprised when I go home.
Okay, it's over.
Let's clean up over there.
Let's put it all in the back.
Put it in and take out the bean ball.
Shogun, turn off the light.
Turn off the light.
It's too hot to touch the bean ball.
Let's go home.
Let's clean up the microphone, too.
We have to get rid of the fire.
Let's get rid of the fire.
Okay, it's over.
Thank you for your hard work.
Turn around.
Who are you talking to?
Hello.
Today's opening is interesting.
It's the best.
What are you going to do with the pranks from now on?
What do people do?
What kind of prank would you like to try next time?
I want to try something I think I don't know.
I want to try something I don't know.
I want to change it to a soft temperature meter that I have.
A stopwatch?
It will take time to notice.
And the ending.
As I said today, the way to go home.
I always hear people say,
I'm going home.
If you say,
Let's think about this.
The most ideal is when you go home.
From the top,
How do you say it?
The stars in the sky are falling.
We'll get on there.
Get on and go home.
No matter where you go home.
If you can do that,
You can go home cleanly.
That's right.
The two of us will become stars.
Because I'm a star.
I'm going home.
Well, if that's the case,
I'll ask for it.
What kind of movie do you want to watch?
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll do my best until next week.
Thank you.
This program was provided by the following sponsors.