Oh, it's a supermarket in Ikkaku-senshin.
Oh, it's a supermarket in Ikkaku.
Thank you, thank you.
Yeah, I'm also using the wheel because the oil temperature is low.
Yes.
It was a fierce battle.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
What I'm most afraid of is the signal.
Whether it will work or not.
Whether it's working or not.
Are you doing what I told you to do?
No.
You shouldn't do that.
The water is cold.
I think we have to deal with it.
It's pretty deep.
It's deep.
Is that all you can do?
I practiced a lot yesterday, too.
And...
Can I ask you something?
When I was searching for sharks,
I found this.
I can't speak.
Because I'm in the water.
When I found sharks,
I found this.
When I found a chopper,
When I found this,
I found this.
I don't think I'll ever find it.
But...
They're violent, too.
If someone pulls my hair,
I'll be fine.
Okay?
Yeah.
I don't know what to do.
I don't have to fight sharks in a shock wave box.
Right?
Yeah.
But...
You don't have to do it.
You can't do it on Japanese TV.
You can't do it on NHK's documentary.
I can't do it on NHK's documentary.
Oh!
Is it a shark?
Is it?
No, it's not a shark.
You have to do it right away.
Otherwise, I don't know.
I'll watch it with this.
Let's go!
Okay.
Be careful.
Why is the rope tied?
Be careful!
Okay!
Let's go!
I don't know what it is.
What is this?
I haven't lost yet.
Are you looking for it now?
Yeah.
I don't know what it is.
I found it.
I don't know.
Oh!
It's a child.
No way!
It's fighting.
Really?
Is it fighting?
It's fighting.
Yeah!
Is this the same thing?
Yeah.
It looks like it's fighting.
It's fighting.
What happened?
Are you okay?
Oh!
Oh, my God!
It's fighting.
I want to stop it.
It's a sea bream.
There is no fish.
Now is a good time.
It's not recording.
It's not as good as we thought.
Let's stop it.
Stop it.
It's not as good as we thought.
Did you go to school today?
Yes, I did.
Do you go to school every day?
Yes, every day.
I see.
That's why you are the documentary of NHK.
That's true.
Let's go to school!
I heard that you went to school.
Well, well.
Let's go to school.
Let's get excited.
I'm counting on you.
Yes.
Wait.
Did you hear something?
I heard it from here.
Did you hear it?
What?
I heard it from here.
I'm looking for it.
What?
I didn't see it.
It's a sweet shrimp.
It's 380 yen.
It's 280 yen for one matumoto.
What?
It's a mackerel.
It's one matumoto.
What?
It's a mackerel.
What is it?
Hey.
It's a mackerel.
What's going on?
What?
What is it?
We did it!
We are safe!
What is it?
We did it!
I got it!
Today's opening is 60 points.
What should we do?
What happened?
Now, when it comes to the topic, it is that,
The Madonna photo book.
Madonna?
What are you doing?
Are you drawing Madonna?
How is it?
Well,
I don't know where it is.
Certainly,
As I do in the news,
I'm surrounded by thin men and Madonna.
After all,
I'm sleeping.
Why are you interested in such a place?
No!
You are a fool!
Madonna is a
Madonna
What the hell is Madonna?
!
Can't we just get Madonna to be an a-hole?
It doesn't make any sense if Madonna is an a-hole.
What's Madonna.
What makes you understand?
Oh, Madonna's to be.
What's Madonna?
It doesn't make any sense if Madonna is頑派.
A-hole?
That's no, no.
You can't hide it.
In my opinion, women have become clear recently, so I don't know if that's the case.
It depends on the country.
There are things that even a father can't do.
It's no good to be united.
It's okay if you don't unite.
That's why I can't get a robot.
Why don't you say something?
I don't know why.
Japan is gradually becoming clear, isn't it?
In Japan, an amateur wants to leave my beautiful nakedness.
There's no such thing as a beautiful thing.
I don't like it.
There's no such thing as a beautiful body.
Something is definitely wrong.
I'm slow because I have a good proportion, but when I'm like this, I'm like an Ultraman.
My bones are like this.
I'm like, I'll give you a check.
It's really a great world, isn't it?
What kind of people are you talking about?
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm not saying anything else.
That's why I can't fall for it.
You fell for it when you saw Miyazawa Rie in the Asahi newspaper.
You're the only one who falls for it in the newspaper.
Are you stupid?
I was surprised.
Why?
It's the first time I've been able to get naked.
My wife pulled it out.
I was turning it over.
I have a wife.
I thought I was going to die.
I hid it.
I thought, go to bed, go to bed.
I checked the story and said, Hira-kun, you shouldn't make a sound.
I said something like that.
Maybe you're watching it before me.
Then the sound of the newspaper will be equal.
You'll think I'm watching it.
Clip.
What about the draft?
What are you talking about?
What's going to happen to the draft?
Who's the star of the year?
It's a guy from Seiryo.
Who?
Matsushita from Seiryo.
It's Matsui.
Do you want that?
How much is he?
How much is 100 million?
Do you want that?
It's amazing.
What's amazing?
The patching.
Is that so?
I'm not the first person to buy that kind of thing for 100 million.
That's why the titans are like this.
Only the titans can buy that?
Is it a draft for that?
Which team will win the auction?
For example, even if I want to buy it, I can't.
What are you going to do?
What are you going to do with Matsui?
Are you going to take him to the scene?
Like Deshiko?
Is that impossible?
Of course it's impossible.
But that's Amada.
What? What's Amada?
Is that impossible?
It's impossible.
Do you have anything to use?
I think I should take it.
Who?
Me.
There?
Anywhere.
Is the test over?
What test?
The professional test.
It's over.
Then I don't know.
Do you want to go?
The entrance test?
Yes.
I'm serious.
I'm going in.
I can't help it at that time.
I'm going to disband gradually.
I'm going in.
Where do you want to go?
Where should I go?
What are you?
What am I?
No.
What's the baseball data?
What's the pitcher?
What's the yas?
It's short.
It's a non-yash.
Really?
Yes.
Where do you want to go?
Daiei?
Why do you want to go to Daiei?
Daiei feels good.
What are you talking about?
It's cheap.
Are you stupid?
Anyone can go to the professional test, right?
Yes, anyone can go.
What is it?
The course, the course.
The course and the course alone are really amazing.
It's a course.
It's far away.
Throw it around like this.
It's not far away.
It's really far away.
I'll throw it.
You're young.
I'll try to throw it to the other side.
It's a circle.
Where are you looking?
I'm sure you've been there a lot.
I haven't been there.
I've been there a lot.
It's a place like this.
I can't get out of here.
I'm so frustrated.
Do you know the difference between Serif and Parim?
I know.
What are you talking about?
What is Serif?
Are you stupid?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but I'll tell you.
It's a giant.
What?
Is it a midday?
Weil's not moving fast.
It's in Hiroshima.
Hurry up.
Then it's the sun.
Sun?
One more, look.
It doesn't matter if I tell you about the sun first.
What's the matter?
There's a problem on the sun.
It doesn't matter.
I'll do one last word.
This is like a spell, so if you don't continue, if I ask you to say the sun, Hamada-kun, I'll be there.
What are you talking about?
I told you to hurry up and go!
I just said it!
You didn't say it, you missed one.
You're a titan, aren't you?
Yes, yes, yes.
The sun!
Yes, one more.
So don't say the sun!
You're talking about a sun too early now.
You're a titan, aren't you.
Yes.
You're a sun, aren't you.
No.
You're a midday, aren't you.
Yes.
You're a Hanshin.
And then you're Hiroshima, aren't you?
One more.
So don't say the sun!
Stop it.
If you say the sun, you won't be told anything.
Isn't it the sun you want to know?
If you say such a thing.
What are you talking about?
I can't say it.
It hurts if you say the sun.
Who are you to say such a thing?
I can't say it's a parry, can I?
It's a save, right?
I can say it's a parry, right?
I can't say it's a save, right?
I can't say it's a parry, can I?
Why are you so mad?
You're so stupid!
What's a save and what?
What?
You're saying it, right?
I'm saying only two things.
You're getting more and more mad!
I'm not mad!
I'm just saying two things!
You're getting more and more mad!
If you say it so fast, you'll be thrown off the field!
You won't be able to keep up with me!
You!
You're thinking that.
You're!
Gosh!
If you can't say that you're a full-backs' sixth team or 12th team, then you're not good at baseball?
I can't say that.
I may not be able to say that, but I'm insanely good!
I want you to try to swing it.
What do you mean?
Like batting.
That was really...
That was really flying.
It's really okay.
It's really okay. If you can't do it in secret, you can do it in the opening like a protest.
There's a standard.
Let's do a speed gun.
That's a good idea.
Let's do that.
How many kilograms of speed gun can you do?
The highest is about 121.
I don't think so.
You're a young bird.
How many kilograms can you do?
I've never measured it.
How many kilograms of speed gun can you do?
What?
Like a spinning top.
I'm sorry. I'm like that.
Matsumoto-san always says bad things about me.
How much do you think you're cool?
But it's not funny to say this.
How many points out of 100 do you think you're cool?
How many points do you think you're cool?
I've never eaten enough.
My eyebrows are a little more beautiful.
There's a part that's a little rough.
I'll take this off and do about 60 points.
How many points do you think you're cool?
There's a lot of parts in the middle.
It's like a Thai.
Don't be so polite.
There's a lot of parts in the middle.
That's right.
About 80 points.
80 points?
How many points do you think you're cool?
20 points.
Even if there are four Joes, you're not cool.
You're amazing.
How many points do you think you're cool?
I'm really sorry.
I'm 100 points.
As a man, I don't know how to say this.
I'm not cool.