Program Comedian
Stand up properly!
So the opening for today is to long for this
Yes
Let's make a show with erotic language
This is for some extent
Let's just leave it as it is
Today, without the two of us, we're going to invite the best.
Please come in.
This person is amazing.
It's Froggy!
Please come in!
Please come in.
Thank you for coming.
Today, we have two wonderful guests.
Wow, it's a surprise.
Did you see it?
I'm so happy.
Froggy, you came alone today, right?
That's right.
When I'm alone, I always act like a woman.
Is that so?
Froggy!
When you're alone, you'll be told a lot of unpleasant things, right?
Don't you do that?
Something like, let me do it.
Or, let's do it.
Unfortunately, I don't do that.
You don't?
Yes.
If you're walking down the street and you see Froggy, you want to talk to her, right?
That's right.
Please talk to her.
Please talk to Spelman.
Shall we start?
Yes.
Let's start with a gentle one.
A gentle one.
Yes.
Tama.
Oh, is it okay if I say it?
No, it's fine.
Is it okay?
Don't worry about it.
Mara.
I said it softly.
Even if you say ra, it's fine.
It's fine, right?
Ra-ge.
Ge.
Ge?
It's fine.
There's no ge.
There isn't.
But, when I do the velatio, I don't know what to do.
Who said that?
That's right.
That's why, if you want to make it a ge,
if you want to make it a ge,
I'll make it a ge.
Ge.
Gezori.
Ah, I see.
It's gezori.
Gezori's ri, right?
Yes.
Gezori is always Ogawa Natsumi-san's ge.
That's funny.
Then, let's call it Rinbyo.
By the way, have you experienced it?
What?
Have you experienced Rinbyo?
Ah, I've experienced gejirami once.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Let's see.
Is it ri or ya?
Yes.
Well...
She's in trouble.
Yarigaegaeshi.
What?
Well, this Nobutoitakumashi Yarigaeshi is called Yarigaegaeshi.
This is the new trend of the 21st century.
Is that so?
It's a trendy word.
Shi...
Shikko.
Ah, that's wonderful.
It's also said that you like to drink it.
Who said that?
No, no, no.
Yes, you like to drink it.
Yes.
Well...
Kondoumu.
That's right.
It's a condom that you've never used.
I've never used a condom.
You don't use condoms, do you?
That's right.
I use a face shower every day.
Thank you very much.
Kondoumu.
It's Kondoumu.
There's a word called Muse.
That's wonderful.
That's right.
I'm a woman, so I don't have any experience with Muse.
In the case that you followed me,
I would like to express my gratitude and give you a wakige.
That's wonderful.
Please take it off.
Can I take it off?
No, it's a pleasure to take it off.
A little more.
That's wonderful.
That way of taking it off.
I don't think it's the first time you've taken it off.
Last night, you actually took off your lover's wakige.
You showed it in your fingers.
Hey, I'm not going home.
Let me stay here.
It's Muse.
Muse.
Well...
Inge.
Kejirami.
That's right.
Mii.
It's a word from the Seisei period.
Mus.
How do you tattoo your breasts?
Lovingly.
Yes.
Tattooing breasts.
It is done by a woman.
Well, thinking of how you've said that, it seems here that the woman's breasts are quite big.
There's eight tiene in here.
There's eight tane.
Who is that?
I think it's nice.
Does everyone know this person?
Man, it's really cold.
No, really.
Yes?
It's that.
What is it?
I think Nina-san has a slight cold.
I don't know if there are people who don't have a cold.
But, maybe there are people who don't think so.
What is it?
I really work hard.
What is that?
No, but I don't think so.
I wonder if everyone doesn't think so.
But I really work hard.
No, really.
Even now, if I'm a little tired, I fall down.
I'm that kind of person.
No, it's not like that.
You've just been working as a regular.
That's right, but I'm tired.
Really?
Yes.
I think the three things that a regular can do are the most important.
Really?
Yes.
It's important to die, right?
Yes, the three things are the most important.
What is it?
You work three days a week and rest four days a week.
No, but I've been working in Osaka and Tokyo for seven months now.
Well, yes.
I have to work hard.
You've been working hard for seven months, haven't you?
No, no, no, no.
Let's make it three.
What do you want me to do?
You can leave the kids and stand up.
Stand up?
The kids are free to do whatever they want, so it's the easiest for us.
Let's leave this.
I'll leave the kids.
Then I'll go to Japan.
Well, let me tell you.
I'm doing a water show.
I'm going to the water show.
I'm not doing it.
Are you saying that?
I'm going to the water show on Wednesday.
What is that?
It's a dream.
It's a bad title.
I don't want to help you.
Let's stop.
I'm getting old.
What are you talking about?
I want to do more hobbies.
I want to do a lot of things like horse riding.
What kind of face is that?
What kind of face is horse riding?
I want to do it.
I have a lot of days off.
I have a lot of days off, but I don't want to spend it.
I want you to stop this.
I've been telling you this for a long time.
You can't go around.
I can't even tell you how much I'm tired.
I'm not tired.
I can do it.
I'm writing a fan letter.
That's why I'm saying it's a dream.
But the fan letter can be written.
You guys are getting in the way of my free time.
Do you write that?
What fan do you write?
When I came back from Osaka, I was on the Shinkansen. It was really hard, but I thought I shouldn't say it was that hard.
I thought I shouldn't say it was that hard.
So I took a taxi to Shin-Oda.
The driver said,
I'm from Tokyo.
I said, Where are you from now?
He said, I'm going to the radio.
From now on, the radio!
Ha!
That's a lot of work!
That's what you do!
I went into the radio.
I asked him,
You look like you're in trouble.
And then,
He said,
He said, Bueh!
That's a lot of work!
Bueh! Bueh! Bueh!
That's what you do!
I can't do it!
I'm not good at drawing.
I can't do that.
Because of you, I had a hard time yesterday.
What?
I had to go to Kyoto yesterday.
Kyoto.
The day before that,
It took until 4 o'clock in the evening.
It's 5 o'clock when I got home.
I had to go to Kyoto on the 7.50 Shinkansen.
I couldn't sleep.
I left home about 6 o'clock.
I was on the Shinkansen.
I arrived at 7.20.
I was on the Shinkansen for 30 minutes.
I was sitting on the Shinkansen.
I was sleepy.
I was watching sports news.
Time passed.
I couldn't sleep.
I was on the Shinkansen at 7.56.
I was on the Shinkansen for 50 minutes.
Hamada, let's get off!
Why?
Mr. Matsumoto told me to bring you back.
What are you talking about?
I have to protect my body.
You're annoying!
I really need it.
I got home at 5 o'clock.
It took only 2 hours.
I took a bath.
I thought I shouldn't sleep.
But I'm tired.
I'm exhausted.
I have a companion girl.
You're just an old man.
I was taking a nap.
I was taking a nap, too.
Yes, yes.
I didn't see you.
And then...
At 7 o'clock, it's Sunday.
It's Sunday.
I'm going to pick you up on Sunday.
Do you call it Sunday?
Where are you looking?
I'm a dance manager.
Ping-pong, ping-pong, ping-pong.
At first, I heard ping-pong.
So I thought it was Ping-pong.
Everyone was there, but I didn't fool them.
I thought it was Ping-pong at first.
But I knew it was Sunday.
I'm not Ping-pong.
That's right.
So I thought it was wrong.
You knew it.
I knew it right away.
You knew it was Sunday.
I knew it was Sunday right away.
It's Sunday.
I'm going to work.
I say what I think and what I think back.
Before the time...
I really like you, but I hate you.
I said it in a strong way.
Women's hearts and autumn sky.
It's similar to the weather in the mountains.
I don't know why.
That's enough.
I'm tired.
I got it.
I wanted to do it once.
You can't do it.
I can't do it.
I said.
Let's go without saying that.
Nitta said.
I can't help it.
I said.
It's like a good taste of a stubborn stall.
Everyone is laughing, but I'm laughing.
There's such a thing.
I wanted to show you something stubborn.
I can't do it.
Then Nitta said.
I got it.
Akagi.
Yes.
Oh, come on.
Today, too.
Pia's.
Bull's eye.
Pia's Bull's eye.
Teresa's Bull's eye.
Akagi's.
I'll give you this for now.
Have you ever seen this program?
I'm sorry.
I have.
I don't use it.
You've got a job.
Have you ever thought about quitting today?
I have.
Hey, look.
What are you doing?
Wait.
That's what happens to humans.
You can't do that.
Idiot.
Thank you very much.
Really.
Please take a look.
Kumi Ozone from Yokohama City.
He's 20 years old.
Mr. Hamada is going to play golf.
How good are you?
I run a golf course.
Yes.
Please come next time.
And the winner of the Chikichiki Golf Tournament will compete with me.
Thank you very much.
I'm not good enough to compete with you.
But you look like you're having fun.
Are you really going to let me win?
I'm sure you'll let me win.
Are you going to let me win for free?
Yes.
Then I'll play golf.
You look like you're having fun.
I'll play golf.
Yes.
The one who wins.
The one who loses.
Yes.
And a little...
Are you allowed to say that?
I'm not that good at it.
I'm not good at it.
You've never done anything, have you?
No, I haven't.
I'll never win.
I'm sure of it.
How good is your par four?
It's still a par, so I'll have to put it in four.
I'll put it in four.
Four.
Thanks.
Therefore, it's not six or seven.
What?
Where you want to put it, six or seven?
You're a pro at it.
No, I'm not.
Really.
I'm a professional. Don't make fun of me.
Let's have a golf match.
Let's think about it.
What if I lose?
Yes, yes, yes.
It's a punishment game.
Let's think of something better than skydiving.
There are times when you're the one who's in the back.
Are you stupid?
You can think of something like that.
You can't do that right away.
You should do it while you're practicing.
What?
That's right.
I'm good at playing on the field.
Have you ever been on a golf course?
Let's play golf.
Let's think about it.
Every time my mother appears on TV, she says,
Oh, Yakuza.
I'm watching it, but I'm going to turn it off.
Well, that's about it.
Do you have a Yakuza?
It's about you.
It's definitely different.
You don't look like a Yakuza.
How much do you...
You're imitating me from a great distance.
Am I stupid?
How much am I?
You're amazing.
There's a dog following me.
There's a pigeon flying around here.
There's a deer laughing.
Where are you walking?
There's a deer following me.
You're walking, but you're stupid.
I'm trying to get close to you.
There's a deer laughing.
I don't know.
Are you going to get up?
If I were to go through that dead flower...
People who've been sick for a long time...
It's going to be a good feeling.
That's you.
The other day...
There's nothing wrong with his standing.
When I went to Hong Kong before...
I went to Hong Kong.
I didn't know what to do when I went to Hong Kong.
After I got there, I went to the tax office.
The people over there are a little slow.
One by one.
If you don't check it carefully, you don't know what you're holding.
Everyone knows that.
Even if you get a certificate, it's already overseas.
Everyone thinks of it as a Tsukimon.
They're lined up like this.
It was a little late.
I went to Hong Kong.
I didn't understand Japanese at all.
I caught a girl.
What's wrong with you guys?
Hong Kong people are...
What do you call it?
They're all over the place.
It's you, isn't it?
How many times have you been to Hong Kong?
I've been to Hong Kong many times.
You don't like Hong Kong people, do you?
Come on, come on.
Don't be so comical.
You've been like this all the time.
What's wrong with that?
But I don't understand English.
You know what?
I understand.
You understand?
Why don't you understand Japanese?
I don't understand.
What I want to focus on is this.
That's why I don't understand what you're saying.
I understand this.
Why do you understand Japanese?
This is...
It's kind of like a baby's cry.
It's common in all countries.
I don't think it's carbonated water because you said it.
I'm back.
Who are you talking to?
That's about it.
What?
That's...
You're not even acting.
You can do the one with Mr. Nika.
I'll do it.
That was a good one.
I'm looking for a copy of the agreement.
Please bring it to me.
Thank you for coming today.
This reminds me of the Shimin Pool.
That's about it.
Mr. Kuroki came to the opening today.
That was amazing.
He was in a good mood.
It was a little intense.
I couldn't say anything because I didn't watch the video.
And Mr. Kuroki.
Next time...
We're all here together.
I'm going to show you what we did together.
Did I say that?
You did.
Are you kidding me?
I'm going to show you what we did together next time.
That's about it.
I'm going to do it next time.
Bye.
Ouch!
I'm going to show you what we did together next time.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.