Chiki Chiki's once a year event! Let's have a great time!
Let's forget about work and have a great time!
Kogoriko, how was your first year?
How was it?
Kogoriko, congratulations!
You're really like Kogoriko.
I was born as a child of a gag called Hohohoi.
It was a year that was dyed in only that.
How was your first year?
Good luck!
How was your first year in Downtown?
It was a good year.
You didn't invite me before.
Cheers!
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Let's get started!
Let's have an apple competition!
Let's start with the first one.
It's number 16, Ai.
It's number 32, N.
It's number 31, Ai.
It's number 21, Ai.
Bingo!
Good morning.
Wait a minute.
I only said three words.
It's bingo, right?
Where was it?
Good morning.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Did you say you're late?
Yes.
It's a tradition.
What's wrong with the board?
There's a leech, but there's no bingo.
It's number 16, Ai.
It's number 32, N.
It's bingo.
There's a leech, but there's no bingo.
Everyone's got a product.
Oh, a board?
Yes.
That's what it is.
I'll take this one out.
I'll take it out.
Wait a minute.
Is this okay?
It's fresh, isn't it?
No, it's not.
Who is it?
It's my wife.
I'm hungry.
What are you talking about?
What's this?
It's my child.
Harumi.
Harumi?
Can I adjust the order?
It doesn't matter.
It's bingo.
It's getting more and more bingo.
Congratulations.
Congratulations on the bingo.
Thank you.
Let's move on.
Wait a minute.
One more product.
What?
This is bingo, too.
I don't like this.
It's different.
It's bingo, right?
Of course.
The types are completely different.
It's different.
The dough is different.
I'm so frustrated.
Let's do it at a good tempo.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Let's go.
It's out.
It's No. 68.
It's N.
Let's go.
It's bingo.
Excuse me.
What is this?
There is no prototype.
There is no standard.
It's bingo.
You just wrote this, didn't you?
What?
The free is at the edge.
That's not funny.
It's bingo, right?
It's not bingo, right?
It's a normal paper, isn't it?
It's bingo.
It's a child's work.
I want to say bingo.
I'm here to say bingo.
There is a rule.
I may have said bingo too much.
Right?
It's bingo, bingo, bingo.
Are you okay?
You look like you just got out of bed.
He was talking.
Harumi-chan.
You're an adult.
You're saying bingo, but you don't know what to do.
Call an ambulance.
That's enough.
Are you okay?
I got it.
That's enough.
Let's do it.
It's B3.
This is a bit...
Super Famicom is a bit...
It's a child's game.
It's fine.
Is it this?
Bingo, bingo, bingo.
This is the most eye-catching.
I don't think kids will understand even if I give them a DVD.
I think they will be happy with the game.
That's not true.
You think so too, don't you?
Of course I do.
I told you.
What?
I don't think so.
I told you I don't think so.
What is this?
Uji, give me all of them.
This is the most eye-catching.
What are you doing?
I'm your junior, but...
Why are you pulling it so hard?
I can't give it to you.
I'll give you this.
I got it.
I'll give it to you later.
I'll give you this.
I'll give you this DVD.
Let's do it.
But...
What should we do?
How about Bingo?
Can we do that?
Let's do it.
At rock-paper-scissors,
we'll give away a Hawaii record!
Thank you.
It's fair.
At this time of the year...
That's amazing.
I'll tell you.
The person who gets Aiko will lose.
That's great.
Rock-paper-scissors!
Are you ready?
Again?
Sorry.
What's wrong?
I was looking at my dad.
He changed.
At first, it was Aiko.
It was obvious.
At rock-paper-scissors,
Aiko loses.
I was looking at Itao.
It was Aiko.
Let's go to the front and do it here.
Let's do it here.
Can we do it in the front?
Let's do it in the front.
Hawaii.
In California.
Rock-paper-scissors!
I won.
Look at it.
There's nothing wrong with it.
I won.
How was it?
I was looking at it in front of me.
I changed.
I didn't change.
What's wrong with you?
Sorry.
I didn't change.
Don't say it.
In the end, there are only three people who won.
That's good.
I don't know.
I don't know who won again.
I don't know how I won.
I don't know how I did it.
I don't know.
If you give me Hawaii, I'll give it to you.
I'll give you a pair.
I'll give you a pair for one trip to Hawaii.
Are you alone in Hawaii?
I'll ask you the other way around. Can you go alone in Hawaii?
It's Hawaii.
On such a large scale.
Alone?
There's a lot of food there.
You can't go alone.
So what?
It's for the family.
If it's for the family, it's a pair.
It's impossible for three people.
I have a neck pain, but I'm wearing it.
What's wrong with your neck?
I got hit before.
Is it still healed?
It's almost healed.
I'll do it.
Bring it home.
It's too late.
I don't have any more.
Thank you.
Please do something for one person.
I understand.
I'll give you a pair for one trip to Hawaii.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Have a good year.
Did you learn Japanese?
Did you read it?
I read it.
You didn't read it, did you?
I'll give you a pair for one trip to Hawaii.
Matsumoto-san.
It's probably over with this face.
Machan, baby.
Hi, hi.
Machan is so cute.
Why Machan?
Machan.
Machan, baby.
Hanna-chan, lady.
It's difficult.
I told you.
Let's change it right away.
Oh, yes.
I'll change it to Bohemian.
It's too late to change it to Bohemian.
Is that so?
I'll give you a new one when I get older.
I see.
But Donkey Kong 64 is interesting.
I've been playing it for a long time.
I don't know.
I've never played it, so I don't know if it's interesting.
It's fun.
What's interesting?
It's like this.
Five monkeys come out.
If there's a barrel and it goes into the barrel, it changes.
It's different.
It's fun.
That's what people who play it do.
If you get hooked on it, it's big.
It's a waste of time.
I can't stop it.
Is that so?
I feel like I'm getting a tattoo on my brain.
Well, it looks like you know.
You look like you're having a hard time.
Even if I'm sleeping, they keep coming out.
Even if I'm eating, I'm like,
Why don't you go over there next time?
What are you going to do if you're so addicted to it?
There's a coin over there.
Why don't you go over there?
I can't do it anymore.
That's how it is.
I had a fight with a foreigner the other day.
I parked my car at the parking lot of my house.
He said,
I'm in this room.
He put a sticker on it.
He's hiding it.
He said he was in this room.
You know he's in the way, right?
He said,
Come to me.
It means welcome.
He came out and he was a white man.
He was about two meters tall.
He had a big chest.
You can't come over there.
He said, I don't understand Japanese.
I said, I don't understand anything.
When I got on the elevator,
A foreigner suddenly got angry.
He said something.
I don't understand English.
He was in the elevator.
He was in the elevator all the time.
He was in this distance all the time.
I don't know what it is.
It's a long story.
Did he get excited?
He's excited.
I'm hungry.
You should have hit him.
He was about two meters tall.
What if he hits you from above?
Me?
Why?
I can dodge a lot of things.
I can dodge more than you think.
I'm big, right?
What if he hits you from above?
I can't do that.
I'll fix his joints.
Like this?
How do you fix it?
He's a king.
I just sandwiched him.
I know you're broken.
I'm not broken.
Be patient.
As expected of a comedian.
He's broken, but he's not broken.
I'm not broken.
If you want to get rid of him, you have to get along with him.
I know how to get along with him.
No matter how big he is, even if he's a gorilla, he can't bend like this.
That's right.
It's okay if you know that.
There's a way to do it like this.
When he's like this, you can go to the movies.
To the movies.
You can go to watch a love story.
I have a question for Mr. Matsumoto, who has a charismatic way of shaking his chin.
My chin is shaking.
Please tell me how to fix it.
This is unpleasant.
What are you talking about?
This is the chosen race.
I'm a ugly chin monster.
Can you fix it?
Can't you fix it?
Just tell me.
I really hate it.
Originally, we humans came from a crooked place.
That's right.
Is that so?
Yes.
Originally, humans were monkeys.
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
The monkey was shaking the tree.
That's right.
At that time, it didn't shake because it was a monkey.
Was there a reason?
That's right.
Why?
There was a person who said, let's get off the tree.
At that time, he said, don't say stupid things.
It's fun to get off the tree.
But that's not true.
There are many adventures on the earth.
You have to broaden your horizons.
There was a monkey who said that.
He got off the tree and shook the tree.
He shook the tree.
By shaking the tree, he was able to go around the town.
That's right.
When he got off the tree, he was shaking the tree.
Everyone was shouting, let's continue.
When he got off the tree, everyone was shaking the tree.
For example, when I was a kid, I was with Tanaka.
We are of the same race.
We only know each other by the shape of our chin.
The shape of our chin.
Tanaka will explain it to you.
I've never seen it.
It's more than any sake.
It's more than any pot.
It's more than any trip.
You can't do this, can you?
But I don't know about you.
But there are so many amazing people.
Among us Shidoku, there is Antonio.
He is amazing.
He is shaking the tree.
Really?
He has a different rank.
He is much higher.
He is above the clouds.
He can't speak.
He can't do that to you.
You have to find him.
You have such a big mouth.
I understand.
There is no one else, right?
I don't know.
I understand.
Kishida...
Kyouko?
Kyouko.
He doesn't do that to you.
What?
For example, when Kishida-san is eating at a restaurant, I go and...
He gets really angry.
What?
He says, I can't eat it.
Because he is from a different race.
But when you do that, it's amazing.
You have a big mouth.
Sometimes when you have a big mouth, you have a big mouth.
This is complicated.
When you say wine, it's like rosé.
When the washing machine is running, what is going on?
I think it's a little party.
For example, what will you be?
A T-shirt or something.
A T-shirt?
Heinz?
Heinz.
What will I be?
A bra?
Can I be a bra?
When it's like this...
What kind of laugh will Heinz make?
The water will come in.
At that time, I'll be a bra.
It's like this.
There's nothing more fun than this.
What do you think?
I'm standing up straight now.
Now it's just Heinz and a bra.
There's a lot more.
There are more things here.
Pants, socks...
The socks brothers will come.
One person will come.
The American with the socks will come.
Hello, hello.
My name is socks.
The socks you lost is American.
Hello.
Hello, Japan is fun.
Where did you come from?
I think it's really fun.
I want to be like that.
But when I open it, I think humans are watching.