The New Year's Eve Gaki no Tsukai's New Year's party has come again this year.
The 4th episode of Gaki no Tsukai Yagahara!
Chikichiki 2003! Happy New Year!
The New Year's Eve Gaki no Tsukai's New Year's party!
This year too, we have a special guest.
What is it?
What did you say?
First of all, the energy has already reached its peak!
Thank you very much!
Next, Yoshimoto Ichino's butt is a mess!
Shimagawa Shouji!
It's a mess!
Next, the person who has to be in Gaki no Tsukai!
Pheromone Venus!
Grandma!
Next, from the extra world...
Black Jack!
Yamada-san!
Thank you very much!
Congratulations!
Hey!
I'm angry!
Yes! What is it?
I'm angry before I do this!
You guys!
Why are you such a piece of shit!
Yes!
I don't know what to say!
It was hard to hold it in!
Come with the suit!
Get hit!
It's the New Year's party!
Get hit by the New Year's party!
Yes!
That's it!
I have one more thing to say!
Actually, I'm the main character of this show.
The main character?
The main character of Downtown!
The small one isn't here!
That's it, everyone!
I'm really sorry!
My partner...
Well, I can't say it here, but...
He got hit by the New Year's party!
Really?
I'm not the main character!
I'll probably be in the video, too.
I have a cold, so I can't sing.
I'll take a break this time.
It can't be helped.
Today, Hanagata-san is not here, but...
Everyone, please have fun!
Please!
Congratulations!
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Unfortunately, Hamada is absent this time.
However, the guests are very lively.
It's a gorgeous New Year's party suitable for the new year.
In the midst of this, this man took Hamada's seat and caught a cold.
Endo, have you decided on a name?
I haven't decided yet.
Would you like me to put it on?
Really?
Yes.
If I put it on, will you definitely put it on?
Well, as a candidate...
No, no.
But I don't know.
If it's a good name...
If you say you'll definitely put it on, I'll say it.
Then I'll say it.
That's what happens.
Why?
That's because my brother said it.
It's definitely a strange name.
But I'll say something interesting.
Something interesting?
I'll definitely say it.
If you don't say you'll definitely put it on...
Matsumoto-san, isn't that right?
I didn't hear it at all.
I've never heard it so much.
Ko-san, I'm sorry.
I'll change my mind.
I'll put it on.
You'll put it on?
If I think about it, Senpai should say that.
I see.
That's absolutely right.
Then in the case of a boy...
If it's a boy...
Yes.
I'm thinking of Miyasako.
2003 HATSUWARAI MANZAI DAIGASSEI!
From now on, we'll be your MCs. Nice to meet you.
Then we'd like you to play the song.
Thank you.
The new year's special program, Manzai Daigassen.
Out of the 25 talent staff, 5 teams will be chosen to perform the manzai.
Will they accept it or not, the fate will be decided by this lottery.
We'll start with the first team.
Okay, then.
First person, start!
I'll press it. Stop!
Number 3!
Who will it be?
Here you go.
Mano-san, stop!
This is tough.
I'd like to see Tajima-san's reaction.
Here we go, start!
Stop!
Number 10!
Aikata, Aikata, Aikata.
Yes.
This is tough.
I think Tajima is tougher.
The second person is the director, Tsutsumimoto.
Aikata will also be chosen by the director, Takahashi.
Takahashi-san.
The third person is...
It's been a while since the last time he appeared, Producer Suga.
Suga-san is the type that's really weak.
He's really weak.
He's been like this for years.
The Aikata we're curious about is...
It's okay, it's okay.
Really?
Okay, the fourth group.
Here we go, start!
Number 3!
Number 8!
Yes.
Thank you.
I don't like the pattern that was chosen earlier.
I'll decide my own fate.
Matsumoto-san's Aikata, please!
Yes.
Where did you get it?
Why did you come?
The talent is overflowing.
That's right.
I'll increase the number of frames.
This is the last one.
Okay, the fifth group.
Here we go, start!
Number 3!
Number 8!
It's me.
The fifth group is Shinagawa Shouji's Shouji.
And the Aikata is...
Number 4!
It's me.
Papariko Endo!
The first group is Yamasaki and Tajima.
The third group is Tama-chan.
The fourth group is Matsumoto and Heipo.
And the fifth group is Shouji and Endo.
The fifth group is the three of you?
That's right.
Wait a minute.
Let's do one more group.
Let's do the sixth group.
The sixth group is...
Number 9!
It's me.
The first group is Shinagawa Shouji's Shinagawa.
If I become a staff member, I'll be famous.
And the Aikata is...
Number 65!
Kokoriko Tanaka!
I'll announce it now.
There is one person who is in charge of the six groups.
It's me!
In the end, Miyasako cried and the Aikata was Komura Saki.
The sixth group is Shinagawa and Kokoriko Tanaka's Bokeh duo.
And Miyasako and Komura Saki decided to go to the public bath.
The 7th group is making up a story in another room.
There are many rivals more than 0 years.
Each duo has less than 4 years to meet.
Number 1 who predicts the new year.
What kind of story will be made?
Thank you for waiting.
The first group is Endo and Shoji.
The topic is Godzilla Matsui.
Go ahead!
Thank you very much.
This is a top battle.
Let's do our best.
It's a major league.
I've been doing it for two years.
The Aikata is an infrared.
It's strange.
I don't know.
Listen to the story.
2002.
World Cup soccer.
Golf was Maruyama.
Sports was very exciting.
I love sports.
Matsui was nervous.
I'm not nervous at all.
Are you nervous?
I'm nervous.
Matsui went to the major league.
Baseball in the major league.
Baseball in Japan.
I had to shorten the distance.
Leave me alone.
Are you nervous?
I'm not nervous.
But you are good.
If Matsui goes to America, I want him to swing.
I want to see Matsui's swing.
Don't be afraid of the result.
Like this.
He is not nervous at all.
He is nervous.
He is not nervous.
You're not nervous.
I have a risk of 4 points.
Matsui wants you to do your best.
He is a great player.
Baseball is important.
Base of baseball. Let's take care of the equipment.
As a baseball player, it's a must.
That's right. That's why the bat and the ball are important.
Thank you very much.
The second team is Hotohara-san and Suga-san.
The theme is Tama-chan.
Go for it!
Hello. Hello.
Hello.
I'm Kikuno. I'm Kikuno.
I'm Oseno. I'm Oseno.
Well, I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
There were many unpleasant moments last year.
There were many.
But the only one that was healed was Tama-chan in Tamagawa.
That was cute.
That was healed.
That was the only one that was healed.
Ah, here is Tamagawa.
Here is Tama-chan. Let's call her.
Tama-chan! Tama-chan!
Tama-chan? Tama-chan?
Tama-chan? Is that you, Tama-chan?
You're just a middle-aged man.
Eh? Is that you, Tama-chan?
Ah, the TV news is coming.
The TV news is coming.
Tama-chan, are you happy?
Do you like TV?
It's coming out, Tama-chan.
Tama-chan, it's coming out.
Wow, wow, she's really happy.
She's really happy.
She really likes TV.
That's not true at all.
Ah, it's coming out.
The TV news is coming out.
Wow, when the TV news is coming out,
she's like a taro.
Tama-chan!
She's really happy.
Wow, that's scary.
What are you doing?
Let's give her some food.
Food, here.
She's really happy.
She's eating food.
Let's give her some more.
Wow, wow, wow.
She's eating a lot of food.
Tama-chan, are you happy?
Are you happy?
Ah, food.
Ah, there's no more.
There's no more.
Scary.
What are you doing?
Hey.
It's scary.
Scary, scary, scary.
I'm calling her.
She's really scary.
She's slow.
What is it?
Eh?
Money?
I don't have any money.
What are you doing?
Getting away.
Tama-chan, you're going to win.
Charing, charing.
There's no money.
What are you doing?
What is it?
There's no money in there.
Stop it.
Hey!
What is it?
Stop it.
Tama-chan has a lot of money.
Hey, there are a lot of cards in there.
Tama-chan, stop it.
What is it?
Tama-chan, where are you going?
I'll stop it!
Sorry.
It's fast. It's fast to go home.
Yamazaki-san and Tajima manager. The topic is Shinmai Papa.
Go ahead!
Congratulations!
Do-ya-sa...
Even though it's three carrots, it's a carrot!
Do-ya-sa!
Eh-yan-kai-sa!
It's a string, a string!
Yeah, a string, a string!
It's a string that doesn't come out that much!
Do-ya-sa!
No way!
But, you know...
I was born with a child.
Mele-ta-yan-kai-sa!
But it's really hard to take care of it.
It's hard to take care of it for everyone.
I wanted the actors to understand.
Thank you, yan-kai-sa.
Thank you, right?
I was born with a child.
Ah!
I always smile.
That's good, yan-kai-sa.
It's more strong, you know!
It's more strong!
It's embarrassing.
It's embarrassing!
Do-ya-sa!
The string...
The string doesn't come out.
Ah, so...
I was born with a child.
Ah!
I always smile brightly.
That's good, yan-kai-sa.
Yan-kai-sa.
Do-ya-sa.
I was born with a child.
I...
I always smile brightly.
You smile again, yan-kai-sa.
Smiling is important.
Do-ya-sa.
It's not Do-ya-sa.
Smiling is important.
I was born with a child.
I...
When I move...
When I'm moving...
I smile brightly.
That's good, yan-kai-sa.
I was born with a child.
I smile brightly.
It finally came out.
I smile.
You smile again.
But it came out.
Do-ya-sa.
It's good, yan-kai-sa.
Really?
I was born with a child.
I...
I smile brightly.
What's with the smile, yan-kai-sa?
Because I always smile.
I don't understand anything, yan-kai-sa.
It's not good at all, yan-kai-sa.
Why?
It's not good at all.
What's with the smile, yan-kai-sa?
The atmosphere has changed a bit.
That's why everyone was worried.
The four teams are Tanaka-san and Shinagawa-san.
The theme is the Nobel Prize.
Go ahead.
The Nobel Prize
Hello.
I'm Gaba-gaba.
I'm a little bit Gaba-gaba.
The two of us are Enemagura.
This is the name of the product.
That's right.
It's amazing.
Well, the Nobel Prize was amazing last year.
The Nobel Prize.
Last year, two people won the Nobel Prize.
One of them was very close up.
Tanaka-san.
What was the Nobel Prize?
Enemagura.
That's right.
It was a tool to fix ***.
It made me feel good even if it wasn't ***.
It's here.
It's finally here.
The theme is Bob Sapp.
Go ahead.
It's amazing.
What are you doing?
The game of Bob Sapp is about to start.
It's too late.
I'm sorry.
Did I make you wait?
What were you doing?
The game is about to start.
I was drinking a little bit.
A little bit.
There's no time left for the game of Bob Sapp.
The game of Bob Sapp is about to start.
You know Bob Sapp, don't you?
Bob Sapp.
You were drinking earlier.
That's your favorite.
You open it and drink it.
It's delicious.
You know that, don't you?
What?
That's Bob Sapp.
Bob Sapp.
It's popular with young people.
They dance at night.
Check it out. Check it out.
Check it out.
Is that hip-hop?
Bob Sapp.
You're more up-and-up than Bob Sapp.
Thank you very much.
Let's move on to the 6th group.
Miyasako and Komurasaki.
The theme is hot spring.
Here we go.
I forgot to turn on the other gagol.
I'm sorry.
But hot spring is...
I have a hot spring here.
Come here.
What are you looking at?
Stop fighting at the hot spring.
Stop it, Komu.
What are you doing?
I didn't do anything.
Stop fighting at the hot spring.
Stop it.
You're fighting at the hot spring.
What are you doing?
But Hiroya, you're competing with a guy like this.
I'm good at swimming.
I'm good at it, too.
You can't beat me.
You guys are fast.
I'm sure I'm fast.
Hurry up and do it.
I'm fast.
Do it.
All right, it's a match.
Thank you.
I'll do it.
Until the end of the bottle.
Here we go.
On your mark.
Ready, go!
I win!
Hot springs are fun, right?
That's all from Noboribetsu Carlos. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
The 7th place goes to Matsumoto-san and Heipo-san.
The theme is Yosoji.
I'm Machan!
I'm Heipo!
We are Machan-Po!
It's about time for us to be in our 40s.
When you're in your 40s, your shoulders start to shake, right?
Yeah, my shoulders don't raise at all.
Sorry, I can't really dance.
When you're in your 40s, your shoulders don't raise at all.
My shoulders don't raise at all.
What a shame!
I've been having bad memories lately.
Oh, bad memories? I'm fine with that.
Can you say all the names of your Morning Musume?
I can say them all.
Tsui-chan, Kago-chan, Milko, Revanna, and Peter Aerts.
Aren't they all K-1 fighters?
Aren't they all K-1 fighters from the middle?
Can you say all the names of them?
I can say them all.
Kago-chan, Tsui-chan, Milko-chan, Taisei, Tsunku.
Aren't they all Appaku-Nontai?
Aren't they all K-1 fighters?
They aren't!
Well, well, well, well, well, well, well, when I'm 40, I'll be a gun center.
I'll be running 10 kilometers every day.
That's not a big deal.
When I drive a car, I can only go 10 kilometers per hour.
I'll be a great gun!
You're singing too much.
Shut up! I'm going to get fired!
I'm fired!
What did you think, Wano-san?
It was fun this year, wasn't it?
I hope we get a prize next year.
I hope so.
We have to work hard.
It's not that we're not getting anything in return.
It would be nice if we could win a prize.
If I get a prize, I'll definitely beat him up today.