This is the second episode of Chikishiki!
It's Producer Hichihenge!
Mr. Shikajima
Yes
This old man really came out
I can't do anything about his energy
Yamazaki did it before
He was pretty popular
If it was him, it would be me
What are you talking about?
It's time
OK
Last time, Yamazaki gave me 3,000 yen
He gave you 10,000 yen in total
Yamazaki gave me 10,000 yen
How much will you give me today?
I'm looking forward to it
Burnt tennis ball
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
What should we do?
Sugachan, you drink too much
It's 300th anniversary, so I should drink
It's 300th anniversary
It looks like you're in love
I took a picture with you on the phone
What is it?
You said you were a producer
I think so
I want to hug you
I'm not good at hugging
I'm tired
I see
I'll ask you
I don't know
What is it?
You're drinking with someone
It's strange to drink with such a combination
I don't know
It's strange
It's better to drink like this
It's a fun program
Why is he wearing a T-shirt?
He's full of energy
I'm full of energy
I'm so hungry
Who are you?
I can't go back
Nagasaki Tsurugi
You're finally here
You're here
I've been waiting for you
I was waiting for you
Hurry up and wash your ass
I can't do this
Put it in
Wow, that's amazing
I just opened it with that momentum
Don't try to hit me
I can't do this
Why are you making that face?
You're making a sad face
Do it
Did you decide?
No, not yet
Speed it up
Roger
It seems that Z has appeared
I'm protecting the earth rather than my job
Excuse me
What's that?
Z's that
Takaitoko version
That's right
That's good
Can you show us your spirit?
Say something
Look at the number
14,000
Z's that is easy
Is it easy?
I was dancing after the trumpet
Ladies and gentlemen
Good evening
I'm sure you can see the difference between us
What do you mean?
With them?
No, you
You and me
Why?
They are drunk
Are you making up a story?
Don't say that
Why are you angry?
You look like you are going to eat something delicious
All of it?
No
You look like you are going to eat the bones
I can eat it
Is that so?
Last week, the airing was like a horror movie
It was
I fell down
I'm sorry
It can't be helped
It's here this time
What?
What are you saying?
It's here
First of all, I was in a big trouble
I was just in a big trouble
It was just an electric shock
When I was sleeping alone at home, I had a fever of 40 degrees
You said you had a fever
I had a fever
Electric shock
Of course, I was
I was living alone
I was living alone with a fever
I saw you in the kitchen
Wait a little longer
I'm making it now
Who is that?
I don't know
It's okay
I can only rely on Okamoto
I can only call Okamoto during the day
I call Okamoto and ask him to take me to the hospital
While I was selling electric shock, the doctor called the manager
You should have told me
I was just selling electric shock
I don't like it, but the manager
What are you doing with the rice?
I'm heating the rice
What are you doing?
I'm about to cry
I'm serious
What are you doing?
When I was sleeping alone, I had a fever of 40 degrees
That's right
When I looked at the thermography, it was red
From the top of the apartment to the thermograph
What is this? It's red
This is the boiler room
What is this red thing?
Sasaki-kun
Who is that?
Who are you calling?
Sasaki-kun
What is this red thing?
It's red
Did you have a stomachache?
I only poop
I really poop
You poop at that time
It's a long time
I poop
I poop once
I poop because I poop too much
I pooped a lot
I want to take it with me
You can't do it often
Can I cut it?
You can cut it
I was hospitalized two weeks ago
Really?
You are cute
You can put it on later
You can do it from the beginning
No, really
You can cut it and fix it
You are a fool
Even if you gather five people who are good at fighting, the weakest one will not come
You were really good just now
I don't know if I'm good or not
If you don't talk to me, I'm still on the way
Can you see my underwear?
Can you see it?
What are you talking about?
If I fall down and come back, you will fall down
I know
I know why you are doing this
What?
You want to play with me, right?
Everyone was saying, Matsumoto, Matsumoto
Matsumoto, are you okay?
What?
I have a new harm mind
What is that?
I'm a woman too
If I come back, I will be like this
What am I?
I will be dark
You have a bad personality
I'm sorry
If you don't do your best, it will be the end of the year
Who are you?
No, really
I don't want to see your underwear
I don't want to see my underwear
And then, the season came little by little
Right
The season came
This year, compared to the previous years, it's difficult
You always say which one is red and which one is white
Wait, I haven't decided yet
I haven't been told anything
You really want to come out
Really
I will come out
What?
Because you are the only one who is not shy
I'm not shy
That's not important
It's my job
You are not red, you are white
No matter where you look, I'm red
I'm black
To be more specific, I'm black
But
Right
I'm white
Your hard work will guide you
But to be honest
I don't know if I'm nervous
What should I do with this face?
Please tell me
To be honest, that's what happened at the hit studio
It was terrible
When I come out, you come with me
When I'm alone, you come with me
I want to see your face when you come out
I want to see your face when you smile
That's really funny
You can't come out
But when you sing, you come out like this
Like Sabu-chan
Everyone can't come out
Sabu-chan is like this
What is this song?
What is this?
I'll send you a letter
This is a question for Matsumoto
What is the maximum volume you need?
Have you ever raised it to the maximum?
No
I've raised it quite a bit
But if it's too much, it'll be like this
That's not good
It's just noisy
You have to overcome that
How much volume do you usually watch on TV?
How do I explain it with my mouth?
You can explain it with pineapple or fruit
Explain it with pineapple
I don't know if everyone watches it with bananas, but it's hard to understand
I can't explain it
I watch it with 15
It depends on the type
The 15 next to it and the 15 next to it are completely different
The 15 next to it is the same, so it's not a number
If it's more than that, it's noisy
But what about you?
You don't understand it?
If it's more than that, I can see a new discovery
You can't see anything, it's just noisy
For example, you watch Nagisa Oshima on TV
You watch Nagisa Oshima?
You watch Nagisa Oshima on TV
You watch the debate until morning
If it's 15, you say, I'll do it
Nagisa Oshima
You say, I'll do it
The volume is going up
And you raise the volume
Something amazing will happen
What?
You've done it so far
What about Nagisa Oshima?
You raised the volume
Nagisa Oshima
You watch Nagisa Oshima on TV until morning
That's Nagisa Oshima
Is it okay to talk about Nagisa Oshima now?
It's okay, anyone can do it
If it's 15, you say, I'll do it
Nagisa Oshima
If it's 25, you say, I'll do it
If it's 35, you say, I'll do it
You'll take it off
Nagisa Oshima is like this
You'll say, it's hot
That's why everyone knows I'm a celebrity
Even women can do it
If you raise it, you'll take it off
Even Yasaki who is saying this now
If you raise it while looking at the kid
I'll take it off
No one raises it now, so I won't take it off
How do you spend your New Year's Day?
I'm thinking of going somewhere
Where are you going?
I'm thinking of where I'm going
I don't have money, so go
Everyone is saying, let's go to Hawaii
That's not good
What's not good?
If you go to Hawaii, you won't get a young woman
No, Gyo-san is saying it
Usually, you go on New Year's with your family
That's also the majority, but he's saying it
Hostesses and old men
I don't know the details
But he's saying it
Hostesses and ninjas
Hostesses and ninjas?
That's interesting
Where are you going?
Kyushu
Old men?
Why is Kyushu an old man?
Kyushu
I understand
It's a matter of how you say it
Maybe Kohaku is watching somewhere in Kyushu
Kyushu?
Don't think about it
No, no
I'm not the one who's interesting
I'm in Kyushu
You're the only one who can walk like this
No, it's not like that
I'm having fun in Kyushu
Why are you eating sushi?
No
You're the only one eating sushi
Eat at a better place
Thank you
What?
300 times
I see
Thank you
300 times
You're the president
I'm the president
Thank you
Congratulations
No way
Don't go home
Did you come here for that?
Yes, I did
I definitely didn't come here for more than 300 times
Why did you lie?