First, we have the young entertainer, Rikujin!
What I'm going to say is that the young people these days are getting more and more new and it's a very good thing.
But it's a bit of a happy joke.
That's right.
Here, there was a stinger from Mr. Yamada,
It was so ugly, right?
It was a 2006 Vzing- Furthermore, strong, that was right under the глав della azone.
...the sound from Het Dad's Scheme Tournament had ا
This Young Patron Array, who are they?
It was a secret project where is was collected the members of the Young Patrons of this quantify age.
The young comedians of Yoshimoto Tojo.
All of them are wearing the same clothes as the old ones.
This will be the key to the surprise.
The two teams are fighting with each other.
The referee Hamada's butt is being hit by the opponent's knee.
Hamada is being hit hard.
The gang members treat the young people as criminals.
The seniors' words are absolute.
What will the young people do?
The family members will say,
You are the one who said that.
They will kick and hit you.
No, no, no.
They will hit you.
I don't believe it.
They don't like it.
If the knife cuts, they will leave.
That's right.
But it's not really a cut.
It's just a little bit.
Well, there are some parts that hurt.
You really have to cut it.
This time's prank.
The target that will be raised at the end of the day is...
13 years of acting experience, barely young, 2-chome-ken-ju.
2003 F1 Grand Prix Fashion, Football Hour.
The charismatic Iro Uemura.
And...
For some reason, Dave Spector joins the team.
What is the reason?
There are people like this.
They are safe...
They are safe.
It's hard to tell.
I'm the one who's scared.
It's this guy.
It's Kōri.
What was Yoshimoto called?
Hugh Grant.
What is this?
It's a British...
This is a coin.
What is this?
Is this a coin?
It's a normal coin.
This program is brought to you by the sponsors you see.
I want to go to the toilet
No!
Before the performance, the youngsters didn't know that the scary prank was waiting for them
They were quite relaxed
On the other hand, the staff was preparing for the actual performance
And then
Good morning
Please
The young men who know nothing, enter the studio without warning.
The first shot.
The first shot is good.
Good morning.
I don't know who is who.
I really don't know.
Please.
What?
What's wrong?
I will explain the scene of the appearance.
A little late, the main character Hamada appears.
Now all the stages are ready.
Hamada-san, please.
Good morning.
Finally, the curtain of a horror prank is raised.
We will now begin the 2005 G1 Special Tag Match.
First, we have the child's voice actor, Nao Generations.
Oh!
Ah!
Are you okay?
Hey!
What the hell is this?
Why are you all on the comedy team?
It's natural for the main character to be on the comedy team.
Oh, is that so?
It's natural.
Rehearsal?
Isn't this a rehearsal?
Oh, really?
I'm sorry to make you feel like it's real.
Really?
You said you didn't like it.
I'm sorry.
Do it again!
With this unexpected happening, the truth of the prank will be even more obvious.
A vitilstein of Bifically Fantastic Little both now and many generations shove in the hole!
Viva!!
Young Generation Zero
You're too much!
Yes!
Okay!
And now, like Aoko, the Young Generation Zero is entering!
Yeah!
What the hell is this?
Himai-san!
Your body is like a long shaku.
Stop it!
After this, Hamada is finally defeated.
At this moment, the young people's reaction is...
Now, we will start the match.
Both teams will receive a bouquet of flowers.
The beautiful part of the body is...
Oh, my!
Hey, you!
Stop it! Stop it!
ejaba, tougher than a soft movies.
If you give up the waterproof suspended film,
you should be able to enter international ¿ultimate ¿见 with important ¿people spheres ¿and with the Whipping power.
Moreover, it'll be a rest software.
Don't get cocky.
Stop what you are doing.
Do it properly.
From the beginning.
You are a fool.
A fool?
Stop it.
Who is the boss?
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
The young men are in the room.
They are the first to see Hamada's fear.
They are all white.
What is their fate?
It feels good.
It feels really good.
It's okay.
I'm angry that I'm doing this in front of you.
I'm scared.
Not at all.
The staff is not here.
I'm scared.
Do you want to resume?
Yes.
The staff is here.
I'm scared.
I can't do it.
I've been waiting for a long time.
But Dave is good.
Excuse me, we are...
Well, we are bad people.
But if it goes on like this, it's not good.
Oh, you're here.
It's like you can change it after you wear it.
You can change it after you wear it?
This is amazing.
It's finally the worst.
I don't know what to do with this.
I don't know either.
I'm sorry to say that you've worked hard.
I don't know.
You're wearing a mask.
I don't know who did it.
Everyone was kicking.
I was trying to crouch.
I was holding the tape.
And while I was doing that, I saw Mr. Omaeda.
You missed the rock.
I missed the rock.
I said, this is not it.
I was kicking it.
You were kicking it, right?
What?
Goto was there.
I was kicking it.
I don't think I hit it.
Really?
Yeah.
This is good.
Eh?
It's not like he's really nervous.
To relax the nervous young people here,
Yamasaki and Kokoriko head to the dressing room.
I want to do it again.
No, you can't.
It's impossible.
I tried to do it, but it's the same.
He hasn't taken off his mask yet.
He says he can't, but he's wearing one.
Hello.
They keep saying sorry.
I don't hear them.
Why do you think they're angry?
Who kicked him?
I think they're angry.
To be honest, I think they're all mad.
They're thinking, why are you getting angry at that?
But, after the shampoo...
The shampoo...
It's been a while.
Yes.
Oh, sorry.
I'll do it.
I was behind Eno-san.
I think he's kicking because he's only stretched his legs.
Everyone's kicking when they kick.
He's saying this because he doesn't remember.
He's saying it from the heart.
I'll teach you.
That's not it.
I think Yandou-san said it a lot.
No, no, no.
I honestly said it a lot.
Really?
Yandou-san.
You did?
You guys said it.
Yandou-san said it a lot.
He said it.
Ah, Yandou-san said it.
For now, everyone is going to be in a good mood, like they're going to get rid of their relationship with Daichi.
Wow, Korori is like a liquid.
Isn't it amazing?
It's going to disappear.
It's like candy.
We're going to change the room.
It's like a change of mood.
What?
What Dave wrote was,
There's a cultural difference.
You're a fool.
To ease the tension of the young people,
They're going to take the next step.
Hamada is also ready to take action.
The surprise is finally coming.
I think everyone's awake now.
Who said, Knee?
Knee?
Uwa, it's a guitar cymbal!
As expected, I missed completely
If I had had a guitar, I would definitely Move.
She is, at that time, have been asked with no excuse.
So, I told her in the beginning to have all software go.
What she said was going to fail if all of the software is Mickey Mouse,
So, you mean she say I我們, Dave?
Since M maravil is standing so...
Captain baby please!
You motherboard don't have knowledge of the A.B.
No we didn't
Um probably......
I'll leave it like this
I would say....
I think there is a point where I think it is.
Among you.
You came, Hyogurand.
Please.
Wow, this is...
Dave and Harada.
Wow, that's...
It's the most helpful that Dave's hit was the most effective.
That's true.
By the way, the people who are here now are saying that Dave kicked them.
That's why they're saying that they went home.
Endo-san was saying that Dave-san is...
Dave-san is a pain in the ass.
The young people who are desperate to escape responsibility are being punished for their sin.
After this, the members of the group will give out the final information.
Yes?
Hello.
I don't know what to say.
The tiger guy said it was definitely him.
I'm not sure if I should say this, but I've been told that it's a tiger's face snack.
Everyone's looking at me.
I've been told that I've licked it.
It's like licking a lager.
I don't know why it's like licking a lager.
Anyway, someone...
Everyone's licking it.
All of them are tigers.
That's not good.
So it's not a team of tigers.
Yes.
That's all.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
I'll go.
It's okay.
I think he thinks it's me.
Why?
He's very sensitive.
You're not a victim?
Yes, I am.
It's like I'm the victim.
It's here.
Who is it?
Is it the police?
For some reason he confesses that he is the culprit.
He walks along the hallway leading to Hamada's dressing room.
What will Hamada show us in the climax of the prank?
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
I'll give you a kiss.
Kohori, do this.
Do this. It's a prank.
Who is it?
Kohori.
You've been saying that you'll do it.
It was a bit close.
But it wasn't me.
I thought it was definitely Eno.
I did it.
Oh, no.
That's why he was so depressed.
He was so angry, but he still hit me.
That's Hamada-san.
Yo! Remember that!
Who is it?
It's you!
You're the one who brought the gachos.
I'm going to do this with you two.
I don't know yet.
I can do it again.
I really can't do it. I was thinking which one is better.
I think rock is better.
But I think rock is better.
Then, can someone bring the rock?
What kind of reaction will he show to call the sudden football rock to the dressing room?
The hair are controlled by a chain.
arts and Definitely,
I think,
Ja'
deshi
Mr.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
That was scary.
That was scary, but you were scary enough.
When Hamada-san got angry?
I was really scared. I almost cried.
Because I was really scared.
I didn't mean to be a prank. I was really scared.
That was true.
In the end, Hamada himself beat up the three students.
What will happen to them?
The atmosphere is heavy.
The three of them can't talk at all.
You guys are different!
You're all the same!
If you lick it...
I licked it.
You had a great face.
What's wrong?
Goto, what's wrong?
Goto is crying.
Almost everyone is crying.
It's close to the end.
It's not bad.
It's quite different.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
I wonder if he'll get angry.
I don't want to take it off.
Hey, come on!
I'm climbing up!
It's dangerous.
You guys are really bad.
I'll admit that it's Dave's fault.
That's right.
I'm scared!
We were watching the monitor and Goto was playing the game.
He was probably trying to take the responsibility of the team.
But that scene was so bad!
I remember!
I was reading the rules.
I got it!
Everyone, we've finished the first part.
Now, everyone will be the initiator.
From now on, the two karate masters will come.
I already wrote thank you I'll record more next time
Everyone is acting properly
They are!!
Allpo are committing to에게
I'm still feeling nervous
So what is the nextament?
Their member will be acting with sheet intervention
I didn't do that either
Their target is Karate
They are going to
This is how you expect it!
You're the one who's going to die!
Hey, you!
Summer's Wind Waker, Ripple Jamboree is being held.
Our Gaki no Tsukai booth will be recreating a tour that you shouldn't laugh at.
Please come and experience it.
Gaki no Tsukai DVD, Episode 6!
The long-awaited, Yonasaki vs. Moriman, Meibaman!
The miraculous release!
A serious battle between a man and a woman, the song of the wind, will be fully recorded!
On sale July 27th!