This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
I know how you feel, Kawagita.
What is it?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
It's been a while. How are you?
I'm good.
You're good?
I'm fine.
That's good.
What is it today?
Today is finally far away.
It's really far away.
Why did you come all the way here?
I'm going to throw up a lot.
Are you okay?
The other day, I was wondering if it was okay for something like that to happen.
Something that surprised me happened.
What is it?
This is... What is it?
I was pooping at home by myself.
I'm sorry to talk about pooping all of a sudden, but I was pooping.
I was doing it like this.
Suddenly, I saw a huge cockroach on the wall.
It's scary, isn't it?
I was here.
If I go like this, the cockroach will go like this.
That's right.
Why?
I think it will do something.
Even animals can feel it.
It moved like this.
I was wondering what to do.
At this time, if I let it go, I don't know how many more there will be.
At that stage, there are a lot of them.
I haven't seen it for a while.
You mean there's only one?
It just came in from somewhere.
I want to think that if I kill it, it should be okay.
I want it to say that.
I couldn't help it, so I looked for something to hit.
There was nothing.
I couldn't help it, so I went to the toilet.
I took it out like a samurai.
I thought I had to do it in one shot.
I couldn't do it at all.
I ran out of the toilet.
There was a carpet outside.
I ran to the carpet.
Cockroaches can't run fast on the carpet, can they?
I don't know.
I was wondering slowly.
I was in this state.
I couldn't do it.
I couldn't hit it.
I was doing it like this.
I was surprised.
Something came out.
What do you think?
It's pathetic.
I think so.
I don't know what it is.
I was able to beat the cockroach.
But it was almost the same size as the cockroach.
It's pathetic.
I was doing it in the middle.
The cockroach was still there.
I went back to the toilet.
But the toilet door was still open.
I could see the cockroach and the poop.
The color was the same.
It was the same color.
Only one of them was warm.
This cockroach was worse than this one.
You did it.
I'll tell you later.
What do you think it is?
I don't know.
You couldn't hit it.
I don't think so.
Did you hit it?
What is it?
I don't know.
I was running away.
This is blue.
I was worried about how to deal with it.
This is a short one.
Can you remove it with a tissue?
No.
I don't like cockroaches under a tissue.
You can remove as many as you want.
You can remove 5 and hit it.
You can hit it.
You don't have to hit it so hard.
You can remove it softly.
I can't do that.
I can't hit it so hard.
It can't be helped.
You can remove it softly.
What do you mean?
You can hit it softly.
If you hit it with this, it's a cockroach.
That's why I don't know how to remove it.
You can't hit it.
You can hit it like this.
You can hit it with a rock.
It's still thick.
I'm relieved that it's stuck.
I was able to remove it.
This is it.
This is better.
Why?
It doesn't move.
Is that so?
You can remove it quickly.
It's a carpet, right?
The carpet's hair is like this.
I'm holding it at the tip of this part.
Now I don't have to hurt them that much.
This fluffy feeling is very delicate.
You don't have to remove it like that.
I don't like that.
I don't like poop.
What is it?
It's poop.
I think I hate cockroaches the most.
If you hit it with a rock, it's over.
I don't like that rustling sound.
Right?
If it was a Japanese paper, it would be like this.
It would stand up.
If I did that, I would scream.
There is such a thing.
No, no.
If I did this.
If I did that, I would scream.
Cockroaches are very conscious of their friends.
When I was a kid, I was killed by a newspaper.
I was killed.
I felt something in my eyes.
I looked at the other side of the wall.
I was scared.
That's...
I just folded it.
No, no. I saw it completely.
That face is strange.
I didn't look at it like this.
I just folded it.
No, no.
It's like this.
It's not like this.
I saw it.
I can't believe it.
There were three or four of them.
I didn't look at it.
I saw it in a different place.
It's true.
I'm sorry.
This is...
No, no.
That was a floor type.
This is a wall type.
It's true.
I didn't look at it like this.
I just folded it.
It's like this.
It's true.
It's not like this.
There were four of them.
I was scared.
It's true.
I didn't fold it like this.
I folded it like this.
That face is strange.
Matsumoto-san, when you were a kid, you ate all the goldfish from the fish market.
How did you manage to eat so many goldfish?
That's...
That's a strange question.
Is that so?
Yes.
What do you mean?
Because...
Goldfish...
That's strange.
In the cage of the goldfish rescue, in the aquarium...
It's not like you were born in a cage.
That's true.
Right?
You were brought here.
That means...
In the aquarium of the goldfish rescue...
Don't say that you didn't organize it.
You were saved by the aquarium of the goldfish rescue.
Right?
Where is the need to save them more than this?
They were already saved.
You don't need to be saved anymore.
Do you understand?
I understand.
If you think about it, this question of his hasn't been established yet.
But everyone was saved by the goldfish rescue, right?
Yes, yes.
That's human ego.
You want to save the goldfish, right?
I think it was me who saved the goldfish for the first time.
That's a big mistake.
Yes, yes, yes.
I understand that.
Right?
You thought your girlfriend was a virgin.
You know how you want to think you're the first man.
But you've been saved many times.
You've been beaten many times.
Are you stupid?
Why are you making such an analogy?
You don't need to talk about the goldfish rescue.
But people who go there don't know that the goldfish are thinking that way.
We were saved once, but you think you're the first man.
You don't understand the feelings of the goldfish.
So last week, I went there.
Kawaguchiko.
I went to Kawaguchiko, right?
Someone said something like that.
But to be honest, I won.
Don't say such things every day.
Everyone saw it.
It's not fun if there's such a big difference.
I didn't tie the thread in the second half.
So I went there.
I said I won the goldfish rescue.
The goldfish that everyone loves.
Don't say unnecessary things.
Let's talk about it.
The big bass that Matsumoto caught.
I didn't catch it for the first time.
It was released by Kat-chan.
It was caught by Sugimura-san in Yamanashi Prefecture.
I don't know.
I'll catch it again.
That's right.
It's not a story.
It's a story about how to treat humans.
So how do you explain the goldfish rescue story?
If you say that, the old man at the goldfish rescue saved it all.
I didn't save the goldfish rescue.
The old man didn't save it one by one.
The old man just put it in a bucket.
I saved it one by one because it cost a few hundred yen.
How did you do that?
Wait a minute.
You're weird.
The old man at the goldfish rescue saved it in a bucket.
Why can't you decide that?
The old man just did it.
I don't know if he managed to sell it.
No, no, no.
You can't go to the store all day.
You want to bring it, right?
Why did it become like this?
You're weird.
It was so much fun back then.
How did you save it?
You can't say that you saved it all in a bucket.
Don't lick the goldfish.
You're weird.
I'm glad it came out.
Are you glad?
Why are you so grumpy?
I'm grumpy.
You said it was fun.
I'm not grumpy.
It was so much fun to the airport.
You're weird.
I'm not grumpy.
If you tell me how to do it, it's over.
What are you talking about?
I'm telling you that I saved the goldfish.
You too, you too, you too, you too.
You might not be like that.
How did you decide that?
I was wearing a patterned shirt.
Oh, really?
That's what I want to say.
It's not like that.
We have a lot of goldfish.
Normally, two or three of them will break.
Right?
You saved all of them, didn't you?
Yes, yes, yes.
You saved them, didn't you?
Yes.
I did.
Didn't you break them?
How much did you break them?
What?
You broke them all at once?
If I broke them all at once, wouldn't I be able to save them all?
Then, I'll write to the old man again.
A new one.
You want to save them all with a new one until you save them all?
That's what I'm saying.
I don't like that.
I don't like that idea.
But it's okay.
It's okay.
You can continue to save them, right?
If he asks me, I'll tell him that anyone can do it.
It's a question of money.
Then, I have an idea.
I'm doing this, right?
I have a bowl here, and I'm doing this, so I can't do it.
I just have to put it in.
If I put it in the bowl, I just have to stand like this.
Then, it's us.
What's with this sense of inferiority?
I don't know if it's a sense of inferiority or not.
Which side are you on?
Who are you talking to?
Are you talking to a goldfish?
I'm talking to a goldfish, and I want to talk to the old man, too.
This story is...
Cut it out.
I'm in a bad mood.
I have a question for Matsumoto-san, who's crying so much even though he's not married.
That's right.
I heard that there are two types of marriage, love marriage, and fake marriage.
What kind of marriage is that?
There's a lot more.
Please tell me about it.
Now, fake marriage is the mainstream.
The most orthodox marriage is fake marriage.
No, it's fine.
Why do you get married when you're already fake?
You get married because you're already fake.
You get married because you're in a good mood.
You get married because you think you're in love.
You get married because you're already fake.
Fake marriage is when a woman is in love with a man.
That's the way it is.
Fake marriage is when a woman is working and a man is doing housework.
It's a couple.
You're always at home, so you get stressed.
You lose a lot of hair.
One day, your wife comes home from work and says,
I'm so tired.
Your boyfriend says,
I've lost a lot of hair.
You're like,
Is it really my fault?
Do you understand?
I understand.
There's a lot more, but I'll leave it at that for today.
I spent a lot of time at the goldfish.
I didn't expect it.
It's you.
There was an ambush.
You lose everything.
I did.
It's the red t-shirt that I wore the most.
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
I want you to do it quickly.
It's that one.
I want you to do the punishment game quickly.
It's that one, right?
Punishment? What punishment?
No, no, no.
What's the punishment?
What's good?
We did it too.
According to a theory, if you win the last week's fishing, you'll become Mr. Goa.
No, no, no.
I didn't say that.
There was a theory.
Who said that?
Suga-chan said it.
I didn't say it.
There was a theory.
What?
There's a theory that you'll become Mr. Goa.
Mr. Suga said it?
That's not true.
Okay, let's do it.
We did it.
What are we going to do?
We had a lot of trouble.
That's right.
Mentally and physically.
Wait, wait.
It's a tag.
24 hours of tag.
A tag is a child's play.
It's a child's play.
No, no, no.
That's right.
We had a lot of trouble.
We played tag and a scary demon appeared.
That's right.
That's the same thing.
You have to do something like that.
You guys lost to me.
I think that punishment game was tough.
But you lost because you ran, right?
Yes.
Then why did I lose?
You said you were a swimmer.
No, I lost because I swam.
No, no.
Why did I lose?
I'm a human with two legs.
No, no, no.
The question is why did I lose?
Why did I lose?
Two legs.
The question is why did I lose?
Listen to me.
If a human with two legs loses by running, it's a shame.
If you lose, you lose.
You do that sometimes.
Right?
Yes.
So...
It's cute.
If you do the same thing as that...
You won't be convinced.
So...
We talked about this before.
You did it, right?
At school for 24 hours.
Yes.
At midnight.
You can do that.
Then...
Please forgive me.
Why are you apologizing so much?
Why?
There's a reason why you lost.
Did you do it, Yamazaki?
If you're a good student, you won't lose.
You're just making excuses.
No, no.
That's not true.
I didn't do it because I didn't like it.
I'm scared.
It's okay.
You can do that.
I...
That's a punishment.
You can do that.
Right?
No, no.
I can't lose.
It's not like that.
Please stop.
No one has a responsibility.
It's you.
It's your responsibility.
No, no.
So, let's do that.
24 hours.
You can't pick one.
You can have Fujiwara with you.
Yes, yes, yes.
Just two of us.
Fujiwara.
I'm sure Fujiwara will be okay.
Sure?
How do you feel?
It's up to you.
President! Who decided that?
Us, us.
No, no, no. What are you doing?
What did you decide on your own?
I bought it for my wife.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
For example, when the five of us went to the toilet,
you decided on the order on your own.
You didn't want that, did you?
You decided on the tuna gosen on your own.
I don't know about the tuna gosen.
Do you know about that?
You didn't want that, did you?
This time, we decided on it.
Last time, we decided on it on our own.
Is that so?
No, no, no. That's because I bought it.
That's why we bought it.
That's why we lost.
Even now, if you play a completely different game,
you won't be able to accept it.
That's right.
What about the customers?
Well, the schedule is difficult.
Little by little, I'm going to get tired.
What?
You're going to get tired?
I'm going to work out.
You're going to work out?
I don't want to.
I think I want to.
I mean I don't want to, but for the sake of this show.
No, it's not for the sake of it.
I lost.
This isn't right.
No.
Honestly, I have a long-standing love for this show.
Then, after Hey Hey Deluxe, I like this number 3.
Number 3?
When did you think of that?
What are you doing, Kazuma-san?