The second round!
Round 2!
Sit-ups!
Wow, that looks hard.
That's bad, right?
Come on, Norias!
Alright!
Your hips are weird.
No!
This is...
Watch out!
Hey!
Watch this!
Look!
My Norias stopped him!
You!
You stopped him later!
Alright!
Come on, Yamagaki!
Yamagaki, are you going to do this with your hands?
Or with your head?
I'm going to do it with my head.
Alright!
Wow!
Norias!
Let's do it again!
Please do it for me!
Alright!
I did it!
Wait, my Yamagaki
is going to do this.
Really?
It's so annoying!
This size!
No!
What are you doing?
The second round!
What's the second round?
Look at this.
The table is prepared.
And the food.
In that sense,
my Norias
is going to
put inago
on top of the food!
Alright!
Norias, go!
Look at this.
He's eating
the inago
like it's pickled.
He's eating
the inago
like it's pickled.
Wow!
Yamagaki
is going to
put inago
on top of the food!
Cameraman,
put inago on top of the food!
Zoom in!
Wow!
It's hard!
Did you put inago
on top of the food?
It's hard!
I'm going to grab
the inago
and eat it.
Why are you shaking?
It hurts!
Don't put it in your mouth.
Zoom in!
It's really cold today.
Right?
I'm going to
put inago
on top of the food!
I didn't hear you!
Alright!
It's not cold at all!
Oh no!
First,
Yamagaki's going to take off his pants.
over here!
Zoom in!
He's going to do that too!
And then...
Let's go!
Water!
Don't look at me!
And the last one is...
A firework!
Okay!
It's beautiful!
It's beautiful, Norias!
The winner of the 2nd prize is...
Kikouchi Yamazaki!
I challenge you to 3 challenges!
What?
Come on, Yamazaki!
Switch on!
It's hot!
What are you doing?
I can't open it! It's really scary!
It's really scary!
I'm waiting for you in front of the otakus!
Hello!
What a beautiful hall!
It's really amazing!
It's going to take a while to get here
It's going to take a while to get here?
It's so dark!
It's like a Taj Mahal!
I'm looking forward to the night
Night like this?
It's really hard now
I have to work every day
I have a lot of work to do
I'm from Edo
But we have to do our best.
That's right.
We have to do our best.
We don't know if we will be reborn as human beings.
We have to do our best as human beings.
Is that so?
That's right.
If we are reborn as human beings, we won't even know if we are dumplings.
Why do we have to be reborn as human beings if we have a soul?
What is that?
Is it the end?
That's right.
Do we have to wait until we are reborn as human beings?
That's a great thing.
What are you talking about?
You are the one who is saying that.
Why do we have to be dumplings?
There is no dumpling.
That's obvious.
You can't move.
If we are reborn as human beings, we can't bend the QB-3 doll.
You can't move the QB-3 doll.
The QB-3 doll is just a habit.
That is a real doll.
What is a habit?
If we are reborn as human beings, what is the lowest rank?
It doesn't matter.
Is a habit the lowest rank?
That's right.
That's absolutely wrong.
It's true that dumplings are the lowest rank.
I can't say that dumplings are the lowest rank.
What is lower than dumplings?
Water dumplings.
We don't know if we are reborn as human beings.
That's why we are saying that we have to do our best.
If we are reborn as human beings, we are reborn as human beings.
And there are many other human beings.
What?
Look at you.
Your sweat is shining.
You are a masterpiece.
Why are you suddenly singing a song?
A volleyball player.
A Japanese player.
He is 2.8 meters tall.
No, no, no.
If he is 3 meters taller, he is 5.8 meters tall.
That's just the way he is.
I wanted to say how tall he is.
I don't know.
But he is not ugly.
If we are reborn as human beings, we are reborn as human beings.
He is a manly deer.
Or a goat.
Shut up.
Hey.
He is a manly deer.
But he is only known as a zookeeper.
He has a great moustache.
He is wearing a pendant.
Why?
Because he is so cool.
He is amazing.
I don't think that pose is cool.
I don't think this pose is cool.
He is a manly deer.
Other manly deers are like this.
But he is like this.
His hair is like this.
His hair is like a panther.
His hair is like a velvet.
He is so cool.
Hey.
I will give this to you.
You don't know how cool he is.
That's why.
He is a manly deer.
He is amazing.
You don't know how cool he is.
He is so cool.
His body is complicated.
But it is simple.
He is flying high.
He changed the rules.
He won when he saw another man's coat.
What's that?
Is that a sport?
No, it's that kind of sport.
Like this?
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at the court.
What's so fun about it?
It's not like I did it.
I'm not saying it's fun.
If it wasn't fun, you wouldn't be able to do it.
If you do that kind of sport,
if you don't stretch your back, your neck will definitely stretch.
If it's that kind of sport.
If you say it normally.
I'll watch it today.
Everyone does it to watch it.
What do you think?
I'll watch it.
Everyone does it.
I'll say, I watched it!
Is it really a sport?
I don't hate it.
Golf?
I haven't played golf recently.
Golf...
I don't like it at all.
What don't you like?
Golf...
Why are you so...
You don't like it?
The word golf...
You say it like that.
Go.
Wake up at 5.
Order a Luzban.
Flamenco.
What kind of sport do you hate?
I've never skied.
Ski?
S...
Like this.
Ki...
You don't like sports?
What is the most profitable sport?
Baseball.
Baseball is not profitable.
Baseball...
Baseball.
I can be a professional footballer, but not yet.
What do you mean?
You're still a non-professional, right?
I'll be a professional footballer, like you.
I'll be a professional soccer player.
Do you want me to join?
I'm good at soccer.
Really?
I didn't know that.
I'm good at it.
I don't drop the ball.
I can play the ball for a long time.
I can play with my leg.
As you all know, I can also tap.
I can tap very quickly.
I'll try it.
Do you know?
I don't know.
See, I told you.
In the meantime, I'll go look for the ball.
Go look for it.
I'll do the tap.
Please listen to my strange mother.
My mother puts strange things in her bento.
It's strange.
It's a bit strange here.
The other day, I put in an anman.
The other day, I put in a yokan.
And when I asked why you put in a yokan,
you said it was a potato yokan, so it's fine, right?
It has potatoes in it.
I see.
You don't have to be so mean.
Have you ever put in strange things in your bento?
This is...
Generally, the most common thing is putting in something like beans.
What are you talking about?
What do you call that?
What kind of beans are you talking about?
Are you talking about the sweet ones?
That's also a bit harsh, right?
There are also the black ones.
The black ones that are in the osechi dish.
That's also a bit harsh, right?
You got angry when you got home, didn't you?
What are you thinking?
When I came home,
my stomach was full.
You shouldn't say that.
You should say,
Welcome home!
Shut up!
It's like something that Okan developed by himself.
My Okan is curry bean sprouts.
He put curry in the bean sprouts.
I hate that kind of beans!
I really want you to stop doing that.
But there are also the ones that even have fruits in them.
You put them in the bean sprouts.
The ones that even have fruits in them are very...
They're very high-grade.
They're like a lady.
You put them in the bento box and they have fruits in them?
That's right.
I also put them in sometimes.
I told you.
The next day, I put in strawberries.
I can't get used to that.
I'm an amateur.
I put them in the rice bowl of a normal bento box.
I have that.
I put them in rice bowls.
I put them in the rice bowls.
I can't get used to that.
Shut up!
I see.
You know what level they're at in the broadcasting industry?
What?
What do you mean?
My house is like a newsroom.
But the newspaper...
There's a bento box and the newspaper is there, right?
Yeah.
They were serving rice balls like this to the newspaper.
Where was that guy?
Morioka Yonekino, right?
He was poor.
I was pretty bad, but he was poor.
Especially when we went on a trip, he was like that.
It was even more shocking.
Morioka's Myoga bento.
What was that?
I'm hungry, Morioka.
Let's eat bento.
Leave me alone for a moment.
Why? Why?
When I went to see it, there were a lot of white rice balls.
That's right, that's right.
With myoga.
That's tough.
It's crunchy, crunchy, crunchy.
Next.
I have a question for Matsuyo.
When you're lost or in trouble, you say, tentekomai.
What kind of dance is this?
Let's have him dance.
Do you need a hand?
No, I don't need it.
You don't need it?
Yes.
Then, please dance.
Then, Mr. Matsumoto.
Do you need a hand?
Hey, you.
Do you need a woman to bathe you?
Now, everyone.
Let's have Mr. Matsumoto dance in front of everyone.
It's tentekomai.
That's it.
Like this, sometimes.
Yes.
Is it OK?
There are a lot of terms.
You say to bathe a woman, right?
Yes, you say to do it.
You say to write it.
I wrote yesterday that I bathed.
That means you did.
You say I had sex.
I'm his mother.
I can't keep up with Tom, Gyo, Kai, Yoko, etc.
Tokyo is amazing.
Right?
Especially the people here.
Especially the staff here. I can't believe it.
Especially Saito.
Saito?
I'll give him a name.
Parma No. 2.
Saito is terrible.
Saito is amazing.
What did you say today?
Well...
What did you say?
That shop has good atmosphere.
Do you know what I mean?
It has good atmosphere. Do you know what I mean?
That shop has good atmosphere.
It has good atmosphere.
What do you mean by atmosphere?
Why did you turn it upside down?
I told you to say Roppongi.
I said Giroppon yesterday.
Say Roppongi.
What's Giroppon?
Why did you turn it upside down?
Motoichi.
I'll give you a good name.
Say it.
Then, shall we go home?
Oh, the ball is here.
My staff is excellent.
Oh, no.
Why?
It's rubber.
It has nothing to do with it.
The official ball is made of leather.
It's a soccer ball.
It has nothing to do with rubber and leather.
It has nothing to do with it.
Hey, you.
Show me what a real person is.
Who is that?
You.
I'm a real person.
Show me what a real person is.
Where should I do it?
Here? Or here?
I don't know.
You can do it here.
Or here.
You should start with your knees.
With my knees?
Here.
Oh, my head is stuck.
Do it.
That's enough.
Why do I have to do this every time?
Come on.
Let's do it.
One.
Two.
Three.
That's the best.
Hurry up.
I've already done it.
Keep doing it.
How many seconds is the end roll?
30 seconds.
That's the worst.
That's not enough.