GENERATION OGAE SOUCHANKA GRAND PRIX!
Today's guests are lucky!
They are the best!
Let me introduce them again.
First of all, Mr. Otake Makoto!
I have to do what you expect me to do.
What are you talking about?
I have to eat for the next 5 years.
Why 5 years?
I have to be like you.
That's enough!
What do you mean you have to be like me?
Stop right there!
You're a criminal!
Don't look down on the police!
Sit down!
Next to me is Mr. Kano Tenmei!
Next to me is Mr. Matsumoto Itoshi!
You don't like it, do you?
You don't want me to be one of them.
You don't like it?
But you're the most decent one, aren't you?
That's a compliment.
The first question is this!
You're spraying a black spray on your head!
You can't be on TV if you don't spray a black spray!
Read it more normally.
Your words are terrible.
I think you're going to make me do something amazing.
What should I do?
Please write it on the back of your head.
You're going to get bald, aren't you?
Jin, you're shaking.
You're stuck.
Don't go anywhere without touching anything.
Everyone in the world doesn't know who you are.
Especially in the Kanto area.
I've been next to this person.
He's wearing a beige suit.
He sprays a black spray on a beige suit.
Please don't do that.
What should I do?
Someone's here.
Wait a minute, everyone.
Someone's here or someone's here.
That's what I'm saying.
I'm going to take this out because it's useless.
If it's useless, you don't have to take it out.
It's useless, so don't use it.
It's the worst.
It's a story of a spray.
Don't use it.
It's okay.
It's dangerous.
Everyone knows that.
I helped you.
From Mr. Otake.
Mr. Otake.
Kishin Hiroyama.
I'm sorry.
Are you sorry?
You're talking about our business.
You wrote it.
You're a criminal, so you have to say something.
I'll tell you some information.
He's doing this.
He's doing it.
I was sick of something.
When Mr. Kishin came in,
When the wind blows in the western play,
I'm going to have a stinging smell.
You're going.
I said, and I said, what's coming?
I want a stinging smell.
Mr. Kishin didn't have anything.
Wait a minute.
Does that mean there's nothing?
No.
I'm saying this for the sake of the photo session.
There's no such thing.
Then I heard about it.
I went to Mr. Kishin's house.
There's a lot of it.
I'm going to spray it in the room.
What's that?
I told you.
I heard it.
Sit down.
Let's go to Mr. Tenmei.
I think this is a normal place.
Yes.
I see.
Now, Mr. Matsumoto.
Well, I'm the only one.
This is that.
I see.
When the autumn festival came out,
He was the one who looked down from the top of the stairs.
It's amazing.
It's like a billiard number eight.
Tamori.
Kenji Moriwaki.
Toshi-chan.
Kume-san.
Tamori.
Ishida Junichi.
Masakazu Tamura.
It's a hot topic.
Toshi-chan.
Hiroshi Tatsu.
Kenji Moriwaki.
Toshi-chan.
Because he has a nori-like head.
Mr. Tenmei is correct.
The next question is...
Here it is.
No one has seen your room clothes.
You idiot.
What the hell are you doing?
Here you are.
This is that, isn't it?
Have you ever taken it out?
No, I haven't.
In short, you haven't seen it, have you?
I haven't.
I just want to see it.
I don't want to see it, but...
That's a runaway, isn't it?
I think it's a little embarrassing.
This...
François Morel.
I don't want to see it, either.
Everyone is moving.
You like foreigners, don't you?
John Shepard.
Someone is talking.
Helen.
Stop being a foreigner.
Let's go.
Mako-chan.
Mr. Tenmei is correct.
Why are you hiding your mouth?
Is that for TV?
Mr. Tenmei is correct.
I want to see this, but...
Tanaka Makiko.
That's fine, isn't it?
I want to see it, but...
I'm a top show, so...
I'll go with this.
Finally, Mr. Matsumoto.
Mr. Tenmei is correct.
Well done.
I didn't get this right.
The third question is...
This one.
Your face has changed compared to when you debuted, hasn't it?
Your face has changed, hasn't it?
You've changed a lot, hasn't it?
It's obviously different.
There's nothing between you and your friends.
What's that?
Please show your answers.
That hasn't changed, has it?
It has, hasn't it?
Hey, wait a minute.
This is red, isn't it?
Please show your answers.
This is the most interesting one that everyone has.
Mako-chan, this has changed a bit again.
That hasn't changed, hasn't it?
This has changed.
This was a very shocking answer.
That's simply because you have a long career, isn't it?
No, it's this, but isn't it too bad?
After doing it, it has changed again.
My daughter has become more mischievous.
Now, Mako-chan.
You don't need to clap.
You went to get this, didn't you?
Yes.
Matsumoto-san.
Yamasaki-sensei.
Hama-chan, Hama-chan, Hama-chan.
Doesn't it feel like you're making a mouthful?
F**k.
Everyone, this is the correct answer.
Hama-chan, why did you come out?
What did you do?
My teeth have become short.
Why?
Because they have broken.
It was long, long time ago.
It's just this.
That's why I can see stitches.
I've been told many things.
Regarding this matter, even if I talk about it in detail, I'll cut it anyway.
That's why it's not that it hasn't broken for a long time.
What are you looking at?
The last question is this.
Omae M*****
Thank you very much.
That's it, that's it, that's it.
Omae, is it S or M?
For me, it's S.
No, S is...
That's why it's S.
The one who does it.
Which one?
If I do it like this, you'll think, right?
Right?
Ah, yes, yes, yes.
Eh?
But there's a point to it.
I don't get it.
If I do it like this, you'll think I'm stupid.
Ah, that's not it, that's not it.
No, really.
If I say something like this, I don't know if you'll misunderstand, but...
I want you to be a little emotional.
No, no, no.
I...
Kaimu!
No, no, no.
I want you to be a little emotional!
I can see your throat!
This is...
No, I can't wear glasses.
Don't be angry.
This is really...
What are you doing?
What are you doing with sports glasses?
This is...
I'm not saying this to make you laugh.
You know, a long time ago...
There's nothing, right?
I have a habit of saying that on that day.
I don't have a habit, but there's nothing.
I'm not saying this to make you laugh.
Leave me alone.
I'm curious about it.
So I want you to think of me as someone who wears glasses.
I understand. I'll do that. Sorry.
I won't talk about it.
I'll talk about it.
That's impossible.
When I went to the hospital,
I got a big finger in my ass.
Yes, yes.
Two fingers.
Yes.
I got my legs raised.
I really hate it.
It hurts.
It's not like that.
I'm not going to do that.
I didn't laugh, but I laughed a little.
While you were laughing?
No, I didn't laugh that much.
I didn't laugh half-heartedly.
Hey.
That's a grim face.
That's a mischievous face.
No, no, no.
There's something like that.
Anyone.
No, that's not it.
I don't get it.
Really?
I'm a bad person.
That's right.
Lately,
there are people who call me all the time on my cell phone.
Right?
There are a lot of messages on the phone.
It costs 100 yen to listen to a message once.
If you do it 10 times a day, it's 1000 yen.
I see.
If you do it all the time, it's no good.
Hey.
Why do you know my cell phone number?
Because I teach you a lot of things.
That's fine.
I don't care.
I'll teach you if you don't do it.
I didn't do that.
That's right.
But I'm telling you that you're going to break up with the person I taught you.
I don't teach you that much.
It's just Yoshinaga Sayuri.
Are you stupid?
Where did you put it?
That's right.
Tell me.
You're the bad guy.
Don't say that.
The one who calls me is the worst.
You're the one who gave me a lot of information on my cell phone.
Do you know my cell phone number?
I won't tell you even if I have it.
I see.
I don't know if it's in a cell phone called Bomber Head.
No, it's not in here.
Why?
I asked you before the show and it was still in there.
I can put it in there.
I asked you before the show.
What is it?
Why can't you recommend it?
Where are you looking?
What are you doing?
I can't eat anything.
You can't use money for this.
I heard that there was a model somewhere.
Which model was it?
Super model.
It was 600 million yen a year.
I have nothing.
I have to get more.
That's why it's not a good idea to buy an instrument and put it in for free.
I don't know how much it will cost.
But when it comes out, I'll give you a discount.
Do you want it?
I don't know what it is.
Why do you want something sweet?
I'm scared.
I want a cookie.
You don't need it.
Why do you want it?
It's hard to find it.
I'll dig up the Genji pie.
I can't give you anything.
You're right.
I'm scared.
Then I'll give you something sweet.
You're targeting me.
You're a man with a knife.
You're talking to me.
You're holding a knife from the other side.
You're not aware of Matsumoto.
You're not aware of SOS Matsumoto.
What are you going to do when it's over?
Are you going to help me?
But I'm in danger, too.
That's the difference.
What are you going to do?
What I'm good at is ninja arts.
I'm talking too much.
I'm going to use the circle I always have.
What?
You're going to disappear.
What are you going to do if someone like this comes?
What?
Like this?
Wait a minute.
Keep your feet still.
Why are you doing this?
I'm talking about Jitaba.
If you do that, I'll run away.
What?
What are you going to do?
It won't go out.
It's normal to disappear like this.
After this...
What are you going to do if someone like this comes?
I'm going to run away.
Matsumoto.
Aiii!
You should have said Aiii instead of Aiii!
Who are you?
I'll throw it for the team.
First of all, please tell us about your life in detail.
If I say something like this, you might misunderstand me.
Then don't say anything.
Why did you disappear?
I was in contact with Lamborghini.
I was wondering what to do with this story.
If you say something like this, you might misunderstand me.
Then don't say anything.
Wait a minute!
It's a broadcast code.
It's a very dangerous situation.
What was I doing?
I'm doing my best to live now.
If I say something like this, you might misunderstand me.
You don't have a face.
I'll think about it after I put it in my mouth.
It's funny.
Was I like that?
I was laughing when I fell into the water.
What is that?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You're scary.
I bought a Macintosh recently.
If you double-click the system holder of the hard disk, the icon will disappear.
Why?
I don't know.
I'm sorry, but I don't know.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You were that kind of person.
Wait a minute.
It's a long time ago.
What do you mean by double-clicking the system holder of the hard disk?
I double-click twice.
Wait a minute.
It's a machine, isn't it?
It's a machine.
What do you mean by double-clicking twice?
There's a string.
A string?
There's something like a string.
I double-click twice.
Isn't it a system holder?
There's something like this.
You're so cute.
Well, it's attached, but it doesn't matter.
The microcomputer will disappear.
If you do that?
That's right.
It will disappear.
Why?
Of course.
That's the final stage.
There are times when it can't be helped.
What if I do that?
If you do that, everything will disappear.
What?
If I take out the outlet, everything will disappear?
It won't disappear.
Do you remember that?
Yes, I do.
Is that so?
Tell me how to deal with it.
There's a green lamp on the back.
I'll replace it with a red lamp.
This is very difficult.
You're going to replace the lamp?
It's a fake video.
Tell me how to deal with it.
You do that when you watch it, right?
It's a video.
You have to change the input.
In the end, it's easy to say.
You don't know the structure, do you?
I don't know, so I'm asking.
It's a dead mouth that fell into the sea.
Why don't you know if it's dead?
Don't talk about your past life.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You don't know the explanation.
No, I'm just saying that I didn't pull the string.
You don't know about the end of the year.
If I didn't pull the string, would you talk about the end of the year?
No, I pulled it again.
It's stretched out.
No, it's not.
You're pulling too much.
I pulled out the yellow tape.
Why is the bath in the love hotel visible from the room?
Being visible means being seen.
Yes, that's right.
You don't like it, do you?
You don't want to be seen in the bath, do you?
Why?
It's not cool to be seen in the bath.
Is that so?
What are you doing in the bath?
I don't know about girls, but when men take a bath, their balls become like this.
When they see their balls become like this, they think it's the end of the year.
Is that what you think?
I understand.
But I don't like it very much.
You don't want to be seen in the bath.
And I don't like to take a bath with a woman.
Really?
I don't like it.
When I take a bath with a woman, I think it's the end of the year.
What do you mean by the end of the year?
When you take a bath with a woman, you think it's the end of the year.
It's the end of the year.
If that's the case, you're the one who is going to be seen in the bath.
That's a good point.
You're the one who is going to be seen in the bath.
That's right.