Good luck Matsumoto, on your way to become a hunter.
Hello.
I want to see your face a little more.
Today I want you to help me on my way to become a hunter.
It's a condition.
Please do your best.
You do your best too.
I will do my best.
This is a duck.
Bring it on!
What?
Sorry, it was my fault.
I shouldn't have done that.
You scared me.
Please.
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't have done that.
I didn't do that on purpose.
Right?
You shouldn't have done that.
That's not true.
What?
It's already decided.
Really?
Bring it on!
Hama-chan, Hama-chan.
It's not like that.
What?
It goes like this.
Do you understand?
I don't understand.
Bring it on!
It's a prey.
Wow!
The duck has become a pig.
Pig?
Don't say that.
Where are we today?
We are at Namco's company.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to...
What do you call it?
What is it?
You know, right?
What?
This is the only place where you can play that game.
That's why I want to train here.
I want you to support me.
You want me to support you?
That's what I want to do.
This is the place.
Now, let me eat something delicious.
That's not it.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
We have a lot of games that we don't have here.
What do you think?
It's fun.
It's like a dream country.
I don't understand.
Why are you so low today?
What?
I'm happy.
If you're so excited, you'll lose to Pink's phone.
Now, this one.
This one.
I want to try this one.
You don't have to say it.
It's working.
It's hard.
Why?
I don't know.
Damn it.
It's hard.
Isn't mine too low?
No.
Damn it.
It's low.
I'm sure it's that one.
That's not it.
I'm counting.
Can you eat it?
Ha!
It's a game over.
What?
40 against 180.
Why is the dog better?
It's delicious.
I don't want to play this game.
This is interesting.
Namco's big push.
It doesn't look fun.
It's made by electric machine.
You're touching it with your hand.
It's electric.
This monkey.
I'll do it.
Lucky monkey.
The title is interesting.
What do you do?
You dig it?
Yes.
It's hard.
Is this it?
Namco.
Namco-san.
It's over.
That's it.
You don't understand Japanese at all.
Do it one more time.
Ha!
Even if you don't say it, it'll come out.
It was fast.
Ha!
Only two hits.
I'll do it in one shot.
Hurry up.
You hit it just now.
Really?
Leave it to me.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
Why?
Why are you using a gun?
Everyone is fine.
Let's do our best to talk today.
We don't have much time.
We'll finish at 8.30.
Wait a minute.
Really?
Yes.
What are you doing?
I'm the one who's going to finish at 8.30.
You're lying.
Otomo!
Your shoes.
You're so silly.
I'll get a letter.
I'm a little curious.
Who's the leader?
Are you curious?
I don't think it's a good idea to point out the leader.
Really?
That's right.
It's not a good idea to point out the leader.
When the leader is decided, the gala will change.
The leader has a certain movement.
I thought I was the leader.
I don't know what you're thinking.
It's up to you to decide.
Really?
When you think of the leader,
For example, if you think of Goranger...
Red Ranger.
Red Ranger has thick eyebrows.
I think I'm the leader.
That's...
That face is cool, but it's scary.
It's scary because I'm the leader.
For example,
There's a group called Cool Five.
I'm with...
Uchiyamada Hiroshi.
Uchiyamada Hiroshi and Cool Five.
Why is Uchiyamada Hiroshi the leader?
That's why he brought up the idea of doing it.
He brought it up?
I think so.
The first thing he said was the leader.
Then it's me.
Why?
You're the one who decided on the printing company.
If I didn't say anything, you'd be sweating.
I don't think there's such a thing as an interesting printing company.
I don't know how to do it.
I don't know who's doing it.
I haven't given up on my dream of being a printer yet.
You haven't given up on your dream?
I can be a printer anytime.
There's a lot of printing companies out there.
You're a professional.
It's scary.
Can you stop it?
I failed yesterday, so I'm saying it.
That's right.
Yesterday, Fujimaki Jun.
He's actually a cutler.
He's in a commercial.
He was in the dressing room.
He said,
You're bald!
He's not bald.
He always says he's bald.
He always says that to me.
Who was it?
The girl in the costume?
You're bald!
Give me my shoes!
When I said that, Fujimaki Jun came out.
No, no.
He came out to talk about himself.
He came out because he was called.
You're bald.
No, no.
He came out because he was called.
That's right.
He's bald.
He came out to talk about himself.
You did a great job.
The two of you are going to be bald.
I told you to wear the pants I prepared in advance.
If you wear your own pants, you won't be able to go home.
I took off my own pants and took off the pants I prepared.
What is this?
My pants.
Who saw my pants?
My pants are patterned in eight.
He was annoyed and came up to me.
He said, I'm sorry for the girl in the costume.
He said, These are my pants.
I said, Take my pants off.
He was about to wear it.
Because he was about to wear it.
I asked, Are you wearing it the wrong way, Hamada san?
He said, I can't say anything earlier.
He took off my pants and put it on the girl in the costume.
Please stop it! My panties are wrapped around my neck!
Why are you doing this to me?
That girl's hair is completely white.
What?
Out of fear?
I don't know what to do.
But my panties are wrapped around my neck.
I don't care about that.
I feel sorry for you.
Please stop it!
Why are you doing this to me?
I don't know what to do.
Looking at you like that, I feel like I should stop.
I feel like I should stop.
I'll be the leader.
I don't care.
They should come on time.
You'll be the leader at the end.
You're a fool!
That's right.
You should come first.
You mean the leader?
Of course!
Great people come later.
I don't care about the great people.
I mean the leader.
I don't care about the leader.
I just want to be the first one.
You should be the first one.
Idiot!
You don't have to do this.
You should be the first one.
No, the leader should be the first one.
That's what the leader is.
You are the leader even though you are a leader.
The leader is not important.
The leader is just a name.
You are the boss.
If you want to fight, you should be sitting in the chair like this.
You are wearing uniform like this.
The leader is the last one who comes out.
No, it's not important.
You should be the last one who comes out.
I don't care about the leader.
I want to be the first one.
I'm going to tell everyone about the dinner joke.
What's that dinner joke?
Isn't it a dinner joke?
What's that?
He's here!
He'll come, right?
He's here, so I can relax.
Right?
What's that?
Oh, you're an amateur?
No.
What do you mean, no?
Is there something in there?
Here, here.
Huh? But you have a book.
What do you mean?
What do you mean, what do you mean?
Well, you know,
people like that write their own history.
Oh, is that so?
Yes, yes.
Well, it's written on the back of the book.
Oh, is that so?
It's written by Mariko Sagamoto.
Well, her father's name is Mitsuo.
What's that?
It's dirty, isn't it?
What's your mother's name?
Oh, her name is Yoshiko.
What do you mean by that?
She's in a good health condition.
She would have died early if she was like that.
It's dirty, isn't it?
It's flashy.
Huh?
This.
It's shiny, isn't it?
You have a good pelvis, don't you?
Right?
Did you have a good pelvis or something?
Yes, I had a good pelvis.
Right?
Do you have a pelvis shop at home?
Are you the princess of the pelvis kingdom?
Are you the prince of the pelvis village?
Thank you very much.
What's this?
You should open it yourself.
It's a letter from someone else.
Morukome-kun's big reward.
It's shiny.
Look.
Do it yourself.
To your father and mother.
Congratulations.
This is an announcement of the 8th generation Morukome-kun's big reward, the 4th generation selection committee's passing.
This is an announcement of the final selection committee.
I didn't say anything, but you passed the 4th generation selection committee.
I passed.
The children on that day, please wear a hat.
The clothes are Morukome-kun's T-shirt.
That's not bad.
When you receive it, you will be given a Morukome-kun T-shirt.
And a pair of pants.
This is for each of you.
We will pay for the transportation fee.
Please take care of it.
How many people will come?
Well, we received applications from all over the country.
Out of 25,251 people, your children passed the 4th generation selection committee.
They were selected as the final selection committee of 50 people.
I would like to congratulate you.
I will give you this.
I can't participate, so I have to push it.
50 people, 50 people passed the selection committee.
It's amazing, isn't it?
But I can't go on this day.
This again.
What?
Really?
This again.
You know better than me.
I can go, but my father and mother can't come.
Why?
I don't know.
I'm going.
You are not my father.
It stinks.
I'm going.
You are not selected, so you can't go.
I don't want to give up.
Why do you give up?
Because it's strange.
It's a waste.
Why is it a waste?
What?
I want to come.
You can't go.
What?
Let's go.
No, Matsumoto came alone.
Where did you hear this story?
I'm always a bachelor.
You're a bachelor?
Why are you Marukome-kun?
Marukome-kun is a bachelor.
You're a bachelor and Marukome.
If you're in the video game, you'll be called a bachelor and Marukome.
Really?
Ah, ahh...
But, not just
pressed a little
Your hand andare
Oh no
Hey, a boy
Oh burden
Pressed a little
You simply don't say that
I know
I don't want to say that
He's holding his head down.
Oh, that's funny.
Let's move on to writing.
What?
No, I'm serious.
What's the pen name?
I don't know.
Good evening, Machiyama-chan.
I'm always having fun with you.
Recently, I often dream of becoming a celebrity.
The other day, when I called my mother in my dream,
Koyanagi Rumiko came out with something like a naked negligee.
Since then, when I see Koyanagi Rumiko, I can't think of anyone else.
Machiyama-chan, has a celebrity come out in your dream?
Has anyone come out before?
I don't know.
I have.
I'm famous.
Yashiro Aki came out.
Oh, Yashiro Aki.
You're writing about Yashiro Aki, aren't you?
Why did he come out?
What's Yashiro Aki like?
Since then, he was quite famous.
Sake has a slimy texture.
Fish is...
Don't sing while you're singing.
Why are you in such a hurry to get married?
Why are you singing while you're singing?
That's enough.
The light is faintly...
It's disgusting.
If you sing while you're singing like that, it's disgusting.
That's enough.
I haven't seen WM yet.
Let's leave little by little.
Not yet.
We talked a lot today.
There's still more.
She's angry.
There's nothing.
There's no man like that.
Let's go home.
Everyone, let's dance together.
Yes.
She's embarrassed.
Please be quiet.
The best.
This is the best.
Let's go home.
Hello.
It's time to celebrate the 100th anniversary.
It's a project to celebrate the 100th anniversary.
How about doing this?
I'm going to ask for an idea.
What do you think?
They're here, but they're trying to get us involved.
It's none of your business.
They're our viewers.
They're trying to get us involved.
It's none of your business.
I think that's possible.
I also need an assistant.
I've been writing about this idea for the past two years.
Send me more and more.
I can't go home without a
Thank you very much.
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.