Chikisugi Bon-san has arrived!
Jan Jan Jan Jan Jan Jan Jan!
Bon-san has arrived, Bon-san
Hello
I am...
like B's Hiromi
I hate wearing things
You are wearing it
Hey!
Who would throw a trash can like this?
So in Osaka,
while Bon-san is saying he has arrived
the other guys are playing
Indian Fundo
Indian Fundo?
Yes, in the center of the Kanto region
they play Indian Fundo all over the country
After that,
Chuchu Takokahina
This is
all over Japan
In Tokyo,
this stupid thing is called
Tako, right?
It comes from there
Chuchu Takokahina
Daruma-san is from Cologne
It costs money
From Hokkaido to Kyushu,
all over Japan
Everyone is from Cologne
Well,
there is no origin
there is nothing
Well, there is nothing
There is something in the Philippines
What are you talking about?
The SM center is shaking
Bon-san is here!
Hey!
What? Me?
You are obviously...
Don't make a fool of me
Bon-san is here!
Hey!
I don't know what you are talking about
What are you talking about?
Don't make a fool of me
Bon-san is here!
Don't do that
What are you doing?
I can't see you
Bon-san is here!
Don't do that
Hey!
You are perfect
Kobayashi
Hey!
Bon-san is here
I can't see you
Wait a minute!
Wait a minute
Look at this
I want to jump in when I see you
Hey
You should talk to this guy
That's right.
Mon-san moved his room!
He moved!
No, he's a kid!
He's a kid.
Mon-san moved his room!
Wait!
No one's stopping me!
Mon-san moved his room!
You!
You can't touch me like that!
Mon-san moved his room!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8! Stop!
1, 2, 3!
That's too much.
I was thinking the same thing.
Sorry! What happened?
I'm sorry!
I was thinking the same thing.
You're kidding, right?
I'm kidding.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8! Stop!
Damn it!
I can't go any further.
Damn it! I'm going to get kicked out!
Let's go!
What should I do?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8!
Stop!
Hello!
Let's do our best.
You're drinking, right?
I drank a lot today.
You're so noisy!
I hope it's quiet when I drink.
That's right.
Today, I'm wearing a beige outfit.
When I was handed this outfit,
I was wondering how I should wear it.
How should I wear it?
I was wondering if other staff members should put their bangs in.
No, it's not like that.
It doesn't matter.
This is Yokoyama's business.
Recently, Hamada-kun started a drama, right?
No, I didn't start it.
He gave me the drama, and he gave me the drama.
You just don't want to do it.
I don't like dramas.
It's a long drama, right?
Yes, it's a long drama.
It doesn't go well with the show.
But in terms of acting skills, I'm ten times better than you.
In terms of acting skills and singing skills, you're better than me.
I'm serious.
If that's what you think, then that's fine.
Huh?
Do you think I'm better than you in singing?
Idiot!
Well, you came out.
It's an opening, so I can't say anything about it.
I'm losing.
Wait.
No, seriously.
What?
Yoshimoto is bad at singing, but you're Shinsuke Shimada.
What are you talking about?
It's something everyone can acknowledge.
Please include Akashiya Sanma, too.
Sanma, too.
These three.
Why?
You're the best in singing.
Idiot!
You're good, right?
Good, good.
You don't know what recording is, right?
You sing along, right?
You cut out all the good parts.
And then you connect all the good parts and make it into one song.
It's not like the guy who sang along is in the recording.
Idiot, in your case,
I have this much range.
That's not true.
It took you three hours to record, but I finished it in 30 minutes.
That's because the song is different.
It doesn't matter.
I asked you to listen to your own song.
I never take off my real voice.
Hey, isn't the song by Hibari Misora difficult?
No, it's not.
Ah, like a river.
You're making me angry.
I don't know if it's an explanation, but
I don't sing that song as an example.
I don't know about that.
I don't know about that kind of shocker.
I'll sing it like a river.
Shut up.
I'll close my eyes and sing it.
Ah, like a river.
I can't sing at all.
It's a song you've never sung before.
Then sing it.
I'll sing it.
I'll tell you a story.
When I sing, it feels like a river is flowing.
I'm opening the space.
Ah.
I have a good singing ability.
I'll never be able to sing well.
For example, I'm looking back and
I'm waiting for my girlfriend.
My girlfriend is pretty tall.
I'll run to her from the other side.
Then I'll look back and
smile at her.
Why do you like that kind of smile?
I can't talk to you because you're fresh.
No, you're the easiest to lose.
His smile is...
I'll be shocked.
No, it's not like that.
Look back and smile.
I'm waiting for my girlfriend.
I noticed her.
I'll hit her shoulder.
That's strange.
Why?
That's your stupid thing.
I just made a fresh face.
I didn't listen to you after that.
That's because you hit her shoulder.
You don't know that she's your girlfriend.
Why are you laughing?
I'm that kind of person.
Really?
Yes.
No matter who says it.
That's the first thing.
It's normal to notice her
after you know who it is.
You can't be a member of the Self-Defense Force.
That's true.
What did you say?
Let's go.
I'm irritated.
It's been 30 minutes.
What's wrong with her?
I can't wait any longer.
Matsumoto.
He's licking her.
Why?
What's with your face?
Your smile is worth a million dollars.
There's a scene like that.
There's a funny scene in a comedy drama.
The boss says something.
The boss looks behind him.
He looks at you and says,
You're annoying.
What?
He does that.
Stop it.
Let's see the letter.
Here you go.
You have a nice style.
Let me introduce you.
Ebihara Yumi.
How old are you?
43?
Are you 22?
I'm 43.
Do you have a boyfriend?
When I asked her,
she said yes.
She said it clearly.
I don't have a boyfriend.
Why?
You don't have a boyfriend?
No.
Why?
I'm a police officer.
But you have a lonely side, don't you?
No way.
Thank you very much.
Which one should I start with?
Anything is fine.
Should I read this?
Your pen name is Tokumekibo.
No one does that.
You shouldn't laugh at that.
I can't open my mouth.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'll read it clearly.
Open your mouth more.
Tokumekibo.
Your pen name is Pekepeke.
My school has a name that makes people laugh when they go to Osaka.
It's called Baba Dai.
Baba Dai.
Really?
I'm sorry to say this,
but my mother is from Osaka,
so she laughed when she heard this name at the entrance ceremony.
You don't know what I'm talking about, do you?
You do, don't you?
In Osaka, Baba means poop.
So people don't think much about it.
But in Osaka, people laugh at Baba Dai.
That's the way it is.
You can be bullied for this.
Poor thing.
The other day, I took a train in Tokyo.
I was riding with my friends,
and I said, I want to be a Baba.
People who take trains in Tokyo are completely normal.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
I didn't realize until now.
That's it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait.
That's it.
It doesn't matter if you're an idol or not.
No, that's not what I mean.
I don't care if you're an idol or not.
I'll tell you a story from here.
You'll be surprised.
How about this?
This is pretty interesting.
Yoshimoto once a year talks about negotiating his salary.
Now, Mr. Ikuyo Kurio is negotiating in a see-through costume.
Mr. Shinsuke is negotiating in a roll.
Mr. Norio is trying to negotiate by introducing a woman.
At the end, Mr. Nozawako from downtown said,
I haven't noticed this mechanism yet.
And if you want to negotiate, how do you negotiate?
By the way, Mr. Hanshin Kyojin said,
If you don't wake up and work, you can take a rest for the rest of your life.
Negotiation is...
I'm...
I'm properly separated.
I negotiate for work.
This regular is...
Let's do it.
It's better than this.
I want to do this.
This is money, right?
This is my money.
You're so mean.
You came to me first because you couldn't say anything.
He's dirty.
You are dirty.
I'll sell my hair if I have to.
You're a warlord.
You're the one who was dirty from the beginning.
You came to the studio as a manager.
Why are you giving me so much money on this show?
Please, you idiot.
I can't do it anymore.
I've been doing it all the time.
Month after month.
Why are you giving me so much money?
I've been doing it all the time.
Even if I'm told to negotiate for money,
I ask the manager.
The manager said,
Let's negotiate for money.
Let's talk while eating.
The two of us.
My manager and the manager.
While eating yakiniku.
How much do you want?
No, I'm not.
What do you think?
I'm addicted to money.
Hey!
You're really making it up.
What are you?
Why am I giving you so much?
And then I started.
I've been doing it all the time.
The manager is so rude.
I'm not doing it.
I don't need money.
Why are you doing it all the time?
I'm not a manager with any power.
I don't have money.
Why is it so little?
What's the matter with you?
What's wrong with you?
I don't need any money.
Don't lie.
I thought I could do this job, too.
All right.
I'm done.
I'm not going to give you my money.
What are you happy about?
I'm not shocked.
It's a strange company.
Shinsuke was joking.
I went to the manager.
I'm sorry.
I'll give you the money.
Take off your jacket and come to me.
I'm serious.
I'm not going to give you my money.
What will you do if I win?
I was joking.
I asked him to give me my money.
He said he'd do it.
He told me to come to him.
What a strange company.
It's a strange company.
The chairman of the company.
He was the one who won the Yoshimoto.
He is like a child.
How old is he? 80?
No, he is 92 years old.
He is holding a cane.
He is holding a cane in the office and making a fuss.
It's a serious story.
He is holding a cane and making a fuss.
I asked him what happened.
He said he went to the toilet and he didn't poop.
He wrote to his manager that he would flush the toilet if he went to the toilet.
And asked him to push the handle.
He is like a roller coaster.
Is that so?
Yes, it is.
There is also a manager who was found to be a woman in the toilet.
Yes, there is.
He was found and asked,
Am I a man?
He said,
I'm sorry.
Am I a man?
He said,
I'm sorry.
Yoshida's way of doing things is to fight.
He is trying to break the balance of the ship.
This is the dirty part.
Katsura and Yasushikiyoshi were fighting.
They were trying to break the balance of the ship.
This is Yoshida's way of doing things.
He is a good talker.
He doesn't have anything.
He has this much.
This is a strange company.
Let's do our best.
I don't have a rival in Yoshida.
This is hard.
In the company?
Yes.
When Katsura and Yasushikiyoshi are fighting,
Yasushikiyoshi goes like this.
I won't lose.
I'm angry.
Yasushikiyoshi is trying hard.
Then, Katsura goes like this.
Then, he goes like this.
If you can do it, come to us.
You did a special, right?
Yes, I did.
It was like that.
It was a share 79.
It was long.
In the middle of the night.
The rating was amazing.
It was 1.2.
How was it?
It was amazing.
I see.
I haven't done any events.
I've done a lot of things.
I've been preparing for Taisho Denoka.
I haven't done anything like that lately.
You haven't done anything?
You have to do it little by little.
I was told to do it little by little.
I couldn't do it.
You were told to do it little by little.
You said, I'll do it.
I was the only one who played the punishment game.
Why?
Hamada's bashing got me angry.
I don't remember the words.
I did a lot of things.
You said you were going to do something.
Do you have a letter?
It's coming.
A hat.
Toilet paper.
A doll.
A stuffed animal.
A stuffed animal that looks like you.
Yes.
Well...
Good morning.
Lucky.
You were lucky, weren't you?
Yes.
Look at the camera.
You were lucky, weren't you?
When you came out,
an old lady came running to you.
Thank you for your luck.
Is that true?
A pig old lady.
Isn't that young?
She said thank you to her daughter.
She said she was surprised.
I see.
If she knew, she wouldn't have done it.
Look.
What are you doing?
What?
Can't you see?
Jogi.
I have many assistants.
I write questions.
I write letters.
I have many assistants.
We are all the same.
Please come here often.
I'm looking forward to it.
Lucky's Skyline.
See you next week.
Bye.