The child's servant, the usual music player
Endo, your daughter is playing with Hamada?
That's right, she's like a family toy
She takes me out to eat
Since when did you become Tameguchi?
I've never been Tameguchi
But you are Hamada
No, Tameguchi is my senior
That doesn't matter
Endo and Hamada are the same
So it doesn't matter if I'm Tameguchi or not
But...
Do you have a problem with your senior?
No, that's not it
If Endo doesn't listen to Tameguchi, I can't beat Hamada
I think Hamada wants me to use Tameguchi
By using Endo and Tameguchi
My partner Tanaka can use Tameguchi
Tanaka can use Tameguchi too
I see
So Yamaaki can completely use Tameguchi
So if Endo doesn't use Tameguchi, it's impossible
I don't think my senior and junior will change forever
It's all about how you approach it
You'll notice no matter how stupid you are
It's pretty stupid
But it's like, huh? What's this weird feeling?
It's like writing on paper and explaining how to get angry
You can feel it, right?
It's really hard
It's hard to remember the basics
You didn't know that much?
I learned it from the smell of bananas
You're a manager
I finally learned it
It's different from the smell of bananas
I think it was around the beginning of the rainy season
It's recent
I think you'll know unless someone opens the box
But I don't know
Because I'm a senior
I'm thinking about the results
Thank you
Hamada came to the scene without knowing anything for a few minutes
Will Endo be able to listen to this man?
This program is brought to you by the sponsors of the 5th generation
The 1st Gagi no Tsukai Arai
Chiki Chiki Kokoriko Endo
Natsuno Ichiyoshi Geki Yuma
Otokonotte Ryori Kyosho
Thank you
It's summer
Endo will introduce you to a dish that goes well with it
I have stamina
I want everyone to eat it
Thank you for making such a place
After this, how will Endo tell Hamada?
If you have something to help
I think there are various things
Hamada, can you do it?
Please break the egg and put it in the bowl
Do it
It's okay to do it alone
It's a recipe
It's fun to do it together
I'm sorry
I will eat this
Thank you
Hamada, can you do it?
Can you mix it?
Mix it?
Yes
I can't do it alone
There are various things
Please do it
The trick is to mix it without breaking the egg
That's right
It's okay like this
It's delicious
I prepared this cold rice
Please put this egg in this cold rice
Do you put it in at this stage?
It's a lot of work
First, put this in
I can't see
I don't know this
I've never seen this
I'll put this in
It feels a little bad
That's not true
Is this okay?
It is said that thick food is not good for summer
Eggs are also good
Please loosen this with a tea spoon
Let's mix this
This is also important
This is very important
Do you cook at home?
I cook chocolate
I don't cook at home
Do you cook at home?
You don't cook at home, do you?
I don't cook at home
Is it okay?
Please add salt
I don't like summer
If it's not delicious, it's meaningless
I know that
I'm not making it properly
I know
Look at this
There is a lot of salt
I don't know because it's salt
I put this rice in
Be careful
I put this in
There is a lot of rice
Is this medium heat?
This is medium heat
Is medium heat the best?
This is important
Look at this
This looks good
This is good
This is perfect
This is amazing
Can you give me sausage and mixed vegetables?
Mixed vegetables are there
Please add this
sausage
This is good
This is not good
How about adding some minced meat?
Hama-san, do you like wieners?
The color is good.
I like it.
That's good then.
Hama-san, can you hold this for me?
Can you hold this for me?
I don't think you should do that.
Don't you remember?
Oh, I remember.
Curry?
It's not curry, it's dry curry.
Dry curry.
It's a bit too much.
A bit more, a bit more.
Okay?
Okay, okay, okay.
I'll do it.
And then, like this...
The way Hama-san mixed it wasn't very good.
The rice is a bit scattered.
It should be a bit more like this.
The point is to do it like this.
You're going too far.
Okay.
It's really spread out.
It's really close.
It's complete.
And then, put it on a big plate.
Isn't this amazing?
This is amazing.
It's spicy.
Look at this.
You put too much curry powder.
And then, there's white pepper.
There's a lot of white pepper.
And then...
What is this?
What is this? A tomato?
No, no, no.
A tomato is a bit...
Why?
It's a small tomato.
A small tomato.
You don't have to do it all over.
You can just eat it.
But this is...
Cooking and appearance are important.
It's okay.
You don't have to put it in.
I'll put it in.
And then...
This is a skinless small tomato.
Yes.
I told you I'd put it in.
It's been a while.
The color of the tomato is important.
Cooking is all about color.
I'll put it like this.
I don't know.
It's done.
I don't need tomatoes.
I told you earlier.
This is a dish with tomatoes.
I think you should try it.
I don't think so.
I don't eat tomatoes.
Let's eat.
I'm pretty confident.
I told you I wouldn't eat tomatoes.
This is...
Children may like it.
That's right.
Ho-san and Tanaka like it.
I like it.
Hame-chan likes it, too.
Children like it, too.
What is this?
This is a little small for me.
This is still small.
This is delicious because it is mixed with eggs.
How is it?
This is spicy because I can't eat tomatoes.
I can't eat tomatoes.
This is impossible.
Tanaka.
I can eat this if I work hard.
Can I eat tomatoes?
What?
Let's eat this.
What is this?
Can I eat this with tomatoes?
I can't eat tomatoes.
Can I eat tomatoes with my favorite sausage?
This is impossible.
Just one bite.
This is all.
Let's work hard.
Who are you talking to?
This is all.
Tanaka can eat this.
I can eat this.
You can eat this.
This is the second sausage.
This is difficult.
I can eat this with tomatoes.
You can eat this.
I eat this.
I can eat this with tomatoes.
This is impossible.
This was delicious.
See you next time.
Thank you for the meal.
This is delicious.
This was delicious.
I think you don't need to eat a lot of curry.
That's right.
I can eat this.
This is delicious.
Endo, come here.
Where are you going?
I'm going.
What is it?
Endo.
I know.
I'm going.
what?
Anyway.
I couldn't eat this.
I was scared.
I couldn't eat this as soon as I thought.
I couldn't eat this even if it was 5 pieces of curry.
I can't eat this.
I was angry when I heard Endo talking to Hamada.
I feel nostalgic.
I want to take a picture of this.
I have 5 pieces of curry.
I was very angry.
It was about 2 or 3 o'clock in the middle of the night.
In the park near my house.
I was doing this.
You were doing it.
I was doing it.
It was about 2 or 3 o'clock in the middle of the night.
It doesn't matter at this time.
It's strange.
It's about 2 or 3 o'clock in the middle of the night.
It doesn't matter.
Are you crying?
I was a little patient.
I wanted to focus on TV.
I was angry.
I called the police.
I see.
I'm sorry.
There is a park near my house.
This is a park that everyone knows.
There is a person who is holding a party at this time.
I want you to do something.
What is the name of the park?
What is the name of this park?
There is a park on the street, which everyone knows.
I'm not sure.
What is the name of this park?
This is a park.
Please be calm.
What's the address?
No, no, no.
I don't think so.
No, no.
I don't know!
I live in the park!
But Otaku live in the park, so it's noisy.
So tell me your address.
No, no.
Huh?
I can't tell you my address here.
I want you to burn the fireworks in the park.
Shut up!
I know that.
Tell me your address.
No, no.
My address is fine.
Shut up!
I want you to burn the fireworks in the park.
No, no.
My address is fine.
You don't have to worry.
I'll tell you my address.
I love you.
Why don't you tell me your address?
Well, that's...
That's strange.
What if there's a huge incident in the park?
What should I do?
What's the address?
No one knows!
Shut up!
Go!
Go right now!
And while you're saying that,
I'll tell you my address.
So tell me your address.
I'll say,
Shizuka!
I'm done with the fireworks.
I'm done with the big fireworks.
I don't know what happened to you.
I'll burn the fireworks in the park.
At least I wanted to see that.
That's right.
I'd like to introduce you to Mr. Matsumoto,
who has been given 108 different nicknames.
Mr. Matsumoto has been given the title of
the famous shocker by the Shocker Corps.
Please tell us why you weren't given the title.
Well,
I was fighting in the front.
What do you mean by the front?
I was fighting near the Kamen Rider.
You weren't in the back.
I wasn't in the back.
I see.
When the Kamen Rider decided the position of the fight,
he always put his hands like this.
Oh, then here.
And he always,
Oh, yes.
I thought it was pretty close.
It was close!
I thought it was like this.
The Rider.
I like that.
So you can give me the title of honor soccer player?
Yes, you can.
Why couldn't you give it to me?
Well, there was a little failure.
You should have told me that, I wouldn't have said that.
First of all, when I came to the award ceremony, I wore a little tight-fitting sleeve.
I was worried that my skin was visible.
There were only two of them, and one of them was a little washed.
It smelled strange because it was dry, so I dried it in the room.
When I tried on the one I hadn't used much, it was surprisingly small.
And it was like this.
But when I got the award, it was really hard.
It's a shocker.
You should have shown your skin.
When I got the award, I said,
What do you think?
You should have said that.
I thought it was a little weird, so I said,
What do you think?
I heard that one of the rooms in Matsumoto's house is made of iron.
Please tell me the advantages and disadvantages of it.
Well, there are good and bad things.
What kind of window is the otaku's house made of?
There are three rooms.
3L, right?
Yes.
And that room is...
That's right.
It's Tetsuko's room.
I wanted to use it, so I said okay.
Why did you say okay?
I said I'd pay 20% of the rent.
It's not a bad thing.
But that's Tetsuko's room.
That's right.
Don't you hate it?
But I said I could use it.
I said I could use it when I couldn't break it.
Oh, in that room.
What are the advantages and disadvantages?
There are many advantages.
What?
Well, when I get home, I come here and do some light washing.
It's better to do it when you're young.
Well, but they do it carefully.
Tetsuko?
I think that's good.
I can cook some okara.
That's good.
What are the disadvantages?
There are many disadvantages.
There are too many.
The woman is a disadvantage.
When I put my head on the kotatsu.
I thought it was a woman.
It's not.
It's a head.
I'm surprised.
It doesn't bother you to live.
Do you mean that Zura?
No.
It doesn't bother you because you have a room.
I want to take a rest today.
But it's like this.
Don't do it when you're awake.
Don't do it when you're not awake.
It's already started.
Agnes is coming today.
Agnes?
I don't like it.
Sometimes I take a shower when I go home.
That's normal.
She doesn't come to the living room, does she?
She does.
Why doesn't she come to your room?
Because I only have a bus on my waist.
You're slow.
It's dirty.
You.
I had a fight with a remote control at the parking lot.
There was only one.
I said I wanted it.
It's 20%.
But I use it more.
I know that.
I use it more?
You don't need it.
This month is Tetsuko.
This month is me.
I called her.
Tetsuko got off the car.
She gave me a ride.
She's your girlfriend.
Is that so?
Let's hang out together.
I'll give you a bus ride at that time.
I'll give you a ride at that time.
At first, she stood up for me.
I got used to it.
Sometimes she came out of the door and hugged me.
She said, I don't love you.
I don't love you.