Black Eyed Girls
Everyone, well..
If you have a stomach pain you can do it
This is all you think is handsome
It's true! I'm sure of it!
I'm sure of it!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Well...
I was in Guam, but it wasn't like that when I was there.
Well, that's how it is.
I was surprised when I came back.
Well...
Rather than being sunburned, I was burning up.
I was burning up.
It's a little scary.
Well, that's how it is.
I was surprised when I came back.
Well...
Well, that's how it is.
But, in Guam...
I stopped going to Guam in the New Year.
Why?
There were a lot of things I didn't like.
I see.
The sunburn you see on your face...
Even your dark circles were a bit white.
I can see the wrinkles on your dark circles.
I'm done this year.
Why?
It's not going to work this year.
You almost ruined my hangup.
I mean it.
I'm not even joking. I don't care about the customers.
I almost died from the sunburn in Guam.
But that's the same level as what you always say about a broken rib, right?
Like a broken rib just from falling from a step like this, right?
It's a different level.
I almost died in a hotel bath in Guam.
Ah, that's...
I washed my feet like this, right?
And the bathtub in the bath wasn't flat enough.
It was a bathtub like this.
And I washed my feet, right?
And there was no place to put my feet.
And I went like this.
And they said, shut up!
I went crazy.
I managed to do a Kokemite.
And on the edge of the bathtub...
I went like this.
I mean...
What's a bathtub?
On the edge.
You've hit your head, right?
A little bit.
Like a bump, right?
It's different.
If you hit it that much...
It goes like this.
At that time...
I went like this to the hot spring.
And it was a hot tub!
But my brain was shaking.
I didn't know it was hot.
I thought it was cold.
I don't know if it was hot or cold.
I was in the hot tub for a while.
And I was lying down.
You couldn't move?
I couldn't move.
Really.
I thought I was going to die...
in the bathtub in Guam.
I was going to die.
Didn't you say that?
I thought so.
It was really bad.
But you were okay after that, right?
But I was scared.
I thought I was going to die in a few hours.
I know that.
Right?
I was really scared.
I was on the poolside.
I thought I was going to die.
You thought you were going to die?
I was really scared.
That's why I couldn't move.
I was like this.
I wasn't laughing.
It's nothing.
Be grateful.
Why?
I wanted to go to the place where I worked hard.
I chose that place.
If I thought I was going to die, I would have gone there.
You didn't go there.
I went there completely.
You didn't come back alive.
What would happen?
A person who was going to die on New Year's Day...
would he be able to survive this year?
He didn't die, so he would survive.
If he had died...
Why do you look like you're going to die?
I died three times.
You look like you're going to die.
Maybe it's because I just got hit today.
Is that so?
You just got hit.
You said you were going to hit me.
I don't say it now.
Let's stop the Osaka fight.
You say it, too.
I say I can hit you.
I say it's plastic.
Let's stop it.
Plastic, plastic.
Plastic is plastic.
Where did you go?
I went to Las Vegas.
That's cool.
It's not cool.
Who did you go with?
I went with my family.
That's nice.
I don't want to go abroad on New Year's.
Really?
I don't want to.
I heard you went abroad.
You said you were going to fight.
That's right.
When I went abroad...
the reporter didn't know what I was going to do.
He asked me what year I wanted to be.
I said I wanted to be a snake.
I said I was already a snake.
He came back to me and asked me again.
I said I was already a snake, so I didn't care.
He asked me a lot about the future.
Miyasako was there, too.
I said I wanted to ask her, too.
She said, how is it?
I asked Yamashita.
Miyasako was depressed.
I had to do my best.
He doesn't understand.
He doesn't understand?
Yes.
Is that so? Did you write a lot about it?
It seems so.
I've heard a lot about it.
I decided not to go on a trip with Yamashita.
Why?
He's a dummy.
He's a fool.
Oh, really?
On Gundam Day, when we were going to the pool together,
he didn't sleep much at the end of the year.
To be honest, he wanted to sleep.
So I told him to let me sleep today.
I said, let's leave him alone for now.
Let's go to the pool together.
I told him to write a message and put it under the door.
I wrote Yamashita and told him to go.
He got out of the car and said, yes.
There wasn't as much space as I thought.
I said, I'll put 5mm of it and it'll be blowing in the wind.
I'll go back in a gas pose.
I said, okay.
I'll fly for sure.
I see.
You'll have to put it in longer.
I'll be sure to be blown away by the wind.
I said, think about it.
I said, okay.
I'll go back and turn the door mat and put a sticker there.
That's...
You'll have to come back and clean it.
I said, no.
I'll clean it.
I'll be blown away by the wind.
I'll open the garage and turn the door.
You'll understand.
I said, okay.
I'm an idiot.
I'll put it where I put the card machine.
I said, okay.
I'll ask you to put it in the room.
More than half of it.
That's more than enough.
I'll go back.
That's a bad idea.
That's stupid.
Miyasako came to my house because she forgot her cap.
She asked me to put it in the post office.
When Miyasako woke up, she went in.
I called him, and he said he didn't go in yet, so what does that mean?
He said he didn't have a place to put it.
There's no way.
Then what do you do with the letter?
There's a place where there's a lot of boxes, right?
Put it in there.
He said he didn't have it.
He said he couldn't tell the number just by having the key.
Then what is it?
The postman, the newspaper editor, all of them locked the door and opened it.
You can definitely put it in.
He said he didn't have it.
I think we need to take care of him a little more.
If I was his junior, I think he would be a really good junior.
I don't know what to say.
I don't know, he was just sitting there, riding a high-speed train.
When the toll booth was getting closer, I should have already prepared it.
I couldn't get in after I got there.
One of the doors in the back was open.
I was in a hurry.
I prepared the money.
I only opened it for a little while, so I had to do it again.
When I was about to pay, he was the only one who took the ticket.
You should have said that too.
That's a little bad.
I see.
That can't be helped.
Thank you.
If I had a bigger hand, I would have done it better.
What do you mean?
I would have done it with this much of a hand.
You would have made the area wider.
But I don't want one hand.
I want both hands.
I don't want a partner like that.
I want only one hand.
I'm going to eat rice from this year.
I'm going to eat white rice.
I'm going to introduce a split.
Why is that?
That's because...
That's enough.
Everyone is making money.
Why do I always have to pay?
That's strange.
Are you making money?
I'm making money.
Is that so?
That's strange.
I don't want to do it anymore.
It doesn't matter if people say I'm stingy.
Why do I have to pay for everything?
Last year we had a year-end party.
Let's go to Fuku.
We called a lot of juniors.
But in the end it was me who had to pay.
If I went to Fuku, it would have cost me 200,000 to 300,000 yen.
If I paid for it, who would pay for it?
Who would pay for 200,000 to 300,000 yen?
You should have said that to that girl.
I can be more generous than Fuku.
What?
That's too generous.
I don't care about money.
I'm going to quit.
But you should have a year-end party.
I'll still do it.
It's already the tenth.
Yamazaki, please give me a year-end party.
He kicked me from the top.
He's a little cheeky.
I haven't done it every year, but I can't help it this year.
I can't do it anymore.
Yamazaki, let's go.
I wanted to do it too.
Do you remember when we were doing Tsumura Illusion in Japan?
White Tiger came and Zeke Freed Android.
White Tiger was doing it.
He was still there.
He suddenly became an old man.
Do you know that?
I know.
I saw a pamphlet in Guam.
There was an Italian restaurant called Peppino Oji.
There was an old man who was very cheerful.
He said, everyone, come and eat.
I said, let's go.
He became an old man.
He didn't react at all.
No way.
He was a different person.
He was a big old man.
He ran around so much when he came to Japan.
That's right.
He came down from the top.
That's true.
I have to do the show from now on.
Zeke Freed is a different person.
He didn't move at all.
Only his partner, White Tiger, was like this.
He disappeared.
There are sad things like that.
At a circus or something.
The clown who was doing it was wearing a lot of makeup.
He was wearing a lot.
I can't forgive him because he's a human being.
There are animals that are strange.
They have something coming out of their asses.
Even a monkey has something like a rose coming out of its ass.
That's because it's such an ass.
There are monkeys that have something like a rose coming out of their asses.
But it's a monkey like that.
It's like a rocket launcher.
That's true.
That kind of thing is not good.
If you put your partner like this and do it at a high place, he disappears.
Only his partner has started.
All of them.
Only existence is walking alone.
It can't be helped.
I think he's walking alone.
Without a doubt, he will disappear throughout the year.
He will.
This is a question for Mr. Matsumoto, who has been an astronaut many times since the time of NASA's Apollo project.
Yes.
Even if you enter the atmosphere barefoot, how do you live without burning out?
How long do I have to answer such a useless question?
No, no.
It's okay if you don't answer.
But you know, right?
It might be a sin to know this.
Right?
So please tell me.
Don't you know?
You're wearing a jumper like that.
No, I don't know.
Why?
I don't know.
Do you know the atmosphere?
No, I don't know.
That's amazing.
It's tens of thousands of hertz.
I mean, if you put it in hertz.
No, I don't want to put it in hertz.
Then let's say the distance.
No, I don't want to say the distance.
What is it?
It's a very hot line.
It's a hot line.
A hot line?
You're a hot line?
What?
No, no.
You're a hot line? That's strange.
It's a hot line.
Now, when it's dug out there.
How can I protect myself?
Who can protect me?
I'm the only one.
At this point.
And by what I'm saying here.
The people who heard this can protect themselves.
Well, if that's the case.
If it's too much.
It can't be.
The age of the universe is coming.
It's coming.
I don't think that's the case.
I can't do that with my body.
Well, you have to try to avoid it.
Yes, yes, yes.
As much as you can.
Yes.
By eating soba.
I see.
Then please tell me.
Try to get out.
I'm trying to protect you from the heat.
Try to get out?
What are you going to do?
Try to get out.
It's a little strange.
What should I do?
Let's say it's coming.
A great heat.
Yes, yes, yes.
What's going to happen?
Please protect me.
As much as you can.
Please protect me as much as you can.
It's not a big deal.
What do you want to protect?
Where do you want to protect?
It's all over the place.
Find some points.
Then like this.
You're melting.
Nothing feels good.
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
First of all, you have to protect your eyes.
Eyes?
If you don't protect your eyes, you'll be in trouble.
I'll put it on my face.
No, no, no.
You don't know.
If your fingers can withstand the heat, no one will have a hard time.
That's right.
This is melting.
There's nothing you can do about it.
So think about protecting the whole thing.
What do you want me to do?
What?
What kind of question is that?
I can't get out of the New Year mood.
It's the same as usual.
I don't even feel like answering.
What do you want me to do?
It's a little inside out.
The heat is going to run away.
It's in the middle.
First of all, you have to think about separating the heat.
That's right.
Do you want to hear it?
Yes, yes.
I don't like it.
What are you talking about?
I'm listening.
Really?
Yes.
It's a little inside out.
Raise your armpit.
Why?
It's better to burn your armpit hair.
It's the other way around.
That's right.
Stop it.
This is a question for Mr. Mazumoto, who ate rice in a kappa plate.
Didn't the kappa get angry when the plate was taken?
What do you mean?
What do you think the kappa plate looks like?
I've only seen it in the manga.
It looks like a real plate is on it.
Do you think it's stuck to your body?
That's right.
That's what you think, right?
Yes.
It's actually just on it.
It's just on it?
That's right.
What is a kappa plate like?
I don't know.
It's like...
It's not like a plate that breaks when you drop it, is it?
No, it's like that.
It's more like a kappa plate than that.
Is that so?
Rather.
It's more like a kappa plate than that.
It's like that.
Is that so?
It's just on it.
If you think of it as a part of your body, you're wrong.
In a sense, a kappa is a plate.
It's also called a plate.
If you think of it as a plate.
That's right.
After I finished eating, the kappa was giving me highlights.
It was sour.
If you think of it as a star, it's a yotsuboshi.
Who?
The kappa.
This store.
I see.
That's what he said.
At that time, I went and took a picture, but I didn't notice it for a while.
I looked at it again.
What?
Hey, why?
That's when I finally noticed it.
I said, I'm sorry.
That's why I'm not angry.
I see.
But I'm really angry.
It's not like I'm going to die because I caught it.
It's not like that.
I'm just angry.
I see.
I think it's a feeling of being hit by a talent.
It's okay, but...
I'm angry.
It's just on it.
I put a double-sided tape on it.
You didn't put it on.
What are you doing?
I'm going to fall.
It's getting weirder.
I'm still being chased.
Did you return it?
I didn't return it.
You didn't return it?
Did you take it home?
I took it home.
So I'm still coming.
Kappa?
Kappa.
Return it.
I see.
If it's like this, it's Iji.
It's a fight between Iji and Iji.
It's his problem.
It's not him.
It's Kappa.
What's wrong with Iji?
I'm angry.
I feel like I lost.
What's wrong with Iji?
You took it yourself, didn't you?
That's right.
You should have returned it.
I feel like I lost.
Why did you do it?
I was angry because I thought I was scared.
What?
If I return it, he'll definitely say it's home.
When I said it, he was scared and returned it.
That's right.
I understand that.
Do you understand that feeling?
I don't return it.
I don't know what he'll say.
I'll definitely scold him.
I'll scold Kappa.
I want to give him something different.
I see.
Like a dumpling.
I don't know what to do with a small dumpling.
I don't know if he'll accept it.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.