Next time, we'll be talking about Kokoriko Endo, the 7th Henge!
Is this Endo's 7th Henge?
That's right. We'll be looking for a spot for Kokoriko.
Today, we'll be talking about Kokoriko's...
Let's call him in.
Endo, please come in.
Good evening.
Good evening, Endo-san.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm really okay.
It's a bit strange.
Are you okay?
It's you who's okay!
Look at this.
There were 7 people in the past.
The 1st place is Otomo.
29,000 yen.
The 3rd place is Takasu, the writer.
7,000 yen.
At the very least, it's your turn.
That's right.
If there's anything worth 7,000 yen,
next week, we'll be having a one-person talk.
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.
There's a lot of new stuff coming in.
What is this? An impersonation of the staff?
What do you do?
I impersonate Kazo Funagi.
Kazo Funagi?
Is that okay?
Excuse me.
Well, well.
You impersonated Kazo Funagi at that time.
This is the character.
I don't know if you're watching or not.
I don't know.
Well, well, well.
What is that?
Downtown's 24-hour marathon.
That's Hamada.
Why?
That's impossible.
It's difficult.
What should I do?
I don't think we should all do something.
Hello?
Is this Inoki?
I'm in Shikoku.
Thank you.
We have a script.
I think it's a little different from the first time.
No, no.
I thought it was fine.
We have to do it.
It's already decided.
Excuse me.
I don't want you to do it.
No, I'm not. I'm not the one who's talking.
I'm sorry if I interrupted you on the way.
Sorry.
It's difficult to talk for 22 hours.
Hello?
Yes.
It's long.
Can't you read the whole thing?
The fact that we're starting to talk doesn't mean that we don't accept it.
I'm sorry.
I got a taxi ticket.
Taxi?
Yes.
I have a lot of free time, so I'd like you to drop me off if you can.
Thank you.
Is this 700 yen?
Yes.
Thank you.
It's a little over 3,000 yen.
I'm always late for work, so I don't know what to do.
It's a little expensive.
It's difficult.
Is 700 yen okay?
The price is okay.
Teacher, do you think this is going to fall?
It's definitely not going to fall.
It's not going to fall.
It's not going to fall?
What is this?
It's a receipt for the convenience store.
It's difficult.
It's not going to fall?
Can't you read the whole thing?
The whole thing?
Read it for me.
It's not going to fall?
It's impossible for convenience stores.
It's impossible for convenience stores?
It's definitely not going to fall.
It's not going to fall.
Matsumoto.
At first, it was a little...
At first, it was a little funny.
I want to read it myself.
It's a
Enno.
It's a picture of Enno.
Hey, this is the worst.
What should I do?
This is dangerous.
Why am I dangerous?
It's cute, but it's dangerous.
It's taken.
Face.
Whose face is this?
It's cute.
I don't know.
It's taken.
Take a good picture.
I think it's off.
This video...
I think it's on.
This video.
Let's stop each other with a more normal expression.
You're really something.
I don't know what to do.
Let's get it on.
I'm telling you in the video.
You're telling the digital camera?
I'm telling the digital camera.
Let's get it on.
Nothing good will come out.
Ready, set.
Do you want to smoke?
Wait a minute.
What the hell did I do?
What should I do?
I don't want to smoke from here!
Idiot!
That was safe.
But when I put out the cigarette, a firefly got stuck in my finger.
It was so heavy that it got stuck in my finger.
Idiot.
I'm gonna smoke.
How long have you been smoking?
2-3 hours.
I've been smoking since then.
I see.
Then next time...
You don't have to smoke.
You smoke.
I'm smoking.
You don't have to smoke.
Then next time, I'm gonna smoke with this.
It was normal for me to be escalating, idiot.
Say sorry to your mother.
What the hell?
It's 16,000 yen.
That's too much.
Ah, Suwa-chan, you're out.
Thank you for your hard work.
Eh?
Thank you.
As for the amount, I'm in 3rd place.
Really?
Yes, 16,000 yen.
Yes, thank you.
It's just that everyone...
How do you say it?
I don't feel like it.
I'll close it for a while.
Yes.
Thank you for your hard work.
Yes, it's me.
That's a very dark ending.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you very much.
Now, Marimo-san.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, I'm sorry at the beginning, but...
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Let's take a look at the players' airs.
It's cold.
You guys, you guys, you guys, you guys.
Hey, hey, hey.
Stop it.
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
I was surprised.
You just left a guest.
You came out of nowhere.
I thought it was a guest.
I don't know.
I don't know if it's over, but...
There are only guests who came to see the mountain.
Yes, yes, yes.
I don't know if I should say hello properly.
I'm scared.
I just ran away.
Thank you very much.
Good luck, good luck.
Don't make me laugh.
I'm crazy.
Hamashou.
Is there anyone on your birthday?
Don't hate me.
We're family.
Naoko.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, dear Naoko.
The results are out.
You can see it in the graph.
It shows every minute.
Yes, yes.
Last time, we started 30 minutes late for Naita.
When you start 30 minutes late, the numbers are good.
To be honest.
I thought it wouldn't start.
Everyone is waiting with the channel together.
Do you understand?
Yes, yes.
Are you a human being?
It's easy to understand.
I was told that.
It was like I was sleeping in the afternoon.
It was a very interesting result.
Until now, Yamagaki has nothing to do with it.
We are on the show.
Until now, the number of viewers is 20.1%.
From now on, Yamagaki is alone.
Shall we call Yamagaki?
Let's call him.
Now.
It's interesting.
He came out.
Did you hear that?
This is the time when you were alone.
Thank you very much.
To be honest, in the second half, we were chasing you.
That part is a little like this.
That's right.
This is the number of viewers that Yamagaki has.
This is the number of viewers that I have.
And you have exceeded 20%.
You have exceeded 20% so far.
I have exceeded it.
This is the time.
It's a game.
Let's see.
Be quiet.
I won't be quiet.
Ta-da.
Up to here.
After all.
This is the line of 20%.
Yamagaki will return to the backstage once.
When I returned to the backstage, we were there.
That's right.
That's why it's gradually coming out here.
Yes.
I have exceeded 20% there.
Yamagaki appeared again.
I thought it was Gakun.
This means that the average number of viewers for Yamagaki is 18.7%.
You are too angry.
It's enough.
It's true.
This is.
I think I did my best as Yamagaki.
This time, the overall average is 19.4%.
It was a little more overall.
That's right.
Overall.
I don't want to see a good guy screaming.
There was a reason.
I want to see the person who cried on the stage for the first time.
Even though I've fallen so far, I went up a little.
It's true that I went down a little with the impersonation of Yumi Adachi.
I went up a little because I was going to do it.
I went up.
I did a good job.
I didn't exceed 20%.
Now.
Punishment.
I can't accept the punishment.
I don't look like this, but I'm really angry.
That's right.
If you spend too much time on your punishment, it will go down again.
No, no, no.
Punishment.
I think I'll get my injection.
Don't die.
Even if you die.
I'm angry.
It's a life-threatening thing.
That's right.
But the audience is not reflecting.
Yamazaki.
Yes.
I think so.
Why is that?
It's embarrassing.
You came out again today.
The entertainer got off the stage and ran away.
I saw it for the first time.
If you're a doctor, you can't get out of your stomach.
Do you know what you did?
I know.
It's a ridiculous thing.
It's ridiculous.
I know that.
I thought about it.
I think I'm going to cry.
What is the punishment?
I don't think I can do this.
I can't help it.
It's not fun to do it here.
Skydiving Bose.
Dangerous.
Tandem.
Skydiving Bose.
Wait a minute.
Can you follow me?
Of course.
I'll fly with you.
We'll fly together.
The doctor behind us will buy it while we're flying.
Wait a minute.
Dangerous.
The doctor behind you is not a skydiving doctor, but a hair salon doctor.
I'm a skydiving doctor.
Why?
You're going to get a weird haircut.
What kind of smell is that?
Which one are you going to take?
That's a skydiving professional.
I'll take a skydiving professional.
But that professional is not a hair salon professional.
You don't want to come down in a weird way, do you?
No, no.
That's crazy.
I'm not a skydiving doctor.
I'm here.
Your cute juniors are here.
Kokoriko also did a seven-stage performance at the opening today.
This was also Don's Belly.
If you want, I can fly with you.
Of course, I'll fly with you.
That's for sure.
Let me say something.
Will it last long?
It will last long.
Please stop.
Why can't we stop?
My nose.
My nose is coming out.
Are you stupid?
That's weird.
It's not weird.
If you turn around, you're not responsible.
Why are we responsible?
Because you're involved when you're drinking.
You said you could get 20%.
I didn't say that.
What are you talking about?
Because this week...
The seven-stage performance is also the seven-stage performance in Edo.
I'm not in it.
I'm not involved.
There's a connection between here and here.
That's right.
I know you can't be punished.
Why?
We're partners.
I don't think so.
I really don't like it.
I don't like it.
But I'm jealous of you.
I'm jealous of you.
I'm not jealous of you.
I'm not wearing it.
I'm wearing a T-shirt.
Why are you wearing a T-shirt?
The T-shirt is a good size.
What kind of T-shirt is that?
After the performance, the audience who came last week had no fun.
So I'm going to go to their house.
I'm going to bring a castella.
A castella?
I'm going to bring a castella and a raw yatsuhashi.
I'm going to go there with a castella.
Are you going to apologize for going to a castella place?
If I don't forgive them, I'll have to think about it again.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I ran away.
I shouldn't have run away.
I brought some sweets.
Isn't it something you do when you have an accident?
It's an accident.
It's called a comedy harassment.
It's a comedy harassment.
Wait a minute.
What did we do?
You're the closest senior to me.
Did you get a haircut?
What are you talking about?
It's not a big deal.
My partner is bisexual.
That's a big deal.
I've done that about four times.
If you were to die tomorrow at 2 p.m., what would you do?
I see.
I'll die at 2 a.m.
I'll definitely die.
I'll tell you the truth.
I won't do anything for you.
What do you mean?
Because I can't do anything for you.
I'll die before you do.
Why?
It's a life without you, so I can't think about it.
You...
You can't do it, can you?
Why do sunflowers look at the sun and bloom?
Sunflowers look at those who give them more energy.
I see.
That's why you're always looking at me.
That's because it's work.
The customers are always looking at me.
In the end, I'm the one taking pictures of you.
Please tell me how to give a high impression to the guy at the toll booth on the highway.
When you pay the money.
You open it again and pay, right?
How to give a high impression at that time.
Even if you don't say anything and you get a high impression, most people don't do that.
Like Mr. Goro.
That's right.
I want to give a high impression to him.
I usually open the window and say,
Long time no see.
Who is that?
Shobari Aikawa.
He looks like him.
It's been a long time, Mr. Eiji.
Why are you doing this now?
It's because of Aikawa.
It's a little popular among me.
It's been a long time.
I want you to say something to him.
Just one word.
You don't do that, do you?
No, I don't.
Have you ever said that to someone?
When I get a high impression, I say it properly.
I do it properly to people who are able to work.
When I get on the highway, I usually pay 10,000 yen.
I show him 10,000 yen.
Do you understand?
Let's all do this.
Otherwise, if you pay 10,000 yen after stopping, he will be in a hurry.
That's true.
I have to tell him that it's 10,000 yen.
But if you pay 10,000 yen, he will approach you.
What?
Even if you pay 10,000 yen, he will approach you.
That's unusual.
If you open the window and pay 10,000 yen, he will approach you.
If you pay 10,000 yen, he will approach you.
If you think about cars, it's not strange, but if you don't have a car, you're a fool.
I don't understand.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.