Congratulations!
Thank you very much!
What is this?
Seriously?
It's been a year!
Thank you very much!
Take it!
Today...
I was reborn as a modified human.
From now on, I'm going to be a bad guy who hits people in the head.
What are you talking about? Take it off!
I can't take it off. I'm having a surgery in Germany.
Today, 5 people came to Mr. Reddy's place.
You and the person who won at the end.
It's a draw.
Are you okay?
I'm okay, but I can't do it like this.
That's fine!
It's okay to be normal.
Now, let's introduce ourselves.
First, self-introduction.
I'm Asuka Hikaru from Shinjuku, Belha. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Now, number 2.
I'm Coco. Nice to meet you.
Number 3.
I'm Hiro-chan from Belpoppins who also came from Shinjuku, Belha.
I'm Sayaka from Belpoppins who also came from Shinjuku, Belha.
And number 5.
I'm Sara.
Are you sleepy?
Your eyes are like this.
Now, the first round!
Let's start the first round! Ready, go!
You're noisy!
Number 3.
It's hard to win.
Let's start with number 3.
Nice to meet you.
You have to pull it.
Are you okay?
Ready, go!
Which one do you think is the first place?
Nice to meet you.
What do you mean by the first place?
I've been doing this for a long time.
You've been doing this for a long time.
You're the big brother of the big brother.
I'm the big sister.
You're the big sister.
Now, let's start.
It's a competition between the two of you.
Ready, go!
No! No!
No way!
You bastard!
Now, it's your turn.
Big sister.
Number 5's big sister.
Big sister, your neck was shaking.
It's amazing.
You're like the boss of the Famicom.
How many times have you done this?
How many times?
12 years.
I've been doing this for 12 years.
You're the big brother of the big brother.
I'm the big sister.
Ready, go!
I can't win.
It's amazing.
I won against the Musa lady.
I'm the representative of men.
That's enough!
He's making a circle.
I was scared of his reaction.
Now, it's your turn.
Ready, go!
Look at this.
I can't win.
Hurry up!
Now, it's your turn.
I can't win.
If I had won, I would have won.
What do you want?
Anything is fine.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Good evening.
Today...
What is it?
What?
What do you mean we're together?
It doesn't make any sense.
Why are you clapping like that?
I think it's fine.
Really?
I'm a little upset today.
Why?
I'm a little upset.
Today, the guests...
It's like a love story.
The guests are bad today.
Really?
Yes.
But there are quite a lot of them.
Somehow.
There are quite a lot of men today.
But it's typhoon today, right?
It's bad for the guests to come.
It's fine.
There are quite a lot of them.
You're late.
I see.
I was going to get angry and spread the story.
But when I came out, I saw that there were quite a lot of them.
That's right.
I was thinking about it, so I didn't tell you.
I didn't want to tell you, but I saw that there were quite a lot of them.
You can't get angry.
I can't get angry, so it's fine.
But you came today, so it's fine.
You came a lot.
Really.
There are quite a lot of men here.
Look, look, look.
There's something strange about this program.
Why?
The people who are watching are not clear, right?
There are various people watching.
Really?
Most of them are young.
The people who come here.
Well, well, well.
I think they sometimes bring their mothers.
There are people who come with their mothers, right?
What kind of family is it?
No, so they're close.
They come with their parents.
And if there's such a small story...
That's right.
It's hard to do it here, isn't it?
It's a small story in front of your mother.
Right?
When I was in elementary school, I watched it with my parents.
It was hard to have a small story, wasn't it?
It was hard, wasn't it?
I think there will be a bed scene.
But I can't run away.
I've been watching everyone like this.
Suddenly there was a bed scene.
I can't go anywhere.
That's right.
I can't run away.
Why do you want to take off your pants?
It doesn't smell like your pants.
That's why I'm looking forward at the beginning.
Because it doesn't mean anything.
But if you wear that kind of thing, it's like this.
Your mother's face has to come forward.
If you can see your own face, it's okay.
I'm looking down so that I can't see my own face.
Your family is in a row.
It's not a family game.
I have a family.
I tried not to be able to see my face as much as possible.
But there are families where you can talk to your parents.
That's right.
There's no such thing at all.
When I was in middle school, I fought with my sister.
I thought I hit her.
When my sister stood up, I hit her hip.
At that time, my family said,
Don't lie to me.
I said,
Wait.
I hit her hip, so I said,
That's right.
Everyone said,
I also hit my sister.
I said,
Hitoshi hit Naomi.
What are you talking about?
Your family is in a row.
My sister also said,
If you hit your stomach, you can say,
I was hit here, so my sister didn't hurt me much.
Hitoshi, don't bite me.
My sister said,
I don't hurt.
It doesn't hurt like a man.
Your mother also said,
I don't want to hurt Naomi.
Why did your mother say that?
When you go over there, it's hard for your family.
But there are families where you can talk to them openly.
That's right.
This program should be more lively.
It's lively, isn't it?
I'm lively, but you're not.
Why am I the only one who says that?
Everyone is laughing, isn't it?
You should also stop telling dirty jokes.
I'm not doing it because I want to.
I'm doing it because I want to.
Who wants it?
The atmosphere on the spot.
You did it before, didn't you?
With only men.
At that time, it didn't matter, did it?
At that time, it was full of dirty jokes.
Men don't want that.
If you want it, your face won't come.
I said dirty jokes.
At that time, there are women.
That's right.
You did it with only men, didn't you?
What are you going to do next?
It's a strange place.
I'm going to shave my beard.
That's not good.
While you're doing it, everyone is shaving their beards.
That's right.
You shouldn't say that.
You're terrible.
I'm going to shave my beard.
You're going to be an old man.
You're an old man, aren't you?
When the show is done, I'm going to be called Zura Miyaburiman.
You can do that at our opening.
I'm going to be dressed like Zura Miyaburiman on the train.
What kind of clothes are you wearing?
I'm going to wear a cape and be a hero.
I'm going to get on the train.
When I get on the train, I'm going to be called Zura.
Do you understand?
When I get on the train, I'm going to be called Zura Miyaburiman.
I'm going to be called Zura.
You're an idiot.
You have to do this on your new show.
The next guest is a nurse.
It's a job.
I have to be older than 18.
Really?
Yes.
I didn't know that.
Really?
That's all? That's all?
That's all
Well, at least once
Maybe a little lower
Ah, that's also possible?
Yes, yes, yes
Like a middle school girl
What's so funny?
It's your responsibility
Wait!
Until now...
You know, really
I'm not interested at all in that kind of stuff
You know, I...
Don't look at me like I'm a lolicon
Let's go with the flag
The flag...
What are you doing?
What are you doing at such a distance?
Hello, let me introduce myself
I'm Tomomi Ebihara
I'm 20 years old
Right now...
I'm a third-year student
I used to be a big sister
I'm also a fan of Downtown, so I wanted to be on the show
Is that so?
When did you become a fan?
When was it?
A long time ago?
No, recently
Recently?
Did you say anything?
I did
What did you say?
I was a fan of Matsumoto-san
But now I'm a fan of Hamada-san
I'm going to cry
Why is that?
I'm scared
Scared?
You're scared of me?
What are you going to do if I don't come?
Why?
Who are you a fan of?
Hamada-san
Well, that's a different story
Who did you become a fan of after talking to each other like this?
Hamada-san
You're pretending to be delicious
I see
Thank you very much
Thank you
On October 3rd, I was on a popular show in the fall
It was called Shobai Shobai
Hama-chan called Giant Baba-san
Baba!
Itsumi-san
Itsumi!
Kayama Yuzo-san
Yuzo!
I said that
After the show ended, didn't you say anything?
You want to throw away your senior
Can you live in the entertainment world like that?
By the way, Matsumoto-san was quite calm
But in front of the fans, he's scared of the weak
In front of the strong ones, he's being mean
He's clapping
Even if the entertainment world turns against me
I'll still be on your side
Thank you very much
This is true
It was cut, right?
Go-san also said that
That's right
At that time, he must have been very angry
Why was he called out by such a guy?
That's not true
Go Hiromiya
Lee, today was the worst
Don't get angry!
You don't sound like him at all
You're just tall
Kayama-san was angry, right?
Kayama-san wasn't angry
Kayama-san, when I got off the elevator
We were together
We were laughing and going like this
That's because I smashed your shoulder
On the spot, you said
Go Hiromiya, excuse me
Ah, it's fine
You don't sound like him!
Even if you say that
Even if he apologizes
At home, Lee is angry
Is that so?
Lee is angry
Lee doesn't apologize
Don't say Lee, Lee
Only Lee is yelling at home
I think this is quite interesting
I'm a fan of the two of you since your debut
I've asked my friend to record the song
But I was doing a show called
It's 4 o'clock
I watched the video
And the next thing became clear
It's always Matsumoto-san who hugs
Matsumoto-san was the first to cry and hug at the first concert
Matsumoto-san was the first to hug with the record selling well
Matsumoto-san was the first to hug and kiss with the record jacket
And so on and so forth
It was recorded in my video
And so, Hamada-san
Even though Matsumoto-san is doing so much
Why don't you show him the same attitude once?
I feel sorry for Matsumoto-san
Just once is enough
Please respond to Matsumoto-san's love
But I often say that I'm a homo
That's not what I'm saying
Eh?
What do you mean?
What?
Do you think so?
When you're sleeping in the dressing room
I'm already doing it
I want to pee
Don't say things that can't be helped
There's no way
When you're sleeping
I'm already doing it
What are you talking about?
Stop with the dirty jokes
Yuta, where are you going with your head?
I have a boyfriend that I've been dating since middle school
The other day, I suddenly went to his apartment
I was in bed with a girl I didn't know
And we had a fight
I was really angry
And I said, I'll have Hama-chan do it
And then my boyfriend said
With your technique, Hama-chan can't beat you
That's what he said
I might not be good at it
But I don't think I'm that bad
I was really angry
I want to break up with Hama-chan
Hama-chan, please do it on TV
Hama-chan, please do it
Should I beat you?
Please reply on TV
And say something to your stupid boyfriend
That's what he said
But there are things like that
Technicians are better
Really?
I'm sorry to say this but
Technicians are better
Really?
There are people who look down on you
You look really good
But when you actually do it, it's completely different
Completely different?
Completely different
That's the most troublesome thing
I'm like a black belt in sex
What are you talking about?
I'm a yellow belt
It's okay to just be a white belt
Being a white belt is the worst
But you like white belts
The other day on a TV show
Natsumi-san said that Hama-san's fart
Is so smelly that it makes you want to kill it
He said that it makes you want to sit on it
Is it really that smelly?
Don't read it like that
We've been together for a long time
I've never bothered you with your smelly fart
But if you're okay with it, please tell me
I'll take care of you from now on
I don't want to
You really should go see a doctor
Wait a minute
Don't say it with a straight face
Say it with a smile
Don't say it with a serious face
Something's definitely wrong
Are you stupid?
My fart is normal
Don't underestimate it
Seriously, this fart
At first I said a lot of things
I threatened you and comforted you
I pushed you away
But you won't stop
Just one?
Your fart is smelly too
Compared to my fart
Compared to your fart
It's completely
White belt
This guy's fart is
How should I say it
Lately it's too smelly
I can't do anything about it
In a normal room
You can say it's smelly
But this is different
It's not something you'd think of in this world
So it's too smelly
What?
That's what I think
Do you understand how I feel?
Is that so?
What?
Don't think about your body
You know
You're in a car
For example
A salaryman with glasses
He jumps out
You're in a car
And you're like
These glasses are scary
What?
No matter what kind of life that salaryman has lived
He ends up wearing glasses
Even if he's a very important person
He has a family
He has kids
And he's wearing glasses
He's like
These glasses are crazy
But that's what everyone says
You say that too
I do
He's like
These glasses are crazy
He's just wearing glasses
That's right
He's crazy
Even if he's with a girl
He's with three girls
And they're all gathered
And he's like
I'm going with the red one
What?
You're going with the red one?
He's looking
He's like
I'm going with the red one
What?
You have a nosebleed
You don't have a nosebleed on your hand
Why?
You don't have a nosebleed
It's been a week
What do you want to do with your nosebleed?
Your nosebleed is bad
What are you saying?
You're just doing it
The nosebleed is bad
Hello, this is Ending
Hello
Yes
For those of you who haven't seen it, there's a little kid in downtown
Ah! It's Piano Bullsone!
Piano? How do you know?
The one who has that is Perisa's Ruby-chan!
It's written on the front
That's right, Piano Bullsone and Perisa's Ruby's fashion ring
We'll be receiving a lot of letters from this program
We'll be giving them out every week to the people we've introduced
Why are there still so many?
Because this program is amazing
What?
We'll be receiving a lot of letters
We'll be receiving a lot of ideas
We'll be receiving a lot of assistance
We'll be receiving a lot of photos and videos
We'll be receiving a lot of letters