Down-Town's Gaki no Tsukai Yaraen, Gekitotsu, Chikitsuki Sannin-chan Marathon Race!
Welcome to the event!
Today, we're going to take care of the mecha.
Matsumoto-san, please come up here.
How are the mechas doing?
You're not sweating, are you?
It's cold.
Say something!
Me too.
Normally, that guy would be cold and tired.
It's really cold.
What the hell is this?
This is the first time.
You've never done this before.
This is ridiculous.
It's the start.
Let's go!
In America, this is a gentlemen's sport.
Do you know where America is?
I do.
Really?
It's a gentlemen's sport.
It's not a cowardly sport.
It's a gentleman's sport?
Yes.
I'm not lying.
You're not lying?
Of course.
I'm a little worried about the mecha.
The oil I saw earlier is leaking.
Where is it?
There's a problem with the tires.
I'll look up.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Shall we start?
Yes.
Please start.
I'll go like this.
Here we go.
Hey!
I told you to do it properly!
It's dangerous!
I'm dead.
What should I do?
What are you doing?
I can't stop sweating.
Let's stop.
It hurts.
It's hard.
It's really hard.
Which way?
This way.
That way?
I'm dead.
Why are you sweating here?
Who thought of this?
While riding.
Excuse me.
Everyone on the way.
Don't you have a lipstick?
Yes.
I see.
Now I understand the meaning.
Downtown?
Stop it!
Get out of my way!
What should I do?
Drink it! Drink it! Drink it!
Can I drink it?
Is this okay?
Yes.
I'm scared.
I can't do it anymore.
Stop it!
I can't reach it.
I'll kill you.
I can't do it anymore.
It hurts.
Hurry up.
I'm really dead.
I'm tired.
But I won.
It's good to exercise sometimes.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Today, I played like this.
Let's go to the venue later and talk.
Yes.
Let's go.
Who is this person?
I don't know.
What?
Ladies and gentlemen.
You're still in front of him.
Yes.
You came to a strange place again today.
But it's Ikebukuro.
I don't know if it's Ikebukuro.
I'm in the middle of it.
What?
And there's a dirty park in front of it.
Wow.
You're crazy.
What?
Thanks to that park, I had a great time today.
What is that opening?
I'm a human being.
I want to kill you.
You prepared a signboard and a thing to use in the sports festival.
I'm angry.
I'm at Tokyo Station.
It's scary.
He's so cool.
That's scary.
Aren't you car scarier?
That's scarier.
Oh, really?
I need your cooperation.
Please cooperate!
If you leave this Неo here won't stop until it reacts to me.
It won't simply ignore me?
If you ignore it, you'll know it.
Please cooperate!
Is it really noisy?
This is really loud.
You want me to bring the box?
That's not what I was talking about.
Yeah
Just bring the money.
Just let us bring it.
It's not very heavy.
Yeah.
I was so angry.
I was so jealous.
I said, huh?
It's not your fault.
And she was like...
What's with that face?
You should have put that in the video.
Don't make that face.
I was so frustrated.
But you shouldn't be like that.
It's not true.
You should have put it in the video.
It was so embarrassing.
I shouldn't have put it in the video.
Isn't it embarrassing?
It's common, isn't it?
The red feathers...
You should do it.
That's right.
The young people are different.
They're shy.
They're not shy at all.
But after they've changed...
The old man says,
They've changed.
You know, the way he expresses it is so rude.
No, it's just in his heart.
It's like, let's go home, let's go home.
That's what it is.
I understand that.
That's a trick, right?
Everyone's perspective.
He's just being nice and trying to look cool.
That's just what everyone hates.
Ah, I see.
That's really what I hate.
The smile that you make when you get tired of it.
But I was made to do that.
I was like, why are you doing this on TV, on stage?
And the audience was laughing, but there was at least one person with a sad face.
Like that guy, Frillman.
Frillman!
Frillman.
You're my mother!
This is a different story.
I was talking to a friend.
Men are really a pain in the ass.
Don't say that together.
Why?
I don't think it's like that at all, but he has a habit of talking.
He's walking and there's no one around, but he says,
Ah, I'm tired.
He says that a lot.
He's not tired at all.
He's not tired, but he says,
Ah, I'm tired.
Even when it's not that cold, he says,
Ah, I'm cold.
He says that a lot.
He doesn't say, I'm tired.
He doesn't say that a lot, but he says that a lot.
Men and women are the same.
And in the case of men, there's something nasty coming in, right?
Like, I want to do it.
There's a way.
I want to do it.
There is!
There are definitely men.
Right?
There was a time when I wanted to write in Osaka dialect.
On Fuji TV.
I was laughing by myself.
It was really funny.
You're laughing too much.
There was a rehearsal in my dream.
When I came,
Uchanan-chan wasn't there.
Uchanan-chan said,
I'm a little late for work.
Uchanan-chan's rehearsal didn't start yet.
I said,
I'm going to the toilet.
I went to the toilet alone.
He opened the door for me.
I want to write Uchanan-chan.
No, I don't want to write Uchanan-chan.
You're lying.
Really.
I'm serious.
I don't want to write Uchanan-chan.
I don't think so.
Really.
I want to write Uchanan-chan.
It's not related to me.
It's mixed.
I don't think so.
I want to write Uchanan-chan.
That's too bad.
I'm serious.
I was embarrassed.
There are times when I'm told to write.
For example,
I'm in the same school.
I was in the school.
The man next to me wrote while doing it.
I don't know him at all.
I wrote it.
I said, hey.
I said, hey to him.
I thought I didn't understand.
That's...
That's my...
I wrote it.
Hey.
Even the old man couldn't stand it.
I couldn't stand it.
I wrote it to a guy I didn't know at all.
That's true.
I just said it.
That's embarrassing.
I was on the plane.
I put on my earphones.
I couldn't understand my voice.
That was embarrassing.
Right?
I was in the plane.
You can't hear the sound of the train.
And Ishikawa Hidemi-chan.
She came in suddenly.
When the train came in suddenly,
Ishikawa Hidemi-chan!
Ishikawa Hidemi-chan.
What is this?
That's me, but...
It was about 5 years ago.
That's right.
I was working in Tokyo.
When I came here,
I couldn't hear my own voice.
So I told the person next to me,
I'm Ishikawa Hidemiya.
I was going to say,
I couldn't hear my own voice.
That's embarrassing.
You have to be careful.
Let's move on to the postcards.
Please show us the postcards.
I can't laugh.
I don't like it.
Are you ready?
You don't have to say who it is.
I'm ready.
Let me introduce the postcards.
There are rumors about you.
That you're the Yakuza Akari.
You're an idiot!
That comment is a copy of your past.
I think you can understand that.
Why?
There are many people who think so.
That's not true.
What are you talking about?
I think you should quit.
You should quit being an amateur.
What are you talking about?
If an amateur comes out,
you'll get hit in the head.
What are you talking about?
You shouldn't talk like that.
You'll break the pot.
I won't hit the pot anymore.
I'll break the pot.
You shouldn't do that.
It's disgusting.
I'm just doing this for fun.
You shouldn't say,
That person in Osaka is Katsura.
There are rumors about you.
You'll get hit in the head.
You'll break the pot.
You'll have to keep saying that.
You should quit.
Don't say I have a bad mouth.
It's not a big deal.
Everyone in Osaka is like this.
That's not true. I'm not that kind of person.
Why?
It's because I'm a waki-jita.
You're a waki-jita?
I'm talking normally.
It's my fault.
Let's be a little more polite.
Can you say that?
You're a waki-jita.
And you like to make fun of me.
What are you talking about?
Why are you saying pan pan pan?
I don't understand.
Shut up.
Why are you saying pan pan pan?
What kind of sound is that?
Hey.
What?
What kind of sound is that?
I don't understand what you're saying.
I don't understand.
Get out of my way.
Pan pan pan.
What kind of sound is that?
I don't understand.
You're a waki-jita.
What kind of sound is that?
Next.
I'm looking forward to the future of Hamada Matsumoto.
How about a penalty game?
You just bit me.
Cupid 3 minutes cooking.
How about it?
It's good.
What kind of game is that?
How about a stopwatch game?
Really?
Yes.
It's good.
Do you still play Cupid 3 minutes cooking?
Yes, I do.
Really?
I like Cupid 3 minutes cooking.
You don't like it?
I like it.
I don't like it.
Really?
Yes.
You don't like it?
I don't like it.
To the girl who is everywhere,
you are going to cheat.
I'm really happy to see you like this.
I really like you.
Only you.
What is this?
I'm really happy to see you like this.
This is how you say, you know?
That's not how you say it.
I'm so happy that I can see each and every one of your letters.
Seriously.
You've never written a single letter back to me.
Don't say such bad things.
I'm telling the truth.
How much do I care about my fans?
I really want to do this and that for each and every one of them.
Who the hell did you leave your presents on the street in Minami, Osaka on Christmas day?
He's a terrible guy.
Look at my eyes.
Which one do you trust, me or him?
You.
You're the one who's holding it and hitting it down.
Don't say such stupid things.
Who did you imitate?
I didn't imitate anything.
You're so stupid.
Stop it.
I'm telling you to stop it.
Everyone knows that I'm kind.
Why?
What do you mean by kind?
I'm the one who has that kind of love.
Why?
Have you ever done anything kind?
Do you know why I'm working so hard?
I save up money to buy a house for kids.
There's no such thing as a house for kids.
On Christmas day, I always bring my kids to the park and play the guitar.
You're lying.
You don't even play the guitar.
I'm so angry.
Suddenly?
What kind of angry?
I'm shaking.
Kids are weak to shaking.
If I was an adult, I'd be able to walk properly.
But they can't walk at all.
Of course they can.
They have a different walking history.
We've been walking for 26 years.
But they're like this.
They're stupid.
What do you mean by stupid?
That's not enough.
They're like this.
They're so good.
I'm going to the toilet.
I'm going to the Japanese-style toilet.
I'm going to theく toilet.
I'm going to the q's toilet.
I'm going to the toilet.
This way.
Go down.
an irresistible
They have dirty everywhere.
I want to put my hands in dirty places.
They're remembered.
Trash!
We are still looking for a punishment game.
If you look at the post, the child's user is...
Hey!
You!
Don't use the public radio!
You're so mean!
You can say sorry!
You thought you were going to hit me, didn't you?
I did that, Yota!
I
don't know how to make a sound!
It would be fine!
Oh, MZ?
When you smell it, you can realize when you came back!
It goes like this.
So I wrap the tissue and use my fingers to scratch it.
It's dirty!
Are you a monster?
If you scratch it, it won't come out.
It will come out cleanly.
It will come out.
Really?
I don't know.
I don't know how to do it.
You can teach me how to do it, but it's difficult.
Right?
Yes.
By the way, it's called Ohira-Aki.
That's right.
It's a punishment game.
We're looking for various things.
That's right.
That's all for today.
Thank you very much.
How was the tricycle?
The tricycle?
Yes.
It was the first time.
It was hard.
It was a long distance.
My legs hurt.
Yes.
It was difficult.
When I came to the park, there was a slope.
The person who made it had a strange head.
I couldn't help it, so I found it.
I can't climb it.
You can't do that.
I prepared a lot of things.
Which one is the SM school you went to?
I'm an assistant.
I don't think it's funny.
What is this?
I'm getting angry.
If you accept it a little, you'll be in trouble.
This is a little strange.
You can't read the atmosphere.
How many times do you have to do this?
I don't know what to do.
What are you going to do next week?
I don't know, so I'll do it next week.
I'm going to get angry.
I prepared such a delicious ingredient.
Why can't I read it?
I can't sell it.
I'm an amateur.
I don't know what to do.
This is a person who wants to drink.
I say it every week.
I don't know what to do.
I'm thinking of a punishment game.
That's all for this time.
Goodbye.