In this season, I want to have a cool feeling.
But it's cold.
It's cold.
In a different sense, it's cool.
This is revolutionary.
I think it's the first time I've seen it on TV.
Let's do this cold thing.
Let's enjoy the cold thing.
Can you enjoy it?
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
Let's show you the cold thing.
It's the last one.
Go!
Are you ready?
It's cold.
I think he's a good actor.
From the previous season.
Is this your voice?
It's the same voice.
It's cold.
You can sing on TV.
It's time to say goodbye.
It's cold.
Are you still alive?
It's the best.
This is the last one.
This is a smart guy.
What are you talking about?
I don't know if you've forgotten the lines.
It's cold.
Don't you have to say it?
I don't have to say it.
If you say it, it's even colder.
I can't talk to you even if I say it.
In a sense, I'm a foreigner.
I can't communicate with you.
Really?
With this momentum.
Let's get cold.
The second person.
It's cold at this point.
Short story 1.
Ultraman.
Gaon.
It's a monster.
Somebody help me.
Ultraman.
Please.
Please defeat the monster.
Leave it to me.
Somebody help me.
It's cold.
It's not stable.
How many are you going to do?
Date.
I'm sorry.
He's late.
I've been waiting for him.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Did you get it?
Just a little.
You're late.
I'm sorry.
I've reserved a restaurant for you today.
Restaurant?
Yes.
Did you get it?
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
You got it, right?
Put your arms together.
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
Don't turn around.
I'm sorry.
You're not going anywhere.
Put your arms together.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Suzuki is very cold.
He came out and walked two steps.
He can't be that cold.
I don't think so.
He walked two steps.
He came out and walked two steps.
He can't be that cold.
The third song.
I'm sorry.
What is this?
He's laughing.
I didn't call you.
I'm sorry.
This is terrible.
There are good guys and bad guys.
It's not good to have a bad guy in the team.
That was a good call.
The cold wind.
A boy will be angry.
It's too cold.
Let's go.
Ready.
Yaaaaay!
I did it!
Here you go.
This is the last one.
The last one is...
The man who loves to catch mice.
The man who also breaks the spine of mice.
I can't do it!
Like this.
It's a tie.
Let's have him do this one.
Here we go.
The man who loves to catch mice.
Next, he opens his eyes.
I can't do it!
First of all...
This is a water from the east.
It's quite a big water.
In this water...
The carbonic acid is quite calm.
He puts his face in this water.
I can't do it!
He opens his eyes.
Let's have him do this one.
Please look closely.
Please open your eyes.
Thank you very much.
Next.
I can't do it!
This is a hose.
Please open your eyes.
Here we go.
He opens his eyes.
Next.
I can't do it!
It's my fault.
I can't do this anymore.
That was intense.
How was it?
It was really dangerous.
What was dangerous?
I was sucked into something.
Something important.
I understand.
Something important disappeared.
This is the last one.
Takasu Michio!
I can't do this.
I can't do this anymore.
I have to do something.
It's really cold.
Time is passing.
I can't do it anymore.
What is it, master?
It's not cold. It's fun!
Robo!
It's a kick!
It's not a punch, Robo!
I don't understand what you said.
Only I understand.
It's half broken.
Good!
Nice, Robo!
You ran away!
Thank you, Robo!
It's cold!
It's been an hour.
That's right.
That's what happened at the opening.
Yes, yes.
You can laugh.
Today's opening is terrible.
I ate forbidden fruit.
It's not good to do it on TV.
What should we do?
Everyone is watching Hamada.
Why?
I'm tired.
No, no, no.
No one is watching me.
Everyone is watching Hana Hosettan.
I used to watch Pink Lady on TV.
But now I only watch Mii-chan.
It's the same as that.
Only Mii-chan.
You only watch Mii-chan.
Everyone is watching Mii-chan.
What kind of Mii-chan did you watch?
I just happened to have it.
Don't say that.
I want to see Downtown.
I want to see Hamada in that word.
To be honest,
I'm not James Dean.
You.
I don't like your attitude.
The theme is Ryunaki Hanko.
I'm not going to win.
What?
I see.
It's still hot.
The other day I went to eat ramen.
I was a little annoyed.
I'm a bad guy in the world.
I know.
But even if you look at me like this,
I'm the most righteous person.
You may not see it,
but I wear a cape.
In my heart.
I always wear a cape.
I see.
I'm a cool guy.
Sometimes there are people in a line at a ramen shop.
I'm so angry.
I finished eating and I'm smoking.
I can't forgive those who talk.
Iater you care about me more.
This will become easier happen from now on.
I am forced to show my clause and Jayikawa related Eenie meenie minieligt.
I am forced to show my clause and Jayikawa related Eenie meenie minie ruin.
I am forced to show my clause and Jayikawa related Eenie meenie minie llike.
You can recognize mine too.
Wait a minute
You see, I'm more in favor of the girl asking Ai to stop eating ramen
Shay-in, who are you saying this about...
I'm really sorry
I'm just gonna ask
locking ears
Girls these days, they go determined to make Anti- ramen
There's not enough soup
Hey, I wasn't talking randomly
Can you ask my mom to tell them a different story?
You're going to make soup and noodles here, right?
And I'll add some green onions.
And you'll make ramen with just a bite.
This is...
Then you should eat Baby Star at home.
Baby Star is different.
When I entered the room, the seats were all full.
I was sitting down.
I was hungry but I couldn't stand up.
I said, please. I'll go out.
I couldn't believe I couldn't do that.
I didn't have a place to sit.
I finished eating a long time ago.
The color of the chopsticks has changed.
It's like this.
It was in front of me.
No one can see it.
I was looking at it while I was talking.
I don't know this.
If you're wearing a cape, you can't go.
I don't have a cape.
For example, when I'm in a car, I don't think it's bad to smoke.
You have a cigarette lighter.
When I have a lot of cigarettes.
I don't think it's bad manners.
My justice is a little distorted.
That's not good. Take off your cape.
That's not good.
I can burn with a cigarette lighter.
That's paper, so it goes back to the soil.
It depends on the place.
But I can't allow it to look like an empty can.
I drank a lot of juice.
Do you have an empty can?
I have it.
I thought it was a feather.
No.
You have one or two.
You have a lot of them.
I don't know that.
I don't smoke, but when I stop at a traffic light, I open it and put it down.
But that's...
What is that?
I do that sometimes.
It's not because the sound is noisy.
I know.
There are two big reasons why you shouldn't throw an empty can.
If you say it's dangerous, it's going to be trash.
Even if you put it down, it's going to be bad.
If it's allowed, it's the place where my old friend died on a motorcycle.
Is that so?
Don't drink it.
It's here.
Please also don't smoke.
Yuzo Kayama and Yuzo Matsumoto are good friends.
When summer vacation came, they often went to Hawaii to visit their family.
Please tell us how it was.
I know that very well.
Your dad and your friend went to a youth festival.
That's right.
I think it was at the Ereiki Youth Festival.
My father was an actor.
He was an actor.
What kind of actor?
Didn't I say this?
My father said, I'm a fake talent.
I'm a very thin fake talent.
What?
Where?
It's soft.
Don't say soft.
What's your name?
What?
I'm Matsumoto Joichi.
You didn't say your real name.
I don't know at all.
There's a video of you.
It says, Matsumoto Joichi, a newbie.
Because you're a debutant.
I don't know if that's true.
I feel like you're a newbie.
If it says, I'm a newbie.
At that time, my father went to an audition.
Since then, he's been on a lot of K-dramas and movies.
He told me to tell you about the villa in Hawaii.
What kind of villa was it?
What do you want me to say?
He told me about the villa in Kayama Yuzo.
Get out of here.
And?
The number of rooms is 26.
That's a lot.
That's right.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I'm trying to remember.
I'm sorry.
27?
It's the same as that. 26.
That's just an accordion.
That's not good.
How many rooms are there in the living room?
I think there were about 30.
30?
It was a big living room of about 30.
Big living room?
In that 30-story living room, my father and Kayama Yuzo had a fight.
What was the reason?
I think it was because of his chest hair.
He said something like, your chest hair is not funny.
Why is it not funny?
What did he say during the barbeque?
He put the sauce on the barbeque.
Well, it doesn't matter.
He was about to cry.
He put the sauce on the barbeque.
His wife came to him and said,
Excuse me, my daughter.
My father.
His name is Joichi.
He said, I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
What happened?
I don't want to say anything.
My Kayama is angry.
He went to my father.
When I looked at him from the window,
He was very close to me.
His upper body was naked.
Since then, you haven't been close to him?
I haven't been close to him since then.
It was so much fun.
Every New Year and summer vacation were the same.
Really?
He was wearing Mongolian clothes.
It's complicated.
When I was in kindergarten,
I told my parents,
Mongolian clothes are complicated.
Is it okay to wear Mongolian clothes?
When I was a college student,
I decided to have more than 100 secretaries.
Are you a high school graduate?
No, no, no.
I'm a high school graduate.
What university are you a high school graduate from?
Are you a high school graduate?
No, I'm not.
In Kansai,
I went to Kyodai University.
I'm a high school graduate.
What university do you go to?
One of the Business University of Kyoto.
You are very famous for becoming a director.
Very famous.
Most of my friends are high school graduates.
That's fine. Masumoto-san, you are a great actor.
Please teach me how to open the door when I have an interview.
Normally, you just open the door and say, excuse me.
I've never had an interview before.
You've never had an interview before?
No.
I'm amazing.
I always have a good reputation.
I've always been praised for being convincing.
Well, there's at least one company that has that reputation.
That's why I call it convincing.
I've been convinced.
No, no, no.
I can hear it when I go home.
So, I don't know if that's convincing or not.
There was a big company that said it was convincing.
That's what I'm talking about.
Bang!
Please teach me how to open the door.
An interview?
Yes.
Then, please come here.
Excuse me.
This is terrible.
It's like climbing a mountain.
Am I doing this?
I can't go in and do this.
I can see the camera.
I have to take a picture of the city.
What should I do?
Next person, please.
Wait, wait, wait.
It's closed now.
It's closed?
I have to do my best.
It's really good to do it naturally.
I'm dressed up.
I think it's best to do it naturally.
I was able to do it that way.
For example, you ask me to write something, right?
Yes, yes.
Please write it.
I don't usually write things like that.
I see.
What should I do?
I mean, really.
I don't care if it's like this.
Why are you sleeping?
Sometimes, like this.
I sometimes eat the skin here.
Even if you're told to eat it.
There are times when I want to eat it because it's sticking out here, right?
I usually do it with my mouth open, but I can't reach it.
I wish I could do that.
I want to see an old man wearing a suit over there.
I agree with that.