Before the recording, he is the only one who is not seen in the usual dressing room.
Excuse me.
Well, Mr. Yamazaki told me to bring everyone here.
Why?
I don't know.
It's a serious matter.
When did he say he would come?
Well, I don't know.
Let's just say that.
What's wrong with Mr. Yamazaki?
He seems to be depressed.
He can't be in the drama.
He can't be in Lee's Japan.
He seems to be thinking about something.
I don't think about it.
Do we have to bring everyone here?
Yes.
Where should we bring everyone?
Mr. Yamazaki is here.
I don't know.
We don't have to bring everyone here.
Can we bring Taro too?
Can we bring him too?
Yes.
Let's bring everyone here.
Excuse me.
It's a serious matter.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Excuse me.
This way.
Yes.
I'm really worried.
What's the matter?
Did something happen?
To be honest,
I'm an entertainer.
When I do various things,
there is a moment when God descends.
But God doesn't descend at all.
The God of laughter.
Only those who stepped into the world of laughter
experience the miracle of birth.
The moment when the God of laughter descends.
It seems that Yamazaki was separated from that God.
I used to be there.
For example, the Moriman battle.
In the Moriman battle,
the beer bottle was like this.
Do you remember the battle with Morio?
Even at that time,
I didn't think about anything.
The beer bottle flew away.
When I shook it up.
Yamazaki vs. Moriman beer bottle battle.
Yamazaki shook up the beer bottle
in the ring where the God of laughter descends.
The beer bottle went to the ring in front of the center.
The audience was caught in the water of laughter.
At that time,
the God of laughter certainly descended to Yamazaki.
A lot of such gods have descended.
If you think about it,
there were some in the past.
That's right.
That's enough.
I'm sorry.
Put the chairs here.
Wait a minute.
Komu.
Why do you call Komu Komu?
I don't understand.
Komu is a staff.
This.
Komu has the same taste.
Do you remember this?
Matsumoto-san.
At the time of the previous Giri.
At the end,
he really went up one step.
That's right.
That's the God who descended.
At the end of the last Giri,
the order came to Matsumoto.
It's amazing.
What is this?
And the last moment.
This is exactly the moment when the God of laughter descended.
That's it.
It's the greatest weapon that comedians need.
Shall I try it?
With this.
Look.
What are you looking at?
Naki-san.
I'm not looking.
No, no, no.
If the God descended,
he would have gone up one step.
If you say that in this country,
it would be one step.
Really.
That's right. You'd be surprised.
You'd be surprised, right?
Shall I try it again?
Yes.
Look.
What?
Well, it's nothing.
I see.
But, Yamazaki-san.
What's the probability?
There are many.
It's not a matter of probability.
Come on.
What?
Bring it to me.
There are many black keys.
There are many holes.
This is a little...
It's a little crazy.
That's right.
So, this is
wasabi Russian sushi.
I see.
There are many.
There are many wasabi.
Yes.
It's in here.
In here.
Only one?
Only one.
There is a lot of wasabi in here.
I don't know what it looks like.
You don't know what it looks like at all.
Yes.
Right?
I'll try it.
Yes.
That's right.
If the God descended.
You can react immediately.
That's right.
Yes.
It's good.
What?
It's funny.
Is it really good?
It's not funny.
Don't be angry.
No, no, no.
But...
I'm sure that
there is one here.
No, no, no.
That's Yamazaki.
There is one here.
It's difficult.
In the past.
After all.
So, in the past,
I was definitely
doing wasabi.
Even if I didn't do it,
something happened.
Yes.
I was definitely laughing.
Come on.
What?
What is this?
Ah.
This is probably
Yes.
1 in 2.
It's 50%.
It's either.
Yes.
This is.
I'll choose this.
I don't know what it looks like at all.
I don't know at all.
I really don't know.
It hurts.
Ah.
Here?
Wow.
It's disgusting.
Wait a minute.
I thought it was fun.
Well, well.
Well, well, well.
Even if we do it,
I don't know.
No, no, no.
I'm definitely going to go to Nikon
with wasabi.
Definitely.
It's history of comedy.
Well, there's even edit this and that,
You know?
Because there are other things.
I'd like to flee to Nagata.
I think it's all real.
But.
Hey,
When I was a kid,
If I didn't feel like thisWho caught.
No, it's
I'm just saying in style.
I don't feel like this in the past.
Don't care about comedy show.
I can't even think about it now!
Is that what you're thinking?
I thought you were going to say it later
I thought about it too much
What is it this time?
You know this, right?
The zoo
I thought about it, but
I'll just open it up
and say, I'm going to buy this animal!
I'll point at it like this
Right?
In the past, it was a really good animal
It was an interesting animal
It was
Let's do it
I'm going to do it
Right now
I'm going to buy this!
Where's the character?
It's the eyes
The eyes of the fox
The four foxes
Don't you know what that means?
I don't know
It's a bit too much
Please try it
It's too negative
I'll try it
I've been buying it for about two months
It's hard to feed it
It's this
It's the earth!
It's hard to feed it
I'm going to buy it in Africa
Right?
If it was me
It would be like this
Right?
I'm going to the earth
I've been buying it for about two months
It's hard to feed it
In Africa
It's okay
Don't worry about it
I have something to say
Wait a minute
What is it?
Look
It's magic
Out of the three
I can't draw only one
I see
I'm going to do magic
I'm going to draw a beard
I can't draw only one
Right?
It's more likely than before
I'm going to draw
Please
Bring me a mirror
Did you say mirror?
What?
Did you draw it?
Did you succeed?
It's funny
What?
It's not funny at all
To be honest
I wanted to draw something that I can't draw
That's right
According to the theory
There are a lot of people who can't draw
But
Why can't you draw?
I get angry and laugh
It's a pattern
Did you draw it now?
I wanted to draw a beard
You took off your hair too much
I'm sorry
What is it?
I drew it
Crab
Put it between the nose
If the crab put it between the nose
It will be good
I'll try
Oops
I'm looking forward to this
It's like this
I didn't expect it
It looks good
It looks really good
Ouch
It looks good
What is it?
It hurts
I think I can do it
Please do your best
Ouch
It's coming
It's good
It's funny
It would be good if you put wasabi here
It's delicious
Crab wasabi
It was delicious
I can't help it
Is it okay?
For the time being
Wait a minute
It looks good
Crab
Fujiwara was funny
It's stuck
This is interesting
This
I don't know which one has power
I see
I'll set it up
I'll choose from these three
It's a vacuum cleaner
Put it here
What are you doing?
It's amazing
Which one?
It's in the middle
Put it down
Hurry up
One
Put it all down
Put it down
It's dangerous
I put it all down
Put it up
It's happening
It's interesting
If it's wasabi
It's amazing
Is there more?
What is it?
It's a lot
You know this
You know
I have scissors
In this
Only one will fall
I'll go
I'll go in the middle
No
It's okay
I'll go
Sushi
I'll try
Let's do it again
There are four more
I'll choose
I'll eat it
Let's do it again
It's okay
It's one of the three
I think you can do it
It's okay
It doesn't matter
It was this
I thought it would be this
You can't do it
Let's do it outside
Why?
If you're a comedy god
You can't come in
You're saying amazing things
I don't think so
I usually eat in the studio
You can't come in
Sushi
There's nothing
Even a kid who likes to play
Can't come to the park
You know
Even the god of weather
Is allowed to come
I'm talking but the train is running
You
You can't hear me
There are buttons from 1 to 10
And
One of the buttons
Is connected here
Fireworks are coming out
It's interesting
If you put it down
You'll know
What happens when you put it down
It's like a black beard
That's why it's a black beard
Monkey
I didn't think of it
If it blows
Please come in
Sushi
Let's bring it
Let's go
From 1 to 10
First
Let's go to 8
Please
Right?
It's difficult
But the god
Is watching
Really?
If it comes in the first time
It means the god came
But if it comes in the last time
It's amazing
I see
Let's take it
8 is no good
Let's go to 4
It came
Sorry
Are you okay?
It came
It came here
Let's go back
What's this?
What's next?
It's like a crab
I don't have it
This
I like it
It's in the water
In the end
The god
It's in the water
I see
This
What's this?
It's two
One has
A goldfish
And the other one
Has a snake
That's scary
But
You know
I know
We've done a lot
But this is the last
Let's do it
Will Yamazaki
Be able to catch the snake?
Hello
He's laughing
It's his feeling
How is it?
It's good
It's the last
Let's go
It's coming
Please do it again
Hello
I said
I'm very thankful for the support
But I think I'm going to die
He came out again
From a sad story
It's coming
Ah
That's when you entered the show
There's drama
Yes
When you're shooting
Why do you think that?
You look very tired
Everyone does
I don't work out
I got muscle pain
It's strange
You're fine
No, no, I don't want to say it too much.
It's just that, you know, even if there's a lot of customers, it's like that.
What's so strange about it?
Overall, it's strange.
Overall, there's nothing wrong about it.
I don't get it.
Please come.
No, no, if it's open, I'll come.
Even if I die, everyone will come, right?
Even if you say it like that.
No, that's because everyone's on a schedule.
Ah, so that's why you're wearing a mask now.
But I can't get out of this.
Why not?
I'll come.
Bring some okaki, really.
I'm sorry.
Okaki and Hanataba.
Eh? Okaki?
Okaki.
Hard okaki and Hanataba.
Thank you very much.
Even though I didn't eat it.
Matsumoto-san, who is a beginner in the Japanese Tank Top League.
At this time, even if you're walking around with a tank top on, please tell me a way that people won't think that you're running away.
This is because, even now, everyone, you know...
Even now, girls, even in winter, their shoulders are out.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Recently, summer and winter have disappeared.
I see.
Yes.
Well, that doesn't really matter.
Well, yes.
But, well, there's a way. There's a way to say it in a way that's not rude.
A way to say it?
A woman is like a clash between jealousy and jealousy, right?
Like, I don't like that girl.
A man is rather casual, but a woman is like, I don't like that girl.
A woman who's a little popular is jealous.
I see.
A woman is like, I'm inviting a man who's rude.
Like that, right away.
A woman is scary.
Yes.
A woman will resent you.
No, no.
Ah, yes, yes.
That's why, you know, tank tops.
Yes.
Tank tops or anything is fine.
When you wear something like that, you add a little something to it.
Ah, she's not such a bad girl.
For example, when you wear a jacket like this, and when you meet at a cafe, when you take it off, your shoulders pop out.
At that time, you're in trouble, you're short of sleeves.
That's right.
You're short of sleeves.
Because of that, this girl might become a best friend.
What?
She might become a best friend?
Yes.
A lifelong best friend.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.