After this, let's go to downtown Gakinosukai!
Let's watch TV as well!
Good evening.
Today is the opening.
It's a little different from usual.
In the past, when we were in Oogiri,
Mr. Uchida came.
Our manager had been doing it for 4 years.
He had been doing it.
In fact, on April 1st,
he was ordered to leave.
He was told to go to the Nagoya office.
We left and went to Nagoya.
The man in charge of the Nagoya office,
Mr. Takeuchi,
was also working there.
Yes, that's right.
Takeuchi went to Nagoya to work.
He said, can't we work together?
That's how this story began.
He was told to leave.
It's been 4 years.
We have to do it properly.
We, including the staff,
want to celebrate
the farewell
of the Gakinosukai-style band.
We want to sing a farewell song.
That's right.
Finally, this day has come.
It seems like a sad and happy day.
Don't say that.
If you don't get angry,
there's nothing I can do.
Excuse me.
Thank you for taking care of me for a long time.
I'm going to travel to Nagoya.
Dad.
Yes.
Say something.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Say thank you to your dad.
Thank you for everything.
Thank you very much.
Dad.
Yes.
Say something.
Just be careful with the water.
It's beautiful,
isn't it, dad?
Yes.
Who's going to return it to me?
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Don't say that.
Thank you for waiting.
The bride and groom
have arrived.
Congratulations.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Stop it.
Why?
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Don't say bad things.
Stop it.
Congratulations.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Stop it.
Congratulations.
Let's have a toast.
The composer of the Japanese TV program,
Mr. Kenji Tsugawa.
Let's have a toast.
Cheers.
Congratulations.
Let's have a toast.
Cheers.
Takeuchi, I'm counting on you.
I'll be happy.
Be happy.
You have to do it well.
I'm hungry.
Don't say that.
I'm not that kind of kid.
I'll give you some food.
I'm sorry.
Congratulations.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Stop it.
Your underwear is visible.
Have a good day.
Go home.
Go home together.
Cheers.
Mr. Tsugawa, I'm counting on you.
I'm counting on you.
Cheers.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
It's cold.
Father, mother.
Atsuo's small chest is full of expectations and anxiety.
Atsuo was happy because he was always surrounded by love.
Atsuo is forever a child of father and mother.
Please don't cry and send Atsuo out.
I'm relieved.
I want to have a child again.
Hello.
It's over today.
It was a little late to start.
It was late to start.
Shut up.
If you haven't seen the opening today, you'll know.
We've been apart for four years.
It was terrible at first.
I don't remember anything.
No way.
At first, he didn't know what to do.
He didn't know how to be a manager, so he was standing next to me.
I can't forget it.
I was in Osaka and came to Tokyo.
I had a job in Tokyo.
I didn't know the staff in Tokyo.
I didn't know what downtown was like.
I was sitting in the middle of a similar aura.
You go over there.
I was told that, but I gradually thought it was three people.
It's okay.
He went to the Nagoya office in Yoshimoto.
He came to Okamoto.
He's a little weird.
He has a crybaby.
He cut a cigarette.
He said,
He came back in 15 minutes.
I don't have it.
I don't have a Marlboro light.
If I don't have it, I don't have it.
I don't know why he came here.
I don't know why.
I said, come here.
He said, hold on a second.
I said, just go.
He said, Mr. Hamada, shouldn't you go home?
What? Really?
What do you think?
I remembered something.
Nitta is really tough.
Really?
Long time ago, he used to drink a lot.
He was so strong.
He went to a tea house in Kyoto.
He drank a lot.
When I was in a taxi with him,
from Kyoto to Osaka,
I said, I'm sorry, please stop.
Please stop.
He stopped.
The door didn't open, but he opened the door.
Then he went out.
Please go.
Please stop.
He repeated that.
He didn't look at me.
Are we looking for a blue bird?
No, really.
First of all,
do you believe in supernatural powers?
I don't know.
Actually, I do.
What?
I believe in supernatural powers.
I can see the other side of the wall.
No, really.
The other side?
What?
I can see the other side of the wall.
What are you talking about?
What?
I think Tsuttsun is preparing a letter.
Really?
Right?
I know.
Tsuttsun must have a letter.
Right?
I know.
Since there was something going on,
I went up to the top of the post
and spيت on Tsuttsun's body.
Tsuttsun's body made a house.
No, no.
I went up to the top of his body.
I really don't believe it.
Why?
There really is no such thing.
You try it like this.
I'll go somewhere and see.
You'll definitely feel something.
Write that down.
I got it.
When you feel something, write it down.
I'll go somewhere and see.
It's like saying you'll go somewhere and see.
There's something there.
Write it down!
What are you doing?
Hurry up and do it!
I'm being told to hurry up and do it!
I can't do it!
You don't have the concentration.
The person who does it and the person who gets hit shouldn't be able to concentrate.
Look!
This!
What?
You idiot!
There really is something.
You're an idiot.
Is that so?
Everyone watching this on TV, try it on the train.
You'll definitely feel it.
When I was in middle school,
the old man who used to be a salaryman,
he did it like this.
He said,
I'll definitely do it like that.
Really?
If you don't do it, you'll definitely get hit.
Is that so?
Really, really.
For example, if the people watching this do it,
you can go home and think about it.
If you do it like Mach-chan said,
it'll be like this.
Then you'll have to think about it again.
No, it's really not like that.
Well, that's fine, but...
I don't have a spiritual sense.
What? Ah, spiritual sense.
I'm a sadist.
You're a sadist.
I don't have a spiritual sense.
Why?
Are you sleeping properly?
I'm not sleeping.
When I sleep,
I always sleep like this,
as long as I have a spiritual sense.
So when I'm really tired,
I think,
I might have a spiritual sense today,
I'll definitely sleep like this.
It's strange, isn't it?
Why did you become a sadist when you were like this?
If you're like this,
don't you tie up your spiritual sense?
I don't tie up my spiritual sense.
It's scary, isn't it?
It's scary, it's scary, it's scary.
If you look at yourself in the bathroom,
you're a real sadist.
In the bathroom?
That's why I told you not to turn around,
but when I'm in the bathroom,
I always turn around like this.
I'll go down, I'll go down.
That's this, isn't it?
No, it's not.
It's not like that normally.
Like this, like this,
do you go out like this?
Do you go out like this?
I don't go out.
When I'm done, I go out like this.
What do you mean?
There's something like this.
What?
The toilet seat.
Yes, yes, yes.
And when you're done, you go out like this?
I go out like this.
There's something like this.
When you're done,
when you're like this,
you look back.
When I go in,
I suddenly look back.
I can't open the toilet like this.
What?
No, when I go to the bathroom,
I go like this.
What?
When I'm like this,
I go like this.
do you go out like this?
Yes, yes, yes.
Don't you forget how to do this?
You've been doing this for a long time.
There's something like this.
Yes, there is.
Occasionally.
Yes.
There are times when you go out like this.
It's strange.
It's always like this.
Is the toilet in middle school like this?
That's right.
Oh, it's wrapped.
Don't wrap it.
Wait for the toilet.
The toilet paper is here.
Seriously, seriously, seriously.
Why is your head like that?
I failed.
Hello.
I fell in love with the toilet paper at first sight.
That's a lie.
I can't live without the toilet paper.
Does the toilet paper have a girlfriend?
What kind of food do you like?
Please tell me more about the toilet paper.
Please.
What about the toilet paper?
Does it have a girlfriend?
I'm in Tokyo right now,
so I don't have a girlfriend.
Oh.
Did you have a girlfriend when you were in Osaka?
I had a girlfriend when I was in Osaka.
I didn't have a girlfriend when I came to Japan.
Oh, a little while ago.
Yes.
How did you know?
Well, there were a lot of fights.
There were a lot of situations.
What's wrong with you?
What are you trying to change?
It's wrapped, but it's in front of a man.
Oh, is that so?
It's like this.
You look like you made it with a pine tree.
Yes, thank you.
Oh, is that so?
Well, I'm glad that this kind of thing is coming.
Well, it's still one.
I have a question for the downtown officer.
I saw someone stealing gasoline at the parking lot the other day.
What should I have done at that time?
Keep it quiet.
You can't do that.
How can you treat a criminal like that on TV?
It's bitter.
What are you doing?
Well, that's true.
I used to have a dog.
It barks.
At that time, I had a brother and a father.
I was the only man.
Bang, bang, bang.
A dog was crying.
And the dog is crying.
Who is it?
I don't know.
Akiko?
I'm scared.
You don't have to say it twice.
It's been a long time since I've seen a dog crying.
I want to see it.
Well, I have to show you what I did there.
That's right.
I'm the only man.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Well, I'm the only man.
That's enough.
I'm the only man.
If you open the window of the toilet, you can see the dog.
If you open the door, a scary man is peeing on the dog.
The dog is crazy.
It's a poor dog.
It's a scary man.
What are you doing?
I'm peeing on the dog.
I opened the door and peed on the dog.
I was scared.
I closed the door.
Nothing happened.
Nothing happened to the dog?
Nothing happened to the dog.
It's okay, it's okay.
I want you to take the dog for a walk.
I see.
But the dog ran away.
In that situation, I can't say anything.
You should talk to the dog.
Last week, the dog was on vacation.
Yes.
Last week, Yamazaki and I were on vacation.
It was very cold.
I was waiting for the dog to be on vacation.
I see.
Then, Yamazaki ran away.
After a while, I ran around Shinjuku.
Did you run out of gas?
No, I ran out of gas.
You are not good at running.
Why didn't you check the gas?
It's cold.
It's very cold.
Then, Yamazaki caught a taxi and went to the gas station.
The gas was frozen and I couldn't go home.
While I was going to Yamazaki, it was very cold.
I couldn't wear a heater.
It was snowing.
About 30 minutes later, I came back to Yamazaki.
The gas station clerk said.
That facility cracked.
The subscriber went to Yamazaki?
He was very angry.
He is crazy.
He is insane.
He practicing his Squatch skill.
Is he insane?
He is very crazy.
The subscriber was very angry.
He was crazy.
When he was operating on his looking.
I'm a cat!
That's right!
What am I supposed to do?
What are you saying? You're a cat!
You're making it sound like I'm saying it?
I'm making it sound like I'm saying it!
Ah, really?
I'm drooling!
And my nose is running too
I'm like, kachakachaa! But it's completely unresponsive
That's right
Even though it's cold, I open it and
I like the nozzle so
How do you say it? The place where you put the gasoline
It doesn't go in that easily
It goes in like this
It's convenient
I see
It doesn't go in
It's really stupid
What should I do with this store?
It's easy to scratch, but it's like this on the side
It's fun!
Yamaguchi is saying something great!
Momoko, go over there!
What should I do with this?
Yamaguchi said, go borrow something
It's like an udon restaurant
If you go there, there won't be anything
The old man there is doing a good job
But he doesn't feel like he's done anything
He doesn't have anything
Yamazaki, go borrow a donburi bowl!
He's putting it in the donburi bowl
He's putting it in the bowl
He's saying, that's enough
And then he's like, is there anything else?
And then Yamazaki puts out something new
Something evil
He came out with a beer bottle.
I said, I don't know anything about machines.
He said, if you wash it once, it will explode.
I said, it will, right?
He said, it won't.
It won't explode.
But he didn't care about it.
He put it in the beer bottle, and it exploded again.
He did it again.
It went in.
It was a huge success.
He told me to return the bottle.
I had to return it.
I see.
I had a fever at that time.
I couldn't bear it.
I had to return it.
I had a fever at that time.
I didn't have enough gasoline.
I had to return the bottle.
The gas tank was empty.
I didn't have enough gas.
I pushed the gas tank.
It exploded.
It was strange.
You were saying,
I was saying,
Who did I say?
Is that what you call a disaster?