Gaki no Tsukai Daishinrenkai has arrived!
This is the 13th Gaki no Tsukai event!
Let's go and celebrate the year 2002!
Daishinrenkai!
This year, I, Jr., will also be born.
Happy, Lucky, Ash, and Rush!
Captain! I'm counting on you!
Why are you counting on us?
We've been laughing at each other for a while now.
Captain!
We have a special guest this time.
First, we have Yoshimoto Kitte's dekoboko duo, Ameagari Kesshita!
Next, we have Yamashita-san, who will be chosen for the Hanayakusen this year!
Thank you!
Yamashita-kun!
Next, we have a mascot girl from Gaki no Tsukai Arahen this year!
Thank you!
Yoshimoto's back-up boss, Yamada-san!
Is it Yoshimoto?
It's Yoshimoto, right?
No, it's not.
It's Yamada tonight!
Don't make me say anything other than it's Yamada tonight!
I thought you'd definitely say it's Yamada tonight!
You have to say it right now!
Next, we have the mascot boy of this show, Downtown!
Please come forward, mascot boy.
Don't tell me the mascot boy isn't Shinji?
Now, we have the evil Kizuchi.
I don't understand what you're saying.
Now, let's be quiet.
Let's be quiet, you two.
Don't make a mess.
Let's be quiet in front of the mirror.
Now, please give us the award.
Ready, set, go!
Thank you!
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Gaki no Tsukai's New Year's Eve party!
Luxurious food and delicious alcohol.
Everyone is celebrating the New Year's Eve party and having a good time.
Everyone, look at this.
He's drinking our Chawanmushi.
Excuse me, can I have some Chawanmushi, please?
Can I have some of yours, too?
I like sake.
Can I have some Chawanmushi, please?
And some sake, too?
And some wine, too.
Wine?
Wine.
This is Chawanmushi, isn't it?
Is there such a thing as wine?
It's an English word.
An English word?
You know what I mean, right?
I've never heard of it.
Why don't you use it, Yamashita?
Chawanmushi is wine.
What are you talking about?
Wine.
I'm turning it around.
No, it's really wine now.
No, it's not.
Why are you looking at me like that?
You're sweating so much.
You're trying to look good.
I'm not sweating like I sweat in sports.
I'm sweating so much.
That's why I said that.
It's like Choshu.
It's sweating like Choshu.
It's like we're on American TV.
It's coming.
I'm going to turn it around right away.
I can't hear you.
What are you talking about?
Stop laughing.
I've been watching you.
Last year, we did something like Lee Japan.
We did it.
We did Kohaku.
It's a different genre.
We did something like Lee Japan.
I'm going to turn it around.
I'm going to do my best.
Don't look at me like that.
Don't make him worried.
Why are you looking at me like that?
This year, we're going to do something like Lee Japan.
I'm going to do my best.
Don't look at me like that.
Why are you looking at me like that?
The 4th 2002 Hatsuharai Manzai University.
First, we're going to draw a number.
If you get it wrong this time, you're out.
Don't put it in.
Don't say you don't like this guy.
Absolutely not.
If you say that, everyone won't like it.
Manzai University's new year's project.
5 teams were selected from 25 talent staff.
It's a test of luck.
The fate is in this triangle.
Did you say it?
I have it.
I'm going to draw the first one.
Number 12.
Who is it?
Isn't it Zaki?
That's right.
Thank you, God.
I'd like to decide on my partner.
Number 23.
Who is it?
Next, the second team.
Number 5.
Who is it?
It's me.
Tanaka.
Tanaka's partner.
Number 11.
Who is it?
It's me.
This is a strange feeling.
The third team.
The first team to be selected is Yamaya.
His partner is...
Director Sakamoto.
The fourth team is this person.
And his partner is...
Number 1.
It's the same as last year.
Endo again?
It's dirty.
The fourth team is Torio.
There are three people left.
This is a lie.
The first person is Torio.
The second person is Hotohara.
Who is it?
Number 9.
It's me.
Yamashita.
Wait a minute.
If you come here, God will come down.
God can't come down on stage.
If you come here, God will come down on stage.
Who is it?
Who will be the last person?
Come here.
Who is it?
Number 15.
It's me.
It's a lie.
Wait a minute.
Who is it?
It's a lie.
No one knows who is number 15.
No one knows I'm number 25.
The first team is Yamasaki.
The fifth team is Torio.
The sixth team is making up a story.
What kind of story will be completed?
It's perfect.
Let's get started.
The first team is Hamada and Endo.
The theme is giving birth.
Congratulations.
I'm Ichiro.
I'm Shinjo.
We are the two of us.
Last year, there were a lot of happy things.
Everyone in the entertainment world was surprised.
Her name is Kokomi.
Her name is Yamachan.
Her name is Zaki.
She is about to give birth.
You will have a lot of memories if you get married and give birth.
I will do my best.
The recent generation has changed a lot.
Husbands have to meet.
I will study hard.
Thank you.
Wife, are you okay?
Wait a minute.
Don't tease me.
Husbands are just watching.
We are the major leaders.
What has changed?
Husbands have to meet.
The moment of giving birth is in the video.
Video shooting is important.
You were born like this after you were born.
It will be a good memory.
Let's do it.
Wife.
I can see you.
Are you going to give birth?
I'm going to give birth.
You were born like this after you were born.
We are the major leaders.
Thank you very much.
How was it?
You are good.
The two teams are Tanaka and Miyasako.
The topic is the secret of Chihiro Sento.
Let's do it.
Hello.
We are the secret of Chihiro Sento.
How was it?
There were a lot of movies last year.
Is there a movie that left a good impression on you?
There was a movie of Hayao Miyazaki.
I can't remember.
I remember.
The secret of Chihiro Sento.
You did it.
You are the best.
Did you know about the movie?
The movie that surpasses Titanic.
I can't forgive you.
What do you mean?
You can't surpass the movie.
Because it surpasses Titanic.
I can't.
I can't forgive you.
What?
I can't.
Stop it.
You have to start the movie.
Do you want me to start the movie?
Of course.
Do you want me to forgive you?
Give me that.
No.
Don't touch it.
Don't do it.
Do not touch it.
I'll start the movie.
I'll tell you something.
What do you like about Miyazaki Hayao's movies?
I love Laputa!
That's not true!
I love Nausicaa the most!
It's definitely Laputa!
Hayao's movies are all about Nausicaa!
It's all about Laputa!
It's all about Nausicaa!
I can't do any more comics!
Please cheer up a little!
Do you want me to cheer you up?
Of course!
Then give it to me this time!
No! Everyone's watching!
Wait a minute!
Give it to me!
I'll hold it in for now!
I got it!
You know what?
What is it?
There's actually a second edition of Sen and Chihiro's Kamikakushi!
Really?
The title is already decided!
What is it?
Sen Masao's Kinkakushi!
Sen and Chihiro's Kamikakushi?
Sen Masao's Kinkakushi?
Say it!
I've had enough!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
I'm sure they're talking right now!
That's right!
Because I'm an idiot!
You're an idiot!
Yeah!
Bye-bye!
That's right!
Thank you very much!
Why do you all want to see the end of the story?
It's not over yet!
The third group is...
Yes!
Yamazaki Hosei and...
Komurasaki!
Yes!
The theme is Kouhaku Uta Gassen!
Well then!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
It's a bath!
It's a toilet!
Let's shake it together!
One, two!
Life!
You're doing it wrong!
It's a bath!
What's that?
You're doing it wrong!
Who's doing it wrong?
I'm doing it wrong!
You're doing it wrong!
Do it again!
Thank you very much!
It's a bath!
It's a toilet!
Let's shake it together!
One, two!
Life!
You're doing it wrong!
It's a bath!
Who's doing it wrong?
I got it!
I get it!
What did you watch at the end of the year?
What did you watch?
I watched Kouhaku Uta Gassen at home with my family.
I also watched Kouhaku Uta Gassen!
Did you watch Kouhaku Uta Gassen?
I watched Kouhaku Uta Gassen.
You shouldn't have watched it either.
That's right.
Don't say it so casually!
There's a tomorrow.
Let's sing it.
Shall we sing?
Let's sing.
I'll do the bath.
Everyone, please look forward to it.
Look forward to it.
It's like this.
Please.
Look forward to it.
Let's go.
Next is the face vacuum.
Wait!
What's wrong?
Hamada-san, look down!
Don't look down!
It's not the time to practice.
Thank you very much.
The topic is the Koizumi Prize.
I will change the Japanese from now on.
First of all, as the founder of the Dozo reform.
This is called the cake recovery in the world.
It's a cake.
This is the sound.
The voice is coming out.
Matsumoto-san, Hotaura-san, and Yamashita-san.
The topic is Hawaii travel.
Please.
Hello.
This is Spaghetti.
This is Spaghetti's Nakori-san.
This is Carbonara.
This is Donbe.
This is Spaghetti.
This is hard.
What are you looking at?
There's something in the middle of my face.
What?
There's something in the middle of your face.
That's a nose.
This is a big nose.
This is a small nose.
What are you doing?
What are you doing this New Year's Day?
Can I ask you a good question?
As you can see, my face is sunburned.
I was making mochi at home.
I'm just repeating it.
You don't have to say that.
If you say that, did you go somewhere?
I didn't go anywhere.
I went to Waiha.
What do you mean?
I don't like it.
You went to Hawaii.
I went to Hawaii.
It's different from Japan.
Japan is calm.
Hawaii is very quiet.
The clear sky.
The wind is blowing.
That's right.
I want to go to Hawaii, but I'm not good at English.
You can't speak English in an international society.
It's embarrassing.
If you go to Hawaii and say you're looking forward to it, you'll get a beating.
And I'll get a beating.
That's cool.
Did you teach me?
Really?
Come on, come on.
Come here, come here.
One more, one more.
I'll do my best.
Come on.
Nice, nice.
What do you mean?
Did I do something wrong?
That's not it.
What's in your nose?
It's in the middle of your face.
I've been waiting for you for a long time.
It's in the middle of your nose.
Thank you very much.
It was really an accident.
It was an accident?
It was a runaway.