If you think it was funny, please send me a postcard.
I don't think there are many people.
I'm interested in this kind of sight.
Today, we are going to Aoyama for the first time.
Yes.
It's cold today.
It's cold, isn't it?
I think it's getting in the way of the sound of the waves.
What?
Let's go home because it's fun.
Taxi!
I'm going home today.
How was it?
Taxi!
It's getting in the way.
I want to go home.
Today, we're going to the showroom.
Down, down, down.
I don't know where the kids are.
Yes.
I wonder if anything's changed.
This is...
What?
This is still...
Don't touch the prototype.
It's annoying.
What do you mean, don't touch it?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
We have to line up again.
That's right.
Today, we're going to the showroom.
Down, down, down.
I don't know where the kids are.
Let's go.
It's hard.
This is hard.
The taxi's stuck.
Let's go.
I'm going home.
See you tomorrow.
This program is brought to you by Sunluck, Oyama International Products, and the following sponsors.
Thank you for coming.
Today, we have a lot of things to tell you.
What do you mean?
Well, I don't know if anyone's seen this, but someone said they saw the Zoom-in morning.
Let's see if anyone's seen it.
Well, I don't know if anyone's seen it.
I saw the first episode.
The first episode.
I shot the bird in the downtown of the 29th district.
At that time, you said,
Well, which one of us is going to win?
Let's guess.
At the 29th stage.
That's right.
I said red.
You said white.
Yes.
What if you lose?
That's right.
Let's bet.
Yes.
If you lose,
Oh, it's a little down.
Yeah.
It's a little ahead.
Oh, I'm sorry.
If you lose,
Zoom-in morning.
What if I lose?
No, it's not.
It's going down.
I'm the Shina Beach Shogun behind you.
That's right.
I was dressed like I didn't know what was going on.
You dressed up as Garara Nyororo.
That's right.
I'm going to do this behind you.
Well, in the end, at the 29th stage, it was red and white.
That's right.
Well, it's decided on the 31st.
Well, at that stage, red won.
That's right.
Well, the 29th was shot on air on the 16th.
And then at the end, let's meet in five hours.
On the morning of the 17th, the day after the broadcast,
I promised to come out on Zoom-in on the morning of the next day.
You came out on the 17th.
Yes.
Zoom-in morning.
That's right.
It was hard for me.
Well, I told you.
Yeah.
I don't know how the general public sees it, but what was interesting to me was that the general public was behind me.
There were a lot of amateur customers.
Wait a minute.
Were you watching TV?
Watching?
You woke me up on the phone.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
I'm the one who says you.
You!
You hung up on me at about 6 or 5 o'clock.
I'm going to be on TV now.
You're so annoying.
Well, I felt nervous when I first appeared on TV.
There was something I saw.
I was sleeping.
I was sleeping, and the whole thing changed.
What was interesting?
So, there was an amateur here, and Mr. Tome was in front of me, right?
And you were standing at the very end.
Yes, yes, yes.
With a lot of garala.
Yes.
That's interesting, but it was a drawing.
So, Mr. Tome wasn't up.
It was a little far away.
It was taken from a distance, so the whole thing was reflected.
Yes.
At that time, the garala was a number.
Mr. Matsumoto was wearing garala make-up and waiting for the ball.
And then, as if the ball had come, the guy who had been doing this until now was waiting for the ball.
That was so funny.
That was funny, too.
I was sleepy, but when I saw that, I laughed a lot in the morning.
This is very popular.
I've seen it.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
But people who haven't seen this program.
This program is only in the Tokyo area, isn't it?
Yes, yes, yes.
I know a lot of garalas in the area, but people who don't know this program.
What the hell is this guy doing?
I happened to see it on Zoom.
I was sleeping.
What is it?
Yes, yes, yes.
I also had an opinion that I thought.
It was early in the morning for me.
It was early in the morning.
And that night.
That night, I was taking care of the baby next week.
Yes, yes, yes.
I was told that I shouldn't let him sleep.
If I return him to his house?
If I return him to his house, he'll never come.
He won't come to the office at 6 o'clock.
Yes, yes, yes.
And he won't let me go.
He won't return me.
I was dragged around in various places.
Three men and three staff members.
I had to kill some time by 6 o'clock.
I had to do something.
Suddenly, the men started playing baseball.
It was a free time.
There was still plenty of time.
There was nothing to do, so we played baseball.
Men and men.
Only three men.
There was a woman.
It was a baseball game.
We started playing baseball.
We were dragged around in various places.
Yes, yes, yes.
We only played with three men.
The woman just watched.
She said it was embarrassing.
That's right.
If you play baseball and lose, you have to take it off.
Yes, yes, yes.
We were dragged around in various places.
We played baseball in reverse.
In the end, only men.
Three men and three staff members.
If you do this, no matter how many women you have,
Come on now.
You guys lost now.
We're wearing kitchen clothes.
Yes, yes, yes.
We're wearing only one pair of pants.
I said, isn't it?
I understood.
I was almost cut in half.
It's a reverse cut.
If you do this, the woman will be in a bad mood again.
Like a clock.
Earrings.
Yes, yes, yes.
Fingers.
In the end, I thought three men and three staff members were dead.
I dug it out.
I said, wow.
I thought I'd take the woman off the horse.
When I looked at it, it was already six o'clock.
I said, I can't fly.
I went to the apartment.
I went without anything.
Yes, yes, yes.
I arrived at the Zoom-in morning.
It was that morning.
I was tired.
I was really tired at that time.
I used up all my power in baseball.
I met Mr. Tome in the morning.
Really?
Yes.
After make-up?
Yes, yes, yes.
When I went there without anything, I thought it was a really strange guy.
I've been saying this for a while.
Mr. Tome said, I understand.
When I opened the lid, Mr. Tome was a little angry.
But when I said Zoom-in, Mr. Tome was half laughing.
Because it's a little bit behind.
Is that so?
Zoom-in.
I saw it now.
If you look at it again, you may not be able to laugh.
Certainly, it was a little bit up here.
I don't think everyone will be convinced just by this story.
Mr. Wada brought a camera from the sea that night.
I was able to do it.
I'm taking a video of what it looks like.
Please take a look at it.
Begging of Zoom-in.
Yes, please prepare a little.
You're a sweaty cameraman.
Today, this place is Honda, so we're going to have a Honda race.
Is it okay around here?
Is it okay here?
Yes, it's okay here.
I'd like you to come out a little earlier and show me a little more of this eating.
I don't think the men will be convinced.
What kind of work are you doing?
I'm going to a race in the Honda campaign.
For example, I'm going to a photo shoot.
What's wrong with your father?
What's wrong with my father?
Oh, really?
You're so funny.
Thank you very much.
Well, then.
Let's take a look at the morning pattern.
I've never seen it before.
But the white was amazing.
Yeah.
I'm going to say this.
Let's bet.
What?
Which one did you win?
What do you do if you lose?
Zoom in in the morning like this.
It's like a battle scene.
I'm going to say this.
You know what?
China Pitch Shogun.
That one?
Oh, you know what?
It's a little different song.
Galala Nyorororo.
What?
You're white, aren't you?
It's red.
Give me a red one.
No.
I'm going to buy a menu.
It's delicious.
I'm going to say this.
It's still night.
It's dark.
It's snowing again for some reason.
It's a very tough situation.
I didn't have this.
By the way, I'm off today.
It's a refreshing morning.
It's the best.
This way.
But I'm really looking at the staff.
You have a great face.
I'm doing something.
Stop this music.
This music is so stupid.
I'm sorry.
Stay here.
Hello.
I'm alive.
I'm still alive.
Hello.
I'm going to go.
Hey.
Shut up.
Watch TV.
I want to do this.
I'm going to call Hanako.
Hey.
Shut up.
Hello.
I'm glad that you have my name.
Shut up.
I'm sorry.
Why is the TV on?
The TV is off.
It's true.
So, shall we go?
Thank you for your hard work.
Good morning. It's Wednesday, January 17th.
The weather is getting better, isn't it? However, the snow last night is very, very cold.
It was the coldest winter this winter.
So if you enter the back road, the snow will be frozen.
Please be careful not to slip.
First of all, let's go to Shizuoka and zoom in.
This is the place where the fire department is gathered.
The number is 146.
154 people were injured.
It seems that a strange person is coming from the morning.
There are many people who don't know how to drive on the snowy road.
It's really hard to drive, so there are some people who say they're going up.
There is a snowstorm at Narita Airport.
It seems that it will be able to fly today.
However, be careful not to slip in the shade.
Let's zoom in on Nippon Network this morning.
Hello, do you like me?
Will you still look at me as a partner?
I did it.
Did you see it?
Tome-san is a little angry.
Let's meet again comfortably as if nothing had happened.
Thank you for your hard work.
Next is the bird-human contest in Hamada.
It's amazing.
I'm glad I was alive when I was blown up by a bird.
Did you see your own bird?
It wasn't acting at all.
It was a real bird.
The man in the middle has a serious face.
There was a person who really came to see this program.
It was amazing.
It was fun.
I won't let it end like this.
I'm thinking about you.
There is a pro-wrestler called Zen Nippon Pro-Wrestler.
Bring a bouquet of flowers and go to a masked wrestler.
You are scary.
The person who saw the video knew how to become a bird.
First, put white on the base.
Anyone can see it.
It was fun.
I was a little angry that I was called.
Let's shake hands.
Let's do something.
Look, look.
I'm going to take it out of the middle and put it on the face.
I've been doing this for a long time.
This is delicious.
Let's decide with rock-paper-scissors.
No.
Rock-paper-scissors doesn't make sense.
Let's decide with rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
I'm serious.
What about the punishment?
It's not a team, it's just the two of us working together.
The two of us working together.
This is really important.
What's the distance between the two of you?
The distance between the two of us is...
It's about 10 meters.
That's right.
It's not that far.
That's why I'll try my best to make it.
You can't fly to me.
I'll think about it.
Please bring me a postcard.
It was really...
It was fun, wasn't it?
It was really fun.
We don't have much time today.
It was a good opportunity.
Like this.
Bring the camera outside.
There's a lot of things.
Let's keep doing it.
Let's do it.
Please appear on this program.
Let's do that.
How about doing this?
If you lose, you should do this.
I'll have a lecture about how to move in a different direction.
You know how to do it.
Why didn't you go to Nagoya?
You're right.
Let me briefly introduce you to the story.
There was a story about a fan of Hama-chan and Mach-chan.
My friend, Hama-chan's fan...
Please draw this in your head.
Height 170 cm,
without a chin,
He is like a cat that is connected from the neck to the face.
And when he laughs, he blows his nose like this.
This is the kind of fan I am.
What is that?
That's nice.
But earlier, we talked about baseball.
I don't know if you think it's strange,
but I'm not embarrassed.
It's not embarrassing to see me poop.
I am.
It's strange, isn't it?
Yes, it's embarrassing.
Why?
You've seen it before, haven't you?
Who?
No, I haven't.
The most embarrassing thing was that I forgot to lock the door.
I can't say that I saw it,
but I forgot to lock the door.
I even forgot that I didn't lock the door.
I was knocked on the door.
I was knocked on the door, so I had to knock back.
When I knocked on the door, the door opened.
I didn't lock the door.
I opened the door with my own power.
I didn't see anything.
I want to show it to you.
I was injured.
We talked about dirty things at the end,
but I'm sure there are things like that.
It was really interesting,
so I tried to go outside like that.
Like I said earlier,
please look forward to it.
That's all for now.
See you next week.
Thank you very much, everyone.
It was really interesting today.
It was so much fun.
What should I do?
What do you think?
People who watch TV
are less likely to say it's a joke, aren't they?
But when I look at the postcards,
there are a lot of people who want me to do more jokes.
Is that so?
You can write a joke.
Is it a tsunami?
No, I just want to see it.
I want to see what kind of joke it is.
I don't think it's funny anymore,
but I want to do it when I get home.
I want you to put out a drama or something.
There is such a thing.
For example, Yoko-giru.
Maybe after a month,
if you look at the postcards,
there will be a joke in it.
It's like I'm in it.
It's so funny.
As usual,
if you have any questions,
please leave them in the comments.
It's not a punishment game,
but if you lose in a game like this,
you can watch this kind of program.
Please leave them in the comments.
We'll be waiting for you.
Thank you for watching.
See you next week.