You're the best, Jojo.
Jojo is the best.
He's the best.
What about you, Masaki?
Are you going to get married?
What?
Right away?
Thank you.
You're late.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Are you feeling down?
Are you feeling down because you're too happy?
Well...
I'm going to get married tomorrow.
Congratulations.
You're so excited.
Last week, Yamazaki was able to get married without feeling embarrassed.
But something is wrong.
There's something that's bothering me.
Marriage blue, right?
It's not marriage blue.
I have a relationship with her.
But as a man, I thought I had to make an end to it.
But you're already married.
To be honest, it's important.
What?
This is a relationship.
You should do it yourself.
It's not like that.
When you're going to get married, you have to make an end to it.
There are people who are dating other than Aya.
I don't like it either.
It's the worst.
I don't have a girlfriend.
Do you have a girlfriend now?
What's this?
It's a two-shot photo.
I know.
This is the composition of the photo.
Is this a two-shot?
This is a two-shot when I went to Izu.
The back doesn't look like Izu at all.
There's nothing wrong with the back.
It's a photo.
This is when I skydived.
There's nothing wrong with the back.
I don't know if I'm going to stay with Yuka forever or if I'm going to break up with her and go to my wife.
Are you still dating?
I'm still dating.
Really?
You're not going to tell your girlfriend.
I have to return the stuff.
What do you mean?
I forgot about it when I went to stay with her.
You went to stay with her?
I went to stay with her.
I thought you were taking pictures.
It was really dangerous. I was really worried.
I didn't want Matsumoto-san to die.
Why?
It's a very jelousy drug, right?
What do you mean by jelousy drug?
It's a drug that you take twice.
I forgot about this.
I left this at home.
I have to return this.
Can I go now?
You can go.
Everyone, please go.
We can't do anything.
I don't know if we can do anything.
I'm going to turn white and go to Aya's place.
You're going to go?
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
When he's with me, he's always...
You?
He calls me Yu.
He's always there.
He's really lonely.
He's married.
It's totally different.
He's not lonely.
He's busier than Yamasaki.
He's really busy.
We can't do anything.
Good morning.
Yu, good morning.
It's a normal morning.
I think you already know.
I'm laughing.
I'm going to get married.
I know.
It's bad for Yu, but...
Let's break up.
I've become a bad person.
It's not just Yu.
What is Yu?
Yu is about you.
You don't call me like that.
You don't call me Yu.
You can't call me Yu.
When we're together, you call me Yu.
We've never called each other Yu.
Don't say stupid things.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to get scolded.
This is my profile picture.
No.
We went to Izu together.
We didn't go to Izu.
That was funny.
Do you remember this?
What is this?
This is a composition.
It's not a composition.
I don't know what a composition is.
Why do you have to get scolded?
I don't want to get scolded.
What are you talking about?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't want to get scolded.
I forgot.
What?
I didn't wear it recently.
You're a fool.
What is this?
Why do you bring it like this?
Don't touch it.
I'll buy you this.
I don't need it.
It's not mine.
I remember this.
What do you remember?
When I was on the same show with Shimura.
You were on the same show.
You disappeared before I knew it.
You disappeared.
That's right.
I was so nervous.
That's why I tried not to talk in front of Shimura.
But in September...
What?
It's a funny song.
It's a good song.
What is it?
Okay.
Hit me.
What are you doing?
Why?
Take my feelings for you.
Say goodbye to me.
I don't have feelings for you.
Do you have feelings for me?
I don't know why.
I don't know why you called me.
Forget that you like me.
It hurts.
Go home.
Take this with you.
I don't need it.
He is...
He looks happy.
As expected.
He was smiling today.
I didn't see it until now.
It was hard.
To be honest, it was hard.
But it's okay.
If it's not like that,
I can't be happy with you two.
Shall we go next?
What?
Not yet?
It's okay.
One time is enough.
No.
One time is not enough.
It's not that kind of problem.
What?
You were holding hands so much.
From the other side,
I was in a big trouble.
If you come after that,
it will be difficult.
That's right.
Who is this person?
Is this person Kaguya?
I didn't know that.
Really?
You are getting along with your family.
Shion is getting along with his family.
Who is this person?
I don't know.
Who is Shion?
It doesn't matter.
Shion is...
Don't say things like that.
Is that so?
No.
I'll say it.
His approach was great.
I forgot to say Yoh.
Really?
This is the one that Kaguya was in.
I didn't know that.
My approach was great.
You didn't like it that much.
I didn't like it that much.
I just thought it smelled good.
I usually...
Do you still have it?
This one.
I have this one.
It's a lotion.
I like it.
You have a lot.
I only use it once.
You only use it once?
I use it a lot.
I'll return all of this.
I'll take it.
He has two.
I have two.
You're scared, right?
That's strange.
Hi.
It's been a while.
How are you?
What's wrong?
There's nothing wrong.
I think you know.
I'm getting married.
Congratulations.
It's not congratulations.
Do you still like me?
Me?
Yes.
I'm not married yet.
But if you were in front of me...
You're crying.
You said you broke up with me.
What?
You asked me to go out with you.
Who?
I'll return this.
What?
This.
You'll make a fool of me.
You're laughing.
I'll take a picture like a family.
I don't think you'll be able to meet someone who's like me.
My children are cute, right?
It's cute, but I know you'll put your heart into me.
You know that.
I don't know.
What are you talking about?
That's it.
This.
What is this?
When Kai attacks me, he always wears this.
Am I wearing this?
This is also Kai's.
What is this?
This is a skirt.
I used it with you.
That's not true.
I made it muddy here.
Absolutely not.
That's not true.
Stand up.
Yes.
You're strong.
It looks like you still have a scar.
Me?
Where am I?
Hit me.
Why do I have to hit you?
You can't forget about me.
I want to hit you, but you're noisy.
It hurts.
I love you.
I'm angry.
I forgot something.
Why is it Hamada?
Why is it Hamada among the four of us?
It's over.
Let's go to the west.
Let's go.
What is it?
You broke up with the girl you loved.
I don't feel that way.
Are you still there?
Yes.
I'm going.
I'm still there.
Are you serious?
It's over.
I don't get tired of it.
You've never been on this show before.
I'm tired.
What are you talking about?
It doesn't matter.
It's time for me to be a man of my own age.
Well.
The next time.
It was a long time.
It's Zaki's turn.
Where did you go?
This is Italy.
Italy?
No.
It doesn't suit you at all.
It was cold.
It's big.
To be honest.
I went to see the ballet.
Really?
I thought it was cute.
It was attractive.
It's scary.
You're not going to give it back?
What?
I'm not going to give it back.
You're not going to give it back.
What's that?
Blue man.
It's too big.
That's right.
Why would you wear it in your house?
I forgot.
When I took it off.
It is the same.
It says Obayashi.
It's evidence.
Isn't it Obayashi?
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna wear it quickly.
Yeah.
He's a scat.
I can tell right away.
It says 182 on that film.
Seriously?
Yes, sir.
You don't smell at all.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
Yes.
I think you know.
Before that, I'll give you back your memories.
Bulma?
Yes.
You said you forgot.
This is...
Whose is this?
It's yours, isn't it?
What do you think?
I don't know.
Put it in.
It's dirty.
Well, I think you already know.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
What?
I'm getting married.
Oh, it seems so.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
There's still a lot left.
There's nothing left.
It doesn't matter.
What do you mean it doesn't matter?
It doesn't matter at all.
It's over.
I think it's amazing that we're on the same page.
I thought it was a ball and attacked.
Please get rid of that feeling.
No, it's okay.
I was attacked.
Really?
All right.
Can I run away?
Ball?
It's a ball.
It's a good ball.
You can hit it, but you can't run away like that.
You can't run away like that.
It hurts.
I don't know.
Your hands are big, too.
It was hard to clean up when we were dating.
I'm relieved.
That's good.
All right.
Let's go to Disney.
Let's go.
I want to go to Disney.
Wait a minute.
What?
I'm still here.
You're still here.
I'm surprised.
Actually, the last one is Morio.
Morio.
Mori Man's Morio.
Mori Man?
It's Mori Man.
No, no, no, no.
I thought it was a game.
I thought so.
It's completely different.
It was very hot.
It was a battle.
It was hotter in the ring.
Their bodies.
You know that, right?
You don't know, do you?
If you look at it, you don't know, do you?
Really?
I'm a junior from Yoshimoto.
I'm a junior, too.
Kana is my wife's type.
Who?
Kana.
I'm sorry.
It's Morio.
Her real name is Kana Sawagami.
She's a great guy.
Why are you looking at me?
I was saying she was cute.
That's all I said.
She's a well-made woman.
Let's go.
Let's go to bed.
I don't want to go to bed.
Kana.
Shut up.
What?
Today.
I'm sure you know.
We're getting married.
Why can't we get married?
What's the score?
I don't know.
It's funny that we're getting married.
Do you remember the song?
What?
Let's walk together.
At night.
What are you doing?
Let's stop.
Stop it.
Morio.
I don't want to get married.
What's wrong with you?
It's not what you said.
I said turn.
What's wrong with you?
I don't want to get married.
I'll tell you.
Are you serious?
He's driving me crazy.
We were dating.
What?
What's wrong?
There's a ring.
What?
What are you going to do?
We can go to the end.
That's right.
I don't know if that's the best way to break up.
The match of fate begins.
Ayamasaki.
Yes.
Let's give it all we've got.
Good luck.
Let's do it.
Go for it.
Good luck.
I've got this.
I don't usually carry this, so I'm going to grab it.
Ready.
Go.
It hurts.
Good luck and win.
Wait a minute.
You should do it.
Hurry up.
Wait a minute.
It hurts.
Thank you.
What's wrong with you?
You're getting married, aren't you?
You're the father, aren't you?
That's right.
Is it okay for a father to do such a thing?
I want to bet with you!
Father.
Good luck, father!
Okay, okay.
Here I go!
Oh, it's coming.
Oh, that's good.
It's a tie, it's a tie.
What?
Oh, it's in my pants.
Oh, it's in my mouth.
Zaki-san!
Zaki-san, call me!
Yamazaki!
He's a foreigner, a foreigner.
Bring me some water!
Bring it yourself!
Why don't you do it properly?
I'll do it again if it's possible.
It's easy to do it in the woods.
Take off your goggles.
Stop it, stop it.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
What's wrong?
I can open it.
The goggles were loose.
That's why I told you to do it properly.
But you...
It's not your fault.
It's my fault.
I told you to do it properly.
Don't use too much power.
The last one!
Kodama Watermelon Shiba Inu!
Here we go!
Good luck!
There's still some left.
Here we go!
It's like a stone bridge in the woods.
What?
I don't want to fight in this way.
It's like a stone bridge in the woods.
Yamada.
I've always loved you.
What?
You're an idiot.
Are you stupid?
It's true.
You look happy.
I can't do it.
I can't keep my eyes off you.
You're happy.
You're an idiot.
You're married.
Why?
Why are you doing that?
You're still doing it?
It's my birthday every year, so I'd like to say something.
I'm so happy.
Happy birthday to you.
Say it properly.
I sang it many times during the planning session today.