Who said that?
What was that?
What was it?
Wasn't there a time when the mic was really smelly?
The mic?
We were talking like this.
Normally people wouldn't have a mic, but...
Why didn't you put it on like this and talk?
But Kouhun-san put it on a lot and talked.
At the concert, right?
Everyone was like, wow.
There was a lot of noise.
We were pretty close, and everyone was like, wow.
We were like, this is the best!
But it was the worst!
This is...
This is the worst!
Definitely.
Well, I understand that.
No, no, no.
I'll tell you.
Can I really say that?
What do you mean?
No, no, you have to tell me.
I was born like this.
I don't know anyone who is this smelly.
Is that what I should say?
Yes, yes, yes.
You have to say that.
Can I really say that?
No, you have to say that.
Well, then...
You have to say that.
I don't know if I've already fixed it, but...
It was amazing!
Until last year.
What was it like?
Well, it was like...
I had a bit of a toothache.
Seriously.
Well, you know...
When you call the guests...
Yes?
Well, you know...
Everyone knows.
Really?
Yes.
It's amazing.
Well, I think...
If you call them here and make them stand there...
Everyone will know.
Really?
Well, when you say, haaaaa...
Everyone goes, waaaa...
Well, when you call the guests...
They just talk normally, right?
That's right.
They don't say haaaaa, do they?
They don't say that.
They don't say that, but...
Everyone goes, waaaa...
It's amazing.
And then, someone...
Well, you know...
A companion or something...
Told me...
Seriously...
Don't make a big deal out of it.
That was the last thing I said.
What did you say?
Well, then...
I started to worry about it.
Well, before the actual performance...
I eat ginseng.
I eat things like that.
But...
It's not something I hate so much that I lose to ginseng.
So, that ginseng...
I put it in my mouth.
I see.
I said something really amazing.
When I try to talk...
Everyone goes, waaaa...
That's funny.
That's right.
Right?
If you talk with your true feelings, it becomes like this.
No, but that's fine.
I don't care.
For someone who's only here...
Yeah, well...
What makes a man so excited?
Hmm?
What do you think?
Well, I don't really...
You don't, right?
I don't either.
But...
It's like, hey!
And you get excited?
Why do I get excited?
Well, I want to know too.
Actually...
Rather...
I'm a bit of a loser.
I see.
Well...
Because, you know...
A leopard...
It stinks!
Well...
The truth is...
That's true, but...
From a leopard's perspective...
A real leopard doesn't smell.
Like, it stinks.
Well, that's true, but...
I have something like that.
Trauma.
Trauma?
A leopard stinks.
Oh, really?
That's my wife's habit.
Yeah.
Hey, wake up!
You have to eat breakfast, or you'll get sick!
What are you talking about?
What?
I don't know what you're saying.
Hey, you!
Yes.
Hey, wake up!
You have to eat breakfast, or you'll get sick!
You stink!
I'm sorry.
But, you don't understand...
From my point of view...
A man should be strong.
I see.
That's what I think.
And I want to make strong things stronger.
I want to be stronger than strong things.
That's what I think.
So, I want to write on a piece of paper.
I want to ride on a piece of paper.
I want to hold down a piece of paper.
Probably.
That's different from excitement.
That...
That's like Zebra.
You don't understand that.
Zebra is weak.
I see.
I want to beat Zebra.
I want to be the target.
You don't understand this.
So, in the end...
In the end?
In the end...
I think you've been here since your past life.
What do you mean?
You've been here since your past life.
My past life was the opposite of the target.
People get excited when they see that.
So, my past life was...
It was a hunting tribe.
A hunting tribe.
Yes, yes.
But, people like us who don't get excited when they see the Zebra pattern...
We are a rich people.
I see.
So, when we see the Chinese cabbage pattern...
We get excited.
When we see the Chinese cabbage pattern...
But, if we see it, we get excited.
If we wear it...
After we take it off, we don't look at it.
We don't look at it.
People say, I'm over here.
What are you talking about?
I think there is a difference between a rich people and a hunting tribe.
We are a rich people.
But, there are people who get excited when they see it.
That's right.
Wow, it's a Zebra pattern.
It's a Zebra pattern.
You used to put a Zebra pattern in your phone, didn't you?
In my phone?
Yes.
What is that?
It's hard to understand.
What is?
It's written in my name.
Did you wear a Zebra patterned clothes?
I did.
It's a Zebra pattern.
Even if it's a Zebra pattern, it's a Zebra pattern.
It's different.
That's right.
What is that?
It's a big Zebra pattern.
Even if you are a baseball player...
Yes.
If you don't explain it like that, it will be hard to understand.
I see.
But, when you have to call it a Zebra pattern...
The voice reaction...
Zebra pattern, Chichi.
You can say Chichi.
If you can only say Zebra pattern...
If you can only say Zebra pattern, Chichi.
Mr. Matsumoto, during the game, you were laughing half-heartedly.
Please tell us more about that death match.
Well, I did a lot of death matches.
It's a death match.
Isn't it a great game?
It's a battle of death.
But, you were laughing half-heartedly?
All the time.
Yes.
I don't feel nervous at all.
Who did you play against?
It was Lou Tez.
You...
How old are you?
How many years?
How long have you been talking about me?
About 20 years.
20 years?
That was 20 years ago.
I was in high school.
That's right.
That's why I was called a young high school student.
That was a big death match.
Is that so?
Yes.
So, now I'm talking about Kanaami and others.
But, to me, it's a silly thing.
It's not a big deal to avoid it.
Really?
Yes.
What kind of rules?
What I did was a birthday death match.
This is...
I was laughing half-heartedly while fighting.
Because there were people who were celebrating with me.
So...
I was going to go and fight.
But, I got a present.
It was an intense fight.
Lou Tez is Lou Tez.
Lou Tez is the same person.
Why are there no fat people in ghosts?
Well...
Even if you watch a movie or a drama,
if you see a ghost in a scene,
there will always be a thin person with a pale face.
Originally, there is a ghost of a pig.
But, it comes out.
Some people can see ghosts,
but some people can't.
Most people can't see ghosts.
The other day, I...
Maybe I saw a ghost.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
What?
Really, I saw a ghost.
Your voice is small.
That story...
Do you want to hear it?
I'm a little scared.
I don't know if it's true or not.
I was sleeping alone.
I was sleeping facing this way.
There was a kotatsu and a chair here.
I was sleeping like this.
When I looked this way,
there was a chair...
I'm scared.
It's okay.
There was a chair with a round cell.
A child ran away.
That's right.
I'm scared.
You said that because you wanted to say it.
It's true.
You were carrying a round cell.
I was carrying a round cell.
You were in elementary school.
I wasn't carrying a round cell.
Wait a minute.
You said you were in elementary school when you first carried a round cell.
Yes, I did.
Now that I think about it, I wasn't carrying a round cell.
A round cell...
You were in elementary school, right?
You were in elementary school when you first carried a round cell.
I wasn't carrying a round cell.
I don't know if you were in elementary school or not.
Then what is it?
I felt like I was small.
I see.
You were small, so you were in elementary school.
I was small, so I was in elementary school.
I was in elementary school, so I thought I was carrying a round cell.
You weren't carrying a round cell.
I wasn't carrying a round cell.
It's ambiguous to say that I was small.
I said that there was a treasure in the kotatsu.
I don't have a treasure.
You don't have a treasure either?
To be honest, I don't have a treasure.
I felt like I was sitting.
In the kotatsu?
But I thought it would be better to say that I had a treasure.
I see.
I thought so.
But I felt like I was sitting in the kotatsu.
I felt like I was sitting.
I felt like I was running.
Did you see it clearly?
No.
It's really the atmosphere.
The atmosphere?
When you first said it, you said it was 100%.
Yes, at that time.
Now, as time goes by, I analyze various things.
What do you think?
No.
I wanted to be noticed by everyone.
You wanted to be noticed?
I may have been noticed.
I see.
But it's a lie, isn't it?
It's a lie.
Every year at this time, I heard that you have a habit of digging deeply with a shovel.
What are you looking for?
It's a wallet.
What?
Wallet.
Wallet?
Yes.
Do you dig so deep to look for a wallet?
Because I dug in a very deep place.
Why did you dig in such a deep place?
Because I dug in a very deep place with a shovel before.
Then why did you dig?
What?
Why did you dig in such a deep place?
Because I was looking for a wallet that I had dug before.
I see.
And I found a wallet that I had dug before.
And when I was glad to find it, it fell down.
And I was focused on this side.
And I said, OK, let's bury it.
And I buried it again.
The first wallet you found was in a very deep place.
And you found it?
Yes.
Look at this.
You were there too, weren't you?
What?
You were there then.
No, I wasn't.
Tell me.
I don't know!
Why did Mr. Hamada need to make a hole in his mouth?
To be honest, this is a trauma.
What?
Trauma.
Me?
Yeah.
Everyone was saying it.
Even in middle school.
When you weren't there.
It was like...
When you were off, it became the topic of the class meeting.
Aoki sensei was saying anything.
Let's talk about Hamada with everyone.
There were so many things to say.
Everyone was crying at the end.
Who would bring bread to Hamada?
That's what he was saying.
That was a trauma.
It's nothing but a trauma.
What?
Why is it a trauma?
If you say it on TV, you can't support it.
Why?
Is it okay to say it?
It's the reason why you became an empty mouth.
That's right.
There's no reason for that.
Because when I said Hamada-kun, he looked at me.
What are you talking about?
Then I'll say it.
My dad is an a**hole.
What's going on in the center of the giant Tatsumaki?
There's a cause and an action.
Someone is doing it.
What do you mean someone is doing it?
I saw it.
I can't beat the person who saw it.
Right?
What's going on?
Is it inside?
Yes.
If the inside is outside, I've never seen it.
If you look at it from above, what's going on in the middle?
Someone is doing it.
What?
Are you an a**hole?
You know,
a woman who has a good sense.
A woman who has about 40 points.
By herself.
She's doing that by herself.
She's throwing her house away by herself.
Why is she doing that?
What's going on?
You see,
there's a lot of things.
Like a backache.
Right?
Since she has about 40 points,
there's a time when she gets a little popular.
That's true.
Something like that.
Her breasts are big, right?
They're pretty big.
Her breasts are pretty big.
That's right.
And there's a guy who just wants to see her breasts.
I know.
You don't know?
I'm sorry for hitting you.
It's hysteria.
What the hell?
All of them just passed by me.
In the end, it's like this.
I thought so.
I got two senses.
About 40 points.
Who are you?
I'm going to the amusement park with her this time.
I'm scared of the screaming machine, so I can't ride it.
Please tell me how to refuse a screaming machine that's not cool.
Sure.
I'll tell you.
It's not cool to refuse a screaming machine.
I can't do that.
Then I'll ride this.
That's possible.
I'll make her think that way.
You can't show her that you're a man who can do it.
I see.
That's right.
But, you know,
if she asks you to ride a sword,
you can't do that.
You can't do that.
You have to be confident.
You have to stand up straight.
Why?
I'll buy the ticket.
I bought it.
I can buy it, right?
You can be confident.
I'll go to the front of the ride.
I'll go straight.
It's the next turn.
Are you going that far?
You can't go up there.
It's okay.
It's okay?
I'm right in front of you.
What should I do?
You can do this.
Can I come?
Yes.
That's good.
You can do this.
You should have done this before you left home.
What are you doing?
You should have done this at home.
You can afford to do that.
It's not a big deal.
I see.
You're right in front of me.
What should I do?
That's right.
She's already on the ride.
You can escort her.
I see.
What is this?
You can hold her like this.
What kind of situation is this?
She has a lot of power.
I see.
It's okay.
She's already on the ride.
I'll sit down.
Hurry up and sit down.
From there...
How should I say this?
I'll ride a sports car.
I see.
You'll ride a sports car?
I'll ride a sports car.
Can I get off?
You can get off.
What?
You can't get on.
I'm scared.
It's okay.
Really?
Yes.
It's okay to get on, right?
Of course it's okay.
I'll sit down.
You can sit down.
Really?
Like this, right?
It's okay up to here.
You can sit down, right?
It's okay.
You can't sit down.
What are you doing?
Hurry up and sit down.
Everyone is lined up.
That's right.
What should I do?
I'll just get off.
I'll get off.
You're like a part-time worker.
I did something like that.
Push.
I'll get off.
He got off.
It's okay.
The time is not over yet.
Really?
Get off.
Is this okay?
It's okay.
Is it moving?
It's moving.
What should I do?
So what are you going to do?
Finally, before you come here, I have a lot of nonsense to tell you.
You...
I don't want to hear that.
That's right. It's a way of saying no.
I'm listening to your way of saying no.
Yes, please.
That's right.
This is better to tell your friend.
What?
Give me a call.
Oh, I see.
It's like this.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.