Isn't it perfect?
You have to spend money on clothes.
You have to spend money on clothes and accessories.
Europe.
Excuse me.
Good morning.
Thank you for your help the other day.
I was so excited.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry. I can't look at your face directly.
I'm looking at you gently.
Today, Oshima wants to give you something.
So I came here.
Me?
Yes.
Hamada-san.
Good luck.
What is it?
It's my love.
Thank you for your help.
What is it?
It's that.
Give it back.
Why is it only Hamada?
You are a human, aren't you?
But it's a girl.
It's my love.
Thank you for your help.
What is it?
Did you make it yourself?
Did you buy it?
Why are you looking at me?
Where are you?
You have a runny nose.
I can't believe it.
You have a runny nose when you give me chocolates on Valentine's Day.
But...
You have a boyfriend.
You have a cool boyfriend.
I broke up with Oshima because I like Hamada-san.
What?
It's a show.
What are you laughing at?
I'm sorry.
Shut up.
It's not funny, so don't talk.
I'm your senior.
What's wrong with you?
I don't think you're making fun of me.
Why?
Why don't you accept it?
Why can't I accept it?
I'll accept it.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
What is it?
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
Thank you.
This is close.
Then Oshima will date Hamada-san.
Wait a minute.
Which side are you touching?
It's embarrassing.
Your face is embarrassing.
You're ugly.
What kind of face is that?
I'm looking at you from behind, but you're in a strange state.
You're in a strange state.
It's embarrassing.
That's what happens.
Shut up.
What?
What is it?
What are you talking about?
What?
What is it?
What's wrong with you?
What?
Stop it.
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
What's wrong?
Yamasaki!
Are you okay?
What do you mean?
You're not going to date me because of this?
That's why you shouldn't date him.
Right?
Shut up, you cell phone!
Hey!
You're a senior!
If you win, you can go out with me.
Ah, that's a bit...
That's a bit harsh.
I can't accept it.
Let's do it.
Valentine's Day!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Yay!
I'll look at it again.
If you lose,
you have to go out with me.
I'll throw away my wife and children.
After today,
I'll go to a love hotel.
Of course.
We'll take a picture and send it to you.
We'll send it to you.
Please tell me the rules.
It's a familiar game,
so I'm sure you'll understand.
If you get three points, you win.
Are you okay with that?
Rock, paper, scissors!
I'll give you a penalty!
The first round
Rock, paper, scissors!
One more time!
You're too high!
Why are you doing it twice?
That's not right!
I'm not good at it, so I can do it.
If you take it, it's over.
That's right!
I can do it.
One, two, three!
High hands, high hands, rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors!
You did it once, so don't do it twice!
You have to hit it here.
I'm sorry.
One, two, three!
High hands, high hands, rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Look at this!
This is a great transformation!
You can't do it with this stick!
You can't do it with a stick!
Look at that!
Look at this!
Good luck!
I'm rooting for Miyuki!
Thank you!
You're easy to get along with.
I can do it.
That's all you have to say.
One, two, three!
High hands, high hands, rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors!
That was dangerous!
Be careful!
One, two, three!
High hands, high hands, rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors!
That was dangerous!
Be careful!
You!
That was hard!
That was a no-go.
One, two, three!
Rock, paper, scissors!
That was dangerous!
That was a no-go.
Wait!
You're wearing a helmet!
Why are you wearing a helmet?
Are you out of your mind?
That's right.
That's strange.
Why?
It's strange that he's wearing a helmet.
A helmet?
Why is it strange?
It's because you can't lose to someone who's half-hearted.
Well, it's true that I didn't lose.
That doesn't matter.
You were losing.
Okay, okay, okay.
Let's say I won.
Let's do it next time.
Okay.
What?
Isn't this the end?
I heard it was over.
Who is it, huh?
Who is it?
I'm wearing a helmet, so I can't start.
I can't start.
It's unfair.
Do you have something you want to do?
Turn around, turn around, turn around and...
Let's do that.
It looks like there's something.
Valentine's Day of love!
Turn around, turn around, turn around and...
Let's have a one-shot match.
One-shot match.
I think we can do it.
Is that okay?
Put it on your forehead and turn around 10 times.
Ready!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10!
Hurry up!
Amada-san wins!
Thank you!
Let's go!
Wait a minute!
What?
I haven't lost yet.
You haven't lost?
It's already over.
It's not over, it's not over.
What about the next game?
It's not over.
Let's do it again.
I can't help it because I've already turned my eyes.
That's right.
Can't you let me do it again?
This is strange.
It's strange.
I thought I was going to lose, so I asked someone else to do it.
Who are you going to ask?
Amada is good at turning.
So I can't win.
Then why do you know it?
I know it and I'll do it.
It's true.
You can't do that.
It's strange.
It's a strange story.
It's true.
Where are you from?
Don't you want to do something?
There's something else.
What is it?
Valentine's Day is approaching and I'm in Hamadan.
I'm in Hamadan.
Hamadan?
It's the name of the person you like.
Well, I don't know.
Do you want to do it?
I really want to do it.
This is the second time.
It's a mess.
What you're doing is a mess.
It's worse than us.
It's a good thing.
Valentine's Day is approaching and I'm in Hamadan.
I'll say it again.
I have to go out with you.
I can't go out.
I'll do my best.
We can do it.
That's what it means.
It's a mess.
I can do it.
You can do it!!
Just a little more!!
It's dangerous!
You can do it, you can do it!!
Miyuki-chan, you can do it!!
Hamada-san, you got it!!
Hamada-san is here!
Mugi-chan, go!
It's outside.
Mugi-chan!
Mugi-chan, go!
How are you feeling?
I'm feeling like a otakebi.
Otakebi!
Hamada-san, damn it.
Kill him! Kill him!
Oh! Wow, great power!
Hamada-san, be careful!
He's been taken down!
Ah, it's no good.
It's no good.
What's wrong?
It hurts.
It hurts?
Where does it hurt?
My heart.
Your heart.
You were beaten by Gringo, right?
You were beaten.
It hurts?
You don't have to lose it.
Ah, I'm frustrated.
Frustrated.
What should we do?
He's an old man.
He's a very busy old man.
What should we do?
Well, we'll just get some chocolate.
Yes, yes.
We can't go out with him.
Yes.
But I'm scared of waking up this morning thinking that we'll go out with him.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.