A T H I C C S of it
Why are you suddenly alive?
Ma'am, Ma'am, Ma'am,
I don't think I can finish the water!
No! No!
I don't want my body!
What are you doing?
No!
No! I don't want my body!
If you don't want your body, can you get rid of it?
No!
My nose is clean!
Are you kidding me?
I don't want my body!
What are you doing?
You came in earlier than me!
What are you waiting for?
No!
Where are you going?
I don't want my body!
If you do that, you can't come in early.
What time did I wake you up?
I came in earlier than you!
Don't die!
You're dressed like this, and you've been waiting in that cold place all the time.
Did you know that?
I was wondering what it was.
I looked over there.
I saw the wall.
I thought you were a strange woman.
Shall we continue?
Shall we go home?
Yes.
If I work 30 more minutes, I'll be on time.
I don't want my body!
Who are you talking to?
He's a virgin!
It's on the 7th floor.
Yes.
I'd like to ask you how you're doing.
This program is brought to you by Sunluck.
Ooyama International Products.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
I'm Hamada from Down Down.
Nice to meet you.
Hey.
Oh, mama.
It was so quiet.
I was scared.
I thought I'd do my first episode of Apocryphal.
That's true.
You're not laughing.
Apocryphal.
This is too much.
Yes.
This morning,
Why?
This is the first time we're shooting in Japan.
Don't say such things.
I can't hide it.
This is the first time.
Yes.
The customers are not always in a high mood.
Really?
From now on, they will be in a high mood little by little.
It was raining a little.
When it rains, it's no good.
It will be like this.
No good.
Why is that?
What will it look like?
I'm a man of rain.
Really?
Yes.
Where did it rain when you went?
When I wanted to do a tournament, it was raining.
Really?
Yes, really.
I don't know.
I went to Saipan the other day.
It's a little different from the program, but I met you in my dream.
When I went to Saipan, it was raining when it rained so much.
Yes, it was raining for about an hour.
It was raining.
I'm really a man of rain.
It just happened to be that.
No matter what I do, it's always raining.
It was like that today, too.
It's so cute.
There's nothing special about it.
What's special about it?
That's right.
What is it?
That time and that time.
What time is it?
There are only two.
I'm a man of rain.
There's only Saipan in Kyoto.
Yes.
Really.
I couldn't say much when I went to Saipan.
It's no good if it rains so much.
I thought so, too.
It's said that the current comedy is the third generation.
Everyone is serious.
You don't really play with women, do you?
That's right.
Saipan is a bread of bread.
Why can't you play more?
Everyone.
But I don't know if you're abnormal.
I was jealous of one person.
Everyone, you, Nan-chan, U-chan,
It's cold.
Women are very serious.
Serious.
That's why I went to the disco in Saipan.
There are only men.
What is it?
Tell me.
I don't know.
It's strange.
There are only men.
I don't think so.
The staff brought five or six women to the floor.
They brought them here for us.
They separated them.
Men and women, men and women.
They put them in properly.
U-chan and I were sitting here.
We sat in our own seats.
U-chan, sit down.
Sit down.
U-chan.
No way.
I said, no way.
I sat down.
I was talking to myself.
U-chan, what do you think?
U-chan sat down with a woman on both sides.
The woman next to me.
What is it?
U-chan and Nan-chan are like this.
They are like soldiers.
They are sitting with their backs to each other.
Right?
This is not good.
I was like that.
I didn't have to say anything.
But the producer, Sato-chan.
Nan-chan, you are newly married.
Please be patient.
If you get excited, come in.
I said, okay.
I sat down and looked around.
They were like this.
There were two women.
I aimed at one of them.
You were fast.
They were like this.
I like them.
You like them too much.
I aimed at one of them.
I was making a joke like a machine gun.
They were like this.
I didn't like them.
I came to the court early in the morning.
They were tired.
Don't laugh.
I want to say it alone.
They were tired.
I couldn't talk to them.
What?
It was bad.
I thought I had to go.
I will change my room.
You know my room, right?
I don't know.
I know my room.
I went home, too.
I came back to my room.
Your face is long.
You were in a toilet.
You were in a shower.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
If you want to read, you have to wait.
That girl can't wait.
That's strange.
It's strange.
There must be something.
Yeah, but it's not cool to play around like that.
So I just calm down.
I change into Yukata.
You change into Yukata and wait.
What a setup.
I'm not aware of that at all.
At that point, you're already aware of it.
I thought I was going to sleep.
When I fell asleep, I was like, ahhh.
I don't want to be like that.
I was sleeping normally like this.
I was sleeping for a little while.
I don't know why, but something was bothering me.
I woke up right away.
It's been about an hour and a half since then.
It's strange.
I'm wearing a jeep again.
Why?
Be careful.
I'm wearing a jumper again.
You're going down again.
I'm going down again.
The disco is covered with glass.
It's like a stone wall.
The outside is covered with glass.
It's a stone wall.
I can't see the inside.
What's going on?
I can't get into the disco.
The people in front of the disco are foreigners.
They don't understand English.
I thought I shouldn't look at the situation inside.
At about 1 o'clock in the morning,
I climbed up the stone wall.
Turn around the entrance.
I wanted to do that much.
I climbed up the stone wall.
No one was there.
No one was in the disco.
I thought I shouldn't do that.
I thought I should go to bed.
I put the card key in my pocket.
I can't open it.
It's broken.
The key is broken.
It's broken and I can't open it.
I'm sleepy in this situation.
I can't open the key at about 1 o'clock.
I don't know what to do.
The people in front of the disco are foreigners.
I don't know.
I can't speak English.
I can't speak English at all.
I thought I should look for Nitta.
Nitta's room.
Open the door.
I talked to Nitta.
Nitta, I can't open the key.
Do something.
I'll be there in a little while.
Kill me.
Really.
Nitta didn't like it.
I was having fun.
I came here thinking about this kid.
I went to the front door and opened the door.
It was the night of the trial.
I read a magazine about Yuya.
I went to the trial.
It was a world of father and son.
That's not true.
Everyone is serious.
The members who were there were.
I was away from them.
I was watching.
I was thinking about Yuya and Nanta.
There was a staff at the table over there.
I went there.
Nanta came on the way.
What are you doing?
Everyone was there.
What about that woman?
It's okay.
You're doing a wasteful thing.
Let's go to karaoke.
We all went to karaoke.
Nanta was in the room.
I closed the yukata and waited for him.
Really.
I can't hold it.
What is this?
Let's go to the back of the bar.
Foreigners are bad.
Foreigners don't get along with foreigners.
That's true.
Japanese people work hard.
Especially in warm countries.
They are lazy.
They don't move much.
The people who built houses were like that.
They didn't use cement.
It took about 10 years to build a house.
It was like a competition with Alizuka.
It's amazing.
I went to the cafeteria.
Everyone in the 14th place was like an old woman.
I'm getting angry.
I want to see her soon.
But my body doesn't listen to me.
Everyone is hungry.
Japan is fast.
There are people who get angry at work.
They are different.
I went to a Chinese restaurant.
They are fast.
It takes about a minute.
Especially in Oshawa.
It was terrible.
Everyone was thirsty.
They wanted to drink coke.
Everyone was like this.
Don't move.
I opened the refrigerator.
It's hot, so I opened the refrigerator.
I enjoyed the cool air.
I opened the refrigerator.
It was cool.
I put it on the glass.
I was surprised by bubbles.
Please bring it to me.
What kind of assistant is she?
I want to be cute.
I have received many fan letters from Nitta.
Really?
First of all, I want to meet Nitta-san.
Who is it?
Let me introduce him.
This person...
I haven't written his name yet.
Please tell me about your Valentine's day.
Valentine's day.
Valentine's day...
Well, nowadays, I get chocolates for doing this kind of work.
But I didn't get chocolates when I was a student.
When I was in the first year of junior high school,
I remember that I gave chocolates to a very annoying guy.
Did you give chocolates to him?
Everyone hated me.
Everyone called me Machamachi.
I was a very strong pig.
I was not a normal pig.
You were a 100-kant pig.
I was a 100-kant pig.
I was even better than that.
When I walked on the streets, I would make noise like a bird.
You are a fool.
I was such a scary guy.
I would make noise like a bird because I was in danger.
Really?
I was very strong like a bull.
I was a pig like that.
I would run around and something would happen.
Something would happen.
I was very strong like an electric jellyfish.
Really?
Where did you live?
You were an electric jellyfish.
I was a pig like that.
This is my feeling.
You had a great feeling.
I was wearing a scarf.
Everyone was laughing at me.
Everyone was laughing at you.
That was also a hand-knitting.
That was a hand-knitting.
I am sorry on that.
I was sad.
Since everyone was watching, you should get the offering.
Yes, I will.
I will say thank you.
I will, but you have a rice fields in front of your house.
So, I will go to the rice fields.
What a bad guy.
I don't know why you were so fat.
But, with all your heart, you don't care about that kind of thing, do you?
It's a lie.
It's a lie!
You're going to turn into a fire!
Are you taking a walk?
The frog looks a little cold.
Ah, I see.
I'll tell you another wonderful story.
Really?
I think this story will be very popular.
What kind of story? Tell me, tell me.
Well, it's an interesting story.
It's from Kanagawa Prefecture.
I want you to come to the Fujisawa Labor Council building in the neighborhood.
Don't mess with me!
Write something else!
There's a lot of things to write!
It's not like this.
You can say that there was something like this in the question.
Right?
Kanagawa Prefecture.
Kanagawa Prefecture...
Speak properly!
It's quite far from here.
It's close.
I don't really know where this is.
This is...
It's called Kinshicho.
When you say Kinshicho...
What do you eat?
Suginami.
Neri-maki.
Sumida-kun.
I don't know anything about that.
Ah, but it's already...
It's in Chiba, isn't it?
If you go a little further.
What?
Don't make such a dirty face.
It's close to Chiba.
It's quite far from here.
It's in the countryside, isn't it?
When I was filming earlier,
everyone was like,
Dabe-dabe!
You don't need to say that.
Someone who lives at this time on a weekday like this...
Isn't he a good-looking person?
Say you want to come,
and bring your letter.
Come on, say it.
Say something like that.
It doesn't have anything to do with the program, but...
What do you usually do?
Are you a student?
Do you have anyone working?
What do you usually do?
I work part-time.
Eh? Are you from the Philippines?
Idiot!
Aren't you from Japan?
When are you coming back?
I work part-time.
What do you usually do?
What's the name of the restaurant?
Tamori.
Tamori?
Call me that!
Say it's San-to! San-to!
Well, that's about it.
Shall we go home now?
That's right.
It's really hard to go home.
I wonder how they wrote it.
Let's have them write again.
That's right.
You want to see this again, don't you?
What are you doing?
I don't know.
Well, that's all for today.
Thank you for coming.
Shall we do a Q&A?
What is it?
There's only one thing I can do.
Think about it.
There must be something.
Tell me.
There's only one thing I'm really good at.
Dad, can I ask you something?
Don't laugh.
It's really funny.
Try it on me.
I can't even do it.
I'm Masakatsu Tamura.
Dad, can I ask you something?
I want to eat curry with you.
What is that?
That's all for today.
Thank you very much.
Today's opening was a failure.
Hey.
Yes?
What is it?
Today's opening was a failure.
That's right.
It was hard to shoot at the place where Hamada wasn't there.
Is that so?
I've been shooting for three or four days.
When you came in, everyone was talking about something else.
I was trying not to be noticed by Hamada.
There was a time when I was late for this program.
I was doing all that for Hamada.
Don't lie.
I wasn't really late.
I'm looking for an idea for a costume.
I see.
What kind of costume do you want?
That's right.
Especially, I want to hear the opinion of the person who went to a good place with a costume.
How can I get into the fans?
Advice.
What kind of costume do you want?
That's right.
I want to hear the opinion of the person who went to a good place with a costume.
Yes.
And, the Fuzusawa Labor Association.
Please come.
I will never go.
I'm sure.
Are you sure?
I can go to various places, but I will never go to Fuzusawa Labor Association.
I'm sure.
I'll see you next week.
Good bye.
What?
I'll see you next week.
Good bye.
This program is brought to you by
Oyama International Products