In the end, Yamazaki said that he would be reborn as a comedian.
So what did he say?
We don't really know, but he said that he would be reborn as a comedian.
He said that he would be reborn as a comedian.
After he met us, he said that he would do 100 push-ups.
We said that it would be impossible, but I said I would do it.
To be honest, 100 is a little too much.
I'm doing it.
He said that he would do 100 push-ups.
You two can't hear me.
You guys want to sell mahjong.
That's difficult to understand.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Luna Arte!
Luna Arte? What does that mean?
I was surprised.
What are you talking about?
Yamazaki-san, there are other customers.
Did you have a meeting?
What?
Sorry.
Did your mother call you?
Why?
Do you want to talk?
Sorry.
What kind of room is this?
What is this?
But there was a bad weather today.
Yes.
Where is it?
Is it cloudy?
There was a bad weather.
The temperature was about 34 degrees.
Really?
It's very hot. 34 degrees.
It's hot.
It's 36 degrees.
It's hot at 39 degrees.
It's hot. I can't sleep.
What's going on?
You're the one who had to move the glass in front of you.
You don't talk at all.
What?
Are you always like this?
No, I don't talk at all.
I'm hungry.
You look like you're hungry.
Why is it?
Everyone is looking forward to why you're hungry.
Do you have something to do?
I don't have anything to do.
What?
But I don't think I'm going to eat it all.
I don't think so.
I'm going to eat a lot of Shinto food.
I have to eat 10 servings of fried chicken.
Which one?
Do you want to have a blind date?
I'll have a blind date.
What are you talking about?
Hamada-san, too.
I'll have a blind date.
You're having a blind date in the middle of the night.
I want to be like Hamada-san.
I don't think the types are the same.
They're all the same.
Hamada-san has a cute face.
It's not like that.
There's a position.
It's not about who's good or bad.
That's right.
It's a game of taking positions.
But you haven't been talking to each other since then.
That's right.
Here it comes.
You're making fun of Don-Guri Manako.
What are you laughing at?
Sing. Sing. Don-Guri Manako.
Can I go home now?
Wait a minute.
It's about time.
It's too early to change.
What are you?
That's enough.
What are you doing?
Yamaguchi-san.
I was talking about the resort mansion.
I was talking about the resort mansion at the convenience store.
Don't make fun of me.
Can I smoke?
You can smoke.
You're a comedian.
Excuse me.
Mild Seven. Mild Seven. Mild Seven.
Marlboro Light.
You scared me.
It's like a pigeon has shot a bean gun.
I'm the one who should be talking to you.
Don't talk to me.
It's too much.
It's not too much.
Hey, hey, hey.
Bicycle. Bicycle.
Mr. Noppa. Mr. Noppa. Mr. Noppa.
Mr. Noppa.
What are you looking at?
What are you laughing at?
Yamaguchi Yasuko.
I'm going to call you.
I'm going to make you the host of Yamaguchi Yasuko.
What?
Don't you have anything to say?
No.
Not at all.
It's painful.
To be here.
It's my first time at such a tough coffee shop.
That's because you're wearing a shirt that tightens your neck.
You're a fool.
Yamaguchi-san.
Yamaguchi-san, you're a big guy.
I've been watching you for a long time.
I'm scared even if you get angry because I can't get into it.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Yes.
What are you eating? What are you eating?
Don't eat cream cheese cake.
Diet. Diet.
Do you want me to listen to your phone calls?
Can you even listen to the radio?
You're embarrassing me.
Tanaka.
What's going on?
You were really determined.
I don't like it.
I think you're going to be reborn.
It's not a compliment.
Should I be like a fool?
Yes, it's a little ridiculous.
Yes, really.
The audience around you.
I'm going to go in more and more.
Can I smoke?
What?
I'm telling you to smoke. I'm telling you to smoke.
Hey.
Yes.
You're late.
You're late. Why are you eating so much?
It was the other way around. I'm sorry.
I don't think I can say it anymore.
If you don't say it, it's hard to be a fool.
Is there anything hard about it?
Hey, what are you looking at?
Hey, say something.
Say something.
You're not wearing a hat properly. Say something.
I'm not wearing a hat properly.
That's what I said.
Are you the last emperor?
I don't need that.
I don't need it.
My nose is running.
I have a runny nose.
This is what I wanted you to say.
Oh, here it comes.
Candies are coming in.
Highlights are coming in.
Highlights.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I'm Kintaro.
I heard a fly.
Who pulled it?
Please forgive me.
You're all over the place.
No, please forgive me.
I don't want to.
What do you hate?
Hey, hey, do whatever you like!
L Whore!
That's the truth!
Let me tell you something.
I'm over you.
Why?
I'm done with this.
If not, I'm done.
What?
It's not cool.
It's not cool?
Yes.
It's because there's another funny one.
There's another funny one, but it's not cool?
Yeah.
It's not cool.
It's funny.
It's not funny?
It's not funny!
It's not funny anymore.
What kind of meeting is this?
It's funny if you keep looking at it.
What are you doing?
Are you looking at the cell phone number?
Huh?
Hey!
This is a big deal.
Yes, what is it?
What are you doing?
Yes!
Congratulations to Yamazaki Tsukkomi 100th time!
Well, goodbye.
Can you still run away?
At the end.
I thought you were going to do a game of mahjong.
It's the first time.
You should have just walked.
That's the worst.
If it's like this.
I got caught.
Thank you.
What do you think of Pokemon?
Why are you asking me about Pokemon?
I don't know anything about it.
Is it in the news?
What's in it?
The audience?
The movie?
It's in the news.
I see.
I can't accept Pokemon.
I don't know anything about it.
It's strange.
Why?
Pikachu, Pikachu.
Pikachu is Pikachu.
Don't be so stupid.
That's what I think.
What do you mean?
You're just shouting your name.
But.
For example, if I say,
Matsumoto Higashi!
Matsu!
But if you say that, they won't talk.
Pikachu!
It's your name.
I don't understand the truth of a child who says that.
You like Pikachu, don't you?
I like it.
Pikachu.
I have a card.
I'm collecting it.
Let me say something about money.
My dad is an entertainer.
I have money.
I don't understand.
If I were a child, I wouldn't have liked Pikachu.
I hated it since I was a child.
For example, when Kamen Rider was popular,
everyone wore Kamen Rider sneakers.
I don't know that.
There's a picture of Kamen Rider here.
But I'm a child, so it's strange.
Kamen Rider doesn't wear such shoes.
That's right.
Kamen Rider wears boots.
If you wear Kamen Rider sneakers and say Kamen Rider sneakers,
you're going to the farthest place from Kamen Rider.
That's why I've never worn it.
That's right.
Kamen Rider sneakers, Kamen Rider furikake.
If you say Kamen Rider furikake, you won't eat anything.
I don't care about that.
But if you say Kamen Rider furikake, it doesn't taste like Kamen Rider.
If it tastes like Mettou.
You'd buy it, right?
I'd buy it.
But if you say Kamen Rider furikake,
Kamen Rider won't eat Kamen Rider furikake.
I don't know that.
I couldn't keep up with that when I was a child.
If I kept saying that, Matsumoto would feel bad.
I didn't have any friends.
We were talking in the dressing room.
I heard it from somewhere.
I don't know if I should say it or not.
A 3-year-old boy came out to the dressing room.
He took it off!
What do you mean he took it off?
What are you talking about?
He took it off.
That's not true.
No way!
Really?
Then I'll say it.
I'll say it.
It's my fault.
from first
You go.
You become bigger.
You have a boom.
Yeah.
A boom.
This is the worst.
Didn't I tell you?
Come here. No, no, no.
Isn't it really interesting?
Come here.
The producer immediately came and told him to stop it.
Tell him to stop all the cameras.
And there's a guest, right?
Guest.
To the guest, this thing...
Don't reveal it at all.
Even if you go home, it's ***.
I don't get it.
I said, okay.
Everyone was returned.
The guest immediately returned it.
As if nothing happened, *** came again.
What?
Where are the 50 points?
Even though he came down, he's here.
50 points.
In this shape.
Even now, where are the 50 points?
What do you mean, even now?
Wow, that's amazing.
That's the rumor.
Even I didn't know.
I don't know if this is true or not.
I don't think that person did it.
But he said he would definitely know.
So it's a rumor now.
It's a rumor, right?
If that story was true,
I shouldn't do it.
But he didn't think of telling the truth.
He didn't think of telling the truth.
He was too enthusiastic.
He should have thrown his head.
He should have been careful.
That's why it's written in writing.
Is this real?
I got a 2.
I heard that this will be written.
This one, right?
This is...
This is occult!
This is Matsumoto-san, famous for being the first to distinguish garbage in Japan.
Yes, that's right.
Matsumoto-san is said to be able to distinguish between men and women.
Even if a child in front of a TV is watching, he won't be attracted to it. Please explain.
You have two children, right?
Yes, yes.
A boy and a girl, right?
A boy and a girl.
It's a boy and a girl. What is this?
Why?
You really wanted a boy and a girl, right?
Why is that?
A boy and a girl is a bit boring, right?
What do you mean by boring?
Because when you get home, you're covered in s**t.
Covered in s**t, my home sweet memory.
This is weird.
What do you want?
Matsumoto-san, you can't distinguish between men and women.
That's why you want to be the third person to be a woman, right?
Men, men, men.
That's right.
More than men, men, men.
That's why I'm going to teach you those things.
Is that so?
I'll teach you both.
What for?
I'll teach you to distinguish between men and women.
That's fine.
Men and women.
I'll teach you to distinguish between men and women first.
Wait a minute.
I'll teach you once you understand all of this.
Then I'll wait.
This is the only thing I want to talk about.
Men's expressions.
Men's expressions don't change?
They do.
Men are about power.
And women are about kindness.
This is the theme.
If you don't protect that, you can't distinguish between men and women.
From now on, you shouldn't look at little girls too much.
It's a very hard topic.
I'll try to suppress it as much as I can.
That's right.
There's a situation like this.
In the end, it's like this.
What should I do?
In the end...
Then you.
You can do anything.
Look at me.
Look at my face.
What do you mean by your face?
Like this?
That's not good.
When you want a man, you have to be more powerful.
This is a man.
And women are women.
You have to emphasize kindness.
That's how you can distinguish between men and women.
You can't do that with your face.
I think you've always been like this.
I see.
So from now on...
From now on...
You can't do that with your face.
But at that time, you didn't look like this.
You're like this.
When the two of you are together, this girl will be born.
You have to have a kind face.
Kind face.
Please make a kind face.
I'll take a nice tissue.
It's over.
Mr. Matsumoto, who is the leader of all sports and has disciples all over the world, has a question.
Yes, I have disciples all over the world.
There are players who throw hammers and throw spears.
There are also baseball pitchers who shout loudly after throwing.
You don't look like you're shouting.
Is there a sport where shouting increases your record?
Of course there is.
You can see the difference between hammers and spears.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
I lost.
I lost because I didn't shout.
Isn't it just sports?
It's not just sports.
It's concentration.
Rock-paper-scissors.
I lost because I didn't shout.
What kind of woman am I?
Right?
Next, let's shout.
Let's go.
I can go, right?
It's very difficult.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Can you read the atmosphere?
What are you doing?
You understand, right?
Why don't you understand?
But it's the same for everything.
It's the same for the back.
What do you mean?
Say something.
Apple.
Watermelon.
It's strange.
Say something.
It's not the answer.
TV.
Shoes.
You just have to shout.
Don't look down on me.
It's difficult.
Actually...
Let's stop.
What?
It's okay.
I just heard it.
I didn't see it.
That's all.
Everyone, really.
I didn't hear anything.
When you say it to someone you know...
Why?
This is really...
It's your song.
It's really...
What are you doing?
Seriously.
It's okay.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.