The secret of Japan.
Here, in the outskirts of Tokyo,
there are few people who know that there is an air pocket that has been forgotten since the present day.
The sound of the wild beast that roars in the dense forest.
The information that demons lurk in the mouth of this secret is embedded in our program.
The last catharsis of the 20th century.
The phantom pearl.
The white-haired bat.
Good morning.
It's so cold.
I couldn't sleep last night.
I talked to Mr. Osaki yesterday,
and he said it was too dangerous,
and he wanted to quit.
But after I killed him,
the whole of Japan became a mess.
Then let's do it.
I'll use this.
Yes.
Don't die.
I can't stop.
I'm scared.
Captain Hamada felt something.
Something just moved.
Let's shoot it.
Are you okay?
What is this?
Huge footprints.
There is indeed a phantom pearl.
Are these footprints?
Hey, is it this big?
It's been here for a long time.
It's here.
It's connected.
What is this?
What is it?
Is it really a phantom pearl?
He found something unexpected.
Be careful.
What is this?
Is it the wreckage of the pearl's food?
Or is it a human bone?
And then...
What is it?
Stop it.
What is this?
Yamazaki!
Hey!
The members are nervous.
Yamazaki!
Hey!
Yamazaki was the first victim.
Yamazaki!
Hey!
What was that sound just now?
I think it's coming from me.
Yamazaki!
Don't go!
Be careful!
Yamazaki, what should we do?
What are you doing?
Hey!
Yamazaki!
The pearl, the white-tailed bat, has come to life.
Yamazaki! Yamazaki!
The white-tailed bat, which emits a mysterious ray of light, has become extremely violent.
Yamazaki!
Ahhhhhhhhhh!
Let's save him!
You idiot!
You're not going to do anything right?
Happy new year!
Hey...!
What are you laughing at?
You're making me laugh.
Don't make fun of me anymore.
Let's go together.
With the help of the research team, the human crisis was avoided.
However, in order to fight the next beast, the research team did not have a peaceful day.
Hello.
Oh, man.
I'm so tired.
I'm so, so tired.
By the way, Mr. Old Dog.
Who are you?
Who is Mr. Old Dog?
Where is your punch today?
It's always here.
Who is Mr. Old Dog?
You're wearing the clothes you wore today.
I brought the clothes I wore today.
My stylist, too.
That's right.
I'm wearing clothes today.
Well, it's been a while since I've been a servant of this kid.
I'm taking a break from last week and the week before.
Why did you take a break?
Well, you know, I'm getting tired of saying it now.
That's what I'm saying.
I'm saying this and that.
I just wanted to show everyone that I pulled that face to the Polaroid and did this.
Well, a little bit.
I'm sure everyone will pull it.
No, no one will laugh when they see that face.
Well, I don't know.
I don't think it's me.
It was really terrible.
It was terrible.
I only look at the face of the day it burned.
If that happens on the second day of the first day, it will be even worse.
That's right.
If it's the next day, I'll be right here.
No, it was that bad.
That's what I'm saying.
My face is all over the place, but yours is all over the place.
The ball is good.
The ball is good, but mine is all over the place.
It's because of the smoke.
That's what I'm saying.
That's what I wanted to say.
Really?
Everyone will come the next day.
Everyone will come.
I won't stop.
What?
At home?
Yes, in my dad's pajamas.
Really?
At home?
Yes, in my dad's pajamas.
What about that?
At home?
Yes.
What?
At home?
I couldn't go home if I exposed my face, so I put on my glasses and it was even scarier.
It was even scarier. Your face was covered in blood, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
No, really.
It was like a disease.
When I took my eyes off, both of my eyes were like this beautiful...
Shut up.
My eyes were like this beautiful...
What's beautiful?
Hey, that's perfect.
It was like a picture.
It was amazing, right?
That was terrible.
Even if you look at it, it's like...
It's like a double panchama.
That's right.
I've been on stage like this for a while now.
I thought it might be impossible in this world.
What?
First of all, when it came out like this, it was no joke.
It was a great shock.
It was a shock that my face was covered in blood.
I thought I could take my nose off without joking.
It hurt like this.
Like this?
I was scared to look in the mirror.
I thought I could take my nose off like this.
I really thought I could take my nose off.
I looked for it.
I thought I couldn't take it off.
There was a camera, and I couldn't show my nose.
I looked for it.
Like this with my feet.
I thought I couldn't take it off.
There's nothing that looks like a nose.
There must be a nose.
But I thought my nose was broken.
I thought about a lot of things.
When I looked in the mirror, it came out like this.
I don't do that kind of comedy anymore.
I'm going to do comedy with a tongue twister.
With a tongue twister.
I'm scared to think about it.
What?
But even if I fall here, I won't get hurt.
You're fooling around.
I fell from there.
You fell like this.
You fell like this, and you got hurt here.
It doesn't matter if I fall.
If I fall here, my head will break.
I don't understand.
I won't get hurt if I fall.
You fell here, and you got hurt here.
If I fell here, I would get hurt.
It doesn't matter if I fall here.
When I said that, it hurt a little.
It hurt a little.
It's because you got hurt.
You fell here, and you got hurt here.
That's why I'm scared.
What's wrong with you?
You shouldn't do experiments.
You're bullying your body.
Today, from 6 o'clock in the morning,
from 6 o'clock in the morning, we went to a location.
It was cold.
I was wearing a skirt.
I was wearing a skirt from 6 o'clock in the morning.
He was a pervert.
His fingers were torn.
It was hard.
After that, we went to a location.
It was cold. Where was it?
Odaiba.
It was windy.
We went there.
You don't like it, do you?
It's true.
Don't you hate it?
CX and Nittere.
CX was trying to eat us.
But only his right hand was left.
I have a question for Matsumoto-san.
Please tell me how you grew up.
I'm a fortune teller.
But I can't see your past.
I smell something criminal.
A smell of crime.
I'm often told this.
I don't have siblings or parents.
I'm the only child in the world.
I can't see my family.
I see.
But to be honest, I'm a normal person.
I'm a rich person.
If it was yakiniku, you would have been raised in a winery.
What are you talking about?
You smell like a criminal.
You smell more like a criminal.
You're amazing.
What?
How many times have you touched other people's things?
Gasoline.
Foreigners' underwear.
You're the same.
But in the end, they went to you.
That's right.
Your grandma's underwear.
You too.
You took your grandma's underwear.
That's right.
In the end, they went to you.
Let me borrow it.
I gave it back to you in the end.
In the end, your grandma's underwear.
You took your grandma's underwear.
Don't say that.
I don't smell like a criminal.
You stole sweets, didn't you?
Sweets?
I don't like sweets.
Didn't you have a hard time on Valentine's Day?
Why?
Chocolate.
What should I do?
I can't eat it.
Don't you get angry every year?
I threw it away right away.
I don't care.
I'll keep throwing it away.
I'm a cool guy.
Bang!
Don't take it.
I threw it away right away.
I don't care.
I'm a fool.
I can't hold it.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you looking at me like that?
I'm a fool.
Your friends are strict.
My friends are strict.
You're terrible.
Tease me.
Yoko too.
I don't care about Yoko.
Pick it up and throw it away.
They'll be upset.
Because you don't give them much.
I don't eat sweets.
You're crazy.
Hatcha! The one who gave me the other day.
When I pulled the string, Mickey Mouse was like...
Katakatakatakataka!
That's true.
Mickey Mouse is a cat.
What makes me angry is...
Please eat my handmade chocolate!
It's not handmade at all!
Why?
It's just melted and put in my shoulder.
It's because I bought it from the Kakao store.
Yesterday, when I was on my way home from school,
I was about to buy coffee at the vending machine.
Five or six elementary school students were playing next to me.
I thought something was bothering them,
but one of them said,
Hey, this girl!
She's cheating!
She's buying coffee!
Why is she in Yamazaki?
That's what she said.
If she drinks coffee, she's cheating, right?
That's how kids are.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Coffee is...
That's how kids think.
You know,
when they say,
Hey, look at that!
and you look at them,
and they say,
Look at the blue pig's ass!
It's crazy!
You're not going to say what you said?
I couldn't say that.
Really?
What was it?
Your mom is a dick!
I didn't know that.
It's not a big deal.
But if you say that,
the kid will be like,
Don't say that!
It's not like I admit it.
I don't know if she's a dick or not.
It's just that the tone is different.
This weird way of saying it.
It's like she's making fun of you, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's like,
Your dad is a man!
Don't say that!
That's what she said.
I don't think she heard it clearly.
I think she said something.
She said, Your dad!
When she said that,
she was like,
You're a man!
I don't know what she said.
It's weird.
There's a weird kid.
It's a kid.
I feel sorry for her.
What is it?
The kid with glasses.
He's wearing glasses.
Yeah.
Even a little kid.
That's cute.
But if it's a little kid,
I don't know what to do.
Yeah.
When I was on the Shinkansen,
There was a family trip.
There were five families.
They were all wearing glasses.
Like this.
They were facing each other.
They were all like this.
Don't say that.
It's true.
The glasses are matching.
They were all like this.
When I saw Fujii,
they were all like this.
It's true.
The color was interesting.
When I saw Fujii,
they were all like this.
They were all like this.
I couldn't wait for three hours.
They were all sleeping.
When the show was about to end in Tokyo,
the five of them woke up.
They were all like this.
Don't lie to me.
It's true.
When the show was about to end,
they were all like this.
Okay, okay.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Let's go home.
I'm serious.
What are you doing?
If you're laughing like that,
what am I supposed to do?
I talked to Mr. Osaki yesterday.
He said it was dangerous,
so he wanted to quit.
What did he say?
He said he had a sore throat.
Why are you laughing?
I talked to Mr. Osaki yesterday.
He said it was dangerous,
so he wanted to quit.
What are you doing?
Come on.
I talked to Mr. Osaki yesterday.
What are you doing?