Tokyo Pier is fun.
What happened to the cherry blossoms?
They fell.
Did they?
It rained a lot.
Yeah.
Why do cherry blossoms fall when it rains?
You hate them, don't you?
Are you criticizing cherry blossoms?
No, I'm not.
I want them to bloom more.
I want them to be warmer.
They'll fall.
Thank you.
I have a favor to ask.
Yes.
My wife wants to see the opening.
Oh, really?
I'm sorry.
I just want to say hello.
Oh, I see.
Kanae.
Kanae?
She's the wife of Mr. Tsubasa.
Hello.
Thank you for always taking care of me.
I used to be an idol singer.
I had a break, but I forced her to get married and retire.
Yes.
Today, I'll give you some sashimi.
I'll give you some sashimi.
Can I have some chocolate?
Here you go.
Wow, that's gross.
I worked hard to make it.
Is your wife still alive?
No, she's dead.
It stinks.
No, no.
Can I have some?
It's my favorite dish.
That's gross.
I put green onions on it.
It's good.
Try it.
I can't eat it.
I'll give it to you later.
What's wrong?
Kanae.
Are you mad?
I'll give it to you later.
It's delicious.
Let's go over there.
Please eat this.
Let's go, Kanae.
Thank you.
Kanae, come here.
What are you doing?
I'm wrestling.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
It's time for the world's most beautiful and exciting heatless kiss battle.
Let's play three games.
We'll win each other's games.
The world's most beautiful and exciting heatless kiss battle.
Thank you.
That's a good idea.
We don't need money.
We've already made a lot of money.
It doesn't matter to the viewers.
By the way, today is the first time that our producer and his wife have come to our program.
It's going to be a hot game.
Let's start the game.
The first game is the world's most beautiful and exciting heatless kiss battle.
It's easy.
I brought a box.
There are five phones in the box.
You can choose one by one.
Which phone will be the first to arrive?
It's time to kiss.
It's like an ademon.
The first one is from the UK.
Nice to meet you.
Wait, wait, wait.
What is it?
Hey, wife.
You don't have a nose.
What is it?
What is this?
I'm a Japanese beauty, too.
No, I'm sorry.
Am I not good enough?
Who brought you here?
I don't know who.
You have to bring someone better than me.
Kanae, Kanae, what's wrong?
What?
Please.
We're in the middle of the show.
Hey.
Wait, wait, wait.
That's not good.
Let me recommend you.
What's wrong?
Do you want to play that role?
Can I go to Kanae?
The project has changed.
I'm a Japanese beauty, so I don't care.
I don't care if you come out.
You can be the world's most beautiful woman.
I'm a Japanese beauty, so I don't care.
Just this time.
I'm sorry.
AD, can I sit here?
I'm counting on you.
Well, then...
Are you going to pull out your phone?
The person who gets the call can be a beautiful woman.
I'm counting on you.
Go ahead.
The order is the same.
I'm counting on you.
I'm really counting on you.
Don't call me.
I'm going to call a beautiful woman.
Are you all okay?
Yes.
I'm standing up.
Raise your head a little bit.
It's the same, isn't it?
The winner is...
Matsumoto Hikoshi!
Congratulations!
I was scared for a second.
That's too bad.
I'm glad I won.
I'll take this.
Thank you.
Well, then...
It's a kiss with a beautiful woman.
Go ahead.
When I said I needed you.
You said you would always stay.
It wasn't me who changed it for you.
And now you've gone away.
It's a kiss with a beautiful woman.
It's over!
Wait a minute.
I feel like my soul has been taken away.
Congratulations.
Wait a minute.
What is this?
I'm counting on you.
I'm really counting on you.
Where are you going next?
Get out of here.
Let's get this over with.
Next up is the love machine!
It's easy.
There are five machines.
Choose one you like.
There's one that doesn't have electricity flowing through it.
It's a kiss with a beautiful woman.
The one that will kiss the winner is...
The Russian!
I'm really into Russia.
Please come out.
Russia.
Go home.
Why are you here?
Excuse me.
Okita.
Kanae.
What?
What are you doing?
Why?
Why are you doing this when I'm here?
No, no, no.
I don't like this.
I don't like it unless it's more beautiful than me.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Yes, yes, yes.
Kanae.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
He's the president, so he doesn't need it.
I promised him only once.
Do you want to do it again?
He's an idol singer.
Don't be a pro-wrestler.
No, no, no.
He's an idol singer.
He has a little pride as an idol.
Kanae.
What is it?
There's nothing.
Kanae.
You're a senior in the entertainment world.
No, no, no.
It's only three times.
If you put this in, it'll be a disaster for both of you.
It's over.
Just this time.
Yes.
Really.
Let's make it the last time.
Yes.
What?
Kanae.
I have something like that.
No, no, no.
Just one more time.
Let's make it the last time.
Let's choose one.
Yes.
I'll go here.
Do you want to go?
Can I go here?
I'll go in the middle.
I don't know.
If you wear this, you're safe.
If you don't wear it, the electricity won't flow.
If you wear it, you're safe.
If you wear it, you're out.
You can't kiss.
If you wear it, you can't kiss.
I'm scared.
I'm scared, but I want you to wear it.
Let's switch on the vision.
Please.
It hurts.
You're kidding.
Everyone is wearing it.
I'm not wearing it.
It's not true.
Take your shoes off.
I'm not wearing it.
It's a lie.
Everyone is wearing it.
Don't lie to me.
No, I'm not wearing it.
Who is it?
Who?
I'm not wearing it.
Who's lying?
It's a lie.
Who is this?
Look, look.
You're right.
Who is it?
I'm not wearing it...
I'm not wearing it.
There are a ton of suspects.
You lie to me.
You're Yamasaki, right?
No, no, no!
It's you!
You're the one who came!
You're lying!
You're not wearing anything, so you're the real one!
It's true!
You're not wearing anything at all!
What?
You're lying!
The winner is...
Yamasaki Yosaku!
Congratulations!
I'm happy.
Because I can kiss a beautiful woman.
It's not a big deal.
I'm grateful.
It's a kiss with a beautiful woman!
Please!
Your face is full.
It's a kiss with a beautiful woman!
It's as long as a Japanese movie.
The last one is a lucky card for a beautiful woman and a pittanko!
There are cards from 1 to 6.
Please choose one.
A beautiful woman will appear and do this.
If you have the same number of cards, it's a pittanko!
It's a kiss with a beautiful woman!
Where is the next beautiful woman?
The last beautiful woman is...
She's from Russia!
It's a beautiful woman from America!
I was surprised!
That's...
What?
There's no nose.
That's strange.
It's a beautiful woman from America.
Mr. Suga.
Yes?
What do you mean?
Please take it off.
I won't.
Really.
Take it off.
It's beautiful.
What do you mean?
It's cute.
It's not cute.
It's from America, right?
It's from America.
It's like a playmate.
You don't have to run away.
It's from America, right?
It's from America.
Playmate.
Cowgirl.
Is this America?
It's the last match.
I'll do it according to the rules.
Please.
The rules haven't changed much, have they?
It's a kiss with a beautiful woman, right?
Isn't there anyone from America?
Isn't there anyone?
Did you return it?
I returned it.
What do you mean?
I'm here.
Cowgirl.
Hey.
Why are you asking?
I returned it.
I'm an idol.
It's too much.
This is not a place to resist.
Why?
This is the producer's request.
Let's do it according to the rules.
We've been crying, haven't we?
It's okay to look at the screen.
It's a rude conversation.
Hey.
Are you the leader?
I'm not the leader.
Isn't it amazing?
Didn't you say something amazing?
I didn't say anything.
It's according to me.
What's wrong?
This.
This is the president.
Isn't the president the leader?
The president is a senior in the entertainment industry.
You know what you want to do if you're a senior.
That's why I want to do it.
That's why I returned it.
I can't believe it.
Am I beautiful?
You're wrong.
No, it's you.
That's right.
What do you want to do?
I want to have a beautiful body.
You have a beautiful body.
We love each other all the time.
I want to kiss you.
You used to have a beautiful body.
I took it from you.
You don't have to say that name.
I'll turn off the light.
There are six of us.
What are we going to do?
Is it possible that all of us are safe?
You can do it again.
Do it again?
If it's safe, isn't it okay?
No, it's okay.
If you do that, you won't be in the picture.
I'm in the picture.
You're going to put out the DVD, right?
I'm not going to put out the DVD.
I won't put it out.
I won't buy it.
There's nothing we can do about it.
There's no way to do it.
Come on.
Why don't you take two?
Why?
There's no way to do it with one.
All right, then.
I'll do it for fun.
Can I see it?
You can see it for yourself.
It doesn't look like it's going to work.
I'll just show you this.
Just take it off.
I wanted to do this.
Hey, play.
That's not good.
That's not a good way to say it.
I'm counting on you.
Hey, are you really going to draw it?
Oh, here it comes.
I did it.
Safe.
One more time.
It's cut off.
What are you going to do if you get three this time?
That's safe, right?
Let's end it here.
Give me a chance.
They say there are three passes, but let's do it three times.
What if you can't do it in three times?
Why did you become the host?
I just did what I wanted to do.
I'm counting on you.
One more time.
It's three times.
Wait a minute.
Three times.
Two times.
Who is it?
It's you.
No, no, no.
What should I do?
I don't like you.
What?
What about me?
I don't like you.
Go home.
You guys can go home, too.
Can I go home?
Wait a minute.
I don't like you.
You guys can go home.
You...
You are the wife of a producer.
I can't help it.
Wait a minute.
This has nothing to do with the game.
Let's have a little kiss.
It's not related to the game.
Let go of me.
I can't believe it!
What are you looking at?
I can't feel my strength anymore!
Hamada-san!
Hamada-san, come back!
Masumasa!
I can't believe it!
I can't feel my strength anymore!
You're dead.
Where am I?
You're all being sucked in.
Cut!
Please give me a name that will become popular in 20 years.
I think that in 20 years, names will be gone.
That's a great thing to say.
What are you going to do if you don't have a name?
What?
You won't be able to ask for it.
Like Matsumoto-kun.
Ah, yes, yes.
You won't be able to call me Hitoshi-kun.
Yes, yes, yes.
Recently, everyone has become really greedy.
For example, even with a cell phone,
one person is no longer a thing.
It's natural to have two.
Also, a sidecar.
A sidecar?
A second car?
There aren't many people who ride a sidecar.
No, no, no.
I knew right away when you said it.
I knew it was wrong.
But I knew it was the same speed as everyone else.
So it's totally fine.
Everyone has become really greedy.
Yes, yes, yes.
They've become greedy, and in the future,
the Japanese population will continue to grow like it did before.
That means there won't be any more.
But in order to circulate the economy,
having two people is absolutely necessary.
I see.
Yes.
Especially as it gets older.
It's fine.
It's fine to have a name.
So, Hiroshi or Takashi.
Takashi.
Mitsuko or Kyoko.
Hello, I'm Tanaka Mitsuko or Kyoko.
At first, you said your name was going to disappear.
That's why, at some point,
at some point, the actress suddenly changed her name.
She suddenly changed her name.
You said your name was going to disappear,
so you kept thinking about it.
That's not half of the story.
Why is that?
That's strange.
What kind of cafe is that?
What do you mean by that?
It's all a cafe.
Well, it will definitely be like that.
Also, Taro of Jiro.
That's a bit too much.
What do you mean by of Jiro?
Are you stupid?
Yes.
If Sato.
What do you mean by of?
What do you mean by that?