Good evening, everyone.
Actually, today, I have a sad announcement to make to all of you who are watching this musical instrument.
We have been playing this instrument for the second time since it started.
Yamasaki Hosei is going to graduate from this program with this broadcast.
We did something like a prank just a year ago, didn't we?
After a year, I realized that it was really going to be like that. It was as if I had foreseen it before. I still don't understand it.
Well, he's a senior to Kokoriko.
He taught me a lot of things that kids can avoid, so I wanted to learn more.
Today's star is Yamasaki Hosei.
Hello.
As Matsumoto said, I think that the people who are watching the TV right now are probably surprised to hear that you are graduating from this program.
Yes.
What is the reason?
He said it was the end of the program.
I see. What is the reason for the end of the program? I hope you can tell that to the people who are watching the TV.
It's been 14 years since I started being an entertainer.
My wife, Aya, and I have been talking about various things.
My wife is very anxious. She's worried that I won't be able to use her.
I heard that she was very anxious.
She's very anxious.
So you're not going to quit?
No, I'm not going to quit.
What?
I'm not going to quit.
It's going to be a little long, but is it okay?
Yes.
I heard that your senior, Mr. Kiyashino, finished eight regular programs this spring.
I was very jealous.
Why?
Because he was very slim.
What?
You don't have to quit.
That's why I don't feel like the story is ending halfway.
Well, let's start from here.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
I don't like this kind of thing.
That's right.
Have fun.
This is the best five that he chose.
Let's take a look at it.
Yes, please.
This program is brought to you by the sponsor you are watching.
Hosei Yamasaki, 34 years old.
It's been 12 years since we spent time with you.
You've been on the show for 12 years, and you've given us a lot of laughter and excitement.
This is the season when cherry blossoms fall.
This program is brought to you by the sponsor you are watching.
Hosei Yamasaki, the master of children.
Fifth place, Hosei Yamasaki vs. Oonishi Jimmy.
What?
There was a person who was said to be your enemy.
Yes, it's Oonishi Jimmy, Yoshimoto's senior.
They always quarrel when they meet.
The two of them are now nostalgic memories.
Stop it, stop it.
Don't drink this.
Why did you kick me?
I was breathing.
You're already a middle school kid.
Stop it, stop it.
You're a middle school kid, so you have to drink like this.
You're a middle school kid.
Stop it, stop it.
Stop it.
Fourth place, Hosei Yamasaki goes back to his hometown.
When I went to the apartment, it was like this.
What are you doing?
When we saw you changed, we couldn't hide the same color.
We all went to the mountains to return you.
Are you surprised?
You bastard.
What are you doing?
You're a coward now.
You bastard.
Third place, Goodbye Hosei Yamasaki.
I was really surprised when I heard that you were going to quit the program a few years ago.
But this was a prank on you who likes pranks.
Yamagawa.
I won't stop using kids.
What did you say?
I won't stop, I won't stop, I won't stop.
Never.
Parfait is a rabbit.
That's right.
Do you know how much you look like a rabbit?
I think it's my chance now.
Look at the other side.
Yamagawa, you're amazing.
2nd place, Yamasaki Hosei vs. Moriman
You had another opponent, right?
Yes, it's Moriman, who has won many famous matches
In the end, he couldn't win even once, but he always made us have fun
1st place, Yamasaki Hosei vs. Moriman
Your sudden marriage announcement really surprised me
And we all watched your moving wedding ceremony
1st place, Yamasaki Hosei vs. Moriman
It's a very beautiful video
Even if you play it in a song, it won't look like this
No way!
Where did you get this?
1st place, Yamasaki Hosei vs. Moriman
The laughter and emotions you gave us will be deeply engraved in our hearts
Goodbye, and thank you for the memories
1st place, Yamasaki Hosei vs. Moriman
It's 5th place from 1st place that you chose
Last year, there was a prank
It was a bit ironic
Now, I'd like to say goodbye to the producer, Mr. Suga
Yamaguchi, thank you very much for the past 13 years
Thank you
I'm sorry for saying such rude things on the show
I have very complicated thoughts about having a child next month
I don't need anyone I don't need on the show
I can't help it
I can cut off the circle of using the child
I'd like you to cut off the circle on the Japanese TV
I'd like you to do your best in other songs
Thank you very much
I think Mr. Suga was trying to make you laugh
Please understand that
This is the last time, so let's say goodbye
Thank you very much
I'd like to learn more from you
This is the end of the prank
See you next time
Thank you
It's not that I can't see you
Thank you for your hard work
In my case, I can't see you anymore
Please do your best
It was a new family
I'd like you to be friends with my new family
Finally, I'd like to say goodbye to Mr. Yamasaki
I'd like you to say goodbye to Mr. Yamasaki
Here you go
Mr. Yamasaki
Do you think you can get a lot of flowers?
I love you
I'm thinking about a lot of things
I'm sorry
I don't know what to say
Mr. Yamasaki, do your best
Thank you very much
I don't know what to say
The title of the program was wrong
I don't know the truth
It's over
I heard that he went abroad and became a gay
Let's be careful
Mr. Yamasaki, don't be a child
Everyone, are you surprised?
I thought I could stop because I did drugs this time
This time, I asked Mr. Kokori and Mr. Yamasaki to do a prank
Mr. Yamasaki, don't be a child
Everyone, are you surprised?
The wind blows and the flowers fall
Even if you get wet in the rain, the flowers will fall
If it's a blooming flower, it will fall someday
It's the love of the same fate
I don't know what to say
Mr. Yamasaki, don't be a child
He asked me to do the same thing last time
I want to do it again
What is the meaning of this?
Nothing
What does he want to do?
I want to continue with this and Moriman
I'm scared
I don't know if I can stop
I think it's a defense
Let's go
Mr. Yamasaki is immortal
I'll do it again
Before the recording of the talk that ended with the audience
Matsumoto also jumps out of the venue
For the time being, he returns to the dressing room
Mr. Hamada, are you okay?
The emergency situation that even the elevator will stop
What is Hamada doing on the 8th floor?
It's pitch black
Hamada was okay
It's been 30 minutes since the power went out
The audience can't hide their anxiety
At that time, behind the scenes
Lighting is impossible
This is the only battery
Mr. Yamasaki, please
Mr. Yamasaki
Calm down
It's okay
To reassure the audience
Mr. Yamasaki goes to the stage
Everyone
The building itself is out of power
I thought everyone was scared
I came with courage
In a little while, Mr. Downtown will come out
Please wait a little longer
Thank you
I'm sorry
Mr. Yamasaki
Who is this person?
The whole area is out of power
At times like this, the information will go out of control
Please calm down
I came in to see
Mr. Hamada was trapped in the elevator
There is no such thing
Mr. Hamada
Where are you going?
It's pitch black
I'll be surprised if you go down
Why?
Well
An unprecedented event happened
The signal has stopped
The monitor is almost pitch black
It's almost pitch black
You can't play 30 minutes like this
That's right
I recorded the opening
I'll use it
What?
I can see you
I can't see you on TV
I can only talk about scary things
You were on the 8th floor of the school, right?
Yes
You were trapped in the elevator
I was on the stairs
At times like this
Do you know the feeling of being a man?
I was surprised
The window of the school was closed
The window was closed
I don't know why I opened the window
I thought he was going to run away
I thought he was going to die
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.