Chikitsuki Forest Project!
Is the Demon King asleep?
You should be more motivated from the opening.
It's just a movie.
Even if it's a late night show, it's not like that.
It's not like that.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
It's a dodgeball match between 500 people vs 500 people.
How much time does it take to dodgeball?
It's from a viewer.
Miki Satoru.
Miki Satoru from Hachioji City.
I want to give him a T-shirt.
Don't do that.
I don't know if Satoru will give me a T-shirt or not.
I'll be in a bad mood.
Don't do it.
I'll do it.
I don't know what's going on.
Next, Lotte Kawasaki Stadium.
Why do we have to meet Lotte?
It's a human dominos tournament.
What are we going to do?
Are we going to line up?
Yes.
Then we'll go one by one.
That's dangerous.
We're going to show that to the Laffy Nose.
That's scary.
I've already forgotten.
Next, 1000 people home drama.
What about this?
There's a drama with 1000 people?
There are already about 30 fathers.
The one who plays the father?
The one who plays the father is already 30.
The one who plays the mother is 50.
If you don't do that, there won't be 1000 people.
I think it's going to be fun.
It's going to be fun.
Next.
Let's call the UFO.
So we're all going to call the UFO?
The way to call the UFO.
How do you call it?
I don't know if it's going to be a gong show.
Let's do it without expectations.
If you don't do it, you'll be disqualified.
That's a stupid thing.
If 1000 people do it over and over again,
the aliens will bring garbage and do it.
Let's call the UFO.
It's better not to see it.
Let's make a promotion video.
I'm participating in 1000 people.
We've been doing a lot of things in the world.
We've been doing a lot of things for 10 years.
At the end, 1000 people will make fun of us.
The ending song that Mr. Yami Ozaki told me about will play in the back.
I see.
Depending on the script, I think I can take it off.
If it's necessary?
Yes.
If it's this work?
I think it's okay to look at it at the end.
It's 10 years, right?
About once.
Last.
Put your butt out.
I say that if you put your butt out, it will be a mountain.
If you put your butt out, it will smell like the poop of a streamer.
You can't smell it with a streamer.
If there are 1000 people.
Let's get rid of what we don't need.
This is a little better.
It's dangerous.
I don't know what this means either.
It's dangerous to walk.
What about this?
Should I leave this?
Leave it.
How many cents do you have?
It's like a piece of sense.
It's like a promotion.
This is a little expensive.
This is expensive.
Yes, it's expensive.
You can't throw this away either.
It will cost money.
Certainly, it will cost money.
I can't get rid of it with this.
Why can't you get rid of it with this?
This is also expensive.
It's a big deal, isn't it?
Yes.
You can't enter the stadium.
I can't ask people to give me money.
It's 1000 yen for 500 yen, isn't it?
I can't do that.
You want to eat grilled squid, don't you?
What are you doing?
That's my money.
That's why I can't do that.
Come on.
One drink, one food.
Which of these two?
This one seems to be more exciting.
This is not exciting.
It's like putting out your butt and saying,
Hey, it's over.
That's right.
I don't have such an interesting butt.
That means.
Let's go with this.
What?
A dodgeball match between 500 people and 500 people.
This is the guy who lost.
That's fine.
But women can't enter the stadium.
That's right.
What are you going to do?
Don't be funny.
It's a penalty game that women can play.
It's a penalty game that 1000 people can play.
Right on the spot.
It's a penalty game that 500 people can play.
I see.
I don't want to cry.
Now that we've wasted some time,
let's play with 1000 people.
Let's play with 1000 people.
Why do you want to play with 1000 people?
Look, I'm Lupin-san.
How many times have you seen this kid?
I'm Lupin-san.
If you do this normally,
It's totally like Lupin.
What do you mean?
It's like putting out your butt and saying,
Hey, it's over.
That's right.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
Excuse me.
There's something happening in the program.
It's a little late, isn't it?
This guy, Shomei-san, is a girl,
but he fell from the stairs.
No, no, no.
I was really surprised by that.
What is it?
I'm not surprised.
You know, he always has a camera here
before he comes out.
He's taking pictures with his sleeves.
You know, before he comes out.
And Shomei-san is a girl,
and he's doing this with both hands.
I said,
Yuruya, I'm going to squeeze you.
Why are you saying that?
Why are you squeezing me?
She's illuminating you.
Yuruya, you're a moon.
It's the sun!
He fell down the stairs.
We were like, are you ok?
And he was like...
That was so sad.
Did he spin once?
Where did he go?
Poor guy.
Sorry.
Then the
Seiri left for a while again.
Idiot!
He did a triple spin!
Giiiin-chan!
Gin-chan!
Why?
Yasuka!
You can't do this anymore.
What?
You have to show your warm side.
I don't care about my warm side.
What do you mean?
You always show your warm side.
Where do I show my warm side?
Hey!
I did my best.
You'll go home soon, right?
Yes, I'll go home soon.
I'll stay until the end.
I'll shake hands with everyone.
No matter how many times you do it,
if you do it once, you'll be late.
If you do it three times, you'll be late.
If I do it again, you won't show your affection?
You won't show your affection?
Hey!
Sorry, it was my fault.
It was your fault.
I showed my affection.
You showed your affection.
The other day, I didn't do much,
and I don't like gambling,
but for the first time in a long time,
I won a lottery.
It was a big lottery.
There was good information.
Well, there were two,
but I won 50,000 yen each.
Yes, yes, yes.
You're a fool, aren't you?
This is what happened yesterday.
In the end, I did it all.
I won 3 million yen.
It's 23 million yen!
Hey!
Hey, are you late?
I'll call you.
It seems that there is a way to understand something.
I have a little bit of foresight.
Don't you?
You can't say that you're a fool.
No, no, I really have a little bit of foresight.
I live in the tower of Babylon.
You're a fool.
No, no, I really have a little bit of foresight.
I have a little bit of foresight.
Everyone has a little bit of foresight.
Has anything happened so far?
There was a time when I ate a little too much.
No!
I'm getting fat!
You know that, don't you?
I have a little bit of foresight.
Does your previous life know anything about you?
Oh, me? I don't know anything about me.
I was wondering if you knew anything about me.
I know about your teacher.
Aoki sensei.
I don't know anything about you.
I don't care about this.
It's just a little thing.
Everyone thinks that humans are the best.
But humans are not the best.
Don't you think so?
Is there anything better than humans?
I don't know. Try it.
I just don't know.
There must be more fun animals.
I'm just flying high.
It feels so good.
I feel like I'm having sex all the time.
I can't stand it. It feels so good.
Sometimes I get stuck in shit.
I can't stand it.
It feels so good.
That's all I can think of.
For example, crying.
This is what God decided.
He gathered all these animals.
I can't talk to you.
Why? Why?
Wait, wait.
Don't be in a hurry.
Why? Why?
Wait, wait.
Don't run away.
You're going to be called a cheater.
I'm not going to run away.
I thought about it.
I'm going to make you cry.
What? What?
What about me?
You can decide for yourself.
First of all, I'm going to have a dog.
You should have said that.
I'm sorry, but I don't let anyone have a dog.
I'm going to have a dog.
The one who says the most is the winner.
That's enough.
You have a dog.
I'm going back.
Run away!
Who is it?
It's me.
A cat came out.
Everyone decided for themselves.
Who are you?
I'm an elephant.
I'm the elephant.
There was a guy in the book who was bullied.
What are you going to do?
Hurry up and decide.
We don't have time.
Everyone decided for themselves.
What are you going to do?
You can't do anything about it.
I think humans still have something.
But humans may be able to fly.
There may be some kind of code.
No one has found it.
If you do it three times, you may be able to fly.
But you haven't flown so far.
Don't you want to fly?
It would be nice if I could fly.
It's natural.
How nice would it be if a comedian could fly?
Don't you think so?
If you fly when you fall, you'll get hit.
It would be interesting to use that way.
It would be interesting.
My prediction is right.
You haven't said it yet.
Make a prediction.
For example, I know when the earthquake will come.
What's the magnitude?
Magnitude.
What?
It's magnitude.
It's called magnitude.
It's coming.
How big is it?
It's as big as a disaster.
That's great.
The Earth is in trouble.
If you noticed, there was an Eskimo sitting next to it.
That's terrible.
It's terrible.
I don't know much about it.
The Eskimo is here.
What is it?
I don't understand one word.
I'm sorry. I didn't study enough.
What is Eskime?
Eskimo, Eskime, Osukime.
You said it.
Hello.
Are you from Ippan today?
I'm a girl from Ippan.
Her name is Eri Kobayashi.
She is 21 years old.
She is from Aichi Prefecture.
What are you doing now?
Are you unemployed?
No.
I went to Eikawara School.
Eikawara School?
Let me talk to her.
What?
Let me speak in English.
How are you?
I'm fine. Thank you.
You are quite successful.
Where?
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I received this.
This is a message from a person who is a double matcha poop.
A guest from the first or second time of the program, which was broadcasted on TV from 12 o'clock on Saturday night,
was on the show.
We were on the show.
My acquaintance is a member of that program.
He said this about the program.
They are very rude,
and they are both late.
They are not good.
Do the staff of the program think the same way?
Do you think so?
Do you think so, Saku?
Be more polite.
I do.
You should never make a mistake in your greeting.
What?
Is that so?
First, look at the person.
When you look at the person,
you should analyze the person in your head.
You are a robot.
You can see the person.
You should not make a mistake in your greeting.
That's right.
You should make a mistake in your greeting.
You should say,
You are my friend.
You should not make a mistake in your greeting.
You should have the energy of a friend.
Do you use that energy?
Of course.
For example,
you should say hello to a friend.
You should say hello to the guy who is a double matcha poop.
That's right.
Really?
In Otomo version.
Otomo.
I'm AD Otomo.
I'm analyzing now.
Good morning, Otomo.
Did you say that once?
Next.
It's normal.
Who's next?
Saito, our chief director.
That's AD Otomo.
That's because he's the chief director.
Good morning, Saito.
Did you say that once?
I can't pull even one page with one piece of paper.
Let's go.
It's a bit long today.
I love Yamazaki from Team Zero.
He's cool no matter what he says.
Don't you think he's fashionable?
Please give him more opportunities to appear on TV.
Please.
That's what he said.
Really?
He moved recently.
That's amazing.
I was surprised when I went to see him once.
There's a road like this.
When the road is like this, there's a door here.
This is the room.
That's because there's a staircase next to the road.
No, it's just a door.
So be careful when you sleep at home.
There's a car running.
There's no fence or anything.
No, no, no.
Really?
Only the window is big.
The one on the back?
No, not the back.
There's a big window here.
Next to the door?
It's transparent.
If you go in there...
It can't be transparent.
It's transparent.
Really?
He doesn't have money, so he doesn't have a curtain.
You can't see anything.
That's right.
When he stopped and tried to think,
I thought he was a mannequin.
I thought he was a show window.
He came to me like, where are you?
Now, let's go to the Yamazaki house.
Let's go to Yamazaki house with the kids.
I'll laugh.
Yamazaki house home tour.
Home tour.
I'll laugh.
I'll be surprised.
Anyway, that's it for today.
That's right.
It's enough.
What are you doing?
Do some Japanese dance.
What?
Japanese dance.
You...
Japanese dance...
You do it.
Japanese dance.
Do some jazz dance.
What do you want?
Jazz dance.
What?
When I entered Yoshimoto, I was told to do jazz dance.
Jazz dance?
Yes.
It's strange.
I can do this and that.
Yes.
Do it with switch.
You...
Why do you do this?
I did it.
Do you know why I do this?
It's like that.
This is...
Ah!
Yes.
This has a seed.
It's like that.
It's made like that.
Does it stick all the time?
Yes.
Ah, it didn't come today.
It's off today.
Oh, it stuck.
It stuck.
Wait a minute.
It was late.
This is a bean ball.
I'll put it in here.
Wait a minute.
Wait.
What?
You...
Does it stick all the time?
You shouldn't do that.
What are you talking about?
Do it.
Everyone, you should cooperate.
Cooperate with this guy.
I see.
This guy...
This guy was a bean ball.
If this guy comes off, everyone will be in trouble.
Yes.
What?
Do you understand?
Hello.
Masato-kun.
You asked me to give you a T-shirt.
I wrote this for a week.
Yes.
I took a look at it.
There's a girl who wants this.
Oh, really?
If you can draw so beautifully,
you should draw on a white T-shirt.
You should make it yourself.
It's enough.
I did it at the opening.
1000 people.
It's an event.
500 people versus 500 people.
It's a dodgeball.
That's right.
It's an event, but the place is decided.
The girl is a goalkeeper.
I'll give you a Hachimaki.
Oh, Mach-chan, Jimu, Hama-chan.
That's right.
What about the guy?
I'll give you a jersey.
That's good.
The girl is definitely a goalkeeper.
Yes.
Nice to meet you.
The assistant is my person.
It's all the same.
The place of the dodgeball is decided.
The losing team has to play a penalty game.
I'll tell you what the penalty game is later.
That's it.
Hachimaki is the most important thing.
Thank you for watching.