Today, we're going to do another prank.
Today's prank is...
I think this is the first time we've done something like this.
Please explain.
Today, Team Zero's...
He's going to do it.
From now on, our program...
He's the director of the Japanese TV.
He's going to bring two people a month and three people in total.
He's a great person.
I think he's doing a great job.
I think he's going to do a great job.
And then...
He found a guy named the director of the Japanese TV.
He said,
By the way, have you ever killed someone with a stick or something?
I'm a little interested in it.
Can you do it for me?
He said,
I'm going to do it while saying that.
Actually, the director of the Japanese TV.
He's Zero.
He's the devil of the director.
And when he sees that, he's going to do it again.
What's going to happen?
This is going to be fun.
It's going to fly twice.
The director of the Japanese TV.
Today, we're going to do the director of the Japanese TV.
First of all, I'd like to thank the director of the Japanese TV.
Basically, I'd like to thank the director of the Japanese TV.
And I'd like to bring the product to the director of the Japanese TV.
It's just changed last year.
It's a copy of Morobare.
You're laughing.
Basically, this is not a company.
It's a company called KINK.
I really ask you.
It's easy to ride.
I'm afraid I'll have to skip the show.
But if you bring it to me, I'll be right back.
That's right.
Thank you.
Good job.
I'll pay you.
Thank you.
Mr. Okada is too good.
That's good.
It's a copy of Morobare.
Thank you.
I'll pay you.
Mr. Downtown.
You have been actively cooperating with our regular program downtown.
I would like to thank you for your sincere effort and consideration.
Mr. Ishikawa is the director of the company.
Thank you.
Mr. Okada is the director of the company.
Mr. Downtown.
I'm glad to see you.
You are crazy.
I'm a member of the team.
I'm an actor.
You can watch it at the opening of our show.
At the opening?
Yes.
No, I don't watch other shows.
Do you have a regular show?
It's a live show of Dantan from TBS.
TBS?
Yes.
I watched it!
Thank you.
It was fun.
Oh, this?
I skipped it.
What should I do?
You skipped it?
No, I can't do it.
You can't do it?
The teacher is right behind you.
Teacher?
I have a lesson.
A lesson?
Yes.
It's for two days.
What?
Do you want me to do it?
No, no.
Then someone else will do it.
No, no, no.
This is a sad journey.
No, I can't do it.
No, no.
The teacher is there too.
If the teacher is there, you can do it.
I can do it.
I want to practice for about an hour before the actual performance.
I want to practice.
Go ahead.
No, no, no.
Oh, no.
I can't do it during the actual performance.
No, no.
I'll do it.
You can't do it.
I'll try to hit you.
Idiot!
Come here.
I didn't do anything.
You didn't do anything.
No.
I'll hit you harder.
Are you okay?
Come on.
Idiot!
I'm glad.
I thought it was bad, but it was fun.
It was easy.
I'm flying around here.
Really?
There's no such thing.
It's funny.
Hello.
How are you doing?
I'm sorry I'm dressed like this.
You're good.
What do you think?
People are happy about other people's misfortunes.
What do you mean?
I've been doing this show for years.
I think the punishment game is the best.
I see.
I want to see how ugly you are.
I like to see people suffering.
You do it at the end of the year.
When the camera sees you, it's like you're drowning.
Or when you're saved by a helicopter.
It's really fun.
My mother loves animals.
When a deer is chased by a leopard,
I tell it to run away.
But it doesn't have a smile on its face.
When a deer runs away, it screams.
When a deer runs away, I tell it to run away.
You don't have to tell it to run away.
It doesn't have a smile on its face.
I tell it to run away.
When a deer is caught, it screams.
I tell it to look at me.
My father is next to me.
We are looking at each other.
I'm happy.
It's easy to increase the ratings of the TV.
It's a condition.
If I suddenly do something funny here,
I'll be in trouble.
If I suddenly do something funny, I'll be in trouble.
52%
A lot.
Really.
Food.
And then...
Food, animals, children.
I take care of these things.
That's enough.
That's right.
That's why I always see a guy like Mutsugoro.
He can do special effects.
He doesn't do anything.
He just takes care of himself.
That's right.
He is the king of Mutsugoro.
Food and animals win.
The best thing is that Mutsugoro can't be eaten by animals.
Really.
I'll see.
85%
Mutsugoro will be eaten.
I don't know.
Really.
That's right.
That's the most fun.
Unfortunately, I'm very angry.
Who are you?
The other day...
I don't think you should hit a normal citizen.
Why?
There are times when you really want to hit him.
That's right.
That guy...
Shut up!
I'm next to you.
Don't touch me.
What?
What do you want?
Who are you?
I don't care at all.
Hurry up and call me.
Where are you going?
I can't hide anymore.
I'm coming.
Come out.
I'm really angry.
I was really angry on the Shinkansen the other day.
I didn't sleep.
I slept on the Shinkansen for three hours and arrived in Osaka.
I had no choice but to sleep on the Shinkansen.
When I sat down, there was a pig next to me.
When I arrived, I started to sneeze.
The moment I saw it, I started to sneeze.
The moment I arrived, I started to sneeze.
That's what I said.
That doesn't matter.
I started to sneeze before I went to bed.
What are you talking about?
You're crazy.
I said, I'm going to sneeze.
The pig started to sneeze.
I remembered something.
I said, I'm going to sneeze.
The pig started to sneeze.
A man with a knife came and started to sneeze.
I thought it was annoying.
But it was in five seconds.
The pig started to sneeze.
And did like this and did like that for a while
And then again, he т dis
And took the abOLD
So that guy.. was he young powder?
íamos a bandana, I given up
But who are we talking to!
Even if asked it's troublesome
He was hitting middle school student
How can that guy allow that?
Ah, but he's a highschooler
If I were a middle schooler, I would've hit them with a bang!
You're a high schooler!
If I did that, you would've definitely been beaten up!
Well, I didn't hit them with a bang.
Apparently, I hit them with my head.
Even so, they're still allowed to do it, right?
No, it's like this. Everyone's like, do your best!
And they're naked.
I don't know why.
They're naked all year round!
And they're like, do your best!
I really wanted to hit them with a bang!
Everyone's discriminating against animals.
It's the same with this show.
If you bully a dog,
if you grab a dog by the chest,
everyone will call you.
What are you doing to a dog?
And they'll say, Kataeya, what are you doing?
Marimo, if you kick them like this,
no one will call you.
What kind of setting is this?
Why is Marimo good, but not good with dogs?
Animals aren't cute.
Marimo isn't cute.
What are you talking about?
They're just staying still.
They're just fluffy.
That's right.
They just look fluffy.
They're cute.
If you do this to a dog, they'll come to you.
But they're not cute.
They're just fluffy.
Marimo will come to you if you do this.
Will she?
She will.
She won't.
You've never done it before, right?
I've never done it before.
Do you understand?
You guys...
You don't know much about Marimo.
I don't know anything about her.
If you do this,
if you do this,
if there's an enemy,
you're stupid.
When you're sleeping,
does your body suddenly shake?
It does.
What's the meaning of that?
Is it someone's doing?
It is.
I fall from a high place.
I usually fall from a cliff.
I know a lot about dream fortune-telling.
What does it mean?
I've never heard of it.
The width is like this.
It's a cliff.
I'm walking like this with this width.
I'm going like this,
but in the end, I fall.
That's why I kick the stove and wake up.
It's like this.
You shouldn't walk on a narrow place.
It's like that.
Are you stupid?
Who is it?
I'm hungry.
You should wait.
You can go anytime.
I've been waiting for a while.
I can't break it.
I'll let you go to the first place.
I'll let you go to the second place.
Where do you want me to go?
What's coming?
Why do animals have tails?
They get in the way when they poop.
They get in the way when they pee.
Why do they have tails?
They don't get in the way.
But you have to lift it up.
Lift it up.
Should I say this?
I don't think they get in the way.
Why do they have tails?
They get in the way a little.
They get in the way,
but it's more convenient than getting in the way.
That's why they're standing.
What is it?
Say it.
When you're walking, your tail goes down, right?
That's what you say, right?
Yeah.
That's a static-free hat.
In here.
In the truck.
If you don't have that, you'll get in trouble.
That was funny.
That was okay, right?
Yeah.
It happens sometimes.
I see.
I really want you to study.
I want you to take a note and read it tonight.
I mean it.
I want you to take a note and read it.
I want you to sketch the people who came to see it.
What's the point of sketching us?
There are foxes named after animals.
In this case, the fox is more important,
so it's in front of the monkey.
That's the reason.
Isn't one of them taking more?
What do you mean?
Oh, I see.
The fox's part is more important than the monkey's part.
That's a little different.
Is that so?
Then what is it?
For example, there's U-chan and Nan-chan.
Nan-chan and U-chan are good.
That's why it's U-chan and Nan-chan.
This is standing position.
This is the standing position of a fox monkey.
Hello, I'm a fox monkey.
That's why it's a pin.
It's not a combination.
It's a pin, so it's a fox monkey.
What do you mean by standing position?
This is a fox.
There's only one of them.
You're a fool.
When the earth was born,
and the life was settled,
what are you talking about?
At first, foxes and monkeys didn't exist like this.
At first, it was only foxes and monkeys that were combined.
Originally, the two of them were doing the story.
Right?
Sorry, sorry.
They were saying that the fox monkey was weak.
Who?
They won until the third week.
Then the fifth week passed because of the fox monkey.
I'm getting tired of myself.
That's it.
In the past, people had to make their teeth black when they got married.
They had to make their teeth black when they got married.
What does that mean?
Why are they black?
It's because they have black teeth.
When I saw him close his mouth, I thought he was a woman.
When I tried to talk to him, he laughed.
It's not good.
His teeth are black.
I thought it was a woman.
He said, I will serve you enough to pull out my teeth.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I got angry because of that.
Call me.
Call me your servant.
What are you holding on to?