Oogiri Dai is here!
Recently, when I'm walking around town, people ask me,
Who's the Gorilla Man?
I'm often asked this question.
Is there anyone who knows who the Gorilla Man is?
I don't think so.
Unfortunately, I can't answer this question.
Today, we have the Oogiri Dai.
I'm your host, Hamada Masatoshi.
Let's get started!
Hanashikas, please come on stage!
First, please introduce yourself.
Recently, when I was walking down the street,
I met Mr. Takamida of ALFIE.
He is the world's...
Shut up!
Yamasaki Hosei.
Next, please introduce yourself.
In Hamada-san's bedroom,
Ikumi-chan found something and spoke for the first time.
Baibu...
Team Zero, please come on stage.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Hamada Masatoshi.
What do you want to do?
Sometimes, I want to cheat.
Shut up!
Spring has come.
In April, I left my job in downtown,
and spring has come to my life.
I'm the manager, Nitta.
Nice to meet you.
Lastly, when I was walking down the street,
I met Mr. Takamida of ALFIE.
He is the world's...
Shut up!
Next, please introduce yourself.
I'm Ayu Eo.
Please say one word at a time.
While saying that word,
please introduce yourself.
What do you want to say?
I...
...am...
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
Give me that.
I'm doing medicine.
Give it to me.
What do you mean by doing medicine?
I thought you were going to continue.
Fine.
The old man was a bit surprised just now.
Now, let's do the other ones.
Ra!
Ra-ri-ru-re-ro!
Now, let's go.
Ra!
It's fun to be blowing the trumpet, but...
Hey!
Hey, Yamazaki-san!
Yes?
What are you doing?
You're blowing the trumpet!
Well, you're a shy bastard.
Ri!
I want to hide Ryu's tattoo.
I don't have it!
Ra-ri-ru!
I don't have enough money to buy a ruby.
Re!
I like racing more than rice.
Ro!
London boots.
It hurts.
Yasu-san, why did you say London boots?
Ah, you didn't know?
I didn't know!
Let's stop doing that kind of stuff.
Now, let's continue.
Please get ready.
Now, let's do the Oricomi-Utagashi battle!
Now, the Oricomi-Utagashi battle.
There are a lot of things you can buy in the market.
Let's sing while doing the Oricomi-Utagashi battle.
Oricomi-Utagashi battle.
Okay?
The music will start.
Let's dance together.
Raise your hand if you're ready.
Now, let's do the Oricomi-Utagashi battle.
Ready, go!
Hurry up!
It's a corner like this.
Why do you keep dancing in the middle of the corner?
I'm tired.
Sing!
Sorry, sorry.
Thank you.
Let's go, Oricomi-Utagashi battle.
Oricomi-Utagashi battle.
Ready, go!
What are you going to do?
I'm going to do the Tawashi dance.
Tawashi dance?
Let's go!
You're just going to do the Tawashi dance, aren't you?
Just like that!
Let's go!
Ready, go!
Now, what are you going to do?
I'm going to dance.
Just like that!
Let's do the Tara dance.
Tara!
Ready, go!
No matter what you do, everyone is dancing.
Just like that!
Now, let's do the Tara dance.
You do the Hoya dance.
You do the Oka dance.
Tara!
Tawashi!
Now, what are you going to do?
I'm going to do the Kisawa dance.
Kisawa dance!
Now, what are you going to do?
I'm going to do the cucumber and papaya dance.
You do the cucumber and papaya dance.
What are you saying?
Now, let's do the last one.
The last one!
I'm going to dance with someone's joke.
Okay!
It's a nice day today.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
Now, let's talk about something.
What?
Recently, you've been busy with work and you don't have your own private time.
Your voice is too loud.
I'm right next to you.
I don't have my private time.
If you have a chance to hang out,
I'll arrange a party for you.
Even if I say I finished early today, it's already 12 o'clock.
It's already 12 o'clock.
The next day was really early.
The next day was already 6 or 7 o'clock.
It was already 6 or 7 o'clock.
I didn't feel safe anymore.
I received my makeup
When I was about to go to sleep, Miku put his bra on.
He's been wearing his bra since 6 in the morning.
He used to do it like this, but recently he's gotten used to it, and he's stopped here.
I don't want to see him like that anymore.
I've become able to do it like this.
What do you think of me?
I didn't watch yesterday's on-air.
I didn't watch it either.
If you keep doing that, you'll be kicked out of the entertainment world.
I'm just saying what I saw.
You were dancing, weren't you?
That's what's wrong with you.
Normally, two people follow each other and one person says something.
Like, hey, hey.
Stop it. Stop it.
I don't think so.
What are you talking about?
It's a twin-turbo.
I won't lose either.
No, that's not it.
Two people follow each other.
The audience is more excited.
Hey, hey.
What's so great about saying, hey?
Stop it.
Two people follow each other.
If one person says something, the other follows.
I don't think so.
I don't look like that.
How are you feeling lately?
My health?
Well, it's the same as usual.
My neck, my back, everything.
I'm tired.
Your body is a little weird, isn't it?
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
It's a little weird.
Normally, if a human has a body, it stretches out and has a neck and a face.
You're like this.
My posture is bad.
Your neck is sticking out like this.
This is...
My posture is bad.
I usually do this.
It's like this, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
If you stretch out your neck, it's like this.
That's right.
You shouldn't be doing this all the time.
You look like you're proud.
I think I'm proud enough every day.
That's my shoulder.
I think so, too.
That's not it.
By the way, I've been feeling a little sick lately.
By the way?
What's that got to do with it?
My body is like this because my posture is bad.
By the way, I have constipation.
What's that got to do with it?
That's why I'm telling you that I haven't lost to you yet.
I'm so frustrated.
There's something like that.
There's jealousy for someone who has a disease like that.
No.
There is.
That's not healthy.
That's right.
That's right, but there's a shadow somewhere.
There's something I admire about that.
You don't have a shadow, but you're creepy enough.
There was something called Okita Soshi.
He had a blood clot.
There's a cool picture of him.
That's right.
I want to get sick, too.
constipation.
It's the first time I've had a constipation.
It's tough.
How many days?
I used to...
I had two days a day.
I didn't even have one day.
I had a few days a day.
Really?
I have a lot of constipation.
If you ask me how much I have.
That's amazing.
It's a secret.
I have to move about four times a day.
That's right.
But each time is a serious battle.
I have a lot of constipation.
It's like a buffalo.
I've never seen a buffalo.
I don't know what kind of buffalo it is.
I don't have one, but it's a secret.
It's a dirty buffalo.
It's like a buffalo.
Each time is a serious battle.
I don't have one, but it's a serious battle.
What kind of face do you have when you have a constipation?
I don't have one at all.
There are times when it hurts.
Yes.
When it's hard.
You're a shy bastard.
When he's a shy bastard.
I want to see his face, but I'm shy.
I'm shy.
It's hard to come out like this.
I can't come out.
I look at you like this.
You look like a daughter of the one who went to the wedding.
Yes.
I look at you like this.
When I have a constipation, I clench my teeth.
I have a lot of constipation this time.
I can't come out, but I can't come out.
I can't come out.
When I went to the wedding, I said,
But I didn't hear anything after I said that.
You're a nobody.
That's right.
I'm not dependable, but I'm dependable.
I see.
Really.
He must be in a hurry.
He's a tough guy.
He is.
You head to a mamajan'sه wall and then have to pose like this!
weißalties can't raise their hips?
They can't, yes.
Should we keep Appai it to grab on to the other tambanist?
The experienced tamanist could use a phew to hold him up.
Yeah, like, that's what Glennum meant.
Well, basically what you need is to do this gesture and then when you lift your hips.
What a useless gesture.
The sir looks happy and registered, though!
Alright, are we ready to roll?
Stop pushing your legs!
You know, like a little Koshikin-chan,
it's like, click, click, like that, right?
Like, go away!
It's like that, right?
Like this, with the hair like this.
Ah, that's it.
Yes, yes.
What do you want to do?
It's fine to write a letter like this.
That's amazing.
Ah, I see.
You know, I was thinking,
in the old days, you know,
there was a game called,
which one of you will win?
Yes, yes, yes.
How about that kind of thing?
Ah, the one where everyone gathers, right?
Yes.
Isn't that kind of interesting?
Gyo-san gathers everyone?
Yes.
That's it.
Defeating dominoes.
What? Defeating humans?
No, that's not it.
Ah, everyone gathers?
Yes, everyone gathers.
That's enough.
Everyone gathers dominoes, right?
That's boring.
But you don't like it,
that kind of skinship with fans, right?
What?
Are you going to tear it up?
Don't say things like that!
You're so annoying!
You know, when you're on location,
there's a location bus, right?
There's a film on it, right?
But the passengers stop and look at it.
So they stop and look at the location,
and when they're done looking,
we try to go back,
and get on the bus,
and from the other side,
you can probably see it,
but they're like,
Ah, Hama-chan, Hama-chan,
and they're doing that,
and in the bus,
they're like,
Let's take a look.
You're so annoying!
That kind of skinship with fans,
I'm going to tear it up!
You're so annoying!
You!
I'm going to return it to you!
Look at it! Look at it!
There's a pig!
I'm going to tear it up!
You're so annoying!
Don't say things like that!
You're the one who's saying it!
I'm going to find it!
Sometimes, when I wave my hand,
Hama-chan,
if I'm on the scene,
remember,
when I wave my hand,
I'm waving it like a fool.
Wait a minute!
That pig is like,
Uhhhhhh!
At first, I thought,
does he have a pig skin?
It's Tsutsumi-moto.
What's that?
Why do you keep saying his name?
No, he's Tsutsumi-moto.
That's right.
Why do you keep saying his name?
No, because I saw Tsutsumi-moto.
Hitoshi Aizu was looking at Tsutsumi-moto.
And then,
Hitoshi Aizu passed it on to Hitoshino.
You!
Did you get it?
Hitoshi Mouse.
I have a question for both of you.
When you see a suspicious person,
you say,
well,
right?
How suspicious can you be?
How can you tell if that person is suspicious?
Please tell me.
That's difficult, isn't it?
Well, yeah.
How suspicious can you be?
If you were in Hokkaido,
you'd think it's suspicious.
You'd think it's dark here.
You'd keep going like this,
taking time trips,
and when you do that,
you can call the police right away.
Right?
Other than that?
For example,
what would you do with a cape on?
That's a suspicious person!
This hand would have become a mecha.
It's not a suspicious person,
it's someone dangerous!
And then,
when you get home,
you'd go like this,
but you don't have any energy.
Yeah.
And then,
This is a telephone line.
What's that?
It looks like a centaur behind you.
Well, that's how it is.
It's perfectly like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's properly made.
It's made of metal. It's made of rubber band.
I can't do this.
Let's do it all at once.
Take a memo of this.
I can't do this.
You said there would be a big earthquake on May 10th on TV.
Now?
Of course.
May 10th.
Really?
Well...
May 14th.
The 11th is Thursday.
Is it my birthday?
There's one thing I want to erase from my memory.
I think it's rude to say this, but...
For example, I can't remember my girlfriend or my family's birthday at all.
But your birthday is on May 11th, so I can't remember it.
I hate it.
Why?
I don't know why I can't remember it.
It's annoying.
What?
You should bring a present to the set at least once.
I'm not your boyfriend.
Do you buy something that looks good on you?
It's funny when I think about it.
When someone asks me if it's a present, I say yes.
That's why I have a ribbon.
I give it to you.
Can I take it?
Can I open it now?
When I play with Karu, their faces turn red.