Gakki no Tsukai's special project, Pichihenge, where comedians put their pride on the line and challenge themselves to make people laugh.
Up until now, many members, as well as comedians and staff, have challenged themselves to this project.
They put their own ideas of laughter and their own sense of humor into it, and have expressed themselves with all their heart and soul.
Among them is that beast in Matsumoto Produce.
Tonight, that person who is currently doing well will be challenging himself.
The first episode of Gakki no Tsukai is brought to you by Chikichiki and Cream Stew!
They say I'm on a roll.
You're on a roll wherever you put it.
But when I look at this, I think, is there anything special about this?
That's what I think.
Why?
Because it's true.
Today's star, please come on out!
I just saw a little bit of Arita tripping over.
This time, it's Cream Stew, but it's Arita.
That's right.
What do you think?
Don't you think the one on top was better?
That's right.
I've seen most of it, though.
You can cry.
It's like he's doing a tsukkomi, and he's going to make up for it with revenge.
I see.
It's very unpleasant to think that he's going to make up for it first.
What do you think, Ueda-kun?
Even if I get a request, I won't do it.
Arita, where do you want to aim for?
I'm a man who aims to be a regular on Gakki no Tsukai.
If I think that way, I think I'll have to take off Tanaka-kun.
You're not a regular around here, are you?
Well, around here, yes.
He'll be done in March, too.
He'll be done in March.
Is that so?
It's really low.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
What should we do?
I'm the second generation K-4.
Hamada Tsuji is the correct answer.
That's right.
This is good.
I heard that you watched the National Assembly.
I didn't watch it.
You were looking at it, right?
I was looking at it.
I didn't watch it.
This is good.
I don't really understand the meaning of this.
What is it?
It means to eat, right?
Do you eat gorillas?
That's right.
I think there's something.
I'm sorry.
I'll be in the room for a while.
I don't want to talk about dinner.
I don't like that either.
I'm in the middle of a meeting.
See you later.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to talk about dinner.
I can't see it.
It's the meat.
I'm sorry.
Get out of here.
He laughed completely.
I'm sorry.
Yamagaki was a little weird.
What is it?
The first one, too.
It was weak.
What?
Can you do it?
Not yet.
I can't do it until I laugh.
Mr. Joshua.
What is it?
Can I talk to you?
Yes.
You won today's game.
How was your opponent?
I was touched.
It's completely different from the opponent.
Didn't you get cut off on the way?
I didn't get cut off.
It's a big deal if I get cut off.
But it's only after I get cut off.
It's only after I get cut off.
I didn't get cut off.
If I get cut off, I can't go home.
I see.
I'm sorry to ask you a private question.
Don't ask me weird questions.
Will you go to the Wind Tribe?
I won't go to the Wind Tribe.
Even if I go, I'll lose weight.
I'll lose weight.
But it's only after I get cut off.
It's only after I get cut off.
If I get cut off, I can't go home.
I won't go.
I'll write it down.
Okay. Thank you.
It's dirty.
I'm watching the story.
That's a lot.
I've been watching that story since I was in high school.
Really?
When I came in, I was embarrassed when I opened my eyes.
I can't get over my fear.
What's in this box?
What is this?
I'll pull it a little more.
I can't do it.
What is it?
Don't pull it.
What is this?
What is it?
It's not.
I'll turn it around.
What is it?
Three times.
Stop it.
What is it?
What about the eyes?
The eyes are big.
This is scary.
What is this?
I see.
You're really into it.
I'm totally into it.
My body is cowardly.
Did you see the chomei?
It's dirty.
It's big.
It really says, what is it?
Is that so?
It even has a question mark.
What is it?
I can do anything if I have energy.
I'm always doing it today.
There is a person who wants to do it.
Come out.
How old are you?
I'm 22.
22.
Put your strength in your stomach.
Let's go.
Come out.
Put your strength in your stomach.
What is it?
You're a girl.
How old are you?
I'm 26.
26.
Put your strength in your stomach.
Come out.
What are you doing?
Let's go.
Put your strength in your stomach.
Don't touch me.
Thank you.
That was close.
2 out of 4 is pro wrestling.
That's right.
I thought it was pro wrestling.
I like pro wrestling.
Pro wrestling is pro wrestling, but not pro wrestling.
Hello?
Ken-chan?
This is Fukubiki.
Come on.
It's late at night.
No, no.
Put it in karaoke.
Salmon flakes.
This song sounds like this.
I found it again.
It starts with a song.
Listen to it.
Ken-chan?
This is Fukubiki.
Can you give me a new album?
I want to listen to it.
Lobby.
Why did you laugh like that?
It's funny.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I see.
Why are you angry?
We're in the middle of a meeting.
I'm going to sing a song at the wedding.
I've decided.
That's good.
Everyone is good.
Why did you decide?
I like the popular songs.
That's good.
I don't care what it is.
Let's practice.
We're in the middle of a meeting.
I don't care what it is.
Let's practice.
I'll sing.
I can't hear you.
I don't care what it is.
I'll sing.
We're in the middle of a meeting.
Let's practice.
I don't care what it is.
I'll sing.
I'm sorry.
I don't care what it is.
I'll sing.
Yama.
Yes.
I did my best.
It's a long song.
I'm popular now.
Please come to the shampoo stand.
Where are you from?
Thank you.
Where is the hair dryer?
Hair dryer?
Is it a hair dryer?
Is it here?
A little more to the left.
A little more.
Is it here?
It's close.
A little more.
Is it here?
It's close.
Is there anything else I can do for you?
I drank my foot roller.
Is it good?
Bring it to me!
What is that!
I'm going to make you laugh.
Let's see.
Here you go.
Thank you.
The total is 짜38,000.
Congratulations!
That's amazing.
짜38,000.
Thank you.
That was close.
The one before was a bit more expensive.
That's right.
Inoki was also a bit more expensive.
Inoki was also expensive.
I wanted to ask you.
What is Fukubiki?
It's a movie called Fukubiki Seikichi.
It's just Fukubiki.
This year is the Asian party!
Hamada's Asian party!
Let me go first!
This year is the Asian party!
Hamada's Asian party!
But as expected, Mama is...
That's amazing.
I can do this for 2 or 3 years.
짜38,000.
I don't really like saying this, but...
Yamagaki has a house.
That's amazing.
I went to see it.
That Yamazaki! That stupid Yamazaki!
He built a house around here!
That's amazing.
He's living there with his stupid wife and stupid child.
Hamada doesn't have any girls, right?
When he has a girl, he's like that.
He has 2 girls.
The older one isn't even 2 years old yet.
He doesn't really care about his wife.
He bought a diaper next door.
I think he's about 1 and a half years old.
To be honest, he's completely naked.
It doesn't really matter.
He's a kid.
It doesn't really matter to me.
Yamagaki, hey.
Oh, you're going to do it there?
I'm going to do it there.
Everyone's going to see it.
Don't show it!
It doesn't really matter.
That guy is funny.
His wife says,
If Momo grows up, will you marry Matsumoto?
He's like,
If Momo grows up and becomes 20, Matsumoto will be 60.
He looks at Yamagaki.
He's not bad at all.
I'm scared of Yamagaki.
If he grows up a little more, what will he do?
What will he do?
I don't know.
Enzo is also a woman.
Everyone is a woman, right?
That's right.
Only Hamada is like this.
But he's like this.
Dad!
Dad, I'm...
Yes, he's a man.
He's like that.
He doesn't smoke.
He doesn't smoke at all.
He has a child and lives in Shinjuku.
Yamagaki doesn't smoke.
He does, but everyone smokes on the veranda.
I'm...
I'm a very careful person.
What?
I don't think everyone understands this.
When I made my juniors,
I was like,
What are you going to bring?
Because I'm a dad.
You think so, right?
I'm very careful.
Really?
I took my juniors with me.
Kimu, me, and the rest of the juniors.
I rented two rooms.
One for my room and one for the juniors.
Kimu's room and two juniors.
I'm in the same hotel as my juniors.
I'm like a woman when I'm sleeping or peeing.
Why?
I'm sorry if I wake you up in a hurry.
Wait a minute.
What are you talking about?
No, no, no, no, no.
That's not true.
That's because you're a fool.
Dad, ah.
That's not true.
Do you think it's going to be popular?
Are you kidding me?
It's true.
And I don't let you sleep.
Why don't you let me sleep?
I'm sorry if I wake you up in a hurry.
What are you talking about?
But the juniors are fine.
I'm going to sleep.
That's what I'm talking about.
On the night of the second day,
When we were having dinner,
I told them that I was this careful.
Kimu was very impressed.
Did you guys hear that?
I told him that I was going to sleep.
Kimu was so happy.
I'm sorry if I wake you up in a hurry.
You guys, get out of here.
And that's what happened.
On the night of the third day,
Kimu and the other juniors were sleeping.
The three of them were sleeping.
I told them that I wanted to go to the bathroom.
I was thinking about what to do.
I was wondering if we should all wake up a little later.
I was wondering what to do for the next hour.
There's a little guy named Hashimoto.
He's little, and he's scared.
He went into the bathroom.
Without making any sound,
Hashimoto came back and said,
I heard what you said yesterday.
I was glad I told you.
I opened the door and I heard you.
He's a shit.
I'm going to throw up.
Kimu.
I can't believe it!
That sound made me fall in love with another girl!
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.