Watch it!
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukaiya, Chiki Chiki Kotsukatsu Combat Fight!
Today, we have a teacher with us.
Everyone's body...
Who is it?
The one with the loudest voice wins?
Yes, simply.
How many points will the three of them get?
Let's see.
Today, Yamazaki-kun and...
Captain.
Captain, look.
Hokurou is holding his neck like this.
I see.
Hokurou's fortune-teller is a leader.
Hokurou is said to be like that.
Now, let's introduce Mr. Sasugawa.
This is Captain Hokurou!
Captain Hokurou is...
He's cutting everyone's body.
And Captain Arato is...
He's a judge.
He's a judge now!
I see.
You're making a duo from a good place.
Don't say that.
Just by touching him, you can tell that he's not in good shape.
Just by looking at him.
Just by looking at him?
By the way, what's the difference between you and me?
What's the difference?
Your head.
I'll go first.
You'll go first?
Let's see how it goes.
Let's start with the neck.
It's good for people with stiff shoulders.
First, there are two on the right.
There are two?
Yes, there are two.
This is one point.
One point?
One point on the left.
There are three points on the neck.
There are three points on the neck?
Yes, there are three points on the neck.
Next, let's move on to the waist.
Good luck hitting me.
I don't know how to do it.
There's one.
There are three points on the neck and one point on the waist.
There are four points on the waist here.
Now ten point for Yamazaki-san.
There are three points on the left and right.
Are there three now?
Yes.
That means there are four more points on the left and right.
That's right.
Really?
olicemment.
K Sar muscles are a bit funny.
There are three points on the neck and the right.
Hamada's ears are weird, and I have a weird head.
You're a great kid.
You've got 8 points.
8 points?
It's easy to get on.
Here I go.
Well, it's one.
One ear.
Get used to it!
You're a plain guy.
Get used to it! Get used to it!
I'll go next.
I'm going to go next.
You're a plain guy.
Hey, wait, you're the best in spring.
Three.
Three?
I'm scared.
Three!
Six, right?
Six?
Yeah, six.
But it feels good.
That's right.
Two.
Two?
Yes.
I'm going to cry.
Come on.
I'm sorry.
Your eyes are bad?
It's 3 now.
It's 3.
It's pocky pocky pocky.
I think there's something wrong with it.
I'm not mistaken.
It's 1 now.
It's pocky pocky pocky.
I don't give up.
It's 4 now.
Can I take it?
Yes.
No, it's 4 now.
It's 4 now.
8 points, now.
Please.
This is the pocky one, isn't it?
The pocky one that takes leadership.
Oh, it's a wet tissue.
Oh, hello, hello.
Well, there's a lot of information.
What kind of information?
There's a rumor that today's guest is quite heavy.
Oh, is that so?
Yes, that's right.
No, but everyone is doing well.
What do you mean by doing well?
Well, normally, you know, it's not like this.
I think it's lame.
No, there's something on it.
Here, here, here.
What's on it?
Oh, I got it, I got it.
Oh, it's coming off.
Something's shining.
What's that?
What is it?
Something.
What?
I ate a bento, chewed gum, ate chocolate.
You're a kid.
You can only eat sweets.
It's crispy and delicious.
Well, today, too.
I'm ignoring my work.
Are you ignoring your work?
I'm just doing my job.
It's no good.
After all, these people are on a regular break.
I'm taking a break.
Yeah.
Well, it's been about two days now, right?
That's why you have a salary.
Why do you have a salary?
Don't underestimate me.
Your salary is about the same as ours.
Really?
I'll quit if I do that.
What do you mean, you'll quit?
It's easier for me to do that.
What?
Can I do it with the same salary as you?
That's a talent.
What are you talking about?
That's no good.
No, it's not.
If you take a break for two days and do it at the same time, it's not a bad thing.
In other words, if these people work without a break for a month and do it at the same time, they'll be satisfied.
That's a little tough.
You're really...
Wait a minute.
If you kill him, it's early in the morning, but if it's in the evening, it'll be over at five or six.
It's over.
You said you'd be done at ten o'clock today.
I'll try it when it's over.
Well, it's too late.
It's too late.
You said you'd be done at ten o'clock, but it'll be over at twelve o'clock.
That's right.
It's early in the morning and late at night.
Stop it.
I don't think you can decide the time.
If you do that, it's over in the morning.
What are you talking about?
In that sense, isn't it good?
That's why it's over in the morning and late at night.
That's all.
That's right.
What are you talking about?
Right now, about 30 salaried men are making about 200,000 to 500,000 yen.
How many times do you want that?
I'm not talking about that.
What do you mean, how many times?
Don't give up.
You're really...
You have a wicked heart.
Stop it.
Wait.
You're a rich man of money.
You're dirty.
What are you talking about?
I don't need any money.
I just want you to laugh at me like this.
What are you talking about?
You're a manager at the scene.
How many hours have you been doing this?
You're a rich man of money.
If the boss of the company comes out, it's okay.
I don't care.
What's that?
As I always say, basically, I talk in front of everyone like this.
Everyone is laughing.
That's all.
I really don't need anything if I have a bowl of rice and a warm futon.
You don't need a warm futon.
That's why I don't need a lot of money.
I get too much from celebrities.
You don't get too much.
The number one is Yoshiko Mita.
She's amazing.
What are you talking about?
How much did she earn last week?
Right?
Don't get me wrong.
Yoshiko Mita doesn't earn that much.
She doesn't earn that much.
I was just singing.
Do you know Yoshiko Mita?
I know her.
Yoshiko Mita, the actress.
How much does she earn?
She earns a lot every year.
That's right.
She doesn't have a lot of money.
No, no, no.
Yoshiko Mita doesn't have a lot of money either.
That's true.
Celebrities earn too much.
Is that so?
That's true.
I'm really on the side of the people.
I'll be running for president soon.
I want to rebuild Japan.
Is that so?
That's right.
Where do you want to go?
What?
What did you say?
Where do you want to go?
Let's go to Tokyo.
Why don't you run for president?
You're still from the Hyogo family.
That's right.
You can ride a car here.
I don't have a lot of money.
What do you mean?
What are you doing?
The microphone is a jumper and the noise is running.
What?
Come up here.
The microphone is a jumper and the noise is running.
Where did you get that voice from?
You should talk more like a man.
Don't think I'm an idiot.
You're going to New York, aren't you?
I'm kidding.
No, listen to me.
I'm not going to New York.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to New York to play dunk.
You're so cool.
What are you talking about?
What?
You're just saying that I can't go because I'm selfish.
No, no, no.
I'm not going to the show.
Next time, I'll ask my ex-wife.
Where is your ex-wife?
There's a show called If You Meet in Dreams.
I'm going to see Nozawa Naoko.
Nozawa is in New York, so we're going to New York to find Nozawa.
You're going to New York, aren't you?
Except you.
I'm not going to New York.
I'm going to see Nozawa.
What are you talking about?
What do you think?
Wait a minute.
I already have a dream of becoming a candidate.
I'm scared when you say that.
I'll tell you this.
I'm a really bad guy.
You're a bad guy.
What color is my blood?
It's green, isn't it?
That's enough.
I hate foreign countries.
Why?
I want to ask you the other way around.
Why do you want to go abroad?
I'm not going to Chibara.
I'm not going to do anything.
I'm just going to have fun.
And I'm going to New York.
I don't like that.
I'm going to ask you what you think.
Golden's two-hour show.
Where's Nozawa?
It's not funny.
No.
Who are you talking about?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm going to stay with everyone.
I'm going to have fun with everyone.
I said I'd have fun shooting a skit.
Don't you think you're more forward?
I want to see you.
I'm not going to run away.
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
I can't do it.
It's cold.
Listen to me.
What are you talking about?
U-chan, Nan-chan, and Mitsu-chan are not like that.
And you are not like that either.
There is something wrong with your feet.
What are you talking about?
Who are you?
You forgot to laugh in the main text.
So?
Are you not laughing now?
Are you the manager of Fujiyama?
No, I'm not.
There is something wrong with that.
Is that so?
Yes, there is something wrong with that.
Everyone is saying yes.
Don't look at me like that.
You are like a fool.
Thank you.
Idols are becoming more and more.
T-Bucks and Girigiri...
This is T-Bucks, right?
Girigiri Girls are becoming more and more.
What will happen to them from now on?
This is a serious story.
They are becoming more and more.
At this rate?
At this rate.
That means...
They have come to a more terrible place.
They look like skulls.
Take them to the doctor.
No, no, no.
They look like skulls.
What is more terrible than that?
I think it's a terrible thing.
Is that a true story?
There are no other stores.
Anyway, they are in magazines.
They are in a good place.
Will they be released?
Probably.
Will there be no more broadcasting code?
Broadcasting code will be improved gradually.
It will be easier to do the next show.
In that sense.
But they are becoming more and more.
It will be natural.
That's right.
In a group of five...
Marudachi...
Let's do it.
It will be natural in that era.
What about the lyrics?
It doesn't matter about the lyrics.
Like Biro Biro Girls?
Yes, yes.
It's Biro.
There are flowers everywhere.
Wow, that's amazing.
It's a combination of men and women.
If there is no dance...
I'm sorry.
Everyone knows the worst use.
Queen.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Sazae went to school.
But he was called to the principal's office.
He was expelled.
Why?
It's time to make money.
Let's go.
I'm wearing a turban.
What are you doing?
Are you riding a horse?
Don't ride a horse.
Let's start with By Happy Hoppy.
Are you a star?
It's strange to hear that.
Tell me five things for a star.
Are you asking me to tell you?
Are there five things?
I don't think so.
There is a saying that if you eat a lot of food, you can't sell it.
That's right.
When I went to eat Okonomiyaki with him, he ate a lot of food.
I don't know his name, but he can't sell it.
I'm very jealous.
I've already finished eating, but my partner's mother changed twice.
That's why I'm jealous.
I'm still doing this in Osaka, but I can't sell it.
I have an idea.
If you don't eat a lot of food, you can't sell it.
That's what I think.
That's the current situation.
That's fast.
It's an hour ago.
There is a saying that time is the most important thing in this world.
There is a saying that human relationships are important.
That's a lie.
That's not true.
Why?
I can't keep time.
There is a limit.
Yes, there is a limit.
No, no, no.
I'm talking to you.
Why?
I don't care if you're late.
Right?
Hey, customer.
There is a limit.
I'm sorry.
It's true.
That's how it feels.
There is a special edition.
April 1st, Thursday.
2 hours from 7 to 9.
Downtown Otoko Mae Yana 4.
It's a punishment game.
Akko-chan is still angry.
It can't be helped. That man lost.
He lost.
I'm sure those who saw Akko lose will understand.
It's a punishment game.
He lost the game.
After that, he got angry.
He said,
Remember Masumoto in front of the camera.
No, you lost the game on your own.
Even if it's my fault.
He's a scary man.
He is.
You're really funny.
I'm angry, too.
He is angry.
Don't look at me.
It's okay.
I'm angry.
Don't look at me anymore.
Go away.
Hey.
What is it?
Thank you.
You...