Now, in the downtown area,
From the Philippines?
No.
We are in Shinjuku.
What are you doing?
Are you from Osaka?
Can you speak a little Japanese?
I can't speak at all, you idiot.
Good evening.
You are younger than the old lady.
I'm older than her.
Do you want it?
Give it to me.
Thank you.
I'll take it.
Can I put it on your chest?
No.
Where can I put it? It's so long.
All right.
This is the first time I've done this.
It's not open.
It's good.
I'll take it.
Thank you very much.
This program,
I'll give you a bouquet of flowers.
Good.
Hey, look at him.
He's walking with his butt out.
Isn't it surprisingly interesting?
What?
A black man comes out of a barbershop.
I'm from Anse.
That's right.
If you want, you can come here.
I'm impressed by the gold leaf that glitters.
This is the comedy theater.
Is it on the fifth floor of this building?
Yes.
This is the comedy theater.
It's the seventh time.
I'd like to know how you're doing.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
I feel like I've been in the city for a long time.
I've been a little off until now.
It's the biggest one so far.
That's right.
The hut.
Isn't it a hut?
There were quite a few customers in Jeju.
That's right.
Everyone is calm today.
There's a lot of people here.
It's like an experimental mall.
It's like saying something funny.
What will happen?
I don't know if it's going to be a hard fight.
There is a boom now.
There is a lot.
It's a little bit of a boom, but it's called a psychic boom.
That's amazing.
Mr. Marikku is still a figurehead.
He's a great guy.
He's just doing that.
Do you know? Well, you know it, don't you?
Recently, Yuigera used to say something like this, right?
Not recently.
Mark.
Just watching.
He just looked at me and did a little, and then...
He threw a cigarette at the endama.
After he threw it, he inhaled it.
It's amazing.
What's with that face?
Put 200 yen in a cup, and if you do something to the bottom, it will fall down.
Anyway, it's amazing that you can break the spoon just by looking at it.
You're a curly pear, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
What's so great about it?
What's not?
You're breaking the spoon, aren't you? You're breaking the spoon just by looking at it.
That's right.
That's right. Why don't you try it? Can you do it?
You're breaking the spoon just by looking at it.
You shouldn't do that.
What?
You shouldn't break the spoon.
No.
You shouldn't do that.
You're breaking it.
Go home and break all the spoons in the house.
You'll get angry.
You're breaking the spoon.
I think you shouldn't do that.
I can't accept it.
Don't do it.
You'll get angry if you look at the spoon maker.
You made it so hard.
You're so surprised.
You have superpowers.
You're so popular that you're going to eat curry all over Japan.
What?
You have superpowers.
You're so popular that you're going to eat curry all over Japan.
I can accept that.
That's right.
What?
Ki.
Everyone knows that I laugh.
He's an old man from Nishino.
Do you know that old man is amazing?
He doesn't touch people.
He's an old man.
He's jumping over the wall.
He's not a normal person.
Judo, Karate, Aikido.
He's a wrinkle.
He's a painter.
He's so strong.
He doesn't touch people.
Ha!
Tunga!
Did this guy call you an old man from Nishino a fool?
Ha?
What?
Did he call you an old man from Nishino a fool?
No.
Then you shouldn't do that.
You didn't do anything.
Don't you feel sorry for being called an old man from Nishino?
Ki.
He's just saying that he'll jump over the wall.
He's a trouble maker.
He's a friend.
He's a person who was thrown over the wall.
If you're so popular that you're going to eat curry all over Japan, what can you do?
You're so popular that you're going to eat curry all over Japan, what can you do?
That's right.
He's talking about Ki.
He's talking about that he'll jump over the wall.
I'll admit it.
If you admit it, I'll admit it.
Everyone will be surprised.
It's over now, but Tsumura Illusion.
Huh?
Did you see it?
He's the only white tiger in the world.
Yeah.
Did you know that?
He's the only white tiger in the world.
I'll get rid of him in an instant.
It's close.
Why?
What's so important about it?
I don't want to erase it forever.
I'll get rid of him in an instant.
It's discrimination.
It has nothing to do with it.
It's strange.
Don't say things you don't mean.
What are you talking about?
I don't like that kind of boom.
You don't like it?
You're talking about the fortune-telling boom, right?
Yeah.
I have a fortune-teller.
It's not about winning.
Fortune-telling is endless.
Even if it starts with a nose fortune-telling,
Seiza,
Tokuro,
Ketsueki,
I like fortune-telling these days.
Fortune-telling is...
What?
You should think about a new fortune-telling.
I'm thinking about it.
This is a boom.
Seiza, fortune-telling, Ketsueki, Tokuro,
These are all new fortune-telling.
New fortune-telling.
What kind of fortune-telling?
Ko-ranger fortune-telling.
What kind of ranger do you like?
How about this?
If you like Momo ranger, what is it?
If you like Momo.
It's the same!
If you like Akari ranger, what is it?
Akari ranger.
You like it so much that you can't speak.
If you like Momo ranger, you like Momo.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about the gourmet boom.
There is such a thing.
So, from a far away, from a countryside.
I think I'll eat the food of the land.
Good evening, everyone.
I am not in a good mood.
Today...
I'm in Gunma prefecture.
Gunma prefecture is a otaku of Mr. Hitoshi Matsumoto.
What will he eat today?
Hello, Masumoto-san.
Good evening.
Thank you for coming today.
Really, how should I put it...
I'm surrounded by this great nature...
In this great environment...
This is a great environment, isn't it, otaku?
No, it's not.
I'm surrounded by this great nature, isn't it?
Isn't it a great environment, Masumoto-san?
Wait, stop it.
Masumoto-san.
Yes?
You can't do that.
The camera is rolling, you know.
What's with that look?
I'm going to hit you.
This is a program, you know.
I'm going up.
Please give it back, as usual.
You can just talk normally.
I'm begging you, really.
I'm going through this in a short period of time.
Good evening, everyone.
Today, I'm Masumoto's otaku.
Hello, Masumoto-san.
Good evening.
You're surrounded by this great nature, aren't you, otaku?
It's not true.
What are you doing?
Wait, stop it.
It's not true.
Is that so?
Be humble.
It's not true if you don't praise me.
I'm begging you.
Again?
Yes, yes, yes.
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening, both you and me.
Good evening.
You're surrounded by this great nature, aren't you, otaku?
It's not true.
Is that so?
I'm going through this in a short period of time.
I'm already on the table.
Masumoto-san, what is this?
It's a rag.
Wait, stop it.
Don't mess with me.
Why are you putting out a rag?
It's true.
I'm angry.
Put it out.
Put out something else.
Are you waiting?
It's this, isn't it, Masumoto-san?
What is this, Masumoto-san?
It's a grandpa.
Wait, wait.
Don't mess with me.
It's not true.
Why are you putting out a rag?
It's true.
Put it out.
Put out something else.
I'm going through this in a short period of time.
Are you waiting?
Good evening, both you and me.
It's this, isn't it, Masumoto-san?
Today, I'm going to check if the pig is cooked.
I'm a big fan of it.
I've been cooking it since last night.
I've been simmering it.
You've been simmering it?
This is a pig called Hanako that I've been keeping for about 15 years.
I see.
You've been simmering it a lot, haven't you?
When I call it Hanako, it's always, boom.
It was cute, Hanako.
Look, the meat is so tender.
That's Hanako's leg.
I wrapped it around her when she was injured.
Oh, excuse me.
Hanako's ribbon is in it.
Everyone, I'm going to try it.
Hanako.
I wonder what it tastes like.
Boo.
Hanako, boo.
Yoshio, move!
Hanako, give it back!
Give it to me!
Hanako, give it to me!
Hanako, move!
Now, I'm going to try it.
Her chest is a bit small.
I'm going to try it.
Well, you've been living in Tokyo, haven't you?
Yes.
Tokyo is a great city, isn't it?
Why?
You can't get a parking lot.
Oh, that's right.
I'm looking for a parking lot, too.
There's a mansion, but there's no parking lot.
And there's no surroundings, right?
That's right.
It's completely packed.
And if you stop for a moment, you'll be transferred to another place right away, right?
Yeah.
I've been thinking about it.
There's no way for me to get a parking lot, you know.
building up one's own Secondary School
You can't get a parking lot anymore.
Today is a little different from the previous program.
That's right.
Please explain a little.
Today, as usual, the story ends, right?
We talked a little like a free talk and said goodbye.
Today, I put out a monitor here.
In fact, from 7 o'clock on this Japanese TV, from Saturday, every Saturday, from 7 o'clock, everyone laughs.
One hour, other than us, B-21, Pink's phone, we are doing various things together.
In the meantime, wait!
How many years are you waiting?
In the meantime, I did a skit.
That's right.
So, in terms of time, I didn't fit in this skit.
The skit that didn't become a comedy show.
It's a waste, isn't it?
Even though I'm doing my best.
Look at that today.
I'm going to die!
Hey!
The water won't come out!
Hey.
Someone!
Help me!
The water won't come out!
Help me.
Someone!
The water won't come out!
Help me!
Help!
Give me some water!
Who will help me?
Everyone!
Someone help me!
Today's child is the most beautiful among the staff.
Really?
It's a little heavy.
Then,
I asked you to bring a postcard instead.
For example,
I have been doing Osaka dialect lectures recently.
By the way,
In Osaka dialect, Hama-chan often says,
Ite-ma-u-do.
What does it mean?
Are you stupid?
Is it strange?
Is that Ite-ma-u-do?
Ite-ma-u-do.
Ite-ma-u-do means,
Shiba-kudo.
What is Shiba-kudo?
So,
Kamasu-zo.
What is Kamasu-zo?
What does Shiba-kudo mean?
Do it properly!
Where do you get the idea of Shiba-kudo from?
Everything!
If you say Shiba-kudo,
it means to hit the ground.
I'll hit the ground, too.
How can you say that?
It means that you can turn around.
I'm not ready yet.
How can you say that?
So,
it means that you can do everything,
including hitting the ground.
You can do everything!
By the way,
you know Yasu-san from Yokoyama, right?
His words,
even in Osaka dialect,
are quite cruel.
It's quite weird in terms of grammar.
It's a special case.
It's his words.
Yes, yes.
Like,
I'll get angry,
but...
But what?
I'll get angry,
but...
It means that you can do everything.
Yes.
How can you say that?
I'm not ready yet.
He's a cartoon character.
Right?
But if it's normal,
There's no way I'll get angry.
You won't hate
you won't hate
when someone said something like that
At a once,
you can't say
but...
What?
I can see that part.
It's really difficult.
How is it difficult?
There's a guy in Tokyo called Harutatsu recently.
I've said this before.
When I'm doing my make-up,
I sometimes say the opposite.
Then,
I say,
Laugh! Laugh! Laugh!
After that,
I say,
It might be strange.
Are you laughing now?
Why? Why are you laughing?
I'm just asking.
I'm not just saying it.
I'm just saying it.
I'll be happy if I get it.
I don't think I'll get it.
It might be strange.
Laugh! Laugh! Laugh!
I've said this before.
In this program,
we're going to make a present.
What?
About two sets.
Huh?
I think everyone will pull this.
I'm sure the motor will be happy.
Don't say that.
What?
I like it.
I don't know if you said it once.
Say it twice.
Two sets.
Why two sets?
My face is written on it.
It's the best.
I'm happy if I get it.
Why are you happy?
I'm happy.
Who's happy?
What?
Are you happy with the other side?
Or are you happy with the other side?
I don't care.
It's fashionable.
My face is written on it.
If I get it, my face will be bigger.
Laugh! Laugh! Laugh!
Hello.
Hey.
Laugh! Laugh! Laugh!
Good morning, Allen.
It's over.
Today was your first attempt.
What?
Showing off your skits.
I think I got a lot.
How was the assistant?
I was taught the dirtiness of the entertainment world.
With the assistant?
Yes.
What?
I don't know where the good guy went.
Who?
Someone hid the envelope somewhere.
The guy who sent it?
Yes.
My manager, Nitta, is secretly keeping it.
It's funny.
But it's okay.
Everyone is young.
It's normal for a man and a woman to be in such a relationship.
At that time, you should not wear what you wear.
For that?
I like it.
Laugh! Laugh! Laugh!
A piece of tissue.
This is it.
I want to keep it.
This is a real present.
I think it's good.
It's good.
Yes.
I'll be a little more smart.
You're a fool.
Laugh! Laugh! Laugh!
What is it?
If you can, try it.
I'll use it.
Which one?
What?
Your face?
I don't care about your face.
What?
I don't care either.
I don't care about your face.
But it's pathetic.
After you go, it's messy.
I think you can have sex with a fun atmosphere while laughing.
That's right.
It's called Japanese sex.
What?
What is this face?
We laugh together.
What are you saying?
Laugh! Laugh! Laugh!
You can think of ideas.
If you make something like this on the show and send it to me.
Yes.
I'm thinking about that.
This program is brought to you by Oyama International Products,
Sunluck,
and Toyo Suisan.