This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Good evening.
I'm glad you're doing well.
Yes.
How are you doing recently?
Ah!
How's this summer?
Summer?
Are you getting on well?
With this summer's boom?
Well, well, well, I'm getting on somehow.
I heard you released another song.
I can't help it.
I've been telling you for a long time.
Come ask me for a favor.
I can't believe you can write such a wonderful song.
You're not going to make a proper song, are you?
I'm not going to make it!
You're not going to make it, are you?
That's why I'm in the Comical department.
Don't tell me on TV that you're talking about ***.
At the music station, it's ***.
That's right.
Tamori's glasses will break.
Why would they break?
Who is it this time? The songwriter?
It's an amateur.
Ah, is that so?
It was sent to a complete amateur.
The arranger made it properly.
If that's the case, I'd like you to let me write a song that will inspire you.
Can you do it?
Of course I can.
I have a lot of stuff.
What stuff?
Stuff like stocks.
What do you mean?
There's no point in making it.
I don't want to talk about your private life.
You have a lot of stuff.
I don't want to talk about it, but I have tape.
What do you call it?
A tape recorder.
What?
It's a tape recorder.
I don't have anything to brag about.
I always put it in the car.
If I come up with a phrase, I put it in like this.
It's true. It's really true.
It's true.
I thought it was funny, so I put it in.
I still know, but...
You put in a phrase for a song?
I put in a phrase for a song.
I put in a lot of 60-minute tape.
Let me hear it this time.
What kind of phrase do you put in?
I've been working on it for a long time, so I play it and listen to it.
Of course, I play my own phrase all the time.
Really?
I'm a studious man.
Even if you put in a lot of phrases, it's not all in one, right?
It's not all in one, but when I want a song, I put it in.
You put it in one?
Yes.
Can you do that?
Of course I can.
You can?
Yes.
I can.
If you can, I'd like to hear it.
I don't get a lot of requests, so I wonder what they're doing.
You're all so slow.
I've been waiting here for a long time.
I see.
I'm glad I asked you instead of that stupid old man.
So if you want a love song, I can do it.
Of course, I can do comedy.
And what else...
Rambada.
Rambada is good.
Even if you sing it now.
But it's going to be a bit of a rambada boom.
That can't be. It ended a long time ago.
If it's a rambada, let's talk seriously.
Let's talk about the boom.
If it's a rambada, I think it's going to be a daikon mochi boom.
Daikon mochi?
What's daikon mochi?
It's a Chinese dish made with a little bit of daikon.
I'm sorry about that.
But that's all I can say.
You don't know much, do you?
I don't.
But this is really good.
It's been around for a long time.
But it's not as popular as daikon mochi.
It's a daikon mochi boom.
It's going to be a big hit.
But Chinese people can't eat it.
They can't.
It's going to spread to the general public.
Probably.
That's why the termites were really popular at one point.
I'm sorry.
I just hit right here.
I'm really sorry.
I hit right here.
I'm sorry.
But that's how it is.
Really?
Seriously.
What kind of taste is it?
It's not that it's delicious.
It's crispy and the inside is crunchy.
I don't get it.
It's like me.
It's crispy and the inside is crunchy.
It's an understatement.
It's good that you say that.
You should request this.
We'll make it properly.
But what kind of song is it?
You want to be number one, don't you?
No.
Right?
If you want to be number one,
Hitoshi Matsumoto is number one.
I'm sure of it.
But I've never heard a song.
No, no, no, I made this.
When I heard it, I was like, oh, really?
If it's going to be like that...
I'll ask everyone to watch it on TV.
Then, let's give you a sample of a good one.
Ah, that kind of thing, it's better to show it.
Ah, because it's a comedy.
It's a love song.
There's one that I put in.
I heard it today, so I remembered it.
Does it have a title?
No, well, I'll add it later.
Ah, I see.
Well, now it's become an a cappella.
Of course, it is.
I like you.
What kind of joke is that?
It's like a love song.
What do you mean, I like you?
It's the way it goes in.
It's okay, it's okay. Listen until the end.
It's not like that here yet.
I like you.
What kind of lyrics is that?
What is it?
You haven't done it yet, have you?
No, I haven't done it yet.
The instrument goes in there.
If that's the case, do it like this.
Ah, I'm sorry.
I don't think it's worth it.
Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang.
It's not like that.
Why is it that only the sound comes in after two phrases?
Keep singing.
Love songs are usually like Tokunaga.
Ah, Tokunaga Nyan.
Tokunaga Nyan.
You have to think of it like that.
I like you.
For example, in a music station,
Next, Hama-chan,
Please go, please stand by.
This week's number one, Hama Wagoji-san.
I like you.
Just like that?
There's nothing like a prelude.
You have to sing it as hard as you can.
I like you.
Then, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang.
It's long.
It's getting longer by the minute.
That's strange.
You're the only one who can sing.
That's why it's incomplete.
It's a sample.
If I get a request, I'll make it.
It's been a long time since then.
The instruments keep coming in.
Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang.
So, one by one,
It's a pattern of me and me.
It's coming together.
Everyone's here.
Everyone's in front of me.
Again, I like you.
At this time, everyone's in one line.
Tamori-san is smiling.
Gura-san is shining, too.
It's okay if I don't shine.
Is that a love song?
It's a love song, right?
Because you said you liked it.
It's a conversation, isn't it?
You said you liked it.
I like that kind of thing.
After all, a love song is a encounter between a man and a woman.
I'd like you to scurry away.
What do you mean?
What is scurry away?
Dan-dan-dan-dan-dan-dan.
...Dan-dan-dan-dan.
Gradually, gradually.
What about that?
What, what, what, what?
I'm sure your heart is beating fast right now.
But you have to give me 4-5 million yen.
What?
What do you mean?
The commission fee.
Of course.
It's that expensive?
If it's you, it's expensive.
If it's not you, I'll take a little more.
But, you know, I've known you for a long time.
And you're wearing a red shirt.
Don't cry.
I'm glad it's red.
Ah, really?
Yes, really.
Can I think about it a little?
Ah, sure.
Well, if there's someone among the audience who wants it,
If you have 4-5 million yen, I'll give it to you.
But if you buy it, you'll definitely sell it, right?
Of course, I'll sell it a lot.
What are you talking about?
Especially you, you're a little cheap.
Ah, sorry.
My shoes hit the floor.
Really.
This is a question for Matsumoto-san, the re-emergence of Black Jack.
Yes.
During the surgery, if the doctor says something like a mess or a sweat,
the nurse who is doing the surgery will immediately respond.
Ah.
They'll hand it over and wipe it off, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
How much do they respond to your request?
Please tell me the limit of the surgery.
I see.
You often see it in dramas, right?
Well, in dramas...
If you want to see the actual scene, you have no choice but to become a patient.
That's right.
But if you become a patient, it means that the anesthesia is working.
Therefore, it's something that ordinary people like us don't understand.
In that sense, everyone is certainly interested, right?
That's right.
Well, I understand it. I know it.
When I say it, I might think,
ah, it's not that easy.
But basically, it's two words.
Two words?
If it's two characters, anything is okay.
I see.
Sweat.
Yes.
Mess.
Like this.
But there are long ones in the equipment, too.
For example, the one to stop.
What do you mean, the one to stop?
I don't know that.
It's the one to stop.
You're a katakana!
No, the one to stop is,
I'll stop.
That's what you have to do, right?
If I say, I'll stop,
he'll stop.
If you say, I'll stop,
he'll say yes.
I won't lie.
You won't lie?
That's what it is.
Basically, it's two characters.
It's two characters.
What do you mean?
Other than sweat and mess.
It's a nose, right?
What?
A nose?
What's a nose?
It's a nose.
There are times when a nose comes out.
There's definitely a nose.
But you're not wearing a mask, so you can't see it.
That's why you have to say, I'm a nose.
That's a joke!
I'm a nose.
If it comes out, it's fine.
So you say, yes.
It's all two characters, right?
Yes, that's right.
Isn't there a more formal way to say it?
There's no other way to say it?
I won't put in words that are stuck together.
Don't open your mouth.
So when you open it,
you say, I'm a nose.
I'm a nose.
If it's worse than you think, you say, I'm a nose.
I quit today.
There are times like that.
It's all two characters.
That's strange.
Enka singers often sing while clenching their fists.
Yes.
What's inside the clenched fist?
Please tell me.
What do you think this is?
There's nothing inside.
There's no way that's true.
When they sing, they do this.
But there must be a reason why only Enka singers clench their fists.
I don't think there is.
Other singers don't clench their fists like that.
It's rare for Enka singers to clench their fists.
Kitajima, Saburo, Hosokawa, Takashi.
Who are they? Hosokawa, Takashi.
Kitajima, Saburo, and Hosokawa, Takashi.
There are two of them.
Two?
Everyone clenches their fists.
There must be a reason why only Enka singers clench their fists.
It's easier to sing.
Or a pose.
A pose for Enka singers.
I've been watching Kitajima, Saburo for a long time.
They clench their fists.
Really?
They clench their fists in the dressing room.
What are they doing?
They must be working now.
That's right.
They clench their fists in the dressing room?
They raise their spirits.
That's good.
They don't raise their spirits by clenching their fists.
That makes them more excited.
If I say too much, I'll get scolded.
It's okay. Tell me.
It's their favorite food.
Kitajima, Saburo usually clench their fists.
They sing like this.
Then they say,
I'm going to eat this later.
Ha!
Then they make a loud sound.
Because they can eat this.
But after that, they become arrogant.
That's why Sabu-chan doesn't clench his fists until Greenpeace.
He doesn't clench his fists like this. He clenches his fists like this.
Everyone does that.
That's right.
Matsumoto-san, you've stepped on the tails of many animals.
Yes.
Which animal has the best reaction?
Which animal has the worst reaction?
That's a good question.
Have you ever stepped on a dog?
What?
A dog's tail?
Of course it's a dog.
I've never stepped on it.
I've stepped on it before.
I've stepped on it from the tail of an unhappy dog.
There are dogs that are as good as that, right?
Of course.
That was only a coincidence.
What kind of reaction did you get when you stepped on a dog?
A dog doesn't make a sound.
It's not funny at all.
It's not something you can say on TV.
So the reaction is bad, right?
It's bad.
It's not funny at all.
The most interesting reaction was when you stepped on something.
Ah, you're asking about that?
I didn't think of that.
Sorry.
Sorry, sorry.
What?
So...
You didn't react to the dog, right?
Yes, yes.
You didn't think of it at all, right?
What was the most interesting reaction you got?
Um...
Moo!
Moo?
Do you know?
What's a moo?
It's in my house.
Moo?
Um...
It's somewhere between a horse and a deer.
It's really weak.
It can only run away.
So when you stepped on it, your reaction was good?
It was good.
What kind of reaction did you get?
Moo!
What do you mean, moo?
Moo, right?
Moo!
Really?
What is it?
What?
Wait, let's talk!
What is it?
When you stepped on it...
But they don't understand it.
Do you understand?
Yes.
If it was an easy-to-understand animal,
they would say,
Oh, so that's how that animal reacts.
Everyone would think about it and laugh.
But when they say,
No!
They can't even think of the shape of the object.
It's like,
Seriously?
They can't think of it.
That's my fault, too.
So you understand it better.
I've been watching No on TV recently.
It just so happened.
That's what happened.
That's what I wanted to say.
When I said, No,
they didn't take it as much as I thought they would.
There aren't many people who know.
I don't know what to do.
I've recently learned the word,
Todo no tsumari.
I see.
I don't know when I should use it.
I'll teach you how to speak with the correct pronunciation of the word.
How about this?
Right now,
I'm using the word,
Todo no tsumari,
to make a short story.
Even if I say it here,
it's like I'm forcing it.
It's not natural.
In the conversation after this,
I'll try to use the word,
Todo no tsumari.
I see.
I don't know when it'll come out.
The more natural it is,
the easier it is to understand.
You just said it in English.
I said it in English.
You said it in English.
Please use it properly.
I will. I'll use it until the end of today.
You will?
Yes.
I see.
Everyone, please use it properly.
This is a question for Matsumoto-san,
from the Dover Kaikyo O-danbu.
U-chan Ran-chan's Uchimura-san,
why are you so white?
If you have a reason,
please tell me.
It's an amazing handwriting, isn't it?
Please use it properly.
Todo no tsumari.
Yes, I understand.
If you're that white,
it's not just one reason.
Really?
It's a combination of many situations.
Is that so?
Please explain the situation properly.
First of all,
you probably killed a white snake, didn't you?
You killed a white snake.
Then you ate too many squids.
Then you got too carried away by seeds.
That's interesting.
The third one is interesting.
Todo no tsumari.
Why are you so troubled?
It was good just now, wasn't it?
Why didn't you tell me the secret at the end?
Because there was a reaction.
I was surprised.
So that's the situation.
Yes.
Todo no tsumari.
Yes, yes.
It's white.
I see.
This is good.
What?
You solved two questions in one.
This is beautiful.
This is beautiful, isn't it?
It wasn't like this before.
It wasn't like this before, wasn't it?
I thought it would be better if the audience's reaction was better.
It was good in the beginning.
Yes.
From now on, there will be something like this, right?
Did you talk about scales falling from your eyes?
It's interesting.
There's a time machine, right?
Yes.
Time machines are absolutely impossible.
What are you talking about? I don't understand at all.
I'm just talking in order.
Time machines are absolutely impossible to complete.
I see.
Because it has never happened to a person who has time-slipped.
What do you mean?
It has never happened to a person who has time-slipped.
Right?
Is there anyone who doesn't understand?
He explained it in an easy-to-understand manner.
For example, if a time machine was made about a thousand years later,
it should be able to meet the person who is currently wearing it on a time machine.
But you've never met a person who has time-slipped and has come from the future, right?
That means the time machine will never be completed, no matter how many years later.
I don't understand what you're saying.
This is an amazing story.
It's a bit different.
Why does everyone come up to the stage and raise their head?
Maachan! Maachan!
Hama-chan's Maachan! Maachan!
Wait a minute.
Maachan is fine.
What's with Hama-chan's Maachan?
That's because I'm thinking about your personality.
If you come up to the stage and say, Maachan! Maachan!
and I raise my head, you'll end up looking like this again.
Everyone will end up looking like Matsumoto Takeya.
Maachan! Maachan! Hama-chan's Maachan!