Thank you for coming!
It's a real pleasure.
Don't worry, don't worry.
It's a bit late to start, right?
Yes.
This is completely because of Yamazaki.
Why?
That kid was so excited.
Oh, is that so?
He was so excited.
Why?
He said he slept through something.
Is this the time to sleep through something?
He didn't sleep through anything the day before.
He didn't sleep through anything, did he?
No, no, no.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
If he gets angry, I'm going to hit him with a Fanta Grape.
That's a good idea.
I have something interesting to tell you.
What is it?
It looks like I punched him.
Koichi Wajima!
It's an interesting story.
A junior from Yoshimoto.
He's a very interesting junior.
A very young guy.
He's going to a classroom right now.
It's an interesting place.
It's on the street.
When he's on the street, the instructor...
What's that?
It's like a digital camera.
Like you're watching it while teaching?
While teaching.
When he's done teaching,
they're all going to watch it on a big screen.
They're going to watch it?
They're going to watch it.
I thought it was interesting.
Miura was driving.
Miura-kun...
Miura-kun.
When I was going to work at Jaguar, I didn't know anything about it.
I was like, I don't know anything about it!
I don't know anything about it!
And after that class,
Everyone, look at this. This is Miura-kun's.
Miura-kun, take a picture of this.
Or, this is Mach-chan's.
This is Mach-chan's.
This is the driver's seat.
I know it's Mach-chan's, but I don't know if this is Mach-chan's.
He said, this is Mach-chan's.
That's great.
That's what he said.
But that's terrible.
But it's a fun game.
It's a fun game, but...
This is a lie.
That's right.
I'm counting on you.
No, no, no.
There are a lot of things like that.
I see.
Please do it well.
I know you failed the third time.
Failed?
It's always like this.
What do you mean, please do it well?
Even if you failed the third time.
It's always like this.
I don't really want to say this on TV, but
My grandmother
She's into haiku lately.
I don't mind.
She's going to a haiku club.
I don't mind if she goes to a haiku club, but
She sent me a letter.
She wrote a haiku?
There are about 40 haiku.
What do you want her to do?
I want her to read it to me.
When I read it in the middle of the night,
I thought she was going crazy.
I thought she was going to be a fool.
It's terrible.
What kind of haiku?
I remembered it.
It's not that terrible.
There were a lot of terrible things.
I was quite surprised.
Heart attack and
The suspense of love and tears.
I don't know what it means.
I thought she was going to be a fool.
She's serious.
It's not that. I thought she was going to be a fool.
I was surprised.
It's all like that, right?
It's not all like that.
There was a beautiful one.
Poiste's
The bird that dances in the autumn.
I don't know if it's beautiful.
There are 40 of them, and that's it.
It's terrible after that.
There is no mother to send carnations.
It's sad.
But that's fine.
Who are you talking about?
It's like you're threatening me.
That's not good.
What are you talking about?
But I understand.
It's scary.
I thought it was done.
How about you?
I'm surprised.
Send me more.
There are a lot.
I threw it away.
It was a love that I picked up in high school.
No, no, no, no.
When are you talking about?
About yourself?
It's creepy.
It's scary.
A woman who is close to 70 years old says that to her 40-year-old son.
When did you throw it away?
It's creepy.
How did you pick it up?
It's creepy just to pick it up.
You're the only one on TV that's creepy.
I've known you since elementary school.
It's creepy.
It's really creepy.
So I threw it away once.
What's that?
It's not Jouichi.
There's such a dirty love.
It seems that there is a place where you immediately stab it.
He said it himself.
He said I stab it right away.
I said it when I was in elementary school.
I don't understand the meaning.
My mother said there is such a place.
It's the same thing.
Shut up.
Don't say it.
I don't understand.
I'm surprised.
I'll tell you when it comes.
It says 100,000.
I thought it was 40,000 for the time being.
It says there's still more.
There's still more.
It's a yoga katakana.
It has a surprise mark.
I thought there was still more.
It's better to announce it on that day.
It's a waste.
It's better to announce it all.
I'm surprised.
What should we do today?
We have to play a penalty game today.
The losing team, please come out.
It's really a sleeping face.
It's amazing.
What are you doing?
I quit.
Really?
Really.
I'm glad you quit.
Why did you quit?
I was setting up the room.
It's hot.
I didn't do it on purpose.
I'm sorry.
You wake up so soon.
I'm sleepy.
It's sunny.
You slept too much.
What time did you sleep?
It was 9 o'clock in the morning.
At work?
Didn't you sleep?
I'm on a TV show called Fandango TV.
I'm addicted to it.
You're on the show.
That's right.
I'm on the show, but it's fun to watch.
You're on the show all the time.
I'm on the show all the time.
I'm a junior.
Why am I in between the two of you?
You're really strong.
Please let me do it.
I don't know why.
That's a strange position.
It's fine.
What are you doing?
There are various days.
The penalty game will be held next month.
That's right.
It's about winter.
It's harder in winter.
I'll do it with the momentum to kill you.
I'm going to kill you.
I'll do it next month.
I don't know the meaning of the penalty.
Why?
Everyone is having fun bowling.
It's easy.
Everyone will go on a hot spring trip this time.
On a hot spring trip?
Yes.
Two days and one night.
That's all.
Is that okay?
Yes.
I understand.
It's not a penalty at all.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
Why didn't you tell me in detail?
You guys should go to the hot spring.
Do you know what's going on?
That's a strange position.
Something is going on.
What does it look like?
It's two days and one night.
I'm going to stay overnight.
But I can't sleep.
You can't sleep?
I can't sleep.
What do you mean you can't sleep?
I can't sleep because it hurts.
What?
I don't like it.
I'll tell you one thing.
There's a tie.
People who are watching TV may think it's funny.
I'm going to play a lot of tricks.
Please don't laugh.
Please don't laugh at what I'm going to play.
People who are watching TV, please laugh a lot.
But if you guys laugh...
Well, there's something.
The four of us are going to the hot spring, right?
Why are we going to the hot spring?
I'm scared.
I can do anything to lock you guys up in the building.
Can you lock us up?
Of course.
I'll make sure you don't run away.
As I've said many times, I just had fun bowling.
It was a lot of fun.
If there was a strike, there was a guard.
I couldn't stop laughing.
It was a lot of fun.
I don't know why people do that.
I'll let you go to the hotel.
I can do anything.
If you don't laugh, it's over.
You can't laugh because you're a professional.
That's right.
If you don't laugh, there's nothing.
You can go back to the hot spring.
That's right.
If you don't laugh, it's over.
If you laugh instead...
I can't stay with you forever.
Why?
I'll be punished.
If I go out with you.
Why are you being so mean?
I don't like it.
I'll go when I can.
I'll be watching you guys.
I don't know if I'll be on the show.
When I'm on the show, I'll do a lot more than usual.
I'm the one who bought it.
I think...
I don't think it's right for all four of us to be punished.
Why?
I see.
From now on...
Can I ask you a question?
Why are you doing this?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Please tell me why.
You didn't tell me earlier?
What do you mean?
Well, I see.
Well, there were some bad guys bowling.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I see.
And then there's the loser and the loner, right?
What are you talking about?
Why are you wearing so many socks?
That's a lot.
What?
Well, there are some bad guys who couldn't bowl properly.
That's true.
So the four of us are going to lose our eyes.
So I think it's okay to narrow it down to one or two people.
I'm actually on your side.
You're on my side, aren't you?
You're on my side.
I'm on the red side.
I think that's what it is.
That's because the times are the worst for us.
I don't know what you're talking about.
No, no, the times are the worst for us.
We're on the red side right now.
Oh, you guys are on the red side.
So we can't be reckless.
No, no, no, no.
You can be reckless.
You can do anything.
Are you stupid?
From now on, you guys can stop.
You have kids, right?
No, we don't.
Why didn't I do it alone?
What?
We don't know.
It's not just the two of us. It's a group.
It's already decided.
What are you talking about?
Then let's do it with five people.
What are you fighting for?
No, no, what are you talking about?
It's okay.
I want to do a lot of things.
Then let's do it with one person.
Why me?
You're the most normal person.
What kind of person am I?
You wake up and it's a mess.
Can't you talk?
It's a big deal.
It's like a dog.
It's like a death-throwing game.
It's a mess.
I mean, I'm looking forward to it.
I can't let you do such a stupid thing.
There's nothing around you.
I don't hear any screams.
Someone's coming to help.
I don't want to lose to this team again.
In the future?
Why?
I was doing something really good.
What?
There's no such thing as who's good or who's bad.
I don't want to lose to this team.
Let's change it next time.
Then I'll do it with one person.
This team versus this team.
Are you serious?
If you lose, it won't be funny anymore.
First of all, let's get a divorce.
I haven't been punished much by Hamada, though.
That's too much.
You're too much.
Get yourself together on the day.
That's right.
Tell the person who's going to get a divorce to get a divorce properly.
There was a place you went to before, right?
It was a place that made you feel nervous.
That's right.
I know this time.
I'm just saying that if you're nervous, there's something.
But people laugh, right?
There are times when people laugh even when they're talking to you.
We're talking normally, right?
Like smiling.
That's why it's selling, right?
We're not doing anything.
We're just having fun.
I'll judge that status.
I just laughed.
I'm a little bad.
Can't you do this?
I'm laughing.
You can't do that.
What? But I can do it forever.
You can't do it forever. You will be beaten forever.
What?
Forever?
No, no, no.
About 20%.
You will be beaten.
What?
You can't beat me.
That's also a detail.
That's not good.
You will be beaten.
No, no, no.
Make a serious face.
This is fine.
That's fine.
You're smiling?
Yes, I am.
That's fine.
It's fine, right?
No.
It's really fine.
You have bad eyes.
That's what I'm saying too.
No, I don't.
That's normal.
That's not good...
Yes, okay.
That's all.
You will be beaten.
What?
I'm scared.
I'm scared!
You're not laughing at all.
No, I'm not.
Don't laugh at me.
It's a punishment game!
Let's do it when you can see his teeth.
No, I can't see his teeth when I laugh.
I can't do it when I can see his teeth.
If you do something so harsh, I'll complain.
Fine.
I can't do it when I can see his teeth, right?
You're so strong.
I said it's fine if you don't laugh.
You're so kind.
I can't do it if you don't laugh.
But people will laugh.
What's wrong with that?
It's something that only humans have been given.
That's right.
I really thought so.
What are you talking about?
I can't go anymore.
What?
What do you mean you can't go?
I can't go to the set.
I'm sorry.
Everyone knows.
Everyone, please look forward to it.
I think it's going to be interesting.
What?
Right?
What is this?
What?
You're a good tiger.
That's right.
I'm scared.
I cried.
That's a prank.
Poor thing.
You don't have to shoot a batminton racket.
But you shoot this.
He's in trouble.
I thought I'd cut it and do it like that.
Just...
No.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing, fur-san?
Huh?
Hey suck my ear.
This is sick.
Hey I'm not kidding.
I can't do this anymore.
That's right.
But this time there are four of us, so it's fine.
It's not like I'm going to focus only on you.
We're all going to do it together.
That's right. I'm going to focus on the person who laughs.
But Hamada-kun, you know...
What do you mean, Hamada-kun?
We've been through a lot together, haven't we?
That's right.
That happened to me too.
It's not like they're related.
No, no, no.
It's been 13 years, right, Hamada-san?
Right? Our relationship.
That's right.
If I say 13 years, it's a long time.
But I only met you at the scene.
That's right.
Endo and Hamada-san...
When I was in middle school,
I saw the first 4 o'clock news.
That's right.
I went to the Nijomi theater.
I was cheering for Hama-chan.
At that time, it was Hama-chan.
Now it's Hamada-san, of course.
I said, Hama-chan, Hama-chan.
I said Hama-chan to everyone.
I said Hama-chan in school.
Yes.
When I went to Karaoke, I sang the first song.
You sang.
Endo sang.
I sang all the songs.
Oh, by the way,
I bought 4 Otsu Nights.
Oh, 4?
But...
That's going to happen.
I bought 4 Otsu Nights.
I want another one.
Let's go home.