Thank you for the food.
The sake is delicious.
I'm sorry.
Actually, the cooler broke.
I think it's a little hot.
I'll fix it right away.
Please be patient for a while.
I'm sorry to bother you.
It's hot.
That's right.
It's a little hot.
It's hot.
It's really hot today.
The cooler is broken.
It's hot.
It's really hot.
It was hot.
Isn't it hot?
It's a little hot.
It's still hot.
It's hot.
I can't stand it.
Is it hot?
Can you take it off?
It's hot.
Can I take it off?
I don't care.
The cooler is broken.
It's hot.
It's cold.
It's in front of the pot.
It's hot.
When I take it off, it's a little hot.
Yeah.
It's good.
The staff isn't hot.
It's really sweaty.
This is the hottest place.
This is the show.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
It's hot, but it's good.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
It's hot.
Really?
It's already spring.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
It's really hot.
It's hot.
I blew one.
Are you okay?
I can't stand it.
You can't stand it.
I understand.
Really.
I'm sorry.
I can't stand it.
I don't have confidence.
It's hot.
What?
My hands are like Onuma's hands.
Really?
Can I have one?
Sure.
I see.
It looks good.
I can't stand it.
Is it hot?
It's hot.
It's good to wait.
Yes.
Crab is delicious.
It's delicious.
It's the best.
It's the best, but it's hot.
It's hot.
I have a cold.
Do you have a fever?
I have a fever.
It's hot.
Soup is hot.
It's hot to drink soup.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
You haven't eaten anything yet.
I can't stand it.
You can't stand it, can you?
It's hot.
I can't stand it.
It's too hot to stand it.
Why do you have to put up with it?
It was hot, wasn't it?
It was really hot.
I'm not laughing.
I'm laughing.
It's hot, isn't it?
No, no, no, no.
What is it?
The steam is all on Mr. Nakamura.
It's true.
One more.
I can't stop laughing.
Mr. Nakamura, isn't this too much?
It's hot.
You're dirty.
Do you take it off?
I take it off.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
It's hot when you eat it all.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
This is not so hot.
No, no, no, no.
It's hot.
It looks delicious.
It's really hot.
It's hot.
This is a
B-H-A-N-D
It hurts...
Hey! Good evening!
Recently, I don't think I can get angry anymore.
You can't get angry?
Yeah.
I used to be like that, but I didn't do much.
Ah, I see.
Maybe I don't have enough calcium.
It doesn't matter.
Recently, I've gotten really angry.
I went to a video store and borrowed a romance novelist.
I see.
Well, it's a good thing.
But now it's a week's rent.
I borrowed it, but it's 300 yen, to be honest.
I thought, let's see it today.
I was looking forward to it.
I dug it up and played it.
I didn't say a word.
Huh?
What is this? What is this novelist?
It has nothing to do with the novelist.
I thought, I don't have enough calcium.
It's strange.
I pulled it out.
What is it? The back of the neck?
The back of the neck?
The back of the neck.
I opened it and it surprised me.
There's no tape.
What?
There's no tape?
No, no. If it was normal, it would be like this.
What do you mean there's no tape?
There's nothing on the tape.
But if you look at it here, it looks like Baumkuchen.
That's why it's cut off.
It's cut off, right?
If it's normal, if it's me before, if it's me when I was a chimp, if it's me when I was a jackknife, that's why it's cut off.
No, no, no, it's okay not to cut it off.
It's okay not to cut it off in response to what you said.
No, it's not.
At that time, I thought it was the end, so I called.
Did you call?
I called the video store.
I called the video store and said, Maruto, I'm not angry that it's like this.
But I said, I have to return it.
You're saying something big again.
That's right.
I'm a novelist who has nothing to do with this.
When I asked him why I had to return it, he said, what do you mean?
Why are you laughing?
You're crazy.
Even if I go to return this, no matter what kind of transportation method I use, it doesn't cost me money.
You shouldn't say such a thing.
That's right.
If I go by car, I have to pay for gas, if I go by bus, I have to pay for the bus.
Isn't it funny? This stupid phone is also my phone!
I'm sorry.
I'm going to get 300 yen.
What is 300 yen?
I'm going to get the 300 yen I borrowed.
But I don't want to take this video.
That's why.
What I'm saying is nothing wrong, right?
It's nothing wrong, right?
No, no, no.
You shouldn't say such a thing.
Okay, I got it.
It's something like that, right?
Then you can take it on my behalf.
But I can't keep the deadline.
I don't know if it will be 5 years later or 10 years later.
What the hell is that?
You just want to wear it, right?
No, no, no.
You wanted to wear it for someone.
That's not true.
So what kind of transportation method should I use?
I'm not asking you to give it back to me.
I'm asking you to give it back to me when I go somewhere.
Are you stupid?
Then I have to keep this video all the time.
I don't know when I'm going to go, but I don't know if I'm going today.
I've been holding it all the time.
When I open it, it's like this.
It's strange, isn't it?
In the end, I said, okay, we'll keep the deadline.
I don't know if it will be a month or two.
I went to the beginning.
I don't know if I'm going by taxi, so I'll give you the receipt at that time.
I'll give it to you.
What did you say?
Well, yes.
Once I went somewhere by car and took a taxi from there.
Do you want me to give you the money?
I'll give it to you.
Really?
I'm not saying this because you say it.
You're the one who made me look bad.
I'm going to get 300 yen.
Let's say the same thing happened.
You borrowed a love novel.
I borrowed a love novel today.
Wait a minute.
Who are you telling that to?
No, it's a wife and a child.
It's a child.
Hooray!
Please continue with the trial.
It's shiny.
Okay, then I'll put it in the deck.
Please put it in the deck.
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
I can't see it.
It's a child.
Why?
It's like a slipper.
I have a question for Alphys.
Yes.
Look around in the snowy mountains.
You'll run into a big tree with that momentum.
You'll hit the tree with your whole body.
And then you'll be buried deep in the snow.
Please tell me how to escape.
I don't have that kind of experience.
I don't think I'll be told right away.
No, no, no, no.
There is.
What?
It's a misunderstanding.
Really?
Please tell me what's going on.
I was skiing.
I was trying to get in the mood.
I see.
You were having fun, right?
And then?
I was thinking, this is Gelen.
It's heavier than before.
I was thinking.
I was sliding.
I was rolling.
What does that have to do with the flow?
No, it's not.
I was rolling and I hit the tree.
And then?
I was sliding.
I see.
I was the one who started it.
It wasn't just you.
All the people around you.
But the people around me.
It was a time when I shouldn't have done it.
I was at the top of the mountain.
What?
Really?
Yes.
Skiing on one foot is basically forbidden.
There weren't many people around.
So.
When I was sliding.
I thought everyone liked skiing on one foot.
And then.
I was hit by the guard.
It wasn't a pool.
That's not good.
I was scared.
I understand.
I didn't expect it to happen.
I was hit by the guard.
I understand.
And then.
The time passed slowly.
Everyone turned their faces away.
I pretended to have two hands.
No one was looking.
I tried to ride on my own.
I was the only one.
I was on my own.
I wasn't even holding hands.
You weren't even holding hands.
Really?
I was holding hands.
But I was holding hands like this.
Then I went up.
Like a giant tree.
I didn't go up like a huge tree.
I spread it like a strong branch.
Then the enemy started to come.
Awesome.
That was amazing.
You've been hoodwinked.
That's right.
When did you realize that?
Ichatani did it like that.
Like 5 meters down.
Think of this ceiling as snow.
It's like this under it.
It doesn't move at all.
Snow is white. That's a lie.
I'm the only one who knows this.
Snow is dark.
It's a place to laugh.
It's dark.
What should we do? It's 5 meters.
How do we reach it?
I've said this many times.
Don't mess around.
I see.
Rather, it feels like a god.
It's like this.
Why is it moving?
I wanted to make it look like a Christ.
I see.
So I waited for 5 to 10 minutes.
It was a big deal.
There were 50 to 60 angels from above.
It's amazing.
50 to 60 angels.
I see.
It was like this.
It doesn't move.
I see.
It doesn't move at all.
It's like this.
I'm impressed with that.
It's like a rock bath.
It's cold.
Really?
It feels good.
What is that?
Is that a cigarette?
It feels good.
This hand is also an angel.
Are you helping me with everything?
When will you come back to your senses?
I can't say thank you.
I'm going back to my senses with the karaoke box.
Why did you bring the karaoke box?
This is also an angel's work.
What is that?
Tomorrow is the day after tomorrow.
The one singing is an angel.
Are you going to sing?
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.