Even today, a storm rages.
Help me!
Stop!
Stop it!
Help me!
I can't go any further!
I want to be a fish!
I'm so scared.
Hey, shake it.
What are you doing?
Shoot faster.
I'm so scared.
You were great.
How are you scared?
I'm so scared.
I don't know.
Throw it Osomatsu.
Throw it.
I'm so scared.
What are you doing?
Save me!
Oh, Collection.
ook Reporter
rain
That's right
game
Oh
Tsu
Bon
ë…
Tokto
Takano
There is nothing to pick up in the forest.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Hey!
You're not a butterfly!
You guys say, hey!
Say it!
Today, I think I should say this.
There are many people who spread rumors.
What?
For example, the fact that I'm gay is obvious.
It's obvious?
What's good about it?
Your behavior is bad, isn't it?
No, no.
What do you mean by behavior?
You say, hey!
No one does that.
Say it!
Why?
You say, hey!
That's not good.
The reason why I'm angry is because I'm doing drugs right now.
That happens to both of you, doesn't it?
I get angry and when I watch TV, I can see it.
I can't calm down.
That's possible.
When I hear that, I get angry.
Look!
I can't show it to you.
I'm not that proud.
Hey!
I'm not proud.
So...
Don't say that!
I was told that on your show.
Yes, you were told that too.
I don't care.
My manager said,
Osaka people don't say that.
Tokyo people don't say that.
That's terrible.
Osaka people have been watching us for a long time.
They went to drink and said,
Hama-chan, you have a mole on your face.
You have a mole on your face.
I'm sure I don't have a mole on my face.
You don't know.
I have a little.
You have a little.
I don't have a mole on my face.
I've been doing this.
I've been making a super powerful joke.
You are using the power of medicine.
You don't know why I'm doing this.
You don't know.
When I'm talking,
Hey!
Say that!
What is it?
I have a little mole on my face.
That's a insult.
If you say that, it's an insult.
No, no!
I'm not going to say that.
I'm doing it because I'm going to say that.
I can accept this kind of thing easily.
I don't know if it's true.
If I say I'm an angel,
I can't believe it.
That's why I'm saying that.
I'm an angel.
I can't say that.
I have a lot of real stories.
I have a story like Kappa.
It's a real story.
I can't believe it.
Where did you see it?
I saw it in the bathroom of my house.
Kappa in the bathroom.
It's not fresh yet.
Do you understand?
It's a cold hand.
It's coming out.
Don't say that.
I don't know what to say.
What are you?
Let me say it with a face like a mountain man.
I really look like a mountain man.
A mountain man doesn't look like this.
It's true.
This is true.
I can't believe it.
I'm rude to Kappa.
I don't know what to say.
It's not Kappa.
Don't force yourself.
I'm sorry, Kappa.
Kappa is different.
It's true.
It's not Kappa.
It's really coming out.
Why are you falling down?
I fell down.
Where?
What?
Where did you fall?
I fell down.
I was in the bathroom.
I was in someone's ass.
It's true.
Stop it.
What?
It's a book.
This is a real story.
I'm scared.
My brother was studying in the book.
A dead old man said to my brother,
Takahiro.
That's obviously the old man's voice.
That's the old man's voice.
I don't know if that's true.
That's true.
You don't believe that the ancestors come back to the book.
It's like Gachapin.
I was watching it the other day.
Let's go to the uninhabited island.
An animal came out.
It's an animal I've never seen before.
Gachapin.
That's right.
Muku.
You guys.
That's right.
What were we talking about?
Do you believe it?
The ancestors come back.
The ancestors.
I don't think so.
That's when we're dumb.
I don't think I've seen anything like that before.
To someone?
To someone.
I can't do anything bad.
During that period.
I can't do it if I want to.
What do you want to do?
What are you talking about?
It's something that you can enjoy by yourself.
What do you mean by that?
If you think you're old and you're not sure what to do, you'll do it.
A jigsaw puzzle?
You're really tired.
I'm tired from work. I'm all alone.
Bring me to a place where you're tired.
I'm all alone.
I'm back.
I'm tired.
I'm all alone.
I'm all alone. What are you going to do?
Don't sleep!
That's true.
Don't sleep.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
Listen to me.
I'm tired.
What is it?
My lower body is...
It's hot.
It's hot. What are you going to do?
What are you going to do?
I'm all alone.
Don't take it off!
It's hot.
That's enough.
Take it off.
I'm all alone.
Hey, come here.
This is Mr. Kaoru.
He's 20 years old.
He's currently on the Omron racing team.
He's a circuit lady.
Did you go to the race?
Yes.
Did you run?
No, I went to F3000.
Oh, that one.
Yes.
Do you have a favorite racer?
A racer from Omron.
Who?
Mr. Jan Lammers.
What?
It's like Mr. Jan Luke Pancham.
Thank you very much.
Everyone has long legs.
Let me introduce you.
How to get home.
We've always thought about how to get home.
From a different point of view.
Oh, really?
I don't have a name for it.
You smoke a cigarette and spit it out.
You're making me go home.
We're here.
I can't get out of here.
That's right.
We're looking at things from a different point of view.
We don't have to go home.
The customers can go home.
Oh, really?
That's good.
I think this is a good idea.
Let's try it.
Can I try it?
The customer was good today.
They didn't do it.
Then I'd like to introduce you to the postcards.
Why do you always put a tie in your pants?
Don't you hate it?
Do you think it's cool?
But does the world see it that way, Matsumoto?
I'm not responsible.
Hamada, what do you think?
What's wrong with you?
Don't show me.
I think I'll have to talk about this someday.
When the time comes, I'll have to talk about it.
I'm definitely going to do this.
Why?
It's just a policy.
I want to tie it in a narrow place.
I understand that.
I want to tie it as narrow as possible.
I don't like it thick.
It's going to be a little long.
That's right.
You can take it out.
What do you call it?
This?
No, it's not.
It's better to cut it.
So, look.
No one can keep up with this year.
No, it's not like this.
I'll tell you a serious story.
If it's like this, your eyes look longer.
It's an illusion of the eyes.
If you do this, your eyes look longer.
This is the long part.
No, it's not like that.
It's an illusion of the human eye.
So, if you put it like this,
It's from 18-year-old Mr. Kaoru of Kannan Kibo.
The pen name is Hamada Nisei.
It's a story from a long time ago.
Thank you.
When I got on the train home from school,
An old man got on and I just looked at his face for a moment.
I didn't know at that time.
When I looked at him closely, he was an old man.
He was wearing a skirt.
He was wearing a beret.
He was holding a bag from his shoulder.
He was wearing high heels.
I was surprised by that.
He was talking to two foreigners on the same train.
And it seemed like they were talking to each other.
I was surprised.
Have you ever met such a strange person?
There is such a strange person.
What is that?
Isn't that a woman?
I think so.
His face is like an old man.
He was wearing a skirt.
And he spoke English.
He is cool.
He is handsome.
In that sense.
There are many such people.
Have you ever seen such a strange person?
He is wearing strange clothes.
He was talking to a vending machine at a station.
He was saying, give me 10 yen.
This is my brother.
Give me 10 yen.
That's right.
He was saying, brother, give me 10 yen.
There was such a woman.
Oh.
It happened in the underground of Umeda.
That's right.
Give me 10 yen.
Yeah.
When I told him no, he said, give me 100 yen.
Why did you say that?
Why?
Give me 10 yen.
Minari is doing it properly.
I don't know if this will be used in the broadcast.
In the past, there was a person like that.
He was sleeping at the station.
He saved my life.
In the underground of Umeda?
In the underground of Umeda.
There is a Koshien stadium, right?
There is an idol baseball tournament there.
About once a year.
Johnny's.
We were working.
There is a place called Umeda month.
I was in a hurry to go through the underground of Umeda.
Because I couldn't make it in time.
The flow of Koshien stadium.
That Gya Gya Gya Gya.
Middle school students and high school students.
Because it is a half train.
I went out to Umeda.
I fell in love with the underground of Umeda.
I was in a hurry.
I saw it.
I don't like it.
I was like this.
I ran away.
I was caught.
That was amazing.
I fell in love.
I couldn't stand it.
From above.
I was riding.
I couldn't breathe.
I was in a hurry.
I was about to be pushed.
At that time.
I was sleeping at the station.
The man was shining.
I dug a cardboard box.
I dug it.
No.
I can't do that.
I was holding this.
It was dirty.
I dug it.
It was so beautiful.
There was a flower path.
I was holding it like this.
It's true.
I wanted to thank him.
But he wasn't there.
He is cool.
He is a man.
He didn't tell me his name.
He only told me cardboard box.
He didn't say cardboard box.
It's true.
It was so beautiful.
That's all.
Shall we go home?
Let's go home.
Goodbye.
One.
Two.
Three.
Hello.
I have a nice present for you.
Really?
Yes.
Look at this.
I made something like this on my show.
What is it?
This is famous in the streets.
Really?
It's a power man No.2.
I made this panel.
I want to give it to you on TV.
It's from our mouth.
Really?
I want you to take it from our mouth.
Here you are.
The youngest one.
Where did it come from?
It's from Mr. Kitaizo's mouth.
Please take it from our mouth.
This is a photo of this panel.
This is a power man No.2.
If you want a photo of this panel,
it's on the bottom of the screen.
Please send it to us.
That's the kind of person he is.
Really?
I want you to come and take it.
Thank you.
I'm waiting for you.
Sign it.
I'm signing it as always.
I'm waiting for you.
The person is signing it in front of me.
There are a lot of lies about the fire.
That's right.
What if it didn't happen?
What would you do if it didn't happen?
So, while you're waiting for the fire,
you can put it on the desk of the maid.
The maid?
Yes.
What would you do if it didn't happen?
What would you do?
If it didn't happen,
you can put it on the desk of the maid.
That's good.
That's a good warning.
By the way,
I can't use you for the next time.
Bye.
I'm really waiting for you.
Start.
It's really hot.
Yamanagi, stand here.
Fried butter, fried butter.
It's hot.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.