He is here.
This program is brought to you by the sponsor.
Good morning sensei
Sensei Kiyoha
Yes
Please give me a lot of these
Please look at various things
Sensei, this is your arm
Ah, that's right
Good morning
Ah, this is...
Ah, I got it
Please
Sensei
What?
Ah, stop it
Sensei
What kind of play is this?
Ah, this is...
He's saying it over and over
This is good
Okay, okay
Ah, the part of the fish is...
It's melting
As a man with glasses
Mr. Ishii
When did you get here?
Ah, the dining table is ready
What would you like to eat?
I'm hungry
This is good
Ah, that's good
This is the best
Hey, wait a minute
Here you go
Ah, this is good
I'm also...
I feel like I'm running out of energy
Isn't this physical strength?
The inside is raw
Even if you say the inside is raw
It's crispy
It's the taste of Koya
Okay
Miss
This is good
It's expensive
I'll take this
Wait
Stop it
Okay
Wait
I'll take this
This is good
No
Wait, what is this?
It's like an art
I'll pour the soup
Ah, this is good
This is good
What is the purpose of this?
What's the purpose of this?
This is a tenderloin
The teacher is proud of this
I'm eating this?
Please eat
Ah, this is good
I'm doing something useless
Ah, you're eating
Eat it while it's hot.
What flavor is this?
It's winter.
I'm sorry.
It's not sweet.
What?
This is good.
I bought this in New York.
This is important.
Stop.
I bought this in New York for the first time.
This is good.
I gave it to you.
Special service.
I'll eat it with rice balls.
You can eat it as it is.
It's not cooked yet.
It's still sticky.
It's still like eggplant.
It's like eggplant.
Please eat it.
You can put any sauce you want.
Yes.
It looks delicious.
It's good.
I'm a bit shy.
It looks delicious.
I'm full.
I can't eat it.
I'll eat it.
It's good.
You're saying woo-hoo.
Shut up.
I'm getting excited.
No.
Please hold it.
Go.
It's good.
How is it good?
The color is beautiful.
Let's eat it with udon.
It's good.
It's like eggplant.
It looks delicious.
Look.
This is the best.
It's like Naruto.
Do you want some soup?
Yes.
It's good.
I want you to drink this.
I'm going to take off my hat.
Wait a minute.
It's dirty.
It's okay to do it with socks.
Do you want to do it with socks?
It's good.
The audience is happy.
I went to the bathroom a lot.
I have courage.
It's good.
I have to take it off.
This is the best.
Thank you very much.
The audience is in front of you.
We are in front of you.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Let's move on.
Let us move on.
Oh, really?
I just woke up.
I was eating soba noodles!
If you eat soba noodles, you'll wake up!
If you eat soba noodles,
that means you're driving on the road,
and you're breaking the bridge.
I woke up,
ate soba noodles right away,
and you woke me up to eat soba noodles!
My body is already moving.
I'm walking.
I'm not walking.
I'm in the car.
Don't say things like a chaos button.
Do you guys know what a chaos button is?
You guys are close.
I'm in the car, but I'm walking up.
Why are you pulling me?
I'm screaming.
I'm in the car, but I'm walking up.
Shut up. Don't say things like that.
It's you.
I'm walking.
I don't know if I'm walking or not.
Did you see that?
Why don't you do this show on a live show?
What?
It's all nonsense.
I'm scared.
Yesterday,
I did a behind-the-scenes show.
You did it live.
I'm scared. I don't know what you're going to say.
I'm not scared at all.
You said you're from the Ra clan.
I can't say anything about the Ra clan.
People in the industry
are like that.
They're always
nervous.
They're always careful about what they say on the air.
For example,
a father, a mother, a grandfather, a grandmother.
Family.
That's a misunderstanding.
No, no.
I said I'm from the Ra clan.
I'm from the family.
I take off my clothes.
I'm from the Ra clan.
If you take off your clothes,
you're not equal.
If you go to the hot spring with your family,
you're from the Ra clan.
No.
I'm wearing clothes on the way.
That's your family.
No.
You can't say that.
The Ra clan is naked on the way.
No.
When you take a bath, you're from the Ra clan.
That's strange.
That's just a normal family.
No, that's stupid.
And if you take off your clothes
in the middle of the show,
they'll say,
you can take off your clothes.
You can't say that.
I'm just wearing my clothes.
I just said that during the commercial.
Even during the commercial,
you can't say that.
I'm just saying it.
I don't care.
I'm not an adult anymore.
If you're watching this,
you're from the family.
you're in elementary school.
You're the same age as Hanaman Hajirau.
16 years old.
You're in your 16th grade.
When you're watching this,
if you're told that,
you don't like it.
You don't like it.
When you're told that
in front of your parents.
The atmosphere changes.
I'm telling you to think about it.
I'm telling you more.
I'm not telling you anything.
I'm telling you to take off your underwear.
I said to take off my underwear.
Don't say things like that.
Why?
Take off your underwear.
I'm playing baseball.
That's the momentum.
I can be on the air,
but you can't be on the air.
That's not true.
It's scary. It's not scary at all.
Editing is scary.
What's scary?
It changes completely.
Harada is a monster of editing.
Really?
Sometimes it's good for you.
He changes people's characters.
Akisai.
He's really good at editing.
Really?
You know.
I talk to him at home
and laugh at him.
I take that kind of thing.
I really laugh at him.
I keep that part.
Only that part.
I got it.
I don't say who it is,
but there's a guy who says something that can't be helped.
Something that can't be laughed at.
After he says that,
I'll give him this.
Is it funny?
At the scene.
This is the reality.
Where are you looking at?
I was looking at something else.
Wow, that's amazing.
And when I look at you.
Give me a break.
That's really bad.
That's dirty.
Why?
I'm editing what I've built up so far.
I'm changing it.
This is edited and brought here.
I'll cut it like this.
Cut here.
And it doesn't have to be there.
It doesn't have to be there.
But it looks natural to the general public.
That's right.
But it doesn't look like it's getting excited.
What I don't like about it
is that
there are a lot of cowardly things.
What do you mean?
Like animals.
And food.
Children.
But what is the most cowardly thing?
Is there anything else?
There is.
What is it?
A plush toy.
You're trying to tickle the child's heart a little.
You want to wear a plush toy yourself.
That's fine.
But you'll get a face.
But that's the opposite.
You're trying to tickle the child's heart a little.
You want to wear a plush toy yourself.
You know,
I do a dog costume on a TV show.
I'll get a face.
When I see that,
no one thinks the child is a dog.
Do you know that?
But if you don't show your face,
you'll look like a dog.
You'll be a little cute and a little cheeky.
You know that, right?
You'll be a little self-conscious.
That's not really...
I'm self-conscious?
I'm wild.
Wild people don't have ears.
Really.
You have to do it properly.
What kind of pose is that?
I can't do it.
You're pissing me off!
What?
What is this?
This is pissing me off?
I'm sorry.
I'm talking to someone.
I'm talking to Victory.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Please write it down.
Why do dogs always say,
ha ha?
They don't say ha ha
so much that it makes you feel sick.
First of all,
I'm alive.
I'm alive now.
We're friends.
I don't need friends.
I want to show my face.
You like to show your face, don't you?
At that time,
I have to say something.
Isn't it okay to say one?
I can't do it.
So,
I'm alive.
I'm breathing.
When I think about it,
when I think of 50 sounds,
I can only say ha ha.
Oh, my God.
I can't do it.
If that's the case,
talk to me.
I can't do it.
Oh, my God.
It's strange, isn't it?
I can only say ha ha.
Ha ha.
Talk to me.
I can't do it.
Ha ha.
Oh, my image.
I can't do it.
So,
I thought a lot,
and tried various things.
And that's why my mother was the one to calm down the most.
Why is the top and bottom of the newspaper all jagged?
The newspaper is jagged, isn't it?
The top and bottom.
Does that mean there are other uses for it besides the newspaper?
What do you mean there are other uses for it besides the newspaper?
If you listen carefully, you'll understand.
I don't know, I don't know.
Even if you suddenly look like an idiot, you won't understand.
If you listen carefully, you'll understand.
What do you mean?
Why are you getting on my nerves?
That's what's getting on my nerves.
Please stop this.
This is what's getting on my nerves.
It means there's a meaning to it while you're reading it.
Shut up, you're annoying.
Listen carefully.
This is my job, isn't it?
Even if you understand that, shut up.
This is strange.
Is there a meaning to it while you're reading it?
Have you ever read the newspaper while you're on the train?
I've read it like this.
When you're looking at it, the person holding the newspaper is trying to steal it.
You do that, right?
It's dangerous if you get any closer to the person holding the newspaper.
Why did the bear in the forest tell the young lady to run away?
He told her to run away and immediately picked up the earring and chased the young lady.
Why did the bear tell the young lady to run away as soon as he saw her?
I know that the young lady told him to run away, but there must be something before that.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have told her to run away.
One day, in the forest...
He met the bear, right?
He met the bear on the road to the flowering forest.
This is fine.
Yes, yes, yes.
According to what the bear said...
Young lady, run away.
This is strange.
No, that's not it.
I don't know if that's number two or not.
I don't even know if that's number three.
If there was nothing between them, he wouldn't have told her to run away.
No, but that's not it.
From number two, suddenly, one day, in the forest...
No, that's not it.
If that's number one and number three is number three, there must be something in number two.
What do you mean by that?
Does that mean there's something in there?
What do you mean there's something in there?
What, what, what?
Number two is right.
Who are you?
I'm not joking or anything.
When I was a kid, the bear was a bear.
It has a little human heart, but it's a bear after all.
So run away quickly.
I'm going to eat you.
Is it such a deep song?
One day, in the forest, you met a bear, right?
On the way to the flowering forest, you met a bear.
That's as far as you can go.
But the bear will follow you later.
That means you're going to bring a spear.
What the bear says is, Miss, run away.
Stacola-sa-sa-sa, Stacola-sa-sa-sa.
Who is this Stacola-sa-sa-sa?
I think it's a young lady.
I'm saying it's a young lady, but it's a Stacola-sa-sa-sa.
It's a little weird to say run away.
What, what, what?
Wait a minute.
Miss, wait a minute.
A fallen thing, a white shell, a small arrow.
Thank you, Mr. Bear.
Let's sing in gratitude.
This woman has a lot of knowledge.
How many songs do you have?
All of Komote's songs are weird.
It's weird, isn't it?
I'm addicted to the pond.
It's hard.
Hello.
I'm telling you it's hard.
Help me.
It's weird, isn't it?
And there was something weird about Doremi's song.
It's weird.
It's weird, isn't it?
Why is Moominpappa wearing a silk hat instead of clothes?
But isn't everyone wearing clothes?
Non-non's brother is wearing it.
I don't know.
They don't have to wear anything.
It's a simple story.
If you don't wear a silk hat, you can't distinguish yourself from Moomin.
And I don't have this.
In the past, my father didn't wear a silk hat.
My mother was very mistaken about Moomin and my father.
My mother wanted Moomin.
I don't know.
I'm a fool.
My mother said,
I'm Moomin.