You're angry, aren't you?
I'm not angry at all.
Is there anything you want to say?
Who is it?
There's a lot I want to say.
When I first came out, I was wondering why the audience didn't say I was cute.
You weren't?
There was something I had to say.
That was, Machan is cute?
I don't have anything to say about Machan being cute. I've already changed my mind about it.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
It's starting again today.
It's amazing. Machan is so cute.
It's all over the place.
Well, I want to say something I've already figured out.
Speak! You have to say something you've already figured out.
Well, how many weeks ago was it?
In my car...
I don't know.
Ah, the scratch?
It wasn't a scratch.
You told me that you had a nail stuck in your car.
Yes, I did.
You did, didn't you?
I didn't want to say it, but it happened again.
This time it was a strange way of sticking, so I bought a tire.
It cost 40,000 yen.
Please.
Why me?
You did it from the side.
Who did it?
It was Jaguar.
You had a nail stuck in Jaguar's foot.
You must be proud of it.
I did it from Yuta.
Oh, come on.
A human being did it.
Is that so?
He's telling me to do it again.
He's telling me to do it from the side.
That's for sure.
That's right.
I'm scared to do it.
Why?
You have your car.
You look like a fool!
You look like a fool who can't drive!
I don't know what to do.
It's okay because I'm here.
Here is more dangerous.
This is more dangerous.
I really can't do it.
What is this?
Can I do it?
What do you mean by scary?
I'm going to do it.
Something spiritual?
No, it's not something spiritual.
Oh, then it's fine.
And it seems that the person himself said it, right?
Yes.
That ******, right?
Yes, yes, it's me, it's me.
That person's story is really scary, right?
Yes.
The other day, I heard it because it was now,
and I was like, wow!
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I really want to say this.
If you hear it, you'll really want to say it.
If you hear it today, when you go home,
your friends will really want to say it.
Because when you hear it, everyone will be like, wow!
Really?
It's a true story.
It's not a story from the past.
Then tell me.
Well, I was tired from work.
Don't suddenly say, wow!
No, it's not like that.
It's like, it's you!
No, it's not such a childish story.
If it's like that, I'll be like, wow!
If it's like that, I won't say it.
Well, I was really tired from work, and it was comfortable.
And it was a mansion.
The elevator in the mansion was open, so I thought I'd get on.
A man with a hat over his head,
he was like this, trying not to show his face.
I see.
I thought it was disgusting.
But it can't be helped.
So I got on and said, good evening,
but it was like this.
And then it opened in the middle,
and he went down.
At that time, it hit him,
so I said, I'm sorry.
I ignored that,
and I went out like this, trying not to show my face.
I thought there was a weird guy.
I went back to my room.
After I calmed down a little, I looked around,
and there was blood on the place where it hit me.
I see.
I thought, what is it?
I thought it was disgusting.
And then a few days later,
when I got home, I heard a sound,
so I looked at it.
A policeman was standing,
and he said, I'm sorry.
Actually, a few days ago,
there was a murder at the police station.
Didn't you see a suspicious person?
I see.
He said that.
He said that, but he was really busy with the drama,
and when I saw him,
he said something about the situation.
It's hard, isn't it?
So I said, I don't know.
Then he said nothing.
I said, really?
And then the next day,
I turned on the TV,
and there was news that there was a murder at the police station.
At the police station.
Oh, really.
That's what I thought.
The criminal was arrested.
And the criminal's face picture came out.
When I saw that face,
it was the policeman.
No!
It's your will, isn't it?
But this is scary, isn't it?
This is scary!
Why did you come?
I came to kill, that's why.
Is that what it means?
That's right.
When I opened the door,
I was killed.
Oh, I see.
It's really scary, isn't it?
But when I heard this,
I really wanted to tell someone.
Normally,
I have a scary story now,
so I can't do it normally.
This is scary.
Oh, I see.
So I had to open the door,
and it was really good.
I see.
Actually, that's right.
I saw it.
It would have been dangerous
if I had told you to wear a hat like this.
I'm completely mouth-closed.
But you're supposed to open it.
I'll open it.
It's the story of the other day.
It's scary.
Living alone is scary.
Well, it's scary even if you're not alone.
I was taking a shower,
and when I came out,
my body was wet,
and I heard a noise.
A security guard came in,
and he was about to come.
Who are you?
I said, who are you?
And he was a security guard.
You said his name.
That's right.
There was a water leak,
so I called him,
but he didn't answer,
so I said I wanted to see him.
And he looked at me.
I thought he was looking at me.
I think it was this way.
Either way.
You can't do that anymore.
But in that case,
you can sign the contract.
You can sign it.
You can see it.
It's really scary.
If you have one security guard,
you can't open it.
There are usually two security guards.
Yes, usually.
Even in the inspection.
That's right.
You can't break it if there are two.
Right?
Don't think it's a lie.
Yes, yes.
But it's like a patrol card,
with only one person.
I have that one as well.
But if you look at it from here,
it's a patrol card.
You can't do that.
It's a security guard.
It's a security guard from the neighborhood.
In general,
there should be a person who knows.
It's scary.
It's really scary.
It's okay.
You can shout again,
if you say so.
You can shout.
Even if you say it, you won't be able to do it, right?
If it was you, you'd probably stop like this, right?
Yeah, like this.
Even if you do this, you'd probably do this.
You came to the bozap, right?
You saw a lot of things, right?
You can win, right?
I can win?
I'm confused.
If you go too far, it's like this.
It's like this.
There seems to be something today, right?
That's right.
Let's all read it.
Hurry up and get out of here!
Endo-kun and I did it!
What kind of name should I give to the child that will be born?
The program?
I asked a specialist teacher to see it.
Really?
Yes.
Would you like to see it?
This time, congratulations to Ms. Chiaki.
So, for the baby who is expected to be born in May next year,
I asked Mr. Junichiro Yamaguchi, the first person of life science.
First of all, both of you are from the planet of hell.
I think that the planet of hell is probably a simple person who does not suit entertainers.
In other words, Mr. Endo is a very serious person and has a very strong personality.
So, he's not the kind of person who does a lot of things in a combination.
So, he's not good at comedy.
I think he's the kind of person who does things like a student or an engineer.
And I think his wife is a very smart person.
She hates nonsense, hates lies, and is very serious, so she helps her husband very much.
So, when I look at this, I think this husband, this father, got a very good god.
I think it will be a good family.
What do you mean father?
What if it's a boy?
The name Mr. Endo is 17 years old and 21 years old.
He's 38 years old just by his last name.
If you add his last name, he's already 50 or 60 years old, and he doesn't have a good last name at all.
I've been doing this for 40 years, so I don't know.
It's a very difficult name.
So, Mr. Endo is only 63 years old.
His last name is Yoshiteru, or Yoshikito.
The name Yoshiteru is the best.
All of them are 63 years old and have a good last name.
Mr. Yoshiteru and Mr. Yoshikito have a good last name of 35 years old.
This name is a good name for Mr. Endo.
Next, by chance, the current Prime Minister is Junichiro.
Junichiro is surprised by his athleticism, so his name is Pittanko.
All of them are 63 years old.
Junichiro is 25 years old.
He's very lucky because he's young.
That's why it was important.
First of all, when the eldest son is born, everyone is Ichiro.
Ichiro and Taro are the eldest sons, so I think this name is Pittanko.
What if it's a girl?
It's very difficult for a girl to have a name.
Uedake is 38 years old.
This name, Yurika, is a perfect name.
63 years old is very lucky.
Yurika is lucky to be married at the age of 35.
The middle one is lucky to be middle-aged.
The environment around it is good.
It's good for money and health.
I think this name is the best.
It's amazing.
It's a good name even if it's old.
Junichiro.
Yurika.
It's up to you.
What?
If it's a girl, it's this.
If it's a boy, it's this.
Let's go with Junichiro.
The name is so easy.
It's okay.
Let's go with Junichiro.
It's okay for a boy or a girl.
It's a bad name.
Let's go with Junichiro.
Let's go home and ask my wife.
I'll give you this.
Really?
You can take this.
I'll definitely take this.
If you take this, it's the end.
It's the end.
You haven't thought of anything yet?
I haven't thought of anything yet.
If it's like this, it's only Tanaka and me.
That's right.
Eh?
What are you doing?
I just want to say something.
By the way,
Other than Endo,
We also want to see your fortune for next year.
Eh?
It's from me.
This person,
From his name,
He is very precious and stubborn.
If you think like this,
Even if the person in front of you says,
He is a person who passes through his beliefs.
So, I think it would be nice to make it a little softer
I think it would be nice to make it a little softer
After that,
If you want to see your fortune for next year,
I want to see your fortune for next year.
From December 2012,
To February 2016,
The fortune is very strong.
In particular, next year,
It is the strongest year of the best fortune in the past 10 years.
If you do it a lot,
16 years will be a little bit of a slump in a year.
If you do it without a slump,
It will be perfect.
With a little kindness,
If you listen to what people say,
It is the strongest year of the best fortune in the past 10 years.
This person has a total of 33 names.
Mr. Konda Soichiro also has 33 names.
Because he has a strong name
I want you to expect a lot from him.
But, there is a number 12 in the middle of the name.
This number 12 is a very bad case of interpersonal relationships.
So,
If you look at it from a person's point of view,
It is the strongest year of the best fortune in the past 10 years.
It is the same hell as Mr. Endo.
Hell is good for the past 3 years.
This year is the best year.
Next year is probably a new first step.
If you do it carefully at that time,
It will be better for the next year to 4 years.
Next year, be careful.
I will be a person who has a lot of potential.
His face is the best in his life in my opinion.
His name is 31,
and he has been blessed with wealth and work for his whole life.
His name is Saki,
and his 23rd month is the best name of all men.
He is always encouraged by the people around him.
He is perfect.
He has been doing well for the past 3 years.
Next year, he will be the best in the last 10 years.
I think he will grow a lot next year.
Oh, he is going.
Mr. Masumoto has a very different personality from the general public.
He is charismatic.
He has a strong mindset.
His luck is very good.
Next year, he will be the best in the last 10 years.
He is the first-place Mercury.
The first-place Mercury is the midsummer.
Next year will be a bit more difficult.
By working hard at the time of the strong star of next year, the next year's fortune will be better.
I'm going to be 40 years old this time, but I'm not married yet.
I'd like to hear from you in the future.
I'm still young when I say I'm 40 years old, but if I don't get married, my partner will know right away.
So I think it's better to meet someone who is older than you.
Even if you're 13 or 15 years old, or 20 years old, I think you'll get along well with that kind of person.
My husband is gone now, but he's kind to me.
A person who can make a husband is a kind person.
I think you have to choose such a person.
If you get married, it'll be the best time of the year.
Congratulations!
I'm looking forward to it.
What do you think? Do you think he's right?
When I'm talking, I hear the sound of a motorcycle.
Mr. Yamada is perfect.
I'm working more and more.
You said you'd grow next year.
My work is getting less and less.
It's true.
We're the same all the time.
I have a feeling that I'm going to grow from next year.
Why?
I don't know why, but I have a feeling.
I'm sleepy.
I don't know if we can talk about this right now.
I have a feeling.
A feeling?
I'm just saying it over and over again.
I'm just saying I have a feeling.
I really have a feeling.
Please do your best.
What's your name?
Can I call you Mr. Matsumoto?
I'm going to be born in May.
Before that, please tell me your name.
I'm Luke Panchama.
I want you to be strong.
I want you to take care of me for the rest of my life.
Thank you.
Please give this to Hanagawa-san.
I'll take it.
If you're born, I'll give it to you.
That's right.
You're going to give it to Endo, too?
I'll give it to him.
Really? Can you promise me now?
Why are you using standard Japanese?
If you're born, I'll give it to you.
Can I tell you a really bad story about my wedding?
Mr. Matsumoto gave it to me.
Mr. Yamada also gave it to me.
These two haven't given it to me yet.
Why didn't you give it to me?
Especially Hamada-san.
I'm still a little nervous.
It doesn't matter.
It's hard to get it.
I want to see if I can give it to you.
When did you give it to him?
I gave it to all of them.
What do you mean, all of them?
The other day, Mr. Komuro came to Hajima.
It was downtown.
He gave me 500,000 yen.
That's a lot.
He asked me if 250,000 yen was okay.
I was driving, and I said, okay.
Why am I the same age as him?
You have a lot of debt to Mr. Komuro.
I see.
That's right.
50,045,000 yen.
Don't say such a bad thing.
It's downtown.
He's dirty.
That's the only time he went downtown.
When did you give him 1000 yen?
I gave it to him in the dressing room.
I thought you were going to throw a party or something.
I haven't done it yet.
I gave 100,000 yen to Endo, and 400,000 yen to me.
How much did you give him?
I gave him a tire.
I forgot.
You don't have a tire.
That's right.
I see a lot of mischief.
Your character is mischievous.
That's good.
It will grow soon.
But 400,000 yen is different.
Keep doing mischief.
That's why I came here.
I did my best.
I received more than I expected today.
But you don't show up here often, do you?
No, I don't.
I don't have a day off.
Why are you lying?
It's true.
I have 8 days off a week.
I really don't have a day off.
So I thought I'd go next year.
Suddenly, in December, I told my manager.
Hey, I don't have a day off.
It's been a long time since I've been on the same stage with you.
I'm sweating so much on this stage.
Endo, say something good.
Something is strange today.
I'm sweating a lot.
You're getting excited.
I've been watching you since a while ago.
I thought it was hard.
I thought so, too.
I felt sorry for you.
I'm finally better now.
There's a lot of white hair here.
But it's better today.
Before the perm, I was like this.
This program was provided by the sponsor you see.