I'm Dantan's child care worker.
Nice to meet you.
Don't be silly.
T-t-that's enough.
Naniwa Kijji
Quite solid!
What will you do if it goes like this?
It's OK.
Really?
This is also gunpowder, right?
Yes.
It's OK.
Good.
How is it?
There are quite a few.
All of these are gunpowder.
I was lucky to succeed the other day.
How much gunpowder do you want?
I don't need much.
You don't need much.
The outside is like this.
I'll do it somehow.
There are quite a few.
I think there are three times more than the other day.
I don't know if it's dangerous.
I was practicing to get out of the rope yesterday, but I don't know if I can do it.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
My hands are tied.
It's dangerous.
Is it painful?
No, it's OK.
Can you do it?
I can do it.
I'll do it.
You can't move, can you?
I can't.
If you do this much.
I can't do it.
You can't?
Yes.
I can't do it anyway.
It's hard to move.
Are you OK?
If I tie my legs, I can't move at all.
Can you do it?
I'll do it if it's three times.
No, it's OK.
I have no choice but to do it.
Thank you.
Let's go.
The key.
Yes.
Thank you.
Are you OK?
Yes.
The key is locked.
Let's go.
It's dangerous.
You should leave.
OK.
Let's go.
Yes.
It's dangerous.
It looks big.
Let's go.
This one?
Yes.
Let's go.
I got it.
It's dangerous.
Can't you get out?
It's too dangerous.
I'll go and check.
Hurry up.
It's dangerous.
It's too dangerous.
I'll go and check.
Hey!
It's moving.
Are you OK?
The key is...
Yes.
I'm hungry.
It was hot.
Eating hot food makes you hungry.
Yes.
That's what I think.
It was hot.
But I did well.
It's moving.
You can do it again.
Hurry up.
Everyone is fine, right?
What are you saying?
The audience is fine, but the people on the stage are not.
I have insomnia.
Why?
I have a lot of worries.
What worries?
I have a lot of things to think about.
Really?
Yes.
Everyone calls me Machan.
But I'm Matsumote.
So everyone calls me Machan.
If I'm Kato, I'm Kato-chan.
When I think about it, I can't sleep.
Kato-chan is Kato-chan.
So you're calling me Kato-chan.
Even if that's the case...
That's right.
I don't think that's natural.
You're living in that world.
I'm always full rotation.
I'm full rotation, but I'm out of charge.
Is that so?
Sometimes I'm really into it and I think it's amazing.
But sometimes I'm not.
But sometimes I'm out of charge and I don't care.
In the middle of the night, I'm driving.
I'm doing construction work.
At about 2 or 3 o'clock, 10 or 20 people gather and dig a hole.
I don't ask anyone to do this construction work.
If I do it as a hobby, what should I do?
Old men gather and say,
Let's do it again.
The people who met yesterday dug a hole.
If I'm doing it, I think it's terrible.
Sometimes I'm not.
Sometimes I'm out of charge and I think it's amazing.
If I'm doing it as a hobby, what should I do?
You're out of charge.
You're out of charge again.
It's not my body. It's strange.
Why?
I don't care.
It's here.
This wrinkle is strange.
It's not wrinkle.
It's the skin, isn't it?
It's sticking. It's impossible.
It's impossible.
When I did it, I wanted to do it beautifully.
But I'm doing it because I'm doing it.
If I do it normally, I won't do it.
It's frustrating.
It's strange here.
It's strange.
If it falls, take it.
I didn't think about it, but I thought about it in my room.
You can just cut yours. We have enough of this.
What is Komura Gairi?
If you stretch it like this, it will be like this, right?
If you think you can do it, you can do it, right?
Komura Gairi? No, I've never been Komura Gairi.
What?
It hurts. The line between the fingers is like this.
Your shoulder is also bad, right?
I've never been Komura Gairi.
I see.
Is your father big?
My husband is big.
He's short.
Why do you want to be Komura Gairi?
If your eyes get tired, your head will hurt, right?
If my eyes get tired, my head will hurt.
I don't want to be Komura Gairi.
What about you?
Why are you touching me?
Why are you touching me softly?
You have a strong head when you were a kid.
What?
Have you ever been hit by a car?
No.
I have.
You have, right?
But I've never been hit by a car.
I was hit by a car.
I was crying.
Are you OK?
I'm not OK.
I said, it's ok.
Then he ran away.
What a scary man.
When we were going to the place,
the guy who was waiting for us was shaking his head.
Oh, I see.
I thought he was shaking his head,
and I thought it would be fine if I went behind him.
I went behind him and he was like,
BOOM!
He was shaking his head like this.
Then he fell down.
It was 30 seconds later.
BOOM!
I said, it's ok.
Then he was like,
BOOM!
What a scary man.
The worst thing that happened to me was,
the brake was stuck here.
The brake was stuck here?
Yes.
At the bottom of the bicycle.
The brake was stuck here,
and I got out of the bicycle.
I ran around the corner,
and a bicycle came.
There was a big bicycle
that was on a rice field.
The old man came,
and I hit him.
BOOM!
I said,
I'm here.
Then he fell down.
It was terrible.
I said, it's ok.
It was so heavy.
It was like this.
I said,
it's ok.
I got out of the bicycle.
I was like,
BOOM!
I'm an idiot.
Well,
I heard that
Nessie was found.
You saw the newspaper together, right?
Yes.
What? You don't know?
You don't know?
You are so stupid.
You remember all the bad things.
What?
You know that if you poop,
you have to clean it.
Everyone knows that.
I know that.
Do you know that?
You were pooping.
I'm not a shogun.
I know that.
You are so stupid.
If you think about it,
there are other stupid things.
There are other stupid things.
Since a long time ago?
What?
I've seen Nekomuzume.
Really?
Hey, hey, hey.
I've told you many times.
I've seen Nekomuzume.
Where did you see it?
When?
When I was in the 11th grade.
Near my house.
Near your house?
With whom?
With Nekomuzume.
What a stupid story.
If you knew that I saw Nekomuzume,
you would have brought more friends.
You didn't think of it.
Nekomuzume left because I was alone.
What time was it?
Around 6 in the evening.
Where? Near your house?
Yes.
What were you doing?
I was playing and coming back.
On your way home?
Yes.
What did you do?
I was wearing a kimono
that looked like a bakabon.
Hey, hey.
It was red.
I was asking for the color.
It looked like a bakabon.
And I was looking at
the back of the kimono.
You were looking at the back of the kimono?
Yes.
I was like,
What kind of hairstyle was that?
It looked like a bakabon.
And your face?
My face was like a cat's eye.
A cat-like eye?
Why were you standing like that?
What were you doing?
I was standing like this.
Why were you standing like that?
Did you talk?
No, not at all.
I didn't talk.
That's the point.
Why didn't you say that?
Why didn't you say anything?
You were looking at me.
That's the point.
I was looking at you.
So I was standing like this.
Ah, at you.
Yes, yes.
I was like,
you.
You!
Didn't you just say that your ears were like this?
You were doing like this.
You were like a cat.
What the hell?
And then, it's fine.
If it's like this, it's fine to lie.
And then, on the roof, you were going like this.
I was surprised.
And then, you were like this.
You were doing like this.
You were talking like this.
And then, you were like this.
It was hard.
But that was really like that.
It was the first time I heard that you saw a cat girl.
I told you.
It was the first time I heard that you were wearing a kimono.
I want to see your kimono.
I told you.
It's red.
And it's colored.
Don't draw your ass.
I'm talking to you.
Why are you drawing your ass?
You're so rude.
That's right.
It stinks.
There's no one who's so cheeky.
You're also cheeky.
Why are you so cheeky?
Where is the material that you're not cheeky?
What are you talking about?
I'm a gentleman.
It's a gentleman's attitude.
You're the one who's a gentleman.
What?
People who meet you for the first time don't talk to you.
That's how much you're a gentleman.
You know.
What?
How to deal with people who are above you.
Do it properly.
I'm not doing it at all.
Because when you're talking in the dressing room in the shadow,
you've never said anything about people.
You.
I've seen a lot of talents on this show.
I've never said anything.
Tamori is.
Wait.
Are you stupid?
I don't understand that feeling.
Did you raise your hand?
Stop it.
Why are you a marionette?
I don't know.
I'm just dancing like a robot.
Don't say stupid things.
You're saying a lot.
I'm not saying anything.
Please correct me.
You're saying a lot of stupid things.
Don't say stupid things.
Even about Sanma-san.
I've never said anything.
Don't say stupid things.
I can't believe it.
Are you stupid?
You're always talking about stupid things.
Say it like that.
Say it.
You're so strict.
You should think about it.
Why are you laughing?
I'm not laughing.
What kind of car do you drive?
And if you can modify your car as you like, what would you do?
Modify my car?
Yes.
You like to tease me, don't you?
You don't drive a normal car, do you?
No, I don't.
I'm driving a normal car.
If it's true, what do you want to do?
So...
What should I do?
I want to cut the roof.
I'm a Century now.
I'm a Big Man.
Why are you a Big Man?
You're a company.
I'm an international company.
Why are you angry?
Why are you so angry?
So I want to cut the roof.
I don't have a Century convertible.
I see.
I want to cut the roof.
That's what I want to do.
I see.
What about you?
I...
I have a headlight.
If I turn it on, a missile will come out.
When something happens.
I'll do my best to turn it on.
Yeah.
And I'll make a caterpillar.
I'll go to many places.
Why are you an elementary school student?
I'll make a tree.
That's nice.
I'll put it on my house.
Next.
I'll stop this.
I'll stop it.
Is it OK?
It's OK.
Time is running out.
Yeah, it's OK.
It's hard to laugh.
Yeah.
It's going to be hard to be a comedian.
Do you know why?
Why?
Well...
Japan is not only Japanese.
Yeah.
There are many foreigners.
There are.
Yeah.
We have to involve foreigners.
But foreigners who have been in Japan for a long time know Japanese.
What's wrong with that?
What?
You're touching the caterpillar.
I'm not touching it.
Why are you acting like this?
What?
When you're talking, if you scratch your butt, you'll get a caterpillar.
Stop it.
What are you talking about?
It's going to be hard from now on.
There are many foreigners.
Yeah.
I was doing construction work.
I was doing construction work in Ashiba-kun.
I was building a house.
Yeah.
I saw it.
They were all foreigners.
Yeah.
They were kneading cement.
They were all foreigners.
The refrigerator was made by Eskimo.
What are you talking about?
They were all foreigners.
They're going to build a house for foreigners.
Yeah.
Hey, ask me something.
Do you know that you're harming us?
Harming you?
All you see are buttons.
Translated by Releska