In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Arai, Chikijiki Miyaji's dramatic action, cue!
This time, I, Oosaki Yamazaki...
Oosaki?
That's my real name!
I'm going to give you a special quiz using Miyaji.
Let me introduce the panel.
Downtown Tsukkomi, Hamada Masatoshi!
Today, we have Miyaji as our guest.
How do you feel?
I want to see how Miyaji moves.
You're not in the mood!
Last but not least, Masumoto Hidashi!
Yamazaki-san has done this before, but I don't think he's done it yet.
What are you talking about?
I don't think he's done it yet.
It hurts when you hold it here.
Next, we have Endo-kun and Tanaka-kun!
What do you think he's doing?
What?
I think he's doing the right thing.
I think he's doing his best.
Let's see your reactions one by one.
Are you going to answer seriously?
Please answer seriously.
Where do you think he's doing it?
If there's a chance, I want him to do it more and more.
I can't do it!
He's the god of comedy!
Everyone is the god!
What are you doing?
B1 producer, Sugakenshi!
Good evening!
You have a good smile.
You have to admit that your attitude is different.
Sugakenshi, you're in trouble.
That's good.
The winner will receive 100,000 yen from me!
Really?
Show us!
Do you have your wallet?
My wallet is upstairs.
That's not good.
I don't understand.
Let's start over.
The winner will receive...
This is Yamazaki-san.
Is this okay?
The winner will receive...
This too.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Let's go to the first question!
Let's do it together!
Dramatic Action Q!
I'm from Kitamachi.
I'm the daughter of Toyama Saemon.
Nice to meet you!
I've been here for a year.
Everyone, please raise your hands!
Why is Otomo speaking in English?
Yuki, is it true that you were forced to leave your father's home
to pay for the rent?
Yes, that is correct.
What kind of father is he?
He grabbed my chest with both hands and pushed me up and down.
Is there anything wrong with that?
Don't be afraid!
Unfortunately, I don't know what you're talking about.
Who are you talking to?
Shut up!
I've been here for a year and I've seen all of Toyama's cherry blossoms!
Stop!
Here's the question.
How many times can Mr. Kin shake his left and right breasts in 30 seconds?
Let's do two at a time.
Mr. Kawada.
Go ahead.
110 times.
Mr. Matsumoto.
It's a little short.
87 times.
Left and right.
Is that so?
Yes.
What are you going to do?
Is that so?
Didn't you hear what I said?
I really wanted you to say that.
Turn off the camera.
Let's do our best.
I'm serious right now.
I'm sorry.
You said you'd do your best.
I did.
Let's go!
120 times.
Let's go with Mr. Kin.
You can't go over that.
Mr. Tsubasa.
121 times.
Let's see the answer.
Dramatic action!
Cue!
That was fast!
That was really fast!
Don't laugh!
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know what she's doing either.
Look at her face.
85 times for the right breast.
127 times for the left breast.
And 212 times for the right breast.
That means...
There's no correct answer.
But if it was Jinjitsu...
Mr. Tsubasa.
If you overdo it, you're out.
I didn't overdo it.
You didn't?
Then stop it.
The second time.
Let's do our best.
Did you overdo it?
I didn't overdo it.
Mr. Tsubasa is correct!
One point.
That was easy.
Let's move on to the next question.
Let's go!
Why aren't you talking to me?
I agree.
The world is heavy, so let's dance.
On the other hand,
a woman's heart is heavy.
It's a piece of cake.
How to get out.
It's a little difficult.
Let's work!
There are 50 pieces of underwear
that Lupin wore on stage.
How many pieces can you take in one minute
with that magic hand
and put on your head?
Dramatic Action Cue!
How many pieces can you take in one minute
with that magic hand
and put on your head?
Teacher.
Teacher is working now.
Fujiko-chan!
I don't know what you're talking about.
6 pieces in one minute!
That's right!
Oh, the sun, the sun.
Oh, it hurts.
Fujiko-chan!
Can I say something?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Dramatic Action Cue!
How many pieces can you take in one minute
with that magic hand
and put on your head?
Teacher.
Teacher is working now.
His last name is Kuruma.
His name is Tranjiro.
Welcome!
My name is Kelake.
My name is Chiyoda.
I'm going to drink champagne today.
This champagne!
What is it?
This is it.
What are you talking about?
Don't be so scary.
You can't do that!
Stop!
I don't understand, what do you want to do?
I'll explain.
Tora-san was about to sell champagne
There are 5 bottles of champagne
The question is how many seconds it takes to open all of them
About 2 minutes and a half
I think it takes about 30 seconds for one bottle
You hit a good spot
I want to make more noise
Matsumoto-san
28 minutes
It takes this long
The pacemaker stops in the middle
It has nothing to do with the heart
11 minutes
That's a long time
What is this?
I think it takes about 1 minute and a half
1 minute and a half is 6 minutes
I didn't say anything
I just said it
It hurts to hit the pacemaker like this
Is that so?
I understand
Stop it
Do you have enough time?
Yes
Let's talk
The last one
1 minute and 25 seconds
Dramatic action
It hurts
What is this?
It's fast
It's really fast
Don't look at me
Amazing
The correct answer is
1 minute and 25 seconds
Congratulations
You can't say that
2 points
Suga-san wins
Thank you
Congratulations
Yamasaki is okay
We'll do it next
Don't say yes
This is better
I'm confident that I can do better
I'm confident
Let's do it
It's okay
Let's go to the next question
Miyaji-san's dramatic action
Cue
The correct answer is
Are there only people?
You can't say that
Is there a reverse?
If there's no reverse, we can't do it
If you win
I'll give you 2 points
It's a reverse
3 points
Yamasaki, where are you going?
Look at this
3 points
Let's do our best
Let's do it
I said it before
What?
I don't know the reason
I don't know
When I got in the car
There was a strong smell of poop
I was wondering why
I couldn't open the window
I looked at my slippers
I was pooping
I know the reason
I don't know
I don't know where I pooped
Before I got in the car
I puke
I didn't go anywhere
I didn't getсят
I didn't get anything
What kind of place am I living in?
I don't know
You probably went to the bathroom
You haha
You don't even abused it
You don't Glen
You pooped it
And that's when it all ended. You threw away your slippers, right?
That was good, right?
Yeah, it was good.
And when you got home, there was no one in the car.
I thought that was the end of it.
And that day, you went home and took a shower, right?
You took a shower and went to bed, right?
And when you got to the bed, you were like,
What the hell?
I knew it!
It was you!
No, it wasn't!
This is one of the 7 mysteries.
I smelled poop again and wondered why.
And that day, I went to bed.
I put up with it.
You slept well, didn't you?
You were in bed and smelled like poop.
And the next day, I smelled poop again.
You did that before you went to bed, didn't you?
Of course, the next day, I took a shower and went to bed.
But when I got to the bed, I smelled poop again.
I was like, what the hell?
Before I went to bed, I smelled poop again.
What the hell?
No, it wasn't.
No, it wasn't!
You can't lie like that!
How did you know it was poop?
It was brown.
Where?
From the back.
How did you know it was poop?
I went to the bathroom and smelled it.
I smelled it, but why did I smell poop again?
Who did it?
I did it little by little.
Little by little?
Little by little.
I did it little by little.
No, it wasn't.
It wasn't.
Why?
It wasn't!
You can't say that as a partner.
But you can only think of it as an outsider.
I even took a shower before I went to bed.
That's strange.
You didn't smell it today?
I didn't smell it today.
Well, I did smell it in my underwear.
I don't care about that.
What do you mean you don't care?
You should be more worried about it.
It's my butt. It has nothing to do with me.
What do you mean it has nothing to do with you?
What?
I'm getting angry.
I'm really angry.
I don't understand it at all.
There are strange things in life.
I think we should talk about that later.
What is it?
You know Sazaebon, right?
Yes.
I'm the one who came up with that.
I wrote about it on an evening show in Osaka.
Just once.
That's right. It was about 10 years ago.
Everyone is talking about Sazaebon now.
I get angry every time I see it.
It was in the court, right?
What the hell is this?
Go to the court.
Why are you backing out?
I wanted to go forward.
This is the real deal.
Go to the court.
I went down once to go to the court.
I went down to go forward.
That's right.
It's the principle of the lower class.
Go to the court.
Don't say it every time.
Hey, don't do this.
How many times have you done this on this show?
I'm sure there are a lot of VTRs.
Is it a picture?
That's right.
It's true.
But you have to back me up.
What?
When I say something, you say,
Soya, soya, soya.
Soya, soya.
Why can't I say it?
Say it.
I don't need that kind of love.
I'll be there soon.
Okay.
You can't do that.
When Hamada-san broke his leg,
At night, Hamada-san ran around the hospital in Tokyo.
I'll ask Mr. Matsumoto of Aikata Moe.
Yes.
In some kind of accident,
When you lost your leg,
Before you go to the hospital,
If there's something you have to do first,
If there's something like emergency treatment,
Please tell me.
This is not a joke.
It's not a joke.
It's not like you can get it.
Why?
I say everything that has a shape breaks.
It's not like that.
When you get it,
Of course you'll go to the hospital.
I'll go to the hospital.
You have to go to the hospital.
It's an emergency.
If there's something like emergency treatment before you go,
If there's something, please tell me.
Do you have Makiron?
Who is that?
Who is that now?
No, it's me.
There are a lot of Makiron.
It's really easy.
It's three keys.
The most troublesome thing is,
You put it like this, right?
I've never been put in a place like this.
That's right.
By itself?
If you leave it like this,
The bottom becomes flat.
So I want you to make a foot with a toothpick or something in your house.
I don't like Twitter.
That's really the best.
The toothpick is good, too.
I don't need a toothpick.
At one point, Mr. Matsumoto said that Hamada had an injury in his foot.
He said he was actually more sick.
What kind of disease is he really sick with?
This is...
Wait a minute.
Hey.
I'm healthy except for my feet.
You're a close friend.
But if I say this too much, I'll get a lot of premonitions.
It's going to be really bad.
I asked him later.
You said I didn't have enough glasses, right?
I looked it up.
I really didn't have enough glasses.
That's not true.
You know,
I was a judge.
Why are you talking in a high voice?
It's true.
It's true that it's true.
There was a disaster, right?
Yes, there was.
At that time, everyone was wearing glasses.
You put it on your pillow and go to bed, right?
It suddenly became an earthquake.
Everyone rushed out of the front door.
After that, everyone had no glasses.
I'm really in trouble.
I was so sad.
That's it.
Actually, everyone in the family had glasses.
I'm a school club member.
I belong to the Rikujougi.
I'm throwing a gun.
The teacher told me to make a voice when I throw it.
So how do you make a voice to throw it far away?
What kind of words should I say?
Please tell me.
By the way, when I ask my friends,
It seems that I'm saying,
Please show me the special of the year of the diamond.
Is there a special of the year of the diamond?
Yes, there is.
There is.
Is there?
Yes, there is.
Please tell me.
Yes, I will.
I'm not a 4th class like Toku.
I will tell you such a thing.
There is a special of the year of the diamond.
Let's throw a gun.
A gun.
Don't do that.
It's the year of the cicada.
After that, it's important.
After I throw it,
I throw a gun.
There is a special of the year of the diamond.
It's not good.
The best word is,
Tsumitachi.
Shimura-san, go home.
I'm on the train.
It's okay.
I often fall asleep.
Yes, you do.
At that time,
I sometimes hit my head against the window.
How should I react?
It's cool, isn't it?
That's because...
I can't do it at once.
If I think it's dangerous,
I should run properly.
It's cut off by the train.
The diamond is messed up.
This program was provided by the following sponsors.