Before the show, the kids are excited.
Let's do it!
Today is the day of the badminton tournament.
This show is different from the past.
Today is a little amazing.
If you get one point, you can get one prize.
Really?
This too?
Does that matter?
This is also a problem.
I didn't spend any money before, so I'm doing it here.
I think I should definitely do it.
I'll do it.
But the wind is strong.
It's difficult to do.
Mr. Kama said he didn't want to do it today.
Why?
I have a fever.
A fever?
Yes.
How did you get on the bus in May, which is 42 times?
It was not like that.
Suddenly?
Yes.
I was stuck in the bus.
I want you to go.
I'm a salaryman.
I'm often with salarymen.
I'll do my best.
Is that Mr. Hamau?
Yes.
He's there.
I'm going to do it.
How was it on the other show?
Let's do it.
Look at the products.
It's very luxurious.
Cars, bikes, 1 million yen.
If you get 1 point, you can get 1 product.
I don't want to do it.
I don't feel like doing it anymore.
I don't feel like doing it since last month.
Last month?
No, last month.
May?
May.
No, last month.
I don't feel like doing it.
I'm tired.
No, no, I'm not tired.
I want to go home.
I don't feel like doing it anymore.
I'm tired of doing it.
I don't know who you are.
You're not motivated?
No, no, no.
You're not motivated.
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Hey, hey, hey.
You're not motivated.
I was told to go to the nearest hospital.
What kind of hospital?
Let's go outside.
I can't go outside.
The tragedy that attacked Hamada.
Is it really that difficult to get a heart attack?
We can't record it like this.
What kind of stupid plan is this?
I wanted to do this with Minto.
This is a spiritual thing.
Do you want to do it with four people?
But the viewer will wonder why.
That's right.
What is it?
Why is the teacher so?
At the time of other projects, why is it like this?
That's right.
Good morning.
Oh, you surprised me.
That's right.
You surprised me.
How are you?
Good morning.
I came to the meeting for the concert.
Oh, really?
I thought you won.
I'm planning to use the bag.
But it's kind of dark.
It's a bit heavy.
I was thinking about playing badminton.
But I had a problem.
Hama-chan?
Yes, it's Hama-chan.
I have something to tell you.
I have a disease.
I don't know what to do.
Can I tell you?
Yes, you can.
If you have any questions, please feel free to ask.
No, no, no.
I'm really sorry.
I'll just leave it there.
I have to go to a meeting.
I'm late.
Excuse me.
Thank you for your time.
I was surprised.
I see.
Even though the appearance of Yoki-Sem Nobuchi, there is no island that is surprised by them now.
To measure the early resolution of the situation, together with the program producer, they return to Hamada.
Wait a minute.
Do not you do?
It will end soon. It is the usual pattern of badminton.
No, I have a little feeling.
May.
May?
What is 5 months?
It's not even 42 months.
It's a disease that makes you a new employee.
A new employee?
What month is it?
The month before the war.
Masaru Shiga wasn't caught either.
It's like that every time.
Yes, I've tried it.
It's terrible.
You should go home.
I will.
Look, look.
Mr. Hamada, you're over 40.
Go home.
Mr. Isaka, you should go home.
I can't help it.
You're acting like a young comedian.
I'm sorry.
I said too much.
Go home.
What?
What is this?
In the recording, Hamada, who has been accused of being responsible for the show,
will be in danger of losing the show.
What will be the solution?
What should I do?
Are you okay?
Is your head okay?
But it hurts, right?
It was painful.
It was painful to watch the young comedian.
He was saying, Batchkon.
I think it's impossible to talk about it.
It's impossible.
It's impossible to talk about it.
I think only badminton players can talk about it.
That's right.
What's wrong?
Can I take a picture?
Yes.
You can take a picture.
I'm curious about it.
But he is an academician, right?
Yes.
The atmosphere is different.
To be honest, I can't do what I'm trying to do now.
You can't do it yet.
No progress.
If that's the case, it's a beautiful power, but...
The ship that was about to board.
Even if I go home and get scolded by Yuri,
Yuri will...
I know.
What?
Yuri is...
The judge of the soccer team.
The one who has the A-class license.
The one who has the license for the nutritionist.
The one who makes mistakes.
My wife.
We have the same child.
So if you don't mind, if you don't have any other ideas, I can talk to you.
No, no, no.
If it's something unnecessary, I'm sorry.
No, it's not unnecessary.
If it's not, I can try it.
I'm a senior in the entertainment industry.
I may be a little harsh on you.
You should have told me.
There are good times.
You can do that.
I'm sorry.
I can't do anything.
If you do it, I'm sorry if I can't help you.
No, no, no.
I'm sorry.
I'll do my best.
Nomuchi is convinced by Hamada.
I'm sorry if I didn't help you.
No, no, no.
I'm really sorry.
Please.
I'll do it if I have to.
It's better for us to get closer.
That's right.
I think it's better to leave it to the crew.
What's wrong?
I just happened to be here.
Yes.
I was just...
Umm...
I just came by.
Oh, I see.
Are you feeling alright?
Umm...
I guess so.
I'm not in the mood.
You're more of a fan than we thought.
I guess so.
Masao is a senior.
I don't know if it's been a year, but I'm sorry to say this, but I like you.
I said it, but you know what I mean, right?
I'm sorry I'm late.
It's strange to say that I've been doing this for years, but I really like you.
I thought it was a good time to tell him this.
He is a cheerful and cheerful person.
That's amazing.
He is like a big brother.
I was able to exercise for free.
And later I was offered a job.
I'm grateful for this job.
And the audience is happy with it.
What are you talking about?
It's a long story.
It's hard to say.
I think you can only see yourself now.
Look around you.
There are many painful things.
Yamazaki, Tanaka, Endo.
They are painful.
What is painful? Their existence.
It's hard to not realize that we're suffering.
You can see that, right?
So, you know...
Life is only once.
It's a one-way trip.
Let's go!
With all our might!
Let's do our best!
That's all I can do.
life goes on
yamato
I loved to search for it
When I closed my heart to sadness
The flowers in the flower shop changed too
In my town, just one more time
Would you like to drink hot coffee?
I was asked at that shop
Why are you doing this?
Is our love over?
The seasons have changed too
You came to visit my room
And you were always cleaning
I don't know either, why are you here?
The town is filled with people shopping, soon it will be lit red
I'm avoiding people today, I'm just going home, just by myself
Without being able to cross the bridge, why are you here?
Belfour
I'll just go home, all alone
I'm waiting for you, who can't even touch my feet
I'm sorry.
How was it? Did you feel like you were a good audience?
You don't know, do you?
I can't say anything at this point.
You can't say anything.
I can't say anything.
Excuse me, your glasses are too hard.
You have a lot of glasses.
You have glasses.
Glasses?
Are you going to die?
Something is coming out.
It's going to die.
Which one? Which one?
This one. This one. This one.
This is amazing.
This is all stress.
In short, the world is full of fools.
Every time I meet a fool, I get a cramp.
I can't fix it.
When I'm in the car, I'm waiting for someone to call me on my cell phone.
I'm calling you from a place that's not a big street.
Then the opposite lane comes from the other side.
If I stop here, I'll stop here.
That idiot Saka Gen is a fool.
If you do that, I'll be half as bad.
Why?
If you let me go, I'll be like this.
I'll take 50% of your stupidity.
If someone who doesn't know comes, I'll be like, why are you here?
I was the only one who was in the back.
Me?
And then from the back, this part was all...
It was all...
I see.
I was like, I'm getting one, I'm getting half.
But the one who stopped by my side wasn't a Puku.
It wasn't. I gave them all to you.
They were all coming to me.
It was like, I was forced to carry one by a smelly, dirty shit.
That's not it.
Until now it was Puku.
I'm just kidding.
You're all so stupid.
I want to change that.
Can I be the mayor?
Please.
I want to change the most.
The parking lot at the intersection.
The parking lot of the car.
I want to make all of them 1 meter behind.
I can't turn when I come.
Okappa, you idiot!
Okappa?
Okappa, okappa!
Next month, I have a question for Matsumoto Residen's upcoming book.
I have a question.
You were a gorilla when you were in the third grade of elementary school.
Why did you change to a hippo when you were in the fourth grade?
If I were a gorilla, I would have been called a moth.
I don't know what you are talking about.
You are a gorilla, so you are not calling me a moth.
I can't say it at all.
Say it properly.
I am a moth.
Is this your first car?
I think I bought it for the first time.
I bought it for 10,000 yen before that.
Starlet.
I'm not a gorilla.
That's strange.
Why did you quit Starlet?
I'm tired of it.
I'm tired of Gorilla.
I'm tired of the law.
You knew it from the beginning.
No.
Cars are a means of transportation to the scene.
I was a member of the Gorilla Corps.
You were a member of the Gorilla Corps?
Yes, I was. I was a member of the 5th number.
I didn't care about anything else.
I was a member of the 5th number.
What did you do when you went to school?
I waited for the Gorilla Corps.
I was waiting for the Gorilla Corps.
Where did you wait for the Gorilla Corps?
I waited for the Churinjyo.
I waited for the Gorilla Corps.
Why do you say that again?
You should have said that at the beginning.
I do the Japanese style stop motion.
In my case, the gorilla was facing this way.
If you get in the way, the gorilla is facing this way.
After that, the gorilla does this.
No, no, no.
From the beginning, the gorilla does this.
Gorillas always do this.
There are times like this.
I usually...
No, no, no.
Hey, get out!
Fanto, whoů
Letů
Just a minuteů
Do not!
Have the power to overcome to me and push me machine!
Counter is boring!
So,if you wille mow down here.
Now after finishing lesson.
I can ln the veins...
OKů
It is also possible to go around because of gorilla.
Always like thatů
Can you suppress that in 3 years?
It's different from Mk.II
Right?
What do you do?
That's my hobby
My hobby is to share
Share?
Do you live with him?
Yes, it was hard
But I'm getting bad energy
This is interesting
I was the first one who ran with only one banana.
You were like, one banana!
So I changed my cover.
Because the fuel was bad?
Yes.
But I had ETC.
You were in the fourth grade?
You changed your ride in the second grade.
I wasn't in the second grade.
ETC is...
That's right.
What? You're just saying it randomly.
Stop with the chest thumping!
I would say that if you meet a bear, pretend you're dead.
What is the best way to deal with aliens?
Ah...
No, no, no.
What?
You've never met an alien, have you?
There is that woman in the area, Shigani Weaver.
You have to make it clear that it's not her.
It's not Shigani.
I'm not Shigani.
First of all...
When you meet her in the area...
When I meet her in the area, I'm not Shigani.
In the area, you only go to Shigani.
You don't aim for Shigani.
I don't know.
But, to be clear, I'm not Shigani.
If I don't say it out loud, he'll come in like this.
He'll come in like this.
He seems to be purring.
I'm not Shigani.
When I say Shigani, he'll start to talk.
If it's Shigani, it means that it's definitely Shigani.
Where are you looking at?
From the inside of my mouth.
Is this Shigani?
That's a stuffed animal.
What are you doing?
Why are you lying down?
This is Shigani.
It's easy.
First of all, if you say it's not Shigani, they'll think it's Shigani.
What are you going to do?
I'm very embarrassed.
You're going to come out and...
I thought I was a deer and I was like...
You're waiting.
I'm waiting.
I'm waiting for this nervousness to run away.
I'm going to punch.
You're the same.
You've been hitting me for a while.
You think you're waiting for me to come back.
Excuse me.
6 years old?
What are you talking about?
If this was a normal 42 year old, you wouldn't be so old, right?
I'm a dead man to you
At that time, if I'm told that I'm not Matsumoto-san, I'd be like, oh no
Well, that's not a good example
I would like to introduce a popular model of me back in the day
One boy in trouble
He looks outht bench
He Go where the hell are you
Give him Ninden
Keine
He proclaims to leach
It was like Hei!
It was like Hei, downwards
One guy Cloud
The other Soul
One girl