This is the first episode of Chikitsuki Super Cannonball at Gaki no Tsukai!
Mr. Tanabashi, the cold season is here again.
But it's okay. This is the last time we're shooting this year.
What?
The last time?
I've decided that there won't be any more shooting.
It's the last time.
So you won't have any more openings until the end of the year?
I don't think there will be any more shooting until May of next year.
That's not good.
It's been a while since we shot outside.
Yes.
It's a big spectacle.
I see.
It's the super cannonball.
It's not just us, right?
Let's start with this person.
It's cold.
Stop saying that.
I'm not saying that.
I'm just saying it's cold.
Let's do our best.
Let's go.
Okay.
Next is this person.
He had a good reputation.
What?
I remember it.
It's been a long week.
Yeah.
He looks like someone from a bar.
Maekun.
Let's go.
Next is this person.
His eyes are dead.
Do you still have a headache?
Good morning.
This is the back of a crab.
No matter how you look at it, it's the back of a crab.
The last one is this person.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
It's rare to see a person like him.
I was waiting for this person.
Is that so?
He told me to do this.
I see.
I got it.
He told me to do this.
Did you have a big mouth like that?
I have a big mouth.
The last one is this person.
Today, we will race with a special machine.
If you win, you will get 100,000 yen.
We will give you a machine.
Let's start with Mr. Mazumoto.
Is that so?
This is serious.
Let's choose machines one by one.
Mr. Mazumoto's machine is a crane.
Crane.
This is scary.
Can I ride this?
This is Mr. Mazumoto's machine.
Crane.
This is Mr. Machan's machine.
I will control this machine and win.
100,000 yen?
Thank you.
It's okay.
I think it's better.
Yes.
I will continue.
Please win.
Mr. Hamada.
Can you ride this?
It's a shovel car.
Shovel car.
This is my machine.
Mr. Hamada has lost the championship.
I can't win.
Last time, Mr. Hamada challenged with a stone shovel.
Next is Mr. Yamazaki.
Mr. Yamazaki's machine is a dump truck.
Dump truck.
I want to drive a dump truck.
This is Mr. Yamazaki's machine.
Dump truck.
Yamazaki is a speed racer.
He will win 100,000 yen with a dump truck.
Mr. Hamada's machine is a shovel car.
Shovel car.
Michael Hamada's machine is a pop mix.
Mr. Hamada's machine is a bulldozer.
Mr. Yamazaki challenges with a powerful bulldozer.
Mr. Yamazaki, what are you doing?
I'm doing a bankroll.
Mr. Okamoto is driving the 6th bulldozer.
The machine is decided.
I'll teach you how to drive the machine.
I don't know how to drive.
Let's see how he will do.
I'm scared.
Are you OK?
I'm OK.
I don't want to fly.
It's easy.
You should have told me before.
I can't win in a race.
It's automatic.
Really?
There is no gear.
Good.
This is the parking.
It's parked now.
Look at this.
I'm driving forward.
I'm going straight.
I'm going left.
I see.
I release the brake and accelerate.
I'm going forward.
I got it.
I'm going back.
The lecture is over.
Let's prepare for the race.
Yes.
Can you prepare for the battle?
No.
Let's do it quickly.
It's cold.
Everyone is here.
It's hard to get into the car.
My face is swollen.
There is a goal in front.
Do you see the flag?
That is the goal.
Let's go.
Cheer for me.
Today's race is cannonball.
Everyone gets on the car.
Who will reach the goal?
Let's see.
Mach-chan is in the lead.
Dump GT is after Mach-chan.
Other cars are slow.
Is it difficult to control?
Is the car too heavy?
Mach-chan is trying to run away.
He is in the lead.
Let's see it in slow motion.
Yamasaki is in the lead.
Yes.
How was it?
I did my best, but I was scared.
Mach-chan is in the lead.
Is he going to reach the goal?
He is slow.
I can't see anything.
I can see the flag.
It's now.
I can see the flag, but I can't see the flag.
It's the flag.
My face is swollen.
What are you doing?
Calm down.
What's wrong?
Don't you run?
You.
He ran away.
Was it fun?
I enjoyed it.
I was nervous.
I said I would go to the bathroom.
I couldn't go out, so I hid in the bathroom.
I don't like it.
It's hard.
Who?
To live.
It's too late to say that.
It's not too late to say that.
I think it's hard.
I don't know when I will die.
That's right.
You will die sooner.
Why?
I don't die.
You and I have different fans.
Do you understand?
I don't like it.
I don't understand.
I don't have many fans.
We have different ways to support each other.
What does that have to do with me dying sooner?
How many fans do you have?
That's a lot.
It's okay.
Let's say 500,000.
500,000 is a good number.
Let's say 400,000.
That's a lot.
500,000 people...
Let's say 400,000.
Let's live!
The power that 40,000 people think of and the power that 40,000 people think of are totally different.
But you're more dangerous.
Why is that?
Damn it!
Zaka!
Gyo-san should be here.
I'm...
Powerful.
You have a knife?
Don't cheat on me!
You know...
You're not good at sex.
It feels great!
It doesn't feel great at all!
You know...
Are you kidding me?
I don't know, but you're more dangerous.
You can say whatever you want.
Why are you from the east, west, south, and north?
There are a lot of places.
In various places?
In various places.
But you don't like the north direction?
You don't like it anywhere.
You don't like the north direction?
In that sense, you're more dangerous.
No, that's not it.
I've never broken up in a way that I've been hated.
You know...
Speaking of this,
A woman broke up with you for a year, and then with me for a year.
I really want to go out with you for a year and see which one is better.
Everything comes to me.
Why?
Well, I don't know if you're really interested, but...
Is it kindness?
I can only say that.
I'm sorry.
Well, I think...
Why do you think it's me?
If I had to say...
Aren't you cold?
No, I'm not cold at all.
Why do you think it's me?
I feel like I'm wrapped up in something.
I think so.
Thank you very much.
You don't have to do that.
Yesterday...
It was an interesting move, wasn't it?
There's a bar in my neighborhood.
If you turn left, it's the house.
I tried to turn left,
but there was a guy who looked like a college student with black glasses.
That's scary.
He was looking at the vending machine.
I turned around and opened the window.
He looked at the vending machine again.
I wondered what he was looking at.
It was a condom vending machine.
If there was a vending machine here, it would be standing here.
Why?
He looked like he didn't know what it was.
He was a cherry boy.
He had never done anything other than study.
That's scary.
I think he wanted to see what it was like inside.
It's a big world.
There are a lot of strange things.
I woke up the other day and laughed.
It was noisy.
I was sleeping with my earplugs on.
When I woke up in the morning, I ate my earplugs.
I don't know why I ate my earplugs.
I had earplugs on this side, but I didn't have earplugs on this side, so I ate them.
Take out your earplugs.
Michael Jackson is coming to Japan soon.
Is it true that Matsumoto is close to Michael?
Is it true that he always comes to your house when he comes to Japan?
I've known Michael since I came to Japan.
How did you meet him?
I went to see his concert.
That's normal.
At first it was normal.
I was the first to see his concert.
Michael must have felt something.
Among the tens of thousands of fans, I'm the only one who sees Michael differently.
I know he's a real fan.
I've been watching Michael a lot.
I think Michael understood me.
Since the second half, Michael has been like this in front of me.
Now he comes to my house.
Will he come again this time?
I think so.
What are you doing at home?
He often helps me with various things.
What?
For example, if I have a plate, I carry a dry towel next to it.
He's a good guy.
If I do this at the table, Michael will bring it to me.
Michael is amazing.
He brings the table like this.
He can go like this.
Michael turns around once.
He can't turn around immediately.
Michael knows that.
He turns around once.
I think Michael is amazing.
That's amazing.
Michael and Michael have similar emotions.
He's a good guy.
He laughs the same way.
Why doesn't he know you're laughing?
When I put the miso soup on the table, he sometimes moves like this.
Michael and I laugh together.
He laughs like this.
I'm scared.
He is a famous climber.
Climber?
Yes.
What should I do to prevent me from falling asleep in the mountains?
You can do this in the snowy mountains.
You sound like Mr. Sai.
Climbing has nothing to do with climbing.
Do you know why you can't sleep?
Why do I die when I sleep?
When you're awake, you release your heat.
But when you fall asleep, your heat decreases.
You can't stand the cold and die.
Should I have been more stupid?
I'm not stupid.
That's enough.
Are you waiting for something?
Of course.
I'm starting to walk in search of that light.
But it's also true that I'm losing sight of that light.
Good luck.
Thank you.
A climber is a devil.
Yes.
In the snowy mountains.
That's it.
Something like that.
What do you mean?
To prevent me from falling asleep.
Is there a night when you can't fall asleep?
There are some nights when I can't fall asleep.
There are nights when you can't fall asleep.
Yes, there are.
There's no rain that doesn't stop.
There's no night that doesn't open.
I don't care about that.
I don't know if it feels good to say that.
I don't care about your feelings.
It's fine, right?
I'll tell you.
The opposite is true.
Yes.
When you can't sleep, you often count sheep in your head.
I used to say that.
One sheep, two sheep.
If you do this, you'll fall asleep.
Do the opposite.
What do you mean?
What?
That dance.
Teach me.
No, no, no, no, no.
Hurry up and walk to the light.
You're weird.
What is it?
I can't help it.
You're really weird.
Your pelvis is funny.
That's the funniest thing today.
You're good at moving.
This Christmas.
I want to give you a present.
What would you give me?
Tell me.
I'm a fan of you.
What I want is candy.
Sweet candy.
Please give me candy.
Let me tell you the truth.
I'm a fan of you.
I'm a fan of you everywhere.
That's right.
What I want is a cotton ball.
I use it when we go camping together.
Mr. Nishin.
Mr. Toyota.
Nice to meet you.
Mr. Nishin.
He gave me a sleeping bag.
He gave me a sleeping bag for yakisoba.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Hisamitsu.
He gave me a sleeping bag in a box.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Hisamitsu gave me a sleeping bag.
You're welcome.
There are so many.
Do you have anything else?
I don't have anything else.
Good luck.
What is the name of the coat I'm wearing?
It's Coca-Cola.
Coca-Cola?
Mr. Coca-cola.
By the way, we were doing Zotto.
We're not strangers.
And the boss is cool.
He's cute.
We're totally compatible.
All in all, thank you to everyone at the company.
Is that so?
Yes.
Next time you go to Seikan, please take care of the service.
Why didn't I lower my head?
Why didn't I lower my head for you?
Don't say it for you.