I'm hungry.
Who are you?
Why are you hungry?
I don't know. I'm hungry.
I think I ate too much chocolate.
It's obvious.
You didn't drink that much, did you?
I wasn't being funny.
I know why.
You didn't drink that much.
There she is! There she is!
There's Hama-chan!
Hama-chan!
Hey, hey, hey.
Hurry up and go.
Hama-chan?
Oh, dear.
Hamada-san.
I brought some chocolates.
It's okay.
What day is it today?
It's late.
I'm sorry I'm late.
It's okay.
Please go out with me.
Why?
Hey, hey, hey.
Just go out with me.
You said you'd do it.
There's no point.
Just go with me!
Last year, during Valentine's Day,
Mori-san came to Hamada's home
to confess her passionate love.
In order to receive her love, she had to go through a battle with Hamada, but unfortunately, she lost her dream.
After that, on Hamada's birthday, Mori-san Chu appeared again.
Hamada had to go to the filming site of the drama she was starring in, but her love for Oshima was never fulfilled.
And this time, Mori-san Chu has come again.
Oshima's Love Story
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
I don't need it!
What?
It's because you had your hair stretched for Hama-chan, right?
I don't need it!
It's fine!
Please do it!
Wait, wait, wait!
Hey, hey, wait a minute!
You know, Hamada-san is a pain in the ass. You too, right?
That's right.
You two have nothing to do with each other, right?
What?
No, no, no.
Maybe we don't have anything to do with each other.
But you're our senior, so you don't have to be so formal.
That's right.
It's our story, really.
It's our story.
Well, Hama-chan is Hama-chan.
We call her Hamada-san.
Then you can call her Hama-chan.
No, no, no.
You don't have to do that.
Senior or junior?
We can't look directly at each other.
What do you mean?
I don't know what you mean.
Just look at him.
Okay, okay.
Hey, you're so erotic.
What?
What do you mean being erotic?
You're the erotic pig.
What are you talking about?
You're not saying anything to your senior.
Shut up.
Don't talk.
You're going to make it dark.
Hey, don't talk.
You'll make it dark.
Don't talk and you'll make it bright.
You'll make it bright.
You'll make it dark.
Don't say that.
You don't have to do that.
You're still a golden child, but you're dying instantly.
That's not true.
What are you talking about?
We're doing our best!
Shut up!
We don't know who you are!
Go home!
It's not like we're friends or anything.
We're just here for work.
I'm sorry.
You're a black-eye.
A black-eye?
Everyone, let's get back to work.
You do something!
You shouldn't be doing something like that!
You're the one who should be doing something.
That's right.
Calm down.
You want to give it to him?
Of course.
You know, for example,
you said something before, right?
You said something.
After the show,
you said,
I don't like women who have a lot of hair.
You said you like women who have a lot of hair.
Really?
You don't have a lot of hair.
That's right.
You can't just suddenly say that.
What's wrong?
These are scissors for hair.
No way.
There's a lot of hair.
Amazing.
You can do it now.
Do it, Oshima.
It's scissors.
Oshima.
What's wrong?
There's a lot of hair.
Do it, Oshima.
I got it.
You should quit.
Go home.
You shouldn't do that.
It hurts.
Oshima, what's wrong?
Go home.
You should show it to Hamada.
You shouldn't do that.
Go home.
You're annoying.
I told you to go home, so do something.
I had a crush on Hanako.
You had a crush on Hanako?
What did you think?
I don't mind if they set me up with Hanako.
Even if you get caught, you'll be fine.
That's true, but...
You can't do that.
No, I can't.
It's impossible to appeal.
I happened to be there.
I can't do such a good thing.
It's over.
Oh no!
It's a nose hook!
It's attached!
I can do it!
It'll be a big deal.
You can do it!
It hurts.
It hurts!
Wait!
You can't do it!
You said you could do it.
You said it before.
What are you going to do?
What is it?
Speaking of which,
I heard you like warm women.
Women.
You like them?
It's hard to make you understand.
What do you mean?
This is...
For example, frogs.
You mean the best?
Frogs?
You put them in your stomach and warm them.
It's hard to make you understand.
You can't make it up.
It's over!
What happened?
It's a fart.
What is that?
It's over!
You can warm your stomach.
I can't hold it.
I feel like a puppy.
Did it get in?
What is it doing?
Where is it?
What are you doing?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Hamada-chan!
My beloved Hamada-san!
Go!
Don't come!
What's wrong?
Ouch! Ouch!
Go over there!
Oh no! Oh no!
Hurry! Hurry!
What's wrong?
What should I do?
Hurry! Hurry!
Over there!
Don't come!
It's embarrassing!
Go home!
What's wrong?
Don't go home!
Go home!
You did it just as I told you!
No!
You're not that big!
I can't help it, so go home!
Go home!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
My favorite is the tough woman.
It's all tough.
I like tough women.
I don't know why, but I like tough women.
Hamada-san has a good mouth.
She's good.
That's right.
If you go with her lips,
You can change her emotions.
It's better to go with her.
You can go if it's Oshima.
Don't go!
You can drop her.
I got it.
I'm pissed off.
Go!
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
You're bleeding.
Go!
I'm sorry!
Wait a minute.
Ouch!
What are you doing?
What?
Ouch!
What's wrong?
I can't see anything.
He's cold.
He's cold, right?
He's cold?
He's really happy.
He's a bit of a long-sleeved guy.
He has that kind of desire.
He's really into his job.
He's a bit of a long-sleeved guy, but he's still being teased.
You guys should help me.
I need to go to the bathroom.
You need to go to the bathroom.
You should help me.
What are you doing?
Ouch!
You should help me.
On glasses, hello!
Ow ow!
My glasses!
Who is it?
Because I'm at work, I have to return home.
Hama-san
Hama-chan! Hama-chan!
Are you angry?
What should we do? Let's follow them.
Hurry up! We have to tell them how we feel now.
Hurry up!
Your glasses are amazing.
The three of you have great glasses.
We can't just let them go like this.
We'll get in their way.
We did a commercial today.
Really? Then let's go and change.
Let's go and change.
Hamada is heading to Georgia's commercial shooting location.
Hamada, the main character, is a typical Japanese salaryman.
At such a busy shooting location, Mori-san and Chuu are hiding in the heat of love.
Let's stop.
Let's go home.
We can't just stop.
Why?
It's not just you guys who have to stop.
Stop it.
The commercial is really important.
This is a serious atmosphere.
This is no good.
Let's go home.
What should we do?
If you don't stop, we can't talk.
Just accept it.
What are you saying?
You're Hama-chan's partner, right?
Do something.
If I had to choose...
I'm remembering the words I wrote in my graduation letter.
A woman without delicacy is a...
What does that mean?
A woman who doesn't have the heart to show her belly or her belly button to everyone.
That's nice.
If a woman shows her belly, it's not good.
It's not good.
There's no way you'd show your belly.
That's right.
That's why we're going home.
What?
What is it?
It's amazing.
It says it's a pump for women.
What is it for women?
It's amazing.
You can show your belly with this.
Why did you get the item the way you wanted?
I'm going.
Go.
Do your best.
Where are you going?
Don't use the key next door.
Don't use it.
I'm going.
That's all for the management strategy of our paper machine.
How's it going?
I'm going.
Don't you have any good ideas?
Cut.
Who is that guy?
Don't do that.
That's all.
I think he was peeing during the commercial shoot.
Go, go, go.
No, no, no.
Help me.
It hurts.
I think he likes it.
Yeah, he does.
I don't think he likes it.
That's not it.
How can I help you?
It's not sharp.
It was long and rough.
It was rough.
I wanted it to be faster.
I'm going to the toilet.
Wait, wait, wait.
Go, go, go.
Hurry.
Next is the park.
In the park?
Let's stop.
We're here.
Let's leave Oshima and go home.
That's right.
It has nothing to do with us.
It has something to do with us.
Why?
There's something like three people in the middle of the forest.
I saw it.
It has nothing to do with you.
What?
Let's go home.
You know, right?
Yes.
Right?
He's not like you.
He likes women who are more mischievous.
That's right.
He likes women who are mischievous.
He likes mischievous girls.
For example,
He suddenly inflates balloons and scares them.
He's cute.
I've hugged a girl like that before.
There's no balloon in a place like this.
Let's go home.
Wait.
What are you guys?
It's just as I thought.
God came down.
Oshima,
Don't be angry.
Let's do it.
Let's make Hama fall.
What are you going to do?
It's starting.
It's too late.
What are you doing?
Wait a minute.
It's too late.
What are you doing?
It's a little bit of a trick.
It's not over yet.
It hurts.
Stop it.
Run away.
It's dangerous.
It hurts.
You guys are men.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
You're angry.
No.
Let's think about it calmly.
It's not calm.
You said you would love me.
We are different.
I'm angry because of you guys.
The director was waiting for me to explode.
It's you.
What are you going to do?
This love will not be rewarded.
If you continue, you will be beaten.
You don't like it, do you?
I'll do my best.
I have to go quickly.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
I'm nervous.
I don't know.
It's hard.
I have to go now.
You guys are different.
I can turn it.
I heard one thing.
He is a woman who turns his head quickly.
I've heard that.
But he can't help it.
That's right.
He can turn his head and body.
He can express it.
That's impossible.
Thank you.
Wait.
I can't go.
I'm going to die.
What should I do?
The wind is blowing.
I got it.
I'll turn around.
It's starting again.
Thank you.
I'm going to die.
Wait.
I can't do it.
I'm done.
What are you doing?
You should have gone home.
Oshima!
He's doing it!
Hey, Oshima!
Stop it!
Let me go home!
I know, but love is the most important!
Look at that. Can you love that?
Go home.
I'm sorry.
Let's go!
You can't just give up.
I'm going!
50 points for the three of you.
Do you have 50 points?
I came all the way here.
I'm sorry.
It was a very close meeting.
I really want to go home.
I was wondering if there was anything I could say.
I thought about it on the bus.
There was a woman I liked.
A woman who doesn't make you feel like she's opposite sex.
Oh, I see.
She's a nice guy.
She's easy to go out with.
She's like a friend.
I used to say that she was the type I liked in my sleep.
In your sleep?
But I used to say that many times.
Really?
I'll believe you if you wait.
Okay, I got it.
I got it.
It's hard.
It's hard to overcome.
You say yes to everything.
You say yes to going home.
That's right.
I'll believe you.
You can do it.
What are you going to do?
It's hard to do it.
It's like a lump of spaghetti.
Look, it's like this.
I don't think I can do it.
I know.
It's started.
What?
No way.
What is this?
I can't feel it.
You can't feel it, right?
I'm an old man.
You're an old man.
This is normal.
Where did you come from?
Abiru.
Are you kidding me?
You're dirty.
You can come out.
You're just a dog in a sauna.
This is bad.
I can't stop it.
I can't give up.
It hurts.