It's a new partner.
The next guest is Yamazaki Hetare, Taiman Gohan Shogun.
I can't accept it at all.
Of course you can't.
This corner is also the second time.
Usually it ends with the first time, but it's the second time.
Yamazaki-kun.
I can't accept it at all.
Of course you can't.
This corner is also the second time.
Usually it ends with the first time, but it's the second time.
Yamazaki-kun.
Let's welcome Yamazaki-kun.
Yamazaki-kun, please.
Last year, I was really angry because I was called Hetare Hetare.
This year, I would like to make the most of my experience as a middle school student and do my best.
I would like to be the best in the entertainment world.
Thank you.
Today is also the fifth game.
OK.
Last time, you almost lost.
Yes.
How about this time?
This time, I will win three games and two losses.
I will definitely win.
You still can't win three games and two losses.
Yes.
Your eyes are small.
Hey!
Mr. Matsumoto.
Yes.
I'm from here.
I see.
Are you ready?
The first game is Honogata.
Please.
Honogata.
Let's get started.
Thank you.
The first game.
What are you doing?
Hey, stop it.
Stop it for the time being.
Please give me the judgment.
This is...
This is a battle, Mr. Yamazaki.
Please stop it for the time being.
Cheers.
I lost to an eight-year-old.
If you put all together, I would have lost.
At this age.
The second game is Honogata.
Please.
The first game is Honogata.
Please give me the judgment.
Wait a minute, Mr. Yamazaki.
What's wrong?
Are you injured, Mr. Yamazaki?
Are you okay, Mr. Yamazaki?
I can't do it today.
Let's get started.
The third game.
Please.
The fourth game is Honogata.
The fifth game is Honogata.
Please.
Thank you very much.
Please tell me your name.
I'm Tokyo Boys.
Tokyo Boys.
You don't move at all.
I don't know how to fight.
You didn't get in the way at all.
I didn't get in the way.
I think it was a very good story.
Don't say that.
The fourth game.
Please.
The fifth game is Honogata.
Usagi-chan.
I've already decided.
Go, go, go.
I'm answering.
I was caught.
Yamazaki is going to be eliminated.
It's my dad, Yamazaki.
Do you want to go further?
Yamazaki, are you okay?
Can you stand up?
What is this guy?
Wait a minute.
Who are you?
Yamazaki, are you okay?
It hurts.
It's out.
Hirakawa is out.
Yamazaki, are you okay?
What is this?
Look, look, look.
Yamazaki-san.
Hirakawa won.
No matter who wins, I'll lose.
Even if you win, it's the same as last time.
That's right.
But, Yamazaki-san.
Yes.
This is the last game.
Let's win this.
I'll definitely win.
Yes.
The last one is this guy.
Please.
The last one.
Ready.
Hey.
Yamazaki, are you okay?
What are you doing?
You can't come out.
Really.
Wait a minute.
Yamazaki-san.
Are you okay?
I can't play anymore.
My blood is connected.
Wait.
Dad wins.
Dad, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Long time no see.
Yes.
I think you have the personality of a parent and child.
That's right.
I think you have that.
Sit down.
Dad, long time no see.
Thank you.
You have the personality of a parent and child.
You're eating, aren't you?
Yes, I'm eating.
I'm doing my best.
Take enough money.
Yes.
Thank you.
Were you okay earlier?
Earlier?
I had a little fight.
You have the personality of a parent and child.
I was a little angry.
I'm usually angry.
I don't appear much in Osaka.
That's right.
I'm popular here.
Yamazaki-san.
First of all, this game.
Yes.
We lost five times in a row.
We all lost.
Yes.
Who was the most stubborn of the five?
My dad.
As an extra, today's killer account.
Dad's confrontation.
No, no, no.
I'm sorry.
Ladies and gentlemen.
I've been cheering for you many times over the years.
Yes.
This is the first time this year.
It's the first time.
There's a foreigner.
His face is all red.
He's shy.
That's great.
If you look at him from the stage.
I don't know what to say.
Well, well, well.
Foreigners.
Everyone thinks we're down-to-earth.
Foreigners think we're down-to-earth.
You're persistent.
Yes, I am.
I don't know.
Down-to-earth.
Well, it's the first time this year.
Well, if I look at the TV.
It's cool.
What is it?
After all, the talent is different.
Mr. Kagura gave it to me.
What are you doing?
What is this?
Your chest is growing.
No, it's not.
Don't do that.
Your chest is growing.
What's your chest?
I don't like it.
After all, that's not good.
That's a talent.
Hawaii is a status.
But everyone.
I have a question.
Why do you go to Hawaii with a talent?
Don't you go to Hawaii?
I'm talking about you.
Why don't you go to Hawaii?
Why are you going to Hawaii?
Why do you go to Hawaii?
It's cold in Japan, so I went to a warm place.
It doesn't matter if you don't go to Hawaii.
Why do you go to Hawaii?
I want to go on New Year's Day.
Why?
This year, you left your wife and child.
Yes.
That's cool.
Why do you go to Hawaii?
Your wife is beautiful.
You are a brandy knight.
Don't do something you don't understand.
You are a brandy knight of your heart.
I don't understand.
I don't understand your heart.
I don't understand you.
I was on the news yesterday.
I went on a trip to Hawaii.
I went somewhere for 9800 yen.
I did it.
It was limited to a few people.
I'm a fool.
Why?
It's cold, but there are so many people lined up.
There are only 200 people lined up.
It was a lottery.
That's right.
What are you talking about?
Don't be so cute.
Don't do that.
Who is it?
I'm sorry.
It was cold.
Don't say it's cold.
It's cold.
I don't understand.
What is it?
I went home.
I came home.
I sat in front of my house.
I was packing my luggage.
That's cool.
I was just packing my luggage.
I did this.
I was packing my luggage.
Hey!
You are a pervert.
I was packing my luggage.
Why?
The reason why I don't like going abroad is...
I don't like Messi.
No.
When you arrive at the country, you are the only one who gets caught when you get a passport.
I get caught.
It's embarrassing.
When you arrive at the country, you are the only one who gets caught when you get a passport.
Why did you do that?
I've been doing that for a long time.
I always wear the same clothes.
It's embarrassing.
I'll kick you this year.
It takes a long time.
I'm always like this.
I think too much.
When people stare at me, I get nervous.
When I get nervous, I think there is something.
I get nervous.
I wear glasses vertically.
They think I'm strange.
Don't you bring anything home?
No.
I ask you.
There is nothing.
Are you nervous?
I get nervous.
I don't know why, but I get nervous.
To be honest, at the end of the year, my friend came to Fuji.
I was crying at that time.
I wasn't crying.
I was crying.
I didn't cry.
I get nervous.
I'm not moved at all.
I don't know why.
I want to ask you.
Is that so?
I don't like it.
I drink alcohol.
I drink alcohol in the plane.
I can sleep.
I don't drink alcohol.
I don't know why.
The next is a man.
He's stupid.
He looks like this.
He's close to me.
He's a strange man.
He looks like such a person.
He may be my friend.
He's close to me.
He's old.
How many times do you want to say that?
That's really bad.
But, that's right.
The overseas record debut.
Sakamoto, the world's Sakamoto Produce.
Sakamoto Ryuichi.
It's okay. It's out.
It seems so.
The rest is just blowing in.
But, Sakamoto Ryuichi is going to New York right now.
That's right.
What are you going to do in New York?
That's why I don't like airplanes anymore.
Sakamoto, the world's Sakamoto.
Come on.
Why?
That's bad.
That's what you said.
You said you were going to debut overseas.
Either way, you have to go once.
You said it.
Why?
It doesn't matter if it's a debut song.
How many times have you sung in Japan?
Idiot.
You sang in Japan and made a CD and sent it overseas.
It doesn't matter.
After all, the debut is in that country.
What?
I have to do a debut concert.
But, if it sells, you can go.
Even if it doesn't sell, I'll go.
Just the recording.
Sakamoto Ryuichi, come on.
Record in Japan for the time being.
It's better in Japan.
That's rude.
Why?
For the time being, you said it.
You said you were going to debut overseas.
It takes 12 hours to get to New York.
12 hours.
That's right.
How many eggs can you bake?
No, that's not possible.
That's for amateurs.
No, really.
It doesn't matter.
What?
Do you want to go?
It's not that I want to go.
They told me it was a good place.
Yes, they told me.
I don't know what to do.
I'm not good at New York.
You're lying.
I came here because I had a bad experience in New York.
It doesn't matter.
What?
That's what it is.
That's right.
You lost.
What?
The White House.
You lost.
Shiro won.
That's a general opinion.
You said it on TV.
Shiro lost to my appearance.
Your appearance?
My appearance.
But you can't.
Did you decide the winner?
Really.
It's a difficult story.
I have to play a penalty game.
I don't know if I'm going to New York.
I decided to make my debut in the United States.
Your debut in the United States.
It's amazing.
I still can't reach you.
Even if you want to come, come to Kanagawa.
Hatsune Shogun's down turn.
It's a big reaction.
Shut up.
What is this?
This is a great invention.
I don't hate this.
That's right.
Don't be angry.
Can you move properly?
I won.
You're laughing.
When I see this, I can't help but laugh.
Why are you always angry?
I don't know.
What are you dissatisfied with?
Why are you angry?
That's right.
I'm shooting a drama.
When we started, it was over.
I was shooting in the next studio.
There was still a location left.
The studio was the last.
The staff came together.
I said, thank you.
The producer hit me.
Why?
The producer kicked me.
You shouldn't do that.
I was told not to do that.
Who told you that?
Why?
There was still a location left.
Why are you angry?
I just said thank you.
I just said that.
There was still a location left.
The shooting was over.
Why are you angry?
This is amazing.
The story has changed again.
I don't care.
I don't want to work with him again.
I heard on TV.
There is a talent.
He has a lemon.
He is the only one who doesn't have a lemon.
Who was it?
I didn't have a lemon.
There were two people.
Who are you?
When I came here.
I was bored.
I said please.
I said okay.
You said okay.
I was dressed up.
Excuse me.
The lemon...
What?
I don't know what it is.
I don't have a lemon.
I have a different image.
You said such a long line.
I didn't have a shower.
I didn't have a lemon.
When I took a break.
I was interested in a lemon.
I thought it would be cool to have a lemon.
Bang! Bang!
Bang!
It seems to be delicious.
Why do you hit me?
Are you strong?
I was beaten by the other side.
I was bad at it.
I was beaten.
Hey.
I think you are a Fanta.
Really?
I'm a Fanta.