We don't have enough money for the team project, so let's make some money!
Wada-san, last week, we spent a lot of money on the opening.
It was about 5 million yen.
After all, that happened.
We don't have any money today.
We don't have any money.
It's not that we don't have any money, but let's make some money.
I see.
You know, on TV, I say that as an idol.
Today, on the table, I have potatoes and bananas.
Today's manager is Okamoto.
Next to me is Noriya from Team Zero.
Next to you is Yamazaki from Team Zero.
Recently, I've been on TV a lot.
I don't know why I've been on TV so much.
Everyone, let's eat one by one.
Let's eat one by one.
So, Mio-san.
Yes, yes.
We've already eaten.
If you want to do it, please do it here.
I feel like I'm going to poop.
If I poop, the person in charge will come.
It's like a hall.
You can eat it.
The person in charge will come.
And...
But this is a TV show.
I think I can do it.
Really? I can do it, too.
I can do it, too.
That's funny.
I can't hear anything here.
Wait a minute.
It's going to come out on the right.
It's going to come out.
Here we go.
I want you to dance.
Blackpink! Blackpink!
If you dance like that, it's not cool.
Blackpink!
Can I do it?
Yes.
Excuse me.
That's funny.
It's funny.
Blackpink!
You should do it properly.
That's funny.
He's a big brother.
That's a great movie.
That's funny.
I feel good.
One more time.
That's funny.
I'm sure it's gonna come out.
Damn it.
Come on.
It's dirty.
If it comes out, if it comes out.
That's funny.
It's funny.
Eat some bananas.
He's eating bananas.
Damn it.
That's funny.
Thank you.
I don't have any money, so I gave up.
Thank you very much.
That's funny.
You should do it properly.
You're not a kid anymore.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
That's funny.
I don't like it.
It's time for a movie.
I don't like talking.
I've been doing it for years.
I hate this time the most.
It's hot.
I sweat when I talk.
I'm nervous.
If I go out in thin clothes, I'm worried about my bra.
I'm embarrassed to be seen.
I don't like it.
I don't like it if I'm wearing a bra.
I'm like an invitation.
I'm very high.
Really?
I will work like this for a long time.
That...
Yesterday,
You know the TV show, CX right?
I went to the bathroom.
I hear a loud noise.
A noisy one.
There is also a shocking one too.
But I краaact to my lower leg, and I jerk it.
What does it mean?
I went to the bathroom and I was like,
Ah, I pooped and pooped my butt.
I pooped all the time.
And I was wearing this Gokugira thing.
That's pathetic.
It was in the way, so I put it on top of the toilet.
I forgot about it and went out.
I went into the studio once and thought,
Ah, the Gokugira belt.
When I went back to the toilet, I was like,
Ah, there must be something.
And Shimura-san was there, right?
Yes, yes.
I went to the bathroom and Shimura-san was taking a dump.
I was taking a dump and saying,
The comedy I was talking about as a kid the other day...
It's not about us, is it?
I'm worried about this.
It's not true.
When I asked him, his face was half serious.
He was half laughing, but he was like,
What should I do if you tell me?
It was completely different, wasn't it?
It was completely different.
I respect Shimura-san.
Why are you laughing there?
I'm in trouble.
I'm making a lot of people nervous.
In the past, on the Shinkansen,
Sendo, Akiyo,
I met him on the Shinkansen.
I met him on the Shinkansen, and there was a passage.
The person next to him was that kid.
He was the same as the manager.
He was wearing something.
I don't know if he was wearing it because he was a fan.
He looked sweet.
He was wearing cream puffs.
He was wearing cream puffs and sprinkled sugar on them.
I hate that.
He was eating with his mouth wide open.
He didn't eat with such a dirty face.
The manager asked him,
What do you think, Matsumoto-san?
I'm already cute.
Don't take it.
That's bad, too.
What are you talking about?
He looked sweet.
I don't need such a guy.
He was sitting next to the window.
I'm worried about him.
He was looking at me.
What should I do with this luggage?
He was carrying a big luggage.
I thought I had to eat it.
Thank you for the food.
It's sweet.
He didn't drink anything.
He ate half of it.
Why?
I hate that.
I'm really sorry.
Even if I stay like this,
I'll end up going to Tokyo.
I have to do something.
What did you do?
When I was about to take a bath,
I went to the bathroom.
Over there?
Over there.
In the meantime,
I went to the bathroom.
I'm really sorry.
When I came back,
I was like this.
It's not good to be late.
But if you think about it later,
it's better to reject it.
It's better to reject it than to throw it away.
I was like that, too.
I was told by my ex-girlfriend
to treat me to coffee.
Please wait.
I was treated.
You're my ex-girlfriend, right?
I don't drink coffee.
I'm a loser.
It's unusual to treat me to coffee.
I was surprised.
Do you drink coffee?
You're a loser.
I can't drink coffee,
but if you say it's okay,
I'll treat you to coffee.
Thank you for the coffee.
I drank it forcibly.
You're a loser.
I don't drink coffee in front of you.
I can't help it.
I can't help laughing.
You have the courage to reject it, right?
I can't reject it.
Put it in your ass.
You're going to marry Nan-chan.
That's right.
I have to go.
Are you going?
I'm going.
I heard it's 12 o'clock.
It's about 12 o'clock.
I don't know the time.
It's cold.
That's true.
Don't think it's cold.
I don't think it's cold,
but if you go,
you have to celebrate again.
I don't want to celebrate.
How much money do you make?
I don't want to catch you,
but I want to see you.
Celebrate.
Think about it.
I think the world is strange.
I'm not going to get married.
I'm not going to get married,
which means I don't have children.
I can't have children.
I don't get it.
I don't get any money for celebrations.
But I'm married.
When you get older,
you'll get it.
Congratulations.
But I don't have a family.
I don't have a wife or children.
Who's going to do that for me?
I did the worst.
That's a waste.
I bought it for you,
and I'm making a lot of money.
Why?
I bought your wedding.
That's 26,500,000 yen.
You're lying.
You're stupid.
I'm going to kick your ass.
No, I'm not.
You're stupid.
And for the children's celebration,
that's another...
You're lying.
13,400,000 yen.
What?
Why is it so expensive?
I can't get that money back.
Unless I get married
or have children.
You said you'd do it
when you wear a chan-chan-ko.
But you wear a chan-chan-ko.
I'll do it again then.
Let's forget about the celebration.
Give it back to me.
Why?
13,400,000 yen.
You can't say that.
25,600,000 yen.
Why?
And the rest is 3,000 yen.
Give it back to me.
Let's not talk about that.
It's not over yet.
Let's wrap it up.
What?
Nan-chan.
Nan-chan?
It's about the size of a human bowl.
That's not true.
That's true.
It depends on the person you're dating.
How much is it?
18,000 yen.
Why?
It's 10,000 yen.
It's nothing.
It's about 12,500 yen.
There are a lot of spies in Japan.
I've never heard of it.
There are a lot of spies.
There are a lot of electric products and cars in Japan.
There are a lot of spies hiding in places we don't know.
I've never heard of it.
There are spies.
There are spies to steal electric products.
They're supposed to steal electric products.
They're supposed to steal technology.
There are a lot of spies in Japan.
Especially in Japan.
Is that so?
How do you know that they're spies?
I didn't even know there were spies in many places.
How do you tell them apart?
I want everyone to remember this.
The first way to tell a spy apart is by looking at their shoes.
Don't act like you don't know anything.
Their shoes...
I'm not a spy, so my shoes are like this.
A spy's shoes are like a telephone.
It's obvious. I'm a spy.
It's obvious.
There are also a lot of underground people.
There are 20,000 Japanese people in the underground organization.
Don't say that.
It's hard to tell them apart.
What kind of people are they?
Underground people have lived underground for a long time.
It's hard to tell them apart.
The other day, there was a paper in the paper killer's container.
There's a sticker on the container's surface.
If you do this with a paper killer, the paper on the surface will get wet.
There's a paper here.
But...
How do you do that paper?
This paper?
How do you draw the paper on the paper?
It's not that hard.
It's hard.
If there's a paper here...
It's not that hard.
It's hard.
If there's poop in the pants, it's like washing them with a washlet.
I'll give you an example.
What?
What is that?
That's not it.
There's poop in the pants.
If there's a paper in the paper killer's container...
How do you say that word?
If there's poop in the pants, it's like washing them with a washlet.
That's not it.
I thought you were saying, ahhh.
No, that's not it.
This is a mistake, but that's not it.
What? There's something like this?
What is this word?
If you look at other people's behavior, it's my behavior.
It's not like that at all.
What?
I don't think we're from the same family.
The other day, I found this scribble in the public toilet at the station.
It said, I'm dating the super-famous comedian H.M. and I'm getting married this year.
Please don't write me a letter.
That's you.
Who would write such a lie?
You wrote it in the toilet when you said you were getting married.
You're a great person.
But when you get married, you'll marry your grandma, right?
I will.
Actually, I'm here at this venue today.
Oh, really?
Grandma isn't here, is she?
I told you, she's not here.
Please come.
You're not in the mood.
No, no, no.
I can't do anything about that.
That's you.
Don't you get together early?
I'm angry with the teachers who are angry with the people who are gathered at the ceremony.
That's not true.
There was such a thing.