This week, we'll be talking about one of the biggest unspoken secrets!
On the veranda, well, it's a mansion, but on the veranda of my house,
every night, recently, a cat comes.
It's a black cat, but it's a great adult.
It's a black cat?
A black cat comes to my house, and the black cat will look at it.
I feed it, but I don't have any cats, so I only feed it with katsuobushi.
You live alone, and you have katsuobushi?
Well, I have to take out a lot of things.
Don't make such a big deal out of it!
Unfortunately, the front legs of the black cat are injured.
You can say that cats are a little timid.
I don't know if the front legs of the black cat were injured by humans.
I don't really know.
That's why it doesn't come to me from about one meter away.
I try to get a little closer with the food, but it's still scared.
I talk to it while laughing, but it's still scared.
I want to catch it as soon as possible and take it to the hospital.
Is it over?
When I say this, I feel like I'm talking to a very nice person.
Say it quickly!
It's a long story.
In the end, what I wanted to say was that Matsumoto told everyone that there was such a place.
That's mean!
You don't have to say that!
So today, everyone went home and called their friends.
Which do you think is kinder, Machan or Hama-chan?
First of all, listen to the story.
I don't want to do it anymore.
I killed a cat.
I also killed a lot of animals.
Who is the most popular man in Japan now?
I think there are various opinions.
Who do you think it is?
Well, now...
The representative is Sorimachi, right?
Yes, Sorimachi.
Who else?
The person who appeared in the drama with me.
Who is so strong?
Who is it?
Sorimachi and...
Take no Uchi!
Who else?
Kimura Takuya.
What is Kimura Takuya?
Do you think it's Kimura Takuya?
That's a big mistake.
Let me tell you a good thing.
For example, there is a data of wanting to be hugged.
There is a little mistake or mystery of such data.
I found it completely.
For example, there are the most people who say they like Kimura Takuya.
And the most popular is different.
It's just that there are the most people who say they like Kimura Takuya.
But it doesn't mean that Kimura Takuya is popular.
No, it doesn't.
There are also people who say they hate Kimura Takuya.
I know that.
It means that the most popular is the top 10.
It doesn't mean that Kimura Takuya is popular.
No, it means that Kimura Takuya is the most popular.
Even if you don't aim for the top 10, there are very few people who say they hate Kimura Takuya.
I don't know about that.
But if you look at it simply,
Everyone thinks that Kimura Takuya is popular because he is the most popular.
Because he is the most popular.
That's the evaluation.
No one thinks that Kimura Takuya is the most popular.
Then I'm the loser.
I'm completely defeated.
You're completely defeated.
That's exactly right.
But I wonder if that's the case.
But if you look at it this way, people usually think that way.
Is it that popular?
Even if you say that, people will come to you even if you walk in the streets.
You'll say that, right?
I'll definitely say that.
You're just saying that now.
If you see him on TV, you'll say that.
I think so, too.
It's completely different from seeing a celebrity on TV.
Even Katsura Kokinji is cool.
He's cooler than watching TV.
He has a small face.
But that's just a small face.
I don't think he's cool.
He's cooler than watching TV.
That's not true.
I don't care about that.
I think that's true.
That's right.
There are so many people who say that they saw Downtown for the first time today.
That's true.
I've been watching downtown on TV for the first time.
I've never seen it live.
He's so cool.
Is he?
I only see you.
It's amazing.
He's so cool.
I don't know which one is which.
That's what it means.
I don't know if it's live.
And...
What is it?
I don't like him.
I have a bad image.
I can go to a cafe and say,
Hey, come on, come on, come on!
But when I say something,
Thank you.
Grab the apron while standing up!
What am I supposed to do?
What's the point?
That's where it starts.
But...
Out of the 10 people here, almost 10 people,
Machan is kinder than usual.
What's that?
That's a long story.
This is a question for Matsumoto-san, who bought a giraffe for his pet.
I also want to buy a giraffe.
How do you take it for a walk?
And what kind of food do you feed it?
Please tell me.
I've seen this a lot.
Where did you hear about it?
How big is it?
First of all, you don't have to check if you really bought it or not.
You believe in the letter and say that you bought it.
You've decided.
Isn't that strange?
You have to ask me first if you bought it or not.
I don't even know if I bought it or not.
Why do you keep going alone?
Is that wrong?
Does that mean you're not buying it?
First of all, do you buy it or not?
I'm sorry.
I heard that you bought a giraffe for your pet.
Did you buy it?
I bought it.
I don't care.
I don't care if you keep going.
There are many kinds of giraffes.
They're all called Kyurin.
Kyurin?
It's a giraffe, isn't it?
Well, it's easy for everyone to understand.
It's a giraffe.
There are many kinds of giraffes.
It looks like a giraffe.
What kind of giraffes are there?
It's not that everyone is big.
There are small ones.
There are such things.
Everyone may have a water ball pattern.
It's not just that.
What kind of giraffe do you have?
What kind of giraffes are there?
What kind of pattern is it?
Well...
How big is it?
If you put it in here, it's almost as big as the front.
If you put in the length of the neck, it will be like that.
Actually...
This is a giraffe.
I can still go.
No, no, no.
You have a neck.
Where do you buy it?
What do you mean?
You don't go inside the house, do you?
I go inside.
It's all blown out.
Is it expensive?
It's expensive.
I see.
Well, that's true.
I'm taking a walk.
You're taking a walk.
I'm taking a walk in the neighborhood.
Well, in the neighborhood or around Shonan.
That's a Shonan animal.
No, it's not.
What do you do when you take a walk?
If it's a dog, you hold a chain.
I see.
You can talk to it.
How do you take it?
Well, most of the time...
Where?
It's the face.
The face?
It's like this.
Well, but...
I'll talk to it here.
But it's hard for this guy to walk.
Why?
It's like this.
But it's okay.
You don't know if it's okay or not.
What the hell?
What?
Why did you kick it barefoot?
Matsumoto-san says he's good at telling stories.
Well, yeah.
Please tell me how to tell the next story.
Okay.
When your friend cuts your hair and it doesn't look good on you.
It's not like I'm telling a story.
By the time I know the moment it's going to hold,
Finished, I must already be looking forward to the next meeting with you guys.
I swear it's a lie.
I don't know about those kinds of stories.
When you say this, you can't say that you were it.
That's how I say that I don't mean it.
It's how I greet people.
It's rude.
I think I don't think it's rude any more
I'm sure.
It's rude, isn't it?
No.
It's not rude at all.
Oh, really?
It's like, I knew it.
There's no way it's like that.
It hurts.
No matter how you think about it.
It's like, I knew it.
It's rude to say it like that.
Why is that?
It's like, are you underestimating me?
I don't think it's like that.
I'll tell you what's bad about the other person.
I see.
What is it?
There are times when you cut your hair and it doesn't suit you, right?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
When that happens, what do you say?
First of all, that hairstyle is weird.
But, but, you're like that.
I like it too.
That's...
What kind of follow-up is that?
There's no follow-up at all.
What is it?
Is it bad?
Your friend's house is too small and dirty.
Your house is too small and dirty.
What is this?
You can't just say it.
Shut up and live in your own house.
What kind of house is this?
But...
I like this kind of girl.
Your friend's father and mother have a bad relationship.
But...
I like her.