Tsukishiki! Hamada Team vs. Matsumoto Team!
Owarai Draft High Tension Battle!
So Matsumoto-san!
Yes, yes!
You've already done it a few times.
That's right!
High Tension!
Today, I've changed my mind a bit.
First of all, before that, we have this assistant here.
What's with this guy?
Today, Idao isn't here, but...
He's only here to read?
But that's better, isn't it?
This side is like this.
There's a big thing attached to it.
He's always on my side, supporting me.
What's with this guy?
No, it's really...
Don't come out!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Today, we're going to split up into Hamada Team and Matsumoto Team.
Today, we're going to be in 12 teams.
We're going to decide that in the draft.
That's right.
We're going to do it in a slightly different way.
Yes, thank you.
Let's get started!
Players, come in!
What is it?
Your tension is really low.
It's low, isn't it?
I have a feeling.
Why is that?
You're going to make me explode from now on.
You must have something you're saving up for.
I think so.
Now, who's going to be Hamada-san?
And who's going to be on my team?
I don't know yet.
We're going to decide that in the draft.
Yes, yes.
Then, let's decide.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Yes, rock-paper-scissors.
Yes!
Hamada-san.
I won, so I'm going to do it.
Yes.
This is...
There's going to be a mistake, after all.
What?
Do you think all of this is a hit?
No, I don't think so, but I don't want to make a sudden mistake.
Well, that's true.
Now, Uchiha.
Ameyawari.
Yes.
Thank you.
Oh, this is a pretty good shot.
What do you think?
This is a bit...
Matsumoto's team, the first one is...
Shouzo Endo.
Thank you.
After that, Hamada's team is...
Wow!
Tetsuro.
Yes!
And Matsumoto's team is...
Who is it?
Funky Monkey Clinic.
I'm not going to do it.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I don't know.
I can't do something like this.
I can't see Tetsu-chan anymore.
Hamada-san, you're stupid.
If you get me, that means you got a chance card today.
That's what I'm saying right now.
I'm back!
The third one, Hamada's team is...
Kokoriko Tanaka.
Matsumoto's team is...
Yamazaki Hosei.
The fourth one, Hamada's team is...
Ryuhei Ueshiba.
Good!
And Matsumoto's team is...
I wonder if it's okay.
Who is it?
I pulled it.
Ryō Fukawa.
Ryu-chan is so excited.
He's going to see this.
Anyway, please look at this.
Tsuruto, you're heavy today.
It's normal.
I'm heavy.
You didn't say anything important.
Everyone is waiting.
I'm not ashamed.
Really?
I'm counting on you.
There are only two or three left.
First, Hamada's team is...
Ritton Chosodan.
Matsumoto's team is...
Jōdanzu.
And finally, Hamada will pull Yamaguchi.
The remaining monkeys will go to Matsumoto's team.
Now all the members have decided.
Matsumoto won.
The high tension battle of the air battle.
Kona and the fate of the Kong is...
The six of them.
Degawa, Ueshiba and the veterans are the key.
Meanwhile, Matsumoto's team is...
Tsukawa, Pankinna and Wakate Chūshin.
How long will Yamazaki, who is left with anxiety, be able to do his best?
In the first half of the third round, Hamada's team will go first.
In the second half of the third round, Matsumoto's team will go first.
That's what we'll do.
That's right.
Now, let's introduce the judges.
The judge is Producer Sugawa Kenji.
Hello.
He's a comedian.
The other three will be the judges.
I look forward to working with you.
Now, let's choose the players for the first round.
We'll start with Hamada's team.
Who do you think should go first?
That's right.
I understand that there's no such thing as going first.
But looking at Tanaka's face today,
it's obvious that he's going to slip.
Why?
I don't know how long it takes for a comedian to slip.
That's not true.
No one looks at me with confidence.
Everyone has confidence, right?
Of course.
Thank you very much.
Tanaka, are you ready?
Oh!
Alright!
I understand!
Don't be silent when I say that.
Yes, I'll show you.
Okay?
Now, it's Tanaka's turn.
Who wants to go first?
Okay!
There's no one here.
You should hold a bell and move.
What should I do?
Alright!
Now!
Well done!
I'll do my best.
I haven't told you yet,
but there's a punishment for the loser.
Oh, right.
There's a punishment.
I didn't say that.
Yes.
I want to avoid that.
Okay.
I'm counting on you.
Let's go.
Please get ready.
Okay.
Let's go!
Hamada team is
Kogoriko Tanaka Naoki
and Hassoro Viking!
What?
Hey!
Why don't you leave me alone?
Why?
Hey!
To the back!
I lost!
Viking!
I did it!
This is good! This is good!
Let's go!
On the side of Jodan's,
One person, Choshu!
It hasn't changed!
Hey! What are you doing?
Where does it end?
This is stupid.
It's over, right?
Yes.
It's over there, right?
It's over!
Well, to be honest, it was really long.
When I first heard it, I thought it was half of this.
I was so excited!
From the moment it started, I started dancing.
There was a biorhythm, right?
I thought it would be okay, but it got more and more interesting.
In the end, it went down.
What about this?
Let's continue.
I'll go with Ritton.
I feel like I can win with this.
I don't know about that.
But I have to make a move here.
Well, what should I do?
Yasasaki!
Ritton Jyosa Dan Mizuno Toru's ideal woman!
Me and this girl's story
Part 1
5, 6, 9
Be quiet! Be quiet! Be quiet! Be quiet!
I'm so scared!
Part 2
Part 3
Part 4
Part 5
Part 6
Part 7
Part 8
Part 9
Part 10
Part 11
I'm sorry!
Kiss!
It's over.
It was fun.
Let's go to the second round.
Who will be the winner?
I made a mistake.
If you make a mistake, you can't do anything.
What do you mean by that?
That's not right.
There's no right answer.
I made a mistake.
No, no.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
You can take a break.
Take a break.
I'm sorry.
I'll go again.
Yamazaki Hose.
Who will be the winner?
The world is about to collapse.
We're going to believe in each other.
Oh, oh!
Oh!
High-high-high!
Yes yes!
Uyaaa!
Uwaaa!
It's not recording!
O-Sei-san!
You're making a big deal out of it!
I can't do this anymore!
It's too late already!
Apologize! Apologize!
I'm sorry!
It's over!
It's not like there's a mistake or anything like that!
I'm surprised!
You!
Let's do the 3rd round!
I'll do it with Tetsu-chan!
Please!
I'm counting on you!
Alright!
Listen to me!
Last year, my dad met with a destroyer!
Really?
Really! So I'll do my best!
I see!
So you're going to use your power of a minus!
That's right!
If it's such a sad story, I'll probably break up with my girlfriend!
So close!
I'll do it a little bit more!
Tetsuro Degawa's strongest man in history!
I'll do it!
What are you wearing?
I'll go wild!
I'm sorry, I made a mistake.
60 minutes 20,000 yen course!
Hotel Daikomi!
Let's start!
You're the company's president, right?
What's going on?
You're a dog here!
That's not it!
If you say you want to extend it,
This is the end!
Time's up!
Okay!
That was good!
Let's go with Fukawa!
Let's go!
That's Ryu-chan!
Fukawa doesn't have the image of tension, right?
That's right!
That's why we have this!
We'll go like this!
We'll do our best with high tension!
No matter what they call it,
I'm the one!
Fukawa Ryo's high tension number 5!
I wonder if he'll be able to stop it.
That was good!
It wasn't bad!
The guy who's been picking beans!
Picking beans, picking beans
Don't laugh and come out!
Ready...
Ouch!
Picking beans, picking beans
Ready...
Damn it!
Picking beans, picking beans
Goodbye!
Damn it!
Let's try crying with a different high tension.
I see!
I can't do this!
When we all came out,
I didn't have a diamond.
Thank you!
I can cry with this high tension!
The next contest is
the Matomota team vs. the Funky Monkey Clinic Fujimoto
the Hamada team vs. the Dondogodon Yamaguchi
They are the first teams to compete.
Monkey Monkey Clinic Fumimono Shouhei's Pikupiku Pikupiku Pikurinpiku!
Bullseye
U.S.A. U.S.A. M.C. M.C. M.C.
Uwaaah!
Okay, okay, okay!
Yamaguchi Tomomitsu's...
Mukimukiyo!
Hikson! Hikson! Hikson! Hikson! Hikson! Hikson!
Guitar Hikson! Guitar Hikson! Hikson! Hikson! Hikson! Hikson! Guitar Hikson!
Hikson is crazy! Hikson is crazy! Hikson is crazy! Hikson is crazy!
It's a crazy city
Let's go!
This is a lot of work
I don't have any complaints
Who said I couldn't stop?
Almost everyone said that
Now it's the last one
The remaining is the end
Let's go!
Thank you!
This is a battle for the grand prize
That's right
Everyone, please
This is the last one
I didn't think it would be this easy
That's right
Look, I'm full of confidence
This is a competition
If you go behind the curtain, it will be messed up
You're weird
My face is all red
Kokoriko Endo Shouzou
Datsu Houhoui 2000
Who wants to hit me?
Tell me his name
But I can't hit him
So I run away
I run away, I run away, I run away
I chase him with a whip
Who is that?
His name is
Kimi no Kokoro
What?
Why?
This is red
Let's go
Let's go to Miyasako
Itoshino Denjiha
Why?
Is it you?
Pick up the phone
Are you stupid?
Is it you?
Where is it?
Damn it
Come out to the front
And
Da da
Boyo boyo
Da da da
Okay
It was good
Thank you
It was good, everyone was good
What was good about this?
If you say curry, it's shabashaba
I just melted the roux in the hot water
This is the end of the high tension
How will the captain's punishment be?
Judges, please raise your cards
Go ahead
Amaterasu
The judge, Mr. Suga, will announce the punishment
The captain of the losing team, Matsumoto
The captain of the winning team, Hamada
Will do the high tension of the player he has chosen
This is tough
It depends on what it is
What will it be?
Sing
I'll do it
Matsumoto's high tension, Mameshibori
The captain of the losing team, Matsumoto
The captain of the losing team, Mameshibori
Go ahead
It's been a long time
Mameshibori
What the hell?
Hey
The captain of the losing team, Matsumoto
The captain of the losing team, Mameshibori
This program was brought to you by these sponsors