Next time on Gaki no Tsukai, Tsukitsuki's physical weakness!
Hello!
Where's your usual dandy Masumoto-kun?
Why do you ask?
Your head is like this!
No, I don't have a head, I can't fix it.
Here, here.
I can see that you're trying to fix it, but it looks like you can't do it anymore.
I can't do it anymore, my body is so tired.
You have a companion.
I can't do it anymore.
Today is the opening.
Physical weakness.
It's like a mental weakness.
When you're ready, you have to do something.
When I'm ready, I can't do it.
When you're ready, I have to do something.
I see.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
I think I remember most of it by now.
One whole raw egg.
You have to put it on the side like this.
Here's the face washing scissors.
I'm so ugly today!
I'm wearing a wig.
Oh, that's not it!
Is this the one?
That's right.
This is it, right?
No, this is it.
This is it.
I don't get it at all.
Don't peel it off.
You!
What's in here?
I thought you were going to touch this.
This is it.
See?
And then...
What?
This is the hair dryer.
I think this is it.
This is it.
What?
No, this is it.
Don't say nonsense.
This is it.
No, this is it.
Don't say nonsense.
I don't get it at all.
It's on top.
I'll lightly touch it.
See?
And then...
Ah!
This is it.
That's not it!
Glasses.
And then...
This is the hair dryer.
And this is the glass.
This is it.
Don't say nonsense.
I don't get it at all.
And then...
Ugh!
See?
It's like a big wind.
This is it.
See?
Ugh!
It's gross!
It's blue!
Next!
This is it.
This is the raw egg.
Are you promoting it?
What is this?
Is it a bird's nest?
Can you put soy sauce on it?
No, I can't.
I can't put Rocky on it.
Can you do it one last time?
I feel like I'm going to puke.
What is this?
What are you going to do with this?
Put this in your mouth and bite it.
Ugh!
And then...
Like this.
Open your mouth.
It doesn't have to be Gingami.
Gingami is more powerful.
What is that?
And then...
Glass kick.
Ugh!
Are you an animal?
I don't really like it.
I don't really like this.
This is...
I don't have soy sauce.
What is this?
Isn't this rotten?
I don't care.
It's okay.
It's rotten.
There's no way it's okay.
It hurts!
Hold my hand.
Wow!
It's okay.
It doesn't hurt that much here.
What is this hand?
It hurts!
It hurts so much!
It's okay.
It hurts!
Next...
There's nothing left.
There is.
It doesn't have soy sauce.
It's all over my ears.
It's okay.
Here.
There's nothing left.
Why?
Mix it.
Is this soy sauce?
Isn't this sauce?
There's nothing left.
There it goes!
That feels bad!
I can't put it into words.
That's all.
Wait, you can't eat 20 times as spicy as me.
No, seriously, I can't get excited even if you make me eat this much.
No, no.
I can't eat spicy food at all.
It's fine, it's fine.
It's good.
What kind of reaction is that?
It's like an animal squid!
It's not like that.
It's spicy!
It's spicy, but it's fine.
Are you kidding me?
No, it's fine.
It's spicy!
It's spicy, but it's good.
If it's spicy, it's like this.
It's like this.
If you say that...
It's fine.
What are you going to do if you're happy?
At the end, your face will be up.
It's spicy, but it's fine.
You have to eat 20 times as spicy as me.
Why are you like this?
Good evening.
Where is the video center?
I don't know where the video center is.
Is this the video center?
Let's talk.
What should we talk about?
Today, I'm going to give you some lessons.
What is it?
You often take a day off from work, right?
I'm sad.
It's not a day off at all.
It's my fault.
It's my fault that I'm doing a different job.
My schedule is...
It was a stupid schedule.
I was on the train for two weeks.
What is that?
It's an indirect bad word to Masakado Tamura.
No, it's not.
It's a bad word.
I wanted to go back to work.
You wanted to go back to work.
I thought it would be bad.
On Thursday, when I finished work,
the moment I was relieved,
I heard the sound of a sick horse.
What are you worried about?
The sick horse is from Osaka.
I'm really sorry.
There are a lot of bad words to the company.
On Friday, I often come here.
I have work in Osaka on Thursday and Friday.
I come here at the end of the day.
I only have one manager, Nitta.
Nitta is a guy who went to Hamada.
No, no.
I can't come from another place.
What do you mean by that?
You are not a person who is writing.
I am writing.
Nitta is a guy who went to Hamada.
He wants to be loved by Hamada.
What are you talking about?
Nitta is a guy who has been assigned by the company.
He wants to be loved by two people.
Nitta wants to be loved by Hamada.
I am not writing.
What are you talking about?
He started his work because he didn't want to be a teacher.
He is a guy who is hated by the company.
He wants to be loved.
I don't want to be loved.
You are wrong.
If you compare a guy and a girl,
they really like Hamada.
If they like Hamada, they can do anything.
That's a complicated way to say it.
I want to be loved by Hamada on Friday.
Okay, I will come to your office from Osaka.
What about the subway?
Poor guy.
Please give it some time.
Tokyo ferries go very fast.
Ready to go and it's raining too.
If we take a cab, things can get worse.
We can't sit in unasel GabBai car.
Why?
Don't say weird things.
It's you!
Why?
The taxi drivers are lined up, right?
Because you want to get on.
Line up!
If you want to get on too.
No, no, no.
They're really lined up!
I know!
But you can't get on if you're not lined up.
Line up!
My body is already weak.
I want to go home quickly.
You want to go home?
I can't get on.
Why?
Line up!
How do you want to go home?
You want to go home without being lined up?
Yes.
That's not good.
If it was a normal office,
they would have brought you to the station.
You would have gotten on and left.
It's raining.
Why can't you be normal?
No, no, no.
It's raining.
They're lined up in the rain.
If you go to the other side,
there are times when taxis stop.
If you cross the street.
But there are no umbrellas.
But if you go there,
there are a lot of people lined up.
If you go there,
you'll get soaked in the rain.
Even if you raise your hand like this,
the car won't stop at all.
It's just a little bit.
It's full of mud.
Why is it full of mud?
No, no, no.
It keeps running.
Oh, I see.
It keeps going like this.
You're lying.
Why are you lying?
No, no, no.
If you do that,
they'll pour water from the other side.
It's amazing.
It's like a stain.
If you go back to the car,
it's double the amount of water
that you should have taken earlier.
And then you go back again.
It takes about an hour like this.
You finally get a taxi.
And then you go home.
Even if you take a taxi,
even if you give the receipt,
it won't come.
It won't come, it won't come.
What is this?
That's right.
It's not up to 5000 yen.
If it's over 5000 yen,
there's got to be a reason.
He's saying he took a taxi.
That guy, Nozawa.
Even though he's on vacation,
he gets paid.
He's been on vacation for two years,
and he's been paid the same salary
every month.
That's a stupid thing to say.
That's strange.
So, as a company,
we treat Nozawa like
he's been on vacation for two years.
That's right.
Why do you think Nozawa is like that?
Simply put,
Yoshimoto Kogyo is a talent
in the Tokyo section.
Yes, yes.
We are Yoshimoto Kogyo,
the head of the Osaka branch.
That's the difference.
The head of the Osaka branch
seems to be nicer.
That's not true.
We have a higher rank
in the Tokyo branch.
You don't understand that.
That's the difference.
But now,
Yoshimoto is in downtown,
and he's having a hard time.
That's not because he's angry with me.
That's because...
No, that's not true.
It's all up to the business.
If I go,
she'll probably say,
do you want to go to Nanbo?
That's what she'll say.
So I say,
do you want to go to Nanbo?
Then she'll go to Nanbo.
That's what she says.
Why didn't you say bye this year?
What do you mean?
You're in charge of the business.
No.
I told you I'd go with you this year.
I'll go, but I'll support you.
Really?
Yes, really.
You'll have to go with me.
What's that?
I thought you'd say that, too.
Okay, I'll go with you.
I'll go with you.
If you say no, I'll go with you.
You're from Hakata?
It's obvious you're from Osaka.
I don't have any money.
Please do your best.
I don't have any.
You don't?
I have the same amount of money.
You should have some left.
What are you going to use it for?
Even if it looks like this, it's not.
You're so funny.
How much do you eat?
I eat a lot.
How much do you eat at a BBQ restaurant?
It's amazing.
The cows are like, give me a break.
What do you mean?
The cows are like, give me a break while you're eating?
Or the cows are like, give me a break.
The cows are like, give me a break.
The cows are like, give me a break while you're eating?
You're so funny.
You're such a joker!
I'm serious.
Look, I won.
On this show.
This fucking local in Tokyo.
I was on other shows all over the country.
This guy...
He was amazing.
I can't live in the entertainment world anymore.
You know...
What?
He's cutting a pumpkin.
What is he making?
Everyone's pushing him.
What do you think you're doing?
You're cutting a pumpkin.
What?
Who did you shoot?
Well...
You know them, right?
Mr. Sekiguchi and Ms. Takagi.
Yes, yes.
And Yamashiro.
I know I'm cutting a pumpkin.
I can't do anything.
Mr. Sekiguchi is faster.
What do you think you're doing?
You're cutting a pumpkin.
What are you doing?
You know...
What do you think you're doing?
Mr. Sekiguchi and Ms. Takagi.
They're all white.
I'm surprised.
In the end,
Mr. Sekiguchi's answer was different.
I knew it.
I told them to make me do it.
I'm a performer.
And when Hamada did it again,
Mr. Yamashiro did it.
Yamashiro!
And when Mr. Yamashiro answered,
it was different again.
Mr. Sekiguchi did it again.
Mr. Sekiguchi said
it was a jam.
And Hamada was like,
I thought I got it right.
But it was a boo.
You're wrong.
You can't just go around
with the answer.
Please play the guitar.
What?
What did you do?
I can't say anything.
When you came out,
I was surprised.
I can't say anything.
What do you think?
The monkey came out.
I told him to come out.
That's amazing.
My name is Lioness Asuka.
My nickname is Lioness.
Lioness.
Stop it.
I'm the world tag champion
of the AAA.
You're getting excited.
You should have told me earlier.
I've been racing lately.
I'm in the middle of it.
I can't fit in the normal size.
Why did you think
you were going to race again?
I wanted to do something
other than pro-wrestling.
I like dangerous things.
After the pro-wrestling,
I want to put myself
in a dangerous position.
We're the same age.
Are you 38 years old?
I'm not an old man.
Are you a rabbit?
Yes, I'm a rabbit.
I was watching you today.
I had a baby
with my wife.
Really?
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You're so annoying.
Are you a mother?
This is like a doll.
Thank you.
What are you going to do if you fall asleep?
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
This is how
people who want to be a celebrity
look like.
It's so hot.
Don't take off your clothes.
Hello.
I had a lot of guests
at the last special edition.
When Hibino Kazuhiko
wore it,
I designed it.
The T-shirt is ready.
This is the back.
This is the front.
This is
the front.
Roll it up.
Everything is okay, right?
Everything is perfect.
Ta- Having clothes that are puffy is
nice right?
You're so lame!
So lame!
It was good, wasn't it?
Thank you very much.
The people who are watching will decide.
If you want it, you'll want it.
And next time,
Let's surprise Ui-chan and Nan-chan.
Tonight, the Grand Champion is
on April 8th, Monday,
from 7pm to 2am.
That's right.
We're also looking for an assistant and a letter.
Everything is the same.
Please look forward to it.
See you next week.
Thank you very much.