Yohan's wife
Yohan's wife is a good friend
Always together
always together
Yohan's wife
I'm your wife
Wait, wait
Who told you to do this?
I don't know
I don't care
But you're a charismatic person
You're a charismatic entertainer
That's not true
You're wearing a charismatic collar
I'm a charismatic entertainer
You're wearing a charismatic short sleeve
It's popular now
What are you talking about?
I don't know
You wear anything charismatic
What do you mean by charismatic?
I do it myself
I'm a charismatic entertainer
That's what you mean
I do it behind my back
It's just the sound of it
I do it in the bathroom for 10 minutes
I don't know
I hope you're doing well today
It's been a year since I became a monk
There were three people who asked me to shake their hands
Even in Tokyo
Can I touch your head?
What are you doing?
You should have been nicer to your fans
You shouldn't have done that
That's rude
You're just walking
What if you get hit in the back?
Don't you think that's annoying?
That's really annoying
Please understand that part
What if you get hit in the back with a towel?
If you get hit in the back with a towel, I'll laugh
Is that so?
You have to be more clear about common sense and non-common sense
What if a 17-year-old girl comes to you and asks you to touch her head?
You'll be hit by a horse
A horse?
That's not good
Can I touch your head if I don't do it?
No
I don't like being touched
You shouldn't do that
Can't you do it like this?
You have to stretch your body
If you do that
What if I put a bandage on my head?
I'll do it like this
If you can't do it like this, I'll give up
Aren't you Mickey Mouse?
Think about it
You're 36
Isn't Mickey Mouse a cowboy?
It's not like I'm wearing it
I can't wear it
I don't want to wear it
Do you want to try it on?
What are you doing?
I don't want to wear it
Wait a minute
You're annoying
I don't want to wear it
I can't believe you're so happy
Take it out
You're the one who turned on the TV
I'm going to ask a question to Mr. Matsumoto
There's a famous fairy tale about the sea getting salty
Is there a fairy tale that people should be able to understand?
There is
I don't know if there is
There's a fairy tale about a old man in Gunma
Really?
Yes
You don't know it?
I've seen most of the old fairy tales
Tell me
There was an old man
There was an old woman
The old man couldn't move so the old woman was taking care of the field
The field came out
After that, the old man went to the side
It has nothing to do with the old man
The old man came out
I don't think that's the story
I don't remember the story
I was just looking
I don't remember
That's not the story
It's a nice story, Mr. Matsumoto
I always want people to think I'm intelligent
Of course
It doesn't work
Mr. Matsumoto
If you say this line, people will definitely think you're intelligent
Please tell me how
Of course
There's no man who doesn't like people who aren't intelligent
You can tell him
Of course I have to tell him
If you say that, you don't have intelligence
I still have a bit of a bone
What?
Was I wrong?
Whose question are you talking about?
This is a very simple story
I want you to come to my house at least once a week
I want you to take a lesson
1 hour and 20 minutes
Why are you talking like that?
1 hour is fine
I was doing it for an hour and a half
It's like tea time
1 hour and 20 minutes
No, but it's easy
I want to teach you
I want to teach the audience
I want to teach the people watching TV
But I don't want to teach you
I won't allow you to absorb it
What should I do?
Let's teach
Let's talk
What is this?
It's not
It's a very simple story
What do you always put English in the conversation?
Do you understand?
If you are asked something
If you don't put at least one English word
I feel like I can't give it back to the other person
Do you understand?
Do you think it's intelligence to give it back?
Of course
It's hot today
It was a degression
It looks like it's going to rain tomorrow
It's a dark side
It's going to rain tomorrow, but it's going to be sunny
It's a stretch
What?
It's a little early
Calm down
I almost cried
You should talk more
You should talk for about one minute
And ask me
Otherwise it's impossible
Do you understand?
Tatsuyoshi's game was in Osaka
He went alone
He went to Osaka Dome by himself
It was the last game
He went home
He went to Osaka by taxi
He came back to Tokyo by Shinkansen
It was a hard day
I didn't do anything