Today, we're going to hang out with everyone.
That's right!
Well, to hang out, we need this thing, right?
That's right.
Well, that's just a common person's story.
When you become a star like us, you don't need money when you hang out.
Don't we actually have money?
We don't.
Well, we only need one photo.
You're going to take one?
If you're going to hang out with us, you don't need money.
You don't need money?
With my face.
With your face?
Wow!
That's why you're rich!
You're so stingy!
Really?
Then, let's have a drink.
You know, Suga-chan told me not to say anything.
He gave me 10,000 yen.
But I don't have any.
I think I'm the only one who's a star.
Oh, you have a star, Yoh.
I only have Orimomasawa left.
Stop it!
That's a camera.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Hey, you're going to give us a ride, right?
What?
What's going on?
Do you know that we're going to ride?
Yeah.
Wow!
Where should we go?
There's a lot of traffic on this road.
Should we take the expressway?
The expressway is free.
What?
Yeah, the expressway is free.
That's why I'm sitting here.
I can't show my face.
You can't show your face?
Yeah.
It's free.
I can't show my face.
You can't show your face?
Yeah.
This is the entrance, right?
Yeah, this is the entrance.
Let's go.
We can see it.
Oh, I saw it.
I saw it.
Hello, downtown.
Oh, hello.
I saw your face somewhere.
May I?
No, you can't.
I'll give you 700 yen.
700 yen?
Yes.
Here you go.
Do you want to take a picture?
Yeah, please.
Wait a minute.
Mr. Matsumoto, Mr. Hama.
What?
Something's wrong.
He said no.
Maybe he's a new member.
Oh, hello.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Matsumoto, are you a new member?
Let's go.
Hello.
What's wrong with you?
Are you a new member?
He said it was ridiculous.
And he said no.
He said no.
That was fast.
What's wrong with you?
You know what?
I don't know what's funny.
What's funny?
He's serious.
Let's get off.
What?
Are we getting off?
Are you serious?
If we get on now, we'll be in trouble.
Let's get off.
Are we really getting off?
We'll be in trouble.
Yeah.
I'm hungry.
I don't mind.
Oh, there's a YOSHINOYA.
Are we going there?
Let's go.
There's no YOSHINOYA?
No.
There's no YOSHINOYA.
Oh, really?
Why do you want to go there?
I don't want to go.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Let's eat.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'm full.
Excuse me.
Okay.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Let's go.
Okay.
Thank you.
That's amazing.
No one's coming, right?
Let's go.
Let's play.
This is amazing.
We can play anything.
If it was a nightclub, we'd go get some air.
Yeah.
Can we get some air?
Everyone's catching a cold.
Oh, really?
There's a nightclub on the side of the wagon.
Oh, there is.
A nightclub on the side of the wagon?
Is this a place to catch a cold?
Can I have some Isojin?
Isojin?
Oh, really?
Can I have some Isojin?
This is really good.
Is it?
You can take pictures.
Can I have two of these?
Yes.
How much is this?
This is 2,800 yen.
If you're in trouble, you can take it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Are you going to pay for the ingredients?
What?
Hamada's going to tell you.
He's going to tell you.
Oh, really?
You guys don't have to come anymore.
We're leaving.
You don't have to come anymore.
Let's go.
How much is it?
8,850 yen.
9,000 yen.
Yes.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Mom, don't talk to me.
You guys drank a lot, didn't you?
Yes.
That's why we're here.
It's just for you.
That's right.
Do you still have your wallet?
I have it, but...
Oh, really?
Yes.
But you didn't need it, did you?
What?
You didn't need it, did you?
Well, basically.
That's right. It has nothing to do with us.
Anyway, you have your wallet, right?
I have it.
Well, we don't have to go anywhere.
Shall we put gasoline in?
Let's put gasoline in.
That's right.
It's dangerous.
Okay, let's put it in here.
Hello.
Yes, we have gas and regular.
Regular.
Is it a full tank?
Yes.
Do you have a number?
No.
Is it cash?
Yes.
Well, it's cash.
You can't treat it like cash.
Oh, it's cash.
It's a receipt.
Is that so?
Yes, it's cash.
Well, we can't treat it like cash.
It'll be 4,112 yen.
Yes.
Mr. Hamada.
I have something to tell you.
It'll be 4,112 yen.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Mr. Hamada, can I see your wallet?
What are you looking at?
Can I see your wallet?
You want me to show it to you?
Give it to me.
No, no.
What is it?
Mr. Hamada.
Excuse me.
Wait, wait, wait.
Mr. Hamada.
What do you want to do?
Can I see your wallet?
Yes, yes.
Isn't it free?
No.
I don't want it anymore.
It's free, isn't it?
I don't want it.
Please.
It's free, isn't it?
Yes, yes.
Well, it's 5,650 yen.
It's my credit card.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
See you later, Yone-chan.
Yes.
When did you meet Yone-chan?
It was definitely Yone-chan.
Yes.
What is this?
Mr. Hamada.
This is really.
What is it?
You said it was free before, didn't you?
It's not free at all.
What?
What did you just say?
Mr. Hamada, what did you just say?
It's free.
What are you going to do?
Do you want to have some tea?
Yes.
To refresh your mind.
Can you go for free?
I'd like to have some tea.
Where is this place?
This place is.
Kamikitazawa.
I see.
That's right.
Yahatayama.
Isn't this Hachiman Yamato-chan?
Endo.
Yes.
Don't talk too much.
Don't show your stupidity.
The fish shop is free.
It's a great place.
I was calculating the price.
You were calculating the price?
Yes. You were calculating the price?
It's 8,000 yen.
You were calculating the price?
Are you okay?
Let's go to the toilet.
Okay.
This is Matagose-san.
Hey, wait.
Hey.
Hey, give it to me.
Hey, wait.
You're a thief.
What?
Please look at Yamada-san's face.
Why?
Why are you paying?
I'm paying you.
How much is it?
3,000 yen.
3,000 yen?
Why did you do that?
Don't call me.
Don't you have anything to pay?
I don't have anything to pay.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
I have 9,000 yen left.
I'm sorry.
9,000 yen.
9,300 yen.
Idiot.
Idiot?
There's nothing to be idiotic about.
What are you talking about?
You guys are crazy.
You're young.
It's all for free.
Leave it to me.
I'll leave it to you.
Take me with you next time.
I can't.
Excuse me.
You forgot your cigarettes.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
By the way,
I didn't get the question earlier.
Oh.
He left.
I'm sorry.
Yamazaki.
Idiot.
Why did you take my cigarettes?
I'm sorry.
How much is it?
5,160 yen.
I'm sorry.
Here you go.
Here's 10,000 yen.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Here you go.
What do you mean?
You're saying it's all for free, right?
I'll pay for it.
He said it's all for free.
It's impossible, right?
We're the same, right?
That's enough.
If you say more, I'll have to close it with a bottle cap.
Idiot.
Yamazaki.
You're so stupid.
Like this?
What should I say?
Everyone is fine, but I'm in trouble.
Why?
It's been a while since I caught a cold.
I caught a cold.
Did you take medicine?
I did, but it's been a long time.
You should see a doctor.
I can't see a doctor right now.
I don't get a fever.
Even if I catch a cold.
Really?
But I'm a little girl.
I'm a little girl.
What kind of girl?
The first thing I can't forgive is the nosebleed.
I see.
What's with the nosebleed?
I can't sleep at night.
If I get a cold, I turn around and sleep.
That nosebleed is funny.
What kind of human body is this?
You like it, don't you?
Are you Japanese?
No, no.
I'll change the word.
We're not Japanese anymore.
It's getting worse.
It's getting worse, isn't it?
It's hard to catch a cold.
You can see the nosebleed, but you shouldn't be in a hurry.
After a while, you have to measure the distance with your mouth.
You have to keep the nosebleed.
If you do this, the nosebleed will go away.
I think it's okay.
After a while, it's like an order stop.
It's like, are you ready?
You still have to measure the distance with your mouth.
You have to repeat it until you get a cold.
Until I get a cold?
Yes.
I'm so angry.
It's not a cold.
You have to drill a hole here.
I don't want to drill a hole.
But don't say anything to me.
What do you mean?
Don't say something weird.
Weird?
What? A hole?
That's fine, but you say something weird here.
I don't like that.
Oh, I see.
But you only say it at that moment.
It's weird for a girl to drill a hole.
It's not that bad.
Sometimes, I put something that I made and dyed my skin here.
Oh, you shouldn't do that.
If you do that, I'll say it.
That's weird.
I don't like that.
You don't like that?
Oh, I remember!
Yesterday was my day!
Why did you turn on the TV?
I told you to go to the police station!
You stupid bastard!
Wait a minute!
I rarely watch TV.
There was something like a notice.
I don't know what it was, but I turned it on, and you came out as a couple.
What are you guys?
Did they give you something by swapping?
It's the duty of the people.
I'll become a couple with you.
Why?
You won't.
You don't know what it is.
I don't know what it is.
You should have told me earlier!
I heard that a lot of people died this year.
Oh, really?
I have a preventive injection.
That's right.
You really do that.
Then why didn't you go to the hospital?
You should have told me earlier!
You only care about yourself.
So why didn't I tell you that I was going to give you a preventive injection?
I didn't tell you, but I did give you a preventive injection.
Machan.
Machan is from Hamachaya.
I gave you a preventive injection, but why didn't you give it to me?
Why are you so kind?
I don't know.
If it were me, I would have told you.
Why?
If there's something delicious, I'll wrap it in a tissue and give it to you.
You've never given it to me before.
I haven't met any delicious sweets before, but if there is, I'll give it to you.
It seems like you have a lot of fever.
It's fine.
Why?
You don't have to worry about it.
You're really...
You're really sad.
What do you want to say?
You make your own food, but you have a fever.
That's not true!
No matter what you do, you're alone.
What is that?
What song is that?
Don't make it into a song.
Do you want to hear the rest?
I think you should get married.
If you have a fan like this,
If you have a fan like this, I want to hear it more!
I want to show it to Yoh!
Yoh?
Did you hear the Japanese song?
It's a part of the song.
If you do it suddenly, without a notice,
I'll do it so that no one knows.
Are you going to die?
I'm working, so I'll get caught.
You're going to tell no one?
No, no, no.
I'll just put it in my seat and do it.
Don't get excited!
Say no!
Every summer, for the children in the city,
If you catch insects in the mountains,
On a sleepless night, in the concrete jungle of the city,
I have a question for Matsumoto-san.
What do insects do in the wild?
They're grinning.
Are you grinning?
Are you going to sleep?
Why are you half laughing?
You're a fool.
Please tell me that.
I've never heard you grin.
It doesn't matter if it's a fly or an insect.
It's his dream to become a fly.
It's his debut.
Tomorrow is his first concert.
If you do it, it's fine.
It doesn't matter if you do it later.
The tickets are sold out.
That's enough!
I'm coming.
Don't tell me.
Your mom and dad are coming.
The manager is asking you to come.
That's...
I know. I totally understand.
That's right before it comes out.
What do you mean?
I don't understand.
For example, the condition of the fly is for about a week.
The condition of the fly?
For example.
The fly on the sixth day is grinning.
It's before his debut.
The fly on the first day is also grinning.
At that time, it wasn't grinning.
What are you doing at this time?
What?
I'm having a lesson.
What do you mean by a lesson?
In this case,
I'm having a lesson about the fly.
What is it?
I don't understand that.
Why don't you tell me the short part of the fly?
I want to go back to the beginning.
It's fine.
What is it?
I can answer anything.
What are you doing on the first day?
On the first day?
The first day is the word for the fly that came out from the countryside.
I see.
You're fixing the fly.
During the period of forced labor.
Sleepy.
I'm doing it because it comes out.
Don't be stupid.
On the first day,
I'm fixing the fly.
You're fixing the fly.
Your cheeks are still red.
I see.
What about the second day?
What?
The second day?
What is it?
You said you were going to take a bath the day before, right?
That's right.
You're saying, here, right?
I see.
Be careful.
I'm scared.
That's right.
I don't understand that.
When it's night time,
you're saying, sleep.
Sleepy.
This is the first time I've been so sleepy.
I understand that.
The next day.
The second day.
You wake up in the morning.
What are you going to do?
I have to go see the president.
I see.
The fly hasn't disappeared yet.
It's a lesson.
I see.
I have to go see the president.
From the second day,
you came out of the countryside yesterday.
From the second day, I came out of the countryside.
I'm taking a picture.
I see.
This is a good fly.
It's a chosen fly.
I'm sorry.
It's not good.
Who are you?
I have to do the choreography.
I see.
Hey, look at that.
It's really not good.
The person who said it looks like a fly.
Change the words properly.
Yes.
After that,
I was touched.
That's what happened.
The day before, you were smiling.
I see.
When the bell rang,
the audience stood up.
Until now,
that was the only thing that happened.
That's right.
When the curtain opened,
it was so beautiful.
What are you doing?
Go away.
This program was sponsored by the following sponsors.