In the middle of the night, it's time to go to the restaurant.
It's hot.
What do you want to eat?
I want to eat somen.
Let's eat somen.
It's delicious.
Stop it.
The entertainment world.
The city without justice.
The city of bones.
The first to be cut off in the entertainment world is Yamazaki Hosei.
And the second to be left behind is...
The one who doesn't know what's scary.
Jimmy Owens.
The fight for justice.
I came to buy something.
You came to buy a swimsuit, right?
I came by car.
This is Yamazaki's car.
This is Yamazaki's car?
What's wrong with you?
Shut up.
Stop it.
You're annoying.
What's wrong with you?
Why did you kick my car?
Why did you kick it?
I was breathing.
It's used.
Stop it.
Why did you kick my car?
What are you doing?
You're a natural-born person.
You can't drive like this.
Stop it.
Yamazaki is better than you.
Why?
He can do anything.
Yamazaki can do anything.
Let's have a match.
Let's do it.
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
Yamazaki is eating raw meat.
Shut up.
Yamazaki is like this.
I'll eat pork.
Pork is not good.
What is this?
This is bacon with asparagus.
If you do this, I can't do it.
I'll do it.
I like one.
This is a video.
He is crying.
If you do that, I can't show it.
I'll show you.
He is crying.
If you do this, I can't do it.
This is amazing.
You're good.
Shut up.
Don't underestimate my Yamagaki.
What is it?
I'm going to eat all the curry powder.
He's talking about spicy food.
Hello.
She knows how to laugh.
I can eat a lot.
This is the victory of Yamagaki.
The victory of Yamagaki.
You have an English book, don't you?
What?
All right.
Did you see my head?
North Asian shop, she said.
You pass an coffee shop.
A long, a long day.
Can't complete.
What kind of person are you?
This is Yamagaki.
North Asian.
An coffee shop.
An Latte.
What kind of person are you?
Do you know what it means?
My Yamagaki doesn't know.
I don't know what it means.
It's obvious.
Let's eat cheese.
Are you stupid?
You are very good at the three-person book.
What?
Look at it.
Three-person book.
You are very good at SVOC.
Look at it.
Listen to the English.
You don't know SVOC.
I know.
The best part of the coffee shop.
Why?
I don't buy it.
Don't say such a thing.
Don't lie.
It's true.
My Jimmy is a little better in terms of nutrition.
Really?
It's strange.
Did you say that?
My Jimmy is hot.
No one loses.
My Jimmy is good anywhere.
Wait a minute.
It's okay.
It's okay even if it's in your ear.
Bite it.
I can't take it.
You don't know.
Look at it.
I'm a man who does it when I do it.
It's hot.
Finset.
Hello.
Don't do that.
I can't drink lemon juice.
Really?
Look at it.
Don't open your mouth.
My Jimmy is cute.
Don't say such a thing.
Who said such a thing?
I can't accept it.
That's right.
Go away.
You're cute.
You're doing a great job.
I haven't lost yet.
Don't say such a thing.
It's none of your business.
My Jimmy can't put a barricade in it.
That's impossible.
I don't know.
My Jimmy is cute.
You're doing a great job.
That's right.
My Jimmy can't put a barricade in it.
That's impossible.
I can't accept it.
What are you doing?
My Jimmy can't put a barricade in it.
Look at it.
You're doing a great job.
I can't let you do such a thing.
Hey.
Yes.
You know what?
What?
My Jimmy is amazing.
He doesn't have a sense of shame.
Don't you feel embarrassed?
Not at all.
I don't wear a panty and run around the shopping street.
What?
Don't tell me.
Let me see it.
It's amazing.
Yamanaki.
Ladies and gentlemen.
What do you think?
It's hot.
The other day.
Yes.
It's like a joke.
How many times did you shoot the Invention Shogun?
Invention Shogun?
Yes.
I've seen it twice.
You've seen it, right?
Yes.
I finished shooting.
Shooting?
You said it was a joke.
I've been told such a detailed thing.
I can't talk.
I finished shooting.
Invention Shogun.
What?
I finished shooting.
Leave it.
I went to the toilet.
I left it.
I finished shooting.
I was doing Invention Shogun.
I left it.
There was no one.
Someone came out.
Okamoto.
Manager Okamoto.
Good morning.
He came out of the toilet and said hello to me.
I said, oh.
He went into the toilet next door and came back.
It's like Bruce Lee's tower of death.
What are you talking about?
Defeat the enemy once in a while.
When I saw the first time I went into the toilet, the toilet was floating.
This is a low level as a human being.
You shouldn't do it.
This is today's opening.
Your spilling story.
Spilling story.
Well, that's probably the case.
Tell me the other day.
Return it.
Your spilling story this time.
The other day.
What?
Well, there were a lot of things.
There were a lot of things.
Don't say it.
Well, I'll leave it here.
Leave it.
What are you looking at?
Well, when you're doing this kind of work, there are a lot of stories.
There are.
Then next time.
I'm going to do a special edition for two hours with a child.
I'm talking for about 30 to 40 minutes.
Well, that's about it.
The stupid staff here told me to do it for 24 hours.
Don't say that.
The guest can't leave for 24 hours.
I can't sleep for 24 hours sitting all the time.
He's talking.
I didn't want to talk for 24 hours. I didn't want to do it.
But I didn't want to talk for a long time.
I didn't want to talk for 20 hours.
I can't do it for 20 hours.
But I can't go camping.
I can't sleep or go camping.
I can't go outside. I can't sing with everyone on the guitar.
I want you to do it for me.
I can't go camping. I can't sing with everyone on the guitar.
I'll recruit you. But I want you to do it for me.
I can't do it for 24 hours.
I want you to do it for me.
I wrote a fan letter the other day.
It's a fan letter. I like you.
I don't know if it's a fan letter or a letter of opinion.
I wrote a fan letter.
I didn't write a fan letter.
I'm a big fan of Machan.
I told my friends at school that I was a fan of Machan.
Everyone said it was disgusting.
Why? Why?
Where is that old man?
It's a flame.
It's a flame. It's terrible to play with women.
I wrote a lot of things.
I wrote what I was told.
But I'm a fan of Machan.
I'm not happy.
Why do I have such an image?
I'll do something like that again.
I heard a bad rumor about me.
What are you talking about?
I met a woman the other day.
I took her to my apartment.
I told her.
Which do you choose, sex or oolong tea?
Is there anyone who says that?
If that woman wants to do it with me,
If she says that, she'll say oolong tea.
That depends on the person.
Why?
Which do you choose, oolong tea or sex?
Which do you choose?
It's strange to say that it's sex.
I wrote a lot of things like that.
I see.
It's an enhancement period for comedy talents.
Who else is being targeted?
Matsumura.
You said that.
In front of the door of Matsumura's house.
I wrote a bad rumor about me.
That's right.
I don't need it.
It's okay to write a bad rumor, right?
What do you mean by a bad rumor?
When I opened the door of Matsumura's house,
There was a cardboard.
Why?
It's strange.
There was a bad rumor.
I opened it.
When I opened it, there was a camera inside.
I was looking at the front of the door.
And Megumi.
The one who was in the way.
I was like a light.
I don't know what happened.
I was standing still.
I looked at the inside.
There was a lot of camera lenses inside.
That's exactly what I'm aiming for.
I'm doing this.
You should have finished cleaning earlier.
I was doing this.
Are you done?
Why are you so nervous?
I said something.
If I don't finish it now, it's a concentrated attack.
I don't care.
I really care about you.
Me?
That's dangerous.
Don't say that kind of stuff.
Why did you say that?
What kind of stuff is that?
That's harassment.
Why do you look up when you get on the elevator?
I don't know what to do.
Humans want to know what's going to happen next.
That's why I'm looking up.
Why are you looking up?
What kind of stuff is that?
That's weird.
It was funny.
You look up when you try to go up.
You look up when you run forward.
Explain it again.
Are you an idiot?
You can't say that out loud.
Listen to me.
I'm going to get out of bed at night again.
I got it.
Are you going to rest tomorrow?
I don't care.
I don't know what to do.
Humans want to know what's going to happen.
That's cool.
That's why I'm looking up.
What are you talking about?
Are you really in the 18th chapter?
You were in the second chapter, right?
The first chapter.
What was it?
It's nothing.
A little more.
I think I was happy.
Thank you.
That's the first chapter.
I don't know what to do.
It's nothing.
You're taking it off too much.
It doesn't change much.
It changes from the next one.
I think I was happy.
The 18th chapter has changed a lot.
From the second to the 18th.
Do you know?
I know.
Really?
I know everything.
What is 14?
14 is the best part.
Please tell me 14.
It's nothing.
It's completely different.
I want to be a wild man like Macha.
What is wild?
I want to be a barretta who is always hiding.
It's nothing.
It's not wild.
I want to be a barretta who is always hiding.
Please tell me what you learn.
I've been farming for a long time.
I can't tell you that.
How many do you have?
I have about 27 or 28.
Please tell me one.
It doesn't matter if you have a lot of chocolate.
Before you go to bed.
You have to drink vinegar.
Please tell me one more.
I want to be a squirrel.
I want to love animals.
I have a lot of things.
Please tell me one more.
What is it called?
It's a bird.
I'm wearing it, but there's something on my back.
I'm wearing it, but there's nothing on my back.
Please tell me one more.
It's just a bird.
I'm wearing it, but there's nothing on my back.