This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
The night is a cryo-kant.
Good evening.
Today, I...
I've reached the point where I have to go.
What's wrong?
I'm in shock.
I'm in shock, I'm in shock.
You're at the top.
I'm surprised.
Last week, there was a talk show, right?
At that time, you got angry, right?
I got angry?
Your role, what's your role?
And then I went in.
What's your job?
Why are you here? What's your job?
I'm a model.
You can't say it loudly.
You can't say it loudly, right?
I'm a model.
Right?
Yes.
There are people who think Hamada is really angry.
Why?
I'm shocked by this.
It can't be.
Where did you get this information?
There are quite a few.
There's something like that before.
Why can't you understand it?
There's a series of Itao, right?
Yes, yes.
There is.
The one that Itao was watching.
He really thinks Itao is that kind of person.
Tokira-san said that.
Why did you say that?
Tell me!
It's amazing that you believe it.
It's scary.
This one, if it happens...
It's a show.
Itao was hit by a rocket launcher.
When he opened the trunk, the stew spilled out.
It was a foreign person.
Why do you think that it's not like that?
I don't know.
Even if you say that, it's like that.
Really.
The other day, I was bullied in a good way.
In your mind?
Yes, in my mind.
It was really good.
Hamada was like this.
If I extended the time a little more, I would cry.
Really, really.
If I pulled it a little more, I might cry.
It feels good.
Even though it's like that...
It's just because you're bad at it.
Even if it's like that...
I don't know.
I'm frustrated.
I'm frustrated with Hamada-kun.
Who?
Senpai.
I'm really angry.
It's the same with Itao.
What is it?
How many of those people are there?
But if it's a person who likes kids and watches them all the time, I think they'll understand.
I've been doing this for 10 years.
I don't even know anymore.
It's like a skit.
The other day, when I said something, the audience was laughing.
There's no way to use that.
If I get angry, I'll be like this again.
If you say that,
Last week, when I saw Suga-chan, she was wearing a skirt like that all the time.
That kind of thing.
So, really, wake up!
Seriously!
Suga-chan has been wearing a skirt all the time.
She's over 40.
There's no point in saying she's over 40.
If she's 18 years old, it's fine.
That's right, but...
You can tell that she's doing it on purpose.
Why can't you tell me?
But it's more than I thought.
I was really surprised.
What should I do?
What should you do?
What's the truth?
I don't know.
You did it somewhere today, too.
I did it somewhere today, too.
But if I'm bad at it, even if I say it like this,
No, that's not it.
I don't think she's bad at it, so I'm just saying it.
At that time, Hana-chan was really angry.
That's why she came out again.
What should I do?
I'll try not to get angry.
That's why.
I'll never get angry.
I don't know who you're talking to.
I don't think you saw all the kids from last week.
But you've seen some of them, haven't you?
If you feel like you're really angry, just raise your hand.
I won't get angry.
I won't do anything.
I won't jump around and hug you.
I'm really...
Actually, I'm a little...
You are?
If there's anyone who thinks so,
I'd like you to say his name.
Do you want me to say it?
Raise your hand.
You are?
Isn't it?
I think Hamada was really angry.
Is that so?
I don't like it anymore.
I don't know what to say.
It's harder to convey than we think.
I think I know what you mean.
I don't think you should be so serious about your face.
But he's really angry.
If you don't make a serious face,
you'll be in trouble.
That's strange.
I thought I was really good at acting.
When I got home, I was really tired.
Then, in your mind...
I'm really good at acting.
I'm sorry.
Who are you?
If you say something like that...
Yes, yes, yes.
You're so loud.
I'm angry.
But it's a good excuse for Hamada to hit you.
That's right.
If you hit me once, I'll hit you again.
What are you talking about?
If you hit me again, I'll hit you again.
I see.
That's right.
I was really shocked when I heard that.
I can't help it.
I'm counting on you.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's okay?
In all these times he was alone.
He might have some things he didn't tell me.
When we got home, he said he couldn't tell me.
He couldn't tell me.
He said, that was true.
What?
What are you doing?
You want to say that again, don't you?
No, there are still things that are seen as wrong in a different way.
Occasionally, many times a year, when I'm walking down the street,
I'm told that I'm smaller than I look on TV.
You're the one who...
You're the one who made me look so big!
In your world!
I can't do anything!
And all of a sudden, you say, I'm the tall Matsumoto.
I'm the big Uri-no-matchan.
I can't even put it into words.
You're the one who made me look so big!
I'm told that I'm smaller than I look on TV.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
You're so annoying!
You!
Wait, wait!
Did you fall so much that you're dizzy?
I'm going to slap you!
Really!
Thank you.
Well, well, I've calmed down a bit.
Then you should have said something.
I've said something, so I've calmed down a bit.
No, I have to talk about something else.
I have to talk about the match.
Really?
I'm going to give you the Kokoriko Yamazaki.
You're going to give it to me?
I'm going to give it to you.
Oh, I see.
Please fight me.
Four against one?
Yes.
That's good.
I've been thinking about it.
This game is very difficult.
You can play golf.
You can play golf, but...
Well, well, well.
I've played it twice.
100 meters.
What?
100 meters of the Tokyo-so.
Tokyo-so?
Yes.
I'm going to run 100 meters on my own.
You guys are going to do it in relay.
In baton.
Okay.
Are you okay?
What?
Wait a minute.
What does your picture mean?
It looks interesting.
I don't know which one will win.
Pretend?
It looks interesting.
Look at me.
Are you okay?
It looks interesting.
What are you doing?
Wait a minute.
You can definitely win if you run alone.
Right?
Really?
You can definitely win if you run alone.
Wait a minute.
Human beings are slow to start.
They gradually accelerate, don't they?
That's right.
It's easy to get in the middle.
If you think about it...
You're free, aren't you?
That's right.
If you become free, I don't have to depend on anything.
It's okay.
Really?
Look at me.
Don't say anything.
Don't say that you can win.
It's an interesting game.
I have to do well.
Should I do this with 100 or 200?
Is that so?
100.
My secretary...
Who is the secretary?
Really?
You are the secretary.
Yeah, you're always smiling.
I'm telling you.
If you think about it normally, if you run 100 meters, you'll be able to run smoothly.
No, no, no, but I don't have the stamina you think I have.
The stamina you think I have is different from the stamina I really have.
Well, that's what they say.
How is it?
But if you run with me, you ran a little before, right?
At that time, you were a little faster than me, right?
Yes, yes.
I can't see how much strength these three people, Endo, Tanaka, and Yamazaki have.
But I think Yamazaki is slow.
That kind of thing.
Wait a minute. That's true.
If you think about it like that, it's a little tough.
25 meters.
Are you guys okay?
We're not okay at all.
Endo says he can win at all.
Why can't you say that?
Why do you look like that?
I'm confident that I can win as another member.
Endo is fast.
I'm 6 seconds.
What is 6 seconds?
What do you do in 6 seconds?
Close your eyes?
That's faster.
Just like that.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Tanaka, too.
I don't think I can win.
He's very naive.
Wait a minute.
100 meters is a little dangerous.
It's very subtle.
Don't you think it's an obstacle?
What is an obstacle?
It's an obstacle race.
What's going on?
Is there a hurdle or a rain?
Stop it.
I don't do rain.
I just go through the rain and go over there.
I don't care about the valley of the chest.
What kind of clothes are you wearing?
The valley of the chest.
Why do you wear clothes that are open?
That's a little...
I understand.
I understand your intention.
Let's think about it.
We have to think about the penalty.
That's right.
There's something amazing about it.
I'm already thinking about it.
By the way...
I think I'm going to lose.
I'm going to line up the four of us.
I'm going to prepare a long bamboo skewer.
I'm going to cut it like this.
And I'm going to catch it.
I'm going to shake it a little.
It's funny.
If you catch it...
I'm going to hold my breath for a long time.
Why?
Why are you holding your breath?
I see.
It's really subtle.
You look like you're confident.
I'm not going to lose to you tomorrow.
I'm not going to lose to you.
I have nothing to lose to you.
I can do it.
I'm definitely going to win.
I'm really fast.
Come on, you guys.
I'm not going to write today.
I'm definitely going to win.
Tanaka.
On TV.
It was really subtle.
It's like this.
It's okay.
Yamazaki, come here and do this.
The start is different.
Ready, go.
It's slippery.
Take it off.
I'm not going to lose to you.
If you do it under your shoes, it's the same.
Hurry up and do it.
This is long.
Why are you doing that?
Do it.
Let's go.
On the count of three.
Ready, go.
See?
It's the same.
Take a look.
I want to go to the third place.
I want to go to the fourth place.
The start is wrong.
Third place?
Who's going to the top?
This is wrong.
It's longer than I thought.
It's harder than I thought.
Tanaka, I have a compass.
Try it.
See?
I think I can earn a lot.
The problem is how to divide the four and one.
It's four and one.
What number are you trying to run?
You're not in.
It's different.
You can't run with five people.
I don't know why this is happening.
That's what happened.
This is okay.
Why?
You said it first.
It was like this after the golf game.
It's strange.
It's in the order of the height of the line.
And...
I saw it now.
I don't know what to do with the order.
I'll decide that.
Why?
That's our strength.
Please decide the meter.
Five meters.
I see.
I'll decide that.
Why?
That's our strength.
Listen.
If you're okay with that, that's fine.
Two, two, two.
Twenty, twenty, twenty.
No, no.
Two meters, two meters, two meters.
And then you run.
I don't have enough stamina.
Two meters.
I see.
I don't have enough stamina.
You have to decide that.
I have to decide that.
There's nothing I can decide.
What?
You can decide costumes.
I don't want to.
Put me in there a little.
There's color of the baton.
You can decide the color of the baton.
I'll decide the color of the baton.
I don't care what color it is.
Well, then.
You're going to say no if I say this.
Green.
Okay.
The green one is no good.
It's normal.
I wonder if there will be a lot of booing.
I'll have to read the rules again.
How fast can you run at 100 meters?
Honestly, at 100 meters.
The one you recently measured.
I don't know that.
The one you measured the most recently.
It's about 11 seconds.
11 seconds?
You're an Olympic athlete!
Why are you running so fast?
Why?
Wait a minute.
How fast can you run?
But...
55...
It was about 7 seconds.
It was when I was in high school.
I ate a lot of dumplings.
Has your running style changed?
It's still the same, right?
It's like Okamame.
Your running style will definitely change.
You've seen it before, right?
No, no, no.
There's no way it will change.
I'm just making the air my friend.
But Matsumoto-san...
You're training him, right?
Yes, I'm training him.
He's amazing.
But, but, but...
Honestly, when I see him running,
he's twice as fast as Hyo.
Hyo is starting to look thin.
He's starting to look like Hyo from the front.
I don't understand what you're saying.
I don't understand this.
I understand that you're starting to look like Hyo,
but you're starting to look like him from the front.
That's right.
What do you mean, from the front?
I really don't understand that.
I really can't say that.
No, no.
What was that?
No, no, no.
That was funny.
You don't have to say it.
I can't say that.
I don't understand.
I don't understand what you're saying.
But, do you want to go with that?
Let's go.
That's totally fine.
You want to go?
I'll decide.
I'm fine with doing it with bare hands.
That's my problem.
If you hold something, it'll be very difficult to do it.
I really want to do it like this.
Like this?
Really.
With your hands?
Like this?
How do you do it?
No, if I do this, it'll be very different.
With your hands?
Yes.
I want to match left and right.
Yes, yes.
What should I do?
If I can't hold it, I'll take two.
What if you take two?
If I take two, it'll be difficult to color it.
You can't do it with one hand.
You can do it with blue and blue.
Blue and blue?
Then you can do it with red.
Why?
Because there are many colors.
You can do it with blue.
You can do it with red.
Even if the children see it, there are many colors.
It's gorgeous.
That's not it.