This week's guest is...
Nadal's 24 hour long interview, the final episode!
During my break, I run around like this
And I see my shoes running off my feet
I run like this
In his childhood, he was bullied
I would go to the toilet and find my shoes
I was really famous
The school days when he was a student who wanted to be a school nurse
I wanted to be a fishmonger, especially in the aquarium
Speaking of your father, what is the thing that you have in your house?
I said it's impossible
You're scared?
Tonight, the bad comedian, Konochi-kun Nadaru, is naked!
Eh, he's so red!
He's dead!
It's 8.26pm.
He takes his tired-looking Nadaru to a restaurant to have dinner.
Nadaru-san, this is your favorite restaurant, right?
Yes, I always bring my juniors here.
Ah, really?
Yes.
What kind of restaurant is it?
Link.
Yes?
What do you recommend?
Mentaiko pasta.
Mentaiko pasta is really good.
Is it an Italian restaurant?
Well...
European.
European?
What?
I don't know much about it.
It's not that special.
There's also a French restaurant.
Yes.
It's a European style Western food.
I want to tell the viewers that they can expect anything.
I understand.
Please wait a moment.
I don't know what to say.
What should I say?
It's pasta.
It's a half-baked pasta.
It's like Capricciosa.
Capricciosa...
Well, that kind of...
It's a bar.
A bar?
A bar like Capricciosa?
And then, NADAL arrives at the Italian bar in Nakameguro, Rink.
It's a very fashionable place.
Yes, it is.
Let's try the recommended Tarako pasta.
This is the back side menu for the regular Nadal.
This is really delicious.
Really?
I'm sure.
You're a special person, Nadal.
The way you eat is like a tea.
It's so hard to cut it
The shape is so hard
It's better to cut it like this
If you were to describe this, it would be like a crepe
First of all, the texture is completely different
It's chewy
This is raw pasta right?
It's not raw
It's different
Why is it like this?
Of course, the interview continues here.
I think that the comedians are also respected.
Do you think Nadal is winning here?
I think he is winning in terms of the humor that comes down.
He is not winning in terms of sense and self-expression.
That's cool as a comedian, but when it comes down to the humor,
Sometimes, something terrible happens.
What about you, Mr. Hamada?
I think everything Mr. Hamada says is funny.
That's why I'm not good at it.
I'm not good at it.
I can get both answers.
I think there are few people who can simply laugh at me.
You're making fun of me.
I'm sorry.
I saw Hama-chan.
Hama-chan was shopping.
I bought it.
Naderu appeared in the shopping video of Hama-chan.
He bought a certain product in the program with his own money.
What is it?
What did you buy?
This is an iron. It's very good quality.
You're using it now too.
What? You're using it?
Iron.
It's very good quality.
Do you use it often?
Yes, I do.
I got it from Hamada.
It's called iron.
Naderu ordered carbonara
What is this? Look at the camera
That's dirty
I don't like this
You're losing
He was very serious
What is this?
You're losing
You're making a difference
Like a beast, he swallows up the pasta.
I'll finish the food.
It's huge.
It's not as deep as in Shibuya.
The pasta is really good.
I'll finish it at the end.
The place was moved to the theater in Shibuya and we heard the story of the situation two years ago.
How did you feel when you actually came to Tokyo?
I think it was good to come. I didn't have any job at all.
I came to Tokyo and did a lot of work. I think I gained a lot of experience.
Among all the jobs you've done, which one was the most enjoyable?
There might not be any shows I enjoyed.
Why is that?
Because they're all battles.
And the comedian who is active in private, was chosen by the audition and formed the Nadaru army.
Yes.
He listens to what I say a lot, he is kind.
He is kind.
The NADAL army was chosen based on kindness.
Actually, there was a member who was in the first group.
Originally, it was Yurian and Assei who were in the NADAL army.
I didn't listen to them much, so I just took the initiative.
You got so popular?
You got so popular that you didn't have time.
It was 11.45 pm.
After returning to the hotel, he continues his interview.
13 hours have passed. How do you feel about looking back at this time?
I want to do my best.
Yes, the battle is still at the turning point.
He is trying to regain his energy and answers the interview.
By the way, what is the NG item?
I think it's about family.
And...
I don't want to be a laughing stock.
You've heard of the Japanese word for a Japanese person, right?
What do you remember it as?
I think it's something like, I said something good.
Like, you're a good person?
Yes.
I think it's something like that.
I think it's something about my ability.
Something interesting.
Is that impression good?
I want to talk but I really don't have anything.
I only have this much.
I've only been in the toilet and talked to Nicoyaka.
Even so, the interview doesn't end.
For Nanaru-san,
You're getting excited.
It's not something that you can't do without, but it would be nice if it existed.
If it existed.
It's annoying.
Amazing!
That's cool!
At 1 am, he moves to a hotel bar and approaches Nadal's love.
Love, huh?
How do you drink it?
I'll just drink it as I like.
What are you drinking?
How can you be cheating?
You can't say something cool.
If I become a city...
If your heart moves a little...
Is your girlfriend here now?
She is.
How did you meet her?
We were just talking.
While looking at the cherry blossoms on Meguro River...
I have something to say to you.
I like you a little.
I would be happy if we could date.
If we could go to the same place again...
Don't drink it here.
I would be happy.
You're a bit of a
It's a bit too much.
Madaru is happy with his love story.
You drank a lot.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You look different.
Are you okay?
He drinks up the cocktail at once.
The next day, he's drinking a cocktail like a tea.
He's drinking like a tea.
You've been drinking cocktails like tea.
I'm not drinking.
It's scary!
Why do you say that?
What's wrong?
That's how humans are.
This is scary.
What's wrong?
What?
Hey, come back!
It's 2 o'clock in the evening.
It's still 2 o'clock!
After enjoying the bar, he had an interview in his room.
15 hours have passed since you started.
Yeah, really.
How do you feel?
I was a little drunk, but I was able to drink.
Thank you.
Is there an ideal way to leave the group?
If I don't accept it, I want to quit.
I don't want to do it while being told that I don't like the jokes.
It's the ideal way to go.
Please tell me about the ideal way to go.
If I don't accept it at all.
It's the ideal way.
This is the ideal way to go.
The ideal way to go.
Is it because of the alcohol?
The interviewer's question and Nadal's answer are not the same.
And...
What do you want to do after retirement?
This is bad.
Nadal-san?
I want to make you a real man in 24 hours.
Can you answer me more seriously?
It's SFX.
Nadaru-san.
Hey.
I thought I was going to die.
Nadaru-san.
Nadal-san.
What do you want to do after retirement?
Nadal-san?
Scary, scary, scary.
You're a devil, you're a devil.
You're a devil.
What?
Did you get it?
Now?
16 hours from the start.
A body screaming.
It's so sad.
Mr. Nadal?
Finally, he's attacked.
Mr. Nadal, please keep your eyes open.
His eyes are red.
He's bleeding.
How will Nadal survive?
What is the most memorable moment after the foundation of this company?
I think it's winning the King of the World Cup.
What is the thing you are most grateful for?
When I said I wanted to quit, he stopped me with all his might.
If he hadn't stopped me, I wouldn't have said it.
And in the shower, he witnessed a unique way of washing his hair.
What are you doing? Stop it!
Stop it!
You're the one who should stop it!
When did you get your first prize?
Yesterday, at the first live show.
It was two years ago.
Pikachu, who shoots 100,000 volts.
Pikachu!
It's a gyro-type...
This is a gyro-type?
What is this?
I'm going to win.
Nadal fights against Suima and continues to fight.
Hello.
Thank you for coming.
We have some questions for you, so please answer them.
Questions for Nadal!
Please ask them!
Me?
Your face is so puffy
I'll take it
What do you think is the rank of Yappezo in the gag ranking?
Also, what is the gag that is just above and below?
It's really below Yappezo
I really can't take it
You have a temper, right?
It's about 200 yen. The top is Hi Oppa Pee. The bottom is... What is it?
What is it?
You won for that.
Let's go to the next question.
Everyone will draw anyway.
What do you pay attention to when you drink with a woman?
I definitely check if the underage is a
I'll check the air.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Don't be so nice.
Please tell me about the Inaba's relics.
I don't want to.
Why are you so mean?
Please tell me about the Inaba's relics.
I don't want to.
I told you.
I'm scared.
I said no.
What is this?
The remaining time is 2 hours and a half.
The staff is exhausted.
And of course, Nadal.
That's amazing.
NADARU-SAN
Huh?
Please analyze the reason why Japan is called the Belgium.
Yeah.
NADARU-SAN
Hey, your voice is too loud!
What's that?
You sound like a Japanese.
NADARU-SAN
Huh?
What's going on?
NADARU-SAN
NADAL-san, please analyze the reason why Japan lost to Belgium.
Mr. Nadal?
One more person?
Let's do the last part.
What the hell is this interview?
The goal of the 24 hours of battle is right there
Megwin awakens the body with the AO drink
And the time of fate is coming
24 hours have passed
Thank you
Have you done anything?
Nothing
I don't have any.
NADARU answers 3126 questions in 24 hours.
This is the last question.
What was your life like?
I think I had a lot of ups and downs.
But I think I had a good life.
I want to work harder to have a better life.
You have completed the 20 hours.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
I'm happy.
What kind of reaction do you have?
I'm not happy at all.
I'm really...
I can't do it anymore
Good morning
We have a 24 hour interview
There is a line that is interesting in Nadal's answer
Please
Who is it?
Hello
Thank you
I'm a man who was
I'm calling this person because there is something that interests him about the answer.
Please.
Hello.
Thank you very much.
He is a man who was
Absolutely not allowed to laugh. American police 24 hours.
DVD and Blu-ray will be released on November 28th.
Was there a lie?
There were lies.
I thought there were lies.
But the first thing that shocked me was the story.
I really did everything.
You didn't say that?
You said half and half.
I said half and half.
I've never done a story in the 7 years of Nadaru.
I'm doing half and half for the story.
We talked and did it together.
You said you were half-half.
I did.
What? I didn't say I was half-half.
You did.
I did.
I'll confirm it again. I said I was half-half.
You did.
I thought you were being conscious.
You said it in the beginning.
When I answered it correctly.
And Hamada-san's Hama-chan.
You said you bought an iron, right?
I remember you had an empty box.
Yes, I did.
You bought another item besides the iron.
A washlet.
You bought a washlet that cost about 24,000 yen.
I'm sorry, Hamada-san.
I was really surprised.
You have a toilet outlet, right?
I don't have one at home.
I couldn't use a washlet because you bought it for me.
So I said, let's change the iron.
And it happened.
Change the iron?
I bought the iron and the oshiret, but I don't know what the iron change is.
What happened?
I returned it, and the new iron...
I got it.
You got it?
You changed it to iron?
I changed the oshiret to iron, but I didn't say anything.
E? E? E? E? E?
You are scary
Very scary
Scary
You are Cream
I'm a bit different from Porto.
He's a bad guy.
I don't know if you can see it, but we're both a bit...
Porto is scary.
No, it's a one-night trip.
It's a hot spring.
If you go in the hot spring, you'll get a bubble.
You can do it!
Ah, ah, senpai!