In the 1st episode of Gaki no Tsukai Arahen, Chikichiki Team Project,
Since We Don't Have Money, Let's Go Pee Grand Prix!
Again, that...
That's a small compliment.
Is it because you don't have money?
Well, we do have money, but...
We don't have money.
We don't have enough to pay for it.
Today, a person who has a lot of pee will receive a prize.
That's nice.
How much is this?
How much is it?
100,000 yen.
100,000 yen!
If you pay for your pee, you'll get 100,000 yen.
That's not a lot.
That's not true.
I wouldn't do such a stupid thing.
Well, you can do whatever you want.
It's time to drink to get more pee.
You're still drinking, aren't you?
I don't want to drink. I want to drink again.
I'm telling you to pee, but you're eating chocolate.
I think I can drink a lot.
Can you drink it all at once?
Yes, yes, yes.
Okamoto-chan.
You're still angry, aren't you?
He's even more angry.
What should I do with Mr. Yokuda?
Don't bother me too much.
It's a game where you pee on a water wheel and the water wheel spins.
Let's do it in order.
I think it's better to sit down.
Don't be distracted.
I see.
I can't go from there.
This guy seems to be a winning candidate.
It's not like I can do it if I do my best.
I'll play the sound.
Be more energetic.
Look at me.
What?
It doesn't spin.
It starts to move.
What?
Do it until it stops.
I don't know if this is good or bad.
It's still coming out.
You're coming out a lot.
You're amazing.
It's stopped halfway.
You're weird.
You're coming out a lot.
21.
This is a strong opponent.
I'll do it.
You're good.
It stopped.
There's one more.
You're doing well.
How many seconds is it now?
15 seconds.
10 more seconds.
It's coming out.
You're good.
17 seconds.
Do you want to do it again?
It's coming out a lot.
You're coming out a lot.
You're weird.
Why?
You're coming out a lot.
It's coming out.
That was a waste.
It's coming out a lot.
Is it coming out?
It's zero.
It's not coming out at all.
How many seconds is it?
It's coming!
30 seconds
It's coming
It's 14
It's 15
No way!
Seriously?
It's not working
It's coming
It's not working at all
You just need to prove it
Go to the toilet
That was fun
I...
Wait a minute
It's coming
It's not working at all
What?
It's spinning
It's spinning a little
That's mean
I'll go
Shake it
I don't want to
It's coming
You're good
It stopped
It's coming back
GG
8 seconds
It's coming
21 seconds
It's 100,000 yen
10 seconds
You can get 100,000 yen
It's coming
Is there more?
15 seconds
A little more
It's coming
4 seconds
A little more
It's coming
It's a little early today
What?
The beginning
I don't have any
After this
I'll go to the studio at night
I don't know
I didn't say I wanted to go
It's not like that
I'm talking to you
As the Matsumoto of downtown
He's already in H-Jung
I don't know
I want to go with you
I'm not H-Jung
It's really hard
You're in a hurry
Are you aware of that?
What?
You came here to say let's go slowly
I can't be lazy
You can't be lazy
You can't be in a hurry
I'm not talking about myself
I don't think it's important
to make people wait
I see
No
I'm going to sleep
There's a reason
I'm late
Why are you so desperate?
Can you make it in time?
I don't know
That's what I'm saying
There's a reason
You're late
I came down
I left a plastic bottle
I can't get in
I'm scared
You're like a cat
I went somewhere
I thought it was impossible
I left the building
I came back and it was gone
I see
I'm watching
It's already started
Of course
If you go live
You'll do something for the fans
Why?
I can only sing
I'm not sitting where everyone is
I'm like Hiromi
Stop
Young people
You need to have a star
I don't really know
You show the right leg
You're needy
You're
I'm not needy
I have the right leg
I know the rules
What about the right leg
It's asking for nothing
Right leg
Humans
It seems convenient, but it isn't.
What do you mean by convenient?
Your body.
Yes, yes, yes.
Don't you ever wonder if there's anything you can do about it?
What do you mean?
You've lived your whole life as a human being.
Yes.
It would be nice if you had a pocket on your chest.
But I'm wearing clothes.
Even if you're wearing clothes,
wouldn't it be nice if you had a little coin on your chest?
Why would I have a coin on my chest when I'm naked?
I have it, right?
For example, I can hide it somewhere.
I can take it off when I'm doing this.
The rest is in a bag.
I don't want it.
I think I can have it.
For example, I can put it on my waist.
I can put a key holder on it.
Why would you put a key holder on your chest when you're naked?
I have this on my chest.
I don't have this on my face.
What would you do if you got caught?
It would be really painful.
And also, you know,
you do this with your fingers, right?
You do this at this time.
It would be nice if you had something like this.
It's dangerous when you use it.
What do you usually do with this?
I do this.
I don't know the face of that person.
This is the proper face.
I don't need this.
I don't need it.
So when you take it off, you go like this.
Why do you do it automatically?
I think about it in my head.
It's the same with your hands.
If you want to take it off, you take it off.
If you want to take it off, you go like this.
You go like this.
Everyone says, let's put it on.
So, for example,
from tomorrow, you'll be swimming all the time.
Why?
Well, it doesn't matter.
You'll be swimming all the time.
And you'll have a girlfriend.
She'll be swimming all the time.
I'll be swimming all the time, too.
Why?
Listen to me.
And you'll have sex.
You'll have a child.
And that child will be swimming all the time.
Why?
And you'll meet that kind of family.
Is that me?
And you'll be swimming all the time with your son.
And you'll be swimming all the time with your daughter.
Of course, you'll be swimming all the time.
And when you have children,
you'll be swimming all the time.
Oh, that kind of child.
So,
you'll try to do something
like you have a pocket.
Right?
You'll try to do something like this.
You don't have one.
Oh, I don't have one.
But you'll try to do it from tomorrow or today.
And you'll marry a woman who tries to do it.
Oh, me?
By doing that, you'll definitely have a pocket.
This is a living thing.
No, no.
When I'm swimming, I think,
maybe,
but I don't have one.
I can't do it.
I want two.
Why?
I think it's convenient.
I don't think you need a pocket.
I can't help it even if I do it like this.
Please show me the paper.
It's deep.
Of course, when you have a hard time,
you'll ride on a white horse and run around the grassland.
Well, that's not the case.
You can do it next time.
Why do you know that?
Well, if you think so.
Do you have a horse?
Well,
I don't have one.
I love animals.
For example, I don't have a horse.
So it's not yours?
Of course not.
For example, when I have a hard time,
when I meet a sad thing,
a horse will come to you.
Will it come to you?
Yes, it will.
In fact, animals come to me.
First, when I'm depressed.
When I'm depressed,
birds come to me.
They eat my microorganisms.
You're disgusting.
They eat my
microorganisms.
They eat my microorganisms.
But you didn't say that before.
You said something like,
when I say,
they come to me.
But here is a hall.
Where do they come from?
They are birds, right?
They come to me when I'm sad.
Birds come to me
when I'm angry.
Why are birds coming to you when you're angry?
You're disgusting.
Why do you throw a Zabuton?
I'm excited.
No, that's not the answer.
No?
Why?
Because I can't sit down.
But you got it right.
You and I got it right.
You're annoying.
You can't get it right.
That was good.
You know,
it was good or bad
what you said when you were a geisha.
No.
You're always good and beautiful.
That's not true.
I don't know what you're talking about.
When I'm angry, they come to me.
I don't trust anyone.
I feel bad.
What do you feel bad about?
I'll show you a tattoo.
No.
Why do you show me a tattoo?
Because I feel bad.
What?
You know,
anger is a power.
It's a power.
Yes.
Animals are very sensitive to such things.
When there's a disaster,
animals make a fuss.
Yes.
It's the same thing.
When I'm angry,
the earth...
The earth is weird.
The earth is weird?
It's not the earth, it's the earth.
But wait a minute.
You just said everyone.
Didn't you say that?
I'm not the only one.
When everyone's angry, they come to me.
Really?
You're the only one talking.
You're weird.
You're not always angry.
Your skin is weird.
What?
You're getting old.
Why do sea turtles cry when there's a disaster?
You're crying.
Yes.
It must hurt.
You're crying because it hurts?
You must be moved.
Because I'm giving birth to a child?
You're giving birth.
Even if you give birth to a child,
it's only a few.
Yes.
I'm giving birth to an egg right now,
but it's broken.
I think I understand.
I think so, too.
Then I'll give you an answer.
Why?
Does that mean it's different?
Don't you think you only cry when you're sad?
That's not true.
I cry when I'm moved.
You cry when you're moved.
Let's think about what you cry for.
When you're sad.
Yes.
When you're in pain.
When you're depressed.
Yes.
And when you don't go the way you want to.
And when you're really depressed.
It's all the same.
Are you ready?
Yes.
There are many kinds of tears.
That's right.
And you say that these tears are moved tears.
Tears of sadness.
Both sadness and emotions are in it.
But you're saying it's different, right?
I'm saying it's different.
Is that so?
Yes.
What's the difference?
These tears?
Yes.
Um, this is...
It's better to think about the time.
There's a little bit of a female cylinder.
There's an experimental tool.
Why are you crying?
I'm answering that.
Why is there a female cylinder?
Well, let's not talk about that.
What do you think?
I said my opinion.
I said it's different.
I see.
Of course.
So what is it?
What is it?
What are you?
What are you doing?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know.
So I'm asking you to tell me.
I'm not crying because I'm moved.
I'm not crying because I'm sad.
That's right.
Why are you crying?
Yes, yes, yes.
Um, this is, of course,
There are various opinions and theories.
I don't think that's the right thing to do right now.
Is that so?
Yes.
What do you mean?
Well, first of all,
Dad.
You think this turtle is a female, don't you?
I'm asking if you cry when there's a riot.
Actually, this is something I found out recently.
I'm an old man.
You're a man, aren't you?
You can't have children.
Yes.
If you suddenly get pregnant and have a baby,
You're going to cry, aren't you?
I'm going to cry.
I cried.
That's right.
There's something like that.
Oh, it was a man.