This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
I've heard that you've eaten the soil of an imaginary creature.
Yes, yes, yes.
Mr. Matsumoto.
Yes.
Please tell me what kind of creature it is and what kind of taste it has.
Well, I've eaten it.
I've become full.
I've become full just from eating soil.
No, no, no.
First of all, where did you find that soil?
Eh?
Where did you find it?
You're saying strange things.
For example, have you ever eaten Beijing duck?
No, I haven't.
Where did you find that duck?
I went to the store and ate it.
That's right. I also went to the store and ate it.
The store?
Why didn't you find your own food?
It's strange. It's strange.
You didn't put the soil in the store, did you?
There is a store that has it.
Actually, there is.
It's in the back of the store.
I don't know where it is.
Where is it?
In which prefecture?
Ah, it's in Tokyo.
What kind of restaurant is it?
Well, I'll tell you.
Please cut this part.
No, it's fine.
In Ebisu,
there is a shop that sells Nepali food.
Is that so?
It's in the back of the store.
No, it's not there.
Why is the soil in the store Nepali?
Well, it's Nepali food.
There is Japanese food in the back of the store.
I see.
It's in the back of the store.
It's called Hanafusa.
It sounds like a steakhouse.
It's there.
It's Japanese food.
It's not on the menu.
It's in the back of the store.
I see.
The boss asks you to serve it.
If I ask him to serve it, he will.
It's very valuable.
I don't know if he will serve it in the store.
I see.
How do you cook it?
There are many ways.
What kind of food do you eat?
The most authentic way is to use an octopus string.
It's grilled pork.
What kind of food do you eat?
I cut it into slices.
I slice it and put curry on it.
You put curry on it?
It has a strong smell.
I see.
That's the most authentic way.
How much does it cost?
Well, to be honest...
The price is...
I only eat it after my payday.
That's a lot.
It's expensive.
It's a little expensive if it's not a card.
It's not a card.
Other than that, it's not grilled pork.
It's Japanese cuisine.
If you go to a Japanese restaurant and eat grilled pork...
That's the most authentic way to eat it.
If it's Japanese cuisine, do you dip it in vinegar?
That's the most authentic way.
The most authentic way is...
It comes out like that.
It looks like that.
I cut it and there's a lot of rice in it.
It's squid rice.
There's a lot of rice in it.
It's not squid at all.
It's all cooked in the same way.
Grilled pork...
Squid rice...
I was told that.
That's what Gen-san said.
I didn't know that.
Gen-san said that.
I cut it and there's a lot of rice in it.
There's a lot of rice in it.
What about the taste?
The taste is...
You said it smelled.
It smells.
If I had to say the taste...
It's the taste of my mother.
I've never seen it before.
I've never eaten it before.
It's the taste of my mother.
It's close.
I put my head here.
I put my head here with sake and sake.
It's salt.
What do you do with your head?
I put it on the edge of the glass.
Isn't that a decoration?
It's a decoration.
It's like a lemon.
Please tell me the name of the restaurant.
If we can line up, it'll be...
I don't know with the current information.
It's the Japanese food that was in the Nepal restaurant.
I don't know.
It's in a place where we can get it.
You can get caught.
You're a fool.
You're good at competition.
Seriously.
You'll be surprised.
It's a big deal.
It's not a story.
Another one will come out.
Seriously.
Where there was nothing.
I want to be Bim-Bim, but another one will come out.
That's...
That's what women do.
I have a question for Matsumoto-san.
What's on the back of the moon that you can't see from Earth?
To put it simply, I was surprised too.
What's on the back of the moon?
There's a
Why don't you understand?
Please explain it in an easy way.
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
I was surprised too.
Look at this.
What is it?
I was surprised that I made a space shuttle and went to the moon.
You don't need to do that.
You can focus on the back of the moon.
The back of the moon is saying strange things.
It's not strange.
Then let's make this.
I made it with homework.
I was tired of going there.
It's impossible.
Why do you think it's impossible?
It's here.
I made it.
Really?
It took me two weeks.
That's fast.
I was supposed to make it in six days.
It took me 14 days.
That's a lot of work.
What did you do with the material?
Material.
The man next to me was in NASA.
What were you doing in NASA?
He was the man of the cafeteria.
NASA?
The man who lived next to me.
He called me Mr. Toba.
That's all you can do?
No, he called me Mr. Toba.
Really?
Yes.
He lived in NASA, but he called me Mr. Toba.
That's all you can do.
Mr. Toba told me not to say such stupid things.
Mr. Toba.
Material.
You're stupid.
What?
You don't know anything.
You're really useless.
What?
Do you know?
Taxi drivers and club mommies.
They know the most about politics.
They listen to you.
They listen to you the most.
In that sense, Mr. Toba in the cafeteria worked for NASA.
He listened to everything you said about the diode not shining.
That's too detailed.
It doesn't matter if it's a light-emitting diode.
Material.
He listened to everything.
What are you doing next to him?
Soba?
Where are you listening from?
He listened to everything.
He pretended to boil the noodles, but he didn't boil them.
There was a lot of surprising information.
When you're eating, you become a human.
You become defenseless.
Eating and life and eating.
I see.
At this time, he says things he shouldn't say.
He says he'll forgive his heart.
It's a sense of freedom.
He listened to a lot of things there.
I listened to Mr. Toba.
I see.
That's how Space Shuttle works.
I got it.
Everyone can do it.
Space Shuttle is easy to do.
Surprisingly.
The name Space Shuttle has its drawbacks.
That's right.
I think it's difficult.
What should I do?
Please tell me.
If it's easy.
What?
Please clean your nose.
What should I do to make it the easiest?
First of all, the mayonnaise plate.
The star-shaped one.
I like mayonnaise.
I don't know if it's a crow or you.
The star-shaped one should be clean.
All inside?
Yes, all inside.
Please clean it.
Then inflate it all.
Please cap it.
This is almost the main engine.
I can't speak.
I think this is almost the main engine.
But this is the main engine.
What's wrong with that?
It's smaller than me.
That's right.
I can't go to the moon like this.
You're a fool.
Why?
If you think so, you're not qualified to go to the moon.
Really?
I'll tell you the most important thing to do in the moon.
You want to go to the moon.
You want to go.
I know that.
If you don't have that, no matter how many facilities you have, it's impossible.
This is impossible.
No way.
Right?
That's right.
You want to go to Yoshimoto, so you want to go, right?
It's different from that.
What do you mean?
Yoshimoto Space Shuttle is very similar.
It's not similar.
It's almost the same.
I think you can't go to the moon like this.
If I'm in a bad mood, I'll go to the moon.
I'm sorry.
You're a fool.
I think you can't go to the moon like this.
Even if you want to go to the moon, you think this is the main engine.
And you're like this.
The main engine of the Shinkansen is like this.
That's not true.
You're a fool.
You don't know anything.
That's not true.
The main engine of the Shinkansen is like this.
It's like this.
That's the basics.
That's what I'm saying.
The main engine of the Space Shuttle is like this.
That's a mistake.
What kind of accessories do you put on it?
You have to fly.
That's right.
What kind of accessories are you talking about?
There are a lot of accessories.
Tell me about it.
First of all, the refrigerator.
No, no, no.
It's a vegetable room in the refrigerator.
It's transparent.
And a cup of water.
A cup of water.
And a cup of vinegar.
And?
And then, the mayonnaise that you made at the base.
Put it in there.
It's a good space if it's not a vegetable room.
It's a good space.
Put it in there.
And then, the hair dryer.
Well, that's how it works.
His laughter is all about telling stories.
That's not how it works.
It's like he's laughing more.
You know, you know.
A hair dryer is weird.
You can't go there.
It's weird.
What's weird?
In the end, the invention is a hair dryer.
Well, well, well.
The last one.
You're doing the beansprout.
Can you tell me why it's on there?
I'll tell you Edison made it.
If you tell me, I'll...
It's weird, isn't it? It's on and off all the time.
It's on and off all the time.
I see.
It's like a hair dryer.
You can only say it's a hair dryer.
A hair dryer.
Then, please explain the microwave.
What?
It's a microwave.
It's being removed from the inside.
What's going on?
Well, that's true.
In the end, it's a hair dryer.
Electrical products, you know?
If you go to a factory, they don't have much.
That's not true.
It's a huge hair dryer.
It doesn't matter if it's big or small.
If there's no part, you can't make things.
No, no, no.
You're really stupid.
Why?
Go home and break the microwave.
Tear off the back.
Basically, there's nothing in it.
If I had to say, it's an amulet.
If you do this, it's going to be a mess.
I hope you get a head.
But...
But I'm sending it out.
Aoka.
Go away!
I don't know.
I don't know about that.
I'm sorry. I didn't know that.
You're hopeless.
I'm doing it at home.
If I suddenly get sick, I can't do it here.
No, no, no.
You can't do anything like that.
Call Miko.
And ask Miko to do it for you.
But he's doing it for Toshiba.
He's doing it for Toshiba.
So who's going to win?
What are you doing?
I'm going to repair it. I'm going to take it to Toshiba.
Even at the repair factory, he's doing it.
I can't help it if it doesn't get fixed.
But I can't help it if it doesn't get fixed.
I can't help it.
I'm going to pray for it.
There are people in India who have been doing this for decades.
I heard about it recently.
I heard that you've been doing this for five years.
How did you spend five years?
How should I put it?
It's either S or M.
I don't know.
I'm surprised.
When I see people in pain or suffering, I laugh like this.
I'm sure it's going to take a while.
I did it with Yamazaki and Moriman.
I'm the one who's the most upset that Yamazaki is being beaten up.
So you've been doing this for five years, you made it right?
Where did the M story come from?
There are times when you этого, people rememberja Kill the mind.
So they try harder when they think.
It's like you're trying to get over it, even though it's about to turn red.
That kind of excitement.
A sense of outlaw.
That kind of thing exists.
It's not painful, is it?
It is painful.
It's painful, but...
It's painful, but I like it.
It makes you feel good?
Yes.
In that sense, I can understand that I've been living with one hand up for five years.
But I don't want to do the same thing as others.
That's right.
I've done a lot of training.
What have you done?
What do you mean?
For five years...
For five years, what have you done?
Ah, for five years...
For five years, I've been surprised.
I've been doing this for five years.
I couldn't do anything about it.
Even if the police stopped me and gave me a license...
No, you could have done that.
You could have done what you're doing right now.
No, but if they took me away, even if they said something like,
You're suspicious!
No, you could have done that.
Even if they said, You're that murderer from back then!
For these five years, it was really painful.
That's...
It's hard to live like that.
It was painful.
To be surprised for five years.
There's nothing to be surprised about.
There isn't, right?
There wasn't.
During sex, I was surprised.
That's because there's no one who's more open-minded than you.
That's right.
You're looking from below and dancing like this.
What?
Am I different from other people?
My panties are all wet.
No, no, don't point your finger at me.
If you point your finger at me, the meaning changes.
When you announce things like winning,
You always use drumroll.
Ah, that's right.
Drumroll.
Winning.
To be honest, I'm sick of it.
It's not like I'm sick of it or anything.
Mr. Matsumoto, when you announce something other than drumroll,
What do you think of when you announce it?
Well, if you say you're sick of it,
You have to think about it.
But everyone's used to hearing it.
They say, drumroll, so it's exciting.
Well, that's true, but
Is it okay because you're used to it?
That's what I mean.
Then the adventure spirit disappears.
I want to find something new.
Well, well, well.
Right? Let's do that.
But there are a lot of people who fail.
Don't say it's new.
There are a lot.
There are people who say it was better before.
That's fine. Then let's think about drumroll.
Let's think about something new.
Let's think about something that's not drumroll.
Like what?
Let's think about it for 10 minutes.
I'm sure they'll laugh at me.
The winner is...
Until now, it's been...
What about the piano?
What's a piano?
The sound is a little different.
Hatsugaya?
That's...
It's like editing.
The winner is...
What is it?
Number 16!
Well, Mr. Matsumoto, that's fine.
That's fine.
Then I'll do it.
The winner is...
I told you to think about it for 10 minutes.
It's not solid at all.
It's a mistake.
Don't force yourself to do it.
I was wondering if I could do it.
I was overconfident.
I'm attacking you right now.
You know...
Why can't I play drumroll?
I see.
I want to say it.