Today we have a new character, Ryo Koi!
Today is the 500th episode of Gaki no Chikai.
It's a special occasion.
A special occasion?
We have a new character.
Really?
Are you sure?
Is this the same as the previous episode?
Yes, it is.
You appear as a demon.
That's right.
Last year I was in Dancing Baby.
I was in the break.
I was in the 5th episode of Yamazaki.
This time...
Child Playro!
Ready...
Chucky!
Don't make a fuss.
The rule is to use all the floors.
Chucky will catch everyone.
What will happen?
Help me!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
If you don't know Chucky...
It's dangerous.
It's okay.
This is for those who don't know Chucky.
Why?
Please take a look.
Child Playro was a big hit all over the world as a horror film.
The shocking story of a doll that was given to him on his birthday suddenly attacking people...
...caused terror throughout the world.
And this doll is Chucky, the soul of the killer.
It's scary if you chase a doll like that.
Let's play the doll.
It's scary.
I don't know what will happen.
Yamazaki.
Yes.
No.
It's a doll.
If you don't chase it...
Please stop in the middle.
Is it from now on?
It's getting scarier from now on.
Sorry.
I'll do it again.
I'm sorry.
It's not getting scarier.
It's getting scarier from now on.
That's right.
Okay.
I'm Chucky.
Kill you.
Yes.
What?
What is it?
He took it back.
He must be tired.
Yamazaki.
It's different.
If you don't chase it properly, it won't be a doll.
Please stop in the middle.
What?
You can't stop in the middle.
It's from now on.
Really?
Chucky is a bad person.
It's scary, right?
Yes.
If you're really scared,
say something like,
help me!
and run away.
My reaction may have been weak.
Dan-san,
I may think it's cool
to play a character
who stands in the way.
It's not like that.
I don't think it's like that.
If you're scared, run away.
But I don't want to run away in this project.
Sorry.
Really.
Let's do it again.
Sorry.
Okay.
Only this is good.
Help me!
I'm going crazy.
What?
What are you doing?
Help me!
Wait! I'll catch you!
It's scary. Help me!
Help me!
It's dangerous.
Help you!
Help me!
What's wrong with this?
You wrote it again.
I'll kill you!
It's dangerous.
Why?
Kill me!
I can't catch you, please!
I can't!
Yamazaki, don't break it.
This is good.
Sorry.
Yamazaki.
How is it?
I'm not scared at all.
I'm not scared.
I'm not scared!
I'm not scared at all!
You too!
I'm sorry.
If you're really scared, what would you do?
I'd scream and run.
You bastard!
Ask the staff to help you!
That might be true.
I've been scared for four years.
I'm sorry.
Shall we take a break?
Can we?
While I'm taking a break, I have something to tell you.
What is it?
It's about the future.
The future?
The story from the first episode of the 500th episode.
You can't decide on the 500th episode!
I'm scared.
How is it?
The other day, everyone was tired because of the ski location.
I felt bad, but Yamazaki said,
It's okay.
That's what happened, right?
I made a good decision.
But I think there's something you can imagine.
I think that's why you're so strong.
I'm strong.
I'm doing it properly.
He was like that.
Let's watch it again.
Let's do it.
There must be something.
It's like a house.
Let's watch it again.
It's starting.
No way!
I'm Jackie!
I'm scared.
Help me!
Jackie!
It's coming!
I'm scared.
I'm going to cut the sub-time!
Help me!
It's like middle school English.
It's dangerous!
I'm scared.
It's coming!
What?
I don't know.
I don't know if it's going to come suddenly.
But it has a cute face.
It's back to normal.
It's true.
It's a doll.
It's so cold!
It was a little cold just now.
This way.
This way?
Not yet.
I'm watching it all the time.
I think it's over.
Is it over?
It's okay.
It's okay, isn't it?
It's over!
What are you looking at?
You can't save it.
Yes.
I think no one will be caught.
I don't want to do this, but...
It's not like I'm caught.
I can't finish it.
Can I ask you one more time?
Yes.
Will you be caught?
Or will you only talk?
Then...
The one who is caught...
You want to get 30% of it, don't you?
I want to get it.
I don't want to talk.
It's okay.
What should I do?
Kill you!
Hurry up!
It's coming!
It hurts!
Kill you!
It's coming!
What?
It's over.
It's over?
Hold on.
Dan-dan...
I'm going to talk for a long time today.
What did you eat last time?
This morning.
Senpai-chan, baby-chan...
You're so cute!
You are so cute.
Why are you?
Peek-a-boo, baby.
Fuwa hawa
It's hard to come out
What's the matter?
Thank you very much for coming to Kamui today
Go home
Yes
Thank you very much
I don't feel good
Well, it's okay to have such a day
You can laugh
So really go home
I came out and was told to go home in a few seconds
It's kind of a legend
How is it? Is it bad?
It's not good
Well, that's it
Is there really something?
What is it?
Wada Akiko almost died
I almost died
The conversation on the newspaper was interesting
Why was it on the newspaper?
The person who reported the accident or found it
I thought it was an old man
And you didn't wear a skirt
I didn't
I saw a girl with a manly personality
I thought it was a girl Wada Akiko
That's a strange story
I told you
A girl Wada Akiko is Wada Akiko
It must have hurt
No matter how many times
I think the poison came out of her teeth
What are you talking about?
Where does the poison come from?
It must have been really amazing
Thank you
I had an interesting dream the other day
A dream?
When I woke up, I laughed
Don't laugh like that
It was a very interesting dream
I want you to do a dream fortune teller
I'm walking around the shopping mall alone
I decided to go to the ramen shop
I decided to go to the ramen shop in front of the shopping mall
Alone?
Alone
For some reason, I was running out of breath
I took off all my clothes
I ran to the ramen shop
When I ran, the ramen shop was in a long line
There were so many people lined up
I thought I'd stop eating
I ran in front of the line
If I was naked, I wouldn't eat ramen
It's weird to be naked
I thought I'd put on my underwear
I went into the alley of the shopping mall
I was going to put on my underwear
It was a white brief
It was wet
Was it wet?
I thought it was okay
I put on my underwear
The brief was so small
I couldn't put my fingers on it
I panicked
Why did you put on your underwear?
It was weird
It was wet
I thought I had to put on my underwear
A kid came out and said
I'm wearing my underwear right now, what are you looking at?
I woke up
I woke up in a great place
What was it?
A dream fortune teller
That's right
I want you to do it
There are times when I want to eat something
There may be
The dream I saw a long time ago was interesting
A dream where you can go to the pool and take a picture
You can take a picture
I tried to put on my underwear
But it fell off again
If you look at this side
It's a punishment
I don't know why it's a punishment
I don't know
It's like putting on glue
It's here
It's a punishment
I'll get it once
But if I take a shower again
It will fall off
It's funny
Thank you
That's right
Please stand up
Are you okay?
Why is there a round ring on the cow's nose?
Please tell me
What do you think?
But that's
You take it with you
You pull it
That's why you put it on
That's not true
I saw a scene of a cow giving birth in a farm
Will it come out with a ring?
I don't think so
I put it on when I'm breastfeeding
I don't care if you put it on
Why is it coming out with a ring?
I've been wearing it for a long time
I'm sorry
I'm going to continue this story
I got it
That's right
Why do you think it's a ring?
It's a round ring
You can only see half
But that's all
You can't see it
You can see it
That's not true
It's not like this
It's like this
I don't know if it's stuck
But if you just put it in
You pull it
That's scary
That's not true
Why?
It's like a hairpin
If you put it in, it will come out
You have to bend it
I've never seen a cow like that
That's the black part
What?
If it comes out white, you have to put it in again
If it comes out black, it's black
Why do you have to put it in for so long?
That's not true
That's not what I'm saying
It's a ring
I wanted to say that it might be
You can't see what you see
But if you go near the cow
You can't see it
I'll ask you
How far are you going to go near the cow?
You can't see it
It's not close to the cow
But you can see the nose
You can't do that
How far have you gone near the cow?
I've gone really far
Imagine that I'm really close to the cow
I'm closer than that
It's usually around here
How far have you gone?
I've gone really far
Really?
You've gone really far
You've seen it here
It's a ring
I don't like you that much
That's why I'm telling you
You've been with me for a long time
I've been with you for a long time
But that's different
Everyone knows that
Everyone knows it's a ring
It's a ring
When I saw it up close it was a ring
But it's a ring
Don't say it's a ring
I'm really angry that it's a ring
Today I'm going to do it all
What are you going to do?
I'm going to take off my underwear
I'm going to take off everyone's underwear
I've decided
I'm going to put it in the mouth of the person next to me
What's so fun about just floating in the sea all day?
I know
I really know
You know how it feels?
I know
For example, last week you skied
Yes
Was it fun?
For someone who can't skid, it's not that fun
It's not
It's the same for everyone
But for a sport you've never done before
What's so fun about it?
I think so too
If you do it a few times
If you do it once a day
You'll gradually understand that it's fun
When it comes to wakame
When you really become wakame
You'll understand how fun it is
I'm going to get the right clothes for that
For that
No, no, no
What kind of clothes are you going to get for that?
I'm going to get clothes that are easier to do in the sea
It's hard to get
If you don't try it
You'll understand that
Right?
If you look at it from the outside
You'll think it's not fun
That's why next week
You're going to be wakame for the opening
Why?
I'm going to put my foot in between Iwa and Iwa
No, no, no
In about two and a half months
It's going to get more and more fun
That's not fun
No
I don't want to be wakame
I don't want to understand the feeling of wakame
I'm talking about skewers and jet skis
It's a sport that's as fun as wakame
It's really fun
I'm sorry
Earlier
I understand
I'm having a lot of fun going down Yudofu
I don't understand what you're saying
Going down Yudofu
We've been talking about going down Yudofu
It's fun going down Yudofu from a place where there's nothing
Matsumoto-san
I heard that you can sing with the most interesting expression in the world
Please show us
It's okay
It's a laugh
Really?
I'll laugh because I'm bad at it
Please
For example, you try it
It's terrible
It's a joke
You can't earn money with that
I'm sorry
I've been to Europe or something
Sensei, I'll leave it to you
Really?
For the people who come here
Wait a minute, why are you crying?
Why are you crying?
I just didn't like this feeling
Please
I'll really do it
Wait a minute
When you sing with an interesting expression, you have to move like that
It's okay if you don't have it
But I want to rely on you
Really?
It's okay, I don't need this
Like a firefly
Huh?
You know
It's okay if you can't laugh like that
Wait a minute
It's fast
Don't look at me
I'm not a guest
I can see your eyes
Can I come out?
You can come out, but it depends on how you move your body
That's right, I've been doing this for 18 years
Huh?
I'm just looking at you
I'm looking at you with white eyes, so I don't even know that you're coming