It doesn't have anything to do with the show at all, but the age of the audience is really increasing.
The older you get, the older you get.
If you go on like this, you'll end up looking like Mino Monta.
Today is the last opening of the year.
Yes, yes.
Which do you like more, to forget the year of 1993?
Yes.
Let's go with this one.
It's not our will, it's not our will.
That's right, it's really not our will.
I can't put it on.
Why?
Okay!
Let's go.
Let's start with the one you like.
Okay.
I don't know.
If this old lady approaches you, let's do it.
She's a very attractive owner.
If she approaches me?
If she approaches you.
Let's do it.
There's no way I'm going to do it, it's disgusting.
Your turn.
Me?
Yes.
Ta-da!
Ramos.
Ah!
You hate Ramos?
I've been on TV too much.
I hate him.
He's a sports player.
You guys are the most popular right now.
I've been playing soccer all my life.
Liar!
What are you talking about?
Your face?
I'm dancing.
Oh, your favorite dance.
Oh!
That's amazing.
Next!
Kagamari-ko.
I like this guy.
Oh, really?
He's kind of cute.
I happened to see him on TV.
He's kind of a pervert.
He's a pervert.
He's a very strong person.
He's very strong.
He came to the club before.
Me?
I hate him.
Oh, really?
You too, right?
You can't say that.
I like this guy.
He's a half-transparent guy.
I like him.
But I hate him.
Why?
I like him.
I hate him.
And you're wearing pants.
It was a life-or-death situation.
So I was so skinny.
I was always shaking.
I thought I had to do something about it.
So I put on a sweater.
But still, I was shaking.
I took off my pants.
I opened the door.
When I opened the door, he came out on his own.
I don't know why, but he was wearing a sweater and pants.
And then!
He went somewhere else.
In the end, he got pulled over by a car.
The man who pulled him was surprised.
The old man who pulled him.
That's...
That's pitiful.
Next.
Super kick bass.
I see.
It's not funny at all.
I'm going to make it into a show.
I hate it.
I think I ran a little too much.
I don't deny this.
It's okay for people who like to do it on Sunday to do it.
Let's do kick bass.
I don't know if it's funny to film it on TV and play it all over the country.
I'm saying, Ken-chan, get you!
Nice athlete catch!
It's not funny at all.
I don't deny it.
Do you have a fan of this guy?
No, I like it!
I like it!
It's cute.
Next.
I like it.
I hate it.
Look at this face!
It's ugly!
I think it's pretty funny.
She's so fat, fat and ugly, what should I do?
There's no escape for this woman.
But she's sexy.
Why?
She's just showing off her legs.
I don't like you, Matsumoto-san.
You don't like me?
I don't like you.
What is this?
There's a lot of this in your wallet.
Is this your first year's total bill?
I didn't want to say this at the end.
It can't be helped.
There's a lot of this.
That's right.
There's dozens of this.
There's a lot.
That's right.
And when she takes a bath, she runs away through the hole.
Because she'll die.
This has been enlarged.
It's smaller.
It hasn't been enlarged.
What?
This...
One, one...
It's like this.
There's a lot of this in your wallet.
And when she takes a bath, she runs away through the hole.
You're stupid.
I don't think I've ever been in a sex scene.
I think I was in the shower room of CX.
I always take a shower when I'm on TV.
There's a mat there.
I think I was there.
You shouldn't use the mat like that.
Why?
The mat...
When you put on your underwear, you do this.
You put your underwear on the mat.
That's right.
The mat in the bathroom?
I put my mat on the bottom of the heater.
You're stupid.
You shouldn't do that.
No, the mat, the mat, the mat.
There's a scratch.
If you do this, your underwear will stick to the bottom.
And when you go up,
The scratch on the mat, when the underwear comes down,
You put your hand on it.
Which one will win this year?
Will you take it?
You're stupid.
What's wrong with you?
Whether you cry or laugh, it's over.
Ladies and gentlemen.
You know, I heard it today.
There was a high school student who was waiting in front of the apartment.
He was told to be careful.
He was standing in front of my apartment.
He asked a reporter,
Are you waiting for Mr. Matsumoto?
What kind of relationship do you have?
I'm coming again.
A new one.
That's right.
Stop it.
The reaction of the apartment is cowardly.
Think about it.
When you become a bad guy,
You rent a room in front of the house you live in and wait, right?
But you're aiming for a big deal, aren't you?
That's right.
But if you're in front of the apartment,
If you're like this from the window,
Everyone will get a little scandal.
No matter what kind of beautiful actress you are,
Open the window and you'll get a nosebleed.
There are times when you get a nosebleed.
That's right.
Even if you get a nosebleed,
Mr. Wada, you have to go to the window.
If you get a nosebleed,
I can't do it.
Don't eat it.
No matter what kind of actress you are,
If you do that, the next day in the newspaper,
You'll get a nosebleed.
Why is it over?
It's hard.
When I was Nan-chan,
I stayed in the same place every day.
All the time.
That's strange.
On the third day,
Why is that car here again?
When I was saying that,
We came back together.
Why are you two going back there?
He's an idiot.
That's right.
It would be nice if we could split up like this.
What are you calculating?
What are you doing?
There's no sand.
The sand is down there.
It's too late.
What should I do?
Don't make me feel bad.
I didn't do anything bad.
I just put it somewhere.
If you do that,
You'll be put in a strange place.
What's a strange place?
In a place like this?
What?
What are you doing?
What makes you feel so good?
If you were a violinist,
You'd be used to it.
You shouldn't do that.
You shouldn't have sex.
I'm not saying that.
But it's the same as what you're saying.
You can say anything to anyone,
But not to me.
Don't say that.
You shouldn't.
If I take a woman,
There's nothing left.
You have golf, right?
That has nothing to do with it.
I only have sex.
Seriously.
That's my hobby.
That's what you're saying.
That's right.
If you take that,
I'll...
Why are you crying?
I don't know.
Why do you only take pictures of women?
Matcha! Fishing again!
You can't do that.
It's the same thing.
Women are also a hobby.
I just went to the dorm to get my driver's license.
And you took a picture of me.
It says, again and again.
It's the same thing.
No, no, no.
That's definitely not you.
That's the same thing.
That might be the same thing.
But at night, you're the same thing.
No, no, no.
That's definitely not you.
No, no, really.
That's why...
You can rent a fake apartment.
No matter what you do, you're going to use it anyway, right?
What do you mean?
You're going to use it anyway, right?
Oh, you're so cute.
Even if you rent a fake apartment, you're going to use it, right?
You're going to use it, right?
Shut up!
Stop it!
What are you doing?
What are you doing.
Stop it!
What are you doing?
You're going to use it, right?
You're going to use it, so if you're going to use it, you should rent that fake apartment.
It's the same thing.
It'll always be found.
Why?
I don't know if you have a house or anything.
When you leave the set, I don't know if you're following me from behind.
When you're at work.
What should I do?
Do whatever you want.
If you were caught once as much as you want, I'd be laughing with your girl.
But if that's the case, I don't think I'll be able to get over it.
Or you two can do this...
I can do this...
And the woman can do this...
I wonder if she'll do it for me.
Recently, the prank calls have changed.
Well, it's better now.
But in the past, it was really terrible.
The phone was ringing all the time.
I would call that phone a prank call.
That's true.
That's definitely true.
A prank call.
I would say, take the prank call.
No matter how many times I call, I don't know why.
It's definitely from NTT.
Even if I say, what's wrong with you?
I would say, I'm from NTT.
I don't know why.
That's true.
But it's an organization, so I don't know what to say.
But even if I say, hey, I'm from NTT.
It would be a problem for her.
What do you mean?
I didn't tell anyone this time.
I only had my phone.
I didn't have to tell anyone.
I didn't tell anyone about my phone number.
Only my manager, Okamoto, knew.
Then why did you call me?
Okamoto doesn't know either.
Bring me the phone.
Why?
Today, Mr. Matsumoto.
You're not wearing a hanagi today.
Put it down.
Who will win the white-white?
Let's see the result.
Let's play a punishment game.
I wrote the winning and losing history of the last 10 years.
Last year, I won the white.
You won the white.
I got it.
This time, I'll use the board.
This is the white group.
The first appearance.
This is a boom.
Takayama Gen-san, I'll freeze your heart.
Who is it?
This person is the leading singer.
What kind of song is it?
Let my heart freeze.
I don't know if it's true or not.
You're such a fool.
Just in case.
Fukuyama.
Fukuyama Masahara.
Checkers last year.
Red.
I'm not saying anything.
Look, it's a bull.
That's true.
I don't have 5 points.
I don't have red points either.
I don't have winter vacation.
I don't want it.
The rest is...
S.M.A.P.
S.M.A.P.?
You don't know?
I don't know.
Really?
What is this 10 dollars?
It's the sales of these kids.
Well, that's right.
Oh, there's a troupe.
Oh, there's a troupe?
Shall we go to the next word?
This is the only one left.
You fool!
Don't joke around with jokes!
It's the 31st day of Kohaku!
J!
O!
I don't even know if it's here or here.
You don't know?
It doesn't matter.
I don't even know if it's here or here.
This time, Kobayashi-san is thinking about something else.
This person is smart.
He's a strategist.
There's something like that, so I can't get rid of it.
I can't get rid of it.
Will it be K?
It will be K.
Won't it be Cho Yonpil?
Cho Yonpil...
Cho-san?
No, it won't be me.
Gao!
What's with his face?
If Gao asks me to go out with him, it'll be hard.
It'll be hard, right?
There's also a drama called Dolly's Come True.
Dolly's?
What's Dolly's?
Dolly's...
Can't you read it?
Yugi Saori-san and his sister...
Wow!
In Moon Desert...
Yasuda Shouko-san.
Why Moon Desert?
Originally, Yugi Saori-san is a poet.
That's right, but Moon Desert...
Who is this?
Nakamura Mitsuko.
Shimada no Bunbun.
Shimada no Bunbun?
What is this?
Do you really know her?
I don't know her.
She'll probably be stopped when she enters the dressing room.
Excuse me.
She'll be asked, who is this?
Nakamura Mitsuko.
So, who is this?
It'll be hard.
She'll be 30 minutes late.
She'll be late for the entrance.
This man will be angry.
Are you underestimating me?
What are you doing?
He'll come out.
In Moon Desert...
Yasuda Shouko-san.
He'll be scolded again.
Please go out with me.
Who is this?
Is this year white or red?
I'm white.
If you're going to be so white...
I don't think white is that strong.
Is that so?
That's right.
Then, I'm red.
You're really not red.
If you were told to give it to me...
Even if you told me to give it to you...
I don't know if I'd really give it to you.
But I'm pretty confident that I'm red.
But if you told me to give it to you...
I probably wouldn't give it to you.
But I don't feel like giving it to you.
If you say that...
What would you do?
Would you give it to me?
I don't care.
Rock-paper-scissors.
This guy is dirty.
You really don't have confidence.
Tengu rock-paper-scissors.
I told you I don't have confidence.
Let's go.
Even if you cry or laugh...
I don't care.
Rock-paper-scissors.
It hurts.
I really wanted to punch you.
I'm going to kill you.
Hurry up and save.
Let's go.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Good job!
I'm so happy!
Red!
Go f**k yourself!!