What was the first time you went to a bathhouse?
Do you remember?
What do you mean?
I think it was...
I think it was when I was in 12th or 13th grade
That's so old!
Tell us!
You two went to a bathhouse together, right?
Yes, yes
I've been there a few times, so I don't remember
At that time, an old man with a razor came in
At the bathhouse...
There's a place where it flows, right?
There's a well
There's a shower
There was an old man sitting there
He was like, this isn't it!
This isn't it!
And he was cutting potatoes, right?
He wanted to cut potatoes
He was cutting potatoes
We two were in a culture shop
There's a culture shop?
Do they have that kind of thing?
That's right
The water was flowing
This isn't it!
That's what he said
You've been there, right?
Yes, yes, I remember
Since then, time has been separated
Separated?
It's been 25 years, right?
I...
I've done it
So...
I can understand how that old man felt
That old man and I...
We've been together for a long time
What do you mean, this isn't it?
Why do you think this isn't it?
At that time, I didn't understand the meaning
It was like a sci-fi world
That old man
It was like a space fantasy
It wasn't a fantasy
Now, I understand
The other day, I did it
Why did you do it?
How did you feel when you did it?
It was too long
That's not what you ask an old man
Why do you ask an old man?
I didn't say that it was too long
I think that old man...
Your feelings are different
I don't need to talk to that old man
That old man and I
Too long?
What do you mean?
Tell me how long it was
What's long?
It's completely long
That's right
It was like a press release
I don't know what you're talking about.
I think your retina is going crazy.
I never thought it was going to be this long.
I think it's going to be here soon.
I don't know how old you all are, but if you're 40, it's going to be crazy.
Your retina is going crazy.
I don't know how your retina is going to be this long.
I don't know how long it's going to be.
It's amazing.
It's really amazing.
Is it in the way?
It's really in the way.
It's long.
It's in the way.
It's going crazy.
I always read a book before I go to bed.
I put my pillow on my bed and read a book.
I don't know what women think, but I'm doing this.
I'm doing this.
I go to the bathroom and say,
This is what it looks like.
Old man.
I don't think you should call me an old man.
Thank you, old man.
Sorry, old man.
It's okay, old man.
There's something I want to ask you.
What is it?
People who live in mansions.
I've been curious about it for a long time.
There's a poster, right?
Right?
On the dial.
662.
114.
It's usually like that. Left, left, right, right, right, left.
What should I do with that?
What do you mean?
For example, if it's 221.
Where does it start?
If it's 221.
If it's stopped at 2.
That's 2.
I'm just worried.
But it depends on the model.
If there's a model that tells you to put it back to zero.
Then I have to try it once.
So.
It's 2.
It's 2 on the left.
If you stop it, it's no good, right?
If you stop at 5 on the way, it's no good, right?
So, until the next 2.
It's no good, it's no good, it's no good.
No, no, I didn't say it. I didn't say it.
But I didn't hear you say it.
So, 2.
2.
1.
Well, every time you open it, it's okay.
What are you guys doing?
I don't know.
I don't know at all.
So, until now, you've been opening it like that, right?
Until now, I don't really know what happened.
It's like the joints are a little weird.
I managed to get through it somehow.
Then you should do that from now on.
But I can't stand it anymore.
If you say it so strongly, I want to do something about it.
You can explain it properly.
You can do it through the program.
No, no, no.
It's just a picture of a crab.
But I don't want to explain it to you like this.
I don't like it if you don't like it.
It's going to be like this.
No, that tension.
No, no, no, no.
That's the tension of the explanation.
It's because you say it like that.
That's why it's cool.
No, it's going to be like this.
It's going to be like this.
You should say it with a low tone.
Well, that's right.
There are a lot of people who don't understand.
No, that's not true.
I'm sure everyone is listening, so they're just opening it up.
No way.
There's no one else in the neighborhood who's like this, right?
I don't think so.
That's right.
You're the one who's always been caught.
Hey.
No, no, no.
I was tapped.
I don't know what you're talking about.
No, I think there are people who understand.
Is there anyone like that at home?
Look, there are.
There are so many.
Then tell me.
What do you want me to do?
Why?
Don't talk to me.
I don't like it.
Why don't you talk to me?
Don't talk to me.
If you go to the right, it's the next left.
Even if you stop, it's up to that number.
Little by little.
If you go to the right, it's definitely not left.
Right, left, left.
Right, left, right.
No, no, no.
Left, left, right.
You just have to go over that number twice.
I've already told you.
Then let's ask over there.
Wait a minute.
You just have to go over that number twice.
Shut up.
I don't know, so I'll just stay here.
You're from the countryside.
That's good.
Well, the intonation is good.
You didn't open it?
Put your hand in and take it out.
That's good.
That's right.
I don't know.
Hurry up.
I'm curious.
You can take it out with your hand.
I don't know if I can take it out with my hand.
Is that a tongue twister?
Pen name Hanpenkozo.
I have a question for Matsumoto-san, who has been the subject of many masterpieces.
I heard that it was Matsumoto-san who stole the motorcycle from Yutaka Ozaki.
After that, I heard that Matsumoto-san also dealt with it.
What the hell did you do?
Was that your motorcycle?
I was surprised.
I bought a book at a bookstore.
I went to the bookstore with a motorcycle and stopped it.
I was surprised.
I ran away.
You stole it.
I stole it completely.
I chased him saying, what are you doing?
I was going to stop.
I asked him, what are you doing?
He wasn't honest.
I asked him to apologize.
I don't want to apologize.
You are crazy.
What am I?
I don't know.
I don't want to be criticized.
You are noisy.
You were crazy.
You took it back by force.
It was a big hit.
When I heard that song, I was surprised.
It was my motorcycle.
It's a terrible story.
My pen name is Komatsu.
Matsumoto knows all the games in the world.
Tell me your favorite Russian game.
There are many.
How many people can I play with?
Let's play with two people.
OK.
I lost 20 points.
I can't win.
I can't win no matter how many times I play.
Let's play again.
Don't do it.
I'm kidding.
It's easy to understand.
Rock-paper-scissors.
I don't say rock-paper-scissors.
I say it in Russian.
You don't understand.
Say it in Russian.
I don't care.
Rock-paper-scissors.
You win.
I lost.
I lose.
I see.
I'm going to run away.
Please follow me.
If you touch me, you lose.
Which is better?
Rock-paper-scissors.
I don't explain the rules.
I think it's better to do it.
I'll chase you.
Why are you chasing me?
Because you won.
Who are you chasing?
Borscht.
Borscht is because I lost.
Do you understand?
If you touch me, who are you?
Borscht.
Borscht is Borscht.
If you touch me, I'm Borscht.
I'm not Borscht anymore.
No.
I'm Borscht's Borscht.
I don't understand.
I don't understand Borscht and Borscht.
I can't play this game.
Why don't you try it?
Hiroshiki...
What are you doing?
Borscht touched by Hiroshiki can't move for a while.
Then what should I do?
If I play with a group of people, I can't find the next one.
It can't be helped.
It's not a game for two people.
That's right.
If you don't do it, you won't be able to stand up.
It can't be helped.
There are only two of us.
Let's go.
There's no place to run.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Can't you do it anymore?
Wake up.
What kind of game is this?
I have a question for Matsumoto-san, the honorary chairman of the Japanese Greeting Association.
Yes.
It is said that the most used word among Japanese people is sorry.
That's right.
What is the 14th used word?
These are all ranked.
Is that so?
Yes.
The fact that I'm sorry is the first place.
I think it's a good thing and a sad thing for Japanese people.
I see.
Please tell me the 14th.
Can I just say the 14th?
If you can, please tell me in the meantime.
I'll tell you.
The second place is...
Isn't there an M for this?
The first place is sorry, right?
The second place is...
Isn't there an M for this?
Normally, if there is an excuse, someone can say hello.
I say it unexpectedly.
How are you doing?
The third place is how are you doing?
There is no M for this between sorry and how are you doing.
I don't remember what I said.
Think about it. How many times do you say there is no M for this?
I don't know.
You say it a lot.
I can't do it.
How about the fourth place?
The fourth place is normal.
It's small.
What about the fifth place?
The fifth place?
It depends on the decision.
Really?
The fifth place?
Then you go down and tell me about the tenth place.
The tenth place is how are you doing?
How are you doing?
The Japanese say it.
I say it unexpectedly.
I didn't notice it myself.
It depends on the decision.
The fifth place.
I want to hear about the 14th place.
Then tell me about the 10th place to the 13th place.
The 10th place is how are you doing?
Then tell me about the 11th, 12th, and 13th place.
The 11th place is...
It's like a greeting meeting.
What are you doing?
Tell me!
Tell me something!
There is a slight difference.
Including all of that.
Then the 11th?
The 12th?
The 13th?
You're going back to the starting point.
Of course.
The 13th place is...
It's still moving.
The one before that is...
I don't know about that.
I can't accept this.
It's the 14th place.
Do you want to go to the 14th place?
If you don't ask that...
Then tell me about the 15th place.
The 15th place?
I want to hear about the 14th place.
Then tell me about the 15th place.
The 15th place is...
The 15th place?
Everyone, you might not like this.
I want to talk about pomeranians.
It might be good.
It can't be helped.
It's not like that.
Then the 14th place.
The 14th place?
The 14th place is...
It changed to the one before that.
This is the 29th place.
That's right.
I think I was waiting for this.
It's changing.
I think so.
Let's start again.
No, no.
What's the 1st place?
I'm sorry.
It's this year.
This year?
Yes.
What's the 2nd place?
Isn't there an M for this?
That's right.
What's the 3rd place?
How are you?
What's the 4th place?
It's small.
What's the 5th place?
It depends on the decision.
What's the 10th place?
What's the 11th place?
I didn't say the 12th place.
What's the 13th place?
It's still moving.
That's right.
What should I do?
You can say the 12th place.
The 12th place is...
It's finally...
It's finally moving somewhere.
What are you doing?
Who said that?
You can't say that.
Let's fill in the blanks.
Right?
Yes.
6, 7, 8, 9.
Say it.
6 is...
Cameloon is slow.
7 is?
That's 14.
What?
Cameloon representative is slow.
That's funny.
That's 14?
I think that's the 14th place.
Really?
6, 7, 8.
Say it and remember it.
What's the 7th place?
The 7th place is...
Thin noodles.
I knew it. Thin noodles.
That's the 12th place.
This is the 14th place.
That's right.
Say something nice.
The 7th place is thin noodles.
And the 14th place is...
Thin noodles.
So that's the 14th place?
Yes.
8 and 9 are left.
They're left.
That's gross.
It's not like that at all.
What's the 8th place?
Nishikino.
The 8th place is Nishikino.
Nishikino, it's you.
What's the 9th place?
The 9th place is thin noodles.
That's the end.
That's good, right?
Yes.
Is it over?
It's over. It's all over.
I felt like Nishikino slipped.
It's not bad at all.
It's not good to show your real self here.
Then let's go home.
That's the 79th place.
It's really the D cup?
It's the next one.
This program was provided by the following sponsors.