It's a soccer tournament where you can't play with a child, so you have to play with a child.
I'm 30 years old.
I've prepared a cake for you.
No, I don't want it.
I've already seen it.
First of all,
I'm 32 years old.
It's a celebration of my birthday.
Is that so?
Soccer, ball, various things.
That's good.
I've prepared a cake for you.
Keeper, this is too different.
Why?
This is a big wall.
This is the same.
This is like a condom.
It's easy to break.
Break!
I can't go in like this.
Ouch!
It's easier to break than to break.
Break!
Throw in!
Dance!
You're a keeper, aren't you?
Of course!
Grab it!
Wait!
Go!
It's okay. It's safe.
Get on the ground and roll.
Hand!
I got it.
Okay.
Get on the ground.
Change the ball.
Break!
I can't do this.
I'm scared.
Break!
I can't do this.
I'm scared.
Hand!
Don't aim at me!
Heading!
Grab it!
I got it!
Hand!
Why hand?
Here!
Hand!
I got it.
You got it.
Here!
It just happened.
I got it.
One more time.
Here! Here! Here!
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello. Hello. Hello.
What do you have?
Hmm.
The other day...
Yes?
I went to the toilet at TBS.
To the toilet at TBS?
I was in the toilet.
I was doing this.
I thought I was going to fall.
I looked at the wall.
It said half way.
I thought,
and I just saw a poop.
So I was in the bathroom at TBS,
and it was all over the place.
No matter how much common sense you have, no matter how much you can study, no matter how much you can do sports,
the one who puts poop in the toilet is really...
You shouldn't have been born.
Even if you say that, you're already 30 years old.
I'm 30.
30?
After 30 years, you must have dropped your dad out of the toilet at least once.
No!
I really haven't.
I've never been next to the toilet.
I don't understand why such a phenomenon happens.
The toilet is next to the toilet, right?
That's right.
When I went in a long time ago, there was a toilet in the bathroom.
When I got out of the bathroom, there was someone waiting for me.
This is a yakuza.
When I was about to go in, he said, hey, don't spill the poop!
And then there's the one who spills it, right?
I don't know if I really did it or not, but I didn't want to be born like that.
So when I was waiting for him to come out, he said,
It's spilling.
It's spilling, isn't it?
That's spilling, isn't it?
I want to say that it's not me.
That's spilling.
Right?
It's not me.
I was doing it, and when I did it in front of my clothes, it was spilling.
There is.
Isn't there?
Rather than that, when I was doing it at home and there was no paper,
I went like this, right?
That's right.
I looked at it, and it was on the road I was walking on.
It's on the road.
I was walking like this.
There is.
I don't know anything.
There's something that's been annoying me lately.
What is it?
It's a certain magazine.
It's a guy who's been looking down on me.
Well, it may be reflected, but it's a family picture.
That's right.
That's not it.
What is it?
Kansai comedy...
It doesn't say Kansai.
It says comedy...
It says comedy... super idol.
Right?
It says, a fool who's been making me sick.
Hello, I'm a fool.
That's not it.
That's not cool.
If you do that, you'll be accused of being dumped when you were dating.
I'm saying good things about you.
What are you saying?
You're a fool.
I'm actually saying good things about you.
That's right.
That's not it.
It's full of lies.
I'm asking for a Calpis soda.
It doesn't say matcha.
I've never had a Calpis soda like this.
That's just a coincidence.
That's right.
I'm asking for a Calpis soda.
See?
According to the magazine, I spilled the Calpis soda.
Matcha, wipe it for me.
After wiping it for me...
You're a fool.
That's not it.
You're like a teenager.
I'm not a teenager.
It just says you were a virgin.
That's not it.
You were forced to do it.
I've been thinking about it.
I'm not a virgin.
That's not it.
You were forced to do it.
After that...
After that, it says you were a virgin.
What?
She was crying.
She was forced to do it.
She was a virgin.
It hurts.
She was sad.
She was crying because she was sad.
She was happy to be with me.
I was like, what?
When I thought about it, she gave me 10,000 yen from her wallet and said,
Go home.
That's not it.
She was wandering around the town.
She said, bring her here.
Seriously.
It's not about her friends.
You should have gone down 100 or 200 steps more.
It was true, wasn't it?
Go down.
You could see her armpit.
Wait a minute.
Do you remember what you did when you had hair loss?
I remember that.
Is that so?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait.
Wait a minute.
What is hair loss?
You don't know much about hair loss.
I got it from someone.
I see.
I understand that.
That's right.
I didn't do anything.
Why did you do that?
If I did that, I would have been a victim.
Of course.
I'm a victim too.
But I'm a victim too.
I got it from someone.
You can fix it.
But it takes some time to fix it.
You can't fix it right away.
I see.
You can play with it during that time.
You can fix it during that time.
But,
you can't fix it with sex.
Stop it.
I've never fixed it with sex.
You can't fix it with sex.
I was in the picture.
That's the picture.
Hey.
What's that?
You're the opposite.
I don't know what I should do.
You're not saying anything.
That's also a memory.
When you say something like that,
I don't know what to do.
For example, when it comes to idol songs,
you say,
I'm a victim.
But for me,
I was told that.
Even if I'm confessed to,
I don't feel any pain.
You felt pain yourself?
I'm a member of the group.
I'm also a member of the group.
I don't feel any pain mentally.
I see.
You were in the picture.
I was in the picture.
I don't think so.
That story is all a lie.
What story?
You came into my house,
and talked about the carpet.
That's all a lie.
But maybe the woman who did it with me,
I don't know if it's true or not.
I'm sorry about that.
I have a sense of guilt.
But that story is a lie.
I'm sorry about that.
I don't know if it's all a lie.
I have a cell phone.
I used to ride a white car.
We used to meet in front of Alta.
Why in front of Alta?
That's strange.
You're on TV,
but you're in front of a woman and Alta.
I don't understand that.
I'm sorry about that.
No.
We met in front of Alta,
and we had a date for the first time.
What are you talking about?
In that sense, Alta is a good friend.
It doesn't matter.
It's a good friend.
I don't know about that.
And in the room,
we made a secret between the two of us.
We called each other Tamori.
What are you talking about?
What's the yellow thing coming out of your mouth?
Is it a bad breath?
No, I just said, ha.
I've been telling you this for a long time.
I have a bad breath.
I can't say ha.
Do you have a bad breath?
Why do you say ha?
I say it a lot.
Do you say it to say it?
You don't say ha.
Let's say I'm thirsty.
Are you thirsty?
I came to play in my house.
No.
Are you thirsty?
Do you want to drink Calpis soda?
I'll take it.
I'll come to the refrigerator.
Why?
Why do you come to the refrigerator?
Let's say it's a lie.
Don't lie to me.
Cancan.
Ha.
Why?
Let's say it's a lie.
Let's drink.
I'll drink a lot.
Cheers.
Ha.
Why do you say ha?
I say it a lot.
You say ha because it's easy to say it.
Why do you say ha?
I say it a lot.
You don't say ha.
I say ha.
Why do you say ha?
I went to karaoke.
On a starry night.
Ha.
It doesn't matter.
You say wonchu.
It's my mother's story.
It's wonchu.
What?
You've lived for 30 years and you've been wonchu.
For example, when are you wonchu?
For example, you drive a car.
A woman jumps out of the car.
You say wonchu.
Ha.
You say ha.
You don't say ha.
Something like that?
What do you mean by something like that?
It's because you can't say ha too much in your daily life.
I can't say it too much?
Everyone can't say ha like that, right?
Be honest with me.
When you say ha in your daily life, what do you mean?
You went into your room.
You came back.
Now, where do you say ha?
Up to this point, I've said it five times.
Wait, wait.
When you get off the elevator, you say ha!
Ha!
There's no way that's possible.
Why?
First, when you push the elevator, you say ha!
Ha!
There's no way that's possible.
But that's a matter of how many times you say it.
If you say it more, it will definitely come out.
Something like this yellow thing.
Everyone knows that.
That's right.
Why is the black dog poop that's fallen on the roadside growing hair?
Is it growing hair?
Well, in a sense, it's like this.
Isn't that because it's not completely digested?
What do you mean?
Is it eating hair?
I...
I don't even have my own poop.
You poop, right?
Poop...
If you poop, people usually flush it out, right?
There have been quite a lot of dog poops.
At one point, everyone pooped at home.
They didn't flush it out, they didn't throw it away.
They put it on the veranda or something.
That's one form of poop.
What?
I'm going to listen to it with all my heart.
I see.
So if you leave the dog poop as it is, it gradually becomes a dog.
That's why you start walking towards the end.
It's already growing hair.
What do you mean by that?
Idiot!
The final match.
Team Hamada has 8 points.
Team Atsumoto has 0 points.
Team Hamada wins by 8 to 0.
But it's 0 points.
Let's do a PK match.
What?
Okay.
Let's do it.
Listen to me.
I don't know which one was better.
I don't know either.
Let's do a PK match.
PK match.
Okay.
I'm counting on you.
Yes!
I can't do it at all.
Be careful with your nose.
I'll do it straight ahead.
Yes.
Like you're scratching it.
It's big.
Let's go!