Yo man, what's up?
How are you all doing in the new year of 1996?
Tonight is a special night.
Last year, 47 episodes were aired.
Out of which, 13 episodes have exceeded the 20% viewer rating.
Tonight, we'll be showing you the best selection.
Let's send off the 95th Koshitoitsu Festival.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
First, the first challenge against downtown's Itoi Shigesato, Black Bass Fishing.
The passionate battle between Reihou Fujino and Kawaguchiko has reached 21% viewer rating.
Will the Black Bass Fishing be able to catch it?
This is the opening of the show.
The first challenge against downtown's Itoi Shigesato, Black Bass Fishing.
What is it?
Itoi is fishing here.
That's right.
I'm sorry I'm so early.
You're the one who's early.
Will you be able to catch it here?
I will.
Do you see what I just caught?
Yes, I can see it.
Can I brag about it?
Yes, go ahead.
It's mine.
That's the one you just caught, right?
Just now.
Just now?
Just now, just now.
I purposely dropped it, but it's fresh.
The battle between downtown's Itoi Shigesato and Black Bass Fishing is about to begin.
Two times a week, Itoi goes to Kawaguchiko and gets to the Black Bass point.
It's already over.
I'm going to do it.
I can do it.
It's coming, it's coming.
It's coming.
Don't be impatient.
His face is completely impatient.
His face is nervous.
His face is up.
He's impatient.
Yes.
Wait.
Okay.
Hey.
Put your thumb in here.
It's scary.
It's okay.
It's really scary.
How do you get the hook?
Put it in front of the camera.
This guy is a fool.
What are you going to do if you get caught by me?
Look at his eyes.
Itoi is on the screen.
I saw it as 28 cm.
This is a good size.
Nice, nice.
Mine is better.
This guy is also a fool.
What is it?
You have to take this off, right?
Yes.
I'm happy.
It's coming.
Okay.
It's small.
Why did you put it in both sides?
I forgot to put it in both sides.
It's a gill again.
The gill is bothering me.
I'm sorry.
I gave up.
I'm going to be a gill.
Get the one you just dug.
That's sad.
It's the worst if you say it by hitting.
That's not it.
Did something get caught?
There is a rope over there.
It's a gill.
He is leaning on the string.
It's the most difficult time to catch from here.
He has the power to make a difference.
It's coming.
Wait a minute.
What?
Is the drag off?
Wait a minute.
It's heavy.
I'm holding it.
It's like a mammoth.
Isn't it a mammoth?
Isn't it a hand?
Wait a minute.
What is this?
It's big.
It's really big.
It's definitely a gill.
Don't let it escape.
Raise the rod.
It's big.
What is this?
Show me.
This is big.
This way.
It's hot.
It's big.
It's 46 cm.
It's 47 cm.
It's amazing.
It's the biggest fish I've ever caught.
I caught it in the United States.
Is that so?
We're going quietly.
It's not a bad thing.
This is a good size.
It's coming.
All right.
It's big.
But it's not bigger than the other one.
It's not as big as the other.
It's small.
This is big.
It's big.
You can catch as many as you want!
What is this?
It's wrinkled.
It's big.
It's coming again.
Wait a minute.
This is big.
Can I wind it up?
Wait a minute.
It's wrinkled.
Did I hold it?
I'll wind it up.
It's big.
I did it!
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
It's coming.
It's big.
Don't rush it.
I changed my way of thinking when I was with you two.
Didn't you see it?
No.
It's big to some extent.
I lost my motivation to fish.
Why?
It's big to some extent.
It's big.
It's coming.
What is it?
It's coming closer.
Next, Yamazaki, who is grateful to downtown for his daily help, prepares to fish in Yagatabune.
The highest viewing rate in 1995 was 23.4% in downtown, where he forgets about me and plays with geisha.
Yes.
Please enjoy it today.
Gaki no Tsukai Settai Kikaku.
Playing geisha in Yagatabune.
This is good.
Good, isn't it?
I prepared all the food in Edo.
All the food in Edo?
I prepared all the food in front of Edo.
Thank you very much.
But you don't laugh much, do you?
That's right.
Yes.
Is it funny?
Yamazaki Settai doesn't laugh.
No, it's okay.
Wait a minute.
Look at this.
The baseball is also very beautiful.
I'll take a picture of it.
It's easy to catch.
Yamazaki Settai Kikaku.
Playing geisha in Yagatabune.
We've arrived at the point.
Here?
Yes.
It's just around the corner.
This way.
Why do you hide it?
Don't hide it.
I'm sorry.
That's right.
Let's go.
Have fun today.
It doesn't matter which one.
A girl.
I love you.
Excuse me.
Yamazaki Settai Kikaku.
Playing geisha in Yagatabune.
It's funny.
I'll take a picture of it and let you practice it.
Why are you all bending your back?
Yamazaki Settai Kikaku.
Playing geisha in Yagatabune.
Who is that lady with glasses?
She looks like an educator.
She is an educator.
Really?
Yes.
From now on, I will show you the performance of Mameyakko, who has been a geisha for a long time in Edo.
She has a geisha.
I will show you the performance of Jin no Shachiro.
That's good.
Are you sick?
Ganbare! Ganbare!
Yoi!
What are you doing?
Don't be angry.
Mameyakko is crazy.
Don't be crazy.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
Are you serious?
I'm scared.
What are you doing?
I'm very scared.
I'm scared.
You look like a geisha.
Is this your sister?
Yes, she is my sister.
She is a geisha.
I will show you the real Shachiro.
That's good.
Thank you.
I came here to show you.
I will show you the real Shachiro.
Look at this.
It's so sad.
What are you doing?
Brother!
Nippon Ichi!
It's not a big deal.
What are you looking at?
Oh, he's gone somewhere.
It's not a big deal.
In the first episode of Chikishiki!
Matsumoto's Prank!
Big Operation!
This project marked 21.1%.
After the shooting,
Matsumoto and his team went on a secret mission.
Matsumoto's true identity was exposed.
Thank you for your hard work.
We're back.
We're going on a secret mission.
Let's go.
Don't get caught.
What?
What is it?
That's it.
It's amazing.
I've never seen anything like this before.
This popsicle is so big and delicious
Tender cut ta me
The flavors are so good
This is my first time to eat this aimu
Let's go get some sake.
Let's go, let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Let's go.
What the hell?
I'm going to check on him.
He's training his body in a place like this?
Let's stop.
What?
It's the first time.
It's not like that.
You can see it at the sports club.
I think the sports club was here.
It's free.
Why is he eating bread in a place like this?
It's a parking lot.
He's so talented.
He went in here.
Let's stop.
Let's go.
He went in here.
What's going on?
There's something here.
What?
Is it a private apartment?
What are you talking about?
That's right.
He rented a room here.
I don't know anything about it.
Who is it?
It's a different room.
Is it an old lady?
I don't know.
What's going on?
There's a lot of people here.
He's shaking his shoulders.
What's going on?
All of a sudden?
I can't imagine what's going on.
It's hard.
I'm sure he's going to put a mosaic on his wife's face.
Is that the only way?
That's the only thing we can do.
Two weeks later,
Oomomichi was full of anger and sadness.
Matsumoto was in the back.
What's the shocking event he confessed to?
Thank you.
We broke up.
This project, which had a viewer rating of 20.4%,
was initiated by Matsumoto, who was burning with revenge.
Did he shake your hand?
He shook Shinmi's hand.
When he said he didn't like it, he said he wanted to put a mosaic on his wife's face.
He wanted to put a mosaic on his wife's face.
He wanted to take a phone call from his family.
He didn't want me to be the only one who was like this.
I'm going to do it today.
An emergency project.
Masatoshi Hamada's great plan for the future.
The continuation will be after the commercial.
After the recording of Gaki no Tsukai, the revenge was finally settled.
Thank you for your hard work.
Let's go.
We can't be separated.
Are you alone?
What?
Yes, I'm alone.
I don't know unless I see you.
Let's go.
Why is it raining?
It's raining.
What?
He's walking.
Look at him.
He's walking like a fool.
He's not thinking about anything.
Is it okay?
Look.
He's walking.
What?
Do you want to do it?
The best soap land.
Suyahime.
Soap?
Do you want to go to the soap?
I can't go to the soap.
You'll be in the scene.
So you've been talking.
You don't even want to go to the soap.
Refreshing.
This is a joke.
You should really look at this.
It's really good.
What is this?
This is good.
He's coming out.
It's refreshing.
Where did he go?
What is this?
The rain is weird.
This is a good room.
There he is.
Jimmy.
It's refreshing.
This is a good room.
Orange juice.
Orange juice?
Are you crazy?
I'm going to the bathroom.
My throat hurts.
There he is.
Where did he go?
What is this?
Isn't that a bathroom?
It's a bathroom.
Why is it a bathroom?
Money is...
This is a good room.
What is he doing?
He's been in Kobayashi and Akira Barrier.
He's in again.
Does the soap taste like soap?
And he borrowed money.
It says Playmate Academy.
There's no academy this time.
He's young.
It's refreshing.
What is this?
He's been in Kobayashi and Akira Barrier.
He's in again.
What is this?
What are you thinking?
He's in Kobayashi and Akira Barrier.
That's right.
He's in again.
Three games.
Three games?
Let's go.
It's refreshing.
There he is.
Did he take it?
What are you talking about?
Let's go.
You should have taken it.
Stop it.
Hey!
What is this?
Excuse me.
Who are you?
Amada?
Excuse me.
I'm not Amada.
What are you doing here?
Excuse me.
Be careful.
Where did you buy it?
What?
That's strange.
Why did you buy it?
It was Amada, wasn't it?
I told you to stop it.
Why?
Who is Amada?
Where did you buy it?
I bought it when I was going home.
I see.
What?
It was different from the store.
I see.
A new program, Downtown presents,
Bad juice, Gachimizu.
It stinks!
It's finally going to be released.
Darn it!
On Nihon TV, the first episode,
at the Nandaro Shop,
starting tomorrow, January 15th,
the new season will begin.
Be sure to enjoy the bad juice.
This program was brought to you by our sponsor.