Happy Birthday to you!
This week's birthday song is Matsumoto's 54th Birthday Song
Thank you
Matsumoto's 54th birthday is celebrated with the original birthday song that the members have written
Do you remember? After the recording
Light shines on the dark world
Tonight
You were born
In addition to the unthinkable Marufigesuto
The partner Hamada will also sing
I hate shining things
I want to go out
That's right
Yes
Excuse me
Welcome
Happy birthday, Mr. Akimoto
Thank you very much, Momiji-san.
Momiji-san, thank you very much.
Today, you're wearing a beautiful kimono.
Thank you very much.
Kitty-chan...
It's Kitty-chan.
I like Kitty-chan, so I'd like you to remember her.
Well, let's do it again.
Happy birthday.
Thank you for coming all the way here.
I was happy to celebrate it.
I was surprised.
When Matsumoto-san held a meeting for various projects,
she often said about Momiji-san.
I often said that I wanted to include Momiji-san.
Really?
I'm very happy.
When I was watching Matsumoto-san's appearance on TV,
I thought it was not interesting anymore.
I was so happy to see the video of the song that I asked her to wear a pink kimono.
I was on the program that I was not on.
What is good about Momiji?
Momiji has a great balance.
She is an actress, so she can talk.
If she is in need, she can also laugh.
I see.
It's a high rating.
Yes.
I'm so happy.
She sometimes uses the topic of the burdock.
I see.
The number of people who have experienced the Omamichi.
That's what I saw.
That's the way Monbi uses it.
I'm very happy that you use it to this extent.
I see.
I'm very happy.
It's strange to be told to stop doing that.
That's right.
It's normal.
It's a big heart.
It's not good at all.
I wasn't here
You're acting like a father
Huh?
The reason why I'm being called to this variety show is because of you, Mr. Matsumoto
I'm sorry
I'm really grateful that you're able to talk about me, an actress who's not funny at all
Well, there are a little more than 70 people with experience.
Even though Matsumoto-san is such a great person,
when I go to greet him at the dressing room,
even during lunch, he would wake up properly
and come to the place where I breathe,
saying, I don't mind,
and he would accept my precious souvenir.
I really like Matsumoto-san
The lovely lady you talk to
Every time I hear about happiness
I noticed, I noticed
I'm secretly in love with the princess
I want to be your daughter
Matsumoto-san's daughter
Happy Birthday!
Even the lines are included.
Please continue with the song.
Oh, she wrote a message.
That's wonderful.
When I heard the chorus, I thought, is he my father?
It's like, if you weren't here, you wouldn't be here.
It's like I was born here, so I'll put it on the variety show.
It's a very meaningful story.
He's the father of the world's best actor.
I thought he was the father of the world's best actor.
He hasn't been on a variety show yet.
I was nervous because I was going to be on a variety show.
I was a little bit dumbfounded, but I was so nervous.
I didn't know if I could say it.
I was so happy that everyone was able to say it.
I'm really grateful for that.
You are the mother of a child, right?
Yes.
So you are the mother of a child?
Dad!
Dad?
Today, I am a mother.
Thank you very much.
You want to be a daughter, right?
I was jealous.
When I was talking about you,
you made a very good movie.
Really?
So I should stop talking about my daughter?
But it was fun to hear.
I love the movie that Masumoto-san's heart is already overflowing.
But we got to know about it.
We got to know about it.
Because it's written in such a private room.
Yes.
It's amazing.
Thank you very much.
It's good. It's good.
It's good for us only?
That's right.
It's a surprise.
You have been on the show once in a while, right?
Yes, we do.
You have been doing a lot of things.
That's right.
I have been doing it with Akemi-chan.
Yes.
That's right.
Kyoko-chan, you came here on purpose?
You got a trap.
Matsumoto-san, happy birthday!
No, no, no, thank you very much!
Here you go!
Thank you very much!
Good evening!
I'm always a big fan of yours.
Thank you very much!
I'll always support you!
I'm so happy!
Happy birthday!
I'm sorry.
Your lipstick is beautiful today.
You have it on your lips.
I'm not used to it.
But recently, I've gotten better at makeup.
Thank you.
You've become more and more feminine.
I'm very happy.
Thank you for coming to this celebration.
Thank you for coming.
I'm so excited.
Really? I'm so happy.
Is there a private party?
No, there isn't.
Is this your first time?
No, it's not.
It's not that.
The first time I saw you...
Legendary entertainer...
It's a little bit creepy to say it here.
A serious man without energy.
We have to do the show together!
How about it?
Sunday, the 24th, 11pm!
Matsumoto's 54th Birthday Party
I'm so happy
Is it a private party?
No, it's not a private party
It's not a private party
a rendition of her 3rd album,
once Pure F Stay
when I saw for the first time
that time when I was able to meet
my dream was
when I was still October
20 years have passed since then
The first meeting of my dreams
My heart is pounding with happiness
I like the way you look, your hair, your fashion
Your big smile, your shy smile, your shy gestures
I like everything about you
I love all of your shy gestures
From now on, forever and ever
Please stay as you are, Matsumoto-san
I will love you forever and ever and ever and ever
I love you
Wonderful!
The harmony was amazing!
She was on the show.
I was very nervous today.
How was it, Kuroko?
You have a good body.
Yes.
How was it?
I was saying that at the training gym,
the people who train with me,
they train Matsumoto's pectoral muscles.
I heard that you were wondering how much you would raise the bench press.
I'm happy to hear that.
Thank you very much.
I feel so good.
I've been watching TV for a long time.
I'm glad to hear the surprise from people who are not regular people.
He usually does things that are very tense.
That's right.
He's a world champion.
When he sings, he gets a little nervous.
That's right.
If he's moving during a wrestling match, he can get a sense of tension.
But he can't move, so he's using the microphone.
But I was going to celebrate with all my might, so thank you.
Thank you.
I hate those who are envious.
I love those who don't call me Papa.
Matsumoto's 54th Birthday Celebration.
The last song is sung by Hamada.
I love the training of my muscles around me
I hate cold water
More than anything, I love to laugh
I met you when I was six years old
I realized I was already 54 years old
I met her when I was 6 years old
Human poison is a poison
but even then, it was you who sang with me
Thank you.
He is the one who gives us all the things we like and hate.
And he is old.
He is young.
He has to take good care of himself.
He is 6 years old.
He is coming to Japan at 54.
That's great.
He is 48.
He is half a century old in 2 years.
He is older than anyone.
Well, I guess I'm closer to him than anyone else.
That's right.
He often says that I'm a human being.
But what do you all think? Do you think it's better to say it?
Should we say it?
Really?
I'm nervous.
Are you really nervous?
If you don't say it, you'll be more nervous.
At that time, I was alone at night and said,
It's dangerous!
The special episode of the kid's world!
A special episode of what you want to ask a legend entertainer!
A real talk show without any MGs!
Everything you want to ask a popular entertainer!
If you say Tunnels here, it's a little bit creepy.
Downtown talks about Tunnels!
And Matsumoto challenges the electric press!
He tries to wash it down!
That's all for today!
Sunday, the 24th, 11pm!
I have a question for Matsumoto-san, who says,
What happens if you take all the L.O.V.D. from Hamada-san?
You shouldn't ask such a big question.
All the questions are on the website.
Oh, so you like hot stuff.
I don't think it's as much as it used to be.
Of course it is.
You too, Yajiro-san.
I'm getting less and less.
You used to have a counter with this much stuff, right?
Not really, but I used to buy 3 or 4 of those.
Not anymore.
I did throw away quite a lot of them.
Before I threw them away, I had this kind of thing.
It's like a pata-pata album.
I put a lot of DVDs in it.
You've kept them properly.
I've kept them.
I put the ones I was worried about throwing away in the back.
The ones I was thinking about.
I just happened to be in a bad mood at that time.
Sometimes I want to see something.
I thought I'd take a look at the one I was looking back on in the past.
If I can't do this, I'll throw it away.
When I saw it, it was surprisingly right.
It's dangerous.
At that time, at night, I was like, it's dangerous!
I understand that.
While blowing.
What are you doing?
He's a fool.
You're a fool.
If you take it off, it'll be like a table.
That's not true.
I think so.
But in your case, it's not a commercial product.
We sell it at a store.
I also sell it at a store.
Again, again, again.
That's enough.
Is there a product that is not sold at a store?
So, your collection is mostly self-made, right?
You're crazy.
I'm serious.
What do you mean self-made?
You've done it before, right?
I haven't.
Really?
No, I misunderstood.
I heard that you are doing it.
What kind of misunderstanding is that?
So, if you take it up, it's not like you can take it up.
You are making it.
Every month, you are being imported.
That...
In-port...
So, I heard that you have a great screen.
Oh, I don't have it.
What?
I heard that you have an AV room there.
It's a bit confusing to say AV or AV, but...
Yes, yes, yes.
But the real AV...
Ah, no, not at all.
What?
It's a normal TV.
I heard that.
No, it's not like that. Someone said it, just randomly.
How many are there in the collection?
How many?
Yes.
To be honest, I have about 20.
I don't have 20, but...
How many are there?
I don't know.
No, no, no.
That's also...
I know.
Then throw it away.
Where are you throwing it?
Where should I throw it?
Don't say it like a corpse.
Does your wife know about that?
She probably knows.
Oh, that's the gray one.
So you can't look at your wife and say,
What is this?
No, I don't look at her.
I just put her in my room.
You're saying,
Let's spend this together!
That's weird!
Once, I got a call from my wife while I was working.
I said, I'm sorry.
My wife is that kind of person.
She's the type to say, I'm sorry.
The living room deck was broken.
I wanted to watch the DVD, so I thought I'd watch it in my room's deck.
But a weird thing came out of the tray.
That thing is printed now.
Like a photo?
A photo.
I said, I'm sorry, I saw that.
I got a call while I was working.
It's not good to say that.
What?
I don't know if I should say that or say that I don't write anything else.
What did you do at that time?
Well...
Well, it's not more than this.
Well, I wasn't told not to use it.
I didn't expect it.
Well, that's what it is.
That's a little bit.
Shall we go home?
I'm sorry.
I'm glad it's the last time.
I'm not saying anything bad.
I'm saying that I'm healthy.
I'm not even exaggerating.
We used to talk about lotion.
Lotion? What's lotion?
Moisturizing?
I used to say, when I do it myself, I use lotion and stuff.
I don't use that anymore.
Ah, but you do use lotion.
I do use it!
What?!
I don't use it!
You don't use it.
I used to put lotion in my bag while I was moving.
That was a long time ago, right?
Long time ago.
When I moved to the second back, I put a bottle in there.
I went back to the hotel and I saw him with a lid on.
His second bag was all wet.
What should I do? I had no choice but to throw it away.
No, no, I just put my hand in it.
You put it in?
I thought he put it in his bag for a moment.
Thank you.