Supercar
Camaro
If you want this, it's worth 100,000 yen
That's 100,000 yen
It will be on air on the 25th
I can't do it
I understand
I want to do it myself
The first time at Gaki no Tsukai
Chikichi
Christmas special Super star Matsumoto
Super Kamaro Dream Jumbo Auction
Good afternoon
Today, 500 people have gathered
Thank you very much
There are a lot of people, so it's a lottery
Even if it's a lottery, you can only choose 20 people
Now, the Super Kamaro will appear
Let's go
This is the Kamaro with the Kobe number
Before the auction, let me check
First of all, I'm breathing
No no no
This is different
What is it?
This is my calculation
What? Calculation?
Did you do it?
That's right
Originally this was a white Kamaro
He made it a plastic model
The plastic model is about to break
I did something I didn't want to do
Who did it?
This guy
This guy?
Matsumoto-san, your nose is coming out
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching
If you want to call the number, please come in
I don't have a tanuki anymore
From the beginning?
No
I knew it when I saw it
That is no
Let's go
No. 244
This guy
Come here
He's not here
Wait
Is he coming now?
I'm Yonezawa
Yonezawa?
How old is Yonezawa?
I'm 26 years old
What did Yonezawa do today?
He paid for the meal
He paid for the meal?
Ito Yokado group
433,200 yen
Really?
It's decided
Wait
That's fast
There are 19 people left
You can keep it
Don't give it to me
You look good with a straight face
Next, 285
It's a woman
Please come to the center
What are you?
Body?
Product
Can I look at Matsumoto-san?
Sure
Please don't show this on TV
This is really bad
Are you a photographer?
You should be outside
I'm having fun
What is it?
When I was 15
When you were 15?
I was a social worker
Are you a social worker now?
No
Because you are a foreigner
I'm sorry
You were too fast
Because you are a foreigner
What is this?
What should I call you?
You are a boy
I was a big boy
It's so hard
I want to see it
It doesn't mean that
It's 325
Here you are
I got this from the matcha house
The sleeping bag you threw away
I threw away the sleeping bag
Why do you have it in his hand?
I was working at Matsumoto-san's house
You were working at a shipping company
Did you steal the sleeping bag?
Yes
You are a criminal
No.124
What is your name?
I'm Asaba
Asaba-san
What are you going to do today?
I'm going to wear the leather coat of Silver Fox
The leather coat of Silver Fox
I brought it
How much is it?
I think it's about 1 million yen
1 million yen?
But I
I'm going to wear it
Look
I'm sure it's 1 million yen
No way
This is good
Please wear it
Thank you
I can't stand it
No.305
What is your name?
I'm Watanabe
Watanabe-san
What is this?
It's a present
Is this a present?
It's 1 million yen
Who is this?
It's my mother
Is your mother a member of the present?
I think it's about 1 million yen
It's definitely not 1 million yen
I think it's okay to eat and wash
Eat, wash and clean
Is it okay until the end of the night?
Yes
That's it
It's scary
I don't like it
How much is the bus?
Are you interested?
70, 80
The bus is 78
That's hard
No.340
This is it
Don't say that
You are the best
This is heavy
How much is this?
I didn't buy it
It fell
Did it fall?
Don't sell things that have fallen
No.338
It's here
You look like a person on the spot
What is it?
Please
Are you really working there?
I'm going to do this today
What is he going to do today?
He is good at golf
Golf putter
Our staff wants this
This
Please come
Manager Okamoto
When I asked him, he said
I'm going to buy it
It's mine
That's not true
I told him to buy it
He bought it
Did you borrow the parking lot?
I borrowed the parking lot
But it's here
I told him that's not true
I told him that you are getting bald
What is that?
I asked him to return the car
Yamazaki
Yes
I brought a joke worth 100,000 yen
I'm going
Hey, Mr. Matsumoto
It's an elephant
It's the mark of an elephant
Matsumoto is a natural person
When I was on the radio
I got a lot of the same letters
Shut up
Don't go home
I'm waiting for you on TV
First of all
Sign
Down down sign
You wrote this
This is our signature
***
And
Tomorrow is your day off
One day
Open
Yes
Really?
On New Year's Day
No
Now
I will announce
It's Udo
I've done this before
I will announce
Mother
By the way
Do you have a driver's license?
Yes
Mother
After this
I will use various tools
Mother
From the first shot of next year's child
Really?
I like it
No one says that
It's like an AD of the program
Thank you
Please give me a gift
That's all I can say
You should have brought it
I don't need that
Thank you
It's amazing
In Omotesando in Harajuku
It's lighted up
On Christmas
Yes
People from the countryside come to see it
I don't need that
So
Thank you for the Christmas present
Thank you
The road in front of you is jammed
Because everyone is watching
Yes
I think
People from Kanto in Tokyo
Don't see beautiful things
I see
We were born and raised in Kobe
Where are you from?
That's right
I'm from Kobe
You were born and raised in Kobe
No
I'm from Amagasaki
What do you think?
Do you want to sing?
Why?
Why do you want to sing?
And what are you going to sing?
I'm going to ask you a trick
If you look at the night view of Kobe
If you look at things like that
Nothing is beautiful
The bay bridge is beautiful
I don't look at it from the outside
You should look at the bay bridge
Why are you looking at the bay bridge?
What are you going to do if you get swallowed up?
I'm being watched too
It's strange
I'm hungry
Don't look at the grilled rice
You're hungry
It's strange
That's true
I don't know
It's already Christmas
Is that so?
It's not the time to do this
Are you stupid?
I don't know
But it's an ugly couple
It's going to be a big deal today
It's an ugly couple
They might be watching this at a love hotel
Why are you laughing at an ugly couple?
I'm laughing because it's an ugly couple
It's an ugly couple
They're talking like a beautiful couple
I can't hear it
Are you drinking something?
It's a weird face
It's tasty
It's the same
That's not good
That's right
Today is not a Christmas
What are you doing?
I have one at home.
That's too much!
What are you doing?
What are you doing at home?
I don't have any plans.
How many do you have?
Last year I bought 5.
What is that?
You're asking the same price.
Yeah, yeah.
Why are you making a fuss?
No, no.
You're obviously betting on me.
I have a question.
When I asked everyone's opinions,
they said,
I'm going to win.
I don't know if that's true.
I've already decided the punishment.
If you lose,
you'll die.
I'm okay with chainsaws.
I'm okay with
going like this.
I'm okay with chainsaws.
Like this?
How painful is it?
It's pretty painful.
Painful is...
I'm thinking about it.
I think it's going to be pretty intense.
Really.
I'm really looking forward to it.
What do you mean?
I'm really sorry.
No, really. I don't think so.
I don't think so.
If I say something like this,
I don't know if you can see it,
but
an iron man who cooks
won an award.
Oh, the other day?
It's amazing.
It's amazing to watch this program.
Every week, every week,
in front of a stupid customer.
What?
Can I do this?
This is definitely
more difficult.
I have to get an award.
Oh, you should
come out as a guest.
Why can't I come out?
I'm begging you.
Make a big face.
That's all.
At the end,
first,
in front of a stupid customer.
This is my partner.
Who are you looking at?
No, really.
It's actually funny.
I'm begging you.
Did you decide what to do on New Year's Day?
If I have to go,
I'll go to Hawaii.
I'll go to Kamenji.
You see,
on New Year's Day,
I'm going to the wide show.
When I come out,
they ask me if it's a party.
I tell them to bring that kind of energy.
That's why I'm here.
You know, I've been to many places.
I've never seen
a gift like this.
It's rotten.
I can't even send a New Year's card.
Why didn't you send it?
I told you to send it.
Do you have a New Year's card?
Yes, I do.
I've never done that.
I know you don't have one.
Why are you looking at my fingers?
Why are you listening to me?
It's like you're saying,
I'm good at this.
That's better.
It's better to hang it here.
There's a lot of nose hair
coming out from the right.
There's a lot of nose hair coming out from the right.
So don't say that on TV.
Why?
I have an image.
My fans think
I don't even poop.
I think I'm a teddy bear.
You're stupid.
When I get home,
I think I'm doing this.
I have a good image of my fans.
I think I'm a fluffy.
Can't you see if I go up?
Okay, then.
Don't say that.
Who told you?
Who said that?
Did it come out?
No, it didn't come out.
Are you stupid?
Don't say sleepy things.
Why don't you sing?
Why?
Why are the books in the convenience store lined up with glass?
It's a promotion.
Oh?
What do you mean?
I'm not really interested.
You know that I'll shake it and you'll be like this, right?
What do you mean?
If you look at the new magazine, you'll see that it's in.
If you look at it from the outside, you'll see that it's inside.
I see.
It's a promotion.
What do you think?
What?
Machan!
You always say something different.
Stop it!
Yes.
Recently, Matsumoto-san...
What?
Recently, Matsumoto-san has only been on variety shows and hasn't been on TV.
Ishihara-kun also came.
I don't know what to say.
Um...
It's because of Ishihara-kun.
No, no, no.
Originally, it was Ishihara Yujiro and Watari Tetsuya.
After that, I was number 3.
Ishihara-kun followed Yujiro and Watari Tetsuya.
Who was next?
Tachi Hiroshi?
Yes, yes, yes.
Before that, it was me.
Tachi-kun came after me.
Tachi-kun is already over 40 years old.
Tachi-kun came and I just switched.
You're already Tachi-kun.
Isn't that weird?
What?
When Yujiro was still alive, he was already there.
Yujiro? Why are you talking about Yujiro?
When the president was there.
He was already there?
He was already there.
When he got sick and was shaking his hand from the balcony, Watari-san was there.
Yes, yes, yes.
I was right behind Watari-san.
You're not in the frame!
No, no, I'm not in the frame.
I was right behind him.
Why are you standing like this?
You should be standing like this.
The president told me not to go out yet.
It was dangerous.
It was me at first.
It was me until episode 2.
Who was with you?
With Shibata Kyohi.
Why did it change from episode 2 to episode 3?
The first one was Taka.