I came to a strange place, but I'm going to do some special training here.
This is the match team!
And this is the match team!
Why are you so lame looking at my uniform?
Why?
Are you just taking pictures?
You're so lame!
I'm going to start with the basics.
I have a teacher here with me today as well.
Please come in!
I'm an amateur.
Don't yawn!
What should I start with?
I'll start with the passes.
You can throw it where it's easier to catch.
You don't have to be particular about the shape.
All you have to do is do it seriously.
I'll do it!
Please come in!
You can do that much, right?
I'll start with Noriyasu, Yamazaki, and Takasu.
Show me what you've got!
Ready, go!
The sun is burning in the sky. I want to hold it in my hand.
You're hitting the side!
You can't do that.
Okamoto, then Naguri.
Then Keibo.
Ready, go!
The sun is burning in the sky. I want to hold it in my hand.
The sun is burning in the sky.
The grasshopper is holding rice!
I can't close it!
What's next?
Next is the goal.
Ready, go!
The sun is burning in the sky.
I can't see it!
You're still doing that face!
Soccer club, soccer club.
Oh, you want to be a soccer player.
Ready, go!
The sun is burning in the sky.
Hey, are you serious?
Ready, go!
What's next?
Next is 1 on 1.
The one who has the ball, please leave the defense.
The enemy team will come from the other side, right?
So I'll wait here alone.
Ready, go!
Keibo-san!
I just took a picture.
Ready, go!
The sun is burning in the sky.
Wait a minute!
I'm sorry!
Why are you laughing?
It's been a long time since I played with a child.
Ready, go!
The sun is burning in the sky.
You guys!
You can't see anything!
I'll do my best.
Ready, go!
The sun is burning in the sky.
What?
Who's dancing?
Damn it!
I want you to come back cleanly!
Katsumato-san!
Ready, go!
The sun is burning in the sky.
What?
Keibo-san!
I'll do my best.
The sun is burning in the sky.
Stand up! Stand up!
I don't know anymore!
What kind of man are you?
Aren't you the chief of this program?
Don't you have a little more love?
What kind of attitude is that?
I'm not feeling well.
If you're not feeling well, why don't you do that?
It's not that I'm not feeling well.
I'm always like that.
Your face is creepy.
Especially your smile.
You have to be careful with your words.
What?
I'm really nice.
Really.
Where are you nice?
I'm really nice.
You're really nice.
Don't laugh!
I go to the convenience store myself.
I go to the TV.
You have to be careful.
It's hard, isn't it?
On that bookshelf.
It's hard.
You have to be more careful when you go out.
You're a human.
You have to be more careful when you're sick.
Why are you so serious?
You used to be a man with a lower back.
You've been a little weird lately.
You've been weird.
Why don't you say it twice?
Don't say it twice!
If you say it twice, I'll beat you up.
That's not true.
For example, when you get home from work,
that's enough.
What's that?
When you get home, there's food, you eat, you take a bath,
there's hot water, you use it,
and when you get out, you pull the blanket,
and you go to sleep.
That's enough!
After you get home.
What?
You cook yourself?
You don't do the laundry yourself.
You don't wait for the guy with the apron?
Happy New Year!
What kind of person are you?
That's what you think.
I'm a normal person.
You're a pervert.
I'm not a pervert.
You're definitely a pervert.
That's not true.
I'm not a pervert.
You're not a pervert?
What are you trying to say?
I'm just trying to get you to like me.
That's definitely not true.
You're probably doing that.
You're definitely not a pervert.
You're wearing a pair of tights.
You're probably doing something weird.
You're saying weird things.
I'm not a pervert.
You're a pervert.
You're saying weird things.
I'm not a pervert.
You're really something.
When you say something like that,
you don't get the image of it.
I don't get it.
Why would I go back to this boring,
tiring house and wear tights
when I'm tired?
I shouldn't be doing that.
You're stupid.
That's a different kind of physical strength
from being boring.
You're the only one
who's the same as on TV.
That's rare.
Normally on TV,
people who say stuff like this
don't say things like
Thank you for your hard work.
I don't say that.
You're still the same.
You're wearing a pair of tights
even though you're a pervert.
You're scary.
What should we do?
What is it?
It's rugby.
We practiced today.
We went to practice.
It's a penalty game between you and me.
There are various rules.
How is it?
What do you want to be?
What do you want?
There are various things.
Penguins.
And legs.
Legs.
And what else?
There's a lot of interesting things.
Well,
it seems like there are a few.
There's a place where the ceiling is made of glass.
So I think A is better.
What do you mean?
You mean you look at the audience like this?
Yes.
There are people swimming here.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's A.
There's A.
What are you talking about?
You're A, too.
What? I'm A?
If you're A over there,
I think it's A.
Isn't it scary?
A?
Yes.
A is not scary, is it?
I don't know.
But you've never heard of
someone who was A, have you?
What are you going to do if you become an anime character?
What are you going to do if you become a couple?
I'm not going to become an A.
Because you're an A, too.
No, I'm an A.
You're going to have an attitude like an A.
That's not funny.
What are you going to do?
What should I do?
What do you want me to do?
What?
Well,
what do you want me to do?
Laugh.
What do you want me to do?
Cover.
Laugh.
Have you ever seen a cover in a aquarium?
It's a cover, brother.
Laugh.
Don't look at it.
I thought about it, and the cover came out now.
And that,
that,
Tatsunoo and Shigo.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
It's floating like this.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, that's it?
I'm going to take a good picture.
What are you saying?
I'm talking to you.
That mouth, that,
the village chief's.
Chiku-chan.
Hello, Hama-chan, Mattsun.
Yes.
A long time ago, Mattsun said that the nipples were useless, so I didn't need it.
So, what about cutting off Mattsun's nipples and putting them on auction?
It's a pretty expensive thing.
No, no, you can't put it on auction.
No, that's.
Are you going to take it?
No, if it's at a good price.
How much do you want?
What about this?
I'll give you two.
I'd better not have one or two.
No, it's okay.
That's your nipples.
Do you want to do an auction?
No, no, no, it's okay?
So, I'll do it if I get A2.
How much do you want?
10 yen.
You know...
What is it?
My mother, Akiko, raised me to be a beggar.
My expensive nipples...
Expensive or not, that's...
I'm going to raise them from now on, Yuka.
Starting from 10 yen...
That's too much.
How much do you want?
500 yen.
No, no, no.
You're pretending to be nice.
What are you talking about?
500 yen.
At first it's 500 yen.
After that, it's a buy-buy game.
You said you'd buy it for 500 yen.
No, I didn't mean that.
Of course you did.
First of all...
If you sell your nipples for 500 yen,
it's funny, so if you sell it for 500 yen, I'll buy it.
I want to ask you once if you're going to buy it for 500 yen or not.
Of course I will.
But it's for three people.
I see. Everyone's a little worried right now.
If you want it, you don't have to worry.
Starting from 500 yen.
500 yen.
1,000 yen.
1,000 yen. Anything else? Anything else?
2,000 yen.
3,000 yen.
10,000 yen.
What?
20,000 yen.
Hey, hey, hey.
Think carefully.
You're so stubborn.
What are you going to use it for?
That's fine.
Because, you know...
There's a tower.
Even in a glass tower.
There's a time when it's noisy.
Are you going to use it as a cushion?
Look at the top and bottom.
50,000 yen.
There's 100,000 yen.
What kind of a person is that?
You're definitely lying.
It's a loan.
Are you stupid?
It's not cash.
It's a loan.
You can't cut that kind of thing.
I'm telling you because I think so.
You're saving up money little by little just for your neck.
You don't have to look like that.
After all, 100,000 yen is the ceiling.
Can you get 200,000 yen?
I'll never get it.
I'll never get 200,000 yen.
I'm telling you I can.
Then cut it.
You can't get 200,000 yen.
What?
There's nothing more than that.
Your neck.
I'll tell you.
100,000 yen.
That's right.
What?
What are you guys doing?
What's wrong?
It's unusual for you to be so stupid looking at your neck.
I'm at my limit.
What?
I'm serious.
Seriously.
I'm not kidding.
I'm really serious.
If it's for love, I'll make my wife cry.
That's what the singer says.
Do you guys agree with that?
Also,
What's wrong with that?
Do you have any complaints?
Do you agree with that?
Or are you against it?
Even though I'm a comedian,
I think it's too selfish.
What do you think?
It's too selfish.
That's what the singer says.
You know what?
There's no such thing as a comedian.
There's no such thing.
It's up to you whether you want to go see her or not.
I don't think I can go see her when my father dies.
Go see her.
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
My father doesn't know.
Did you get caught?
I got caught by my father.
I almost got killed by my father.
Don't say that.
There's a theme park next to the rescue center.
There is.
There's a theme park next to the rescue center called the Deluxe Pool.
I went to the pool when I was in elementary school.
The pool with waves.
I can't reach it because it's an adult pool.
I'm scared.
Why are you asking for money?
I can understand that.
The waves are so strong.
They are so strong.
It's okay if you can't go in.
The waves are different from the waves I saw as an adult.
It looks like a normal wave from here.
It's a child's point of view.
In the world of children, the waves are scary.
From a child's point of view.
What are you looking at?
I'm not looking at anything.
I don't know what I was thinking.
I was holding my head high.
It was strong.
I can't stand it.
I thought I wouldn't be able to swim.
The waves were so strong.
Do you know?
When the wave comes close to death,
I want you to try it at home.
If you hold your breath as long as you can,
it becomes blue.
It's a danger signal.
Don't do it anymore.
It's coming out.
It's a danger signal.
It's a father.
I can't kill it.
It's coming out.
I hugged it.
If you had helped me,
it would have been a danger signal.
It's coming out.
You have no choice but to die.
I have no choice but to die.
Then I locked myself in my shell.
I saw a fairy.
You are too beautiful to summarize.