There's no place for kids in downtown, so have fun.
Let's have a drink and have a good time!
So, what are we doing today?
Today, Team Zero has been making a lot of appearances in the opening.
I'd like to see their talent.
Let's have a drink and have a good time.
So, this is how it's set up.
That's right.
So, let's have a drink and have a good time.
We can't stop drinking with comedians.
Is that so?
I drank twice when I made my debut.
Drink!
So, let's have a drink and have a good time.
By the way, if you drink on the stage and have to throw up,
this is a serious story.
Team Zero will never be used on this program again.
Let's have a drink and have a good time.
We need more and more newcomers.
That's right.
We'll have them do the story.
Do you really want us to do the story?
Of course.
You guys are dressed like that.
Merry Christmas!
Mom, I'm a little excited.
Get out.
I'm kidding.
Get out!
What's wrong?
What happened?
Mom, I don't understand at all.
You'll understand when I play for you.
Good job, Miyabuta.
Mom, are you fat?
Hey, don't lead the way!
Don't lead the way!
Dear Santa,
When I turn 20,
I want to get on the Countach.
It's called Hosei.
Bring me a present from Santa Claus.
What?
Don't tell me...
It's a lie, you idiot!
It's a lie!
Hey, that's too easy!
What are you doing?
Easy, easy!
Sit down, sit down.
Give him a drink.
Oh, thank you.
Good job, Mr. Utae.
Here you go.
Drink up!
Drink up until you run out of bubbles.
Get on the Countach, we'll take turn.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Drink up!
Over there, that's isn't their place.
I'll go quick.
I don't know who are you telling to do so
Okay let's go.
Let's do this.
3, 2, 1, go!
Yeah!
It's fun, isn't it?
Yamazaki, how's the recent downtown?
It's a little tough.
It's really tough?
I really want to see you in yellow.
Let's drink! Let's drink!
Let's drink!
We're the ones in the TV.
We're competing.
That's all.
Please come again. Thank you very much.
60%, 70%, 80%
I'm doing it.
How is it?
It's like a 3 o'clock party.
It's a bubble!
You're drinking!
It's like a Hamachan.
I like it.
Thank you.
Really, this is...
I really can't say it.
I...
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
It's like a 3 o'clock party.
I'm giving you a Christmas of two mothers.
But it's okay.
Because there's love.
But, I got a letter from my husband for 10 years.
What's wrong?
I don't know what to do.
I'll go up to my husband.
Let's sing a song.
Christmas.
Everybody's thinking now.
Don't cry!
Thank you very much.
Is this on air?
Give me a hug.
It's the best!
I don't know what to do.
Ladies and gentlemen.
What is it today?
Wait a minute.
Camera.
It's so cool!
What is it?
It's so easy to set your hair.
Isn't this good?
Let's do it.
Especially in Tokyo, at the end of the year, the road is crowded.
It's annoying.
There are so many cars.
That's because I'm the first to go.
On the contrary, drivers in Tokyo are stopped at the yellow sign.
That's true.
Why is it stopped at the yellow sign?
I want you to see that.
If you stop at the yellow sign in Osaka, you'll get a fine.
I'll get a fine.
I don't know.
I'm the one who cares about cars.
I don't know at all.
The other day, when I stopped at the yellow sign in Shinjuku, there was a fight.
I hit him.
He came down and said,
No, I didn't hit him.
You're hurt, aren't you?
No, I'm not hurt.
We're looking at each other like this.
Look at this.
I thought he was a fish.
I don't know.
I wonder if he'll be interested in me.
I'm sure he will.
When I was on the bus, I was like that.
If I hit him, he'll be depressed.
I don't think it's funny.
The third day, I hit him on the door.
The other day, I hit him on the guardrail.
I hit him again.
Humans are stupid.
I'm worried about that.
I'm not worried about animals.
I hit him on the dog house.
I don't think he'll look at me.
I don't think it's funny.
I'm serious.
I'm not worried about animals.
It's not funny.
I'm concerned about animals.
I'm worried about animals.
I think I'll hit him.
I hit him.
I'm serious.
I don't think it's funny.
It's so cold.
It's raining.
I can't stand it.
I'll go to the car.
I was about to go to the car.
I was like this.
I was so angry.
I was like this again.
I can't stand it.
What's wrong with you?
You're the boyfriend of Baikinman.
I don't know.
I don't know that.
I stopped the car once.
I played for a while.
I came back.
The front glass was broken.
The door of the car was broken.
It was written here.
It was written in magic.
I came back from work.
You came back from work.
That's right.
I looked at the back of the car.
The back of the car was broken.
It was broken.
I thought I was going home.
That's right.
What?
My car was shining.
It was so bright.
It was like a jewel box.
It was shining.
I thought I was going home.
The back of the car was broken.
The side was broken.
The inside was full of glass.
That was hard.
But I could laugh.
You can't laugh.
You can't go home.
If I have a driver's license, I'll be in trouble.
Do you have a driver's license?
I still have a driver's license.
But I can't go home.
I looked at my car.
I could see it was broken.
I had a driver's license.
That's not true.
It was broken.
You're a fool.
How about that?
That's impossible.
I've been to Okamahora twice.
I've forgiven everything.
I said, it's okay.
You're a bit old.
Why?
That's strange.
If only the steering wheel, the steering wheel and the frame were left, it would be fine.
I would run like Lupin.
You are not an anime character.
You run with your bones down.
By the way, the car is like this.
This guy is amazing.
The car is like a president.
This guy is riding a Century.
You are amazing.
You are riding a Camaro too.
Camaro and Century are completely different.
I am an international Century.
The price is completely different.
That's not true. You are riding a Camaro too.
Is it 4 million yen?
It's like this with cash.
I am riding a Camaro for 4 million yen.
What is this Century?
Thank you.
In my head, I think the Century is higher.
That's fine.
Last week, I took a break.
What was it?
Punishment game?
The punishment game we played until now.
Everyone, please watch it.
I was playing all night.
I thought I would start little by little.
You started when you were about a year old.
That's right.
I had to decide what to bet on.
I thought I would bet on Kouhaku.
What do you think?
I don't know the members.
I am sorry.
Kouhaku members.
We can make it. We can make it until next week.
We can make it next week.
Let's decide next week.
Which one is red or white.
Then, we will have power.
We will know when we are older.
Let's decide what to do.
Punishment game?
It's been a long time.
Shall we pull our teeth?
Let's stop it.
Why do we have to pull our teeth?
What should we do?
Let's make it physical.
Let's stop it.
If we lose, we will have to go to the hospital and open our brains.
Then, we will be written as a fool.
You are so good at it.
Let's stop it.
Is there any punishment game?
If you are bored, you can play a game instead of an object.
What is it?
Business.
What is business?
If you play roulette, it will go like this.
At that time, it will go like this.
If you take 400,000 yen, it will go like this.
Your face will go like this.
It is possible.
But, I want to play this game instead of a punishment game.
It is interesting.
What is there?
Let's play Cupid's 3-minute cooking.
What should we do with Cupid's 3-minute cooking?
Let's put Cupid's 3-minute cooking next to you.
You can change the punishment for me and for you.
If I lose, you will eat Cupid's 3-minute cooking.
What if I lose?
If you lose, you will eat bungee jumping.
Really?
Why can't I fix it?
I almost died once.
You should also jump once.
I can't jump.
Why can't you jump?
When you were on the plane, you said,
Goodbye.
You said it for a long time.
I can't do it.
You can't do it.
I can't fall.
You can fall.
Why do you say that?
When I was on the plane, the teacher was here.
If the teacher moved, I couldn't move.
I was so weak.
I can't fall.
No, no, no.
This is the sky.
If you come here, you will fall.
I can't fall.
I will stand still.
This is a problem for me.
Do it here.
Why do you say that?
Stop here.
It's dangerous. Stop it.
I said I can't fall.
I have the feeling that it's dangerous.
Even if you have the feeling, it's not dangerous.
You can do it. Stop here.
What?
You can't stop.
You can't fall.
Hama-chan.
Thank you.
Hello, Hama-chan.
Actually, I saw something unexpected of you.
What is it?
When you entered the studio of Albano,
you said you can laugh on December 3rd.
It's good that you came out of the car in a cool way,
but you got caught in a chain and fell.
I remember that your face was bright red.
You are a bastard.
There is no such time.
Big brother.
There is such a time, isn't it?
There is no such time.
Really?
You got into the car suddenly.
When I got into the car...
There is a chain.
There is a chain like this.
That's right.
It's not so bad that you can cross it.
If you can cross it, then cross it.
I know that.
There is an older brother of Honda Gano.
Can you do this for me?
When I got out of the car,
I ran out of the car.
I thought you came.
I thought I should go.
When I thought I should go,
I got out of the car.
You are so cool.
If you do this for me,
I will go home soon.
Did you go home?
If you do this for me,
I will cry on the bed.
You are not so sad.
You are so cool.
If I don't go home,
I will cry on the bed.
I will call my mother.
I will tell her that I fell down.
You are so cool.
I have fallen down.
I have never fallen down so much.
Really?
But yesterday,
I was a little bit cool.
What did you do yesterday?
Yesterday,
I was shooting a movie.
I dressed up as a monkey.
I wanted to go to the toilet.
I went to the toilet.
I came back.
I went to the studio.
I dressed up as a monkey.
I looked around.
I didn't see many staffs.
Thanks to everyone.
I didn't see any staffs.
You are so cool.
I don't think so.
I thought it was my studio.
I didn't dress up as a monkey.
I dressed up as a monkey.
I looked around.
I didn't see many staffs.
I didn't think I was going to shoot a movie.
When I saw you,
I thought you were Matsumoto.
You are so cool.
I will never see you again.
You are not cool.
You are cool.
You are so cool.
Your face is so red.
When you are so cool,
How much you can be upset.
When I try to be upset,
I am caught in a trouble.
I am taken away.
I am so confused.
I can't go like this.
If you were alone,
I would be fine.
If it's like this, it's going to be like this.
That's not good.
That's not cool.
Have you ever opened the bathroom door?
I've opened it, but I've never opened it.
When you open it, it depends on how tight it is.
It's tight.
If you open it too much, it depends on how you want it.
If you open it like this,
If you open it too much,
It's going to be normal.
It's going to be normal if you open it.
It's going to be like this.
I don't know how to say it.
Like this?
What is this?