Next time, we will be at the popular camp at the Gaginosu Skyline!
It's nice here
Is the camp popular?
It is
What are you going to do?
I'm going to try camping
Do you have any experience?
Yes, here
Liar!
You again?
India is popular
Call Hiroshi
No, no, no, no.
There are members, too.
I'll pull them.
When we play games, we have a meeting.
We act like we know the difference.
I can't trust you.
You're waiting for us, aren't you?
I'm waiting for the new director.
Who are you?
I'm sorry
When you think of camping, tent
Let's all work together
First, let's build the tent
I've never done this before
But it's okay
There's a piece of paper inside
You just have to put it on
It's already shaped
That's fast
You put this on
You put it on?
Ready, set, go
It's like this
You pull the orange one with this and put it here and fix it.
This is also fixed.
It's easy.
Enos-san, there.
Do you need this?
But it's very dark. Do you need it?
No, no, no. I need it.
You can't fix it.
But I need it. Pull it and make it double.
Is this okay?
Don't come too much.
It's only a bell.
I'll take it.
Amagawa-san, yes.
Sorry for the sudden visit.
Are you recording?
Oh, you're here.
Yes, I'm recording a camp.
I'm around here.
Oh, really?
Yes.
I'm in Tokyo only when I'm working.
The world is difficult now, so I'm here.
I usually come here.
Oh, I see.
I happened to be at a campsite.
Really?
Yes.
What is it?
I don't know.
Full tension, 5 people.
What?
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
It's Gyagawa-ken.
Gagaken
Gagaken?
Don't you know?
Hollywood celebrities like Paris Hilton and Madonna are in it
Gagaken
Son Goku who makes a mistake in the balance
You guys, take this!
Ka...me...ha!
Oh no, I got the wrong balance.
A small one came out.
A small one came out!
It's a good thing.
Sorry, I'm still not finished with the tent.
This is a bit...
Hamada-san, then this one.
Ah, this one...
Wait, wait, wait.
Yamashita-kun, you're in danger.
A primary school student's song of change.
Pee and poo, one letter difference
The butt and the glasses are three different characters
I'm sorry.
That's right.
Why are you laughing?
Sing, sing.
Maybe the sound of the can-can.
Ah, look.
Here, here.
Chaka-chan, Gin-chan, Gin-chan, Gin-den-den.
Every time, I tell a stupid story.
I heard that a
Shut up!
I'm going to finish this!
I got it, I got it
He's stepping on it
He's stepping on it himself
Hey, change it to this one
It's okay, it's not a camera
3 seconds before the he, he, he
3, 2, 1
Mistake!
Ah ah ah ah ah!
What's wrong with him?
He's crying!
The baby is crying!
I have to help him!
He's crying!
No, no...
He's laughing
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have recorded this
I'm sorry
Let's go!
It's my first time.
I won! I won!
I got it!
Yagawa-ken...
It's my first time.
I don't know what to do.
What should I do if I can do this?
I think you should light a fire.
Really?
I'll do it.
Cool.
When you come in, you can see the camp site, right?
That's right.
Camp site is good.
I've never seen anything like that before.
It's easy.
I changed my image a bit.
I wonder if it's a circle.
Is there a fire?
But it's nice.
OK.
It's on fire.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
Is it this easy?
It's easy to make a fire like this.
That's right.
If you sit down,
Sit down.
It depends on the type.
I want to make a fire by myself.
I want to make a bigger fire.
I think it's just right.
I will talk with my ears.
The fire is a little scary.
I'm gonna kill you!
Fine.
Alright all right.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, it's coming I'll get the Hell Fang!
Fine.
One, One, One, One, One!
It's coming I'll get the Hell Fang!
Alright.
It's coming.
You're right.
Alright, stop it, stop.
That's dangerous!
Why do you go over there is so scary.
What a foolish applauding of form in the back.
This is the snow here, not the ninja?
Well, it doesn't matter what, it's dangerous here.
So, I told them not to go.
I got it.
Sorry.
I think the fire is a little strong.
We are filming.
I know that.
This is a pass.
It's a usual walking course.
If you don't take them for a walk once a day, they get stressed.
It's different.
Yes, it's different.
It's a little scary, but it's a pain.
Change the mood!
Push! Push! Push!
The wave of the picture of the North Sea.
It's scary.
It's going to fall.
It's coming.
I got it.
Let's get excited! Let's get excited! Let's get excited!
Takata, Takata, hey!
Be quiet! Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey!
Take it! Take it!
Hello, world!
He's so energetic.
Gagawa Ken.
Yes, he is still young.
I got it, I got it.
It's OK, it's OK.
I'm sorry.
The siren sound is very responsive.
Hey, come here. I'll return it to you.
Sorry to bother you.
The first shot is delicious.
I understand.
Young people are very energetic.
I want to do it when I'm beaten.
I'm a young man.
What are you trying to do?
It's hard to take care of a person.
Would you like to eat something?
I want to eat it
Do you have ingredients?
Yes, we have
Really?
This is a great food for camping
Wow, it's great
It's a barbecue
Ta-da
Wow
Really?
Next, they enjoy camping with a barbecue
Is this seasoned butter burning?
Yes
Salt and pepper
There's some
Before eating
Yes, the seasoning
No no no no no!
one, two
1, 2, all of you, slurp!
I don't know...
Um, I'm currently...
I'm wearing panties, right?
The cloth is not very good.
The needle is not very good.
Can I check if you are wearing panties?
No, no, no.
Thank you very much.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I'm cold! Panty dance! I'm cold! Panty dance! Panty! Panty! Panty!
I'm all wet!
The first time meeting, rice paper butterfly!
I'm the type to sweat my pants.
I'm Baichon!
Let's start the show!
Yes, Tamayo's Baichon!
Yes, Manze!
Chuchuru Chuchuru Manze!
Manze is...
Yabai! Yabai! Yabai!
Once you sing it, it's long.
It's long, right?
What are you talking about.
I got it.
sleepy everything
ones here
The next relationship.
We need to get along.
It needs to be unusual.
Where are you going?
I understand.
Hey.
They are behaving himself.
Everyone.
There are families, right?
If you have children,
Don't forget this!
Tamayo's place is a school zone!
What's that?
The suspicious person can't enter!
The mess is long!
It's dangerous to go near the fire!
My legs are burning!
I'm sorry!
Tamayo's butt is a fire!
Yes, yes, yes!
Someone!
I can't use the gun.
You're wrong!
I got it.
Calm down.
Sorry.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
I can't move.
Hey, Tamao.
Minus 4.
It's okay.
You're doing this on purpose
I'm sorry
Chin
Chapchae
Let's go
Chin
Chin-jao-ro-su
Yes, stir-fry the peppers and the chins and then stir-fry them
Stir-fry the peppers and the chins and then stir-fry them
This is a terrible prayer.
This is a bad joke.
That's what it meant?
It's best to pour water.
I can't stop. I'm sorry.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's amazing.
That's right.
You're buying a lot.
Do you need water?
Certainly, it is for digestion.
It would be helpful if there was a little behind.
I'll get some water.
Do you need it?
Certainly, it would be helpful if there was a little behind.
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm going to go.
Everyone, please divide your roles.
I'm going.
I'm doing it here.
Is there anything else to do?
Yes, there is a little bit of this.
Well, that's the beauty of camping.
You have to take care of it.
Yes.
All of these are from the same place.
It's a log.
It's amazing.
He is very worried about the water
What is the situation?
Endo, who went to collect water, does not come back
He is very worried about the water
The water is right there, right?
Yes
He should have come back
Is it there?
Yes
Because it is there
Where did he go from?
He went to the river
He does not drink the water of the river
He should be able to go immediately
I can smell something.
Huh?
You don't say anything.
The chimney?
What's wrong with the chimney?
The chimney is saying it's going to collect water.
It used to say that it was a big accident.
Oh, that's just right.
The Giga dog I'm taking right now also has a rescue dog.
Let's find it.
Can you find it?
There's something that smells like chimney.
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, where are you going?
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Hey, hey, hey.
He's quiet.
I see. I smell something.
I'm grateful that you're looking for him, but...
I'm filming here.
That's right.
Miki-tei!
No, that's not it.
That's not it.
He's not the one looking for him.
It's a different place.
It's amazing.
No, it's a
It's dangerous.
I'm worried.
Mickey is different.
That's right.
It's different.
I went to the other side.
You smell it, you're outside the neighborhood.
You're just shouting.
Is it okay?
Don't smell it.
It's not that place.
It's far away.
It's close.
Maybe it's drowning.
You're smart.
He's smart.
I think he's different from the one he was before.
He's very persistent.
Miki-san!
He won't be able to speak tomorrow.
He's already flying.
That's probably true.
Miki-san! Miki-san! Miki-san!
What's with that way of saying it?
Bring him here! Bring him here!
What? Really?
Did you get it?
Miki-san!
I got it! I got it!
I found it!
You found it?
What if I go?
What? What?
I got it! I got it!
I got it!
It's dangerous if we all go there!
That's right!
Oh, it's true!
Endo, are you okay?
I got it! I got it!
Ouch!
Did you get hurt?
I think my leg got hurt
Thank you
That was a relief
You are very smart
I'm glad I didn't get hurt
Excuse me
That's the whiskey
The river is dangerous, so be careful
Thank you
It's quiet when the mission is over
It's not coming out.
It's empty.
It's going to take a little longer.
Move your body before you eat.
Let your stomach empty.
Would you like to eat?
I'm going to eat badminton.
I've been preparing for badminton.
Would you like to play badminton?
I'm not good at sports.
If you think about it, something will happen.
How do I do it?
Are you going to play it when it's over?
What should I do?
I'll do this and you do this.
I see.
How many times do you do it?
It's not easy.
Yes, yes.
Who's next?
I'll do it again.
One, two, three.
I did it!
It's quite difficult.
Six, seven.
10, 9, 10, 12, 13, 14, 15.
Hey!
Hey, what?
He is taking them.
There is one.
Wow!
Hey? Can we go?
I've never seen it.
Oh, really?
I've never seen a sword fight.
I'm a professional.
You mean you bought that much?
That's right.
It's a bargain.
There was.
There was. I'm doing a location.
I'm doing a location.
I know.
But this is a place where anyone can do anything.
I don't think it matters.
But I can hear your voice.
There is a gathering of Gaggers once a month.
They come from far away.
So we thought we should play here today.
Oh, Mr.Kanishi.
Oh, I see.
It means that it's great.
Double slap on the earlobes.
You only do Gaggers around the face.
He's wearing it.
Ears!
Ears! Double stop!
What does that mean?
Ears double stop.
Straighten your lip.
It's because he's biting.
Oh, that's a bit of a resistance.
There's something about it.
It's a bit scary.
His character is rough.
Only this guy wears it.
Hey!
You're really getting on my nerves!
Listen to me!
You're used to the board, aren't you?
You're really getting on my nerves!
Your earlobes!
Stop turning your face!
We don't know the rules, nor the rules of the game.
You're turning your earlobes to someone else!
It's a Jyagawa prefecture...
If you take it off, it won't come off.
It will come off.
That's amazing.
Please take it off.
What should we do?
It won't be a good location.
That's right.
Let's go.
Let's go to the top of the mountain.
I can't do it.
In the case of Itago, that's the only way.
I'll give it to Matsumoto-san.
Matsumoto-san, it's hard to talk to him like this.
It won't be a good location.
Oh, no, Oba-chan.
Shido, come here.
I want to continue the location.
Oh, that's fine.
That's not what I meant.
No, it isn't.
That's what I meant.
Excuse me, sorry to interrupt.
Stop it!
Hey, hey, hey!
I got it!
Gagacon...
It's definitely a Kamehameha.
What about a comedy comedy?
I definitely did it.
I didn't put it in.
so cold!