In the second episode of Gachi no Tsukai, we are going to make a scary movie!
Today is the second episode of Gachi no Tsukai, so let's explain to those who haven't seen the first episode.
It's very simple.
There is a kid in the back, and we are going to make him cry.
Last time, I played the role of Mr. Yawa.
Mr. Yawa?
I played the role of Mr. Yawa in the movie, PUNCH BOMBER.
He didn't cry at all.
That's right. Can we see it?
Oh, let's do that.
Mr. Matsumoto, go ahead.
He's crying, but he's not crying.
Don't cry.
What are you doing?
There are six of us.
There are six of us, plus Mr. Toshihide.
Please say something to Mr. Toshihide.
Mr. Toshihide, don't be silly.
Now that we're ready, let's start with Mr. Hamada.
Mr. Hamada, go ahead.
I'm scared.
I'm sorry.
We're going home.
I'm calling you.
I'm sorry.
I'll call you Matsumoto.
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
Mr. Matsumoto is here.
I'm completely ignored.
I'm hated after all.
Can't you be an idol of a little girl?
Now, Mr. Matsumoto is here.
Let's go.
Mr. Matsumoto, go ahead.
Are there any bad kids?
There are sweets.
Sweets.
Are there any bad kids?
Are you scared?
Thank you very much.
Are there any bad kids?
I was scared.
I was scared for a moment.
There was a girl who was crying.
There was a boy.
Are there any bad kids?
He was crying.
He was looking at you from behind.
You're stupid.
Were you scared?
Not really.
Was it Yu-chan?
No, it wasn't Yu-chan.
Everyone is talking about Tatsumi.
Aya-chan?
He's a good guy.
Do it.
Yay!
Do it more energetically.
He's doing it.
He's like a child.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you very much.
So, what are we going to do today?
I dressed up today.
I just wanted you to laugh.
I understand that you don't like it.
But you can't help but think that you've done it.
No, no, no.
It's not like that.
If I had dressed up properly, I would have laughed.
But I'm dressed up in a fashionable way.
You're a bit of a businessman.
I'm a businessman.
I have a bit of a CX.
I also make a polo shirt collar.
My staff is also wearing it.
And TLS is a bit smaller.
It's hot.
Oh, is it?
It's very cold.
Recently, I have to think a little more about the heating.
Oh, really?
It's extremely hot.
Extremely hot.
You have to tell me clearly.
I don't know how to reply.
What do you mean?
It's extremely hot.
Suddenly.
Yes.
It's extremely hot.
I can't catch it.
I wonder why.
I can't do it at the right temperature.
What temperature is it now?
Outside.
If it comes in from outside, it will be cold.
It would be strange if it was this hot.
That's definitely wrong.
Don't you think so?
Is that so?
I thought it was a bullet train.
I'm angry.
The bullet train is hot.
What is it?
I think I'm going to get a cold.
It's hot.
I've never done that before.
Show me this time.
That's strange.
You have to think about it.
There must be a person who is cold.
You have to think about things around that person.
If the grandmother is in a car like this,
I can't help it.
The grandmother is.
The grandmother is really cold.
There's nothing I can do about it.
How many times have I killed my grandmother?
It's so hot.
I'm sleeping in the cooler.
I can't stop it.
Why don't you stop it?
It's so cold.
It's not cold at all.
It's not cold.
I'm getting a cold.
Because it's hot.
That's right.
I'm getting a cold.
It's not cold.
I feel sick.
I'm sick too.
That's right.
I'm sick.
It's really hot.
I think humans have gotten a lot weaker.
You can't get a cold, can you?
The old humans were healthier.
That's why I've been living a normal life since the time there were no colds or heat waves.
You know what?
What is it?
It's the temperature.
What is it? I don't get it.
What is the temperature?
It's the temperature of the human being.
Oh, I see.
No, no, no.
That's not true.
You're lying.
It's Hama-chan's fault.
If you say so, I'll have to work twice as hard.
We've always been partners, right?
After all, there are times when you get annoyed no matter what you do.
So we're like that, too.
There's a rhythm, isn't there?
There's a combination that's been running with a bad rhythm all the time.
I'm sure there were times when it was good.
Oh, yeah?
What do you mean?
You're wrong about that, aren't you?
If it were us, it would be funny and we'd say,
You're so annoying.
There are times like that.
There are.
So don't say,
Stop it.
That's right.
Don't say that.
That's not funny.
That's right.
That's what you say.
That's not funny.
I don't know if I should tell you a little bit.
That's not how you say it.
That's right.
That's why I'm so sick of you.
Hey!
That's what you do.
I'm so angry when I smoke.
Why?
Why do you smoke?
You're already done, aren't you?
That's right.
Hey!
What's wrong with him?
That's amazing.
I thought so.
It's hard to do something in the dressing room.
I'm sleeping and I'm sick and I'm sick.
Hey!
That's what you say.
It's the same as an outcast.
Outcast.
That's why I'm sick of you.
The waves are scary, aren't they?
The waves.
That's why I'm telling you to breathe together.
That way, it's hard to get out of the ship.
That's why I'm sleeping.
I'm sick of you.
Hey!
That's right
I'm sorry.
But I'm not, you know?
I'm also sick of you,
but I didn't do what could piss you off.
Hey!
I don't have that. I'm not that kind of person.
What?
What's wrong with me?
I usually don't care, but when I talk on stage like this,
I smell like food I ate during lunch.
It stinks.
When I'm angry, it's a lot.
It's like, wow!
What did you eat?
I'm like, wait, wait, you're fine.
I'll just say it.
What did you eat?
What's wrong with you?
I'm like, wow!
I can't move.
I can't move and get hit.
That hurts strangely.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's really hard.
Really.
There's a lot.
But I think it's the same for both couples.
It's been a long time.
I've been doing this for 11 years.
I'm a comedian.
That's enough.
The other day, on February 14th,
I was listening to the radio.
There was a take-off of Yoshida Eisaku.
Who is that?
Yoshida Eisaku, the most popular comedian.
There's someone like that.
In the program, Yoshida Eisaku said,
I'm grateful for the fans.
But these days,
I've got about 10,000 fans.
About this.
I've got 10,000 fans.
What do you think about this?
I'm sorry.
But Yoshida Eisaku.
There's a flow of fans.
I don't think I'm going to come here from such a place.
I think it's rare for Yoshida Eisaku to come to my house.
There was something like this.
I've been thinking about you for a year.
I'll switch to Masaharu Fukuyama.
I'll continue to support you as I have done so far.
I'm sorry, Machan.
Goodbye.
The quiz challenge corner.
Melonpan and Shokupan were walking down the street.
If you say,
Which side will you turn?
Shokupan, the answer is Mimi.
That's it.
Boo.
Yay, yay, yay.
If it's Boo, it's Boo.
Tell me the answer.
The answer is Shokupan.
It's Shokupan, isn't it?
It's Shokupan.
The answer is correct.
It's correct, but it's called interpretation.
That's different.
No, it's because I have an ear.
It doesn't matter if it's Mimi.
No, no, no.
No, there's no reason for that.
No, no, it's not.
If the interpretation doesn't matter, it's Shokupan.
It's Boo, isn't it?
It would have been nice if you said Shokupan.
If you did that, you would have passed.
No, it's because I have an ear.
It doesn't matter if it's Mimi.
It doesn't matter if it's Shokupan.
For example, Mr. Koji Ota and Mr. Takashi Yoshihara.
When I read it, Mr. Takashi Yoshihara turned away and Mr. Koji Ota didn't turn away.
Why did Mr. Takashi Yoshihara turn away?
There's no reason for that.
No, it's because I have an ear.
It doesn't matter if it's Mimi.
It doesn't matter at all.
I don't think the ear groove is convincing.
I don't think it's useful.
It's just that it takes a lot of effort to gather the earlobes.
What is the ear groove?
The ear groove is the upper part.
Wouldn't it be strange if all the earlobes were extended?
Why is it strange?
It's not strange if everyone does that.
It's because I have an ear.
Oh, it's like this.
It's just that it takes a lot of effort to gather the earlobes.
It's there to accumulate.
This is making air resistance.
So, this plays the role of a parachute.
If this doesn't happen, humans will walk at a very high speed.
It's just a few millimeters round.
Let's not go too fast by collecting wind here.
Let's do it!
It's already ringing, isn't it?
Do you understand?
Of course I do.
The speed at which you are walking is not the original speed.
Actually, the power here is just to walk faster.
Even though it generates power, it is protected by this ear.
If you don't do that, it's no good.
A problem has arisen.
What kind of problem has arisen?
After all, it is an economic problem.
If you walk too fast, you will have an economic problem.
I see.
What does this mean?
I don't know.
I don't think I can understand it even if I say it.
No, no, no.
You can't say it.
Well, it's okay to say it.
It's going to be very difficult.
I don't care.
Can you say it in English?
I'll try to do it somehow.
I don't like it if it takes too long.
No, no, no.
I'm counting on you.
Please.
Put it on the table.
First of all, by walking, the air accumulates.
That kind of thing doesn't mean anything.
It's impossible.
And then, what do you call it?
First of all, first of all.
First of all, money.
What kind of first of all?
I'll tell you now.
First of all, there is money.
What kind of money?
Booking.
Who is booking?
What kind of booking?
It's a professor who looks at what he knows.
Tettare.
Tettare has nothing to do with it.
Booking of Tettare.
Tereko Tereko.
Moro Moro.
When you won the marathon, what was that strange hat made of leaves?
Is it some kind of secret?
What is that?
Gekkeiju?
Gekkeiju.
It's a leaf of Gekkeiju, isn't it?
In the end, it's a leaf of Gekkeiju.
It's a leaf of Gekkeiju.
Well, if you have time for plants.
Time?
If you have time for plants, it's a leaf of Gekkeiju.
You can look it up.
In the sense of a leaf of Gekkeiju, there is a meaning of winning the marathon.
Basically.
Basically what?
There's a lot of, what do you call it?
Present.
And then...
Butter.
What are you doing?
So, on the leaf of Gekkeiju.
What?
Let's do our best to cover the leaf of Gekkeiju in the marathon.
That's right.
Everyone who does the marathon thinks so and runs.
That kind of...
Anji is coming.
The old general has arrived.
That's what he said.
What kind of person is this old general?
What kind of person?
Yes, I hear that a lot.
That's what they say periodically before the winter comes.
It's called the coming of the winter general.
So, from now on, it's going to be that, isn't it?
It's going to be cold.
What kind of person is this winter general?
What?
What kind of outfit is this?
The winter general is not a human being.
That's stupid.
It's called the coming of the winter general.
That's why I'm alive.
I don't know if it's a role, but I'll do my best.
It's not a human being.
Is this a human being?
It's called the coming of the winter general.
That's right.
Let's write that the coming of the winter general is coming.
It's a human being.
It's not a human being.
It's a human being, the winter general.
The winter general is amazing.
What kind of clothes are you wearing?
The winter general is a design perma.
It's clear.
If you don't have a clear head like this, I can't touch it.
I understand.
What kind of clothes are you wearing?
It's a side split.
Is it a side split?
If you split it too much, you'll be told to take it off from there.
Sometimes from here.
I'm thinking.
The winter general.
What kind of clothes are you wearing?
Mostly.
T-shirt.
Mostly T-shirt.
The winter general is wearing a T-shirt.
What kind of T-shirt are you wearing?
It's a movie of skulls.
What kind of underwear are you wearing?
Vintage fashion.
The winter general is very tight.
It's a historical record.
I'm going to do it this time because I know it.