The first time, the child's use is not enough.
The 94th Sokesson, the natural botanist grand prize.
Mr. Matsumoto, the judge.
Yes, I'm the judge.
What's the matter today?
Well, I don't know.
I'm sorry, I don't really understand.
I'm the judge.
I think it's a very easy-to-understand project to decide the number one of this year's natural botanist grand prize.
Let me introduce you to the three nominated people.
Now, audience, please.
Let me introduce you again.
First of all, this is Mr. Yamasaki Hosei.
And next to him is Mr. Koda Shin.
And last but not least, Tetsu-chan from Degas.
Thank you for having me.
Mr. Matsumoto, why are these people nominated?
Well, the schedule was open, wasn't it?
Today, I came to my friend, Mr. Hamayan and Mr. Matsumoto.
Tetsu-chan, you look very nervous.
No, I'm not nervous.
No, I'm not nervous at all. I'm relaxed.
You just came out, but your expression is strange.
I'm relaxed.
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
Well, Mr. Matsumoto, let's get started.
First of all, let's listen to the lecture.
Mr. Matsumoto, this is a natural skill.
Yes, it's something that ordinary people like us can't understand.
It's something we can't think of.
The first question is this.
Japan passing.
Come on.
The phone is ringing.
The phone is fast.
Go ahead.
Oh, Japan passing.
You are Japan passing.
How do you live in a dirty city?
What do you want to do?
How is it?
It's okay.
Mr. Hamayan is talking now.
I just saw a
biscuit.
If you don't mind, you can eat it, but it will be gone in a second.
Next.
Can you do that?
Yes, I can do it with Japan passing.
Please.
So if Mr. Degawa can do it.
One, two, one, two.
Japan passing.
I've been told that until now.
Go for it.
The history of Japan is.
Congratulations on your 1st anniversary.
The bad atmosphere has gone away.
It's gone.
Mr. Yamasaki also got a biscuit on his 1st anniversary.
Oh, Kouda.
Kouda, are you okay?
It's Japan passing.
You gave me my life.
What kind of song is that?
Here's the next question.
Are you okay?
When I was in the 3rd grade, you were in the 1st grade.
You always take the lead.
Go for it.
I'm sorry for the pass.
No, no, go for it.
It's a great honor to give.
Why are you in the 3rd grade?
I'm a classmate from downtown.
Mr. Negawa.
I'll change the momentum.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Yamasaki came out.
Shall we go?
Yes.
When I was in the 3rd grade.
Talk to me.
You're in the 1st grade, aren't you?
What?
Don't talk to me.
When I was in the 3rd grade.
I'm sorry.
Go for it, Kouda.
When I was in the 3rd grade.
The next question is,
I'm sorry for the pass.
Go for it, Kouda.
Thank you very much.
You can't just give the pass.
You have to give the pass back.
That's right.
You can give the pass back.
I want you to aim for this.
Go for it, Kouda.
It's a hint.
I'll pay you.
That's all.
I've never seen such a hint.
I have a warabi mochi for you.
It's a warabi mochi.
Kouda, it's 100 years old.
Thank you very much.
Yamasaki, please.
Please don't be shy.
I'm a shiba inu.
What have you been doing lately?
He's saying, I'm a shiba inu.
Go for it, Kouda.
It's 4000 years old.
Thank you very much.
I'm a shiba inu.
Next, Degawa.
Hey, hey.
You're Kato-chan, aren't you?
Isn't that right?
I know how you feel.
I have no choice.
I'll give you a hint.
Here I go.
What's the meaning of this?
It's like this.
Kouda Shin.
I'm in trouble.
Is it wrong?
Here I go.
What's the meaning of this, Chikubi-chan?
I'm sorry.
You're still in trouble.
I'm in trouble, Chikubi-chan.
It's U.
U?
Yes.
U!
I'm in trouble.
U...
U!
The flower road of the Ukiyo stage is both the front and the back.
That's the joke.
Please say it with Ha.
I'll do it like this.
The eye-contact is different.
It's more cloudy than before.
Ha-
Ha-tsunai-ki-
Ha-tsunai-ki-yossha-yossha
That's good.
Yamazaki-kun, let's go.
Are you going to do it again?
18 more laps.
There will be a problem.
Yakult!
Yes.
You have to say it. What's the last one?
It's Yakult.
Tonjiru.
That's good.
It's natural.
Tonjiru.
You said Tonjiru.
I can't do it.
This may be popular.
I'll do it.
Re-re-re-re-re Oshiba-da!
Da.
It's Da.
Are you going to do it again?
I'm going to do it.
Are you going to do it?
I can't help it.
If you get this wrong, your body will hurt.
My body hurts.
I don't know what to do.
Let's go.
The winner of the 1994 Tennenpoken is...
Udo-kun from Kyain.
Matsumotochi.
Hello.
This year is almost over.
It's over.
It's amazing.
This program doesn't air at all.
There's a little bit.
It's hard.
I heard.
Why do celebrities go abroad?
Do they go to Hawaii?
The mystery has been solved.
Why?
Actually, over there.
There's a little party for celebrities.
That's a delicious party.
That's right.
You can't do it in Japan.
Celebrities meet in Hawaii and introduce each other.
They often become a couple there.
There's such a thing.
That's why I'm here.
That's what I heard.
That's why.
Go away.
I see.
Why are you all here?
Is that true information?
That's true information.
I can't believe it.
Is that so?
When I heard that, I was relieved.
Why are you relieved?
I had a question.
Why?
There was a big question mark.
Go away.
Well, that's right.
Why?
I might be mistaken.
That's enough.
I'm very popular.
That's right.
But go away.
But if you're on air,
If I come as a New Year's entertainer, I'm a fool.
I'm very cool.
I'm coming.
When people see me on air,
They can't see me.
My face turns red.
I'm sure there are tourists behind you.
Did you have a party?
My face turns red all the time in Hawaii.
Who's doing the kanji?
You mean this?
That's right.
It's strange, isn't it?
A sports player and a talent entertainer.
Why do they hang out with each other?
I'm an entertainer myself, so I can't help it.
What's that?
There's an announcement for each entertainer.
At the end of the year,
Is there a paper with a date, place and time?
How is it?
I don't care at all.
Tell me.
There must be a dark route.
There is.
I'm so angry.
I'm hated.
There's a kanji.
And there's a guy who moves around.
What should I do this year?
This and this.
Someone said, take them off.
downtown
downtown?
If you wear a mask, you'll be in trouble.
I'm sick.
Are you saying it's my fault?
That's right.
Do you have a disease?
I'm sure you do.
If you ask me how I got to know you,
I'll tell you about my acquaintance.
That's my acquaintance.
That's a party in Hawaii.
Everyone wears a mask like this.
That's right.
They're wearing glasses.
Actresses and actors don't act in dramas.
They do.
That's strange.
Right?
Everyone does.
But the actor's friend is a celebrity.
Party?
I don't know if the actor's friend is a celebrity.
What?
I don't get it.
They're dating.
Even though they don't know each other.
But he's an actor.
I don't know if there's a way to introduce him.
I don't get it.
Why don't you get it?
Are you stupid?
That happens.
Really?
Right?
Not just in Hawaii.
I solved a mystery with this.
I want you to show your face.
I can't tell you to participate.
Wait a minute.
He gave me a mask.
I don't get it.
Let's figure it out.
But you don't get it.
I don't get it.
He gave me a mask.
You don't get it even if he gave you a mask.
Are you stupid?
Seriously.
I'll look it up.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for today.
I don't get it.
If it's like this,
I'll use the route.
I'm in Hawaii.
But...
I'll support you.
I don't get it.
Yuta's part at the party.
He's not in Hawaii.
But I don't know how many people will come.
I don't get it.
I'll sleep.
I thought this was a party.
But when I arrived, I was so nervous.
I thought I was going to die.
That's a real party.
The other day,
Yes.
I sent you that.
Kudasanta.
That's...
The AV mosaic is gone.
No, no, no.
That's Super 8 or something.
You have the opportunity to make the AV disappear.
What?
I gave it back.
Why?
Because I couldn't see it.
It's a little thin.
There's an area.
Everyone, listen carefully and go home.
You see the AV, right?
There's something like this at the game center.
I have to match it with the place I want to see.
I have to grab that lever.
I want to grab a different lever.
I see.
You want to grab your own lever.
That's right.
You want to grab a machine.
I can only do the same thing.
Right hand and left hand.
So if the lever is like this,
I can do this.
No, really, really.
I can only move in parallel.
That's weird.
I don't understand.
And it doesn't look that clear.
That's why I said, let's stop.
Stop? Who are you talking to?
Who are you talking to?
It's peaceful.
What are you talking about?
Please put me on.
What do you mean, please put me on?
There are about three cushions behind the car.
Please put me on.
Three cushions.
The one with Santa Claus.
If I get it right, I'll send it to you.
What are you talking about?
You don't know that.
I'm personally sending it to you.
If I say something like this,
Please put me on.
I sent it to you.
Where did you put it?
Showa Shell.
I put gas in the Showa Shell.
Please put me on.
I want a lie detector.
It was sold somewhere.
Really?
I wonder how accurate it is.
I don't think it's going to work.
Nishin people give me a lot of things.
If you say it.
I have a sleeping bag for Robocop.
I gave it to you.
I have a sleeping bag for Yakisoba.
Yakisoba's toothbrush.
Please put me on.
I went to see boxing the other day.
Oh, that's right.
Tatsuyoshi.
Yes.
After that, I called him to my room.
It's amazing.
After it's over.
Boxers haven't had a fight since then.
It's all over the place.
My nose is broken.
My hands are broken.
It's been like this all the time.
It's amazing.
You don't have anything.
No, I talk a lot.
The couple is funny.
It's been two hours since the world war ended.
What are we going to do tomorrow?
My wife said,
You have to clean my house.
Do it for me.
Unlike men, women charm men in two places, the face and the chest.
Where do women get excited when they see men?
What do you mean?
I don't understand.
When a man looks at a woman, he looks at the face and the chest.
Where do you look at a woman?
Where do you judge?
First of all, you shouldn't talk.
Really?
You shouldn't talk to a beautiful woman.
I'm the one who gets angry when I talk to a beautiful woman.
Do you think you're beautiful?
I'm beautiful, but...
I'm a man of my word.
What kind of man of your word is allowed?
Rakugo is a man of his word.
No, I...
I went to work the other day.
I really want to go out with a woman like that.
I've been playing with you all the time.
What?
When you look at a woman, where do you look at first?
If you look at her like this, you can't see her at all.
Then I'll look at her face.
No, I'm talking about the face.
I can't even look at a woman like that.
Where do you look at?
I look at the legs.
Where are the legs?
One centimeter square, right?
One centimeter square...
Please check it out.
That's weird, too.
What do you mean check it out?
You're talking about the legs...
The calves.
Are you looking at the calves right away?
No, I can't do it unless my legs are beautiful.
What?
But I'm not as big as I always say.
I'm not as big as I always say.
No, I'm not as big as I always say.
But you know, like in the AV.
You're fat, but you're big.
That's true.
If you're that fat, you're big, too.
That's funny.
Let's use the word again.
If you're that fat, you're big, too.
That's funny.
You know, Max.
Everyone knows Max.
What do you think golf is?
I think it's the beautiful soul that flies away.
The soul that flies away.
Yes, when you see the soul that flies away.
That's what I think.
Mentally.
Where is your max when you sleep with a girl?
I think it's the last one.
The whole time?
The whole time.
But it depends on the person.
There are people who don't do that.
They're really elegant.
They don't kill bugs.
When I open my legs like that.
That's what I think.
I don't really like to hear this from the audience.
I'm having a lot of fun.