.
You picked up a
hungry,
hungry tonkatsu.
I can't do it.
Are you reading the same thing?
What kind of coincidence is this?
I'm scared.
Be quiet.
Can you stop doing this to me?
My whole heart is ruined.
You're blabbering.
It's a coincidence.
I can't bear it.
You can't do that.
What's going on?
One, two, three...
Ouch!
What's wrong?
What is it?
It's a syringe.
A syringe?
It's noisy.
It's a syringe.
What is this?
I don't know what it means.
One, two, three...
Ouch!
Can you help me, Hamada?
What?
Please put a syringe on it.
I'll hold it.
Can you help me, Hamada?
Don't make a sound.
Can you take it off?
I don't know what it means.
I don't like it here.
It stinks.
What should I do?
I'll help you.
It stinks.
What are you doing?
Be careful.
What is it?
I don't know what it means.
What?
I'm scared.
Don't move.
OK.
Let's go.
I'll hold it.
Don't move.
Be quiet.
Where do you think you're going?
Follow the rules.
It's dangerous.
That's enough.
I don't like it here.
I'm scared.
Don't move.
Put it on yourself.
Look at the screen.
It's cold.
I can hear it faintly.
I'm going crazy.
Don't talk so much.
It's small.
Your nipples are so small.
It's scary.
It's not about the nipples.
Be quiet.
Don't talk so much.
What is this?
It hurts.
It's spinning.
That spin is painful.
It looks good.
This is a little better.
This hurts a lot.
It's not about the left and right.
I'm scared.
I'm scared of my nipples.
Oh, no.
I'm going crazy.
Don't talk so much.
It hurts.
What is this?
This is a good flow.
This is good.
Please put this on.
Excuse me.
Please take a good look.
Please put this on.
I'm going crazy.
This is a good flow.
Please put this on.
I'm not confident.
I'm scared.
I'm going crazy.
One, two, three.
I'm really scared.
I'm sweating.
I don't like this.
I won.
I'm sweating.
I don't like this.
I'm really scared.
I'm going to run away next time.
Last one.
Why?
New York and Matsumoto.
Let's open one by one.
What's that?
Let's choose first.
It's a pattern that can be chosen.
Really?
Who will go first?
Can you go first?
From Yama-chan.
Put it down.
1 in 3 minutes.
Which one?
This is Matsumoto-san.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors with three people.
Let's start with the winner.
There are two here.
I can't do it.
I can't do it today.
That's where the story started.
Rock-paper-scissors with three people.
Rock-paper-scissors.
I don't like this.
It's not good either.
It's not a nipple?
It looks like a face.
Isn't it a nipple?
That's not a nipple.
It's a nipple.
Put it on.
It hurts!
You!
It's a face.
It's not a nipple.
It's a nipple.
I'm ready.
Let's do it.
It's a face.
What is this?
It's not a nipple.
It's a face.