From now on, we will begin the second trial of Akihiro Onuma.
Prosecutors and lawyers, please come forward.
Next, the defendant, Akihiro Onuma, please come forward.
Hmm? Wait a minute.
Lately, everyone has been talking about me, so I might as well treat them to a meal.
Alright, you guys. I'll take you to a meal.
What? You're going to treat us to a meal?
Yay!
Eddie is happy that Onuma is going to treat us to a meal.
However, Yoshinoya is the one who is going to treat Onuma.
Welcome.
What should I have?
Should I have a large serving?
Excuse me, I'll have a large serving.
Excuse me, Nami-mitsu.
Hmm?
Onuma is insisting on ordering Nami.
Eddie has decided to follow suit.
And...
Let's eat.
It's delicious.
I'll have some oshinko.
Where are you opening it?
How much do you want me to pay?
I don't mind if it's just a little ginger.
Onuma is angry at the 50-yen oshinko.
And the next day...
Yesterday, a young man treated us to a meal.
I'm so jealous.
As for this case, we'll have a witness.
Is that alright?
Please come forward.
This is terrible.
As a junior, I'll treat you to a meal.
For example, you two.
I'll treat you to a meal.
You'll be happy, right?
Yes, I'll be happy.
I won't tell you what to eat.
I'll just tell you to eat.
I want to grab your heart.
What?
That's how it is.
That's how it feels.
Is there anything else?
Onuma often asks me to buy this and that.
He asks me to go shopping.
He says I can buy anything I want.
I see.
You can buy anything you want.
Yes, but...
I don't have anything I want.
Just for me?
Or when I don't have enough.
Really?
Stand up.
What do you mean?
I'm telling you to buy anything you want.
But you're giving me so much.
If I tell you what I want to eat,
and you calculate it,
you'll have a lot left.
What do you mean, I don't have enough?
I knew this before,
but he doesn't know how valuable shopping is.
I think I've known him for 20 years.
The kids are playing around.
Matsumoto is dead.
It's a virtual reality show.
It's when they're telling their goodbyes
in the setting of Matsumoto is dead.
I'm going to drink it up.
What should I do?
What should I do to make them accept?
Onuma is having a hard time
because he can't think of anything funny.
While he's doing that, the rehearsal starts.
Okay, let's start the rehearsal.
And then, Eddie...
What?
Suddenly, everyone around him is laughing.
That was funny.
If we do that in real life,
I'm sure we can do it.
Really?
Onuma, who has been watching this all along,
had a creepy smile on his face.
And finally, it's time for the real show.
The recording is going well,
and the order of Onuma has been changed.
I wanted to end it with Matsumoto.
What?
The recording has been cut.
What do you think of this?
This is not a gold coin.
It's not a gold coin, but it's a kind of...
It's bigger than that.
That's right. It's a big sin.
It's a person's property.
I'd like to ask Onuma about this.
This is completely messed up.
I think there's a misunderstanding.
I was going to do that before the recording.
That's a lie.
Then let's do it like that.
I've been in the entertainment industry for a long time.
I happened to be in the entertainment industry.
But if someone younger than me does it,
I'll do it in a different way.
I see.
That's an AD.
What do you think about that?
There's a saying that laughter is like water.
What do you mean?
That's...
Don't say that in front of us.
That's a great statement.
A staff room for kids.
As usual, there are a few people in the meeting room.
This is a meeting, isn't it?
What?
Well...
If it's a meeting, I'll pay for it even if I eat.
Okay.
Then I'll take the delivery.
Onuma, who made sure he didn't pay for it,
ordered a delivery to the AD.
I'll have a beef curry.
Okay.
And after 30 minutes, the delivery curry I ordered arrived.
Thank you for waiting.
This is Onuma's.
What?
Wait a minute.
That's strange.
Why do you have more curry?
What do you mean?
I ordered a large serving.
What?
Why did you order a large serving?
Idiot!
In the end, Onuma took a large serving from the AD.
It's delicious.
Hello.
Please come in.
Please explain the situation of the delivery.
The curry will be delivered, right?
One person is out of the chair.
I'm looking at the roux.
It's Miyadai-ku.
That's amazing.
I think it's amazing.
Stand up.
Please stop the roux.
Excuse me.
Do you have any objections?
Objections?
Obviously, the amount is clear.
It was the same beef curry.
I didn't ask you.
You can compare the amount, right?
Why do you compare?
Why do you compare the amount?
I ordered the same thing, so I thought the amount would be the same.
When I checked the amount, it was clearly different.
So I didn't ask you why you ordered a large serving.
I was told that I ordered a large serving.
You ordered a large serving, so the amount is different.
I think the VTR is a little too much.
Actually, I ordered the same amount.
I didn't order a large serving.
You ordered a large serving.
I ordered the same amount.
You ordered a large serving, so the amount is different.
Please stop the roux.
Why do you do that?
It's strange to see it like this.
It's strange.
It's a habit.
Habit?
The person who ordered the large serving has more rice than usual.
This is natural.
There is a lot of roux.
That's right.
So you can eat it deliciously.
If you remove the roux, there is a lot of rice left.
That's right.
The roux.
I see.
I don't think that's the case.
That was a good sound.
I have evidence that the large serving is a fake.
Let's take a look.
This is a kid's hat.
Do you know this?
I made this four years ago.
At that time, the large serving was not a kid's hat.
Why is that?
There is a reason for this.
At that time, I was working with the Invention Shogun.
We were in the same family.
Did you hear that?
What is it?
There is a strange English word.
Where did you get it from?
The staff room.
Which staff room?
There is a staff room for the Invention Shogun and the kid's hat.
The same staff room?
Yes.
There?
There.
This?
I put it there.
You put it there?
That's strange.
Where did you put it?
Did you put it in a bag?
No.
I put it in a cardboard box.
Last time, I stole a lunch box from someone's show.
I'm scared.
My fingers are going to bend.
Let's stop.
Here is the evidence that this guy is the most stingy.
This is a cell phone.
It's been 11 digits for four months, but it's still a 10-digit number.
I don't need it, so I can't change it.
That's right.
Even when I call, the 030 number comes up, right?
I look at it, pick up the phone on the desk, fix it to 090, and call.
That's amazing.
It's an amazing first aid bag.
I've been using this for almost a year, but the cumulative fee is 33,000 yen.
What?
In a year?
It's 33,000 yen in a year?
I've only been using it for 33,000 yen.
This is Mago-gyaru.
Mago-gyaru?
Is that it?
What do you do with your phone?
Do you have it?
I don't think I have a tele-card.
This is the evidence.
You wrote it well.
This is also evidence.
This is evidence.
I knew it.
Wait a minute.
That's all you say.
Isn't this Amex's gold card?
What's wrong with this?
This is made by a normal person, right?
Who is it?
It's mine.
It says Onuma Akihiro.
What's your gold card?
It's amazing.
It's not over yet.
Is there more?
It's not like this.
Please watch the next video.
One day, the producer...
I'm sorry, but I can't use the taxi ticket anymore.
Please tell everyone.
I understand.
The producer told the staff.
I'm sorry, but I can't use the taxi ticket anymore.
Please tell everyone.
It can't be helped.
The staff agrees that it is due to the influence of the storm in recent years.
I'm sorry, but I can't use the taxi ticket anymore.
Please tell everyone.
What?
What do you mean?
The taxi ticket won't come out.
I'm just telling you what to do.
Please tell the producer.
I'm sorry, but I can't use the taxi ticket anymore.
Please tell everyone.
It can't be helped.
It wasn't the producer.
It was Onuma Akihiro.
The producer came to him.
Hey, Onuma.
I think you've heard of it.
Please tell everyone about the taxi ticket.
It's okay.
It can't be helped.
He's a real man.
Did you meet him?
I saw him.
Please explain.
It wasn't all of them, but some of them were like that.
It was a contact.
I heard that.
I thought it couldn't be helped.
Only Onuma came to me.
I thought he would come by car.
I told him to drop me off at the parking lot.
You're a woman.
That's the worst.
Please tell everyone about Onuma's car.
He doesn't gamble.
I told him I was going to start gambling soon.
I told him I bought a horse ticket.
I asked him.
I asked him to buy a horse ticket twice as much as 1.2 times.
I'm serious.
I think he bought a copy of the book.
The copy of the book is very low.
It's very hard.
I don't want to lose it.
It's a bad place.
Did you get it?
Thanks to you.
I'm so bad.
I'm like a town girl.
This is the last time.
This is also human nature.
There are various things.
Please watch it.
One day, a producer came to AD.
Do you want to go golfing next time?
Really? I'll go.
AD was invited to play golf for the first time.
This is my first time playing golf.
I'll do my best.
AD, who doesn't have a golf club, called his parents.
He borrowed a golf club from his father.
Dad, I'm going to play golf next time.
Can you lend me a golf club?
Are you going to start playing golf?
Then I'll buy you a new golf club.
Really?
His father, who was impressed by his son's growth, gave him a golf club as a gift.
And on the day of golf...
I'll do my best at this new club today.
And then...
What is it at a time like this?
Yes, hello.
Hello, it's a big swamp.
You're free now, right?
I have a problem with my battery.
Please come to the car now.
Now?
That's right.
You're free, aren't you?
Be quiet.
Wait a minute.
I don't know if I can make it in time for golf.
AD went to the scene without being disobeyed by his seniors.
Thank you for waiting, Onuma.
It's too late.
Hurry up and connect the battery.
I'm in a hurry.
But the battery size is different between Onuma's Benz and my car.
I can't do it.
It's okay.
But I think it's better to call Jaff.
Shut up.
If you call him, he'll pay.
Hurry up.
Onuma can't help but connect the battery.
Look, it's working.
I'm in a hurry.
See you later.
But I'll make it in time for golf.
AD looks at Onuma and hurries to golf.
But...
What?
The engine doesn't start.
I can't go to golf with this.
In the end, AD left the car on the road.
He gave up golf and took a taxi home.
And the next day, he went to pick up his car.
What?
There's no car.
The car was damaged.
AD couldn't go to the golf he was looking forward to.
What should I do?
AD called Onuma and explained the situation.
Then...
I understand the situation, but is it my fault?
You're not going to take money from me, are you?
What?
This is a big problem.
This is...
Here you are.
This is your compensation.
Please.
The car repair fee.
The battery is gone.
I bought it for 40,000 yen.
This is a fine for parking.
15,000 yen.
This is 84,000 yen.
I bought it because I wanted my car to have a good battery.
I want my car to have a good battery.
What do you think?
Did you buy the battery?
Did you buy it?
No, I didn't buy it.
You didn't buy it?
Why are you lying?
You'll find out soon.
What do you think?
I didn't buy it.
You're lying.
I bought it for you.
You spent almost 100,000 yen.
I went to the scene.
The situation after that...
Why were you in such a hurry?
I went shopping.
That was the last thing I bought.
That's a bargain.
Is that a bargain?
Did you want to bargain?
That's terrible.
You're amazing.
This is not a burden.
I don't think it's a burden.
It's worse than last time.
My heart is broken.
This is a serious matter.
That's all.
Please go to another room.
There's no point in going to another room.