It's the O-san team!
Do you have any experience?
I don't have any.
You don't, right?
I have almost no experience.
Did you do it?
Yes, I did.
Where did you do it?
What do you mean?
Where was the position?
What?
Po?
Position.
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
You don't have any experience.
Do you want to do it right away?
Do you have a judge?
I don't have one.
Oh, you have one.
Thank you.
From now on,
this coin, 100 yen, will be yours.
Are you listening to me?
Shut up!
You stole it!
You stole it, didn't you?
Ready!
Why did you do that?
You just need to whistle.
That's right.
I have to say everything?
Ready!
I can't hold this ball.
Stand up!
It hurts so much.
From here.
When I was doing it,
it wasn't like this.
I didn't even have a ball.
What are you doing?
Ready!
Go!
I'm scared.
It hurts.
From here.
Is this funny?
It hurts so much.
Ready!
Go!
I didn't tell the office
when I left the key.
I was calling for this.
Who are you?
Hey!
Mom!
Goal!
We won!
18-0.
The Hammers win.
You played.
I did.
Look at that.
Superball.
I've never seen it.
You played.
You look like an old hero.
Who's that?
Let's have three players from my team.
What's that?
Let's do it.
Sure.
We're going to borrow your chest.
Really?
I see.
Look at me.
My muscles are like art.
They're so beautiful.
You can't see this beauty on TV.
Who's that?
He's from Harvard.
From Harvard?
Yes.
I'm going to borrow your chest.
Goal!
What's going on?
I thought you were going to come.
At first...
I don't know much about amateurs.
What's going on?
I get it now.
Goal!
This is not how I do it.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
This is not how I do it.
Really?
I see.
I used to do this with my neck.
Thank you so much.
Come back again.
I'll go eat something.
Thank you.
I'll show you another one.
What are you doing?
I'm doing business.
Ladies and gentlemen.
To be honest, how do you feel?
When you come out of the bar, people are screaming, right?
Are you happy about that?
Or are you not happy about it?
I'd be happy if it was a normal voice like now.
Sometimes there are people who sound a bit painful.
They're like, I'll say something, just remember it!
It's a bit tough to be made to understand that kind of thing.
I was really angry the other day.
It's been a while.
I was angry after a long time.
I was driving.
There were a lot of traffic lights.
The fans were standing there.
Even on my way home, it was like that.
I wanted to receive the fan letters as much as I could.
No, no, no.
What's so funny?
The traffic lights stop, right?
Then the big ones gather.
I don't think you can do it.
I can open the window.
When you open the window, the empty space is dug in.
I was really angry.
It turned red and blue.
I closed the window.
When I was about to close the window, a video came out.
And you stopped it.
The video was stuck in the window.
I thought it was going to come out again.
I opened the window and the video came out.
It's terrible!
You guys!
I don't want to do that.
What are you doing?
It's a sudden pose.
Wait a minute.
I don't want to do that.
If it were you, you wouldn't have done that.
I'm sure the video came out of the window.
I'm sure the video came out of your mouth.
When you get in the car, I think you'll understand how I feel for the first time.
You always say,
It's dangerous.
Be careful.
Don't say that.
It's dangerous.
Be careful.
I'm sure it's a lie.
Why do you want so many fans?
I'm angry with that commercial.
The one with Yuji Oda.
I opened the window and the video came out of my mouth.
What is that?
I'm angry with that commercial.
Idiot.
How annoying would you be if you did that?
I think some idiot would be like,
I don't think we understood that.
When I was a kid, I didn't drive a car.
I don't know how important it is.
I drew a lot of things with a marker.
I drew the door on one side.
It was a delivery truck.
I was driving all the time.
It says rice here.
I don't understand.
I don't think I can drive it myself.
If you did that, you wouldn't complain so much.
You shouldn't complain now.
You're dirty.
I don't understand myself.
I don't like it when someone does that to me.
Why?
I always have Maria on my shoulder.
What?
I don't like that.
I have some contradictions.
For example,
if I had a daughter when I was young,
I would take good care of her.
I don't like that.
If I had 12 daughters,
I would take good care of them.
I don't like that.
I've done that before.
Were you taking care of her?
No, I wasn't.
I wasn't taking care of her.
You're a criminal.
You should go to college.
For example,
if I had a girlfriend,
I couldn't get mad at her.
I've done that before.
It doesn't matter if she has a girlfriend or not.
My father is strict with me.
I can't get mad at him.
Hello.
My name is Matsumoto.
What kind of relationship do you have?
What should I say?
For example,
if you're a friend of my school...
I'll say that I'm a friend of your school.
But what kind of friend are you?
You keep attacking me with questions.
You push me away.
What are you talking about?
I can't avoid you.
What are you doing?
Don't take it back.
You're talking about my daughter.
I can say that.
My parents know that my daughter is mean.
So I don't want to talk about it.
I don't want to talk about it.
In a different sense.
But it is obvious that my daughter is mean.
But parents don't notice it.
It's not that they don't notice it.
When I was in elementary school, I was still cute.
When I was in middle school and high school,
as a parent,
I was like,
I'm home.
But when I was a married man,
I looked at my daughter and said,
Look at my dad.
Ah, look at that.
It's become so hard these days.
The color of your forehead has changed.
Don't say it out loud, dad.
Don't say it out loud!
I know that.
But look at that, dad.
There's that kind of thing, right?
Yes, there is.
Say it out loud.
Ah, it's so hard.
You're so big.
If you say it out loud, it'll be so smelly.
That's true.
Even for celebrities,
there are some girls who get married and get a daughter.
It's so hard.
And they appear on morning TV shows as their parents.
It's so hard!
The host can't even get this far.
Don't say it out loud!
Say it out loud!
This is the hardest thing I've ever done.
It's that person.
It's that guy.
His daughter is a gorilla.
Are you serious?
I've never seen that.
That's why I'm sitting here.
I was so surprised.
I wonder why he's here.
He's smiling right next to me.
What's that?
What?
I'm going to tell you everything.
And...
He's a f***ing old man.
Everyone thinks of him as an old man.
He's a middle-aged man.
The girl I married the other day
is also a weirdo.
She's a weirdo.
But if you marry her,
she'll fall in love with you at first sight.
If you were asked to change your nickname
from a 30-year-old to Machan-Hama-chan,
what would you change it to?
In my case,
there's still downtown.
But I...
But I'll change it to Machan-Hama-chan when I'm 30.
When I'm 30,
I'll change it to Kurohyo.
Don't talk!
Why do you keep saying Kurohyo?
That's not cool.
Who are you talking to?
Kurohyo?
You're not 30 yet.
I'll tell you when I'm 30.
Have you thought of something?
What is it?
Poison scorpion.
You're a pervert.
Why didn't you say it sooner?
I said poison scorpion.
That's not cool.
Downtown's Kurohyo and poison scorpion.
It'll go poof!
It will?
Who will?
The fluttering part around the pillow...
It's the cover!
When you buy it at a futon shop, they sell that.
So everyone buys a cover and puts it on.
But at the time of sale, the pillow is already like this.
From the moment it's like this, does it have a cover?
It does, right?
I don't think so.
Why?
There are some that don't have it, and some that do.
Not all of them have it.
But still, it's a cover.
The one with the fluttering part is usually a male.
And the one without it is a female.
What?
You think a fluttering part is a female because it looks like one, right?
That's not true.
The one with it is a male.
The one without it is a female.
The one with it is a female.
It's a cover.
You are such a fool.
Is that so?
The one with it is a female.
It's a cover.
So Miku...
Who are you talking about?
Where did you get those three?
I tried wearing them.
What is the white thing under the nail of your finger?
It's on the nail.
I don't have it at all.
See?
You are such a fool.
You don't know?
No, I don't.
Why not?
I can see the bone of your finger clearly.
Wait!
It doesn't matter because I can see it.
If you can see it, you can tell how dark it is.
What do you mean by that?
I know it so well.
It's the same as a pot.
What do you mean?
It doesn't matter because I can see it.
Does it matter?
That means you don't have a bone.
I do.
I don't have a bone.
Happy birthday to you.
I'm so embarrassed.
Let's sing at least until the end.
Happy birthday to you.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
Are you watching Fuji TV?
This is the birthday cake.
He is sleeping.
Hitoshi.
Congratulations.
Hitoshi, can you calm down?
How many times have you been on this show?
Four times.
Did you start when you were 26?
Yes.
If you do this, I'll hit you.
I've never done that.
Actually, I have a present for you.
What is it?
What is this?
It's a water bottle for Sugata.
It's from Yamazaki.
Is that so?
A toast.
Keep up the good work.