Today, we're here.
It's like we're being called.
We're being called here.
Hotel Charum.
It's Hotel Charum.
We're supposed to wait here at the parking lot.
Is that so?
I don't know.
This is a love hotel, right?
It's a love hotel.
There's also an air-conditioner.
If we wait here...
Is there something fun?
Today's star is going to appear.
Why are we being called?
Well...
I'm sure you're confident.
Is that so?
I think you can guess who it is.
You're on this show, but you're being called.
Anyway, at the love hotel parking lot,
we were told to wait.
There's a car coming in.
Good morning.
Is this guy being called?
Yes, this guy.
It's not me.
Good morning.
Listen to me.
What is it?
Today's opening.
I came up with it.
Please use it.
Is it a project to attract people?
It's a project to attract people.
Please use it.
I thought about it.
I'm in my 30s.
You're not in your 30s.
I'm not in my 30s.
I'm in my 30s.
You're in your 30s.
I'm going to be an old man.
If I think about it,
I can't get out of downtown.
I see.
Even if I continue to be a celebrity,
I can go to a good place like downtown.
That's great.
But I can't get out.
I see.
I'll give you a character.
A character?
Yes.
What is it?
Super dirty.
Is there anyone who sells that?
I've heard that kind of legend.
Is that so?
Super dirty.
It's just a legend.
But it's a little thing.
You can't be super dirty.
That's right.
Don't be crazy.
What?
Dori.
Oh, this guy.
I'm serious.
Can you sell that?
I'm going to do something special today.
I'm looking forward to it.
Show me your partner.
My partner?
He's in the car right now.
I came with him.
What is it?
Yamada-san.
It's a surprise.
I'm going to do this today.
It's cute.
Yamada-san.
Yes.
I want you to see this.
This program is brought to you by the sponsor you are watching.
I'm in a hotel room right now.
That's right.
I'm wondering if I can really see the legendary super dirty.
This is all private.
Yes.
Let's go, Sumire-chan.
I don't like this room.
It's big.
Look at this.
It's called Sumire-chan.
It's a cute name.
Let's sit down.
Come here.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Look at this.
Really?
I don't know.
It's still early.
Wait a minute.
Sumire-chan.
What is this picture?
What do you like about Sumire-chan?
Look at this.
I can't stand it anymore.
Sumire-chan, I can't stand it.
I want to go out with you.
Don't put a video of you dating.
what?
What are you doing?
Stop it.
Look at this.
Sumire-chan.
Please forgive us.
Dad and mom.
Do you want to buy something?
Sumire-chan.
What's wrong with you, Sumire-chan?
Show me your bag.
What is this?
I like you.
Come here.
What is this?
What's wrong with you?
Don't you like me?
Show me your bag.
Why are you here?
You know that, don't you?
You don't like me, do you?
I don't like you.
I'm going to take a shower.
Wait a minute.
I'll be right back.
It felt good.
Did you take a shower?
Come here.
Ouch.
What are you doing now?
What are you doing?
Don't do that.
You scratched me.
You look like this.
Did you take a shower?
Let's take a picture of Sumire-chan.
You are cute.
Look at me.
I like the way you tie your ribbon.
Take a picture of me.
Why are you so angry?
How is Sumire-chan?
Did Sumire-chan take a shower?
Sumire-chan, don't do that.
Don't break your promise.
You are so mean.
Come here.
What did you say?
You are so mean.
You are funny.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Are you tired?
Drink something.
I'm not tired.
Really?
I thought you were tired.
What are you talking about?
I'm not tired.
Sumire-chan is acting like a fool.
He is acting like a fool.
You are acting like a fool.
That's not true.
It's hard to act in a drama.
From the third time, it's 38%.
That's not true.
I went to the filming site.
The atmosphere is different from variety shows.
That's not true.
Why are you so quiet?
Especially before the show.
I can't do that.
Really?
I experienced it for the first time.
Is that so?
Did something happen?
Dreams are strange.
Why do people dream?
I don't know.
It has nothing to do with dreams.
People dream even if they don't think about it.
That's right.
Recently, I dreamed of Miyazawa Rie.
With Rie-mama.
In my dream, Rie-mama and I were in the corridor.
I was angry.
I fell in love with Rie-mama.
Why do people dream?
I used to be like that.
What?
I dreamed of Yashiro Aki.
I fell in love with Rie-mama.
I feel good.
When I wake up, I feel empty.
Sometimes I fall in love with Rie-mama.
I used to be like this.
Is that true?
Yes.
In winter, I used to kick the stove.
That's true.
I dreamed of a taxi driver.
I used to fight with a taxi driver.
That's true.
I dreamed of a taxi driver.
I used to kick the stove.
At that time, I was walking on the cliff.
I fell in love with Rie-mama.
I used to be like this.
Now you live in a big house.
That's true.
What is this?
I don't know yet.
I don't know either.
It's really strange.
Don't write it.
Well.
What do you think?
There is no such thing.
What is it?
I don't know.
Please show me the picture.
Yes.
I can't say anything.
Time is running out.
This is a question for Mr. Matsumoto, who has travelled around the world twice.
Yes.
In Japanese toilets there are only Japanese-style toilets.
Are there only these two toilets around the world?
No such thing.
They exist.
What is that?
What kind of toilet is it?
There are many types of toilets.
You can see various cultures.
Don't say such boring things.
Where was it?
Was it when I went to New Zealand?
It's kind of easy, isn't it?
I went deeper into New Zealand.
Where did you go deeper into?
I went up to the 23rd floor.
Okay!
I went into a fairly secluded area of New Zealand.
The 23rd floor?
Yes, I went there.
That was amazing.
I think it was right in the middle.
Oh, I see.
The area between the Japanese and Western countries.
What was it like? Were there people playing with each other?
Well, this side was like this, and this side was like this.
It was like this.
Isn't that a picture of me standing on my knees?
What is this?
If you're going to do this, then stand up!
Also, if you went deeper, there was something like this.
Ah!
Sticky, sticky, sticky!
Sticky!
Well, there were a lot of things like that.
There are a lot of things like that in the world.
I'm not a old man!
I'm not an old man.
So you mean that the toilet was here?
That's right.
There were only holes in the toilet.
What do you mean by holes?
There were only holes for poop.
So, there were holes for poop, and there were holes for ass, like this.
Like this, like this, like this.
I've never done that.
There were countries like that, too.
I've been to a lot of places.
Really?
Yeah.
What surprised you the most?
That surprised me.
Where?
I don't know if you said that.
I was surprised all the time.
Oh, really?
That's a lot, isn't it?
It was a lot.
My face was surprised all the time.
Why are you like this?
What kind of face is that?
You can't make that face.
I was surprised.
Where?
That was in Riviera.
You remembered the song.
There's Riviera, right?
Where is Riviera?
Riviera is not directly from Japan.
Then where is it?
It's outside.
So, where is it outside?
What is it?
What shape was it?
What shape?
What do you mean?
It's the most important thing.
Why do I have to tell you such a thing?
It's the opposite.
You've been like this all the time.
Then let me tell you.
What I saw and heard,
I have to tell you everything?
I have my own precious memories.
My precious memories.
A postcard.
Why do I have to tell you?
I have a wooden sword.
Say sorry.
What?
You can't tell me what it is.
I was surprised.
That's why I told you to say it.
Are you going to say that?
Please tell me.
I'm sorry to say this.
The toilet is small.
It's very small.
The toilet is like this.
That's the shape of the toilet.
It's a toilet with a gold cover.
Is it Japanese style?
It's Japanese style.
It's Japanese style, but it's this small.
When I opened the toilet, there were about 20 of them.
Riviera is amazing.
It's coming out little by little.
That's right.
If it goes all the way, it won't be washed away.
I see.
There's also time.
Is there time?
There is time.
It's like a game.
The end.
Who said that?
How to measure the time without a clock
How can I measure the time without a clock when I make cup noodles?
You can measure it for about 3 minutes.
What?
I don't have a clock.
Don't you know how to measure 3 minutes by yourself?
I don't know how to measure it?
Everyone needs to know how to measure 3 minutes.
Is that so?
That's right.
What should I do?
What?
3 minutes...
That's scary!
For example, you can do anything, right?
Yes.
Hmm, let's see...
Then...
Let's do this.
Right?
How many seconds is this?
I don't know.
There's no way I'd know.
Please measure it.
Can you hold your watch?
I'll do it.
I don't even know how to measure it!
How many seconds is this?
It's 3 seconds.
How many seconds?
If you do this 10 times...
That's enough!
Don't say it!
10 times?
Yes!
I can't do it!
I can't do it 10 times, but...
It's a simple story, right?
So, how many seconds is this?
I don't even know how to measure it!
That's not it.
I...
If I knew that it was 3 seconds,
I wouldn't be in any trouble at any time.
You just need to move it until it's 3 minutes.
I just need to move it.
It doesn't have to be this, right?
It can be that.
This is fine, too.
How many seconds is this?
I don't know!
Measure it!
I can't do it!
That's right.
Okay, let's go.
I'm so stupid.
How many seconds is this?
4 seconds.
That means you just need to do this 80 times.
4 seconds...
This is 60 seconds, so I'm in trouble.
I don't want to be asked the first question.
I'll get hurt.
Then, please watch the next one.
Yes, yes.
I get hurt dozens of times a day because my intestines are different from others.
Right?
If I get hurt in the elevator, what should I do to trick them?
It's a matter of sense of value.
Sense of value?
Don't you think it's embarrassing to get hurt in the elevator?
I see.
I'll make a normal face.
I won't close my butt.
I'll get hurt, so I can't help it.
I'll just go straight to the elevator.
I'll go straight to the elevator.
I'll make a normal face.
Why don't you get hurt?
I'm scared.
I have a question for you.
The last question.
When does a chick become a chicken?
When does it start crying?
Please tell me.
14 years old.
14 years old?
From a girl.
I see.
When does a chick become a chicken?
I've never seen a chick become a chicken.
It was a chick on Wednesday, but it became a chicken on Thursday.
That's not true.
There are times when a chick becomes a chicken.
One thing I can say is that it's an earthquake.
An earthquake.
For example, when you're not confident, your voice gets smaller.
I don't know. I didn't notice that.
If you say that, I'll end the conversation.
For example, if you know a difficult question, you can answer it with a loud voice.
That's true for everyone.
But if you're asked a question you're not confident in, you're like...
I see.
That's what happens.
In the end, the chick says it's an earthquake.
Are you nervous?
I'm not confident.
I have a strong feeling that it's something like me.
It still looks like that.
That's right.
Right?
I respect chickens.
When you're older...
When you're about 20, you can't say that because you're older.
I can't say that.
I understand.
That's why the chick says it, but it's...
It's like, huh?
But it's a big change.
What change?
It's the same as being a talent.
When you debut, you become obsessed with it.
Among the big talents...
Among the big chickens...
Among all those chick
One chick...
That's the worst.
I can't talk about it.
I can't speak about it.
That's right.
From now on, there are chickens on TV.
I understand.
I don't think I can speak.
I don't think it's something like me saying that, do you?
That's how I feel.
What do you mean by that?
That's the only thing I can say.
Let's just say it for now.
But you can't say it out loud, right?
So if you have a chick at home,
I'll ask you slowly.
Put it on like this.
Put the pin mic on the chick.
Make it yellow.
Make it match the clothes.
If you put it on, it'll say,
Kogeko!
Gradually, you'll gain self-confidence.
You'll grow up.
I'll be the big brother.
You'll be the big brother.
You'll get a lot of regulars.
You'll be able to talk to the people below you.
And you'll have a big group of people.
And when that happens,
gradually, until yesterday,
you'd say, Kogeko.
I understand that.
I'll act it out now.
But if you don't do it on time, you'll get in trouble.
I'll get in trouble.
With the big brother?
Even though I haven't even started wearing Tosaka yet,
he'll say,
in that scene,
you're a cocky cocky guy!
He'll say that, but...
I can't do that.
He'll say that later,
and I'll be like,
what's going on?
He'll say that.
You've been through a lot.
The manager will be rambling.
I'm sorry, I still don't get it.
I can't do it.
If I get on top of the guitar,
everyone will be against me.
They'll be against you?
I can't say that.
You can't say that?
The big brother won't say it.
He won't say it.
But if you really say it,
you'll get in trouble later.
I won't get in trouble.
What are you trying to say?
I can't say it.
Oh, I said it.
If you say it, I'll get angry.