Good evening. I'm a kid's teacher.
Actually, I have something to tell you.
Hamada-kun is off today.
What?
Why?
Well...
There's a TV show.
I'm not sure if I can play a full match.
I want to play baseball.
What are you talking about?
Baseball?
What are you doing, Hamada-kun?
Shut up!
So...
Did you do your job?
No, I didn't.
What are you?
I didn't do my job.
You didn't?
Shut up!
I have to do something for the show.
I'm off today.
Today, we had a lot of guests.
What are you doing?
We had a lot of guests.
I'll show you my skills.
What are you talking about?
I don't know if I can show you everything.
Please watch it.
I'm sorry.
Start!
Turn the video around!
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Please watch it.
You're in the way!
I haven't done any sports in the opening.
First of all, NAMIKI PRO.
Good evening.
This is the commentator.
I don't like it.
What's wrong with you?
Is that a real ball?
I don't do that.
I'm the host of Shiki Shiki Manga Dojo.
I'm the host, Hamada Masato.
Please draw a circle with a hot spring mark.
First of all, Ebisu.
This is a kappa.
The sun is shining on my head.
Are you scared?
It's a round sushi.
I drew a round sushi.
I'm a foolish boy.
A light woman.
No, it's something that spins.
It's something that spins in Harappa.
Good!
That was amazing.
I went to the Olympics.
It hurts.
Yes, that's it, a wide balance.
You're not there yet.
That's it, a big jump.
A full turn.
Get it!
Spin, spin, spin.
I did it!
I've been planning this for a long time.
But I couldn't get their schedule.
We have a great guest.
He's good.
Let's have him on stage.
Yamada Yasuo and Negoro!
Are you serious?
No, I'm not.
I had nothing to do.
That's a lie.
I'm not going to let you go.
That's good.
That's a nostalgic song.
It's nostalgic.
Thank you.
I heard that you were sent to the middle of Shinshu 5 years ago.
If there's a paper to throw away, there's a paper to pick up.
Read it.
There's information that Lupin 3rd is going to join the Sarlowin Association.
So we want to arrest Lupin 3rd with your help.
There's also an arrest warrant for Interpol.
Lupin 3rd, I'm counting on you.
Lupin? Are you really Lupin?
I'm Yamada Yasuo.
Good evening.
Thank you.
We're going to have a first class English class.
It's in English, right?
It's in English.
It's the best pattern I've ever done.
Excuse me.
Mr. Kento Teikaku!
Mr. Kento Teikaku
Mr. Kento Teikaku, how are you doing? It's so nice to see you again.
I haven't seen you since that party. Where was it?
That was a great party.
I can't believe it.
That was great.
When did you start talking?
Let's start the class.
Kento, look at this.
I'll do this.
Do you do this in English?
Laura!
That's Japanese!
It's Laura!
Is this Mr. Saejoh Hideki?
That's right.
This is how you do it.
Don't use Japanese.
Okay, come on!
How many people are there?
There are six of us.
We have two guests.
First, we have Mr. Amikoshi.
You're doing great, Mr. Amikoshi.
I'm not saying anything weird.
Next, we have Mrs. Komori.
Do you still have a crush on her?
I have a crush on her now.
How about you, Mr. Amikoshi?
Mr. Amikoshi doesn't call people like Mrs. Komori.
Mrs. Komori doesn't call people like Mr. Amikoshi either.
It's not like that.
Let's get along.
I don't want to do this anymore.
What are you doing?
You're annoying.
I don't want to do this anymore.
This is the hide-and-seek show.
There was an unexpected twist.
I didn't think she'd be in the bathroom.
This is the first time she's been in the men's bathroom since 1981.
It was a little hard today.
I don't want to do this anymore.
Thank you, Mr. Amikoshi and Mrs. Komori.
You'll be lucky.
Saito, you're in trouble now.
You're not good at this.
Thank you for watching.
This is the first episode of the hide-and-seek show.
This is Mr. Shiro Magi.
How many types can you do?
I can do about seven types.
You can eat with that.
I'll never go to the same place again.
Let's call the teacher who will do the magic.
This is Mr. Sumie.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Please shake this.
Three.
Put the three cards in front of you.
Clean up the rest of the cards.
The back is red.
This is red, this is red, and this is red.
It's all red.
This is all blue.
Even if I shake it like this, the three cards will come out.
If you shake it 10 times, it will come out 10 times.
The five came out.
What do you mean?
It's Trump after all.
That's what you just said.
Who is the real one?
First of all, let me introduce the answer.
This is Mr. Fuyuki Motoh.
You don't usually do anything, do you?
I usually have a lot of mesh.
Next to me is Mr. Kongo Trunk.
Are you shaking it?
I'm shaking it.
Mr. Kongo has a lot of mesh.
I've been shaking it for about three hours.
I prepared this for you today.
Mr. Kongo.
That's a great head.
It's like a bad boy.
The first one is the second one.
The third one is the fourth one.
The fourth one is too much like Katsura.
This is a lie.
I see.
I'm the fourth one.
There's a big hole.
It's like the most Katsura-like Katsura.
It can't be helped.
The second one.
Let's see the correct answer.
Please.
The first one.
No.
It doesn't fly.
It's a
It's broken.
It's not a sound of rain.
I'm a little excited.
It's broken.
The fourth one.
It's the third one.
It's a rehearsal.
This is the school.
I set up the place before coming back.
But you're not going back.
I'm okay.
I'm not going back.
It's where I'm doing now.
Who did this when I was making the first one?
Oh, it's the same as the one before.
Welcome!
Dance, dance, dance!
Good evening.
We started with dance, dance, dance.
Let me introduce the judges.
First, Sugii.
He is the ace.
Wonderful.
What is wonderful?
Next, Chieko Kishi.
Thank you very much.
The way you waved your hand,
you stopped in the middle.
Yes, yes.
I think it would be better if I didn't stop.
With that, the waist should be like this.
Like this.
You!
It's finally the last performance.
The last performance,
as you all know,
I'd like to start right away.
Oh, he looks quite nervous.
It's his 40th performance,
so it's the last performance.
No, no, I'm nervous.
This is ridiculous.
Let's go.
No. 40, pass line.
How was it?
How many points did the judges give?
He is a comic artist.
What a pity.
The judges, please give him more points.
Are you doing it alone?
Yes.
He is doing it alone.
Did you make it alone?
No.
What?
Who made it?
Yes.
Did you make it alone?
He made it alone.
The judges, please give him more points.
He made it.
Don't fall down.
Congratulations.
I'm glad.
He made it.
He is not going to make up like this.
I'm glad.
I want to make it and
I want to make it with you.
I want to give you a hand.
I have a wonderful friend like this.
He made it.
Stop it.
I'm getting embarrassed.
Thank you.
He made it.
Here we go.
Please give him more points.
Thank you very much.
It's a nice car.
I'm going home.
Thank you very much.
Did you get it?
Yes.
We did a good job.
How was it?
I couldn't introduce all the guests.
I changed the content of the video.
I sent it like this.
Next week, Hamada will be fine and go home.
I want to show you how to use it.
Thank you very much.
OK.
I'm glad.
Hey.
Don't make a mistake.
I'm sorry.
I'm not disappointed.
I thought Yamazaki would drop me.
I expected too much from Yamazaki.
That's all for today.
Thank you very much.