Hiroshi Fujiwara
I'm Hiroshi Fujiwara.
Lately I've gained too much weight, and it's become difficult for me to cut my toenails.
I'm Hiroshi Fujiwara. My wife is becoming more and more like me.
I'm Hiroshi Fujiwara.
I'm doing a fun New Year's event in Guminedo, Yoshimoto.
Everyone, I'm waiting for you.
You're doing a fun New Year's event?
Fujiwara-san, are you going to cut your toenails again this year?
Yes.
Why don't you just cut your toenails with your license?
I'm begging you. If everyone says Fujiwara, I'll remember you.
I'm sorry.
This year, I've been chosen to be the general manager for seven consecutive years. I'm the former downtown manager, Hiroshi Fujiwara.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Also, this year, I'm the one who knows the most about the use of children.
That's amazing.
The way you're knocking is amazing.
I'm Kocho Bashibu.
This year, Kocho Bashibu has made a breakthrough in the field of high-speed rotation, which has been created in the past.
He's laughing.
Kocho Baffaro's general, Matsumoto...
He's a fool.
It's hard to watch.
It's so hard to watch.
It's dangerous.
The K-1 fighter, Ernest Faust, is participating in this project in which the person who draws the skull card in the library has to be quiet
The K-1 fighter, Ernest Faust, is participating in this project in which the person who draws the skull card is to be quiet
I have something to tell everyone
I think Hamada is a little drunk
When I went home, I said hello to Haruhiko Kato and Shidou-kun, but when I looked at myself, I was a little drunk
The license to take care of children is set up for the members
But
The other child is a teenager who just graduated from high school this year
What?
He said that he likes young men
From tonight?
But he heard that he was one hour late, so he went out after spending some time
And one hour later
The K-1 fighter, Ernest Faust, is participating in this project in which the person who draws the skull card in the library has to be quiet
It's still only me
I'm completely in tune
It's not the usual Seiji
It's funny
I don't know what he's talking about
That's the only thing
I just got a call from a woman
Excuse me, cancel today
What?
And
The license to take care of children is set up for the members
But he heard that he was one hour late, so he went out after spending some time
I won't do it
I don't know
Why don't you say it?
It's impossible
I don't know what to do
What is this?
I don't know
I see
There's a lot
Everyone was strange
They don't talk about it
They don't
I'll talk about it next year
Really?
Will you get a license next year?
There's a pattern
There's a pattern to get a license, but there's no pattern to get a license
There's no pattern to get a license?
I want to see the karaoke after the host
Karaoke
The VTR
It's amazing
I want to see the karaoke after the host
It's good
It's amazing
Next, please look at the 6th to 4th place
Next, please look at the 6th place
The first time Hamada was called Kona Sonia
What did he see there?
The war is over
We were born
Without knowing the war
It's a good song
It was amazing
It didn't fall at all
Everyone got sweets
Without knowing the war
How many groups were there?
I don't know
Happy Turn
How many groups were there?
In the first episode, Yamazaki is 36 years old
He is the last samurai
Yamazaki is going to compete with a comedian of the same age
He is going to compete with a comedian of the same age
But this is actually a high-profile prank
He doesn't know that
Kouji Higashino wins
Let's win
I'm not tired
The camera is out of order
It's okay if it's the last one
It's just a little
I'm sorry
It's a technical problem
It's the last one
It's impossible
It's a little difficult
I don't know what to do
It's strange
Why didn't you talk to me on the way?
You should have stopped me on the way
I'm sorry
What?
Yes
You didn't talk to me
I'm sorry
We are doing the same thing
Yes
Let's ask him to do something
Let's ask Higashino to do something
Let's do that
Let's ask him to do something
I'm sorry
Thank you
Can you wait a minute?
I'm sorry
I thought you were going to say you were sorry
Let's go back to Higashino
I've prepared the costumes
Yes
To
It's different from the last one
Today
Senor will have a lot of worries
What?
I want to solve it
Please stay with me
I hate music
I'm always teased by girls
How can I sing like you?
Let's solve it
It's okay if you don't sing
It's not like that
Producer Suga invited the members to a high-class French cuisine
However, there is a strict rule that you have to be good at cooking
4th place Hema Chi and Paris
First, Matsumoto
It's beautiful
It stinks
I'm really happy
10 minutes later, Matsumoto again
It stinks
Is it delicious?
I see, it's like this when you put the mushrooms on the back
I want to die
Then, Hamada shows his amazing machine to stop Matsumoto's poison
It's here
However, this is just a small wound
Is it delicious?
Don't you eat this?
Let's go next
It's like this
It's like a wallet soldier
I can't do it anymore
This is amazing
This is scary
It hurts
What should I do?
This is the end
I don't want to do it anymore
It's really delicious
It's delicious
As usual, Hamada was surprised
Even though I knew it was a prank, I was scared
This is the second time in Paris, isn't it?
It's like a handicap
That's right
It's not a big deal
I've done it many times in other shows
The best 3 will be announced
In March, a charming couple, Eri, suddenly appeared in the dressing room and showed Matsumoto their love
The first blow of Eri
It's a blow
It's cool to be smoking
What are you doing?
In October, half a year later, she appeared in the dressing room again
The incident happened there
Actually, I have something to tell you
I want you to break up
I have someone I like
Who is it?
I can't tell you the name
I don't want to fight
I don't know what to do
Please tell me
I can't tell you
I know you
I didn't say that
I'll tell you
I can't stand it
Then, they put their love on Eri and make her disappear
Let's start
It's the worst
Eri is doing it
Wait
It's dangerous
Isn't it dangerous?
Hiro
Are you okay?
You can't touch it if it's on your back
Hiro
What is it?
Don't touch it
The coldest women on earth
Come closer
Thank you
Kokoriko Endo lied that she was attracted to the famous film director Harimoto
and called her to an audition
The biggest show is Samurai Hohohoi's Hohohoi
Are you motivated? I saw something terrible, please leave
Next person, please
Hai
Thank you for waiting
The late Hohohoi's actor Thomas MacLegar has arrived
Please
Konnichiwa tokyo
Konnichiwa
And the audition is coming to an end
Samurai Hohohoi's actor Thomas MacLegar has a homosexual wound
Please play the role of Samurai Hohohoi
Hai
No no no
Why are you dressed like this?
What are you doing?
Sorry
Who are you?
Endo
It's a big success
It's terrible
No.3 and No.2 are really good at acting
I was watching the show, but I didn't understand anything
I don't understand
Everything started with this man's words
Recently I don't have much money
According to what I heard, Inse is a local, right?
That's right
Yamasaki, who lives in Inse, wrote and composed the original songs for the four people in downtown Kokoriko
He started to produce all the arrangements, songs, and costumes
And this is the finished song
I always think of you when I was a kid
You are an actor
This is completely terrible
It's funny
My song is in the middle of the town
In the middle of the town
I don't understand
I remember the second time I heard Tanaka's song
I didn't hear Matsumoto's song
The last song Matsumoto sang was Pine Book
The last song of this year?
Yes
That song?
I can't go back