I don't know how to use it.
Welcome.
Which one would you like?
Coffee cup.
Yes, coffee cup please.
Coffee cup please.
Here you go.
Coffee cup.
Two people.
Three people?
Three people.
Please sit down.
Please be careful if you have a weak heart.
Please sit here.
Are you ready?
Yes, please.
Coffee cup start.
Please sit here.
Start.
It's over.
Thank you very much.
Welcome.
Which one would you like?
Water coaster.
Three people.
Here you go.
Water coaster.
He doesn't like it.
Here you go.
Be careful.
Are you visiting your mother?
Yes, I am.
Here you go.
Water coaster.
Start.
Be careful.
Water coaster.
Thank you very much.
Are you okay?
Welcome.
Two people.
Which one would you like?
My house.
Take a look.
There is a pool.
What are you going to do?
Magic carpet.
Be careful.
Thank you very much.
Here you go.
One by one?
Yes.
One by one.
Okay.
Here you go.
Magic carpet.
Start.
I'm scared.
Are you okay?
I'm afraid you'll get hurt.
The end.
Let's go.
Please take a picture.
Magic carpet.
Start.
The end.
Thank you very much.
See you again.
Come to see me again.
The magic carpet is over.
I'll put up a parade for the next customer.
Okay.
Next customer.
Welcome.
The time has come.
The technical parade will begin.
Please take a look.
Technical parade, please.
The lights are beautiful.
The end.
Are you ready?
Dad.
Let's go to the observatory for your dad.
I'm going to the observatory.
Dad, I'm going to the observatory.
Dad, please be careful.
Excuse me.
Please take a look at the observatory.
Thank you very much.
Dad, you're lucky today.
It's a observatory like a technical parade.
Thank you very much.
This is the exit.
The observatory is over.
I only have two left.
I'm lucky.
Welcome.
Pirates.
Pirates, please.
This is my favorite, Pirates.
I'm lucky.
I have Pirates left.
Please take a seat.
Pirates.
Please.
Please be careful.
Pirates.
Pirates, please.
Please be careful.
This is the end.
I'm lucky.
I thought Pirates would be gone.
Thank you very much.
Please remember that I have a pool.
Welcome.
Please come in.
I'm surprised.
I'm lucky.
The second parade is about to begin.
There is a parade with lights.
Pirates, please.
The surface is beautiful.
It's shining.
I'm lucky.
I was given a coffee cup and a magic carpet.
Octopus.
Octopus, please.
Please enjoy it.
Octopus is about to start.
Please move.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much everyone.
This is the end of Mini Toshimaya.
Please come again.
Thank you very much.
Hello.
You are very energetic.
I'm a fool.
I think the audience today is listening to Team Zero for a longer time than listening to us.
What?
Now we have a special edition.
I'm a little hungry.
I'm wearing a lot of clothes.
I'm wearing a lot of clothes for the body.
So today Team Zero is a child's play.
We are a child's play.
Yes, yes, yes.
The story just now will be on air.
I really like birds.
I'm free.
I really can't do it today.
I've been saying a lot of things until now, but I really can't do it.
There are times when I write.
You're touching your chin every now and then.
What happened recently?
Did something happen?
Hana-san passed away.
After all, a comedian's life is short.
Is that so?
I've been an actor for a long time.
There is no job that is as stressful as a comedian.
Is that so?
That's right.
That's what I wrote in the weekly magazine.
If the weekly magazine said it was true, it was true in your case.
That's different.
That's right, but it's true to some extent.
Because he seems to have a great attitude.
You can see that he seems to be great.
He's a little stubborn, isn't he?
His courage is being dispersed.
I don't know about that.
Have you ever done it?
A little.
Did you think that he was a lowly guy at that time?
No.
That's it.
I went in and there was a pool in front of the studio.
I saw him and thought,
He's a monkey.
Then,
I saw the script like this.
That's amazing.
Everyone said,
Thank you.
I saw him and thought,
He's a monkey.
I didn't say hello.
I'm tired.
That's ridiculous.
I don't think so.
But I didn't see that.
I didn't talk to him.
But that attitude is a little.
It's a little.
You should have said hello properly.
I don't know.
I saw it once.
You've seen it.
For the moment,
You can say,
It's fine if it's just this much.
But it's fine if it's this much.
If it's like this.
I'll make it a bit more clear.
I won't say, thank you.
But it's fine.
That's a bit too much.
Why is that?
I don't want to say bad things about you, but...
You're saying, aha?
You're saying aha at a place like that?
Other things...
You're saying that?
What are you?
We've talked about a lot of things, but I...
I like you.
I like you, so I'm thinking of getting your autograph.
I really like you.
I like you as a man.
It's just that...
Before I entered this world, I was like, I hate this guy, I hate that guy.
But when I met a lot of people in this world and talked to them,
there wasn't anyone I didn't like that much, right?
There wasn't anyone I didn't like, right?
No, no, no.
It's not that, I'm more angry!
Let's talk about men and men more.
No, no, really.
Did you have something?
Something you didn't like at first?
Something you didn't like?
There are people I don't like.
Who are they?
I don't understand what you're saying.
It's not bad at first, right?
But when you look at them, they're amazing people.
Who are they?
There are a lot of people like that, right?
That's why I really think that this world isn't that bad.
That's right.
I really think that.
Is that so?
Yeah.
In the past, there was a time when you hated this guy or that guy.
So who is that?
Who is that?
Wait a minute, did you have something?
You had something, didn't you?
Who is that?
Well, sometimes.
There are people like that.
There are a lot of young actors like that.
Oh, really?
I misunderstand something.
It's okay, who is that?
For example, who do you think you're misunderstanding?
Well, um...
Do you want to cut that out?
Tokiyama Goro.
Who is that?
It's no good.
Are you about to cry?
I'm about to cry.
It's already late today.
It doesn't matter if it's good or bad.
What are you talking about?
On the contrary, what are you talking about?
Then you guys should take a good picture on Monday.
Try it.
What?
It's such a big deal.
You're hiding.
You're having sex.
Try it.
It's a lot of trouble.
That's true.
I thought it would be more fun to be an entertainer.
In that sense, there are restrictions in life.
There are restrictions.
There are no restrictions at all.
I want to take it off and do it.
You're taking it off.
You're taking it off enough.
What's the hardest thing for me is that I can't go to the beach in the summer.
It's really hard.
You can't go to the beach.
You can't feel anything.
Do something in the room.
I used to do scuba diving in peace.
What is scuba diving?
This is scuba diving.
That's why I want to do it more.
I want to do it like this.
I want to hit and hit.
I really don't like it.
I can't walk on the road with a hat on.
I'm walking in peace.
I'm going to kill you.
I can't make as much money as I thought.
I'll make it clear.
I have 180,000 yen in my hand.
I've been on TV so much.
I only have 180,000 yen.
I don't know what it is.
I was pulled 180,000 yen.
I thought it was a better business.
I thought it was a more popular life.
It's not like that.
What are you talking about?
You've been talking about me lately.
You're ugly, but I'm not.
You have a plastic surgery.
Why?
I've said it many times.
I don't have a plastic surgery.
No, no, no, no.
You're making fun of me, aren't you?
If you make fun of me, I feel sorry for you.
I'll make you look a little more beautiful.
I'm sure that woman won't stop her father.
I'm going to put you in a bra.
That's a scam.
I'm going to break the rice and turn it around.
I think my father is big.
I was trying to call you for this.
That's not good.
You have a pretty bad eye.
I'm going to do something about it.
I'm not going to do anything about it.
What's that?
You can't tell from the top of your clothes?
I still don't know.
It's a scam.
You have a pretty bad eye.
If you do this, something will fall off.
Something will fall off.
What's going to fall off?
It's a scam.
When I'm using the bathtub, there's always someone in front of me.
They try to scoop it out, but it's hard to get rid of it.
What is it?
It's a scam.
I already know the answer.
Why?
That's the way to say it.
You're trying to get rid of it, but it won't fall off.
You can't get rid of it like this.
How did you get rid of it?
I see.
What is it?
I think there's something in the right ear.
The secret is in the right ear.
It's in the right ear.
What about the one without the ear?
The one without the ear is...
The one with the ear is hard to get rid of.
I see.
But the amount of the secret is different for each person.
There's a lot of them.
You don't have to open it.
It's already fallen off.
I feel sorry for the ones with so many secrets.
I see.
There's one more.
Why is there a plastic thing on the handle of a bicycle?
It looks fun.
It's waving in the wind.
Idiot.
The tricycles sold at MUJI are...
They're cheap.
So they're not so cute when kids ride them.
It's like when they're shining.
But that doesn't explain it.
Kids can enjoy it.
It's waving.
It's waving in the wind.
Do kids like it?
Kids like it.
I don't know if kids like it.
It looks fun, right?
Why is Matcha so cute?
I'm a fan of Matcha.
Matcha is more attractive than the Mont Blanc cake in front of you.
Please continue to be a lovely Matcha.
I love you the most in the world.
Idiot.
I really think so.
What's amazing about you is that you can read letters like that yourself.
Why?
You're a man.
That's true.
You're a manly man.
If I were a woman, I'd want to be hugged by you.
No way.
If I were a man, I'd bite my tongue.
If I were a woman, I'd want to be hugged by you.
No way.
I'm a manly man.
Idiot.
There's no man like me.
I thought you were done with your homo.
But you look like you have a lot of hair.
I don't need a character like that.
I'm serious.
I think I'm perfect.
It's up to you.
Everyone thinks they're perfect.
I'm not as bad as everyone thinks I am.
I think everyone thinks so.
Even the audience here thinks I'm ugly.
Even if there's no ugly woman, I can laugh.
It doesn't matter to me.
Really?
Yes.
Humans are scary.
So are you.
I think I'm perfect.
But when I look at you,
your nose is like this.
And your chin is like this.
It's up to you.
That's all I can say.
When I look at you, you're cool.
When I look at you, you're funny.