In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Arahen, let's have a look at the beautiful and talented entertainer, Kudoki Tekugase!
Mr. Wataru, our staff has done this before.
Yes, we have.
It was a mess, wasn't it?
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
I thought that this would not work.
Entertainer?
Entertainer.
There must have been many.
That's right. Among the entertainers, there were many who had a very good fortune.
All of them?
That's right.
The three sleeping lions.
Is that so? I understand.
Then, let's have the three of them appear.
Do these three have a very good fortune?
That's right.
You are amazing.
Really?
That's great.
If you have a wife, you have a child.
Don't you want to see how such people do it?
It's a handicap race.
Speaking of which, how about this handicap?
This program is brought to you by the sponsor you are watching.
Who will go first?
First of all, let's start with the young ones.
I see.
They are very active right now.
That's right. Kanda-kun.
Yes.
Is the person next to you there?
That's right.
Yes.
That's great.
Do you know me?
What?
Yes.
Look, I'm on TV.
Do you know me?
Kanda-san?
Yes, I know you.
I've seen you before.
Really?
Yes.
You look like Keigo Matsuzaka.
I've never been told that.
I knew it.
Yes.
What?
That's right.
Is there a type you like?
Fukuyama Masaharu-san.
Fukuyama Masaharu?
I lost.
I admit it.
Fukuyama Masaharu?
Yes.
I see.
Don't move.
Don't talk like that.
I know Fukuyama Masaharu.
Is that so?
Do you want to talk to Fukuyama Masaharu?
I want to talk to him.
Do you want to talk to him?
Yes.
Really?
Let's go to the room.
He's a criminal.
He's coming.
Really?
Let's go.
Fukuyama Masaharu.
Sit down.
Yes.
You have to call Fukuyama.
Wait a minute.
He's doing it in real time.
I don't know what's going on.
Hello?
Masaharu?
See you later.
I don't know what's going on.
You should have told me.
You're a fool.
He can't answer the phone right now.
Is that so?
You're a fool.
I don't know what's going on.
You should have told me.
I see.
Why are you doing this?
If you give 100 points to Fukuyama Masaharu, how many points will I get?
But it's a different genre.
He said he'd buy me something.
Is that so?
But...
Go ahead.
You're a fool.
Let's go to the restaurant.
I see.
Talk to him.
Your fan wants you to change the phone number.
Yes.
Really?
What?
You're a fool.
Is that so?
What?
Talk to him.
You're a fool.
You should have told me.
Are you kidding me?
Wait a minute.
You're a fool.
I don't know what's going on.
Are you kidding me?
You're a fool.
Are you sure?
Your fan wants you to change the phone number.
I don't know what's going on.
But...
That's it.
You're a fool.
You should have told me.
I don't know what's going on.
I'm about to cry.
Let's go to the restaurant.
Okay.
Would you like some juice?
Would you like something to drink?
Thank you for the food.
You're welcome.
You're welcome?
Who asked you to do that?
May I?
Sure.
Oolong tea.
You're a bad guy.
Where are we going?
Don't touch me.
Just a little bit.
Where are you going to take me?
You can leave it to me.
I don't like bad guys.
I'll take you.
You're a bad guy.
Then, if we have a moment, we can take a picture.
Sure.
Why do I have to pay?
What are you going to cut?
You can leave it to me.
What?
There you go.
I'm bad.
I'm a bad guy.
How many do you want?
How about that?
I'm sure you can do it.
How many?
How many do you want?
Five.
What?
Five?
Five.
How many?
Five hundred.
Five hundred?
How many?
Five hundred.
One, two, three, four...
He said three million when he made my small bridge.
Five million?
I want to kiss you on the cheek.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Mahoto Ozaki.
I'll let you taste the best sex in the world.
All of a sudden?
I came down from the sky for you.
I'll let you taste the best sex in the world.
That's all?
Go ahead.
I'll let you taste the best sex in the world.
Let's take a bath.
Look at the sky.
A nice shooting star.
Here it comes.
He's a manly man.
I wonder if he's confident.
That he won't go home.
What?
What are you doing?
I was just looking at his feet.
What's wrong?
Huh?
Come on.
Let's have sex.
Is it okay here?
No!
Come on.
Don't bend over.
I'm bending over.
I'm rubbing against you.
What are you thinking?
I'm holding you.
Come on.
Maachan.
Maachan, try it.
Next time.
If you want Maachan to do it, do it.
Is that so?
I know.
Prepare a wonderful woman.
I'm wearing a microphone.
Maachan version.
Please whistle a little.
You're so fluffy today.
You're fluffy.
I look warm, right?
You look warm.
I'm getting cold.
I see.
You have to be fashionable.
That's right.
It's a business that can't be seen.
You're getting red.
I see.
I can't think of that.
It's too late.
I'm going to the magazine again.
You're still in the top five of fashionable entertainers.
You're in the top five.
What's the talent you think is a genius?
I'm from China.
Why?
It's nice.
It's fashionable.
Why?
I'm just wearing what I've been prepared for.
What you've been prepared for.
Why?
Who's a foreigner?
I don't think it's fashionable even if I look at it today.
My relatives put this in a cardboard box and sent it to me when I was in elementary school.
I don't like that kind of clothes.
I'm sorry.
I know that.
I don't wear this at that time.
I saw it the other day.
You're wearing pants.
That's right.
You put out your pants up to here and lower your pants.
Yes.
Is that okay?
That's...
You took a picture like this.
What is it?
You're not wearing pants.
I'm surprised.
What's good or bad?
I know that.
I don't even know what gum is.
It's similar.
It's similar, but I know that.
I'm sorry, but I'm wrong.
After all, men, women, and men are the contents.
What do you mean you're training the contents?
For example, when I'm free, I'm in the outdoors.
That's why you're always at home.
No... no... no... no... No matter how many times I say it, I'm at home.
I'm not at home.
You can't make it up.
I don't know if you thought I knew you since elementary school, but I knew you.
I don't want to know.
I want you to tell me the number of my phone number.
No... no... no...
There must be a crazy country.
I thought you wanted to know theây.
I already know that.
I don't want to go home.
Your parents...
My hat is falling off.
Your parents know about it.
What?
Of course they know.
You're lying.
If they know, I'm lying.
Wait a minute.
You're lying.
Listen to me.
I want to know everything.
You're lying.
You really don't know about the group?
Yes, I do.
You're lying.
It's normal.
But he...
It's not normal.
I want to know everything.
You don't want to know anything.
No, no.
There's something.
But I'm really strict at home.
I can't teach you that.
I can't do that.
No, no, no.
No, really.
If I...
No, no, no.
If it's okay to ring the bell...
Why would I ring your bell?
I don't like it.
I don't want to get caught again.
If I tell you the truth now,
you won't listen to me anymore.
You won't be able to catch me anymore.
No, no, no.
Don't do that.
I mean...
Don't pay attention to me.
Oh, really?
Where do you live now?
I don't know.
Where do you live?
You're saying that, but I'm asking you little by little.
No.
I want to prove it.
Where do you live?
I can't tell you that right now.
No, no, no.
That's fine.
I'm just saying that my head is a 3.
You must be a little nervous right now.
Oh, it's a 3.
Should I say it quickly?
It's okay to be nervous just by hearing 3.
I'm telling you that you know me,
but you don't know anything.
Oh, at first.
Do you know that I'm into cooking lately?
Oh, really?
This is amazing.
It's my one-pack curry.
What is that?
You're making it while running around.
Are you a fool?
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
What's in it?
Oh, it's amazing.
No, no, no.
What's in it?
First of all,
band-aid.
What's in it?
Makiron.
Makiron?
Yes.
Beedaman.
Well, well.
It's my one-pack curry.
I wonder how many of you have been there lately.
I've been waiting for the car to start all the time.
I can't stop.
What? No way.
They're waiting for me.
When I say thank you, they ring the doorbell.
Boo!
They're always ringing the doorbell.
That's funny.
You know, cars are just like humans.
For example, a wiper is a hand.
You mean I have to pay with this?
Yes, yes, yes.
When you cry, you use your hand like this.
That's a wiper.
Passing means, you know,
when the previous one was melted,
if you do this, the light goes like this.
This is like, huh?
And when you shake it,
you ring the doorbell,
saying, thank you.
Thank you.
Boo!
I know that.
What you did was...
Thank you for this trip.
We talked all the time.
All the time.
No, no, no.
This trip is really...
It's been cold lately, hasn't it?
It's been cold, hasn't it?
It's a little lonely to sleep alone.
No, really.
I mean, I only sleep alone.
But when you're done, you're like,
hurry up and go home!
You're alone when you sleep.
When I'm done?
It's bitter.
I don't know if it's that bitter.
Isn't it Heiko-kun?
No!
I was waiting for Heiko-kun.
No, it's not.
There are times when I want to push you.
Ah.
Shall we go?
Yes, go ahead.
When I posed like this,
my spine went crazy.
What?
Nothing.
You wanted to show me
putting a hat in the back, didn't you?
If you talk like this,
you can see it all the time.
Enjoy the various angles of Masatoshi.
Is that so?
This is from someone who knows me.
Ah, is that so?
Yes.
Pen name.
It's from the 4th comedian,
Yamasaki Hosei-san.
First of all, there's a request below.
Please put a song on this poem.
Is that okay?
The title is,
A Crystal Night.
Please take a seat here.
It started with a greeting.
Come alone.
I don't want to play games alone.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Well, well, well.
I wrote a lot of songs.
Ah, songs.
Well, yes.
Is that so?
I wrote a lot of songs.
Anything?
What I do is,
Well, I don't have a piano today.
How do you always make it?
Well,
What are you talking about?
Why are you seriously saying,
Well,
First of all,
Do you have any talent like this?
No, I don't.
Well, well, well.
I wonder how much an amateur can do.
It's a love song.
It's different at this point.
No.
I'm an artist.
Ah, that's good.
Greeting, from a greeting.
It's different.
From a greeting.
Ah, it's kind of like Shibukakitai.
OK, OK, OK.
A new story of Shibukakitai.
Let's go.
Love, love, love, love.
It started with a greeting.
Are you changing it?
I'm sorry.
That's love, love, love, love.
How is it? Ballad?
How do you want me to do it?
Please call me Shanson.
Shanson, right?
Ah, Shanson.
Yes.
Ah, it's kind of like Shibukakitai.
Thank you very much.
Ah, Shanson, right?
What are you talking about?
I don't know the lyrics.
Well, the lyrics are good.
I'll kill you.
Hey.
Do you want to die?
Then, let's do it like a ballad.
Yes.
It started with a greeting.
Ah, that's not it.
You're like Dragon Ball.
You're like Pac-Man.
I'm serious.
It started with a greeting.
Wait a minute.
That's a long story.
Can you do it properly?
What's your name?
Kamizono Shiro.
Who is it?
The lyrics are different when you say Shiro.
Kamizono Shiro.
Four.
I used to sing two songs before.
That's amazing.
Megitsune no Onna.
I don't know.
What's Megitsune no Onna?
It was very popular.
It became a million seller.
There was a title called Megitsune no Onna.
The title of the cover was Hey Melo.
I don't know why.
Help me.
Thank you for waiting.
The last album was a big hit.
I didn't expect such a big hit.
It was a million seller.
The second song is expected.
It's a long story.
This song has been broadcasted many times.
Kamizono Shiro will perform for the first time on TV.
Please sing Crystal Night.
Roomba.
I'm tired.
I feel sick.
Are you okay?
What are you talking about?
Your hands are dirty.
I feel sick.
Are you okay?
I'm scared.
I feel sick.
Don't do that.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.