Shinshun-Nails
Recently, large-scale Neverland возмож fee festival has been held again.
What, fifteen?
Neverland Devils haven't visited
So let's stay friendly as always in 2004
Tada!
It is also the 15th school fishing festival this year
Introducing myself, I'm the general manager.
Introducing yourself?
I'm Yabazaki Hosei!
I have a special guest today.
Even though I have more work to do, I can't stop laughing.
I want to get rid of my worries!
Good luck this year!
Next...
This year's S.O.N.A. Combi No.1, Shinagawa Shouji!
I'm the white giant of Gaki no Tsukai, Yabana-san!
Thank you very much.
Next, let's look at the mirror.
He's the mascot of Gaki no Tsukai and La Hende.
Thank you for coming to Downtown!
Thank you!
Today, we don't have any behind-the-scenes stories.
It's going to be tough.
I've been doing this since I debuted in 2018.
It's like my arms are going to be cut off.
All together now!
Thank you for coming!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
This year's S.O.N.A. Combi No.1, Shinagawa Shouji!
Everyone is celebrating the beginning of the new year and having a good time.
Shouji seems to be in a good mood.
He's drinking at a high pace.
He's not drinking, is he?
He's drinking.
What?
Hey!
He's a senior.
He's a senior!
He's drinking!
Cheers!
It's good.
What are you looking at?
Why are you looking at the lighter?
That's why I hate the Kanto-based soft drinks.
That's where it came from.
Don't mess with us!
What?
Suddenly, Yamasaki began to talk about this year's grand goal.
I want to be in R-1.
You can't win, can you?
I want to win and open a hole in your nose.
Open a hole in your nose?
If you open a hole in your nose, you'll be in trouble.
I'll open a hole in my nose.
Once a year's fun!
Shinshun Manzai Daigassen!
Thank you!
Everyone, please listen to the news at 9 o'clock.
Please look forward to the new year's festival, Manzai Daigassen!
25 talent staff will draw a card with a number on it.
5 teams will be chosen and each team will show the original Manzai.
I'll choose the first one.
Please!
Stop!
Number 18!
What?
The first one is the new director, Keshigomu.
I hate you, Keshigomu!
Please!
Stop!
Who?
The opponent is the manager, Tajima.
Thank you!
The second team is...
Number 8!
Tanaka!
And Tanaka's opponent is...
Number 13!
It's me!
I'm glad, Tanaka!
The third team is...
Number 12!
It's Hotohara!
Hotohara will draw a card with a number on it.
The opponent is the new director, Kubo.
Which team is it?
The fourth team is...
Number 20!
Yes!
Miyasako!
The opponent is...
Number 11!
Matsumoto!
Matsumoto and Miyasako will form a team.
It's harder than I thought.
I'm looking forward to it.
And the last team is...
Number 5!
First, it's Kokoriko and Endo.
The opponent is the producer, Kobayashi.
It's not funny.
It's Endo!
There's one more!
You can do it in Shinagawa.
I don't want to do it.
Shinagawa likes manzai.
You can do it in the M-1 drama.
Shinagawa Shouji will form a team.
What are you going to do with that?
It's Hamada!
Hamada, can you do a rap?
Why?
I'll put Hamada in a weak team.
It's already decided.
What are you doing?
What are you going to do with this?
If you say let's go, it's not a good idea.
Hamada will join the team.
The theme of manzai is martial arts.
The second team is Yamasaki Tanaka.
The theme is Ore-Ore-Sagi.
The third team is Kotohara and Kubo.
The theme is trivia.
The fourth team is Miyasako Matsumoto.
The theme is Manifesto.
The fifth team is Endo and Kobayashi.
The theme is Matsui and Major.
The sixth team is Shinagawa Shouji.
The sixth team will go to another room and make up a story.
They can't slip as a person who laughs.
What kind of story will they make?
I can't do it anymore.
Let's go to the first team.
Hamada, Keshigomu and Tajima.
The theme is martial arts.
I'm the class president.
I'm the backboard.
I'm the student council president.
The martial arts of last year was very exciting.
This year, the world champion Mike Tyson will come out.
All martial arts.
I wonder what will happen on TV.
But there is one thing I regret.
It's hard to understand the game.
It's hard to understand the victory.
I don't know if I can say that.
So today I came up with a very easy-to-understand martial art.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors and Katao wins.
I see.
I don't know if I can say that.
Let's do it.
Rock-paper-scissors.
That's good.
You are crazy.
I haven't seen it yet.
I don't like it.
I have another idea.
Really?
I want to say that.
Thai kick battle.
Thai kick battle?
Yes.
What is it?
It's a Thai kick match.
I see.
It doesn't matter if I win or lose.
It doesn't matter.
Let's do it.
Let me do it.
Hey.
Wait, wait.
It hurts.
Why?
Stop.
It hurts.
I didn't do it on purpose! Thank you very much!
Tajima-kun, you only had the lines of the song when you were a kid.
I apologized right away with my sleeves.
I'm sorry.
The song is by Endo-san and Kawai-san.
The theme is Matsui Major.
Here we go!
I'm Endo.
I'm Kobayashi.
We are P-PALAZ.
We often go to this bar.
It's in Nishikuni.
I can't tell you where it is.
I love baseball.
I watched a lot of baseball last year.
I did my best.
But I thought I'd do it.
You thought?
Why?
It's Godzilla, right?
It's Mechagodzilla, right?
It's Mosura.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I can't do it.
I'm talking about Godzilla in New York.
I did my best in New York.
I can't do it in New York.
It's all CG.
I can't forget Godzilla in the movie.
You have no chance.
You are losing your tension while doing the cartoon.
I'm talking about Godzilla.
I went to Matsui in New York, right?
Where are you going?
I'm going to Matsui.
We're good friends.
We are good friends.
I'll go to New York.
But I don't know about Godzilla.
You don't know Godzilla's nickname?
It's Godzilla.
No
Oh, really?
If it's Godzilla, it's Minira, right?
So, it's not Gao.
Thank you very much.
Let's go to the 3rd round.
It's Mr. Hosei and Mr. Tanaka.
The theme is Ore Ore Sagi.
Let's go.
Hello, I'm Yama-chan.
I'm Tanaka-kun.
The theme is Homura.
I'm not convinced.
There were many incidents last year.
The incident that hurt me the most was Ore Ore Sagi.
That's not good.
Do you know?
It's an incident that stole a house and a relative and asked them to prepare 2 million and 3 million yen.
That's not good.
It's not good.
Ore Ore Sagi.
Let's do it right here.
Okay.
Oh!
Prrrr!
Oh, it's a phone call.
Gacha.
Hello?
It's me.
Who am I?
It's Ore Ore Sagi.
You can't say that it's Sagi.
I'm counting on you.
Okay.
It's a phone call.
Prrrr!
Gacha.
Hello?
It's coming out once!
It's coming out once when I say gacha!
I can't use the teleprompter.
What are you doing?
The teleprompter...
It doesn't matter now!
Ore Ore Sagi.
Can you do it?
I can do it!
Prrrr!
Oh, it's a phone call.
Gacha.
Hello?
It's me.
Who am I?
You're that old lady, right?
That's right, but...
It's me, but...
So who am I?
No, it's me, but...
You can't touch me.
What?
It's a phone call.
Yes.
Prrrr!
Oh, it's a phone call.
Gacha.
Hello?
They're both old ladies.
Why is it coming out once?
I can't use the teleprompter.
Prrrr!
Gacha.
Hello?
Is that voice from Hiroshi?
Yes, it's from Hiroshi.
Is it really from Hiroshi?
If it's from Hiroshi,
please imitate that old lady.
Ah!
Murayama Tomiichi-san!
Isn't that a friend?
That old lady...
Change it.
Change it?
Please.
Okay, I got it.
Gacha.
Hello?
Is that an old lady?
It's an old lady.
Ah, it's me.
Ah, it's Hiroshi?
Yes, yes, yes.
What's going on?
Ah, actually...
Yes?
I'd like you to prepare 1 million yen.
Why do you need 1 million yen?
Ah...
I ran into an accident.
What kind of accident?
That's right.
If you have to pay 1 million yen,
please send me 1 million yen.
Eh?
What kind of accident?
That's too much.
I'd like you to cheat on me
around here.
Eh?
I feel like I'm going to get divorced.
This is tough.
Thank you very much.
I want to do this at that convenience store again next year.
The 4th group is Hotohara-san and Kubo-san.
The theme is trivia.
Here we go.
Hello, I'm Hotohara.
I'm Kubo.
We're both beach boys.
I'm worried about you.
You're doing great.
Are you okay?
It's a daily routine.
Well, this year has started, too.
There were a lot of things.
Especially when I watched the show Kirina,
there was a good show.
There was.
Trivia.
That was fun.
It was fun.
You don't have to study math.
Do you have any math?
I don't care about math.
What do you mean?
If I can do a comic,
I want to imitate it.
No, I mean trivia.
If you suddenly want to imitate it.
Let me imitate it today.
Who can do it?
Takami Sakari.
Takami Sakari is popular now.
Do it, girl.
Oh.
You don't have a board.
Hey.
That's it?
Do you have to do it
until you stop the flow?
I still have it.
It's not similar at all.
Can you do it?
The one that looks like you.
Suiken.
Is it Suiken like Jackie?
Yes.
Suiken.
That's why it's difficult.
What is this?
Is this Suiken?
Are you okay?
There are a lot of comedians
who want to be on TV.
I'm in trouble
if I'm on TV so much.
I don't know how to do this.
What's the last one?
It's Bruce Lee.
Bruce Lee?
It's Takamizaka.
I won't let you do it.
Thank you.
It's the fifth group.
Matsumoto and Miyasako.
The theme is manifest.
Here we go.
Good evening, everyone.
Today, I would like to study about manifest with you.
We have a manifest researcher,
Mr. Uonuma,
Mr. Hikari Koshi.
That's my story.
The manifest when you forget something when you go out in the morning.
Here we go.
Manifest.
The manifest when you are thinking
and you are stopped by someone.
It's annoying.
Teacher.
What?
Stop it.
The manifest when you fall from a high place.
Manifest.
Manifest when you go to a cafe in the middle of summer.
Like this?
Excuse me.
Ice manifest.
Manifest when you meet your ex-girlfriend in an art museum.
Manifest.
Manifest when you enter McDonald's.
Fillet of fish set.
Attena...
Miyasako.
Number 4.
It's me.
Here we go.
Manifest.
Manin took off his vest.
Manifest when you get a call.
Manifest.
Manin.
Manifest when you are driving.
Manifest.
Manin.
It's hot.
Number 6.
Shinagawa Shoji's theme is victory.
Here we go.
I'll do my best.
Last year Hanshin won the championship.
It's been 18 years.
I think 18 years is amazing.
18 years is amazing.
Shut up.
I think 18 years is amazing.
18 years is amazing.
You can do it.
I can't.
Idiot.
I can't do it.
You can do it.
I'm scared.
I can't do it.
You are funny.
I'm scared.
I'm glad I played with you.
Hanshin is a big fan of you.
I'll do my best.
Come on.
I'm scared.
It's too long.
What should I do?
Make it shorter.
Come on.
It's too short.
Make it longer.
It's too long.
I think...
What is it?
Everyone is a good guy.
That's enough.
Thank you very much.
Next year, Yama-chan and Tanaka will be together.
What?
I will be with Miyasako.
No, no, no.
Thank you very much.