Don't think you can win, if you think you can't, you'll lose
Even if you lose, you'll get back your gold
The dream of Yawaru living deep inside of me is waiting for you once in a lifetime
Both teams, assemble!
In the middle of the city, under the clear sky, the legendary Japanese Kaiokai Queen Hibari gathers and a hot battle begins
From now on, the Hibari team vs. the Hibari team will begin the match
Both teams, captain, shake hands
Attention! Eyes!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors
In the first round, the Hibari team will attack the first one, Shoto Hibari
In the second round, the Hibari team will attack the third one
In the third round, the Hibari team will attack the fourth one
In the fourth round, the Hibari team will attack the fifth one
In the fifth round, the Hibari team will attack the sixth one
In the sixth round, the Hibari team will attack the seventh one
In the seventh round, the Hibari team will attack the eighth one
In the eighth round, the Hibari team will attack the ninth one
In the ninth round, the Hibari team will attack the tenth one
The next batter is pitcher Hibari
Why me?
Drinking alone at the bar
I feel the taste of tears
The next batter is pitcher Hibari
The last batter is pitcher Hibari