The chief director of Gaki no Tsukai Arahen is still in his 40s.
He has the world's first encounter with an actress he admires.
Good evening.
Kazuma-san.
I have a different guest today.
I'm going to help people.
I saw Otomo-san's video.
There's another unhappy guy.
Last week and this week...
No, no.
Last week, I tried to kill him.
This week, I'm trying to help him.
I'm happy.
I'm the world's Heipou.
Heipou-san, please come in.
I have a different guest today.
Please come in.
He's wearing a suit.
I'm the chief director of Gaki no Tsukai Arahen.
Kazuma-san, this is the past.
There's an article in the TV industry.
There's an example of a famous talent getting married.
The representative is Sayuru Yoshinaga.
He's the main producer of Fuji TV.
Yoshiko Mita.
The producer of NHK.
There are many producers.
What about this?
Is it going to be on Kaminuma TV?
No, no.
Kaminuma-san will be on Kanzai TV.
I know that.
I'm counting on you.
I'm sure some of you have noticed.
There's no Japanese TV.
Even if there's Fuji, NHK, and TBS.
There's no TV.
Let's put Heipou in here.
That's right.
Who does Heipou like?
This person.
Naoko Amihama-san.
Naoko Amihama.
She has a mysterious look and a slender body.
She's very active in singing and drama.
27 years old.
That's just right.
I'm 40 years old.
I'm 82 centimeters tall.
82 centimeters.
What do you think?
Is your father taller?
No, I'm just 82 centimeters tall.
82 centimeters is good.
You're very stylish, Amihama-san.
I like people who are tall.
I see.
I like Heipou who is tall.
That's right.
Heipou is as tall as Kanabun.
Amihama-san.
Yes.
I'm calling you in the morning.
Thank you.
I hope you have a good time today.
That's right.
And there's a silhouette.
Mr. Matsumoto.
This is it.
Yes.
Mr. Matsumoto, for example, you have this.
I'll turn on the switch when it's off.
Yes.
It's open.
It's pretty good.
This is an indication.
Is it an indication?
Yes.
It's more Heipou.
That's right.
Go.
Run, Heipou.
Yes, I understand.
This is the sign.
Yes.
Do you remember that time at Godanda?
I understand.
It was like this.
Yes.
Put it in your pants and put it on your butt.
It's a little Heipou.
Yes.
Is that okay?
It's a little Heipou.
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
Hello.
Thank you for waiting.
I'm sorry.
Naoko, come on in.
Thank you for waiting.
This is my wife.
Hello.
This is Naoko.
Nice to meet you.
Please sit down.
Naoko, sit down.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
Really.
Yes.
The weather is nice.
It was good.
Really.
I brought Naoko's book.
Is that so?
Go ahead.
Thank you for waiting.
Have you ever met Toshihide?
No.
This is the first time I've met him.
Is that so?
Yes.
This is the first time I've met him.
Is that so?
This is Mr. Amihama.
Mr. Amihama.
Yes.
You always say that.
Mr. Amihama.
That's good.
My Naoko is not here either.
Yes.
This is the first time.
How do you feel to meet him for the first time today?
He's a beautiful person, so I'm very honored.
Is that so?
Thank you very much.
What about Naoko?
What?
It's the first time I've met him.
I've seen him on TV.
Have you seen him on TV?
Yes.
How do you feel to see him in person?
It's better to see him in person.
Is that so?
Yes.
It's rare.
He looks dirty on TV.
I'm sorry.
It doesn't matter.
Naoko.
Yes.
Do you drink alcohol?
I'm sorry.
Is your wife alone now?
I'm alone.
My husband is gone.
I'm sorry.
But I can do things by myself.
This is funny.
This is a masterpiece.
This is an interesting story.
Is that so?
What are you talking about?
TOSHIHIDE.
I'm talking about you.
Can I ask you something?
TOSHIHIDE?
Yes.
I heard something amazing about TOSHIHIDE on the previous show.
What is it?
I heard something like this.
Is that so?
TOSHIHIDE is lonely.
Yes.
TOSHIHIDE sometimes depends on GANG.
Is that so?
How about you, Naoko?
Yes.
Do you depend on GANG?
Occasionally.
That's good.
That's a good match.
That's funny.
After all, we are young people.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
I didn't notice at all.
I didn't notice.
TOSHIHIDE, thank you.
See you later.
I'm Saito.
I often see you on TV.
I've been a fan for a long time.
Is that so?
Yes.
The other day, I went to the baseball game.
That's funny.
I've been a fan for a long time.
I was surprised.
What are you talking about?
Thank you.
I was surprised to see you.
That's why I'm here today.
I've been a fan for a long time.
I have a lot of photos.
Is it better to have a big chest?
No.
That's just right.
I'm sorry.
You should have a big chest.
You have a big chest.
It's a long time since I've been with HEPO.
I'm laughing at HEPO.
I'm laughing at Zaito.
I'm a little nervous.
What about Zaito?
Zaito?
I think Zaito takes all the stories.
Zaito is the leader.
Is that so?
Is there anyone who pulls you?
That's not true.
I work hard.
When I come home, there are people who spoil me.
I think that's the way it is.
That's the way it is.
Please come here.
This is a narrow place.
How big is it?
I don't think it's big enough.
I think this is a little too big.
It's like an action star.
That's funny.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry to ask you this for the first time.
Do you have any memories?
Yes.
I kissed you.
I'm grateful for that.
I don't know if he's in a hurry.
I'm sorry for the sudden request.
Please drink.
It's hard.
I'm sorry for the sudden request.
I think you're a mister.
It's okay.
I'm sorry for the sudden request.
I think you're a mister.
Please drink.
I'm sorry for the sudden request.
What is that?
I can't drink.
I'll drink a little.
What should I do?
It's my first time.
I'll drink a little.
No, no, no.
Shut up.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
You can't do this in the future.
I can't drink.
Ladies and gentlemen.
It seems to be disbanded again.
What?
We.
It seems to be disbanded again.
I don't know that.
Downtown something.
This is it.
I'm sorry.
Why do you have so much?
Hama-chan.
Hama-chan's singer debut.
What does this mean?
Matsumoto-san published a book and became a bestseller.
I had nothing to do with it.
I came here and Hama-chan said,
I'm going to make a bestseller.
I made my solo debut.
Even if it's just the two of us, if you do something like that, we'll be like this.
If that's the case, it's disbanded.
The difference in this year's income is open.
I'm going to sing this song next year.
That's why it's disbanded.
What is that?
Why are you exposed?
Why?
I saw it at first.
Is this you?
No, no, no.
It's Speedy Wonder.
That's right.
No, it's Matsumoto Hitoshi Speedy Wonder.
It's Speedy.
It's completely different.
Is that so?
I didn't know this.
When I went home after the show, I told you.
It's not broken at all.
When I went home the other day, it was broken.
If it's broken, it's broken.
It's still annoying.
It's not broken.
The window was open.
You can give me something.
No, thank you.
I can give you a lot of candy.
When I opened the window,
I heard the sound of the car.
I put it in the car.
It's annoying at that point.
And I put it in the car with a magic cap.
Stop it.
That's not funny.
It's nothing to laugh about.
It's been a long time since I've been so pissed off.
You were so pissed off.
Poison was coming out of my nails.
Are you human?
I'm not saying that I was that pissed off.
I know that.
I was really pissed off.
Did you tell her?
No, I didn't.
What?
I didn't tell her.
I see.
I'm pissed off because...
Other girls around me were like,
I'm scared.
I said I'm not scared.
You'll get angry.
I'll get angry.
We're the same.
You won't get angry with me.
Poison comes out of my nails.
No, no.
You're the only one.
In a week...
You have a week, right?
You're done with school, right?
There are some things that piss me off.
I went to eat Cambodian food the other day.
Oh, you went to Okunino?
No, no.
I think I went to Okunino.
You missed it, didn't you?
I was like...
Excuse me, can I have some yakisoba?
I went to a Cambodian waitress.
It was a woman.
Can I have some yakisoba?
Say it.
What?
I can't hear you.
It's so good.
What?
She yelled at me.
Don't say that.
I can't hear you.
I can't hear you at all.
No, no.
She yelled at me.
What?
It was so good.
She yelled at me.
I couldn't stop laughing.
It was worse than getting angry.
I couldn't stop laughing with her.
What?
It was funny.
She yelled at me.
I was surprised.
I didn't think she yelled at me.
Do you want to go to a Cambodian restaurant next week?
Come here.
She doesn't know anything about talent.
Do you want to go to a Cambodian restaurant next week?
Please give me yakisoba.
You are really...
Maybe the keyword is yakisoba.
So, if you order extra food at a random place,
If you order extra food and say,
Please give me yakisoba,
I'll definitely say,
Let's do that.
Let's go to a Cambodian restaurant next week.
I'll definitely say that.
I've met a lot of people like this.
It's because you are a pervert.
I'm a pervert?
You're a pervert, so you're a pervert.
I'm a pervert, so I'm a pervert.
Why?
Did you get on the bus?
You were in a press conference, weren't you?
I was in a press conference with Mr. Komura.
Again?
What are you talking about?
You were doing something, weren't you?
That's right.
Let's go to the post office.
There's someone you like sitting behind you at school.
Is there a way to give that person a good feeling?
You're sitting behind me, right?
I don't know.
That's right.
You're sitting like this, aren't you?
Yes.
If you sit like this, you'll be like,
What is this guy?
I have to look at his face.
Yes.
Of course, you have to look at his face.
It's painful if you don't have a little more contact.
Yes, I do.
You do this, right?
If you do it like this...
Sensei!
I'm scared!
Sensei, I'm scared!
Matsumoto-kun is weird!
It's like this.
Shut up.
You see?
There's nothing for Sensei to do after I give you the hint!
Just give it to me already!
Why are you looking back and not dancing?
Ma-chan, you said you wouldn't be late this year.
How is the actual situation?
This is...
How do I say this?
I was so surprised by myself.
I don't remember being late at all.
No, no, no, the other day at the shopping district...
I looked at the clock and it was already 3 o'clock.
That's weird.
Is he at home right now?
This is the real thing.
I don't think I should say this.
What do you mean?
There are a few episodes of this show where you laugh, right?
Why are you crying, Matsumoto-kun?
The audience is screaming.
I'm scared of that.
You have a blue face.
I was awake.
You were awake?
I was wearing an Armani suit.
I was up and I was wearing an Armani suit.
He didn't have one.
When I was about to go,
It's like a rakugo roll.
It's like...
Open it. Open it.
The heat...
I don't want to go back to my room, Shou-chan!
Shou-chan lives in the neighborhood.
Shou-chan's mother is holding Shou-chan.
Why is she holding you?
I don't want to!
Oh, you're such a small kid.
I see.
And then...
Something terrible happened.
You're Shou-chan?
There's a fish called Shusseifu.
For example, when a Kampachi comes out, it becomes a Hamachi.
And when it comes out again, it becomes a Buri.
What do you...
What do you mean by coming out?
Do you know? Kampachi becomes a Hamachi.
And Hamachi becomes a Buri.
Do you know?
I've heard of it.
But I don't know exactly what Kampachi is.
Fish is really amazing.
Do you know what comes after a Buri?
What?
Isn't it a Kanketsu?
It's coming out.
The Buri is...
While I'm doing this,
the Buri is coming out.
It's coming out more and more.
Why isn't it coming out at the fish shop?
That's because it was killed during the Buri stage.
You can't kill it.
It has too much power.
It's a fish.
No, no, no.
It's up to the Buri stage.
If you can kill it, it's amazing.
Stop it.
Stop it!
Hey!
Who are you?
What comes after a Buri?
What?
A Super Buri?
Then it becomes an FX.
It's a Kamen Rider.
It becomes a Black.
What are you talking about?
It becomes a fake Buri.
That's what it becomes.
Let's laugh a little more.
It's funny.
It's a fake Buri.
The color of the scarf is different.
I didn't know what you were talking about.
What are you doing?
It doesn't matter.
The other day,
I went out with my girlfriend for half a year.
She said,
You have a big ***.
Mr. Matsumoto,
Don't you have anything to gain from your ***?
Of course I have.
It's a big ball.
I don't have anything to gain from it.
You know what?
I think it's good for greetings.
Why?
Normally, you say,
Hello.
It's not like that.
It's a big ball.
It's a ***.
It's like this.
It's elegant.
Then,
Why is it out?
Because it's big.
I can see that it's big.
It's a big ball.
What are you doing?
It's going to stick to your tongue.
I'm going to stick it to my tongue.
I'm not going to do anything.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm going to do the ***.
No, no.
C-g-g-g-g-ra-g-a-a-g-a-g-g-
Because this will stop pew pew seller
And in hot of this the strong cookie
What about my secret weapon
You um
I am talking about Setsuna-ken
What?
What's that?
Is it a sadism?
The one who did it, or rather the one who got hit...
What's that?
Which one?
No, no, no.
The one who got hit...
...or rather the one who got hit...
...or rather the one who got hit is sadistic.
Is that a special move?
What are you talking about?
It's a mistake.
What?
Does that mean I'm going to be a partner killer?
That's none of your business.
I don't like that.
Do it.
What's that?
That's...
...a sadistic move.
It's already started.
It's a sadistic move.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Don't hit the Setsuna-ken.
I'm sorry, it's a sadistic move.
The power has already been accumulated.
It's a simple story.
It's not strong at all.
I'm sorry.
Please do it.
I'll go.
Yes.