This time, Gaki no Tsukai is...
It's the last time! It's the last time!
If you say that, I'll punch you in the face!
Every time, the recording time is longer than one hour.
It doesn't stop at the broadcast time.
We couldn't show you until yesterday.
Bakushou Hizoutoukyou.
It's a big release!
Laugh as much as you want.
Please forget all the bad things.
Gaki no Tsukai Hizoutoukyou
Laugh as much as you want.
Please forget all the bad things.
This program is brought to you by the sponsors you see.
Gaki no Tsukai
What are you talking about?
The Olympics, the Olympics.
It's so noisy.
What is that?
I'm not interested in it.
You're not interested, are you?
You're not, are you?
But...
Wait a minute.
This is bad.
What?
You're shaking your head like this.
In the middle, it's like this.
It's like this.
Is that so?
Are you looking forward to the Olympics?
Somehow,
You say that once every four years.
That's a lie, isn't it?
Why?
It's not a birthday party for Hikaru Nishida.
It's obviously too early for me.
Isn't that strange?
No, it's okay.
I'll do it properly.
Is that so?
I don't know.
I don't know who's in it.
Is that so?
I only know Yawara-chan.
Yawara-chan is still annoying.
You can be sued again.
Wait a minute.
What do you mean again?
I've been sued once.
Again?
Actually,
I found out a little while ago.
When I heard about Yawara-chan,
I became a huge fan of downtown.
I heard about it.
It's a rumor.
I don't know if it's true or not.
Apparently,
Everyone was looking forward to it.
The two of them became ugly together.
If it's Yawara-chan,
I can't stand it anymore.
This is...
I think it's pitiful.
It's funny.
Everyone was looking forward to it.
If it's Yawara-chan,
The two of them became ugly together.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm sorry.
I've heard about it before.
Is that so?
I can't stand it anymore.
You've grown up recently.
Your face is...
To put it bluntly,
Sexy.
Right?
I don't think so.
I thought,
Kawasaki has grown up.
When he was doing this group,
He was like,
I don't have any white hair.
I have a gold hair.
That's what I meant.
I want to say,
I don't have any white hair.
To put it bluntly,
Sexy.
You don't have to say that.
Other than Pyonkichi-kun,
I've heard that there are flat-faced animals.
Yes, yes, yes.
Matsumoto-san,
You're wearing a T-shirt today.
What are those flat-faced animals?
You're wearing a T-shirt like that today?
I'm wearing it.
I have a lot of flat-faced T-shirts.
You only have one?
Yes.
Why don't you show me once?
I don't know if you'll be surprised.
I'll be surprised.
I have a lot of them.
Really?
The one I'm wearing today is a snake.
A snake?
It's a snake-flat-faced T-shirt.
Why did that happen?
I made a mistake.
A snake-flat-faced T-shirt.
Normally, it's like this.
Yes, yes, yes.
I thought it was vertical.
Vertical?
Like this.
Eh?
Where was this?
What kind of situation was this?
I thought it was vertical.
It was strange when we bumped into each other, right?
At the camp.
I was going to the camp and the snake was rolling down the slope.
I was screaming like this.
When the snake roared,
It rolled down the slope.
So the snake's face was facing forward.
I could only see the side of the snake.
It was crouched.
So I couldn't tell the snake from its face.
You couldn't tell?
That's right.
So this was...
And it was a little off to the side.
I thought it was facing forward,
but normally you don't go in the middle like that.
So it was a little off, and the face was facing this way.
I thought it was coming this way.
It wasn't funny.
I couldn't tell.
No, that's not good.
So I was in trouble.
So besides the snake, what else?
You have a lot, right?
I have a lot.
Other than snakes?
Yes, snakes.
I have a frog, though.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Like Pyongji.
I have one like Pyongji.
It's attached to the back.
Over here.
I can't see it. It's always sticking out here.
It's like a pig.
You see,
it's attached to the back.
Taku isn't on it that much either.
It doesn't seem like it hurts when a sea turtle sheds tears,
so why do you shed tears?
Sea turtles are often asked about this.
But there are videos like that too.
Yes, there are.
They say they cry and cry.
My mother used to say that a lot.
Look at that.
She used to say that when she saw a kingdom of the wild.
That's so nostalgic.
Yes, she used to say that.
It doesn't hurt, does it?
A sea turtle doesn't hurt.
Oh, really?
Because that kind of thing doesn't have a lot of nerves.
That's not true.
No, it's true.
Even if it's a fish,
when it's put down on the sand, it can't do anything.
What?
Pain is a human feeling.
Even if you cut down a fish,
it won't hurt.
It won't hurt at all.
It's just that it's surprised by the situation.
The knife comes in,
it doesn't hurt.
It's just that it's going,
So it's just bouncing?
It's just bouncing.
It's just that it's going,
and that's all.
Is that so?
Yes.
A fish that hurts like that,
that's just a premonition.
That's a little strange.
I don't know why you like that.
Why are you crying?
Why? Do you want to know?
It's not because it hurts, right?
Then what do you think it is?
That's why I'm asking.
I thought it would hurt, but it doesn't hurt.
Then you can think of it as a human woman.
What do you mean?
Let's say a human woman is giving birth to a baby while crying.
If the doctor says, do your best, and the baby is crying, why is that?
If a human woman were to cry, what would happen?
In that sense, a human and a god are the same.
Why is it so quiet?
I'm the only one who's talking.
That's the way it is now.
Why are you crying when it doesn't hurt?
You can tell me that.
There are many theories.
Really?
There are 8 theories.
You said it yourself.
8?
Yes, there are about 8 theories.
One of them is that it's not the child of the person you like.
What if it's all true?
What about the god of the sea?
The god of the sea doesn't fall in love, right?
I don't know that.
Do you think the god of the sea would fall in love?
Then why would he lay eggs?
That's why the god of the sea isn't love.
It's more of a match made in heaven.
It's a forced marriage made in heaven.
But because it doesn't go against the will of the god of the sea,
the god of the sea will do whatever the god of the sea wants.
But he won't call.
He'll just do it.
He'll just run away.
He's a bad guy.
That's right. The god of the sea isn't a bad guy.
He'll say, I like you, I like you.
Why are you saying it twice?
He'll say, let's do it together.
He'll say, I'll call you again.
But he'll never call again.
What are you doing?
He'll say, I'll close the door.
Aoyama.
Right?
He'll say, I was just playing around.
He'll be surprised.
That's strange.
He'll throw up.
He'll go to the hospital.
He'll go to the hospital and check if it's true.
That's it.
Right?
He'll realize it.
That's why he'll run away.
He'll run away.
I don't know.
I want to go to the beach.
Women like sour food.
Men don't.
I want to go to the beach.
Then he'll run away?
Yes, he'll run away.
He won't look and place box.
It's not that he's a man she likes!
And then she'll cry for him.
And he'll cry?
And then she'll cry.
A Beautiful Girl
Let's see...
This is a good one out of the 8.
I'll just end it here.
The skin of the head...
The skin of the head, even if you pinch it, it doesn't hurt that much.
This is one of your tricks!
And by the way, ask the guy next to you!
Don't ask me!
It can't be helped.
You're such an idiot.
It depends on how you feel about it.
It might be hard for a woman to understand.
You're probably thinking, is that so?
And here too, right?
Ah, here?
Here too, right?
It's pretty close to here.
But if you pinch it, it hurts, right?
What do you mean?
If you pinch it, it hurts a little, right?
Does it hurt here?
If you pinch it...
No, it doesn't hurt at all.
If you pinch it yourself, it doesn't hurt.
What?
It hurts.
If you pinch it...
Take out the skin.
If you pinch it, you'll get caught!
I don't like it!
You're making me sadistic!
I know!
I can see it!
I'm scared of the pain!
I hate it!
When I go home and take a shower,
my skin turns blue!
I'm the one who got hit by Hamada!
My skin turns blue after I go home!
I know!
But I can understand it myself.
If you pinch it, it hurts.
That's true.
So what is it?
I want you to tell me why it doesn't hurt.
Ah, then...
I don't know!
What do you think?
Please tell me.
I think it hurts.
What are you doing?
I'm doing it, but it hurts.
It hurts!
It doesn't hurt.
It doesn't hurt!
Then, pinch it!
Then, pinch it yourself!
It hurts!
It doesn't hurt!
If you pinch it like this...
If you roll it, it doesn't hurt!
Then, pinch it!
It doesn't hurt?
No, but...
Then, pinch it like this.
That's right.
Then, pinch it.
I don't like it anymore.
The legend of the flying body from the Tokyo Tower without any equipment.
Please tell me again the legend of the flying body from the Tokyo Tower without any equipment.
Ah, that's how it went.
It's an old, good era.
Does it have anything to do with that?
It's from the 70's.
Ah, you're blushing.
Yes, it does.
What does this mean?
What is it?
Why?
A movie?
A movie.
Yes.
What kind of role did you play?
What kind of role?
What scene?
The detective.
The detective from the Tokyo Tower?
He's dead.
This is...
The detective.
I told him to spare me.
But the director said,
This is something only you can do.
I want you to do it.
From where?
From the Tokyo Tower.
From the top.
What do you mean the top?
The top?
The highest point.
The highest point?
What do you mean the highest point?
The highest point.
The highest point?
It's hard to go up there.
Yes.
What?
I climbed up there on a crane.
A crane?
Up there?
There's no crane like that.
I was surprised when I went up there.
What was surprising?
It was very sharp.
What?
I was sharp back then.
That doesn't matter.
What's that?
I was holding a stick.
What?
How did I do it?
What kind of state were you waiting for?
For that stick?
You have to hold it like this
It's amazing
The wind is so strong
And then?
And then you go like this
You went backwards?
That was scary
No, I don't get it
That's a movie, right?
It's a movie
It's a detective
That detective
Why did he climb all the way up
And fall down like that?
Please watch the movie
I don't know if it's on video
That detective
Is it a suicide scene?
What?
What is that?
Is it a suicide scene?
What?
No, it's not
Why did that detective have to jump?
Tell me about it
You're so complicated
It's not funny at all
He found the culprit
I don't get it
He was looking at the culprit from above
And he was like, that's it!
And then he fell down
What are you going to do?
You're going to die
But
It's a strange story
The more he changed his life
The more he was chasing the culprit
I understand how you feel
There's no continuation to the story
He's already dead
The end
What a strange movie
What is that?
Is that the end?
It's the end
There were only a few actors
I was surprised
But you were okay
Because it was a stunt
You were the stunt for that role, right?
That's right
You didn't put anything on
I didn't put anything on
What happened?
I just fell down
It hurt so much
That's not true
What do you mean it hurt so much?
I fell from the top of the Tokyo Tower
Have you ever been to the Tokyo Tower?
It's made of concrete
I fell down there
It hurt so much
Where did you fall down from?
From the top of the Tokyo Tower
How did you fall down?
I just fell down
You didn't even change your weapon
You just fell down
If you were that far away, you wouldn't be able to do this
Your head is heavy
You wouldn't be able to do this
It wasn't like that
Really
I just fell down
It hurt so much
It hurts
The makeup artist came to me and said
Are you okay?
It hurts
Where does it hurt?
In the end, I went to the sushi restaurant
I heard that you haven't found a cure for water bugs yet
I heard that you have a cure for water bugs at the convenience store
What should we do to cure it?
I have a cure for it
You have a cure for it at the convenience store?
I did it at the convenience store
A German professor told me
You are such a fool
Really?
What did he tell you to cure it with?
At the convenience store
There is a safe
There is
You can put in 1 yen coins or 5 yen coins
At that place
At the foot
The skin will go in
I see
I am a sexy man
Since Marilyn Monroe's Monroe Walk
Sexy walking has not been born in the world
Please teach me the new sexy walk of the 21st century
But it may be true
What are you talking about?
Speaking of which, that may have been the best
Recently, there are some Japanese women who say that their proportions have improved
Right?
But there are not many people who walk in such a sexy way
What do you mean?
Like Marilyn Monroe
Do you know how to walk in such a sexy way?
I have never seen it
Monroe Walk is just the way Monroe walks
It is not a special way of walking
But this is Monroe Walk
Since then, it has not been born
Please teach me the new sexy walk
All right
Please teach me
Oh, my disciple, take it
He is not here
It is a sexier way of walking than Monroe Walk
In the 21st century
To be honest, it may be hurtful for women to say this
But there are still some women who walk in such a sexy way
Right?
Right now, there are some women who walk in such a sexy way
There are some women who walk in such a sexy way
Why do I get a phone call from the country and from the countryside?
Oh, from the countryside? Oh, I was surprised
I want to see my grandchild
I want to hear a good story
You are the one who is being told that
They may come
I get a bit nervous
But I don't want to have a blind date
I want to have a love affair
There are some people who are worried about it
Among the guests today
Oh, there are
They come out and I am one of them
It is a sexier way of walking
The way of walking is different?
Yes
Then, please tell me
What will happen if you do that?
There are two men and three women
Just by walking like that?
There are two men and three women in a group of four
It is complicated
You are the only one
One of them is coming
What is it?
Just walk
Why are you leaving?
What is it?
Just walk
Why are you walking like this?
Like this
Well
I got a bit
I can't do this
I thought I could do this