In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai, we have the manager of Chikizuki, Mr. Dantan, Mr. Isomata.
Mr. Isomata again?
Yes, that's right.
Mr. Isomata is the star of Gaki no Tsukai.
Despite his wild side, he has a kind heart. What will he show us today?
Today, we're going to talk about cooking. Usually, when I watch shows like this, I don't feel like they're delicious.
I see.
That's why the main topic is important.
This is the most important topic.
That's right.
This main topic is, you shouldn't be in a warm living environment.
I see.
That's what we're going to talk about today.
Let's get started.
Nice to meet you.
I'm wearing makeup today.
Are you wearing makeup?
He's wearing makeup in front of the mirror.
Why is that?
I'm changing my mood.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
First, we'll challenge the title call.
Do your best.
Let's go.
Ready, action.
Isomata Takumono, Oishinbo Manzai.
Why are you doing that?
The sauce is in front of me.
What if I put my hand on it?
You'll put your hand on it?
Yes.
You're the assistant director.
Let's do that.
The cameraman can do it.
The cameraman can't do it.
I can only hear your voice.
Ready, action.
Isomata Takumono, Oishinbo Manzai.
It's cold.
Okay.
That was okay.
I'll take the cold one.
Isomata, the food is ready.
It's time to eat.
Where are you looking?
I'm here.
You bastard.
Let's eat.
Welcome.
I'm the chef, Kumagai.
I'm the manager, Isomata.
Nice to meet you.
Let's eat.
This is my first time eating this.
First of all, he tastes the world's delicacy, truffle.
This tastes a little hard to describe.
What?
I've been waiting for this for a long time.
I don't know what to do.
Let's eat.
Next is the escargot croquette.
How is it?
I've never eaten escargot before.
It has potatoes in it, so it tastes like croquette the most.
I made it with the image of croquette.
It's croquette.
I've never tasted escargot before, so I don't know what it tastes like, but it tastes like it's been erased.
Let's eat.
The main dish is red wine.
This is really delicious.
How do you express how delicious it is?
I'll repeat what I said earlier.
It's easy to get familiar with the fact that it doesn't taste like French food.
It's delicious.
But this is French food.
This gourmet program has been completed.
It's mid-March, and it's getting warmer and warmer.
Good evening, I'm the manager, Isomata.
I was invited to such a spring atmosphere today.
I would like to eat delicious traditional French food like escargot in Yoyogi.
Let's go.
Welcome. I'm the chef, Kumanai.
I'm the manager, Isomata.
Nice to meet you.
Today's entree is called a vegetarian salad.
It's a salad with foie gras, truffles, and duck.
It's pretty cold.
Is it cold?
Yes.
It's a little cold, and it's only warm.
It's the first time I've had it, but it's not much different from chicken.
This is escargot croquette.
Croquette?
Yes.
The one on the far left is escargot.
This one?
Yes.
I'll give it to you.
It doesn't really taste like escargot, does it?
No, it doesn't.
Today's main dish is red wine with beef with bones and bulgogi.
Where did you learn to be a chef?
I lived in France for a while.
Really?
Yes.
I don't really like or dislike anything, but it doesn't taste good.
I don't really want to eat it again.
Cut!
Eat it!
That person has finally stood up to Isomato's insolence.
He moved the stage from French to Chinese cuisine for a location tour.
Yamachan Shuren and Oishinbo Banzai will be on the air in the second half of the program.
Ready, go!
Hello.
Good evening.
You're a bit late today.
What's the matter?
Huh?
You're a human being, so you must have something to say.
Nothing.
I'm afraid of heights.
Really?
I don't like heights.
I really don't like heights.
You skydived, didn't you?
What?
I didn't do it.
I can't do it.
I can't do it no matter how many steps I take.
You skydived.
That's right.
I was about to fly, but you got caught in the string.
I said, I don't like it anymore.
I saw a gentle side of you.
What?
Well, well, well.
But if you go that far, you have to do it.
You have to do it, too.
No, I didn't do it.
I don't like things I don't like.
I'm good at things I'm good at.
Someone said that.
Anyway.
I don't like things I don't like.
I'm taking you to a punishment game, so you can't say you don't like it there.
No, I'll say it.
I don't like it.
You're dirty.
That's not good.
You have to do it.
I don't like that kind of thinking.
What?
It's bitter.
I don't like it, but I have to do it.
Where did you come from?
I don't like that person, but I have to go out with her.
I can't do that.
No one said that.
If you don't like it, you can go out with her.
That's a strange example.
Kiss me.
What?
What is it?
It's easy to do it.
That's not it.
If you do it like this, you can't do it like this.
Where are you looking at?
We all decided that.
What are you doing?
I'm talking to everyone.
Men are scary.
Why?
When you're with a girl,
I don't know if the girl feels that way,
but when I'm with her, I look at her.
That's because you have a good father, right?
I don't know if I have a good father,
so I look for a man.
At that time, I have scary eyes.
I know that I'm doing it myself,
but I don't know at that time.
I don't know if it's true.
That's too much.
It's really scary.
I have scary eyes all the time.
I don't think so.
You're looking at her casually, right?
Yes.
I'm saying,
It was too late.
I'm looking at her like this.
Long, long.
My legs and my father.
I'm going to get caught.
I haven't noticed the woman.
It's long.
I shouldn't look at her like that.
I'm looking at her like this.
That's funny.
I don't think there's a woman.
I don't think a woman can look at me like that.
You mean like this?
Yes.
I'm not waiting for that.
No way.
Men are scary.
It would be nice if there was a woman.
I'm saying,
The bell rang.
That's too much.
You shouldn't focus on the bell.
What's this?
You'll get caught.
If that's the case, let's look at her.
As a man, I've never experienced a woman looking at me like that.
I see.
But what about women?
I don't know.
But your father will definitely look at you.
I guess.
I don't know how much he's looking at you.
But if you wear a skirt like this and sit down like you're drinking,
he'll definitely look at you.
He'll look at me, right?
I don't like the way he looks at you.
Your father will listen to you.
Even when you're talking.
But he'll obviously look at you.
He'll be like,
What are you talking about?
He'll be like, what are you doing?
And he'll look at the menu and go like this.
He'll be focusing on the other side and go like this.
Really.
That's dirty.
And then he'll come out like a horn.
He'll come out like this.
You're making a bad face.
Men are scary.
You really have to watch out for women.
I have a question for Matsumoto-san, who's also the leader of the sexy group.
Yes, yes.
Just like a flower has its own flower language,
sushi also has its own sushi language.
What kind of language does sushi have?
That's all there is to it.
I've never heard of sushi language.
That's why we don't say it.
Do you know what a flower language is?
There's something like that.
What about the tulip flower language?
I don't know that.
What is that?
Why did you come here today?
You don't even know that.
If that's the main thing, I'll go look it up myself.
What did you come here for?
My...
Language.
Of course there's a language.
What month were you born?
May.
May, right?
That means...
Shrimp, right?
That's just one of your favorite dishes.
No, no. I was born sushi.
I'm tuna sushi.
Huh?
I was born sushi.
I'm shrimp.
You should at least know that.
My sushi was shrimp.
It was shrimp.
Wait, wait. You were born in September, right?
September.
What sushi were you born in?
Oh, Maki.
Maki.
Maki?
Maki sushi?
Maki sushi.
That's not very good.
Well, that's not a problem.
I taught you the main thing.
What is it?
I don't understand.
I told you to teach me the sushi language.
You want to hear that?
Oh, really?
Yes.
That's fine.
So I'm shrimp, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
You should at least know the sushi language of shrimp.
I'm Maki.
I know.
So first, teach me the sushi language of shrimp.
Oh, that's fine.
Yes.
So tell me why you're panting.
If you're panting here, I wouldn't be able to tell you.
Yes.
Are you sure?
Yes, I am.
So hurry up and tell me.
That's right.
You were born in May.
That's why I'm telling you.
Do you know that?
I know.
You were born in May.
Yes.
Oh, okay.
So hurry up.
Why?
What do you mean hurry up?
What should I do?
You should have come.
I went, so what?
You were born in May, right?
Yes.
Hurry up.
Okay, okay.
Thank you.
What are you eating?
It's a fu.
Hey.
What?
Tell me the sushi language of shrimp.
Okay, I'll tell you.
You should have woken up in the morning.
I woke up.
I woke up, so I'm here.
What are you doing?
What?
You should have woken up in the morning.
What about the roll?
What are you talking about?
I have my own sushi language.
So tell me that.
You were born in September.
I want to know.
What about the roll?
You guys are out of rolls.
I am shrimp.
I should have woken up in the morning.
You...
You should have woken up, Matsuo.
The sushi language of roll.
You were born in September?
Are you talking about that?
Can you tell September is the previous and the second period?
It's my turn.
I was born in September.
So I'm the previous period.
It's okay.
The previous period is okay.
Who taught you that?
The fat one, right?
It's divided into the fat roll and the thin roll
The previous one was the fat roll
Then the fat one
The fat one, right?
Kawajan is...
What is this?
What is Kawajan?
I want you to remember my words
That's why you should say it
I'm so angry
You're angry?
If you say that, you'll have to say it from January to December
It's fine
Right?
Is there anyone from January?
Yes
This is a rose
What?
A rose sushi?
The current one is a rose sushi
It's not a big deal
Yes, a rose sushi
A sushi word
It's fine if you gather
What is this?
It's like you're throwing it away
At this pace
You can't even make fun of 12 of them
It's obvious that you won't do it
Aoka, this is the end
Do you know anyone from January?
A rose sushi
This guy is annoying
It's fine if you gather
Anyone from February?
There are already a few
What about February?
Kanpyo
Kanpyo maki
It's Kanpyo maki
It's Kanpyo maki, so please remember it
What about the sushi word?
It's fine if you don't have it
What are you talking about?
That's how you feel about Kanpyo maki
Right?
It's fine if you don't have it
There are 10 more
That's how it is
What do you mean by that?
There are many things
Is there anyone you want to ask?
What month?
December
It's the end of the year
What about the sushi word?
What about December?
I was surprised
I thought it was fine
I see
It's the end of the year
It's a joke
It's gone
It's gone since January
I see
It's gone since December
I thought it was too much
It's the end of the year
It's fine if you don't have it
This is a question for Dandy Matsumoto
Thank you
If you do this, it's the end
Please tell us the 6 things your dad does
There are many
Really?
It won't work
I don't think so
It's the best 6
I see
What's the 6th?
The 6th is
Writing your name on your underwear
That's not your dad's fault
It's your mom's fault
You write your dad
It's the end of the year
It's your mom's fault
Then it's the 7th
What?
Then it's the 6th
The 6th
What do you think it is?
There are thousands of them
What do you think your dad is?
My dad...
When he wears socks, he does this
He does this
That's stupid
It's stupid, but tell us the order
It has nothing to do with my dad
I see
What is it?
Tell us the top
The top?
The top is
When he gets angry
Hey!
That's stupid
This is pretty bad
When he gets angry
That kind of dad
What's the 5th?
The 5th is
When he gets angry
It's not that different from before
It's all about movement
What's the 3rd?
The 4th
When he hits
How do you make this funny?
I don't know
Stop it!
Yamasaki Hosei's Oishinbo
Oishinbo Banzai!
The last dish
It's Beijing Koya
Beijing Koya
It's called Beijing Duck
Beijing Duck?
It's black
It's because of the rain
The rain?
When?
Beijing Duck
It's a luxurious dish
Now
I'd like you to eat the Beijing Duck
It's for you
I'll give you an example
Sometimes
When you're drunk
You walk home on the train
When you're not on the train
At that time
You remember
I don't know what to say