Chikichiki, Urekkosakka, Takasu, how do you call them?
I don't know
Chichihenge
Chichihenge is the 7th time
There were 7 changes during the meeting
The one who laughs after seeing them has to pay 1000 yen
It's a serious game
Let's go to the main character
Please come in
A childhood friend in downtown
He is now a popular writer in a variety show
How much money can he collect?
In the past, Isomata was the most
I did it
I put Isomata in
Really?
I don't know the meaning of putting Isomata in
After all, he is an amateur
He said that he came up with an idea
Because he came up with an idea
Yes
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching
What should we do?
Let's do skydiving
Skydiving?
What does it mean?
Skydiving movie
Do you want to do it with a girl?
Nakamura Kayosho
Do you want to see Kayosho?
I thought I wanted to see it
Recently, Isomata is not Okamoto
Isomata is amazing
Yamazaki still has a task
There is a task called Mori Man
What is that?
If you can clear that, you may be able to do it again
Let's see a new one
Let's see if I can do it again
I don't feel that I haven't done it before
It's a new morning
You can't do it either
It's too long
It's impossible for Yamazaki to do it
Skydiving
No
I can't do it
In a simple place
That's a great name.
May I?
My son is here.
May I take a picture with you?
No, no.
Excuse me.
My son is here.
May I take a picture with you?
Takeshi!
Who is it?
I don't want to see her.
Why don't you go?
Why are you silent?
Go away.
Why don't you go?
What's wrong with you?
Let's go.
Look at me.
Don't be arrogant.
No.
I'm sorry.
That doll is funny.
What's that doll?
What's that?
It's creepy.
It's so real.
Do you really want to see mine?
It's funny.
Let's go.
The tea on the right is broken.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Well, I heard that there are many interesting stories.
I heard that there are many interesting stories.
This is the end of the story.
What are you doing?
You are getting popular in the second half.
I'm tired!
Not tough enough?
I just got tired?!
What are you guys doing here?
It's hot. It's hot.
I'm tired.
Thank you for your hard work.
I told you, didn't I?
How much did you pay?
7,000 yen.
The lowest?
No, not that much.
No way.
Nakamura P. 9,000 yen.
This is the lowest.
I'm going to drink tonight.
Drink!
Thank you.
Today's opening was a little boring.
It was the same last week.
This week, too.
This week's opening is the worst.
It's the worst.
That's why I have to do my best here.
That's not good either.
Why not?
I'll do my best.
What should I do?
There's nothing to do.
How many years has it been since we started?
It's been about seven years.
About once.
The silent return home.
We're the silent return home?
I think this girl should do her best if she's paying for the ticket season.
There's nothing to do with this.
There's nothing to do with the ticket season?
There's nothing to do with it, but she's paying for it.
But I'll give you the money.
I'm just being honest.
What?
If I die, will you cry?
I won't cry.
You won't cry, will you?
You haven't done anything.
If you say that, I'll make fun of you.
But if I die this time, I'll cry.
Why?
Why won't you cry?
Who are you?
Do you know?
Wait a minute. What will happen to you if I die?
He said that.
What will happen to you if I die?
What do you mean, what will happen to you?
I know, I know.
You're sleeping.
You're sleeping tonight.
Hello?
It's Okamoto.
What is it?
Masumoto-san just died.
That's not possible.
You have to do it now.
You'll cry, won't you?
I won't cry.
You won't cry?
He just died.
I don't know how to say it.
He was caught in a container.
Where was he?
Next to the container.
Why?
He was next to the container.
He was caught in the container, so he was next to the container.
But in normal life, there's not much happening next to the container.
There is such a thing.
There isn't?
Next to the container, like this.
What are you doing?
What is this?
Why is this happening in a container?
It's a container.
Sorry, what is a container?
What is a container?
It's like a box made of iron.
It's a container.
What is a container?
Why are you caught in a container?
I was raised by the Kimijima family.
I graduated from the top fashion school in Paris.
I have a question for Matsumoto-san.
What kind of clothes are popular this summer?
In general, when it comes to fashion,
it's more like Hamada than me.
Actually, it's different.
Well, that's how it is.
Yes, yes.
What about you?
What kind of information do you have this summer?
I don't have any information.
That's cool.
You don't have any information, but when it comes, it's popular.
It's like the trend is following you.
Who are you following?
Old man!
Let's go to the trend.
What are you doing?
The trend is behind you.
Don't be thrown down.
Sorry, sorry.
Please calm down.
The wind is strong.
I got it.
I'm sorry.
What is it?
The trend of summer.
Ah, the trend.
You can see the trend.
Really?
Do you know what was popular last summer?
What was popular last summer?
It's Pichi Tea.
Pichi Tea?
It's definitely Pichi Tea.
It's not Pichi Tea.
Ah, Chibi Tea.
Laugh! Laugh!
Yes, Chibi Tea was popular.
This summer...
First of all, the best information.
Yes.
Right?
The fastest information.
Yes.
This year...
This will surprise you.
What?
Eh...
Bullets.
A lot of bullets.
Bullets?
A bullet?
A bullet...
I don't know if it's a bullet, but...
I'll do it like this.
No way!
The one with a lot of bullets...
It's stupid.
Is it stupid?
No matter where you go, it's always like that.
Summer.
This summer, Matsumoto-san...
How many bullets are you going to use?
With bare hands.
Summer.
Ah, is that so?
Yes, yes, yes.
You have to do it first.
Matsumoto-san, do it.
But if you go to the beach with that, it'll be hot, right?
Go to any bar in the world.
Just by ordering the first one, you'll surprise the people around you.
This is a question for Matsumoto-san, who is called the king of first-class menu selection.
When you go to a super high-end bar,
how do you order the menu so that the people around you won't think it's your first time?
It's all in one go.
For example, you know golf, right?
Yes, yes.
You go to a country club.
Ah, yes, yes.
You go like this, right?
Country club, yes.
Right?
You go like this and ring the bell.
There's probably a bell, right?
Well, there is.
Ring the bell!
I want to go around at 90.
That's up to you.
If you do that, you'll be told to go around at 90.
Depending on what you do, the other person will look down on you.
That's different.
The bottom is 90 and the top is 120.
Then the other person will be surprised.
What is that?
It's the same as when you go hiking.
The other person will be surprised.
When I go hiking?
That's what you did when you went hiking, right?
What?
Well, at this time of the year, I want to go up from the front of the station.
Yes, yes.
I don't want to show off, but I know that.
Everyone does that.
I'll tell the owner.
This guy is crazy.
That's an interesting story.
I've heard it before.
I'll tell Cathy, of course.
Cathy, too.
I don't like the eyeballs.
This guy is crazy.
I'll tell her.
It's the same as when you go to a super high-end bar.
That's right.
Of course, it's different from the moment you enter the bar.
It's different from the moment you enter the bar.
What?
From the moment you enter the bar?
Yes.
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
I don't know.
There are two more times.
I'm sorry.
I'll be waiting.
How long will you be alone?
There's one more.
Oh, man.
I'm really sorry.
I'm waiting for you.
Oh no.
Homemade chance?
Well,
I'll be waiting for you.
It's a chance to go home.
Well, well, well, well...
How should I put it?
Like this, right?
Well, like this.
Oh, it's a little slanted?
It's slanted.
And, well, put it as low as possible.
It's not cool at all.
I really don't know what's going on.
Are you going to show me?
It's dark.
What are you talking about?
I don't know what's going on.
Well, as low as possible.
And, well, like this, like this, like this.
And, well, the menu.
It's the menu.
Oh, it's light.
I'm not trying to make you laugh.
It's a cool order.
Oh, really?
Of course it's an order.
I'm going to order something.
Oh, do you have wine?
Yes, we do.
I'll get you some wine.
What kind of wine is it?
Huh?
What kind of wine do you have?
Well, I've got everything ready.
Oh, really?
If you want.
Do you have everything?
Well, I've got everything ready.
It's red wine, though.
Oh, it's red.
Do you have everything?
Yes, I do.
What?
Do you really have everything?
Yes, I do.
I'm in a bad mood.
Why?
I'm going home.
This is a question for Mr. Matsumoto, who is famous for killing women.
Yes, yes, yes.
What's the secret that women come from the other side?
It's a great question.
What?
This is a little different from the previous questions.
Matsumoto Makimono.
That's what I'm talking about.
Right?
I don't know why.
Please introduce it to me.
How do you get a woman to come to you?
First of all, move fast.
There are a lot of them.
Well, let's press eight.
Yes, eight.
You like to press something, don't you?
Eight.
Move fast.
What does that mean?
Everything moves fast.
Yes, yes, yes.
Move fast.
Is that okay?
First of all, hit this on the head.
I see.
And draw a circle.
What does that mean?
For example, there's a microphone over there, right?
Yes, there is.
Please touch that microphone.
Wow, it's an old man.
It's an old man.
Move your hand forward a little bit.
You're saying that too much.
It's an old man.
It means draw a circle.
What do you do?
Say it again.
Wow, it's an old man.
It's a little small.
It's an old man of an electrician.
When you leave the hose at the front door and come to pick it up, the electrician will come.
When you turn on the air conditioner, the hose will come to the front door.
That's enough.
That's why I said move fast.
I'm saying draw a circle.
It's an old man.
That's why I said what do you do?
Well, it's like what most people are doing now.
It's an old man.
There's more.
It means draw a circle.
It's an old man.
What is that?
It means draw a circle.
It's important to draw a circle.
Is that so?
Is that a circle?
Well...
This is my business talk.
I can't draw a circle when I'm talking about business.
Women have to draw a circle.
It's different from usual.
It's very sweet.
Do you usually talk with your voice?
No, at home.
At my house.
At my house?
And?
The door is closed.
What did you say?
What?
It's a chain.
It's a bad news.
It's going up.
Do you want something to drink?
What?
Calpis soda.
Are you sick?
Why are you crying?
It's cold.
What?
It's the sun.
Thank you.
This is interesting.
The hair is long.
What?
It's stretched.
I've come this far recently.
I used to have short hair.
Short hair is good.
What?
I wanted to stretch my hair.