You are doing well.
And the young boy is coming.
He's so handsome.
You have to punish him.
Right?
Today, I'm going to interview him.
I'm going to ask him about the TV station.
These two are going to be the main characters.
Thank you.
I'm going to interview him today.
Taino coincidence.
We'll ask you about III Annihilating weeds on fireat.
We're going to interview Taichang.
We are watching the Amon gram.
We'll adjudiquing it from here.
We'll say.
How far are they now.
I'd like my staff to ask whether it's all OK.
Let's go to the venue.
Put the car in the right place!
You're the one who's being too much.
I'm telling you to put it in the right place.
Why?
I'm surrounded by fans.
I'm not a fan of Saito-san.
I'm going to sing in the corner of the car.
You're singing in the corner?
I'll sing in the beginning.
The song I'm listening to is...
the song is called,
I'm going to use the word,
I'm going to go to the C-Make in Japan.
What kind of woman is that?
Don't make her이라고 싶어.
What was that?
That's what I said.
You can say what I said.
I'd be down if somebody asked me.
I don't get like this sometimes.
Don't say I gots you.
Such a chatty guy.
He's pissed.
OK, let's go to the audio.
I see your Chauffe.
I'm working.
I'm making money.
If you have hands like me, you can earn as much as you want.
Are you saying that?
I have this.
I have a different cup.
Hey, everyone.
This is the only point.
Let's stop it.
Depending on the situation, we can think about it.
I'm listening to this only.
She's wearing earphones.
Our command will go here.
If you don't mind, we'll listen to you.
Let's go.
I'm looking forward to it.
What are you going to say?
Are you a guillotin?
Excuse me.
Can you take a picture of me?
I'm not a guillotin.
You want me to take a picture of you?
Please take a picture of me.
Please write it down.
Please write down Aya-chan.
Aya-chan's Aya.
That's the top.
Please write down Aya-chan.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Can you take a picture of me?
I'm not a guillotin.
You want me to take a picture of you?
Please write it down.
I'm not a guillotin.
Let's go.
Thank you very much.
Please take a picture of me.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
When I was shopping, a high school student came to me and said,
I went to a tea party with Sugawara of Ichiro Produce.
I was asked to go home by the stove.
Are you happy?
I don't feel bad.
Is that so?
Excuse me.
Can I ask you a private question?
Do you have a girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend at the moment.
Do you have a girlfriend at the moment?
I'd like to take a picture of you.
Can you give her a cigarette?
Can you look to the left?
Can you change your clothes?
Can you put on your helmet?
Can you raise one foot on the chair?
Can you do a pose of a beehive?
Then, please stand up and do that.
I can't do anything.
Like this.
Keep doing it, keep doing it.
Please do that for a while.
Then, please keep doing it for a while.
If you can do it like this.
I can't do it.
Okay.
Go, go, go.
I can't do it.
Is it better to do it higher?
Higher.
A little higher.
Okay.
It's difficult.
I can't do it.
Go, go, go.
Do it.
Hey.
What are you doing?
I can't do it.
You are.
I won't say no. I'll do it all.
I'm surprised.
You brought a banana.
You came all the way.
I thought the last one would be a little strange.
But it's easy to start.
Look at the camera.
Ready, set, go!
Don't get carried away.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
Good morning.
I haven't slept much since yesterday.
Why?
I've been thinking about you.
I'm happy.
Tell me.
Tell me what you thought of me.
This is also a kind of telling.
It's hot, isn't it?
Isn't it especially hot this year?
It has nothing to do with the week.
It's really not hot this year.
It's hot.
Was it this hot every year?
Yes.
Is the air conditioner on?
It's on.
What do you do when you're sleeping?
I leave it on.
No!
Why?
When I was in middle school, my family died.
I slept with the air conditioner on.
It happened to me.
Why did two people die?
If there was one person, I would have died.
But my grandparents died together.
They were sleeping in the same room.
I'm confident that I won't die even if the air conditioner is on.
I won't die.
I won't die even if I sleep in the electric room.
You shouldn't blame it on the air conditioner.
That's wrong.
Is that so?
That's human life.
That's a coincidence.
There are people who die sleeping in a kotatsu.
Even if it's dry.
There are!
There are people who die in a kotatsu.
I don't believe it!
I don't believe it either.
I've never heard of it.
People who die in a kotatsu after they dry themselves.
That's right.
Because they take all the water.
If you have a thirst, you should drink something.
You don't have to stay in the kotatsu forever.
You can't stay in the kotatsu all the way.
Is that how you do it?
That's how I do it.
That's wrong.
You don't even feel that you're thirsty.
What are you?
Are you a housewife?
No, no, no.
I'm talking.
You don't even feel that you're thirsty.
You feel like you're dreaming.
I'm thirsty.
I can't do this.
That's strange.
What are you going to do to celebrate your 100th birthday?
I'm looking for something to do.
I don't know if you can go, but you can go on a trip to the moon in a few years.
Yes, the moon.
You've been there, haven't you?
I haven't been there.
Why not?
It seems like a great place.
What's wrong?
I'm scared to go on a plane.
I want to go skiing.
Are you scared to go on a plane?
No, I'm not.
Aren't you scared?
No, I'm scared.
What are you talking about?
You're from Butohaya, so you're pretty scared.
It doesn't matter.
I'm scared.
You're scared.
You're going to shake.
You're fine.
You're always shaking a little.
That's not what I expected.
When you're shaking, your face is so bright.
That's right.
When I'm scared, I act like I'm reading a book.
But when I'm shaking...
I really don't know what to do.
You know, when you're scared, bad things happen.
I can't do anything.
I'm really scared.
I think I said this before.
I was on a plane three or four years ago.
I was on a plane on my way to Osaka.
I was hungry, so I went to the studio.
I brought food from the plane.
I got on the plane and saw the screen.
It felt like New Year's.
Happy New Year.
Last year, I saw the news about the earthquake.
I was on the news about the earthquake.
So I thought I'd ask you to make a video for me.
I thought I'd ask you to make a video for me.
I broke my leg.
Please let me off the plane.
I really wanted you to let me off the plane.
I wanted you to let me off more than a boy I hated.
Now Komashiro has gone.
He hasn't gone.
I'm going to make him go now.
Really?
Don't do that.
It's like this.
I don't believe them.
When they go, they say,
Welcome.
I'm always thinking,
Can I go back to that world?
You're thinking too much.
Why do you think like that every day?
When I'm on the plane,
I can't help it if I fall.
But I'm on the plane.
That can't be helped.
That's right.
If you get on the plane,
Can I eat the candy on the plane?
When a kid says that, I can't help it.
Do it after you get on the plane.
After I get on the plane?
You're here.
Yes.
Are you a general?
What are you doing now?
I'm a student.
A student?
You're a student?
You're overdoing it at night.
I'm not.
I'm quiet.
Quiet?
You're overdoing it.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Not now.
Not now?
What do you mean?
Did you break up?
When I was in kindergarten.
When you were in kindergarten?
That's funny.
You idiot.
That's amazing.
Thank you very much.
It's called boldness.
Boldness.
Good evening.
I have something I want you two to talk about today.
It's a sardine.
Everyone, let's get ready to laugh and listen.
So let's talk about this kind of theme.
Is that okay?
The first person who finds it will be the name.
I went to the deserted island.
Who?
Sribachi Yohei.
That was the end of Edo period.
There was a person called Sribachi Yohei in Edo period.
I went to the deserted island.
That's right.
You can't go when it's cold like this.
What are you doing?
I have a wallet like this.
Sribachi Yohei went to play.
He went to play.
His chest is wide open.
He's having fun.
You can't go to a place where there are so many people.
That's why it's heavy.
He went like this.
There's no one.
That's right.
When I looked back,
Sribachi Yohei.
That's it?
He went to the village alone.
He went to the deserted island.
There's no one.
Sribachi Yohei.
That's how he was discovered.
That's right.
But Sribachi Yohei.
The number of people who use it will decrease from now on.
Is that so?
It will disappear.
There are a lot of things that will disappear.
What?
Because if all the old women who are alive die now,
Kanzashi will disappear too.
But what?
Kanzashi?
People who do that kind of work will use it.
What kind of work?
It's not a geisha.
Geisha will disappear too.
That's right.
Sumo will disappear too.
It's a national sport in Japan.
It will definitely disappear.
Pigs are fighting against each other.
Which one will win?
That's right.
It's not a geisha.
It's better to choose the strongest one.
I'm not interested in sumo at all.
What are you saying now?
What?
Young people.
Why?
There are people like that in the Ujishima room.
I will definitely win.
Who are you talking about?
Who is the strongest now?
The strongest?
Takahana is the strongest now.
I will win.
I will win twice.
You said the number of times.
I will win twice in a row.
Really?
Really.
Takahana must be busy.
Please come to me.
Don't you see me?
Please, Takahana.
Takahana.
Please.
Come to me.
Please, Takahana.
Please.
Please come to me.
Please, Takahana.
That's a foreign manga.
I will definitely win.
You are slow.
I can see you when you turn around.
That's not true.
You are a fool.
You are a dinosaur.
I can see you when you turn around.
That's not true.
You are a fool.
I will definitely win.
You will not win.
If you get caught, you will be punished.
I don't have a place to be caught.
What?
What are you wearing?
What are you wearing when you play?
I don't have a place to be caught.
That's my favorite party dress.
It's a wine bottle.
I don't have a place to be caught.
If you get caught, you will be punished.
You should have just killed me.
It's impossible to punish you.
Because you are my partner.
It will be over soon.
Let's go.
Booby, Booby, Booby.
I would be spending my whole life listening to this kind of apartment music
Letting myself be done right
Will that be reasonable to you?
Goma, Heroes, you look like it's in Campus TV
So I would be the kind that
would show up right on the day it's going to be sold out
Thank you
Now go straight to the quewing
Go from way over there
What?
Hello, I'm Henteki.
Thank you very much.
So, let me tell you something.
There will be no broadcast on Tuesday, August 13th next week.
Oh, what is this?
It's a one-time show.
Oh, I see.
There is no broadcast for this, so the next one will be on Tuesday, August 20th.
Oh, I see. It's a one-time show.
Why don't we all go to Giroppon together?
That's nice.
So, we will take a break next week.
Let's meet on Tuesday, August 20th.
Yes.
So, please look forward to next week's broadcast.
Thank you.
This program was brought to you by the sponsor you are watching.