Let's get started.
Good evening.
Oh, hello.
What is it?
It's Chi-Chi.
It's Chi-Chi's otaku painting.
You're so cocky.
It's a great painting.
It's not great.
It's Jomo Goten.
Jomo Goten?
I don't know.
Excuse me, may I?
Sure.
Excuse me.
You're wearing slippers.
You're wearing sandals.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Chi-Chi's house has been renovated.
It's been about six months.
Six months.
Well, he's sitting somewhere.
Hello.
Please come out, camera man.
I can't get through.
A weird guy is here.
Hello.
Are you his wife?
What are you talking about?
Thank you for coming.
Please say hello.
Thank you.
Ma'am, this is a little boring.
Thank you very much.
What are you doing?
It's cold.
Excuse me.
Please come in.
I'd like to have a special sushi.
I can't believe you're a wife.
Thank you very much.
I don't need to serve you anything.
Do you want some coffee?
What?
Yes.
Well, that's fine.
What?
This is a mansion.
This is not a mansion.
Well, this is...
This is outside.
Outside?
You're amazing.
Where can I get out of here?
Is this okay?
Please open the door.
That's great.
What are you doing?
You look like a child.
Open the door.
Are you an elementary school student?
You're using a luxurious land, aren't you?
Why?
That's great.
You can have a room here.
That's true.
This is a small table.
A small table.
That's right.
This is a staircase.
Of course, the second floor.
The second floor?
This is a staircase.
Is this a fireplace?
It's not a fireplace.
It's a bus stop.
There's a space like this in the back.
What is this?
I don't know.
There's something written here.
There's a girl here, isn't there?
There is.
There's a girl here.
I can see her panties.
What are you going to do with her panties?
Ma-chan will come today.
Let her go somewhere else.
It's dangerous.
Why?
That's the right thing to do.
I can't do that.
Why don't you go to an art museum?
I'm going to a forest.
What are you up to today?
It's a celebration.
What kind of celebration?
What kind of celebration do you usually bring?
Is it a tepura?
Is it a cake?
It's a delicious toro cake.
He's a bad guy.
What is it?
You came all the way here.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to do something useful.
That's right.
We're people who can only think about other people's bodies.
You've helped me a lot.
That's right.
What are you going to do?
I'd like you to lend me some money today.
You're causing me trouble.
I can't help you at all.
I don't need your help.
You came all the way here.
I'd like you to lend me 2 million yen.
I'd like you to do something useful.
What are you up to with 2 million yen?
Today, I'm going to look up the power of the new house.
Why are you looking up the power?
It's been half a year since I built the house.
I thought it would be a little dangerous.
There's a mistake.
Koji?
Koji.
I'd like you to look into it.
I'll ask someone to do it.
No, no, no.
What are you talking about?
Downtown is about looking up the power.
Originally.
Oh, yeah.
You're looking up the power.
It's a direct translation.
Downtown.
It's a suburb.
That's right.
I'm looking up the power.
Can I drink the coffee you put in?
The cameraman is angry.
I can't drink coffee.
First of all, you use a vacuum cleaner.
If you use a vacuum cleaner, you use a lot of electricity.
But it's okay now.
It's okay.
And here.
Use a stove.
I don't need it now.
It's hot.
Use a stove.
I'll make it the best.
680W.
That's right.
I brought a lot of stuff.
And then.
Oh, that's nice.
There's rice in it.
That's nice.
But it's hot because I turned on the stove.
It's hot.
Let's turn on the fan.
Should I turn it on?
No, not yet.
I think it's okay.
Is it electric?
Electricity.
It's okay to do that.
Let's turn on the mixer.
It's stronger than I thought.
It's strong.
That's strange.
And then.
Use a dryer.
It's still working.
There's no mistake.
That's nice.
I'm tired.
You're tired because you've been here for a long time.
I'll give you a massage.
Why are you so serious?
I'll give you another massage.
It's still working.
Where are you going?
Chiichi.
What is it?
I'm doing something useless.
I'm doing it for you.
Let's turn on the dryer.
It's still working.
There's a lot of laundry.
Let's do this.
Let's set the timer.
How much electricity do we have left?
It's been about 9 years.
It doesn't fly much.
Do you want to blow up our electricity?
I don't want to blow it up.
Let's go to the microwave.
Switch on.
It's working.
What are you doing?
Oh, no.
Chiichi, it's pitch black.
Everyone watching TV today, it's pitch black.
Let's say goodbye.
Thank you very much.
I'm Chiichi's otaku.
What are you eating?
What are you putting on your teeth?
Why is it so dark?
There's seaweed on it.
You must have eaten something.
It's just vinegar.
Didn't I say that?
I'm nervous because I'm on TV.
You're nervous.
You're the one who's nervous.
There's a theme today.
It's a big legend.
That's a big deal.
I'm doing it today with the theme of raising my waist.
That's good.
Today's guest is no big deal.
Don't say that.
I'm sorry, but this is the time when I can respond to my body.
It's a big deal.
I think it's been 24 hours since I started this.
That's right.
I'm sure you're doing it now.
It's tough.
I think I have a strange organ.
I can't see anything wrong with my body.
I think I have a bad artificial dick.
I'm sorry.
You're saying that artificial dick is bad.
Stop it.
Let's go to the toilet.
I can't.
I don't want to.
I have to do it.
But I'm watching you.
I hate today's guest.
What do you hate?
Look at him.
Everyone's looking at me.
I don't mean to say it in a bad way.
It's dirty.
It's better to be dirty than dirty.
If anyone says it's dirty, it's not good.
What do you do?
You don't say dirty people are clean.
You're the guy who's really dirty, but you don't say it's clean.
What do you say?
They're all dirty.
You're not talking about a girl who's full of dicks.
It's the swimming
you're talking about.
You know, it looks like...
You always come out with two guys, right?
Yes
Well, you're in charge of the guys, you're in charge of the ugly ones
But you come out with two guys
I do that
When you come out, the fans are really big
It's different today
When I come out, most of the people's eyes are like this
Why?
When you talk, they look at you, when I talk, they look at me
No, no, no, you're a guest from Hamada
Look, look, look, look at that
I think I'm a little crazy
What are you going to ask?
Which one do you want me to ask?
If you're going to care about that
I know
I really know
Really?
Yes, yes
What?
Which one do you want me to ask?
Are you going to ask one by one?
It's going to take time
It's better to ask in front of you, isn't it?
Which one do you want me to ask?
You're the first one, why are you glaring at me?
You have a bad taste
What are you eating?
Are you going to use it as food?
Give me a theme
If there is no theme, I can't do it
When you're tired, if there is no theme
Favorite food
I'm originally a seafood bowl person
I'm not a seafood bowl person
What is it?
I'm a human being
I'm originally a good boy
I'm a good boy
Food too
Food was pretty noisy
The food I liked the most was chikuwa
It's a high-class food
I put cucumber in chikuwa
You're a sticky man
That's delicious
The people are different
I've been to a lot of places
You've been to me?
I've been to China
China?
I've been to Fujian, China
You've been to Fujian, China
Me? I've been to China
He went to Starwars
He went to China
He went to Hahar
verified
went to China
he went to China
Melissa
Yes, the rice ball that you hold with the right hand of your right-hand man.
Let's move on to the next one.
What the hell are you laughing at?
You often say MVP in the award ceremony. What does MVP mean?
I have no idea.
It doesn't mean nothing.
That's true.
For example, if you say Chuck YKK, it means something.
Wait a minute. Chuck YKK?
I didn't say anything.
YKK means something to Chuck.
Can you tell me?
Sure.
Do you want to hear it?
Please.
But it has nothing to do with this.
No, no, no.
What does YKK mean?
Our...
K
Kid
What do you mean by our kid?
Our
Young
Our?
Yes, yes.
We are
KID
Always
Yes, yes, yes.
KID
Always
That's what it means.
What?
I'm a big shot.
Right?
That's what it means.
That's enough.
Tell me about MVP.
I want to hear about MVP.
I want to hear about it.
What do you think?
I don't know.
Please tell me.
MVP
Everyone
That's good.
MVP
Everyone
V
Surprised
That's good.
P
Let's repeat it.
Think about it.
Everyone
V
Surprised
P
Let's go to the pool.
I don't want to go to the pool.
People often say that eel and umeboshi are bad for your stomach.
Why is that?
People say that it hurts their stomach.
It's the same as eating.
What happens is...
For example,
There is a dressing room.
I'll put you in there.
Please put me in there.
This is the situation when I ate eel and umeboshi.
When I opened the dressing room,
I was talking to the side.
Who? Who? Who?
If you come into my dressing room...
You never talk.
What happens?
What happens if I put you in one of the dressing rooms and lock you up?
In the end, they fought and clashed with each other.
Can you break this place?
They jumped out.
It's a so-called kick.
Now...
You've said it well.
Why doesn't the lens bubble?
I don't know.
In the past,
Lenses used to bubble like this.
In the past, why did you put hot water in the water dispenser?
You're good.
I'm sorry.
Why doesn't the lens bubble?
I'm sticking it.
What do you mean by sticking it?
Your bad breath is all over the place.
Can you say something like that?
You can't always say something like that.
What's wrong with you?
I can't do it anymore.
Wait.
If you say something like that, I can't say it anymore.
I'm sorry. It was my fault.
Why can't you say something like that?
Why doesn't the lens bubble?
It's because the bubble burst.
Damn it.
Even if the audience cheats me...
Hama-chan comes out in various fashions every time.
Why do you wear the same clothes every time?
You...
You look like a fashion leader right now.
I'm not.
You have to be careful.
I haven't changed at all.
What I'm aiming for is antique.
For example, if you wear the latest fashion clothes.
It's okay now.
It's cool.
You think you're a leader, right?
10 years later, 20 years later, you'll be laughed at.
For example, Masatoshi Nakamura.
He was cool back then.
Now that I think about it, it's terrible.
It's like Uchimaki Carl.
That's a total...
It's like a ragged rapper jean.
But he's back.
He's back with a rapper jean.
Giba-chan used to say,
Soiya! Soiya!
That's not embarrassing.
It's embarrassing.
He used to say, Soiya!
Who said, Soiya?
Let's do it again.
Don't take it off.
Can I ask you one thing?
What do you like about Hamada-kun?
That was...
It's not funny.
The video is playing.
What do you like about him?
Let's ask him.
Sure.
What do you like about him?
Everything.
Everything?
Well, when I'm in the second place.