I asked 100 people around the world.
What do you think?
Today, I'd like to use this opportunity to ask you a lot of questions.
I see, I see.
How many people are there?
100 people.
How many men are there?
If you are a man, please press the button.
26 people?
26 people have men?
27?
What is it?
Get out of here.
I'm just looking at you.
Everyone is laughing, but it's true.
This program is brought to you by Lions.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Let's ask the young women.
If the maximum amount of money you've ever received from a man is more than 50,000 yen, please press the button.
Why are you giving me little by little?
I want to press it.
Are you underestimating me?
You should be honest.
You should apply to the government.
Why?
Who are you talking to?
This is a conscious survey.
It's still increasing.
This is a conscious survey of young people.
Young people?
Are you an entertainer?
This is a conscious survey of young people.
I'll do my best.
But I think this machine is different.
Why don't you change the question?
I'll change the question, but you have to press the button.
What is this?
Are you a twin?
I don't think so.
It's not a machine that can be used properly.
It's probably a bird's nest.
I'm watching you.
Even if you use it like this, you can see it with your naked eyes.
It's a long distance, so you have to look at it with your hands.
It's a bird's nest.
If you are picked up by a celebrity you admire in the street, how far are you okay?
If you give me your phone number, I'll tell you.
There are a lot of people.
It's okay.
It's okay as far as you can go.
Don't stop.
It's about half.
Let's ask who it is.
For example, who is it?
Hideki.
If it's Hideki, I'll do it.
If it's okay, I'll do it.
Switch on.
It's Hideki.
Hideki, welcome.
Taishu Kase.
Zero.
I want you to do it.
Wait a minute.
There are 30 people, but there is no man.
What should I do with this man?
It's okay to be picked up.
Men are okay, so it's okay to be picked up by Kase.
Switch on.
It's not as much as I thought.
Let's go with only men.
Kase will pick you up.
Leave it to Kase.
I'll leave it to Kase.
It's your lead.
Switch on.
It's not as much as I thought.
There is a chance that Hamada will win against Taishu Kase.
What?
Hamada.
Let's do it with me.
Switch on.
You?
There is a chance that Hamada will win against me.
Is it okay, sir?
Wait a minute.
Are you sure?
Me and you.
There is a chance that Hamada will win against me.
Switch on.
We will do a good job.
What do you think?
I see.
That's good.
I'm thinking of continuing this program.
It's good that I won against Taishu Kase.
Let's listen to the last part.
With Masumoto.
Switch on.
It doesn't matter anymore.
It's almost half and half.
What?
I don't know if it's a man.
Who do you think I am?
Me.
There are more people who think I'm a homo than those who want to do it with me.
I haven't been told the truth.
I haven't been told the truth recently.
I've been told not to say it on TV.
I'm watching TV.
It's a man.
I knew it.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
I didn't have to make you wait.
I'm here to change your clothes.
That's why I asked you to come today.
Three or four weeks in advance.
Really?
How many people are there?
Two?
Two.
There are only two.
How many people are you looking for?
28.
28?
Hey.
It's one difference from us.
Is that so?
It's crazy.
You look like a peanut.
It's a difficult story.
It's not difficult.
I saw a photo of Kanako Higuchi.
Yes.
It's amazing.
She's bald.
I want to share it with her.
It was amazing.
Really?
That's you.
Look.
I'm not looking.
You should look.
There's one more person.
What?
How old are you?
I'm 23.
You don't have to worry about it.
It's crazy.
What's with the strong bangs?
This is...
There are many people like this.
But it's a little forced.
My hair is like this, but I'm like this.
It's like a Matsuyama Chiharu.
23 years old.
You're young.
You should do your best.
I remember it's crazy.
I was about 20 years old.
It's early.
I'm okay.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Please watch theactions from now on.
Please watch it.
There's a story about putting this kind of stuff out there.
It's like putting a nude photo of me on the governor.
It's a penalty.
The governor of staola
That part hasn't disappeared yet.
That part even.
If you lose again?
Yes.
Semi-nude
I've made a lot of mistakes, but there are still a lot of mysterious parts of you that are still hidden.
I didn't make that many mistakes on purpose, so if you like it, you can do it in the world of SM.
I don't do it because I like it.
You like to show it to people, don't you?
There's a little bit of exposure.
There is, isn't there?
I light up the radio studio and light up the cigarette and light up the rubber.
What should I say?
You have a pretty strong body.
Where is it?
Don't tell me.
I'm pretty busy.
Where is it?
It's like this here.
Well, that's fine, but it's been a while since I've been in February.
For example, what happened in February?
What?
What happened?
First of all...
What do you mean, what happened?
What happened? I'm asking you at this distance.
What happened? Well, for example, today...
What?
Today, I dropped my wallet.
Your wallet?
When you came from Osaka?
Yes.
In the Shinkansen?
I dropped it in the license plate.
I've picked up the money, but the amount I dropped was about 1 million yen.
And it was taken from the dressing room.
It was taken from the dressing room.
There's someone who takes it from the dressing room.
It was stolen about 200,000 yen.
Really, really.
From the bank.
I don't care about the dressing room.
Well, I'm on stage now, so it's okay.
Hey!
You're not as cheap as you look now.
I was so angry on the Shinkansen today.
Oh, really?
I was so angry.
And I always sit at the window seat.
I don't know that.
I only sit at the window seat.
Yes, yes, yes.
When I got on the seat, there was a man who looked like an elite with white hair.
He was sitting there with a newspaper or a foreign book.
He looked like a gentleman.
So I said, excuse me.
He said, excuse me?
I'm not sitting on my seat.
Yes, yes, yes.
He suddenly changed.
What's wrong with him?
I sat down and looked at my bag.
I realized I didn't have a wallet.
I had some time before I left.
I thought I might have forgotten it at the store.
I was running around.
It wouldn't be funny if I came back and went to the Shinkansen.
I went to the store with my bag.
But I didn't have it.
I had no choice but to take the Shinkansen.
When I came back, he was still sitting there with me.
I was angry.
I'm not angry.
And he said something.
I looked at him and said,
Aren't you going to sit down?
What is it? What is it?
While I was saying that, my teeth started to hurt.
It was terrible.
It was the last time I saw a strange man and my teeth started to hurt.
That's not all, you idiot.
I was so angry that I couldn't say anything else.
I went to the plantain store in Osaka.
I went to the plantain store with my business card.
I'm not angry.
An ugly woman is choosing her underwear.
That's because I'm wearing white underwear.
You're an idiot.
You're an ugly woman.
There's a part of him that he shows off to someone.
If you go out with a friend like that, you'll be satisfied, right?
You can't show your underwear to a man.
It's like that to some extent.
It's like choosing silk.
There's no way I can show you that.
It's a secret.
You're the most beautiful woman in the world.
You don't look at him.
I'm surprised.
You're like a camera.
You're amazing.
You're an ugly woman who's bet on Tessio.
Who's bet on Tessio?
Who raised you?
He's already chosen.
He's already chosen the last two types.
I'm a little flustered.
I wanted to see that.
What?
You're not a pig, but you're ugly.
I'm not a pig?
Pigs lose weight.
You can't help it if you're ugly.
If you say that...
Why do you say that?
You're dirty.
You're a coward.
You have the same opinion as me.
But you're a high school student on TV.
You don't have an idol idea.
You're like Mayuzuki Hikaru.
Who's that?
Who's Mayuzuki Hikaru?
You look like him.
How many years ago was that?
I haven't had a girlfriend recently.
I haven't had a girlfriend for five years.
You said you haven't had a girlfriend.
I'm...
I'm not a bad guy like Kato.
I haven't forgotten.
When I was in elementary school...
Don't say that!
You haven't forgotten.
When I was in fifth grade...
I haven't forgotten.
That was terrible.
I had a toothache from the morning.
I didn't go to school.
No one was home.
I was the only one.
I had a toothache at home.
I didn't want to do anything.
I didn't want to eat anything.
I just stayed at home.
Then the lady next to me said...
Mr. Matsuo!
Your dog is running away!
Ouch!
She came out and chased me.
She thought I was playing with her, so she ran away.
She was happy to see me.
She was like this.
My teeth hurt, but she ran away.
My dog is big.
It's big, isn't it?
I couldn't catch her while I was doing a head lock.
She was like this all the time.
She didn't smell at all.
She ran away.
When I looked at her, the chain was cut off.
I took her to the front yard.
I could hear a ringing sound.
I thought about it.
I had an important phone call.
I thought it was a phone call.
The door was locked.
Yes, because it was the front yard.
I thought I had to get closer.
My teeth hurt, but I ran away.
I was like this.
I came back to the front yard.
The chain was cut off.
I was like this.
It's a complicated story, isn't it?
It's because you didn't go to buy ramen.
Hitoshi, bring the ramen here.
I don't know where to go.
Hello.
I just remembered the dance.
Are you coming with your friends today?
No, I'm not.
What are you doing?
You can't dance at all.
Let me introduce her.
She's from Chiba Prefecture.
Do you go to college?
No, I don't go to college.
What are you doing now?
I'm a freelance part-timer.
You're a pig?
Yes, that's right.
You're a part-timer, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
What do you do?
I run a water business.
Is that so?
You're so good at talking.
Do you go to a club?
Yes, I do.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
Don't apologize to me.
Did you get any expensive gifts for your customers?
No, I didn't.
You didn't.
I'm sorry.
Is that so?
What is this?
What a strange girl.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Please go home.
Wait a minute.
What is this?
Can I leave this here?
Yes, you can.
Why did you turn your back on me when I was leaving?
What is this?
I don't understand.
Let me introduce this person.
Her pen name is Teruko Haruko.
Her pen name is Parman 1 and Parman 3.
Parman 2 is missing.
I'm going to pick him up.
Parman 4 is the manager of Nozanago.
Please take good care of him.
I'm taking care of him now.
Yes, you are.
I heard that Parman 2 is walking on the street recently.
He looks tired.
He looks like a middle school student.
If you see Parman 2 in the street, please talk to him.
We promise you.
If you see him, please talk to him.
If you don't talk to him, please contact us.
This program is for the audience.
We have to do this.
We apologize to you.
Yes, we do.
This is the first time to bring a child here.
There are four people in the family.
I'm a little in the way.
Hello.
Good evening.
I have something to tell you.
As we promised on the program...
Stop it!
As we promised,
if you see Parman 2,
please tell him that you see Parman 2.
He will say in a loud voice,
I don't care who you bring.
If you see Parman 2, please tell him that you see Parman 2.
If you don't tell him, we will contact you.
We are waiting for you.
What should we do?
I don't know.
Let's think of a punishment.
I don't think of a punishment.
This is a punishment only for Parman 2.
We will punish him so that he won't lose to the punishment game.
If we play the punishment game, Parman 2 will be in a good mood.
We will play the punishment game, but we won't play the punishment game.
This is the most effective punishment.
Really.
We are looking for an assistant.
Please send us a letter with the same address as Parman 2.
Please send us a letter.
Please.
This program is brought to you by LION and the following sponsors.