Please, please, Gaki no Tsukai Ara Hende!
Good evening.
It's Gaki no Tsukai Ara Hende.
Hey, today, from the waiting room of this soap...
That's not it!
Today is amazing!
Is that so?
The title is long, long!
Long?
Yes!
Three and a half years of history.
Oh!
Souketsu-san's Perfect Preservation! Gaki no Tsukai's Battle and Punishment Game! Soushiu's Golden Spirits!
Up until now, we've played the battle and punishment games.
In Gaki no Tsukai.
Yes.
Today, we'd like you to see all of that.
Oh.
That's what we'll do.
Oh, my turn is slow.
That's not it.
Hey, but Kohaku was amazing.
Yeah.
I can't believe it. Which one did you win?
Eh?
People who watch TV know.
Shall we bet?
Eh?
What?
Which one did you win?
Let me go first.
Red wins.
I'll go with white.
If I lose,
I'll do this behind the camera on Zoom-in Morning.
I'll dress up like this.
I don't think that's right.
You do that.
It's a different song.
I'll do a garala nyorororo.
I'll do a garala nyorororo on Zoom-in Morning.
It's a refreshing morning.
Good morning.
It's Wednesday, January 17th.
First of all, let's go to Shizuoka and Zoom-in.
We started at 5 o'clock in the morning.
There are 146 people.
And 154 people were injured.
It's like a strange person is coming from the morning.
My son wants to become a creative person.
Maybe I'll do that after I go home.
I'm going to make a cafeteria with industrial food.
It's so large that the wall doesn't have
What is the correct answer?
I can answer anything with su.
Sweet.
Usu.
Suika.
Karasu.
Sushi.
Shiwasu.
You said it.
I said shiwasu the day before yesterday.
You can't do that.
You lose.
The end.
You can't do that.
Wait a minute.
Don't do that.
It hurts.
It's noisy.
You'll get a cramp in your hand.
That's good.
This is cool.
I'll do the promotion.
Thank you very much.
Let's go this way.
Let's watch it at 1.40 a.m. in the downtown.
Let's watch it at 1.40 a.m.
in the downtown.
Let's watch it at 1.40 a.m. in the downtown.
The current speed is 3,500 km per hour.
Welcome.