I've been waiting for this day for a long time.
I change my hair every day.
Please show me.
If you look down, you can see my hair.
This is not something to play with.
I'll do it.
First of all, kiss on the cheek.
It's light.
This is 5 points.
Don't you hit the cheek?
It's a kiss.
If you shake hands.
Is that okay?
1 point.
Thank you.
If you say hello, 10,000 points.
Thank you very much.
That's too much.
30 points for putting your nose in.
50 points.
There's something like this.
This is his weapon.
This is about 50,000 points.
If you put this here.
50,000 points.
If you grab it, 50 points.
I see.
If you do this.
It hurts.
Who benefits from that?
100 points.
What happens if you take a picture?
Let's take a picture of that, too.
How many points do you get?
If you take a picture of that, you win.
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
I'm tired.
I'll dance.
Let's go.
That's it.
I set it up like this.
That's nice.
This time, alcohol, man, and life as a writer.
I see.
Let's call him right away.
Yes.
Mr. Kiyuki Nosaka.
Nice to meet you.
It hurts.
Which one is Matsumoto?
I'm Matsumoto.
It may be bad to say it roughly, but it's really interesting.
Is that so?
It's already in, isn't it?
It's in.
What is the best thing in the progress of science?
I think it's a birth controller.
What's that?
In other words, you don't have to give birth to children, do you?
Yes.
You don't have to give birth to children.
In other words, when you say something, it's just a joke.
What are you talking about?
Please say it quickly.
When you say it roughly, it's a secret.
I really don't know what you're talking about.
What's wrong with you?
It's obvious that it hurts.
For example, if you want to get married at the age of 17, that's a great message.
Why are you twisting your hand?
I don't know how to put it in words.
Your hairstyle hasn't changed much.
It's been like this all the time.
You're barefoot.
That's true.
If you loosen this, can you take it off?
I can take it off.
In general, this is the upper class of Japan.
I don't know what you're talking about.
How much did it cost?
It was 180,000 yen.
No way.
180,000 yen?
It doesn't matter.
I don't know how to put it in words.
You don't know how to put it in words.
In the old days, this hairstyle was all bald.
Is that true?
I don't know if I have a bald head.
Everyone has a bald head.
I always want to rub my father's hair.
What about you?
I have a bald head.
Have you ever played with a man when you were young?
I've never done that.
I'm an old man.
That's funny.
Do you still have a woman in your 60s?
It's crazy.
Are you crazy?
Yes.
Do you still have a woman in your 60s?
I have a woman once every three days.
Once every three days?
I can masturbate.
Do you still have a woman in your 60s?
I used to masturbate a lot when I was a primary school student.
Did you just fart?
You did your best today.
I did my best today.
I have a strange figure.
It hurts.
You were strong.
If it was a crab, it would have been removed.
Let's see my score.
My score is...
1,088 out of 60,000.
Let's see your score.
Thank you very much.
1,759 out of 60,000.
Why?
You did your best.
I scored 50,000 points with a microphone.
I see.
Did you dig your shoes?
I did.
I scored 10,000 points.
I have 60,000 points now.
What did I do?
You have a lot of points.
You have only one point.
Don't you have a record?
Let's record this next time.
I may never do it again.
You're still fresh.
This is for summer.
That's good.
Let's make it short.
It would be good if it was popular again.
You did it again.
It won't be popular anymore.
It won't be popular after three years.
I'm sorry to say this to you.
What?
I think you're very depressed.
What about me?
What?
You may die.
I'm sorry.
I want to throw up.
What do you mean?
You have a hole in your stomach, right?
What?
You want to throw up?
I want to throw up.
Don't do that.
I want to throw up because I smoked too much two or three days ago.
I know the cause.
You should quit smoking.
Did I smoke too much?
I don't know how many times I've been told.
What are you doing?
It happens sometimes.
I don't want to live a long life.
How long do you want to live?
That's not true.
People think I'm crazy.
I did everything I wanted to do.
I ate a lot of caviar.
If you eat a lot of caviar, you can't do it.
I ate a lot of foie gras.
I don't care when I die.
I don't want to die in pain or fear.
If I die in fear, I won't live until tomorrow at 2 o'clock.
Why are you cutting off time?
It's okay.
That's good.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
My lungs hurt.
Do you go out with people?
What are you talking about?
Have you ever been there?
No.
I'm not loved by anyone.
You can't say that.
I'm a loner.
It's okay.
I'm scared.
I used to be called a loner.
I was called a loner.
I have a scar here.
If I say I'm a loner, people will think I'm a loner.
People think I'm a loner.
I have a scar here.
It's a cancer.
It's clearly a cancer.
That's not true.
It's okay.
This doctor is not funny.
I'm scared.
Have you ever been to the hospital?
I've never been to the hospital.
I've never had a bone.
I've never had a surgery.
I had a surgery in Osaka.
I have a scar in my throat.
I had a surgery.
It's not here.
It's here, isn't it?
You've been doing this for a long time.
It's clearly here.
I had a scar.
Did you go to the hospital?
I went to the hospital for a week.
I want to go to the hospital for a week.
Really?
Do you know what a nurse is?
I know.
Don't say that.
You're an old man.
Did I say that?
It's not popular in the world.
A nurse is strict.
You noticed it.
I thought I was being strict.
I thought it was okay.
You followed me well.
This is a fact.
A nurse is...
It's written in the textbook.
If there is a patient who is in a state where both hands are broken and cannot be used,
you have to do it by hand.
How did you know that?
I've been aiming for it for a while.
You can't be a nurse.
That's impossible.
You can't do that.
That's not it.
That's the feeling of a personal nurse.
No.
I don't like it.
Why are you so desperate?
If you say you don't like it, it's no good.
That may be true.
There aren't many people who say that.
But if you can't use both hands, there are times when you get sick.
On the contrary, it may cause other diseases.
It may cause a disease.
Only people who can't use both hands can do that.
That's right.
There aren't many people who can do that.
There aren't.
The way to do it is to do it by hand.
You can use it anywhere.
I see.
But it's by hand.
What are you doing?
There are many ways to do it.
What?
You can do it with your hair.
In a commercial?
Yes.
In a girl group?
What was it?
It's called something monkeys.
Yes, yes, yes.
Why are you singing?
You have a bad mood.
I know.
What is it?
Super monkeys.
Yes, I know.
There is a guy who looks like a leader.
It's exactly a monkey.
Do you want to sell that girl?
This is a question.
Look at the commercial.
He's the only one on the screen.
The other members are dancing with him.
But he's the only one on the screen.
You can't see the other members.
Yes.
Do you know that?
The other members don't have families.
Really?
You're not on the screen at all.
I'm not on the screen.
I think your mother is cuter than that guy.
This girl's mother says that.
Yes, she says that.
But the screen is full of guys.
Yes.
What does that mean?
But that's what a group is.
You just want to sell that girl, right?
That's not true.
Hibagon will be on TV.
Can you sell that Hibagon?
Really.
I saw the magazine the other day.
Hibagon was laughing.
That's impossible.
But Hibagon is working hard.
There are no fans of Hibagon.
Yes, there are.
There are.
Are there fans of Hibagon?
Yes, there are.
Hibagon is here.
You're a fan of Ei-chan, right?
Did you watch Ei-chan's drama?
Yes, I did.
How was it as a fan of Ei-chan?
You're quite silent.
That's terrible.
Are you just waiting for other people's opinions?
Are you just waiting?
You were really Ei-chan.
You can't say, Yada-san, please do it again.
Why is that?
You've been here a lot.
That's because Yada-san is a big fan.
Yada-san, you can't say that now.
That's true.
You can't do it.
Please do it again.
Why is that?
Yada-san, you were silent just now.
You can't say, Yada-san, please do it again.
Can I be silent?
You're silent.
Ei-chan, you can be silent.
You've been in L.A. for a long time.
No, no, no, no.
That's because it's in English.
That's because it's in English?
I see.
Let's watch her.
What?
It must be hard.
Open your eyes.
I don't know.
I don't know if she's changed at all since episode 2.
I heard that Ei-chan is a different person.
Really?
She's told to put a refrigerator in the dressing room.
She's told to put mineral water and Ghana chocolate in there.
That's what she's told to do?
She's told to put that in there.
If that's all she's told to do, she'll be able to work.
But the dressing room isn't Yaza's.
It's open for about three days.
On the day when it's open for three days from tomorrow,
she brings a bag from home and packs it up and goes home.
Yaza does it herself?
Yes, she does it herself.
She's so cool.
Why do you have two holes in your nose?
I don't think one of them is wrong.
Please tell me why you have two holes in your nose.
If you have one hole in your nose, it's hard to breathe.
If you cut all of your nose hair,
you won't be able to breathe.
But if you do that, it'll be embarrassing.
If everyone does that, you won't be able to breathe.
If everyone does that.
But if you have one hole in your nose,
if it gets clogged, it'll be embarrassing.
Right?
It'll be over, right?
I'm wearing it as a sub.
But if you cut this part, it's big.
It's big.
Does it ever get clogged?
It's big, but it makes my nose runny.
That's true.
It'll make your nose runny.
But it's big enough.
I can take as much as I want.
That's your fault.
When you commit suicide,
you often put your shoes next to your clothes.
Why do you take off your shoes when you commit suicide?
Is it bad manners to commit suicide with your shoes on?
But that's true.
When you die,
you want to die, but you want them to find you soon after you die.
So you want them to find you soon,
so you put a message saying,
I'm dead.
You don't know anything even if you put your arms around your body.
It's like an old man taking you home.
Idiot.
Are you stupid?
It doesn't matter if you're cheating on me.
Do you think someone jumped off the bed when you were cheating on me?
I think so.
I wonder if you're playing catch ball somewhere.
Who plays catch ball on a rock?
If you're cheating on me,
if you look down, it's like a shark.
It's perfect.
But your shoes are the easiest to take off.
That's true.
I don't have a bra.
You're trying to take off your bra before you die.
I'm not the one who's going to fall.
Hamada-san seems to be friends with Miho Nakayama.
Do you know what Miho Nakayama's poop is?
You know what?
I don't know.
No, no, no.
You know what?
Hamada-chan!
Why do you want me to see that?
Maybe you have something to say.
No, I don't.
I saw your poop when I was in middle school.
You pooped in Sakanishi's house.
When I pooped and went home with Naga-san.
That's right.
You should have done that before you went home.
You were still there.
You might have wanted to go home with Naga-san,
but you were still there for about an hour.
That's why I pooped in front of you.
My pee is...
It's so soft.
It's the softest poop in the world.
I wonder what it is.
I think it was made by Okamoto Taro.
I think Sakanishi had a hard time after that.
He had three family members.
This program was provided by the following sponsors.