...
Hello!
You haven't done any talk shows for a while, right?
That's right!
You've done a box game too.
The audience was wondering if you were going to do more talk shows.
They were wondering if you were going to do more talk shows.
You didn't have any reaction when you came out.
I'm counting on you.
I'm not in the mood at all.
You're not in the mood at all.
What's going on?
I'm not in the mood at all.
Did you go home?
I think so.
But we're getting paid.
That's not the problem.
Let's work hard in the back of our minds.
This program is brought to you by the sponsor you see.
It's been a while.
You've been abroad, haven't you?
You have a lot of money.
It's nice, isn't it?
No, I went to Okinawa.
I went to Okinawa.
Is that so?
That's right.
There was nothing around me.
So I stopped thinking about it.
But it was a great success.
The typhoon came.
The typhoon came directly.
That's right.
So I went to Okinawa to borrow a video.
I said, I'm not from the main island of Okinawa, so I can't lend it to you.
What are you talking about?
I know your face.
I can't lend it to you.
The manager isn't here, so I can't lend it to you.
So I borrowed four videos from the girl I was looking for.
That's right.
Did she lend it to you?
Yes, she did.
I went to Okinawa to borrow a video.
It was my first day in Okinawa.
I thought it was fun.
My phone rang.
What are you talking about?
I don't like it at that time.
I know.
I don't like it when my manager calls me.
That girl was playing with me.
She was playing with my feelings on purpose.
Her tone was low.
I said, hello.
She called me.
Hello.
I know.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Yes.
Friday is...
What?
What is it?
Nothing.
I asked her.
What is it?
When I got the call, she said it didn't matter.
You should have told me earlier.
You should have called me.
It didn't matter.
It was the same for me.
I was excited.
You didn't call me when you were off.
I didn't.
You didn't call me.
When I was off, I got a call from my coordinator.
That's mean.
She was looking at me.
Yes.
What is it?
I really want you to stop.
Right?
There are times when I'm on a public show.
I'm having fun talking, but the manager is like...
What is it?
I want to hear it quickly.
I want to hear it.
There must be something.
There is.
I know.
I totally get it.
I'm getting goosebumps.
That's my fault.
I'm sure it was on purpose.
That's right.
When did you come back?
Where did you stay?
That's what I asked her.
I asked the coordinator.
I brought her here.
That's right.
I asked you to keep this a secret.
What is it?
Let's just keep it open.
I don't know who you're dating.
It has nothing to do with me.
I can't get married.
That's how it is.
It has nothing to do with me.
That's what I did.
Don't say things like that when you're on vacation.
I really hate talking to you on the phone.
That's not good.
It was on purpose.
Where did you go?
I went to Gamue.
I went to Okinawa and Gamue.
Did you have fun?
No, because I was on vacation.
It was terrible.
The hotel was out of power.
The weather was terrible.
You couldn't go outside.
I couldn't.
I asked if I wanted to go to a movie theater.
I didn't go to a movie theater.
There was no subway.
When the typhoon came, the traffic would stop.
I couldn't move.
It was terrible.
That's why you're on vacation.
There's nothing to do on vacation.
I see.
There's really nothing to do.
There's nothing to do.
Hamada...
Hamada is...
He has a occupational disease.
What are you talking about?
Tell me clearly.
I'll tell you.
He has a occupational disease.
He was peeing.
An old man came to him.
He said,
Hey!
In the bathroom at the station.
Yes.
He kept saying,
Hey!
But I know that.
I really know that.
The other day,
I went to a ramen shop.
It was a fast-moving ramen shop.
There was no alcohol.
There was no smoking.
I ate and went out.
It was a fast-moving ramen shop.
I was eating ramen there.
There were four old men.
Four old men came.
Excuse me.
There were four old men.
They came.
Then the clerk said,
If there are four old men,
It's impossible to eat at the same time.
I'd like you to sit away from me.
He said,
Hmm.
I see.
I'll sit away from you.
I'll wait for you.
What?
Did the four old men line up?
If you can't eat, just go to sleep.
It's been 22 years.
What?
What is that?
It's a good name.
Then I'll wait for you.
What?
I'm really surprised.
You're all stupid.
You have a bad feeling.
If you don't talk,
Don't go to a ramen shop.
That's right.
Then I'll wait for you.
You have a bad feeling.
That's a great word.
It's a counter.
When I was a kid,
I was hiding from my parents.
I bought Shishimai.
I asked Mr. Matsumoto.
Please tell me about your touching encounter with Shishimai.
And sad parting story.
It was when I was in the third grade of elementary school.
When I was in the third grade of elementary school,
I was playing catch ball.
In the park.
Yes, yes, yes.
My opponent was a weak guy.
There was a stick flying.
I said,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I went to get it.
I found the ball in a place like Kusamura.
I thought,
I found it, I found it.
Katakatakata.
In a cardboard.
About this much.
Katakatakata.
It was thrown away.
There were four of them.
But the others didn't say Katakatakata.
It was like half-open.
Only one was Katakatakata.
Katakatakata.
That was the encounter.
I took one of them home.
You took one home.
What happened to the other three?
What?
The other three were dead.
Really?
There was only one left.
When I held him in my arms,
he didn't say Katakatakata.
I wondered why.
The two little men were like this.
Oh, that's what it was.
And the old man was with them.
Snacks are always...
I have a question for Mr. Matsumoto from Disco.
Yes?
What happens if a child doesn't get a snack even once?
This is...
That's right.
Usually, you give them snacks, right?
Yes.
When they're little.
We were chosen.
What was chosen?
Whether to give them snacks,
or whether to give them allowance.
I was asked by my mother once.
I see.
I said, it doesn't matter.
Now that I think about it...
But if you give them to a child,
they're going to be chosen soon.
That's right.
Whether to give them allowance,
or whether to give them allowance.
That's about it.
I gave them allowance.
Is that so?
Yes.
Is it okay to talk about the four sisters?
If there's another chance.
We were talking about snacks.
I'm saying this because I couldn't give them snacks.
Their life won't change that much.
That's okay.
I see.
That's okay, but...
They'll definitely...
They'll probably walk with a cold on their shoulders.
Does that mean they'll slip?
No, they won't slip.
Will their attitude change?
It's not that they'll change.
For example, if they're a salesman,
and the child grows up to be a salesman,
they'll still do the massage properly.
It's a service business.
I see.
Is that okay?
Yes.
Thank you.
I'll do it again.
When I said that,
just a little...
Just a little bit.
That's enough.
It's okay.
It's okay, but...
You don't have to worry about it.
That's right.
Also,
if I had to choose,
I'd be in front of a confectionery shop
and do a Poiste.
I'd definitely have a sense of presence.
Well, I feel like I understand.
Well, isn't that okay?
That's about it.
Yes.
This is a question for Onmyoji Matsumoto-san,
the comedian of the comedy world.
Please tell us the easiest way
to chase a fox when it's tired.
Ah.
Do you know that?
What?
Do you know the story of a mosquito?
A mosquito?
It's a mosquito.
A mosquito.
Do you know the story of a mosquito?
I don't know.
Do you know it?
No, I don't know it.
There's a thing called a bee.
Oh, I see.
It's something like this.
I see.
It's a machine.
You put a battery in it.
When you listen to it,
it makes a sound.
It makes a sound.
When it makes this sound,
the skin doesn't come close.
I see.
What is this sound called?
This is the sound of a male's skin.
I see.
And it sucks the blood of a female's skin.
At that time,
the female's skin wants to reject the male's skin.
It's the season.
So,
you're convinced.
Do you know it?
Is that a male's skin?
That's right.
When it makes a sound,
you think there's a male's skin,
but the female's skin doesn't come close.
I see.
People don't suck the male's skin.
That's right.
They're all females.
I see.
If you think about it,
the male's skin is killed because of the female's skin.
It's just...
It's just flying.
The skin is open.
Bang!
It's being killed.
I'm not a male!
I see.
It's the worst.
If it's the female.
It's said in the human world.
That a man gets hurt because of a woman.
I see.
That's it.
When a fox catches it.
It's simple, isn't it?
Yes.
We're going to get into the main subject.
That's right.
After all,
when a fox catches it,
Because it's not a fox, it takes over, right?
The fox thinks it's a human being, so it takes over.
Right?
The fox doesn't take over the fox.
Ah, I see.
That means,
It's better to say,
Then, I understand how to not take over.
But, I want you to teach me how to chase after a fox when it gets tired.
Ah, I see.
And the easiest way.
You're saying that it's better to say,
It's better to say,
I'll take you home.
I'll do it every 20 minutes.
But, if you don't do it,
If you don't do it,
I'll get in trouble.
But, if you don't do it,
I want you to teach me how to chase after a fox when it gets tired.
Ah, I see.
You're not saying it.
I want you to teach me how to chase after a fox when it gets tired.
Ah, I see.
It's easy, isn't it?
If you do that, I'll get out of here right away.
The best thing is,
Ah, I want you to teach me how to chase after a fox when it gets tired.
That's how you get caught by a white snake quickly.
That's how you get caught by a white snake.
If you get caught by a white snake,
I think that foxes are dangerous.
Ah, I understand.
So, how do you get caught by a white snake?
After all, it's better to make a gap.
A gap?
Put on pants as wide as you can.
Like Manbo pants.
If you're wearing slim pants,
It's hard to get in.
So,
Please make it short with wide pants.
If you do that,
I think you'll be able to get in.
Like this.
Pen name Bichibichisan.
What makes Dracula so scared of the cross?
I can't read it.
Dracula is a fool.
He's like a wife.
He's like Bichibichisan.
He's not that scary.
He's really scary.
Dracula.
Dracula's wife is really strong.
I see.
She turns the table upside down.
If you turn it upside down,
No matter how many times you make rice,
She'll knock it down.
Just now, you were making somen.
Come on! Stop it!
That's what she said.
She mistook it for a cross.
She said she mistook it.
She said,
Don't read it!
Yoshike!
It's not Yoshike.
Speak properly!
Yoshiko!
Do you know that?
She's laughing at something else.
That.
She's hiding it.
She's hiding it because she can't read it.
But you don't like garlic, do you?
I don't like garlic.
Then what is that?
Why don't you like garlic?
That's because it's easy to eat.
It's easy to eat.
I'm sorry.
I don't like the light.
It says,
Come home in the morning.
It's already morning!
You'll get scolded by your wife!
So it's Mitsuko?
It was Yoshiko.
I was shocked.
She said,
You!
I understand.
The light is coming home in the morning.
That's right.
Then what about garlic?
What do you mean by garlic?
You said it yourself.
Ah, garlic.
You don't like garlic?
No, it's like,
It's coming out.
Ah, I see.
I understand.
What is that?
That is,
I simply don't like it.
I'm a little bit bad at it.
Even if I put out garlic,
I'm not that scared.
What is that?
It's like,
I put out a huge amount of garlic.
But it'll take ten hours.
That'll take ten hours,
I think.
That's right.
In the morning,
you can take your wife's face in the morning.
Even if it's not Dracula,
I'm scared.
Then anyone will run from me.
Dracula is stupid.
It's true.
The wife's fangs are like this.
It's like a saber tiger.
What are you talking about?
You'll see your wife go crazy.
But nothing will happen.
No, it will.
If your wife goes crazy.
You'll die, right?
I won't die, but I'll be your wife.
I hope so.
No, but if you become the wife of Dracula,
Dracula will have to endure it.
That's what I'm most afraid of.
Pen name, Holiday-san.
Holiday?
If you die in the sea, is the question for Matsumoto-san.
Please tell us about the Marimo for a week.
How much do you know about Marimo?
It doesn't matter how much I know.
It's nothing. It's nothing.
You'll get a phone call.
Who's calling?
It's just a phone call.
Wow, that's a terrible way of saying it.
But I think Marimo is saying the same thing to you.
I don't know if it's true or not,
but it doesn't matter if you don't see it.
You'll definitely get a phone call.
I can't do anything right now.
No, no, no. You'll be busy for a week.
Busy?
Busy.
I'll just sleep.
But you haven't seen it for a week, right?
I haven't seen it for a week.
You'll definitely get a phone call.
I can't help it.
What are you busy with?
First of all, Monday.
Monday.
Yes.
I'm thinking about getting a call tomorrow.
I've been thinking about it all month.
That's the end of Monday.
I'll try to get a call tomorrow.
I'm thinking about getting a call tomorrow.
But I'm not sure if it'll be funny.
I've been thinking about it all Monday.
And on Tuesday,
I was wondering why I was so worried about getting a call.
I don't know.
That's the end of Tuesday.
And on Wednesday,
There's a way to get a call.
I've been thinking about it.
I'll definitely get a call tomorrow.
I'm surprised.
And on Thursday,
I'm thinking about getting a call.
I've been thinking about it all Thursday.
And on Friday,
I've been thinking about getting a call.
I've been thinking about it all.
And on Saturday,
I'm thinking about getting a call.
I've been thinking about getting a call.
And on Sunday,
I'll be quiet and close my eyes.
Call!