It all started from here.
The genius boy, Yamasaki's idea.
A match between Wasabi Sushi and Russian Roulette.
The person who eats the Wasabi Sushi out of the 100 sushi will be penalized.
The game will continue until one of the downtown people eats the Wasabi Sushi.
Until then, if Yamasaki Kokoriko doesn't eat the Wasabi Sushi, he'll be safe.
Safe!
And then, Yamasaki's 6th turn.
Come on.
Don't shoot in the middle.
What?
That's enough.
Tanaka, choose.
Safe?
Safe.
It's probably safe.
It's safe.
What are you doing?
Don't be stupid.
What?
It's safe!
First, Yamasaki, the inventor, is eliminated.
After that, the rules are changed.
The four of them will eat the sushi at the same time.
Ready, set, go.
Okay.
What?
Safe?
Safe.
It's safe.
What?
Tanaka?
Finally, Tanaka is eliminated.
Ready, set, go.
I don't know.
What?
I'm safe.
End safe?
Matsumoto is safe.
Wait.
It's safe.
It's safe!
Yes!
Now, Hamada, Yamasaki, and Tanaka
The punishment game for the three找 are decided.
What the contents are
Last time, the commercial home that they suffered
It's more difficult than the hot springs that Z prosperity
Is great.
It's a 5 minute car wash!
In the midst of a harsh situation where they can't laugh at all, the comedians are attacked.
If they laugh, a severe punishment will be executed.
I was really looking forward to it.
This hellish punishment game will be even more scale-up under the management of Matsumoto Produce.
A one-night, two-day trip to a hot spring that you should never laugh at, in Yugawara.
Tonight, we'll show you the highlights.
On the day of the punishment game, the three of them arrive at the hot spring town of Yugawara.
In this town, a harsh punishment game will be executed.
And soon, the first trial of the punishment game will begin.
Everyone in the town is welcoming us.
Look.
This is bad.
They're raising the town.
This is amazing.
What exactly did the three of them see?
What exactly did they see?
Furthermore, a mysterious wrestler appears as if to chase them.
What? We've arrived in Yugawara.
One, two, three.
Disqualified, disqualified, disqualified, disqualified, disqualified.
Disqualified, disqualified, disqualified.
This is amazing.
What exactly did the three mysterious wrestlers see?
As soon as they took a rest, the three of them got on a taxi and moved.
Of course, on the way...
Yamasaki.
This is bad.
Who's going to get on the taxi?
They'll laugh at this.
They'll definitely laugh at this.
On the way to the inn, the three of them visit a temple.
What exactly did the priest say?
Finally, the three of them arrive at the inn.
The three of them are attacked by other wrestlers.
Hamada, you're out.
Stop it. Stop it.
I can't do this. I'm a grown-up.
Hamada is addicted to comedy.
This time, a large number of guests appear as a role model for comedy.
That popular young duo.
What is it?
I'll do my best.
And that gravure queen.
Black glasses.
Actually, Hollywood stars are staying here today.
What?
They want to say hello to people like you, so I'll be surprised.
Here you are.
Is it a secret date until that big Hollywood star comes?
I'm getting goosebumps.
At the New York Times, which soothes the tiredness of the day, comedy traps attack.
What exactly happened to the three of them?
And this time, Matsumoto himself is the strongest candidate.
Hamada, Yamasaki, Tanaka, out.
What the hell are you doing?
Get out of here!
At the night show, which was held at midnight, comedy traps attack.
What are you doing?
The big star of the Showa era came to Yugawara.
In addition, the nostalgic brother Ryo is also enthusiastic.
The comedy traps attack one after another.
Can the three of them stand it?
At the bedside, which was finally about to fall asleep.
Hamada, Yamasaki, out.
What happened to Yamasaki, who was attacked by a cat?
Can the three of them successfully complete the punishment game?
What the hell are you doing?
This show will be on air for two hours from 9.30 pm on December 28th.
That's amazing.
It's been a long time since we talked.
I went to a place like a cherry blossom garden by myself.
By yourself?
Yes, I went there by myself.
What's the smell?
It's an elevator.
I'm aiming for the first floor.
That's right.
I'm alone from the 7th floor.
I went to the 6th floor.
A woman like the back of a child came.
A woman like the back of a child and a woman like the front of a child came.
I've never seen the back of a child.
I saw it when I was running.
A woman like the back of a child and a woman like the front of a child came.
Separately?
They're friends.
A woman like the back of a child and a woman like the front of a child came.
A woman like the back of a child...
I don't know which one.
A woman like the back of a child.
If I push the button.
A woman like the back of a child will say no.
I said it's the 4th floor.
A woman like the back of a child will say yes and so the button has already been pressed.
I can't help you, can't I?
It was too hard because I was feeling in a relationship with the back of a child.
in the 4th, 3rd, and 6th time
I don't care about that
Apologize!
Why do you apologize?
In the end, I'm always the idiot
Who's the idiot?
It's just a little thing
There are idiots
I don't care about that
I've been hearing that for a while
What kind of idiot?
Behind me
There were two girls and two boys
There were four of them
They were talking like a bunch of idiots
That's good
I thought they were idiots
But that was good
I'm so full!
You should say that
I can't bear it
I'm so full!
All four of them
But don't you want to eat ojiya?
I thought I wanted to eat ojiya
I want to eat it
Do you want to eat ojiya?
Let's eat it!
Excuse me
Can you prepare ojiya?
I can make ojiya
I can do it
How many people should we serve?
Let's see
Four people
That's impossible!
One person can only serve one person
What kind of world is ojiya?
It's not a family restaurant!
Shut up
I'm full!
Shut up!
I'm so full!
You should say that
But my ojiya and the ojiya at the restaurant are the same
I'm so full!
I'm going to start walking
What's that?
Come on
He is a man of the sea who was fishing for octopus and squid
The other day you met something unexpected while scuba diving in Okinawa
Tell me about that
You don't do scuba diving, do you?
I don't
When you do it you encounter many things
Really?
Yes
That's amazing
Why don't you do scuba diving?
Because my ears hurt
You're fast
You're quick
Really?
I don't understand unexpected things
You don't do scuba diving
I saw almost everything
What did you see?
Everything
Are you going to tell me everything?
For example
For example, a supermarket
What does it say?
Aisai-go
Aisai-go? A washing machine?
A washing machine
A washing machine is fine
What?
A washing machine
I knew that it was Aisai-go
I could say it was a washing machine
You should have told me
All of it
What I'm saying is
Don't put everything in the sea
I see
Where are you diving?
In Okinawa
I'm in Okinawa
Really?
What else did you see?
I'll tell you everything
You could have told me 3 or 4 things
A lid
A lid?
You're so annoying
You're so stupid
You have so many lids
I don't like going into the sea
What do you mean?
If a kid sees you, he'll be surprised
Really?
I like the tropical fish
There are so many tropical fish in Okinawa
What?
I'm walking on two legs
I'm walking like this
What is this?
I'm growing up
You're about the same age as me
Run away
Run away?
What are you doing?
There's more over there
There's a blue one over there
It's yellow
That's funny
It's amazing
It's yellow and it's growing
Tell me
There's a blue one over there
It's the same blue one as me
I heard that the human body has a part called the human body
What part of the human body is that?
Around here
From here to here
That's a lot of space
No, don't put it here
Put it here
Like this
Why is it like that?
If you say it like this
Like this
It's like this
Why is it called the human body?
Do I have to talk about that?
Of course
This is the first time everyone knows
This is called the human body
Don't say it like this
Like this
This is the human body
No, if you go that far it's called the human body
Even Wakisaka-san is included
This is the human body
If you say it like this it's Wakisaka-san
Just a little bit of Wakisaka-san
It's usually the human body
Why is it called the human body?
You think it has my name on it right?
Yes
That's strange
This is from the name of Matsumoto-san
You're wrong
Before I was born
The human body part was from the name
That's shallow
So my father
Told me to become like this
To become a child like this
That's why it's called the human body
You don't understand why it's called the human body
I don't understand that
I understand that
That's right
There are many theories
Don't say that
What about this one?
What do you call this one?
Does it have a name?
It's the face on the left
This is the only one
That's right
Didn't you say something about it?
What did I say?
This is a question for Matsumoto-san
Who lives in a mysterious world
Matsumoto-san, one morning
When you woke up, you were Matsumoto-san
What were you like before you became Matsumoto-san?
There are things like that
How old were you?
When I was 4
When I met you, I was already Matsumoto-san
That's right
What did you do before you were 4?
But when I talk about this
It takes a long time
What did you do before you were 4?
It's a simple question
It's not long
Before I was 4, I did this
After I say this, it's over
It's not a story that takes that long
That's right
Why are you talking like that?
It was that morning
That morning, I became Matsumoto-san
It wasn't until Wednesday
I became Matsumoto-san on Thursday
I see
It's not, it's Monday
Monday is fine
Wait a minute, was it Monday?
No, it's Thursday
Then it's Thursday
It's Thursday
Let's be surprised, it's completely different from Wednesday
That's right
Then it's Monday
Monday is fine
It's the next Monday after Thursday
It's fine, either way is fine
I don't know
Then it's Thursday
Then what did you do until Wednesday?
I became Western
Ah, it's not
It's Monday
It's Monday, what did you do?
What is Western?
I don't know, you said Western
Do you know laughing?
What do you mean?
If you say something that is too far away, it won't come right away
This is a good example of Western
I don't know
There is a sense of humor
Whether you can see it or not, it's just right
That's the best way to laugh
If it's too close, it will be blurry
It will be like that
If it's too far away, it will be like that
It's best to be in a position that you can see
It won't float
You can drink it if you want
The 3 people's punishment game will be released
The two-day trip to the onsen that you can't laugh at
This time it's amazing
Matsumoto stands in the way of the punishment
That's why I'm laughing
Please subscribe to the channel