Kishinako no Yureru
The love that sways and sways
Is a taxi driver
Arashiya
All right
Maku
Why are you looking at me like that?
It's strange
You don't really have to be surprised
Well
I don't have a boyfriend
How old are you?
I'm 5 years old and 8 years old
Have you been transferred to another school?
No, I haven't
We were together all the time
I was in the sixth grade at that time
Are you double as a elementary school student?
I'm in my 40s
But haven't you changed your body type?
Why?
It's about this year
My body type has changed
It has changed
How has it changed?
I used to be fatter
I've become slimmer
You said a great thing about yourself
I used to be really fat
My hands are smooth now
I used to be sticky
You can make a plastic model if you don't use glue
That's an exaggeration
But I've become slimmer
That's a good thing
He's better off that way
But when I get in the car, I smell like an old man
I don't know
What kind of smell is that?
It smells like I got in a taxi a few years ago
In the car?
In the car
When I get in the car, I feel sorry for the car
It's bitter
But it's okay
That's how it is
When I was in Heihei, you suddenly made me sing
Yes
I've been thinking about it since then
But I'm not good at singing
I don't think so
I don't think so at all
I think you're better than average
But is it different?
It was a little bad
The other day
You've gotten a little better
Compared to before
A little
Why is that?
Are you getting used to it?
Nakajime Miyuki
What?
I'll ask you as a representative
Who is it?
Nakajime Miyuki
It's Teisei
I don't know
You don't know Nakajime Miyuki
Don't laugh
I don't know
Listen to the last story
Nakajime Miyuki's sister
Nakajima Miyuki
Why is it a sister?
It's a different name
I know if it's a different name
Which one is Nakajima?
There is no Nakajima
There is a person called Nakajima Miyuki
What was that song?
There is a song called a man has a man
It was a drama
There was something
I can't sing that song
No matter how many times I sing
It ends right after I sing
There is a man has a man
There is a home
It ends
Is that wrong?
Is it wrong?
It's like it's wrong
I want to start more
Next time I have to go to a woman
I can't sing that
Why is that?
I don't know
I understand
There is a man has a man
It's strange
I can't continue
Please fix me
Please hit me
You have to hit me
I can't sing
I can't
There is a man has a man
U2
I don't know
You don't know U2?
I don't know if it's a foreign song
Arabesque
It's old
I think there are people who don't know Arabesque
You don't know?
Why don't you know?
You're not interested?
It's old
The picture is old
Is that so?
It's old
It's okay
The distance between the audience and me is getting bigger
If you know that, it's a good story
That's strange
Don't say that
Let's talk about the mangrove
That long story, Saiyuki
I read it in just 10 minutes
I heard that you can do a lot of things
Please show me some of them
I hate long stories
I can talk about everything
I always think that everything is fast
For example, look over there
Hamada, you're slow
Look over there
You're slow
Why?
You're not looking over there
I'm looking over there
Hamada
Tanaka
That's not Tanaka
Why are you looking at me?
That's not good
I'll call him
You'll call him?
It's fast
But before you call him, I want you to promise me something
Call me Matsumoto
You're dirty
Yamamoto
I want to see how fast it is
Why are you looking at me from the side?
Turn around
You're so kind
Is this okay?
Here I go
You're not saying anything
I'm fast
2 plus 5 is?
You're slow
I feel sorry for 7
3 plus 4 is?
I have a question for Matsumoto
Yes
Please tell me the source of money for your partner Hamada
What kind of person are you?
I'm working
I'm getting paid from Yoshimoto
That's right
Of course that's right
But this is my main job
And you have a lot of clothes
You're saying interesting things
It's not interesting
What did you say?
You don't show your bag
What?
You don't show what's in your bag
I don't show it
There's a lot of stuff in there
Don't say that
I can't talk
You're in a super car
I'm not in a super car
You're in a car like 007
If you press a button, it will start
What is this?
It's like cutting wood
You can't buy a car like that
How much is it?
It's nothing
Let me touch it
Why would you touch it?
It's like marble
It's not marble
But it's like marble
Why?
You're in a super car
I'm not in a super car
I have two cars
You have two cars?
Two cars?
Do you have two cars?
I don't have one
I'm barefoot
You're barefoot
My feet are hard
I run a lot
I have two cars
I have a high-speed car
I don't have one
If you're that fast, you should have a car
A high-speed guy told me
All the guys have this
The guy you passed by happened to have a car
Like this
If you make a mistake, it's fast
It's really fast
I got caught in an office once
I was called by the police
It's a camera
If you exceed the speed limit, it will flash
It flashed
I was called by the police
It was last summer
I said I didn't know
What kind of world has a high-speed car?
Why would it flash?
It flashed
I was surprised
The pendant was yellow
My chest was wide open
What are you wearing?
It's a bathrobe
You went to the bathroom
I had an accident
What kind of accident?
I was protected
You were in the shower
I was looking away
I didn't know the car was stopped
I was fine
From behind
I was drunk
You were drunk
You should have gone
I was in the car
Nothing happened over there?
It was dark
It was bad over there
From behind
They said sorry
I was like a junior high school student
A junior high school student flashed a high-speed car?
I didn't shine