Ladies and gentlemen.
Today we don't have an opening, right?
Really?
What do you want?
I want to show you something.
Today I'm here to show you Hamada-kun's documentary.
Bring the monitor.
Why are you so excited?
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
I came here to see you, Kin-chan.
Can I go home now?
You should have told me earlier.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Let's take a picture.
Hamada-chan.
Yes?
Can't you do it?
I can't.
I know what I want to do.
You look tired.
I don't want to do it.
No, no.
I just want to run.
I don't know how to do it.
Ouch!
Which one do you want?
I brought a lot of collections.
Here you are, Hamada-chan.
Here you are.
You look good.
You look cool.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
Yes.
I'll be right back.
Really?
Yes.
I'll be right back.
This one.
It looks cool.
Yes, it does.
Let's go.
You're here.
Good morning.
Are you wearing a mask?
You look funny.
Thank you.
I heard about you.
Really?
Shall we run?
Let's run.
Thank you.
You're funny.
Let's go.
Yes.
Thank you.
No, no.
You're welcome.
It's rare to see a man wearing a costume.
You're cool.
You're good.
You're really good.
Yes, I am.
Let's do our best.
Can you show us?
I'll do it.
Let's go.
One, two, three, four.
You're too much.
Thank you.
One more time.
What's wrong with you?
Wait a minute.
Yes.
You're moving too fast.
You go first.
Why are you wearing it so many times?
You're slow.
You're moving too fast, so I'll do it again.
Thank you.
I'm waiting for you.
That's good.
Go next week.
I'll wait for you next week.
Don't say that.
Well, that's it.
I'm done.
I'm waiting for you next week.
You're a talent, so I'm waiting for you next week.
Don't say that.
I'm a runner.
But I know you're watching today.
I'm not a runner.
I'm not trying to be nice, but I'm watching the monitor and I'm wondering if you're really a runner.
Really.
You're really good.
But I'm not a runner at all.
That's enough.
Well, that's it.
You're next week.
It's okay to do this once.
I won't do it twice.
You were shooting a short story when we met in my dream.
I thought it was over early.
This is my staff.
Let's go.
It was your dream.
Who is it?
You said it yourself.
You're a dream chaser.
Hama-chan.
Don't touch me.
The air I'm running in is going to air on Thursday next week.
Everyone, please watch it.
I'll lower the monitor.
Hey, you.
What?
You know what?
I'm going to do special training before Marukome.
No, no, no, no.
Marukome doesn't exist in this world.
It does.
That's not true.
The Marukome commercial is like a box with a kid in it.
You're going to do that, too.
Mom.
I won't throw it.
Hello, mom.
No one is laughing.
Mom.
It's okay.
No.
You're going to do special training.
I'm not going to do it.
I sent you my resume.
I'm going to do it tonight.
What are you looking at?
I'm going to do it.
No, no, no.
You look like an underworld beast.
I'm not going to do it.
You're going to do it.
I'm going to do it.
I'm going to pull it.
All the staff are going to do it.
I'm not going to pull it.
No, no, no.
I'm going to pull it lightly.
It's not plastic.
I think it's three or five people.
The old men in the audition are sitting there.
The kid is like this.
You're sitting in there, too.
There's a view next to the kid.
I'm going to do it like a mother.
Like a mother's child.
I'm going to do it.
And I'm a mother.
You're my mother.
I'm going to do it.
Let's do it before that.
Run properly.
I'm going to do it with energy.
I'm a kid.
I'm going to do it.
It looks like fun.
Understand?
The hand is like this.
You should do it.
I can't do it.
I can't.
I don't understand.
I can't do it.
I can't.
Why?
It's decided by the person.
You know how I feel.
I don't understand at all.
What?
For 10 years, the two of us have been doing it with our eyes closed.
Even when we're having a hard time, we're doing it together.
That's why.
I'm telling you.
What?
Think about when you're having a hard time and you can't eat.
What do you mean?
What?
I don't know.
I don't think I've had enough strength before.
It's okay.
What?
I was totally exhausted in Fukuoka yesterday.
It doesn't matter.
You know what?
I went to a regional office like Fukuoka.
I was so tired.
I went there.
Don't mess with me!
Then, yesterday's Nijinon Broadcast in Fukuoka...
I'm not going there!
Don't talk to me!
Our new idol singer don't.
You're so loud!
We'll shut up!
We were rehearsing when we got into the studio.
We were setting up.
The all-Kyushu comedy contest!
It stinks, doesn't it?
That's all right.
I was on this stage.
I was in rehearsal.
Then, the musician came out from here and explained to me.
Oh, I see.
This guy.
I was listening to his explanation.
Around here.
After a long time, I asked the audience.
What the hell are you doing?
I...
What?
I was doing something.
You're the one who has a bad attitude.
The set is...
It's a countryside, so the set is...
It smells like countryside.
It's a dirty set.
I looked at it and it was like this.
You're the one!
That's you too!
That's you!
I was listening to his explanation.
It's been broken for a long time, so it's strange.
What is it?
If you say it's a countryside, it's a dirty set.
You're the one who has a bad attitude.
It's you!
It's true that you have a bad attitude.
What do you mean?
Makeup is just putting on foundation.
Normally, you put on a lot of makeup.
But you can't do that.
You put on a lot of foundation.
Then, you put on a lot of foundation.
When I asked if you had a powder, you said,
Huh?
Is it powder?
I don't know.
It's powder. Don't you know?
What did you say? Is it a cod roe?
You're a bad actor.
Why?
Why do you have such a bad attitude?
What do you think?
What do you mean?
It's true.
I was on a plane.
I was so angry.
The man next to you...
The man next to me was sitting next to me.
It was a two-seater.
The man who was sitting next to me...
I was so angry.
It was amazing.
And I saw his nose was stuffed.
The nose was stuffed.
He was breathing heavily.
And...
When I got here...
What was that?
I fell down like I was dancing like a god.
My nose didn't come.
Hey, it stinks! Come here!
I did it 10 times, and in the 11th time I got wet with tears.
This really stinks!
I was a demon hunter, and I was told that I can grant 3 wishes.
First, I want money.
And the next, I want to get rid of all the stinky people in the world.
And the third, I want to get a new partner.
The second wish is to get rid of you.
Shut up!
It's so hot.
First, I want to bring a fan.
You scared me!
What's going on?
Thank you very much.
It's Moriko Watanabe.
Did you write this yourself?
Yes, I did.
What's wrong?
What?
Did you want to be on the show?
Yes, I did.
In this rotten show?
Yes.
It's the most memorable one.
The one when I broke a tree.
The one with the bad character?
Yes.
It was like an occult movie, wasn't it?
The ogre comes and wakes you up, right?
That's right.
He says, where were you yesterday?
And when he takes a picture of you, a bear comes out of your eyes and says,
I don't care where you are.
Thank you very much.
Can I avoid you?
What?
It's over.
Already?
Yes.
Can I take this?
No, no.
If you take this, it's over.
Aren't you going to read it?
I will read it.
What about me?
I don't need it.
I'm sorry.
I said I don't need it.
I've had a few entertainers come up to me.
But this is the first time I've seen you so nervous.
No matter what.
I'm sorry.
I understand.
See you next week.
Thank you very much.
She's funny.
She's a funny person.
I'm a big fan of Machan and Hama.
Please make me your teacher.
Why?
I've been doing this for 10 years.
I can't be his student.
What are you talking about?
It was funny.
When I first saw this, I thought it was a postcard.
At first, I didn't know what it was.
I looked at it and said,
Please make me your teacher.
What?
Don't lie to me.
Whose student are you now?
Now?
When I joined, I was asked if I was going to join the Shunryu or Hanshin Kyojin.
You were asked.
Now?
I'm here now.
You should be at the bottom.
Why?
I dare to.
Who is good?
There's a lot of things.
What are you talking about?
Who are you?
Don't stare at me.
What are you doing?
No, no, no.
That story hasn't disappeared.
It's over quietly.
What are you talking about?
It was funny.
I'm still the same.
Don't be afraid of what people say.
I don't think so.
What are you talking about?
Don't break the joke.
It's not a joke.
If it was a joke, I would have said it.
What?
That's enough.
What is this?
What you're doing is different.
That's enough.
Good evening.
I heard on the radio that you started to go to a car lesson.
What do you think about beating me?
I haven't gone yet.
But I want to go.
You already have a driver's license.
I got a driver's license.
You got a driver's license.
How many years have you been a drunk?
That's a long time.
No, no, no.
But that's about two years.
About two years?
If you haven't been on for two years, you should have.
Yes.
I haven't been on for two years.
Then try it.
What?
Try it.
You get in the car.
Yeah.
Open the door.
I should open the door.
You should open the door.
I'll open it.
Gacha!
Close the room!
You can't close it!
Good shot!
Close it first!
I've received a lot of projects to commemorate the 100th anniversary.
Ah, that's right, it's the 100th.
I've received about 10,000 of them.
I've received the letters from Numazu City in Shizuoka Prefecture.
Last time I was in Okinawa, so this time I'm going to Hokkaido.
I'm going to visit my father, Shibori.
I'm going to take my father back to Tokyo and save the children of the Karishimo family.
What are you talking about?
This is not a good thing at all.
It's not a good thing at all, but Hokkaido is good.
In terms of location?
Yes.
Where do you want to go?
I'll take you anywhere.
Anywhere?
I want to go to Okinawa or a cool place.
I don't have a vacation this summer.
Let's go to Hawaii or somewhere.
Why do you want to go?
I don't want anyone to go anywhere.
I don't want to go anywhere like that.
I don't get it.
I want to go around the globe and snap my fingers.
I don't want to go.
What are you going to do if you end up in Africa or something like that?
Don't you want to go?
More than that, if you go around the globe like this, you'll probably end up in the ocean.
That's not impossible.
I don't want to go to a strange place.
No, it's fun.
It's up to you.
That's why I'm telling you to go somewhere!
I don't want to go.
Never.
You don't want to go?
I don't want to go.
It can't be helped.
Hey!
You're so honest!
I don't want to go.
Is that so?
It's kind of easy, isn't it?
Well, we're looking for people like that.
Yeah.
But it's only 100 times.
It's too early.
Well, everyone, have fun again.
Goodbye!
You're just an idiot!
Hello!
Hello, hello.
What?
We talked about what we should do for the 100th anniversary.
Let's recruit them.
That's right.
What should we do?
Where should we go?
It's up to you whether to involve them or just us.
Well, that's true.
So please let us do it in various ways.
We'll recruit them.
If you have any questions, please send them to us.
And how to get home.
We'll go home in a van.
We'll smoke and go home.
We're also looking for ways to get home.
That's all.
And the assistant.
We're always the same.
That's all we know.
So we can't do anything about it.
Goodbye!
Send them to us.
Say goodbye to the camera at the end.
Goodbye!
What are you doing?
No, no.
Look forward.
I saw it.
Look at it carefully.
Look at it.
Don't look away!