What is today's topic?
Today...
Here
That's right
Look
He says he has worries
Yes
I'm sure you do
That's dirty
I'm sure you have 1000 or 2000
That's a lot
But
I have a lot of worries now
But I have the most
What do you think?
I want to break up with you
With Suwa-san?
No
You're still going on?
What do you mean?
Stop it
It's Inoue Harumi-san
What?
I want to break up with her
Inoue Harumi?
Yes
That's what it is
Really?
Yes
I'm friends with Inoue Harumi
So I wanted her to talk to Otomo-san
What?
You're friends with her?
No
I'm calling her
I'll talk to her first
Then I'll talk to her
Then I'll break up with Otomo-san
That's amazing
I'm sorry but I have to use the TV
Sorry
How do you know her?
That's amazing
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors
Why are you going out with her?
It's been a while
I think you know
She's coming
What?
I think you know
She wants to talk to you
I think you should talk to her
Who?
Otomo-san
It's been a while
Sit here
It's hard to talk to her
The reason I asked you to come here today is
I thought it would be better to tell Harumi my honest feelings
Don't say it's a bus
Sorry
You came from Kumamoto
You won the 91st Grand Prix at TV Asahi Idol Academy
Then you started performing at Sakurako Club
You didn't even look back at your debut song
Of course you have it
I trained you to be a top idol
What are you talking about?
That was about a year ago
A year ago, I was happy when I didn't have anything
You started singing
In the end
I thought about getting married
But in the end, it was my body
I think you'll notice, but it was my body
That's why
Thank you
What?
It's nice to say goodbye
The cherry blossoms are blooming
It's good to say goodbye
What?
Thank you
You don't have to remember today
We were worried
Mr. Onuma is worried
It's a good time to say goodbye
Let's talk
It's hard to say goodbye
Mr. Onuma had a girlfriend
He's popular
He's very popular
Good morning
I'm sorry
You're late
Were you waiting for me?
I was waiting for you
He's here
I'll call him
Him?
Yes
He's here
I'll tell you everything
You have something to say to me
What's going on?
What?
Did you cut your hair?
Yes
What's going on?
Why don't you talk to me?
Why don't you talk to him?
Him?
You know I like long hair
No
It may be good for fans
Your relationship with me is not like that
You have something to say to him
It's not like that
I'm tired
I don't think I can date you
You don't think you can date him?
I'm attracted to Hina Yoshikawa
She talks to me about everything
He's crazy
I can't date you
Good bye
Thank you
Let's go home
Wait
I have something to say
Who are you?
Are you a driver?
Where are you going?
What's going on?
I have something to confirm
I can't go alone
You can go with me
Me?
Wait
Do you know me?
I think so
Really?
I have something to confirm
I'm curious
I want to know
You want to know?
Who are you?
I'm Noriko Tachikawa
That's a good place
I didn't know
I'll help you
Wait
You look blue
Tachikawa
Long time no see
I don't know why
I have something to talk to you
What?
To you
To me?
Wait
I'll call you
I said what I wanted to say
I'll talk to you
Good luck
How are you?
Long time no see
What?
What are you hiding from me?
Can I have some water?
Wait
What do you want?
Are you seeing a man?
I didn't put a lid on you
This?
Yes
I bought this yesterday
It's too late
How much do you like?
I don't know what you're talking about
I don't want to break up with you
I don't know if I can break up with you
It's up to me
It's up to you
We don't know
Let's break up
It's okay
You changed
Let's break up
Let's go home
Okay
I failed today
Let's go home
Good bye
How was it?
I wanted to break up with you
But you changed
You can be a man
I'm not
I can't do it
Be careful
Idiot
You are an idiot
He's always in a bad mood
I don't like it
His neck hurts
He has many diseases
He doesn't have many
His neck and butt
His butt
He doesn't have many
He's amazing
He has a great body
Stop it
Why?
Don't say that again
It's a bad image
People don't know that
He's not a bad guy
He's a bad guy
I don't know what's inside the box
He said it's a dice
That's why it's rough
He said run away
I understand
That's why it's rough
Stop it
Don't force it
What?
No, don't force it
Don't force it
I'll tell you
You have a middle-aged body
Right?
I'm hungry
I'm surprised
You have a middle-aged body
My abs
It's amazing
Your abs
I don't know if I can break it
I'm sorry
Really?
You used to tell your family about this
You should do something
I'm a pig
I'm far from pigs
What are you doing?
I'm thin
I'm fat and thin
But you're like this
You're like this
You're wrong
Why?
You know it
I used to be fat
Right?
When I debuted
I was about 20
But I didn't think I was fat
What about me?
But you used to say, what about me?
Because I'm fat
No, you used to say, what about me?
What about Chocobo?
What about me?
This is strange
When you're famous, people call you Hama-chan or Machan
But before you're famous, people call you by the atmosphere
They call you big
But back then, people used to call you fat
I used to get hit by this
I was like this
My joints were strange
I wanted to lose weight
I see
But I was strong-willed
I lost weight
I was like this
Right
Back then, I weighed 53kg
Now I'm 55kg
That's not true
Stop being a pig
I'm not a pig
I'm not trying to be a pig
I used to be like that
The real pig is like Fujiwara
I was riding with him when we were heading to the NK hall
We were riding together
He didn't have a female seat
Why?
It was raining
But the car was cloudy
I used to be like that
I could feel the gas coming out of my body
I was like, are you new?
I didn't say anything
I was like this
Hey, it's cloudy again
I'm sorry
He must be hot
If he's fat, why?
Fat people have heat
When I think it should be cloudy
I get excited
That's what you call a pig
I'm not a pig
I'm not saying I'm a pig
I'm just saying I used to be like this
I don't think you've changed
I'll tell you one thing
You say you're hungry
But everyone is hungry
I can say that
I was 24 when I was born
Then let's be clear
Even Sorimachi Takashi is hungry
I'm hungry
When they're on TV, they do this
They push their whole body
They're doing it because they're still young
They have that kind of intention
Don't take it!
It hurts
That's not funny
It's okay
They're interested in each other
Because it's a popular business
Sorimachi...
I get it
When they're on TV, they do this
Hello, I'm Sorimachi
Why are you wearing a uniform?
That's how it is
When you're young, you still have that kind of desire
I'm the farthest from pigs
I already have a name tag
That's a new word
A name tag?
Wait
I have it in my bag
You have a name tag in your bag?
What does a famous musician do?
A star
For example, what are Inoue Yousui and Nagabuchi Tsuyoshi doing right now?
That's a good question
People are interested in that
That's right
You can't meet them on the street
Inoue Yousui is a normal person
I don't think he's changed
What about Nagabuchi Tsuyoshi?
He doesn't have a lot of privacy
I think that's all I can say
I'll tell someone who's only here
I'll edit it
Wait a minute
I'll take a look
What?
I'll call Nagabuchi Tsuyoshi
I'm sorry, I'm in a new place
I've never been here before
Let's take a look
Ah, ah
This is new
Ah, I see
I got it
I'm making gyoza sauce
There was too much vinegar, so I thought I'd add more soy sauce
It's almost done
It's said that the first thing you see is an egg shell
That's right
I think there's a limit to that
A limit?
How much do you think is an egg shell?
How much do you think it is?
It's a living thing
I see
For example, let's say you were there when the shell broke
I think it's you
Is that so?
No matter how heavy you are
I don't care
Then it's fine
No, it's not
You're just like Kuyo Kuyo
If you say that, everyone will think I'm heavy
What are you doing?
Don't call me Kuyo Kuyo
I'm going to pee
Where?
I'm going to pee where Kuyo Kuyo is
Then add some weight
No, I won't
Why not?
Then people will think I'm your father
That's what I'm saying
I see
People will think I'm a person with a deep heart
It's fine if you're a human
I'll say it quickly
You're the only one who's lost
You're in the way of talking to me
I said it one by one, but you're a human
Then a dog
A dog will bark
What do you mean by a dog?
It's scary
It's fine, I'm your father
It's fine
It's fine for a dog
Then the dog will say
You're not going to do it with me?
Do it!
Then the dog will say
What are you doing?
Are you my partner?
Then a fish
A goldfish
I got it, let's do it
What is it?
It's taking a long time
I'm your father
Goldfish is fine
Goldfish is
Do it!
Goldfish is fine
Do it together
I want to do it with you
If you don't want to do it, then go home
That's what I want to know
Will you do it in the future?
Say it now
If you don't want to do it, then go home
What about cockroaches?
You came to a good place
Thank you
It's hard to call this a father
I see
Let's do it
I'm your partner
It's like an old comedy
This program was brought to you by these sponsors