I wonder if everyone is having fun today?
If you do it, you'll live forever!
Chikiseki Matcha Hama-chan vs. Karaoke Udasu-san!
The pink team is the matcha team.
These are the members.
The blue team is the Hama-chan team.
The pink team is the Hama-chan team.
This team is not red-faced.
Where is this guy from?
No, no, no, why?
The reason why this team is red-faced is because this team is a former team.
The pink team is the Hama-chan team.
As I said at the beginning, the captain will be the player.
We will have a match.
In the end, both teams will get a total score.
It's simple. The team with the highest total score wins.
If you lose, the losing team will be punished.
I'll do this.
Let's say it together.
Coach!
Don't talk!
The pink team is the Hama-chan team.
I'm glad.
It's okay.
I'm glad I got over 80 points.
You're not good at this.
You're not going to change at all, though it's sad
Don't close your eyes
Don't worry, just go in, just go in, don't come out
That's not good
There's a song like that, there's a song like that
It's so good
You can't say such a thing
You can't sing
No, no, you can't
What's wrong with you?
You can't sing this song
Don't think about it
You can't even think about it
You can do it
I don't like this kind of pessimistic thinking.
You're too excited.
Who are you?
I said, who are you?
You know, I've been pretending a little bit, but I'm going to go all out from this time.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Right?
I'm not going to lose.
If we win 5 points each, we're going to win.
Oh, I see.
Are you ready?
Yes, go ahead.
At the end, there's my charm of low temperature.
Where's the low temperature?
Hey, turn around.
At the end, there's my charm of low temperature.
Why do you say it twice?
I want you to hear it again.
I wanted to say, why do you say it twice?
I'm going to go.
It's okay.
Don't be angry.
You shouldn't have thrown it.
Stop it!
You can win this!
It's cold
Ah, it's wrong
It's going up
The festival is somewhere in this world
It's not funny
Shabang
Ah
Take a shower
Hawaii
It's two
Thank you
You like this song
This is all
It's dirty
Shabang
Even if I look back
I'm a Hamada
I'm a Hamada from downtown
It's short
I sang until the second part
Thank you
Today, I was praised by a bad actor
I'm a fool
I'm sorry
I've been doing this since elementary school
Ah
I'm doing it
Sing
Eiko E
It's Eiko
I'm a fool
I've been doing this since elementary school
Why?
This is impossible
This is a score
Peru
It's still
It's going up
I'm nervous
Peru
Peru, your skin is getting thicker
Peru, did you get sick somewhere?
Peru
Grandpa
Grandpa who was doing takoyaki
Wait a minute
Even my dad
Actually
Eiko E
Let's take a look at the total score
The person who automatically says it is Machan
Eiko E
You are taking too much time, the audience is getting angry
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry
Go home
This year was hard too, 24 hours
I didn't do it! I didn't do it!
I went to Budokan
You're lying!
I went like this
If you're going to look at me like that, then go out!
Am I that kind of man?
This year, you said you didn't want to do it so I refused
Wait!
I didn't do it
But I really wanted to do it
You wanted to do it
What?
I didn't want to do it
You wanted to do it, didn't you?
What do you mean?
Whether it's high or low
What are you talking about?
Oh, low?
That's not it
What?
I didn't say I didn't want to do it
That's right, you wanted to do it, didn't you?
That's why I wanted to do it as Matsumoto Hitoshi
What are you talking about?
Then let me do it next year
How many times?
You have 24 hours, let me do it next year
That means I'm alone?
No, Matsumoto Hitoshi wants to do it, right?
Matsumoto Hitoshi is an individual
Matsumoto Hitoshi doesn't want to do it, he doesn't want to sing Sakura Fubuki
That has nothing to do with it
He sang Sakura Fubuki alone at home
What are you talking about?
He sang it last year
Don't lie
Why don't you take off your clothes and go home?
It looks like Kanpei-san is satisfied
That's good
It's amazing
That's why I think
You run, right?
You push yourself into a difficult place
People are getting closer to God
I see
You're getting closer to God
Yes, yes
Safe, safe
You're becoming very kind
Yes, yes
You're becoming humble
What are you talking about?
What's with that hand?
How do you do that?
I think that's true
But this year
The world championship is in the way
That's dirty
It looks like the world champion is running on a bike
That's not true
Well, well
That's dirty
He's pooping on his pants
That's really dirty
It's not what I'm saying
He's mentally pooping on his pants
Don't say things you don't understand
Everyone has pants in their heart
I don't have a dream
If you think about your pants, you have a dream
Life is about your pants
What about my pants?
What are you talking about?
Don't point your finger
It's sunny
What about your pants?
Stop it
The other day
I was reading a book
It's been a long time since I saw someone pooping
That man came to me
He was standing behind me
We're lovers
Were you here?
I thought you were gone
I was here the whole time
Don't say things you don't understand
Let's go over there
What kind of person is he?
Stop it
Give me back what I just said
I was so surprised
Don't say things you don't understand
A couple who are both ugly
Have a very good conversation
An ugly woman and an ugly man
They are licking each other's wounds
They are saying something amazing
I was surprised
You're the only one I can see
Wait
I was told
Is that so?
I'm scared
Where did you see that?
Don't say things like that
I'm saying things like that
I'm saying it on the bench at the park
You're saying it on the bench?
I'm scared
You were saying something amazing
An ugly woman
At the same cost
It's shocking
Who? You?
You're talking about what you saw
A long time ago
There was an ugly woman who was unthinkable
When I turned around
She was there
She was waiting for me
She was screaming
You're not a poop
If it's that bad
It's not like this
It's a very refreshing feeling
Ah!
How do you want to change your name?
Do you usually change your name?
What's that?
I don't know
I changed it to something like this
Matsumoto, something, something, something
Matsumoto?
It's a word that we don't understand
I'll go with Whiskey Coke
What?
Idiot!
You're saying good things
I don't know what you're talking about
Whiskey Coke is stronger
Let's go with this
Why?
It's something like this
Why? Because the main character is a crow
That's the question
After the crow, it looks delicious
What's in that?
What did you put in it?
I think it's the other way around
What?
Instead of being stuck in the skin and bulging
If you get stuck in the skin, it shrinks
Other than the part that got stuck
If you get stuck in this part
If you get stuck in this part, the whole thing shrinks
Only this part is left
That part is the memory
The one before
The one before you get stuck
The skin sucks blood
If you suck blood
Only the amount you suck
Only the amount you suck will come out
This is the skin
You should stop that
No one will kill the skin
That's not good
That's it
If you stick your face in, that's it
It's coming
That's not good
That's where you get killed
That's it
Everyone thinks that's not good
Stop it
On the highway
Ah
The old man on the highway
How did he get there?
I've seen it many times
Really?
Why?
They send you to a bus like Hiace
Really?
That's it
This is funny
How did he get there?
What?
From Arujan
The old man on the highway
How did he get there?
In a wagon
I've seen it many times
The punishment game
It's a seasonal game
It's a fun festival
That's right
It's a punishment game
Thank you
The losing team
Why are you like that?
It's really annoying
The reason I lost is because of this man
He should be good at singing
How many points did you get?
57 points
Koba
How many points did you get?
51 points
Let's go
It's hot
You're too excited
Who is it?
It's hot
It's like I'm being punished
What is this?
It's hot
Producer, do you have a fan?
I want you to press it
Let's see your face
Put it on
It's done
I'm scared
He's saying he's scared
He's worried
Let's see your face
This is good
He's getting better
Is it good?
Let's see your face
It's good
Everyone, press it
It's the last punishment game
It's fun
He looks like a super saiyan