Thank you for your hard work.
Now, we are in downtown Gakinosukai.
Hello, I'm Genno.
This is the studio of Nittere.
We just finished the show.
Now, we are in downtown Gakinosukai.
Don't zoom in on me.
I'm sorry.
This is our manager, Mitake.
Today, as promised, we are going to do the SM.
Let's go to the venue.
I had a picture in my head.
It's 10 times bigger than I thought.
I'm like the last warrior of the Famicom.
If I defeat him, I'll be free.
Now, we are on Japanese TV.
This is Kanda Pansen.
Let me introduce him again.
He is the monster of Nitta.
Good morning.
That was close.
I laughed when I first saw him.
Did you take the bullet train on Sunday?
Yes, I did.
Don't be so serious.
Nitta will be free today.
I'll see you later.
Please look forward to it.
Are you ready?
Yes.
I'm Hamada, the mayor of Kojima.
Nice to meet you.
Leave it to me.
Yes.
Your son will be saved.
Thank you.
This kidnapping case is not a big deal.
Really?
I've done it many times.
It's easy.
Listen to me.
Thank you.
You'll be fine.
I'll tell you one thing.
Yes.
Even if the criminal calls me,
don't tell the police that I'm here.
Yes.
Okay?
If the criminal calls me and finds out that I'm here,
don't tell the police that I'm here.
Listen to me.
Okay?
When the criminal calls you,
take as much time as you can.
Yes.
Just do it.
Don't do unnecessary things.
Take as much time as you can.
Ma'am.
Don't do it.
I'm sorry.
I'm nervous.
You have to take it right away.
Yes.
It's over.
Don't do it.
Yes.
Listen to me.
Do you understand?
Yes.
When the criminal calls you,
take as much time as you can.
Yes.
That's enough.
Why are you speaking in such a low voice?
Thank you.
Yes.
It's okay.
This is...
What is it?
I have to record his voice.
Hello?
Is my son okay?
How much do I have to pay?
I'm sure you didn't do anything.
That's good.
Very good.
Thank you.
Let's ask him.
Yes.
Hello?
Hello.
This is Nikonikonkaku Shujuku.
Is my son okay?
He's doing well.
By the way,
your salary has been accumulated for about two months.
How much do I have to pay?
It's 64,000 yen in two months.
You didn't do anything to my son, did you?
It's okay.
This is not Sparta Shujuku.
Thank you.
Madam.
Don't do it.
Yes.
I'll beat you.
Don't do it.
Yes.
Listen to me.
I'll kill you.
No.
Thank you very much.
Do you really think so?
I can't do it.
I'll kick you.
Yes.
Okay?
Answer me.
Yes.
Okay?
If the criminal calls you again,
Yes.
don't get in trouble.
Okay?
Yes.
Don't make the criminal angry.
Don't make him angry.
Yes.
This is the rule.
Okay?
Yes.
Do you understand?
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'll call you.
Don't make him angry.
Yes.
Hello.
The criminal.
Is my son okay?
Your son?
That dirty dog?
What?
Is he okay?
He's not okay.
It's about time.
Did you hear?
The criminal.
What?
Calm down.
Don't make him angry.
You're a criminal.
You're a criminal with a black face.
You're a fool.
Yes.
I'm a criminal.
My son.
What are you talking about?
You're a criminal.
You're a criminal with a face like a fool.
What kind of face is that?
I'm sorry.
You're a criminal.
Did you call me a criminal?
You're a criminal with a face like a fool.
What kind of face is that?
Who did you call a criminal?
The criminal who looks like a fool.
What kind of face is that?
You're angry.
What?
Don't make him angry.
With a face like a fool.
What?
Pooh.
A little more.
You're definitely looking down on me.
What are you talking about?
You.
Do you have to say that to me?
What do you mean?
If you say that to me, I'll kill you.
I'll kill you.
You'll kill a kid? Do it yourself, idiot!
You're weird, you're weird, hey!
Don't be such a crybaby, you idiot!
Idiot, idiot!
Antenna.
The other day, when I was on my way to Tokyo Station, I slipped.
In a taxi?
Yeah, in a taxi.
About 10 meters.
I slipped like crazy.
I thought I was going to die.
You wouldn't die if you slipped.
That was really dangerous.
I've been there before.
I see.
When I was freezing.
I was with a friend of mine who was freezing.
On a day like this, there are probably a lot of idiots who are freezing.
About three minutes later, I was already used to it.
I was like, it's dangerous!
And then, I was like,
The first time I saw it, it was the scariest.
The driver was wearing a red sweater.
The girl in the passenger seat was wearing a white sweater.
And then, it spins.
It looked like a pink sweater.
I thought it was scary.
It was spinning so much.
The driver was a man.
The girl in the passenger seat looked like a pink okama.
Idiot!
I don't think anyone believes it.
It was really scary.
I'm scared of cars.
I've experienced a lot of things with cars.
Me too.
I had a standing wave test.
You go to a training center and you learn about the standing wave test.
If the air pressure is low, the tires will burst.
I was the first one to get a test.
I got a test for 10,000 yen.
Idiot!
You should buy anything.
I got a test for 10,000 yen.
Starlet.
That's amazing.
I wanted everyone to ride that car.
It was so funny.
It was so worn out.
Really.
It was about 7 years ago.
When I got on the highway, I heard a weird sound.
I heard a weird sound.
You're lying.
I think something was living on the roof.
When I got on the highway, I heard a weird sound.
The wind was blowing from somewhere.
I was running.
I heard the sound of a helicopter.
I thought there was an accident.
I thought it was close.
I was running.
I couldn't fly a helicopter.
I was flying with a joke.
I was flying like this.
You were singing a song.
I was so tired.
I stopped at the parking lot.
I couldn't see the tire on the right.
I thought I was going to be killed.
I was in a hurry.
I went into the car.
I looked at the rear view mirror.
It was a very dangerous car.
When the traffic light stopped, I didn't know what I was saying.
I think it was a real car.
The only thing I could do was...
A woman was sitting next to me.
I told her to stop.
I couldn't see the rear view mirror.
I opened the door and tried to get out of the car.
I was looking at the rear view mirror.
I tried to get out of the car and then pushed the arm to her.
You didn't try to get out of the car.
Don't do that.
The woman in the front seat sat down ligth.
At that moment, you know what?
I tried not to look up.
I put my hand in the Baby next to.
I took her because it was almost a miscarriage.
I thought I was still putting my hand in the baby's紗.
It's hard to get out of the bed.
I was on the train, and suddenly I went to the toilet, and I was in trouble.
What happened?
I was on a narrow road, and I was shaking like this.
You were sweating.
I was sweating, and I couldn't move.
You were shaking like this.
I was shaking like this, and sometimes I had to use the accelerator like this.
I couldn't open it, so I had to do it like this.
I was driving like this, and I was shaking like this.
The front tires were like this.
Really?
Why were the tires like your legs?
If it was dangerous on the Majinger Z, it would have been like this.
The car was like this, too.
But you've never been wet, right?
No, I've never been wet.
There's a saying that you can't tell what's going on because of the heat, right?
Yes, there is.
My brother was crazy.
In the past, we were sleeping together.
The heat was about 40 degrees.
I don't know what he was thinking.
He woke up at about 3 o'clock in the evening.
He woke up and said,
Winner? And then he fell asleep again.
What is it?
What is a winner?
It was funny, so I couldn't sleep until the morning.
It's a boring story.
With my wife.
Moriguchi Hiroko's office.
He was from Moriguchi's office, so I couldn't tell him.
So you went on a trip with your wife, right?
Yes, I went on a trip and stayed at a hotel.
I told my manager that I was going on a trip with a different person.
When I was sleeping.
He suddenly woke up and said,
Hey, I'm going home.
He woke up and said,
My wife said,
Where are you going home?
I'll show you the postcard.
It's cute.
I'm a salaryman.
It's nice.
Well, I'd like you to wave your whip.
You're going to graduate from university.
We're going to shoot a commercial.
Wave your whip.
Where are you going home?
In Itomori.
It's cute.
Thank you very much.
I can see your panties.
Let me introduce the postcards.
You've all seen it.
In the opening of Zoom-in Asa on January 17th,
Machan was dancing strangely.
But it's a big laugh.
It seems that Zoom-in Asa has become a comedy program.
From now on, there will be a lot of games.
The loser will do various things.
Please enjoy it.
For example, Hama-chan will go out to welcome the newlyweds.
Are you going out?
Are you stupid?
I don't want to go out.
I want to go out, but I can't.
Do you really want to go out?
I want to go out.
I want to go out, but why?
I don't want to go out.
I can't help it.
It's a matter of fate.
This person is...
Good evening, Mr. Ochihama.
I always watch your show.
There are various things.
When I took the questionnaire in our class,
It became like a tongue.
It's just one of us.
Please don't worry.
All the best 5 are included.
First of all, if you want to be my boyfriend,
First, me.
Hama-chan.
Second, Hiromi.
Third, Mach-chan.
Fourth, Chin-san.
Fifth, U-chan.
If you want to be my brother,
First, Hiromi.
Second, me.
Third, Nan-chan.
Fourth, Chin-san.
Fifth, you.
If you want to be my marriage partner,
First, Mach-chan.
Did you hear the sound of bowing?
It's already low.
Second, Hiromi.
Third, me.
Fourth, Chin-san.
Fifth, U-chan.
Your personality...
Your personality seems to be good.
I haven't told you yet.
First, Hiromi.
What?
That's strange.
First, Hiromi.
This is strange.
Second, U-chan.
I know this.
Third, Chin-san.
I know Chin-san.
Fourth, Nan-chan.
I know this.
Fifth, me.
I don't know.
Isn't there a me in it?
There is no better personality than me.
This is the most strange thing.
I can't believe that you are in it.
Oh, no.
If you can do this,
Bring your sister here.
Tell me everything you've done so far.
What did I do?
You brothers are amazing.
Godzilla vs. Biolance.
I had a fight with my sister.
I only had a towel.
I ran to the beach with a towel.
I got wet and got wet again.
This idea is amazing.
If I had only a towel, I would have stopped.
I decided to get wet.
I got wet.
I made a decision in a few seconds.
This is impossible even for Golgo.
It's amazing.
I see.
I had such a time.
I like to make food like this.
I like to make curry bread.
I like to make Fanta.
Fanta?
It's sweet, so it's good for hormones.
I like to make hormones.
I like to make a lot of sauce.
You said the same thing.
I like to make yogurt.
There was a boy, named Chichiasa.
He said, come over here.
racers
Me and my friends were having lunch.
He asked.
Is Chichiasa different from Chichiyasu?
I said yes.
Chichiasa?
He threw the one that I gave him deliberately in the blackboard.
It was a Chichiyasu.
I'm Chichiyasu Yuta!
It's an interesting first dream, isn't it?
Wait!
I saw it with my own eyes!
And then I was like, well, well, well...
You know, I have a lot of strength.
If I do something like that, I think I'll get hurt.
I can't use my right hand.
What are you talking about?
Even though I'm weak at arm wrestling, I have a lot of strength.
Wait!
I'm weak at arm wrestling?
Let's do it.
Let me tell you this.
I don't like to simply do arm wrestling.
I'll do something.
No, no, I'm confident.
Liar!
What are you talking about?
No, no, no.
Can you do it?
Yes, I can.
All right.
Now you can watch the second showdown.
What?
Can you do it?
What do you mean?
Well, let's do it.
Which one are you going to do?
What do you mean?
Don't show your hand at first.
And then you make me think you can win.
And then you do it seriously next time.
You're like a Showa Shoki.
Who did it?
Showa Shoki.
Don't do such a classic thing.
Don't do it.
You're like a old man.
Your attitude.
I'm a little bit of a skirt.
Anyway.
Come on.
Like this.
No, it's not like that.
Who says this to the whole body?
Put your strength in.
Come on.
It's not like that.
Put your strength in.
The first showdown is good.
The staff is excited.
Where was it?
Yutake.
What?
Girls' High School.
I'm going to rip your pants.
Why?
Why do you have to rip it?
I'm going to rip it.
It's like a gathering of college students.
If I can't rip it, I'm going to cut it.
What are you going to do if you cut it in reverse?
If you give me a postcard, I can enter this room.
You can enter the room?
I can enter.
I'm going to rip it.
And in the opening...
I was thinking about SM.
I forgot.
I'm going to rip it.
He's not walking outside today, is he?
He's only in the car.
I wonder if he's outside.
That's right.
He doesn't have a stroke until he goes to the dorm.
He's outside.
I'll have you put in a mosaic.
If you're watching on TV,
if you want to come to my house,
please come to my house.
It's like a zoom-in.
It's like a punishment game.
Let's do something like this.
Please call me with this.
I'll be waiting for you.
I've already told you everything.
This program is 300.
Ooyama International Products
Sponsored by