Oh, oh, you can't miss this!
The two's free talk is the basis for the downtown kid's use and Arahen.
The recording is actually close to an hour, so there are a lot of things that could not be broadcasted.
So tonight, let's release the secret TV talk all at once.
Kid's Use Marugi Preservation Room Unpublished Talk Show
Now, gotta check this out!
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
First, from this year's unpublished talk broadcasted on January 7th.
Matsumoto-san, it seems that you gave birth to a boy last month.
How difficult was it? Please tell us your impressions.
Hey, hey!
Well, if you're going to give birth, you have to be a Yagizano kid.
Was it a boy?
Yes, it was a boy.
It was really difficult to reduce it.
How difficult was it? Where did it come from?
What?
Where did it come from?
Well, from the side of the ***.
Where is the *** side?
From the side of this ***.
Oh, so you had to cut it?
What?
What do you mean, what?
There's nothing open.
There was nothing open.
So when I was in high school, I hid it in my pocket.
You were hiding it in your ***.
I didn't want to be found out.
You didn't want to be found out.
So I hid it in my ***.
You were a foreigner?
Yes, I was a foreigner.
Your partner.
Yes, my partner.
What's your name?
Stranger.
What are you doing now, stranger?
I'm working.
What are you doing now?
Well, I'm working at K-ON twice.
What?
That's the thing.
It's strange.
I can't do this.
Next, the unspoken question of the day of January 21st and the unit of illusions.
Matsumoto-san, please tell us one thing about Matsumoto-san, who played the role of the face of the entertainment world and the 80% of the entertainer couple actually had an affair behind his back.
It's a secret information that even Komuro Family's Awada-san doesn't know, but Komuro is going to form an imaginary unit this year.
It seems that he is one of the members that the whole of Japan is looking forward to. Does Matsumoto-san know about it?
Yes, I know.
I'm wearing it properly.
What are you wearing?
It's a cell phone.
A cell phone?
Do you know about it?
Yes, I know.
It's a new unit.
Yes.
I'm going to be surprised. I don't know if I can say this.
Really?
Yes.
How many people are there?
Please don't be surprised.
It's quite unexpected.
Is that so?
Yes.
It's a Chiba Shinichi and a dog.
Komuro-san, what are you going to do?
You brought a Chiba Shinichi and a dog. What are you going to do?
I was surprised in a different way.
Are you holding it?
I'm holding it.
Are you holding a dog when you sing a Chiba Shinichi song?
If you think of it as holding a dog, that's it.
But it's a unit.
But you have to do something. You have a role.
I'm not going to avoid it.
Are you going to avoid it?
No, it's like this.
I'm not avoiding it.
I'm standing up, but my feet are on the ground.
I'm holding it like this.
If you're going to avoid it, you have to stay like this.
That's right.
Every time I move, I'm like this.
But...
Next, the three unopened talks.
Matsumoto-san is active as a super model who can see the world.
He's going to take a break from the program.
I'm going to have this party next month.
Next month?
Yes.
Where did you see it?
The party.
What?
I saw the party in me.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to have a party next month.
Is that so?
I don't know if it's convenient for work.
Do you work as a model?
I do.
It says super model.
That's right.
90% of my income is model.
That's not true.
No, no, no.
I've been looking at it.
Where have you been?
I've been looking at it on my nose.
That's harsh.
What kind of clothes do you wear?
I can't tell you that.
It's hard to do that.
Tell me a little bit.
I'm going to get angry.
I feel sorry for you.
It's been a long time since I've seen you.
Really?
Yes.
What do you mean?
It's hard to do that.
I feel sorry for you.
I'm going to get angry.
It's hard to do that.
Tell me a little bit.
What are you going to do?
Do you know what's going to be popular this year?
I don't know.
Even if you're called the leader of the fashion world, you don't know.
I'm sorry. Please tell me.
Do you know what's going to be popular this year?
I don't know at all.
You don't know that?
Yes.
It's a popular food every year.
What was popular last year?
I don't know.
I don't know that either.
I don't want to talk about this anymore.
I'm telling you because I don't know.
Last year, white was popular.
You're saying what?
I don't know.
You didn't know?
I'm sorry.
This year, yellowish green is popular.
Yellowish green.
Yellowish green is popular.
Really?
Yes.
This time it's a jacket.
I'll wear a jacket.
A white jacket.
No, no, no.
That was last year.
This year?
This year.
Ninety-six.
I'll ask you this.
If yellowish green is popular, is it all yellowish green?
No, that's not it.
Wait a minute.
There's yellowish green.
Of course there's yellowish green in it.
I'm sorry.
First, a white jacket.
A jacket, right?
A white jacket.
And a pair of red pants.
A white jacket and red pants?
Let's wear red pants.
You'll wear them, right?
I'll wear them, right?
And a pair of black gloves.
And a white hat.
I'll wear them.
It's all yellowish green.
Well, that's fine.
Will this story spread?
Where did the yellowish green come from?
And then...
What's this?
I have a bat.
It's yellowish green, so it's one point.
I'll catch you.
And here it is.
What happens if a herbivore eats meat?
I don't think about it.
Well, to tell you the truth, they all want to eat meat.
Right?
They all want to eat meat.
Even rabbits really want to eat meat.
But they can't eat it.
Why is that?
They don't have the means to catch prey.
Even if their ears are this long, they won't die.
Even if they come close.
Well, they all want to eat it.
It doesn't matter.
Well, for example, people who don't smoke.
If they suddenly start smoking, they'll go like this.
It's the same thing. It's a rejection reaction.
It's a bit of a PP.
That won't work.
I've seen it once.
A deer eating meat.
A deer eating meat?
It's like a deer eating a cow.
Really?
What happened?
I was surprised.
Who?
I saw it and thought, I did it.
You did it?
Yes.
What did you do?
I think I did it.
Why?
I think it was happening.
Happening?
Happening.
Happening? What?
It was happening.
What's happening?
It was happening, right?
It's happening.
What? Happening?
It's not happening.
What is it?
What if it didn't die?
The deer?
The deer was excited when it ate the meat.
What is it?
It's like, is there enough money?
What is money?
It's so happy.
It's so expensive.
It was opening its mouth.
I was just kidding.
It was saying, I got the receipt.
It was opening its mouth.
It was saying, I'm going to the basement.
Furthermore, this talk.
Can you tell us how to distinguish a woman from a man in one shot?
I've learned a lot of things.
And I've finally reached that point.
You can distinguish a woman from a man in one shot?
Yes.
It says, in one shot.
Yes, you can distinguish.
Really?
What would happen in this case?
What would happen?
Would it be your girlfriend?
Or would it be someone walking on the street?
This is something you don't see.
You don't see?
Would you be able to tell that it's her when she walks by?
Would you?
Got it.
Well, first, a woman in one shot.
Doesn't wear a skirt.
Oh, really?
It's something you don't like.
It's defenseless.
You want to keep it firm.
That's serious.
Not everyone would say that, but that's how it's usually done.
First, remember this.
And then, pants.
Some people like g-pants.
But even with pants, wearing white pants is absolutely impossible.
I see.
It's like an old lady's laugh.
Yes, yes.
And then, I observed various things.
For example, let's pick up a girl.
What about this guy? What about today?
First, pants or pants.
I see.
All of these things are safe.
Wear a skirt.
And it's not even a white skirt.
This is a pretty high percentage.
I see.
80% is OK.
At that time, I'll do something a little mean.
I see.
I'll say, show me your bag.
And then, the girl...
And then...
If she sees it, it's bad.
Is that OK?
And then, when I said, lend me the toilet.
She said, OK.
I glanced at her.
I can see almost everything.
That kind of person wears a mysterious small bag.
It doesn't matter if it's research.
What's that?
No, no, no.
I think I'm saying something pretty good.
It's not a good thing.
It's like, yes, yes.
Well, I don't know about the small bag.
For example, today...
So, you're saying that you can see everything at once.
Let's say how much of this is 100% correct.
This is a scene from my show, NINZA-BURO.
The person wearing black pants is correct.
So, for example, today, you're in the audience.
Is that OK?
When you look around...
Oh, there's a girl.
She's wearing black pants.
What a coincidence.
Wait, wait.
Why are you here?
Oh, Otaku, by the way...
Wait, wait.
You have to say it properly.
Don't be shy.
If it's true, it's true.
If it's not, it's not.
You really have to say it.
What do you think?
It's not.
She's wearing it with her boyfriend today.
What?
These are black pants.
A girl and a boy.
She doesn't have sex.
That's the other way around.
What do you think?
It's not.
What's not?
What do you mean it's not?
I don't know if you know.
I know.
I'm not going to say it's not.
It came suddenly.
It's not.
I don't know.
She's wearing black pants.
According to my research, if there are four people, one of them is like that.
What does that mean?
If there are four people, one of them is like that.
That's what the emperor said.
What did the emperor say?
Because girls usually have sex for a week.
You're laughing too much.
They have sex for a week.
If they have sex for a week, that means they have sex for four times a month.
If you think about it, it's one-fourth of the probability.
If you think about it, if there are four women, there's one.
That's the calculation.
So you and you and you and you and you and you and you.
It's 25% probability.
That's the calculation.
And if she's wearing pants, it's 50%.
That's it.
And if she's wearing black pants, it's 80%.
And if she doesn't like the bag, it's 94%.
It's a mystery.
I understand.
By the way, there are four or five women around here.
Who's the manager?
It doesn't matter if I'm the manager.
It doesn't matter.
Why doesn't it matter?
It's like, there's no problem!
But I understand.
I understand.
What?
It's because the children are the best.
There are a lot of shows, but they're all useless.
But you always put them in the show.
You should say it on the spot.
Really.
I haven't watched TV recently. What's useless?
What's useless?
It's almost useless.
I don't know what's useless.
What's useless?
Which is useless?
But recently, I don't think it's decreasing.
I think it's a good tendency.
I see.
It doesn't matter if a weak person puts it on.
It's useless!
You've been telling me all the time lately.
Who's doing that?
What?
I don't know.
You don't know?
I'm going to say it!
You aren't telling the truth.
You didn't say that?
You're not saying something you didn't mean to.
Say something.
Say sorry to me.
Ouch!
I didn't say that!
The voice of the government!
What are you doing here, Yo-san?
What do you mean?
I don't know at all.
No, no.
What?
Shall we take a look?
Let's take a look.
What are you doing here, Yo-san?
Please.
Rolling stone.
What are you doing here, Yo-san?
An unreleased talk on February 11th.
What is the Iwafu Telephone Phrase?
A man named Masumoto-san, who once passed the Kyoto University, but chose to stay in Yoshimoto.
In the case of a college entrance exam, it is often said that a person who failed to pass the exam will receive a cherry blossom.
But I feel that it is a bit late, and it is a bit blue.
Please think of a complaint that will not make a person who failed to pass the exam blue.
Did you pass the exam at Kyoto University?
At that time, did you pass the exam with a cherry blossom?
At my university, I didn't do that.
You didn't do that?
I didn't do that.
It was a little more fashionable.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Both the person who failed and the person who passed the exam did it properly.
What did you study at that time?
When I passed the exam...
When you passed the exam?
Yes.
Kyoto University, right?
Kyoto University.
Yes, Kyoto University.
What did you study?
Well...
Ma-eba-kira.
Kira is good.
Kira is like, oh, I passed the exam.
What is Ma-eba-kira?
Oh, I see.
Ma-eba-kira is a joke that makes you happy.
Ma-eba-kira.
I see.
How did you pass the exam?
Uh...
I was a little jealous.
Huh?
You don't really understand that.
I really don't.
You really don't understand that.
Ma-eba-kira, I understand what you think.
But you don't understand that I was jealous.
You understand, don't you?
It's not something that makes you happy.
This is like, oh, oh, oh...
And then, you're like, shah! shah!
And then, you're like, bo!
You don't like it, do you?
I don't like it.
That's why.
You haven't become that blue yet, have you?
Of course you think that's okay, right?
Even if you say, Munagebon, I don't know what you're talking about.
Excuse me.
Kyoto University.
Munagebon.
I'm hungry.
There's a lot of meaning to it.
It's when you pass the exam.
What?
I'm hungry?
You're hungry.
Isn't there something good about it?
In the left-hand side.
What's that?
Following that, on February 18th, Hama-chan's unknown past was discovered.
This is a question for the president of the Japan Animal Lovers Association, Mr. Mazo.
I don't like animals, but it's said that there are a lot of evil people who hate animals.
I also want to be seen as a person who hates animals, but what should I do? Please tell me.
I see.
Are there a lot of evil people who hate animals?
Everyone feels that, right?
When a woman says she hates children, it's like, wow, this woman is a terrible woman.
There's a fixed concept like that, right?
What kind of person says they hate animals?
I see.
Right? That's different, right?
It's different.
It's difficult to say that you like it or hate it.
Even if you look like this, you like animals, right?
That's right.
You really look like you're going to kill them.
I really, really like them.
Even if you don't like them, it's normal, right?
Seriously, if I had a bag, I'd like to put a kangaroo in it.
I like it so much that I'd like to put a kangaroo in it.
Even though you're going to put it in?
Even though I'm going to put it in, I like it so much that I'd like to put it in.
I don't hate animals that much either.
Why are you pinching my nose?
Stop pinching my eyes.
I've seen a lot of you doing that.
You'll get in trouble if you do that.
No, you've done it before.
You've done it before?
You grabbed the horns of the deer and turned them upside down.
I was surprised by that.
That's true, it's easy to do.
I can do it, so just watch.
I can't do it.