After this, it's downtown's Waki no Tsukai Yara-hen.
This is Wada-ben.
It's Waki no Tsukai Yara-hen's Chikiriki!
Matsumoto, Kasutaya, and Hamada haven't borrowed 3,000 yen yet!
How many points will Wada-ben get?
Now, you've finally returned 3,000 yen.
That's not what I'm talking about.
I haven't borrowed it yet!
So, what should we do?
So, today, we're going to settle this game.
Today, Wada-ben has come as a guest.
Today, we're going to talk about TV.
We're going to talk about TV.
In this talk, we're going to, for example,
Wada-ben, we're going to touch his body.
We're going to hit him.
We're going to score points.
First of all, the easiest thing to hit is here.
With the back of the sword.
I'll give you one point.
That's easy.
This is really easy.
After all, the head is important.
It's important, so I think it's okay to do this.
How about pulling his hair?
That's a gold card.
This is one point.
I'll give you 30 points for the hip next to it.
Well, I'm doing this.
How about this?
I'm a little angry.
It's 10 points.
Well, it's in the middle of a talk.
Wada-ben is not here yet.
Ben?
Try again.
It's a guy named Ben.
I'm a little angry.
That means, this is also a point.
I'll give you 30 points.
What happens if you go from behind?
What happens if you go to the nose hook?
This is a bonus.
I'll give you 50 points.
Is there such a talk?
If you start a talk suddenly, it will be messed up.
In the first half, I had a normal talk.
While drawing out the charm of Mr. Wada-ben.
Three minutes from where you are.
I think there's tea.
I'll drink it up.
I'll drink it up all at once.
Three minutes from the time you drink it up.
I'll give you a bonus in the meantime.
On the contrary, you can't touch it until then.
There's something I want to say.
I'll say something I can't help it.
I'll be upset.
If you hit it while you're drinking it up, you'll get minus points.
It's still a start from minus.
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
I'm serious today.
That's right.
Today, we have a guest, Mr. Wada-ben.
I'm going to turn off the TV now.
That's right.
I think we can have a meaningful conversation.
Is that so?
Let's get started.
Mr. Wada-ben, please.
I'll call you Wada-ben.
You can call me Wada-poop.
It's the same thing.
I see.
I think your clothes are different today.
Is that so?
What do you mean?
Shouldn't you wear a gown or a jacket?
Is that so?
Downtown.
No, no, no.
Downtown is fine.
I got hit.
I got a high score.
Today, even if I say I'll turn off the TV,
Let's talk roughly.
You have to turn it off.
Oh, really?
I'll turn off the TV.
Then your clothes will be different again.
Why is that?
You have to dress up like you're going to turn it off.
I don't understand the show at all.
I see.
Here you go.
You'd better turn it off.
Oh, really?
I don't want to see your face.
You're fast.
It's important to be funny.
That's right.
If you're serious, you can't help it.
I see.
I can't help it.
That's right.
I don't know if it's funny or not.
Why is that?
I can't help it.
But...
I'll turn off the TV.
There's a masterpiece like this.
I'll turn it off.
I'll turn off the TV.
There was nothing the other day.
I see.
How old are you now?
I was born in 1996.
How old are you?
I was born in 1956.
It was a little more broken.
I quit.
I write it as a thought of giving up.
You don't know the principle of giving up?
What is it?
Well, whatever.
It's a poop.
It's not a poop.
I took my son's hand and walked in the hallway.
It's called an aging phenomenon.
At that time...
From the other side...
Do you know Morimi-chan?
It's Mori Mitsuko-san.
She appeared.
She said this.
Oh!
A big fart and a small fart appeared.
You bastard!
How was it when you were young? Were you popular?
Let's be young.
What did you do when you were young?
This is...
Even if you're young, even if you're old, it's the same.
Is that so?
What did you do on TV?
I want to make a drama on TV.
Who are you using now?
Everyone's dead.
I see.
It's called Cinderella.
Is there a dead person?
Even if you do that, it's not exciting.
I'll do a drama.
Please do it.
I want to be encouraged by a proper person.
If you encourage me...
You're encouraging me.
I'll encourage you.
The result came out.
I got this kind of score.
I got the final score.
Let's go.
What's the score?
158.
249.
Are you kidding me?
You got 249 points.
That's too much.
Hello.
Mr. Hamada.
Everyone's smiling at me.
I'm shining.
I'm smiling like this.
You're laughing a lot.
I was talking about the punishment game in the dressing room.
There's nothing good about it.
I've done a lot of things.
There's no doubt that you're going to play a punishment game.
Why?
This time, really.
So I'm going to talk about how to extend your vision to the outside world.
You can't go to America.
You can't go there.
I was talking about the Statue of Liberty.
You're going to fly from the helicopter.
You're going to run into a huge hedgehog.
Don't copy me.
That's not good.
The Statue of Liberty is a symbol of America.
If you hit it...
If you hit it, it's going to be hard.
Amazon.
Amazon is a one-way trip.
I'm not alone.
What are you going to do in Amazon?
I'll have lunch in one hand.
You're going to have lunch somewhere?
No.
I don't know what's going to come out.
I'll be wearing a pair of socks with a collar.
You're going to walk.
I was talking about this.
I'm going to wear a penis.
I'm going to be the president of a company.
What are you doing?
President of a company.
Let's think about it.
If you don't think about the confrontation, you'll be punished.
Confrontation is not a time to fight.
That's what you're going to do, right?
That's right.
That's definitely right.
I understand.
I'll think about the punishment.
Do something dangerous.
Why?
Why don't you ask?
There's that thing.
Do something like this.
Put your head on a plate.
I'll die.
First of all, it's okay.
Why is it okay?
It's three bullets.
Is that so?
It's better than being targeted with one point.
Are you stupid?
It's three bullets.
The bullets are flying all over you.
I'm going to do something good.
What are you talking about?
Who are you?
Who said that?
Daimonjiyaki.
There's Daimonjiyaki, right?
In Kyoto.
In the scene of Daimonjiyaki.
You become a Hidaruma.
Go to the top of the table and die as a dog.
If you do that, you'll lose your partner.
It's okay.
What's okay?
You become a Hidaruma.
Let's think about various conditions.
What kind of conditions?
You become a Hidaruma.
Let's think about various conditions.
It's okay.
Why is that?
If you come to the left, it's okay.
What's okay?
It's not okay.
It's so good.
If I do it, I'll do it.
No, it's not okay.
You've never done anything scary, have you?
I'm not scared of my life.
That's right.
But it's scary.
You'll get hurt.
Where do you want to get hurt?
Why?
Do you want to get hurt?
You're a fool.
I'm a fool.
Where do you want to get hurt?
What if your wings fly away?
That's your way of doing it.
I'm the one who moves it.
It's not okay.
You'll get hurt.
It's scary.
You're just doing this.
You don't know how scary it is, do you?
When I'm in the car, I can see the entertainer.
Today or yesterday.
When I'm waiting for a signal, the person who's stopped is smiling at me.
I don't know if he's smiling at me because he knows me.
When I was going to CX yesterday, when I stopped at the signal, everyone was smiling at me.
They're looking at me.
They're smiling at the car itself.
I'm definitely in the car.
They're looking at me.
They're smiling at me.
I'm wondering if they're looking at me.
They're looking at me so much.
I'm definitely in the car.
It's not my fault.
It's my car.
I got off at CX and looked at it.
Nothing was written on it.
I was shopping at a convenience store before.
The old man was smiling at me.
I thought he was smiling at Matsumoto.
But when I got home, he had lipstick on his lips.
I was like, I can't do this.
It's your fault.
Wipe it off properly.
That's not good.
At that time, I did it in the dark.
I did it in the dark.
What are you doing?
It's not Rumiko and Kenya.
I put on my shoes and closed the door.
You're a bad guy.
Why did you do it?
That's right.
It's like you're planning something.
I'm planning something.
But I close the door and turn off the lights.
At that time, it's a half laugh, right?
It's a half laugh.
After that...
It's not Rumiko and Kenya.
I pass it like this.
Why do you do that?
I turn the woman behind me and pull out my hand.
I'll do it.
I stand up like this.
Not yet.
I like it.
I do it twice.
After that, I lie down.
I lie down.
After that, I bring a tarai.
Why?
That's good.
It's dark.
After that, it's over, right?
I'll send it as it is.
I'll send it.
But it's always there.
It's always there.
It's amazing that it's left until the end.
Are you licking all over the place?
I don't lick that much.
If you don't like it that much, lick it to some extent.
I don't like it.
If you don't like it, go out.
You licked it, too.
I thought I'd go to the convenience store.
I thought it was me.
I went home and looked in the mirror.
It's here.
I laughed.
You have to check it.
You have to be careful.
A woman's lipstick.
That's not good.
That's really not good.
There's lipstick everywhere.
There's no choice.
It's around here.
It's here on the T-shirt.
That's right.
It's here.
This is...
If you put it there, it's all over the place.
I do it like this.
It feels good on this side, too.
The T-shirt is all over the place.
I don't have enough training.
If you press the place near the wrist of the palm, what comes out?
What is it?
It's coming out.
Isn't it meat?
It's round.
It's coming out.
I have two.
What is this?
I used to say the number of children I could have.
Really?
I used to say that.
I have two.
You have two?
Yes.
I see.
What is this?
Let me press it more.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
I don't like it.
Really?
I'm sorry.
It hurts twice as much as before.
It hurts.
What is this?
This is probably...
What is it?
It's like an abnormal food.
In the end.
When I really can't stand it anymore, I think I'm going to eat this.
I have two.
The right one tastes like soy sauce.
The left one tastes like miso.
The one with three tastes like curry.
Well, what should I do?
What should I do?
Chashu.
What is this?
I don't know yet.
This guy.
Chashu.
What should I do?
I often see flies and bugs on the train and bus, but can they go home?
I don't know.
I don't worry about my parents and siblings.
I don't think they can go home, but they are on the train to go home.
Really?
They don't take the train to go home.
They take the train to go home.
They can't take the train to go home?
They can't take the train to go home.
Why?
They have a lot of power.
They can fly.
They are tired to go home.
They stay somewhere.
Yes.
There are flies in the studio, right?
There are.
Those flies are amazing.
Why?
There are a lot of them.
Are you visiting the studio?
Visiting the studio.
There are a lot of them.
Well, let's go home.
It's hot.
It's just a punishment game.
You said you were going to Thailand.
Thailand.
Thai kickboxing.
They go into the ring.
One of them is going up.
I don't know.
E!
What?
It's a new joke.
E!
It's a lie.
There is E.
There is a big E.
They sit on it.
They drink tea.
It's hard to find it.
It's a lie.
Is it?
They want to find an imaginary animal.
It's impossible.
There are animals that haven't been found yet.
They don't think they are animals.
They don't know they are animals.
There are animals.
I wonder.
There are definitely animals.
For example, if you say a tiger, everyone thinks it's a tiger, right?
I wonder if that island is also an animal.
They live in the same place as the tiger.
It's an island that's trying to be protected by the tiger.
I don't know if that's still an animal.
That's why the tiger doesn't look at humans.
Please stop the movie.
I'm sorry about that island.