In the first episode, we're going to measure Mr. Matsumoto as a sudden entertainer!
Mr. Matsumoto!
Yes, yes.
Finally, the day has come.
Well, no one has done it on TV before.
No one has done it before.
We're going to measure various entertainers today.
Mr. Matsumoto, it's your first time, isn't it?
Well, even if you call me an entertainer, I've gathered a lot of big people today.
Well, I've heard a lot of things like how many entertainers you've cut down.
That's right.
I don't know if that's really worth it.
Yes.
We're going to show it on TV for the first time.
Are you going to show it?
Yes, we're going to show it.
Oh, are you going to quit?
No, we're going to show it.
Oh, I see.
Mr. Matsumoto, please come over here.
Yes, yes.
Please come over here.
This program is brought to you by the sponsor you are watching.
Does anyone know?
Well, my machine has been studied.
Who is it?
Professor, Sumi is here.
Let him sit down.
Sumi, sit down.
Professor, is this the machine?
This is the machine.
Now, let's take a look.
Please sit down here.
Let's go.
Professor, I have a question for you.
Answer it with yes or no.
Yes.
Baseball is a pitcher, but at night it's a batter.
Okay.
Throwing is left-handed, but at that time it's right-handed.
No.
That's left-handed.
At that time, it's left-handed.
Okay.
It's out.
Yes.
Professor, what does this mean?
What is it?
This is my meal today.
Whose meal is that?
This is what it means.
Sumi's meal is thick.
Yes.
It's thick.
Don't complain if it's this much.
What is it?
Is it this thick?
Professor, this is impossible.
This is what it means.
This is what I expected.
It's a little thicker.
Thicker?
This side.
This side?
This side is a little thin.
I see.
But it's amazing.
Sumi's meal is this thick.
This is amazing.
You must have said that a lot.
You must have done a lot of things when you were an actor.
Is there a sports player like this?
This is a little out.
It's out.
A yellow thing is out.
Hamada-kun.
Yes.
Next patient.
Here he is.
Professor.
Dr. Taka.
Come here.
What are you doing?
I'm not laughing.
Please sit down.
Sometimes I step on my own balls.
Is it that dangerous?
Sometimes it's dangerous.
It's a little out.
Answer with yes or no.
No.
It's no.
I often get beaten down by women.
You have to answer honestly.
Next patient.
Yes.
I'm the type to blow first.
I see.
If you sleep with me, you'll be in trouble.
The data is out.
Let's go.
Taka's meal is this.
What is this?
It's small.
Is it a snack?
It's not reliable.
And it's sticky.
Is it this?
I'm not satisfied with this.
It's rude on TV.
Don't you have a measure?
I don't have a measure.
I really want to compare.
This is normal.
This is normal?
I see.
I don't know the rest.
Do you want to measure it?
It looks like this.
And it's getting shorter.
Do you want to do it?
Don't call me.
I'm being called.
Hey.
Get up.
I don't want to work.
I'll give you back your word.
Don't film me.
I'm working with you.
It's the same.
Come here.
What?
You have to have a word.
Why am I here?
I'm an electrical engineer.
Don't talk.
Sit down.
Wait.
Look at it for the future.
I'll measure it.
Why do you have to measure it?
Sit down.
This is a new show.
It's not a new show.
First question.
Have you ever floated while standing?
Yes.
You're lying.
You'll float tomorrow.
I've been in the air before.
I see.
What is this?
This is a yes or no.
It's an input.
Where are these connected?
Here.
It's noisy.
Next question.
My wife has become a big fan lately.
Yes.
Really?
It's not a big deal.
When I was a kid, I hid in my house.
Why?
Yes.
Stop it.
It's a yes or no.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
There's a hole in the meter.
It's from the east.
What is this?
It's a big one.
Nice.
It's disgusting.
It's a windbreaker.
You're throwing it out.
What the hell are you talking about?
I'm talking about the white one
Are you stupid?
What the hell is this?
Is this me?
Hey, it's not that big
I said it floated when I touched it
It floated, but it's not that big
It's not that big
I know it's different from this
I'm busy now
I'm sorry
Let's do this like this
Can we do this like this?
Like this
Excuse me, what is this?
What the hell is this?
Ladies and gentlemen
We have to get out of this hall by 10 o'clock
What time is it?
It's set until 10 o'clock
So it's 10 o'clock including departure?
I don't know
We have to go home
I'm sorry
The light of the firefly is flowing
I have a manager
His name is Tsukimura
He's a little crazy
He can speak English
Tsukimura is really crazy
He's really crazy
Sometimes he gets angry by himself
He says to himself
Why didn't I get angry?
I'm still immature
He can speak English
He says it in English
Cool
It's so scary
I had a meeting the other day
When I went to the restaurant, the car had stopped, so I couldn't stop the car.
There was a couple trying to get out, so I told them to hurry up.
Then the man of the couple came down and said,
What do you mean?
It's natural for you to do that.
He kept complaining.
Is Tsukimura weak when he complains?
I'm sorry.
Did you apologize?
After that, Okamoto came.
He's the chief, so he kept complaining.
The man of the couple didn't try to get out.
I got on the car and said,
Okamoto has to do something about this situation.
What do you think?
Okamoto is in pain, too.
I was watching it like this.
What kind of ending will this story have?
Okamoto suddenly got angry.
He wanted to hit the man.
Tsukimura is a fool.
I'm sorry.
The man of the couple said,
That's enough.
Okamoto is good.
On the contrary, if you hit your man,
Can't you tell him to stop?
I don't know if it's all his calculation.
You did that crying bag.
I said, that's enough.
I cried like that.
The cause is Tsukimura.
Yesterday, CX and I finished the studio.
I was walking around the hallway.
I was jumping on both sides.
Tsukimura said, GAN!
I said, GAN!
I was walking normally.
I didn't hit the panel.
I was like this.
Tsukimura said, GAN!
I didn't know what was going on.
Okamoto was waiting in front of me.
I said, Okamoto.
They're crazy.
Let's go home.
Why did you listen to Tsukimura?
It's not Tsukimura.
I don't care what kind of guy Tsukimura is.
What?
What are you?
I'm downtown.
What about you?
I've never seen you.
I see you sometimes.
I'm on TV a lot.
You're on TV?
Yes.
You're dressed well.
I can't beat your necktie.
It's a bit wild.
It's loose.
I don't want to be wild.
It's natural.
Wow.
Really?
Yes.
I don't like tight pants.
I used to like them.
But I don't like them anymore.
This is fashion.
Are you wearing them?
Of course.
It's fashionable.
I see.
I'll go like this.
What?
Are you going to do it?
I told you.
Let's go to the post office.
Matsumoto, you often say that Hamada's armpit stinks.
Why?
I don't say that often.
Tell me what it smells like.
I think it's Hamada's armpit.
I don't have an armpit.
It's not that bad.
There's nothing wrong with an armpit.
Close your eyes.
Think of the most smelly thing you can think of.
Did you think of it?
I think it's 45 times more than that.
I thought so.
I thought it would be twice as bad.
This is Hamada's armpit.
Nice to meet you.
No, it's not that.
He said it's my armpit.
He often says that it stinks.
He just says it.
Have you ever said that my armpit stinks?
Yes, I have.
I don't know.
I'm disappointed.
I was told that by my partner.
I always say that my armpit stinks.
Say it properly.
Wait a minute.
If you raise your armpit, it will roll down.
It's boring.
Overaction.
Don't say that.
I just said it.
Don't go that far.
Don't do that.
You are a real asshole.
Have you ever said that my armpit stinks?
Don't say that.
This is also a part that hurts my armpit.
Where does this smell?
It stinks.
Please tell me how to do it without hurting it.
I see.
You don't have to say that.
What do you do if you don't want to get hurt?
There is a sound wave that humans can't hear.
It's above the sound wave.
There are people who laugh at the sound wave.
At this time, the sound wave is coming.
If you are nearby, the sound wave is coming.
Lower the sound a little.
Do you understand?
I will tell you whether you can hear it or not.
For example, we are talking.
What did you eat last night?
You have to talk to me.
I'm telling you to talk.
What did you eat last night?
I ate curry.
You like curry.
Do you go to Egypt?
That will hurt you.
I said it clearly.
I heard it clearly.
It's a little unpleasant.
Do you often watch dramas?
It's fun.
I can't hear it.
You can't hear it.
Do you often go shopping?
I go sometimes.
Are you okay?
You will be told.
If you hear it, you will be beaten.
How can I go to the second round after the first round?
I don't know.
After the first round, I take a break.
What should I do when I challenge again?
What are you doing?
Do you smoke?
I smoke.
It was very intense.
You sweat a lot.
Of course I smoke.
I'm a smoker.
What?
That's enough.
What are you doing?
I smoke.
What are you doing with that ugly woman?
That ugly woman is sleeping next to me.
You are ugly.
Wait a minute.
I'm just sleeping.
I'm sleeping.
What are you going to do?
I'm sleeping next to you.
I smoke.
Are you naked?
Is there anyone who wears clothes cleanly after the first round?
You can wear clothes cleanly, but you have to wear underwear.
I don't care if I'm naked.
You are cool.
I'm a little excited.
You are like a poppy.
What is a poppy?
It's a compliment.
I'm glad.
Thank you for the title.
I have a good example.
I put a cigarette in front of me.
I can smoke.
That's not true.
You know that, so you don't smoke.
In a different sense, the two of you are burning.
That's not true.
You really don't know.
I'm sorry.
You smoke.
I'm glad.
I'm scared.
You have to take care of yourself.
Why are you so arrogant?
He likes me.
I'm your ugly woman now.
I'm lucky.
11.53
11.53?
Let's do it again.
When does a woman laugh?
For example, young people in their teens and 20s.
When they are in their 60s, they laugh like a drifter.
They are in their 40s.
Where do they laugh?
Say 40.
When they are in their 40s, they laugh.
When they are in their 30s, they laugh in their 40s.
You can find out.
For example, 30.
31.
32.
What's the difference?
It's changing.
33.
What about 32?
32.
33.
It's the same.
34.
This is the point.
It's the same.
It's long.
35.
Listen to me.
Let's do it.
It's the same.
36.
Listen to me.
I can't stop laughing.
This is the point.
I can't help it.
It's like a boomerang.
37.
Listen to me.
38.
I can't stop laughing.
What are you doing?
It's the same.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.