Next time, at Gaki no Tsukai,
Live Broadcast!
Chikishiki!
Bonjiman Contest!
Good evening!
This time,
We've invited various Bon people
to decide the number one Bon.
Let's introduce the judges.
First, Yoshida Hiro!
Mayu Keppon!
Good evening!
Oh, it's already over?
Boo!
Interesting!
The best!
Here you go!
Next, Yuko Inoue!
Good evening!
Thank you for coming!
You and I are here today because we're annoyed.
No, that's not it!
Why are you so annoyed?
No, it's not that.
I was looking forward to today.
This program has a good number of viewers.
That's why!
I didn't know there was someone like you.
No, it's not that.
It's just that Hana-san said it herself.
I often watch it.
Oh, is that so?
Yes!
Can't you do it with a leotard?
What about the leotard?
What?
Is it a leotard?
It's like this.
If you put one shot under it, it's okay.
No, that's not good at all.
I haven't been out since I got my hair done.
The last person is this person!
Mouth burn!
Do you want me to bite you?
Can't you do it now?
It's not good at all.
Let's have the person in front come out.
Yes, please.
What's with your teeth?
It's like a piano.
In between.
How much bone is it?
Let's try it.
Yes, a little behind.
How much?
First of all, how much bone is the lip?
Yes.
Look, if it's this much bone, it's that, right?
Please try it, Mr. Hamada.
It's dirty.
I'll make it smaller.
What are you doing?
Yes, thank you very much.
Next person.
Yes, please.
Ha! Bone!
It was shaking, wasn't it?
I'm a little nervous.
It's Ha! Bone.
I'm going to call the director.
I'm the director, Saito.
This is our chief.
Yes.
The chief is like this.
This is Ha! Bone.
It's this big.
If it was normal, it would have been three meters tall.
Isn't it amazing?
It's Ha! Bone.
The corn is already fast.
Is that so?
Please.
I'm going to eat it.
You're eating it with your tongue.
Let's make Saito do it.
Yes.
Start.
Yours is faster.
What are you going to do if you win?
Thank you very much.
Yes, let's go.
Next person, please.
Eyebrows Bippon.
Please say your eyebrows are Bippon.
Please wait a moment.
The eyebrows are Bohn.
Look at these eyebrows.
Why are you wearing a ribbon?
Wow!
What?
Can I take this off?
Sure.
Wow!
It's really long.
Wow! What is this?
Don't say it with this.
It's amazing.
Kiyoshi is also surprised, right?
Should I do it like this?
I know, I know.
Is it hard to understand?
What are you doing?
Don't hit me.
You're an amateur.
You're hitting me with a scissor.
Thank you very much.
The last person, please.
Meat Bohn.
The last person is Meat Bohn.
This woman is a pure regular.
If you look at this, I think you are more beautiful than me.
What?
But I have a taste.
It's not that you don't like it.
If you look at the side, it doesn't smell.
Why?
Please prepare it.
What should I start with?
First of all,
everyone, please look at Meat Bohn.
Switch on.
Look.
Like waves.
It's a fish.
Are you good at fishing?
Actually, Nagatomi is very good at it.
Despite this body shape,
she is very good at it.
She is good at it.
She is so light.
It's like an SFX.
Shall we start?
Let's start.
Bohn.
I have changed my way of thinking.
What is it?
I don't work too much.
Is that so?
It's not like that.
How about this tax?
That's enough.
You are really persistent.
I will say it.
Why did you say it twice?
The current situation in Japan is very strange.
Shut up.
I can't sit next to you.
Let me tell you something.
Every month,
I get 10% of my salary from the company.
That's enough.
It's the current situation.
It's not enough.
Give me some more.
The country is in a bad situation.
It's not like 5,000 yen or 6,000 yen.
It's enough.
Do you know how much I have to pay next month?
30 million yen.
I have to pay 30 million yen in taxes.
30 million yen?
Have you ever seen 30 million yen?
I will tell you a detailed story.
I have an office in downtown.
I have to pay taxes in June.
I have to pay taxes in my office.
50 million yen is not enough.
You and I have to pay 50 million yen.
Why 50 million yen?
You are a fool.
You and I have different positions.
Think about it.
I am the president of your office.
You are a fool.
You have a family that you don't understand.
I don't have anything.
I am a vegetarian.
You are a fool.
I don't listen to you.
I feel sorry for you.
I don't want to talk about it.
If I go to the public toilet, there will be no paper.
I don't care.
I can't buy a toilet paper.
You are doing a good thing.
You are a fool.
I will be a bad person.
I have a lot of bad things.
Remember it.
I will be a bad person again.
Are you a bad person now?
Yes.
You are a fool.
I have a lot of bad things.
I want you to use the tax well.
You can't use it for good things.
I have a lot of money.
I have a lot of bad things.
I want you to use the tax well.
You are a fool.
I have a lot of bad things.
I want you to use the tax well.
You are a fool.
I have never used the tax well.
Did you ride a swing recently?
Do you use the public toilet?
I rarely use the public toilet.
You don't use it.
You don't want to use it.
I have a lot of bad things.
Do you use the public toilet?
You look like a prima donna.
The one who stands up with their feet.
Oh my.
You are right.
You are wrong.
You want to escape?
Where do you want to escape?
We'll hold hands with each other.
Don't you want to run away to the end of the sunset?
Where is it?
If I can run away, I want to run away.
That kind of thing...
I'll get rid of it, you know.
Well, yes.
The good thing is, after all, the bad thing.
That's why...
I'm talking like this, right?
I don't know if it's a comedy or something,
but I'm going to say it's a bad thing.
And this talk is...
It's in place of the sutra.
A young person like that talks about a stupid thing.
If it were me, I would have bought all the products.
In the morning.
Now I don't even need a stylist.
I'm going to go anywhere with you.
In the morning.
Oh, it's late.
What's that?
It's so cute.
I heard you came to play.
I'm not lying.
I came to the opening.
Well, but...
Thank you for staying.
No, no, no.
It's nothing.
I came out in a swimsuit today.
That's right.
I didn't bring it today.
What?
Why did you come out in English underwear?
Because the underwear is not cool.
No, it's big.
What kind of underwear are you wearing?
You're wearing underwear that's up to your nipples.
It's very normal, but the cut is not so strong.
Is that so?
Yes.
What about the one with the string?
The string is...
Too much?
It's hard to wear.
Oh.
It's hard.
That's right.
If you untie the string while it's growing, it's hard to tie it.
If you tie it and wear it, the string becomes loose.
Is that so?
Why are you...
Are you really wearing it right now?
Is that so?
Thank you very much.
There is something I always find strange.
There is a golf club that old people often talk about.
Why is that limited to golf?
I think it's a pro-wrestling club where naked people sweat.
I think it's okay to have a bungee jumping club.
What do you think?
No, no, no.
But why is it only golf?
Well, generally, golf is...
I don't know about that, but while playing golf...
What?
Do you say something?
While doing something, you get caught up in it.
I walk until I go to the next stop.
At that time...
Hey, Mr. Nantoka.
Please take care of me.
Don't you walk around saying that?
It's no good not to take care of you.
What kind of conversation do you have while bungee jumping?
Why?
Didn't you hear what the other person said?
He was screaming.
That's no good.
It's not a conversation.
Covering.
Covering is hard.
That's why.
It's a real conversation.
So it's no good not to take care of you.
Is that so?
Yes.
So it's no good not to hurt the other person.
It's no good.
But it's no good not to take care of you.
I wonder if you can play golf.
Even if you miss a shot like the other day,
you say, nice shot!
And maybe the guy in the lower part
will come slowly,
so he'll go ahead,
kick the ball,
and do it in front of you.
He'll say, I'm jumping this far!
I wonder if that's the case.
I don't like that kind of world.
I really don't like it.
The other day, in the newspaper,
there was an article saying,
when I do this and that,
it's like a giant has won.
What?
When?
I...
I always...
I go out of the house.
I say something and go out.
So when I do this and that,
I don't say that.
You did!
You said it twice!
I didn't say a word.
No, you said it twice!
I didn't say it.
You did!
You said it twice!
I didn't say a word.
No, you said it twice!
What?
What was that?
So,
even if it rains,
he said,
tomorrow,
even if it rains,
I'll definitely go out.
Even if the giant wins,
I'll go out!
That's what he said.
Even if the giant wins,
I'll go out.
That's what he said.
Even if the giant wins,
I'll go out.
Ma-san said,
even if the giant wins,
he'll go out,
so he went out to buy bread, didn't he?
But he said,
even if the giant wins,
I'll go out.
That's not true!
Why?
Even if the giant wins,
I'll go out.
So, he said, even if the giant wins,
Even if the giant wins,
I'll go out.
That's not true!
He said that!
Why do you always say that
when I'm thinking?
You should say it more often.
You should say that.
I've never seen you like this.
Don't lie!
I'm thinking about it,
but it's too late.
Even if the giant wins,
I'll go out.
So, even if the giant wins,
I said, even if the giant wins,
I'll go out.
You idiot!
What are you talking about?
There's no twist or lie!
Why don't you twist it?
Then, say it straight from the beginning!
I'm kidding.
I'll say it properly from now on.
I'm not going to twist it.
I'll just talk.
Please!
This giant is not a baseball giant.
What?
It's a giant...
What do you call it?
This is about my father, right?
It means that the number of times my father won is different.
It's painful.
It's different, isn't it?
I got it.
I finally got it.
That was a lie, wasn't it?
This giant is not about baseball.
That's what I just heard.
The giant won.
I'll go home right away.
This is...
Is it okay?
Wait a minute.
I got it from your intonation just now.
Masao went to the toy store.
To the toy store.
That's funny.
He went to the toy store.
There's a toy store like this.
Why are you angry?
What are you angry about?
I don't know.
Is Masao like that?
It's a proper toy.
Eight thousand and five hundred yen.
He sold it for eight thousand and five hundred yen.
The giant.
It's cheap.
It's expensive.
Masao said.
What are you talking about?
Was Masao in elementary school?
To my mother.
What are you talking about to your mother?
I'm so excited.
It's a grammar mess.
He went out.
Masao in elementary school.
Father.
I thought Masao was me.
He's calm.
He's calm even though he's my son.
Let's buy it for him.
Come on.
Go to the toy store.
Masao.
Go home.
He said.
That giant.
That's right.
I understand now.
What if you suddenly become a bird?
For example, if Machan becomes a bird.
How do you make Hamachan understand that you are Machan?
Even if Hamachan understands it.
I'm confident that I can do it with a bird and Hama-chan.
How about this?
What if you become a bird?
Even if you become a bird.
But you know me somehow.
I don't know.
I know you.
What's the name of this hall?
This is Minami Otsuka Hall.
Minami Otsuka Hall.
5 o'clock.
If it's 5 o'clock, I'll be there.
It's close.
What?
I'm telling you.
We don't know that.
You might be telling me.
I'm talking to Sugachan at 5 o'clock.
What?
I don't know if you're talking or not.
If you say that, I can understand it.
So I'll be there.
I can understand it in that state.
No one knows that you're a bird.
It's 5 o'clock.
It's already 4 o'clock.
But I can't see you.
I'm sleeping.
I can't go out.
No one will come out.
Really?
Then, what's going on outside?
When I thought about it,
There's a Zabuton over there.
You're turning around.
I'm turning around.
Piyo?
I'm saying Piyo.
This is what a bird is like.
Really?
That's right.
It's sitting on a Zabuton.
At that time,
Don't you think this is not Matsumoto?
At that point?
Yes.
I don't think so at that point.
Well, at that point,
After all, I can't see Matsumoto.
You can't see it.
But the audience is already here.
Yes.
I can't help it.
I'm sorry, but can I be alone today?
Ladies and gentlemen.
Come on.
It's coming out.
I'm here.
I'm here, too.
I can't see it.
I can't see it again.