On the day of the showdown
Thank you
We broke up
What?
You broke up?
Last week we were in a non-air
I'm sorry
I broke up with that woman
I asked her to appear on TV
Ah
She dumped you?
That new girl
Who is it?
Isn't it a different room?
Old lady?
What's that sound?
A dog
What is it?
I'm getting drunk
Iyama-chan, you said you wanted to do mosaic
I said I wanted to do mosaic
I got a call from my parents
Ah, really
I don't want to do this alone
Today I'm doing Hamada
You have a family
You have a child
But I wanted to be in the seat
That may be true
But we did the opening
I'll go home
Let's go
Ladies and gentlemen
I'll do my best
You can do it too
If you do your best, you'll get something
What will I get?
If you do your best, Hama-chan will be called cute or cool
What are you talking about?
Why are you so twisted?
I'm not being told that
If you do your best, you'll be told that
You'll be told a lot
I'm not telling anyone
If I do my best, I'll do my best
The more I do my best, the more I'll do my best
He's crazy
We've been doing it together
Together
You're getting prettier and prettier
Really
I'm the dirty one
You can be the dirty one
Is that what you wanted?
But
I'm the dirty one
I don't know what you're thinking
You're being cheeky
You're being called small
That's the worst
I don't care about the last one
Junon's kind man, number 9
What?
What is this?
Let's shake hands
You're being cheeky
Let's take a picture together
You're tired, right?
In the drama, everyday
It doesn't matter
It doesn't matter in the drama
I'm going to work
If you're on air, you'll be cool
You're being cheeky
I don't know why I'm like this
You think that's better?
I don't think so
I want to be told that I'm kind
If a woman wants a kind man
It's really dirty
Even if you do something bad, you won't get hit or scolded
Is that what you're thinking?
Definitely
If it's about me, I'll get hit
You're acting wild again
What should I do then?
Are you tired?
No, I'm fine
That's good
Are you tired?
Yes
If you look at me like this, I'll look away
That's because it's you
Wait
The audience is here to see you
I don't know what you're talking about, but I'm pissed off
I don't think we're meant to be
You're talking too much
I have a bad reputation
Who?
Us
Really?
If there's something I don't like, I'll hit the staff
They think I have a stick
What kind of stick is that?
I'm walking around with a stick
I'm in downtown
I'm in downtown with two people
What do you think?
If there's something I don't like, I'll hit the staff
That's the rumor
No one would believe that
If you want to change things, you have to be in downtown
That's why you have to be in...
Magical Brain Power
Why?
If you say something, it's something
Why do I have to be in it?
I don't want to be in it with you
That's really rude
It's really rude
I'm watching
I can't believe it
It's fun
I want to see it
You want to see it?
But you don't want to be in it
I don't want to be in it
I'm sorry
What kind of atmosphere is that?
I know you very well
I know you
So even if there's a wall, I can do a gesture
I don't know that
Don't do that
I want to see it
I know you very well
I know you
I don't know if I can do that
It's a dirty image
That's right
I can't believe someone who does this has a stick
In order to change that image, you should appear
Radical snow power
My face is so red
I don't know why it's so red
It's okay, just do it while it's red
Then you can get rid of it
That's scary
Is it okay?
Yes
Don't laugh
Why is Matsumoto-san so well-bred and elegant?
Do you know?
No
Do you know why?
Even if the two of you are doing this, it will show
The house design
I hate that
I don't like it so I jumped out
You jumped out of the house where tatami came out
No, no
Not that
I jumped out of the original house
It has nothing to do with the old house
It has nothing to do with that
It happened after I jumped out
What happened?
I'm not like you
I'm the younger sister of my mother
Then I'm your aunt
Aunt
Where are your parents then?
I'm the teacher of Ikebana
In your head, the good kid is Ikebana
Not in my head, I'm talking about the real past
I'm not making it
I'm sorry
I'm Ikebana sensei
My father is the director
Director?
It was tough
What was tough?
The discipline?
The discipline was really tough
Is that so?
Yes
Did you have a hard time?
What?
I couldn't do this
I was at home
I thought I was free
If I did this, my mother would say
I didn't do anything
My mother is not a high school student
My father is a director
Don't say director
I don't understand
I heard you
I heard you touched it
So you don't have to say it correctly
My father
Matsumoto-san has a mirror that only reflects beautiful things
What does it reflect?
Does it have a mirror?
It does
Of course it doesn't reflect what it sees
I'll say this clearly
It doesn't reflect
That means I'm not beautiful
If it reflects in the mirror
I thought I should break this mirror
I put it in my bedroom
One time I had sex with my girlfriend
You're saying it clearly
At that time it was reflected
Our sex
When I saw it
How big is it?
That's good
The three of you are the markers
Good sound
Matsumoto-san, I have a question
From the surprise box, did something surprising come out?
Stop it
From Matsumoto-san's body
You should read the paper that spreads
It's a paper button
Listen
Something surprising came out
Isn't this person blue?
From Matsumoto-san's body
What kind of surprising thing came out?
Isn't that a report?
Yesterday there was a guest
Everyone said it
The person in the middle of the guest
That person is Kaona
You really shouldn't think about it
That person wanted to watch the show
So he wrote a postcard
Hopeful hope
I don't think it's one or two
He wrote three or four
He finally got it
He thought he could finally meet downtown
He was looking at it
He was surprised
How did you feel when you went home?
Today was fun, Mayumi-chan
Right?
Why are you so depressed?
That's what happens
You can't tell your mother
That you got sick
You can't tell your mother that you got sick
Your mother will worry
Why?
To be honest, I've never been sick
Seriously
Really?
Yes
That's why I...
Sometimes I make a sound from my butt
You're sick
Sick
I act like I'm sick
You're annoying
You're sick
There's a saying
You think you're sick
So people think you're sick too
You're sick, but I'm not
It might be the same sound
It might be similar sound
You're sick, but I'm not
In my case, my butt and butt rubbed against each other
You're sick
You can't act like that
What was that?
It sounded like a bell
It wasn't a bell
It's different
I don't know
Your butt is moving like this
It's sick
Yours is sick, but mine isn't
I'm surprised
Did you remember?
Really
It's sick
It's not sick
It's not
That's why
It's rubbing against each other
It's different
In the middle of autumn
I'm crying
That's funny
Is it true that Hama-chan's butt doesn't move at all?
Your butt is amazing
How is it amazing?
It's smelly
Everyone is smelly
But in your case, it's not that smelly
As you all know, I rub my butt
I think everyone will rub their butt when you're pooping
But your butt
You don't rub it
You don't have a place to deliver it
No one will take it away
It's a little smelly
Where will you take it?
I think
You'll be depressed
You have to roll it
If you think like that
Where is it?
Mama, I had a hard time today
Roll it
I want to drink a lot
Like a snack
I don't want to do it anymore
What's wrong? Did something bad happen?
What are you doing?
If you want to roll it, roll it
I'll give you a card
I don't want to do it anymore
I'll do my best
Thank you for your hard work
Let's go
We have to talk
Are you going alone?
Alone?
You have to order
Let's go
Why don't you drink it?
I don't know
There it is
It's walking
Look at that
It's walking like a blue sea
I don't know who to tell
Look at this
It's shaking
It's not thinking about anything
Look
What is it?
It's moving
Do you want to do it?
The best soap land
Suyahime
Soap?
Do you want to go to the soap?
I don't want to go to the soap
I'll be at the venue
So you want to go to the soap?
It's running
You're a fool
That's not true
Let's stop
I won't bite
Let's get off
It's a soap
It won't come out for 90 minutes
It won't come out
Let's stop
I won't bite
It's refreshing
Everyone should watch this
It's really good
It's good
It's coming
Let's go home
It's refreshing
What is it?
It's good
Let's go
It's a good soap land
It's a really good soap land
Let's go home
termuo
It's coming
It's clean
I also want to see Mamma
Mamma is doing
You'll meet her
I will meet her
It's like a movie.
It's like an orange juice.
I'm gonna get on the car.
Come here.
There he is.
Where is he?
What's that?
Is that a sara-kin?
It's a sara-kin.
Why is it a sara-kin?
It's money.
It's a good car.
It's full of soap.
Why is it full of soap?
It's running out of money.
What are you doing?
It's full of soap.
You're going to the orange juice.
What was that orange juice?
You wanted to have a little break.
I'm thirsty.
It's refreshing.
I'm already out of the car.
I don't know what to do.
You got caught again.
Why did you do that?
You should have borrowed it.
I was going to finish it on the second try.
It's a little boring.
I don't know what to do.
What are you thinking about?
I'm going to give up.
That's right.
You got caught again.
Why did you do that?
It's not because you're very happy.
I can't do this anymore.
I think you should say it.
I can't do it with this.
I don't think it's so good.
I can't do it.
I don't think so.
I think you should say it.
You shouldn't use your tail.
Or you'll have to make an excuse later.
But what should I do with this?
Don't make an excuse. Just hold the scene.
Because this is really good.
Refreshing.
This is good.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
You shouldn't say that.
Let's go.
Hey!
What is this?
Excuse me.
Who are you?
Hamada?
Excuse me.
This is not right.
What are you doing?
Excuse me.
Where have you been?
What?
I was wrong.
You didn't change your mind?
I shouldn't have done that.
That's strange.
What's wrong with you?
You were a kid.
I told you to stop.
Why?
Who are you?
Where have you been?
I was wrong.
You didn't change your mind?
What?
I was wrong.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.