Last week, you must have seen the heartwarming events of the two of them.
The one who stood out was the quiet hot spring town of Yamanashi, Isawa.
In this town filled with smoke and rain, Ikko had a big party to relieve his daily fatigue.
However, the performance that was done mainly by the staff was not good enough.
A-chan is close!
It's a little funny!
And the staff's comedy was just a slip of the tongue.
You're such a wimp!
I'll give you a heart attack!
In particular, the stage of the comedy show was too cold.
I knew it!
Um...
No, that's...
We've been hungry for a while now!
What are you doing?
The party ended at 6 a.m. four hours later.
Matsumoto, who is a good friend, finally carried out the plan after a long time.
In the morning, it was just the two of them's birthday.
The plan is to sneak into Hama-chan's room while she's asleep and throw a birthday party just for the two of them.
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday dear Hama-chan!
Happy birthday!
What are you doing?
Happy birthday! You're 24 years old!
I'm so glad!
Happy birthday!
I thought it was a lonely birthday.
You like yakisoba, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Look!
What are you doing?
I'm going to make a lot of sauce.
Where's Matsumoto?
I'll see you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
Oh, it's good.
What are you doing?
I don't know how to make it.
But in the midst of this heartwarming birthday, there was a guy.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
What are you doing?
I'm angry.
Are you angry?
Why are you angry?
The staff and Matsumoto are still awake at this time of the day.
We're all awake and working.
But our senior, Yamazaki Hosei, has been sleeping all the time since about 2 o'clock.
I don't know what to do.
Let's do our best.
I'll be in the upper room.
Are you awake?
I'm awake.
Slowly.
Turn on the lights.
Slowly, slowly.
I'm awake.
I fell asleep.
It's cute.
It's complete.
It's a magic.
There's a magic here, too.
Yes.
More.
One more time.
I'm scared.
Good morning.
What's wrong?
Everyone's working.
Only Hosei.
It's hot.
What's wrong?
What do you want to do?
I don't know.
It's hot.
It's hot?
I don't know.
Your thighs are hot?
What do you want to do?
I'm sorry.
Where are you going?
It's hot.
But there was someone else sleeping in Yamazaki.
Everyone's been working since morning.
There's no one sleeping.
That person is...
Who is it?
Kenji.
Kenji?
Your face is amazing.
That's what I think the most.
I'm going to put my butt on.
It's dazzling.
Smell it.
Do your best.
This is Nakamura-san.
I sang that song at the White Sea.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
You guys slept too much.
Everyone's been working since morning.
In addition, the sub-sub-human writer Suzuki's sleepiness was attacked.
He's awake.
It's funny.
Let's finish.
What are you doing?
Let's stop.
It's fashionable.
Let's eat.
It's dangerous.
I'm sorry.
Suzuki is dangerous.
After the commercial, the Isawa hot spring project is still exciting.
To apologize for sleeping last night, a delicious project from the producer.
Let's eat the famous hot spring.
Hot spring.
What is that?
It's a famous hot spring in Yamanashi.
What kind of famous hot spring?
Is there a reason?
The reason is...
It's the most delicious hot spring in Yamanashi.
It's a famous hot spring in Hoto.
What kind of hot spring?
It's like udon.
Let's go.
It's fun.
Thank you.
Let's go.
There are a lot of people.
Chikichiki Suga presents Hot Spring in Hoto at the first Gaki no Tsugaya.
The five members of Downtown, Yamazaki, and Kokoriko will challenge the famous hot spring in Yamanashi.
The time limit is one hour.
If you succeed, you will receive a prize of 1 million yen.
This is a present.
Okay.
I understand.
But it's 100 times.
It's like eating 20 times out of 10.
That's right.
I don't feel like giving a present.
I understand your feelings.
I understand your feelings, too.
I got angry because I got angry.
Machan challenges.
I don't feel satisfied.
Wait.
Let's go.
1 million yen.
Good luck.
I don't know if I can eat it all.
You have to eat a lot.
Taste it.
You have to hurry.
It's delicious.
It looks delicious.
One minute has passed.
You have to eat a lot in 30 seconds.
That's right.
You can eat a lot in 30 seconds.
I will eat from now on.
I was waiting for you to have a birthday party alone in the morning.
I was very happy.
We are good friends.
Okay.
I ate a lot.
I ate 100 times.
It's delicious.
Okay.
The fourth cup is over.
The fifth cup is over.
I will eat 15 more cups.
You have to eat 15 more cups.
Did you hear that?
I heard it.
I can't eat it.
You are fast.
Answer it.
Please eat it from now on.
I can't eat it.
I will eat it from now on.
Good luck.
It's delicious.
The fifth cup is over.
I can't eat it.
Hama-san, you can eat it.
I want to eat it.
It's time.
50 minutes have passed.
The eighth cup is over.
It came out.
It's pumpkin.
The noodles are under it.
It's called a pumpkin knife.
It's a lie.
Hama-chan cleared the eighth cup and touched Yamazaki.
Yamazaki was delicious.
I will eat 70 cups.
Hey.
Your pace is bad.
It's just a full cup.
Really?
It's a lie.
In the end, Tanaka...
It's a scheme.
It's a lie.
Don't do that.
I'm in a bad mood.
It's a lie.
It's a waste of time.
You are very naive.
The remaining time is 30 minutes.
It's a pretty bad situation.
It's a bad situation.
Excuse me.
I have a suggestion.
The program will not be fun.
Yamazaki is not funny at all.
That's right.
He is not funny at all.
This is the second time.
I will change the rule.
I said 100 cups.
I said 40 cups.
Can ENDO turn the tables?
ENDO, that's right.
I can't taste it.
That's right.
ENDO is amazing.
I'm counting on you.
You are cool.
15 minutes left.
He is very good at drinking.
He looks like he is drinking.
30 cups.
This is the last 10 cups.
You can do it.
We can't do it.
We should do it.
We are young, so we can't do it.
We cannot do it.
We can't do it.
We should have 32 cups.
32 cups.
Thank you, YAMASAKI.
Hey, take it easy.
YAMASAKI, you can do it.
You have no time.
ENDO, ENDO, go.
It's all over the place.
Alright, let's go in. That's the power.
It's a bat. It's a bat.
Endo, the last spurt of anger.
If you eat two more cups, you can go one by one.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
I'm going to push myself. I'm going to push myself from now on.
One more cup. One more cup.
Four minutes left.
It's hot.
What was that?
I don't like it. I don't like it.
Mom, you said it was hot.
I didn't feel it at all.
Three minutes left.
Thanks to this, you'll get 1 million yen.
Good luck, Bokoriko.
It's really good.
You can eat a lot in 30 seconds.
Don't say that.
Who's the best?
You're still the best.
It came out.
It's a ghost.
Don't leave only the pumpkin.
What kind of ghost are you?
One minute left.
Four minutes left.
It's a miracle.
You can eat a lot in 30 seconds.
I'm hungry.
I can't eat anything.
It's the end.
The end.
I don't think I can say anything.
You're making me really angry
But he still has a chance
I'm sorry I didn't have any sense of humor
You don't have any sense of humor this time
I'm going to attack you with all my sense of humor
I'm sorry
Please get involved
You're stressed out, right?
I'm going to do my best here
I'm going to attack you
There are a lot of people here
It's old
I can't see it
The signboard is amazing
I'm going to attack you with my face
You're so stupid
Chikichiki! Suga presents
Take off your beautiful clothes and do a sexy baseball game
What's your name?
Anri
I'm going to play baseball with Anri
Suga gave me 1 million yen
1 million yen again?
Yes
The rule is that we will play baseball one by one
We are 5 members
If you win 5 people straight and take off all of them
You will get 1 million yen
I can see such a good thing
You can get 1 million yen
Let's start with Mazumoto
Really?
Please
If you lose, it's over
If you want to play baseball, you have to do it like this
We have to win
Start from the bottom
Suga, it's my turn?
I don't know if I will lose
If you lose, you have to do it like this
Amazing
Really?
If you lose, you have to do it like this
We will win for sure
Really?
It's a miracle that we won 4 times
I don't know if it was good
I'm happy too
It's complicated
Thank you
It's Tanaka
I'm always like this
A warm friendship with Machan and Hama-chan
This trip will be engraved in their hearts