We found a really good restaurant.
We told them to bring us there.
What's that? A food court?
That's what it's called.
We didn't know it would be this crowded.
It's already crowded.
I don't know what's going on.
It's not like that.
What is it?
We made a lot of reservations.
But we're finally here.
Really?
Was there a famous restaurant?
It's here.
It's here?
It's a restaurant.
There it is.
He's looking at us.
Good morning.
Is the camera off?
I don't think so.
We're finally here.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Good morning.
You're late.
This is the famous restaurant.
It must have been hard.
It was.
When I said I was coming,
a lot of people came to see us.
I'm really sorry.
What?
I'm listening.
We're here.
Who are you listening to?
We have a lot of reservations.
We got them today.
Yeah, we got them.
I wouldn't have called a regular restaurant.
We're all busy.
Except you.
Don't say that.
We're busy.
But in Tokyo,
there are a lot of celebrities.
That's right.
Of course.
You see them in magazines.
You see celebrities here.
I don't.
It's not like that.
It's not?
I was surprised.
I came here for work.
There are a lot of celebrities here.
What?
What's that?
There are a lot of celebrities here.
They don't move like that.
That's right.
While we're waiting,
maybe today...
What?
Kijime Shiro?
Wait a minute.
He's running.
Kijime Shiro?
Wait a minute.
He'll be surprised.
What?
We're telling you.
He'll be surprised.
He's not being chased.
Nobody's here.
There are a lot of celebrities here on Christmas Eve.
For the sake of it.
It's a couple.
There's a lot of celebrities.
Seriously, this place is...
What?
He's running!
Who's that?
Wait a minute!
Isn't that Suu-san?
That's Suu-san.
Who's Suu-san?
It's Suu, right?
Is this Suu Tomitoku?
He's here!
There's no doubt about it.
It's Suu Tomitoku!
Suu Tomitoku is running!
You'll be surprised!
There's no doubt about it.
There's no doubt about it?
He's running again.
If everyone's running to the other side,
there must be something there.
That's what I thought at first, too.
Hey, Mimato-san!
Mimato-san's running!
That's Mimato, right?
That's Mimato-san.
Mimato's running like crazy!
That's amazing!
But Mimato-san's house is around here.
It's called Nakano.
It might be.
It's an amazing store.
People who watch us on TV
only know that it's Nakano.
That's right.
Who's this?
He's running.
It's Marianne!
Marianne!
Marianne's running!
Why is Marianne running?
That's amazing!
There's no time to talk!
What's going on?
If he starts running,
this is...
That's why I thought
I should apologize for calling you.
No, not at all.
I wanted to show you.
I'm so happy!
By the way, who was running?
That was amazing!
From Mori no Fukuro...
Who's Mori?
Pappara Kawai.
Who's Mori no Fukuro?
I was looking for Pappara Kawai.
How many people
are there a day at this pace?
Wait!
Who's that?
I have no idea.
Isn't that Ijiri?
Really?
Ijiri Okada?
Poor guy!
I've never seen anyone running like that.
Is that really Ijiri?
It's Ijiri Okada.
Poor guy.
I've never seen anyone running like that.
So far away!
I don't think he's running.
He's just running.
That's right.
That's why I'm surprised to see him every other month.
He's just running.
That's right.
Oh?
Not yet?
Shun!
He's going shopping!
I ordered, but I didn't have the ingredients.
So I was in a hurry.
There's a reason for that.
It's said that your wish will come true while you're running.
That's right.
Kiyohiko!
I was so tired I just looked at him.
What?
Kiyohiko!
I knew it.
He's running so much.
I didn't know he was going to run.
He's running like he's going to bleed.
That's right.
It's amazing that he didn't let us do it.
He didn't let us do it.
No, no, no!
That's amazing!
What?
That's Kato Taka!
Kato Taka!
I thought he was going to run over there.
That's right.
He's running now.
It's not like he's going to fall.
That's right.
Excuse me.
What?
He's running.
Who is that?
That's Heipo.
That's Kato Taka.
Heipo.
It has nothing to do with him.
That's Kato Taka.
I saw it.
He's not counted.
That's right.
He's not a celebrity.
Not at all.
Who is this?
It's close.
It's Romi Yamada.
He ran right over here.
It's Machi Gotan.
That's amazing.
What?
Who is that?
Shinji Yamashita.
That's not correct.
Shinji Yamashita it is Shinji Yamashita
It's not Shinji Yamashita.
Shinji Yamashita.
That's Yoshinobu.
That's wrong.
It's hard to distinguish, but he's actually good.
Is that true?
That's not true at all.
Really?
It's really not.
That's enough.
142 00
I'm sorry, it took too much time.
I want to eat more.
I'm sorry.
I'm going home.
Let's go.
Who's this?
Who?
It's Taka.
He's going to the bathroom.
He's in the studio.
It's almost over.
Wait a minute.
What?
He's here.
He's running.
Who's this?
It's the host, St. Louis.
St.?
It's St. Louis.
That's amazing.
Isn't that amazing?
When did you run?
No, Tama.
It's my first time.
Is it Iji and Machiko?
No, it's not.
It was orange.
It was Ijiri.
You're surprised.
I'm not surprised at all.
St. Louis.
That's St. Louis.
There was something.
He's here.
It's Ijiri.
Where?
He's here.
This is Ijiri.
Let's take a closer look.
Is this Ijiri?
Oh, it's you.
It's Ijiri.
There's no mistake.
It was Ijiri.
He said,
I have to go now.
Right?
But...
Yes.
It was amazing.
I'm not just waiting.
I'm waiting.
I see.
That's right.
I'm not just waiting.
I'm not just waiting in the car.
That's right.
I know.
Are we done with Ijiri?
Yes.
Let's go to Ijiri.
Will there be a second car in Ijiri?
They'll take this road.
This will be their last car.
What?
He's wearing a suit!
Wait.
That's not a suit!
That's a suit!
That was a suit!
What are you doing?
You're wearing a suit?
Am I wrong?
I'm doing the Mario Kart!
Oh!
Mr. Ume!
Hey, you!
Oh, sorry!
That's...
That's... Mr. Kiyoshi!
Mr. Romi Yamada!
Mr. Romi Yamada?
Oh, it's Taka!
Buzz Lightyear!
Who's this?
Oh!
Hoshizawa Sentou!
Wow!
Crazy!
Oh, you!
It's Ui!
I'm Ui!
This is the best part!
Crazy!
Tooooooooot!
That was funny!
I've got to say, that means,
this is our first time meeting them.
But the fact that they know us much...
They really trip me up.
Well, you know...
Well, well, well, you know...
I was a bit surprised the other day.
What?
It's scary.
You know...
Whoa!
You're old! You haven't said it yet!
That's also old.
The other day, I was shopping in Shinjuku.
You know, I was shopping in Shinjuku and parked my car there.
When I came back from shopping, you know...
Well, it's a prank, right?
Glass...
Huh?
Beware of broken things?
Glass?
You don't need to know.
You're the only one who doesn't know.
There's something like that!
It's like sticking a sticker on a cardboard.
It's like being careful of broken things.
You know?
After I finished shopping, I got in the car and started the engine.
There was a guy who was sticking a sticker on the front glass.
I couldn't do anything about it.
I opened the window and took it off.
I threw it away.
I went like this.
Then I went from Shinjuku all the way to Sasazuka.
I had a cup of tea in Sasazuka.
Then I came out again.
It was stuck on the front glass again!
You were stuck on it.
I was stuck on it!
Where is it? Where is it?
It was scary!
I came from Shinjuku to Sasazuka in a hurry.
It was creepy.
I took it off from the front glass.
What is it?
I was worried about the back glass.
I went to the parking lot.
I saw it and it was stuck on the bottom.
What is it?
I thought I didn't know.
It was completely stuck.
I went home.
I took it off.
I put it on the bed.
I noticed it.
I think the three were stuck together.
You didn't notice it at first, did you?
That's right.
I couldn't see it at all.
I was running away.
I thought I was being chased by something.
It's not scary.
You are scary.
I don't think I'm smart.
What is it?
It's a blind spot.
You didn't notice it.
For example, a girl I was dating at the time left her toothbrush.
My toothbrush and the girl's toothbrush.
You left it.
I left it.
I replied immediately.
You sometimes invite other girls to your house.
That's right.
At that time, you hide the girl's toothbrush.
But sometimes you forget to hide it.
I see.
When the girl comes, you say, that's my toothbrush.
That's right.
I don't know what to do with this.
It's a trick of Machan.
I see.
Why do you say that?
I hide my toothbrush.
I don't have to hide her toothbrush.
If I have a toothbrush, I can hide it.
When I hide my toothbrush, I know it's hidden.
This is amazing.
It's amazing, but you can't get out of it again.
That's right.
I have a lot of tricks.
One time, a woman hit me.
Someone came to my house.
The woman said, no one came.
I said, I know.
I said, it's okay.
I know.
There is a point that only one person can understand.
I did everything.
I saw it from the side.
I don't know what to do.
I said, I don't know.
I can't tell you because it will happen in the future.
I thought about it after the show.
There was nothing.
That's right.
That's what I did.
You look like a woman today.
You don't want anyone.
You're sweating a lot today.
That's strange.
What are you talking about?
When you see someone who is about to lose to the cold of winter, you hug them and make them warm.
It's a long story, but I understand.
Where can you get the black sand in the sky state circuit?
There is such a place.
Where is it?
It's in Stockholm.
There is such a place.
Was it better in Japan?
I don't know if it was better or not.
Let's ask a little further.
It's in Stockholm.
One side is like that.
It's like Tottori Sakyu.
Tottori Sakyu.
Next is Tottori Sakyu.
It's a little like Maki-ji.
Tottori Sakyu.
It's Tottori Sakyu.
It's like that.
It's a place to take pictures.
They don't know anything about the sand when they see it.
They don't shake it.
Do you understand?
I understand.
There was a high school baseball tournament in Stockholm.
I'm starting to understand.
Tottori Higashi High School.
Tottori?
There was a high school baseball tournament in Stockholm.
It was a championship high school.
I see.
After all, Tottori High School was better, wasn't it?
I lost.
I wanted to take it home.
I put it in a bag.
I took it home.
At that time, I said, wait a minute.
Did you shake it?
I want to shake it.
I'm not the only one. Everyone knows.
I know that.
It's not a joke.
I'm the minus point.
Why is that a minus point?
What is it?
Tell me.
I took it off.
I thought it was warm.
What's wrong with that?
This is a question for Mr. Matsumoto, who has been involved in the naming of new products in various industries.
Are you stupid?
Aren't you involved?
I was involved.
That's right.
What are the new products?
There are many.
Did you do this?
This naming.
Yes.
Please tell me what kind of product it is.
This is rotten.
When I opened it, it was rotten.
It doesn't sell well.
But how is it at the convenience store?
Fluffy.
I don't care about the current situation.
I'm worried about the current situation.
It's fluffy.
I don't care about the current situation.
It's a shelf that doesn't sell well.
That's right.
It's a product.
Do you know what's in there?
I know.
Why are you selling a glove with a puff?
I don't need it.
Who buys it?
I can't buy it.
I have never given money to anyone.
You are a person who buys.
What?
Please tell me what kind of product it is.
It's rotten.
It's fluffy.
I don't care about the current situation.
I'm worried about the current situation.
I bought it.
It's a shelf that doesn't sell well.
I know.
What is it?
It's a mix of Okonomiyaki.
I don't need it.
I'm worried about the current situation.
You buy it.
If you have it, you buy it.
If you don't have it, you buy it.
It depends on what's rotten.
Raw fish.
You don't have to say that.
It's rotten.
The package is rotten.
I don't buy it.
Who buys it?
It's interesting.
It doesn't sell well.
There are many other products.
I don't care about the current situation.
I ate it.
It's a chestnut.
What's the situation?
I ate it.
I don't buy it.
The package is rotten.
It's rotten.
I don't buy it.
It's interesting.
It doesn't sell well.
I don't buy it.