What is Gorou's specialty?
He can see through the true nature of people when he first meets them
He reveals the true nature of mysterious Inagaki
Quiz! Inagaki Gorou's 100 words
What is the drink that Gorou likes?
Wine
Sometimes, if you think that he showed his true self
I thought it was a bit of a twist.
It was a bit of a twist.
I think it's Dan.
Unexpected answer.
I think he was dancing.
If I had to choose, it would be Yuka during the summer.
Endo.
Really?
I didn't have that much of a difference.
It's like nobody cares.
Hosei.
I have the image of sweating on TV.
He spits poison on the members.
I'm Hiroko, a non-local.
I've never heard of him.
He's a mysterious man, Inagaki Kuro.
Sometimes he's like a father, sometimes he's like a lover.
What is his truth?
After 48 questions, the correct answer is...
...Tanaka Endo is the leader
Will Hosei Matsumoto be the winner?
If you were asked to sing a cry, what would you sing?
This is a service problem
Crying with a cry
There are many things
There are many things to think about
Answer open
I thought it would be a little off
Do you want to adventure?
Wolves are quite adventurous
Really?
Then the correct answer is
Please let us hear your cry
Pig
Pig...
It wasn't even in the head
What is the first thing you check when you see a woman?
I see
I want to know
Where should I check?
Answer Open!
I see.
I feel like Hosei is going in a different direction.
Hosei himself likes butt.
Sometimes he seems to jump on it.
He said it.
He is continuing his life of desire.
Now, the correct answer is...
The aura that that person has
It's getting difficult
What happens when Goro gets drunk?
Hmm...
I don't drink wine.
I wonder if it's wrong.
Well, either you're spoiled or you cry.
Ah, it's a little bit of a perverted feeling.
What about Endo?
The basic rule is the same.
I can't drink alcohol.
It's the same as usual.
Now, the correct answer.
It's the same.
Damn.
I see.
It is.
It's not correct.
It is correct.
It's basically the same.
It's the correct answer.
I'm so frustrated.
What TV show does Goroh watch without fail?
This is difficult too.
It's difficult.
This is difficult.
I think so.
The Darwin is here.
Well, Goro-chan seems to be saying it.
The dawn of Gaia is also...
Well, I understand.
I understand.
Asadora!
For a long time.
I will definitely watch it if I like it.
I know. I thought I would watch the whole show.
Surprisingly.
The correct answer is...
E-Tele's...
La La La Classic.
I thought I would not get it right, so I will give him a bad hand.
I don't watch Miya-Neya, so please listen to it.
Do you watch Miya-Neya?
Ah... I don't watch it.
You don't watch it.
I said it clearly.
I don't watch it.
You don't watch news wide shows.
Really?
What is the most memorable word that Gorou said to the person who saw him laughing?
Ah...
You did it.
It feels good to be able to guess this one.
Answer Open
This is difficult.
Yamaguchi-san, I know. I thought it was similar to this.
It was a small hint.
Now, the correct answer.
Everyone said, you did well.
I see
That was close
Well, it was the correct answer
That's right
That's true
Who do you think is the most
displeased with Goro?
I see
Answer open
No
I don't have one.
I was thinking of Tanaka.
But, well, it's a bit like hatred towards Yamazaki.
If it was me, I would hate Goro-chan.
Well, it's not strange if it's me.
I don't have one.
I think he hates you in general.
He might hate me in general.
Does he hate me?
It's normal.
Now, the correct answer is...
Eh...Housei-san.
Why?
Hey!
Let's ask him the reason.
Eh?
It's not Tanaka.
No, this is the truth.
I don't understand.
Let's ask him.
Ask him.
What's the reason?
I told you before.
I knew him at the first meeting.
I can't believe it.
You saw him at first sight?
Really?
There are people who don't think so
If this question comes up, we can get it
We can get this
When was Goro's first love?
It's a sequence
You can guess a little
Answer open
That's right
A boy
It's a kindergarten
It's a very simple question, but...
Endo-san, you're a bit late.
I thought of the teacher of the teacher.
I thought of that.
Endo-san, how old were you?
I was born early.
You're already old.
Now, the correct answer.
10 years old.
Wow!
That was close.
I didn't think...
I didn't think it was Endo.
It's been about 5 years since elementary school.
So, he's the real one, right?
Yes, he's my classmate.
Please ask him, the first love.
What kind of person is your first love?
He's my classmate.
He's serious.
It was surprisingly close.
It was close.
Why did you cry at the end of the 5th floor?
The last one?
It's the last one, right?
That's right.
The answer is...
Hosei-san.
Yes.
It's when Hiro-san left.
You love Hiro-san, right?
Yes, I do.
It's definitely around here.
Mr. Enzo, you watch TV and you are an animal.
As a human being, I am an animal.
I can be an animal.
Mr. Tanaka is like a world-class woman in the world.
Cry?
World-class woman.
You're sad, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
That's not right.
The correct answer is...
It's a question that humans can't answer.
I cried when I saw Violet Evergarden.
It's like it's completely taken off.
The answer is...
Inoue Yosui-san, there's no umbrella.
I see.
No, no, I didn't think wrongly
I don't think anyone would like it
An incorrect answer
It's an honest answer, but
Hiro-kun is also there
After 79 questions, Endo is the one with the most correct answers
Can he escape like this?
The manager is 2 hours late. What will happen to Goroh?
Answer open
Yes, that's right. I understand.
Somehow, the flow so far, Endo-san
I don't get angry easily.
You don't get angry easily?
Tanaka-san?
I say easily.
I don't get angry easily.
Yamazaki and I are almost the same.
Yes, we are the same.
Now, the correct answer.
The manager is 2 hours late.
How will he get angry?
Please look at this camera.
It's okay.
It's okay. Don't get too close.
You're taking care of your own territory.
It's right that he's not angry.
That's right.
What was the line that Goro said in a quarrel?
What is that?
I regret saying it.
Answer open!
Kasu?
Really?
Torn?
Kasu?
Don't look down on me.
I regret saying that.
Now, the correct answer is...
This is from when I was a kid, but when I was in elementary school, I said,
Your mom is a Debeso.
What is that?
You don't have to regret it.
There is a possibility that it was a Debeso.
If Gorou were to be a new member of the group, who would it be?
The answer is...
It's quite surprising
No, I don't think so.
I'm not that old.
It doesn't matter.
I think that I'm aware of the fact that you are a member of the Ho-Sei.
I'm going to be a member of the Ho-Sei for a long time.
Good or bad.
Now, the correct answer.
Matsumoto-san.
What is the reason?
I think I have a lot of power in the entertainment world.
That's right.
That's true, but...
No, no, no, I'm not happy.
I'm not happy.
I didn't imagine that.
How does Goroh use his head to make a fool of himself?
A fool of himself?
Otama, right?
Answer open!
Will it be the same?
It's probably a quick answer
That's right
Otama?
Otama-kun?
Let's see the answer
Otama-kin? What is Otama-kin?
Otama-kin
I don't know
Now, the correct answer
Please use Otama to make a fool of yourself
Please use it at your own timing
This kind of Otama?
This is really...
Already?
Yes
Let's go
Let's go simply
Simply
Please use your head to make a fool of yourself
This kind of head?
This is definitely...
Already?
Yes, already
Let's go
Simply
The principle of being a fool
No, no, no
That's terrible.
Otama Kin was close.
He was the closest.
Really.
If you could use magic only once, what kind of magic would you use?
This one.
This might work.
Tanaka is always slow.
Tanaka is using a lot of time.
That's why it's incorrect.
It's world peace, right?
World peace?
I think that's what it is.
I'll use it.
Endo-san...
You'll become a real detective and really arrest him.
Stop it.
You're suddenly getting tough.
Tanaka-san...
My favorite place is the teleportation.
You can just teleport.
You can't put a
That's why it's long
Then the correct answer is
In the land of Japan
French wine romaine conty
Make a field like the soil of the field
Make a wine field
I can do it
You're right
Let's get started
What name would Goroh use if he became a pro wrestler?
There's no way I can get this right
Just give me a close answer
Answer open
Inazuma's Ina is Thunder Goroh.
Inazuma's Ina is Inagaki's Ina.
Endo's Ina is Dynamite Goroh.
I like Dynamite.
I put it in the song.
I wanted to tease you, but I thought I had to.
That's why you wrote it.
You're going to Goroh, right?
I'm going to Inagaki.
It's Inagaki.
So it's called Dirty Inagaki.
Dirty Harry is also on it.
Ah, I see.
Dirty Harry's Dirty Harry.
So it's Dirty Inagaki Harry.
It was good, but...
I'll never say it.
Now, the correct answer.
Jet Inagaki.
Ah, it's Inagaki.
It was Inagaki.
Inagaki is amazing here.
It's amazing.
You'll definitely get Gorou.
Jet Inagaki.
You're being pulled by Jet Namikoshi.
Question 96.
If Gorou was to be molded, where would it be?
I'm not sure if I can mold it.
I don't know how much it's been banned
This is marine
Ah, it's not enough
I don't really understand, but it's to put a mole
Like this, to make it look like a double-eyelid
What is this, Endo-san?
To change the tongue
I'll change it to a tongue that can make all of them delicious wine.
What?
What's with the mold?
I was wondering how far the mold would go.
It's not mold.
It's a human experiment.
Now, the correct answer.
There is none.
Why is that?
Because if you mold it now, it will be revealed.
Everyone knows my face.
I see.
You're suddenly serious
Just wait for it
Don't know who is number 1 and who is the least
Will next question is for 99
Maybe it was.
Let's do this then.
The answer is open.
Ah, I see.
It's Tanaka's.
I thought it was easy.
I thought it was Matsumoto-san.
Now, the correct answer.
Matsumoto-san?
What?
I have a lot of energy, so I feel comfortable.
It's like a hidden camera.
That's a hidden camera.
Hidden camera type.
Well, it's muscle.
Hidden camera is closed.
Question 100.
I'll take it at least.
What would Boro do if the world ended tomorrow?
Well, which one should I choose?
While drinking wine, we'll end the show.
Right, we'll drink wine and have a good time.
Hiro and only two of them.
But I want you to be more strict with them.
I'm not strict with them.
I'm waiting for them.
Anyway, only two of them, and they didn't do anything.
I even called them my dad.
When you drink wine with Hiro, you want to fight.
Yes.
Now, the correct answer.
After all,
I wonder if he is meditating quietly.
I can't drink. I can't drink wine.
I said, after all.
After all? What is it?
After all, it's not wine.
The quiz, the 100th person of Goro Inagaki, will announce the winner with the most correct answers.
Who is it?
Who is it? It's a bit...
Well...
It's that person, right?
The winner is...
Shouzo Endo!
Thank you very much!
You were watching, right?
Well, I skipped the first half, so...
Yes.
Golf related stuff too.
Golf related stuff, yes.
Oh, there's one?
I didn't know that.
Yes.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
I was very happy.
It seems that you are interested in me.
But you are not interested in us at all.
It's true.
You are hurt.
What will you do?
You are sweating again.
That's not true.
That's the image.
It's hard.
I thought I wanted to be alone. I wanted to change my life.
I didn't want to do anything.
I thought you liked me because you were interested in me.
I was a little distant.
Who won the championship?
I'm Endo.
I have a present for you.
Thank you.
This is the restaurant I'm directing.
It's called Bistro Joe.
It's a new restaurant.
We can have a toast with wine.
Really?
I'm happy.
I have wine here.
Yes, it's from Burgundy.
Thank you very much. I'm so happy.
Yes, please come to our show.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work!