The 4th episode of the secret project, Matsumoto Shintoshi is serious about Shirahadori again and again.
You did Part 3, didn't you?
No matter how you look at it, I think you're turning it the other way around.
You're saying that again?
Yeah.
So, it's like you got caught in Mach's moves.
I didn't get caught.
No, no, that was normal for us.
If you think about it, it's a serious Shirahadori's first challenge.
He has a sword as a toy.
In the 2nd episode, he was wearing a helmet.
In the 3rd episode, he was doing it the other way around.
And this time, Matsumoto Shintoshi again...
Matsumoto Shintoshi!
...sacrifices his life.
So, I told Mach that I was going to do Part 4 today.
Come on, you can't do that.
Isn't that frustrating?
No, no, no.
Do you know the Shirahadori Shoko-gun?
Yes, I know it.
It's pretty famous in the industry.
If you do Shirahadori, you can do the Hatsumei Shoko-gun.
I did 27.1 in Yamakaze the other day.
That's amazing.
If you do Shirahadori, you can do Downtown Deluxe.
If you do Shirahadori, you can do Gottsuei Kanji.
If you do Part 4, everything will be better.
So, the ratings are important.
This is your original plan, right?
Yes, it's my original plan.
I don't mind doing it 4 times.
You got permission.
If you do it, I'll do it.
Are you a writer?
It's my original plan.
What's wrong with him?
Hey, what are you doing?
What?
Don't you know?
We're doing it for you.
We're doing it to make you a star.
What's wrong with him?
I'm sorry.
What?
Do you want to do something good?
No.
No?
Let me go.
Yamazaki.
So?
Thank you.
He's doing it for you.
He's doing it, isn't he?
He's doing it.
But, that's not for me.
He's doing it for you.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
I'll do it.
Let me do it.
He's just like you.
Stop!
What's wrong?
Don't do that.
Stop!
Don't do it.
Stop it.
That's not it.
Don't do it.
I thought it was the other way around, so I got a cramp.
Yamazaki, open your mouth.
I'm sorry.
This is the last time.
What are you going to do if you get hurt?
If you become a star with this, isn't it true?
No, what are you talking about?
Don't open your mouth, Sugachan.
I didn't like the way you walked.
I want to do it properly.
This is the last time.
Today, I'm going to do it on a white-legged bird.
Like this.
Let's try it with this.
What?
Like this.
Are you stupid? What are you talking about?
If you don't do that, you won't be trusted.
Don't do that. It's dangerous.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I can see the friction and the problem.
The rest is just a matter of feeling.
It's okay if you do it.
Why are you laughing?
What?
You're laughing.
I've been telling you for a long time.
What are you guys?
I'm going to be a star.
What is that?
I've been telling you for a long time.
I'm not talking about ratings.
Let's do it.
Let's take a picture together.
Take a picture together.
Let's go.
It's time for the challenge.
Please take a look at the moment of the challenge.
Thank you very much.
I'm counting on you.
Okay.
Do you really want to do it?
Of course I want to do it.
If you don't want to do it, don't do it.
I'm sorry.
Please do it.
I can't do it.
Do it with me.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
Don't do it.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Today, we came to see Sumo.
Kenko is here.
He talks a lot.
He has a face like Muro Fukudou.
The world of sumo is strange.
I heard a lot of stories.
In the end, you don't have to quit even if you get bald?
If you can't lose a little, you have to quit.
Why? If you can't lose a little, it's okay if you're strong.
But that's like a uniform.
It's not good if you fight naked.
It's not good.
It's natural.
If you can't lose a little, you have to quit.
I feel sorry for you.
I'm sorry if you look at me.
What?
I can't do it.
It's like a gift.
It's hard.
If you're strong, you can do it.
But there's no past, right?
There's no one who quit because he couldn't lose a little.
It's not possible in other worlds.
The fact that you're working with your butt out.
What do you think?
When you're working with your butt out, do you have a hard time?
I think so.
They're from the side.
Do you put something on your butt?
Do you say it out loud?
I don't say it out loud.
Wow.
What's that wow?
Why did you say it out loud?
Do you want it?
You want it, don't you?
Why did you say it out loud when you said wow?
Last week's kid was sent to the Olympics.
Oh, the Olympics.
I can't watch the Olympics.
He said he got a gold medal.
Last week's kid was a gold medalist.
He was about 90kg.
He said he could fly.
He was nervous.
When you said wow, you were lucky.
But I said it was a failure.
Even a welder can't fly when it's windy.
You should have done it like this.
You should have said wow on a windy day.
You did your best, but you got the gold medal because of the wind.
There's a wind, but it's hard to do this.
The ground is gone.
I don't know how to do it.
You can't fall down even if you fly.
You've come this far.
You've come from high up.
You can't be stupid if you find out.
You can fall down after this.
You can't fall down after this.
Why not?
I don't like it.
There's a reason for you to fly.
It's a distance.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter if you land.
I'll fly.
You can't say that.
I'll fly today.
It doesn't matter.
That's your idea, isn't it?
What? You want me to get off with my shoes?
That's not a shoe!
What's that long thing?
That's not a shoe either!
I want you to do this!
No one wants to get off here!
You're the only one who wants to get off here!
Everyone wants to get off here!
You don't understand!
Why do they have to wear such tight clothes?
Isn't that to prevent the wind from blowing?
Prevent the wind from blowing?
It's to keep the wind from blowing.
If it's fluttering...
That's not right.
When the wind blows...
You have to keep it tight.
But it's like a parachute!
When you put it on a car, it's easy to drive.
When you put the brakes on, it's easy to drive.
But when you're flying, it's hard to fly.
That's right.
What are you talking about?
That was fast!
Don't you think Nihon is underrated?
Underrated?
He's underrated.
He's like, oh, I got a gold medal.
If you get a gold medal in a foreign country,
they'll give you a lot of money.
But in Japan...
There's a kid who forgot his phone in the box.
He was a wrestler.
He called, broke the gold medal, and left.
That was a long distance call.
No, no, no.
Wasn't that funny?
He called and left.
It was a long distance call.
He didn't have enough money.
So he left a gold medal.
That's what I'm talking about!
That was pretty good, wasn't it?
Who are you talking to?
Answer me!
I don't feel like talking.
But it was pretty good.
Um...
How was it?
A joke?
A quiz joke?
Speed skating?
That's pretty bad.
What?
The start.
I don't care about that.
That's weird.
I'm telling you not to do it now.
I'm telling you not to do it now!
You can't run like that.
Don't do it!
I'm telling you not to do it now.
I'm telling you not to do it now!
That's weird.
How was it?
That was pretty good.
What do you mean?
You never listen.
That was pretty good.
The other day...
You can't do it now.
I'm telling you not to do it now.
The other day...
Why are you doing that?
I was doing a shoot.
And suddenly the Yakuza came.
The Yakuza came.
That's weird.
He had a short perm.
He was wearing a red shirt.
He was looking at me like this.
He was a little far away.
He was saying,
It's too early to see the Yakuza.
He had a short perm.
He was wearing a red shirt.
He was saying,
It's too early to see the Yakuza.
Who are you doing a shoot for?
He was wearing a short perm.
He was saying,
Who are you doing a shoot for?
He was throwing all the trash at me.
He was saying,
What are you doing?
Come out!
He took me away.
There is a Yakuza near here.
He is a fish.
I see.
I'm afraid of the Yakuza.
I'll tell you.
I know that if it's a yakuza,
That is a yakuza.
But I'll show you how to greet each other.
I've never heard you say good morning to the AV.
You're a fool.
I put it in the morning with a message.
I've been thinking for a while.
The lever often said big show.
Does that mean the amount of water?
Or does it mean the other way around?
Doesn't it mean that both of them are involved?
The lever says big show.
But let's say you pooped.
When you pooped, you pooped a lot.
That's definitely not a big show.
But you pooped, so you have to turn the lever.
You pooped?
No, I mean you pooped.
Even if you poop, poop is poop.
You pooped for an hour and you didn't stop.
You pooped a lot.
Which is the biggest poop?
I pooped a lot.
That's strange.
You shouldn't poop.
It's not that big a deal.
You pooped a lot, but you didn't stop.
I'm glad you pooped.
That's a big deal.
But if you have to poop, you have to turn the lever.
I don't think that's right.
Why not?
It doesn't make sense.
Whether it's a big show or a small show, the amount of water is the same.
That's not true.
Even if I poop, I have to turn the lever.
That's cool.
Why not?
I don't think that's cool.
What are you talking about?
Don't say something I don't understand.
Don't talk too much.
I'll tell you what to write.
Go ahead.
When I pooped, I pooped a lot.
It's a so-called questionnaire.
For whom?
There are a lot of people who do this on the street.
The wind of a car.
The wind of a person.
It's like that.
It's in every house, right?
Yes, of course.
How much do people poop?
How much do people pee?
I'll pick it up once a month.
Who?
This month, everyone pooped a lot.
What?
Who's happy?
That's why I'm telling you.
Who?
It was funny before.
Hello.
I'm suffering from a disease right now.
That disease is a disease where you can't stop pooping when you go into a crowd.
Don't say something I don't understand.
When I'm on a date, I poop a lot, so I run away.
I'm so happy to see them pooping on TV that I'm crying.
I'm jealous.
I've had a lot of drugs before.
Can't I just pee on my butt?
What should I do?
You can put up with it.
I think it comes from the spirit.
What do you mean?
When people come together, I want to run away from there as soon as possible.
There's something like a turbo in my body.
I want to run away as soon as possible, so I poop.
Poop!