The first time, I was in the middle of cleaning the kids' toilet.
I was like, my body doesn't like this, auntie!
I'm not in a good mood!
Dun dun dun dun!
What is this?
What?
Your body doesn't like this, auntie?
Apparently, I'm going to run around the shopping district with this.
I'm embarrassed.
With the money I got from this, I'm paying for electricity bills and phone bills.
You're paying for it, right?
I'm eating.
You're eating, right?
I'm already sending it to the city.
You ran away.
You're really fast.
I know you don't like it.
I'll chase after you.
When you lose sight of me, use this transceiver.
Like this.
I don't want to lose it.
I don't want to get caught.
I have this.
I don't care if you go somewhere I don't know.
I see.
Then, please go.
If you think it's about time, come to me.
No!
What are you doing?
This is really cool.
One more thing.
When you wore auntie's clothes, didn't any of my friends come?
They went over there.
Where did they go?
What?
Idiot.
Where are you now?
I'm here.
Idiot.
I don't care.
Where did they go?
Idiot!
This program is brought to you by Sunluck.
Ooyama International Products.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
They're coming.
Where are you now?
I'm here.
What?
Where did they go?
They went over there, didn't they?
Idiot.
Mom, where did the guys in strange clothes go?
Hurry up.
He's fast.
Idiot.
Stop.
No.
How much are you paying?
Why would I pay?
Come out.
No.
Come down.
Idiot.
They're coming.
Can I wear a mask?
Huh?
Ah!
I don't like this!
Wait!
What is this?
Are you in the shopping district?
No.
I don't want to say it.
He's coming!
He's running!
Run! Run! Let's do this!
Ah!
What?
Well, it always ends with the first time.
I don't want to do it twice.
Anyway, the old lady ran away.
That's what I said.
Ladies and gentlemen.
I don't think it has anything to do with the people watching TV.
What is it?
I don't know.
It's unusual to be so energetic.
It's really unusual.
I think the people who watched the opening today will understand.
I'm tired.
I ran around.
I ran around the shopping district.
In front of the station.
I only slept for about an hour.
I'm exhausted.
When I woke up in the morning, I was irritated by the low-blood guy.
He dressed up like an old lady and said,
No! I don't want to do it!
I ran around the shopping district.
It's a shopping district.
I was irritated.
We were having a meeting in Shin-Osaka.
I went in and sat down.
I was irritated.
I was so angry.
I was so irritated when I was knocked down by a trench.
I ordered iced coffee.
He said,
Yes, it's a katsu-toji set meal.
It's not a joke.
Don't make such a mistake.
What's the difference between iced coffee and katsu-toji?
That's a lie.
I can't believe it.
When I asked him,
He said,
It's an art car.
He asked me what I ordered.
What did you order?
I ordered iced coffee.
It's a katsu-toji set meal.
I told you.
I was so angry.
I told you it's a katsu-toji set meal.
I ordered iced coffee.
I was in a bad mood in the morning.
I was in a bad mood in the afternoon.
I shouldn't have been angry.
You regret it later.
Can't you get up?
I can't get up.
I turn on the volume of the stereo.
So that it makes a sound when it's time.
I can get up right away.
I can't get up.
But when I'm really sleepy, I can't get up.
I sleep like this to match the stereo.
And then I'm really sleepy.
I can't get up.
I was thinking about that the other day.
What is this?
I'm sure everyone has it.
There are times when you get a tingle.
What is that?
What?
I'm sleeping.
I feel like I'm pulled by a small hand.
You have it.
What is that?
You just fold your hands.
Just fold your hands.
Yes, yes.
Especially around here.
What is that?
It's like being pulled by a small hand, something like this.
Something like this?
Something small like this.
Yes, yes, yes.
Something like this.
Ah, what is that?
Is there such a thing?
What?
There is, isn't there?
Yes, there is.
What kind of thing is there?
The face is normal.
The face is also normal.
Yes, yes, what is it?
What is it?
Tell me.
What is that?
What is it?
I also have something like this.
What is this?
When I was in elementary school, it was the first time I had this.
It was really uncomfortable.
Ah, you were sick.
I also have a butt.
I don't have a butt.
What?
Where is the butt?
This hard part.
If it is like this, it will be like this.
It's annoying.
It makes me angry.
If it is like this, I will hit it.
I can't take it anymore.
I feel good about my body.
But it still makes a sound.
In the morning, when I'm in a hurry, my butt makes a sound.
It's really annoying.
I have never been in such a situation.
Even if you say it's annoying.
When my face makes a sound, I want to look in the mirror.
Is it really moving?
Yes, yes, yes.
I don't think it's moving by itself.
I was driving my car.
What about here?
In front of me.
When I actually saw it, it was moving.
It's not moving.
In the morning, when I'm busy, I forget my watch.
I melt my head.
In the morning, when my jacket is cold, it makes a sound.
It's dangerous.
You should hide.
Why?
Is there something?
No, no, no.
Really.
It's really annoying.
My body is really strange.
There is, but it's not that good.
I want to solve that strange thing.
And the hair I was talking about.
What?
Who is the hair?
It's annoying.
Why?
The hair grows.
I think it's annoying.
When I wake up tomorrow.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm going to cut my hair.
When I think about it, the next day.
When you set your hair in the morning.
I set my hair.
It's pretty good.
I can't say it's bad.
After two or three days.
I'm going to cut my hair.
The hair is alive.
One by one.
Do you understand?
It's alive.
I don't want to be cut by my hair.
I don't want to be cut.
I want to fold it as long as I can.
I want to fold it.
I don't want to cut it.
When I say I'm going to cut it short.
My hair will go like this.
Please listen to me.
Then.
Your hair is going to be cut short.
And theそa is going to command you to roll up your sleeves.
Please listen to us.
I didn't wanna be cut by my hair today.
Listen to me.
I'm going to be cut by my hair tomorrow.
Don't be arrogant.
The白es over there.
I can't help you tomorrow.
Eda-kun, calm down!
Yes!
If you have a hangover, go to sleep!
Don't be like that!
Do you understand?
Yes!
And the next day, if you go to the public bath, it's clean!
What?
You're saying something good!
If you say it's okay not to wear it!
Yes!
Everyone, good job!
Good job!
I'll break it!
I don't know about this guy!
I see!
But in the end, you'll be cut!
Yes, yes, yes!
At times like that, it can't be helped!
Say goodbye!
Yes, yes, yes!
Say thank you!
I think there's definitely something like that!
The human body is mysterious!
Also, when you drink something hot, after you drink it,
it's the same with anything, even cold things!
After you drink it, you go like this, right?
Why is that?
Or after you've shaved your beard, you go like this!
Yes, yes, yes!
Bup!
Ah!
Um...
Ah...
What's that?
Well, if you're a soldier, you'll understand!
Even if you're a soldier, you'll just go like this!
Ah, I did it!
I understand that!
You'll say, I did it!
But if you drink something hot, after you drink it,
Ah...
What's that ah?
I don't need it!
But if you're told not to say it, it's hard to drink!
After you drink something hot, after you drink it,
Ah...
It's because you say it!
That's why you have a big face!
I remember when I was in middle school,
I think it was a year ago,
I had a fight with my dad.
I was tired from sleeping in the kotatsu,
And my dad brought me a sweet sake!
He brought me a sweet sake, and I was sleeping next to him!
In the kotatsu, he brought me a sweet sake, and while I was drinking it,
Ah...
What's that?
Ah, I was so angry!
Ah...
I was so angry!
Dad, you were drinking sweet sake!
You should've said ah!
I thought, when will this end?
If you drink it all, it'll end!
It's over!
I thought it's over, so I went over there,
And brought some more!
I didn't drink it all!
I've never even touched it at home.
Ah, don't say that!
This is Matsumoto family's ah-sign.
What's that?
Ah-sign?
Please bring me a note.
What's wrong with you?
Thank you very much.
It's over?
It's over.
It's no use touching it.
This person is from Tokyo,
Machidashi?
Takahashi-san.
I enjoy watching it every week.
By the way, on the 20th of February,
It's about a child's user.
After I read the note,
At the end,
When I saw the note,
It said,
A child's user?
After that,
It became a simple story.
That was also interesting,
But I wanted to hear that child's story,
So I couldn't sleep at night.
What does that mean?
What was I trying to say?
There were a lot of notes,
About the end of the child's user.
I wanted to say that.
The child's user,
The last episode is about to end.
There were a lot of notes like that.
I wanted to comment on that,
But I couldn't think of anything.
So I said,
Yes, yes, yes.
This child's user who has been loved by everyone.
How many years has it been?
Well,
It's been half a year.
That's short.
It's been going on like this.
Well,
The people who came today are lucky, right?
It's a small number.
It's one of the few remaining numbers.
What? Are you underestimating me?
If I say this,
Normally,
What?
There should be more children, right?
What kind of brain do they have?
There are a lot of lucky people.
Well,
There were a lot of notes like that.
I don't know who said that,
But it's still going on.
At least for now.
There are a lot of people who get it directly.
It's supposed to end on March 1st.
Yes, yes, yes.
This time,
This feeling has been like this all the time.
But instead of us,
Daruma Shokudo will do it.
Who is it?
I don't know at all.
Let's go to the next one.
This person is from Otaku.
Good morning, Machan.
I'm a fan of Hama-chan.
Are you a fan of Hama-chan?
Hama-chan has been getting fat recently.
That's right.
I wonder if his belly is happy.
He's getting fat.
I used to be thin.
At one point,
He broke his teeth.
His teeth.
At that time, he couldn't eat rice.
At that time, he was quite thin.
After he broke his teeth,
He started eating rice again.
I don't know if he's getting fat.
That's right.
I can't say he's making a lot of money.
But I can give you money that you can put in your mouth right away.
I'm a rich man.
I can give you money that you can put in your mouth right away.
You shouldn't look at your teeth.
Even if you shave your teeth,
It won't take long.
That's your money.
Leave me alone.
You want to give it to someone who is fat.
I broke my teeth during the show.
That's right.
What is it?
If you break your teeth here,
I'll get you out of the child care center.
That's it.
That's right.
If you want to have beautiful teeth,
You should hit it hard.
That's right.
That's it.
I thought it was okay.
I said goodbye.
I hit it hard.
It's here.
It hurts.
That's not the case.
You broke your teeth during the show.
I lost eight of my teeth.
Your fangs are rauslan cuestión.
I'll tear you down.
My fangs are all round.
reverse
I'll bite with better strength.
That's it.
What's wrong with you?
You really like to talk, don't you?
Your head hurts!
Because I ran too much.
If everyone in my body changed, I'd be surprised.
Why does he have such a painful head?
He can't even talk.
He's having a hard time right now.
I'm always like this.
What do you want me to do today?
Galangu.
Galangu, right?
I'm jealous.
You can still use it.
Next?
I'm jealous.
I can still do this.
Next?
Takeda Tetsuya.
Kuruya!
He's pitiful.
The one who did it first.
It's okay.
What's next?
Ikariya Chosuke.
What?
I can't do it.
Ikariya Chosuke.
What?
Hoi!
Kato Shimura.
Tamaki Koji.
Who?
I'm jealous.
It's like he licked the whole person.
We're out of time.
Okay.
That's all.
Yes.
Please write more on the show.
That's right.
If you have any questions, please don't hesitate to ask us.
That's all for today.
Thank you very much.
Please come again.
We're recruiting a lot of people for the show.
That's right.
We've been recruiting a lot of Nitta-kun, but we're still recruiting more.
We'll come up with a better idea.
If the show is good, we'll introduce the show.
That's right.
We've been coming up with a lot of ideas.
We'll come up with a better idea.
This is still a bit too much.
It's too much.
We can't win with this.
We can't win.
If you have a bad idea, you'll want to come up with it.
You can leave that to us.
We'll come up with a better idea.
And we'll come up with a costume other than Nitta.
So, the sub-character, Saito, is not wearing underwear.
Do you hear me?
He's not wearing underwear.
One camera man, one person.
Saito is wearing underwear.
Please film him wearing underwear.
Let's think about it.
The editor is Suga.
Saito is wearing underwear.
I want him to say it.
That's right.
Let's give him a name.
Takasu.
Tsuchiya.
Suga.
Saito.
What was it? Yanaoka.
We'll come up with a better idea.
Goodbye.
This program was brought to you by
Sannaku.
Oyama International Products.
Thank you for watching.