Alpha members
Oh, Good afternoon
It's such a longer interview
It's long, right?
Yes, it is
For those who haven't felt like this for a while,
we have no live image ever
from the audience
We don't have Caraway
I see
Now everyone can respond to this
Seriously?
This program is sponsored by the following sponsor
Hey!
What?
I've told you before
You should make a more comedic face.
What do you mean?
Do you know?
What?
When you come down, you're always like this.
You're completely a chimp.
Smile a little more.
I don't know.
I can't make a face like that.
It's a huge difference from a T-shirt.
I don't know.
You look like you're going to kill me.
Smile a little more.
You're lying.
It's better to do it with a serious face.
I was doing it normally.
Did you take a hidden camera once?
It's amazing.
There's Kimoto, there's Makise, and in the meantime...
The AT guy says, please.
Did you go somewhere in the summer?
I didn't go.
You didn't go.
But you went to Okinawa, didn't you?
Okinawa is my work.
When you came to play.
I went to Okinawa at exactly the same time.
To be honest, Okinawa wasn't very interesting this time.
It's no good.
The day I arrived, I went in the day before.
I was filming.
In the car on the way home, Tajima was saying,
Yes, yes.
What's wrong?
He said, Masumoto-san, the hotel room is impossible.
What?
What do you mean by impossible?
He said, let's go home.
I was able to get a hold of something.
I called him right away.
I said, I managed to get a hold of something.
He said, what is that?
I don't understand.
I don't understand why the hotel was taken.
I said, is it going to be taken?
But when I asked him, he said it was a good place.
Really?
Yes.
He said, I don't understand why the hotel was taken.
I wanted to look for it myself.
Really?
I was so angry.
What's wrong with the hotel room being impossible?
It's not like that.
When I arrived, I thought it was strange.
When I arrived at the hotel, I arrived before noon.
When I arrived, there was a middle-aged man there.
What?
I thought, what is this?
Are you filming?
When I asked him at the front desk, he said something like, you're lucky today.
There is a live broadcast at the hotel today.
We will broadcast the poolside live.
It may be broadcasted.
It's a good match.
It's funny.
Your way of filming is funny.
I finally took a break and came to Okinawa to enjoy my private time.
But I didn't hear anything.
Did you use the poolside?
I used the whole poolside.
I went to my room.
I went to the bathroom.
I went to the balcony.
I looked at the balcony.
I thought, what should I do?
It's like it's starting now.
I put on an apron.
I put on a cape.
It's like a comedy.
I've never seen a comedy in Okinawa.
No, no, no.
This is hard.
There are three cameras.
I can see the pool from anywhere.
The sun is bad there.
I still want to watch a video in my room.
I brought a video.
I can't bring a deck.
I thought it was at the hotel.
Excuse me, do you have a video deck?
He said, no.
If it's a suite, I have one.
You can't say it like that.
I can't say it like that.
If it's something like that,
I thought, what should I do?
There's an electrician over there.
I can't think of anything.
Last year, I was able to use my cell phone.
But this year, it's like I'm out of town.
I have bad luck.
That's why it changed.
It wasn't funny at all.
Why wasn't it funny?
A lot of things.
The plane is noisy.
I can't help it.
Why do you put a kid on a super seat?
That's fine.
Don't say bad things about a super seat.
It doesn't matter where you are.
It doesn't matter if the kid is noisy.
When I got on the plane,
I was like,
the kid is noisy again.
Ouch!
I got pinched!
My mom is noisy, so I pinched her.
Ouch!
I got pinched!
That's funny.
It doesn't matter.
How many days did you stay?
Two or three days.
I stayed for three days.
If you don't stay for a week,
you have to go back when you say,
I'm finally leaving.
I don't know what you're talking about.
When you get used to it,
when you know what it's like,
you go back.
That's not good.
I don't know why I went on a trip.
The poop doesn't pollute the toilet.
I'm a guest.
When you go on a trip,
you poop in the toilet, right?
I don't know if it's everyone.
There's no one in the hotel to clean the poop.
Everyone poops, right?
I don't do it at all.
I don't poop.
Really?
It's not Okinawa's fault, is it?
It's because you didn't go on a trip.
It's not Okinawa's fault.
My hair stinks.
Everyone tells me,
Heminchu! Heminchu!
Have you ever heard of Yamatonchu?
I'm really sick.
I don't care about that.
My mother called me.
She said she saw it.
She said,
Your father is angry.
Why is he angry?
I'm not an alchoholist.
I'm not poor.
I'm a comedian.
My mother said,
What did you say?
I thought it was funny.
That's our character.
What did you do?
What should I do?
It's something my father had.
My father had a big explosion.
Please show it.
You've been to all the entertainers' houses.
I've been to all the entertainers' houses.
Tell me about the house of Seinkamyu.
Do you really want to know?
I want to know where you live.
First, the apartment?
Yes, the apartment.
Where do you live?
Seinkamyu.
Really?
It says Kamyu in the title.
It says Kamyu.
It says Tomita in the title.
I wonder if you live together.
I see.
I have a luggage.
How big is the house?
It wasn't that big.
Really?
Yes.
It's about 18 square meters.
It's a little small.
I don't think it's small.
You live in a big house.
18 square meters is a big house.
It's not a big house.
It's not that big.
Tell me about the house of 18 square meters.
I don't want you to tell me.
I don't know if that's true.
What does the house look like?
There's a 30-square-meter living room.
Really?
It's diagonal.
It's 30-square-meters.
It's physically impossible to move.
It's 30-square-meters like this.
It's just below.
That's right.
I can't go up there.
It's a tatami mat.
The eyes of the tatami mat are horizontal.
I'll do my best.
At first, the eyes were the same.
That's why I'm doing this.
The same.
I had to take the things out of the closet.
And I did this.
I did this.
I'm having fun.
That's right.
But I'm not stupid.
I can move the tatami mat like this.
I can go to the middle.
But you can't move the tatami mat.
But the living room is not like that.
I said that.
You said that?
Yes.
I just said that.
I don't really get it.
I don't really get it either.
I said that it's not like that at all.
That's enough.
So there's a 30-square-meter window on the first floor.
Yes.
And what's on this side?
There's only the living room, right?
When you open the door.
At first, there's only the living room.
So there's something on both sides, right?
There's nothing on both sides.
There's nothing in the bathroom?
There's nothing.
It's on the top floor.
What?
It's the same as the stairs?
That's right.
On the top floor, there's a bath.
I think there were three baths.
I said that it was just the bathroom.
I don't really get it.
I said, it's not connected to the bathroom.
There are three bathrooms.
The bedroom is spacious.
The bedroom?
There was a bedroom.
On the second floor?
It was on the second floor.
But I don't think it's taken that much, because it's a 18-inch building.
I see.
I should have used it from the beginning.
I should have made the living room 30 stories high.
No, it was just a dream for the staff.
The living room of 30 stories.
With that 18-inch building, it wouldn't have been possible.
Yes, it wouldn't have been possible.
It's not a 30-story building.
That's what I thought.
That's what I thought, but there's a bit of Sein's personality in it.
It's like, I'll do it even if it's at an angle, that kind of Sein's way of thinking.
Let's move on.
Yes.
This is a question for Matsumoto-san, who still hasn't broken the record of being in Koshien 6 times.
What kind of habit does a so-called Koshien demon have that no one has seen before?
Ah, a demon.
What kind of habit does he have?
I saw it during the summer of Kouni.
You saw it?
Ah, I see.
When I said, from now on.
What did you say?
Did you see it?
From now on, when I said, that thing.
That thing?
The entrance course.
I see.
Yes.
Summer, summer, summer, summer, here, summer.
Bam, bam, bam, bam, bam, bam, bam, bam.
I saw it.
Yes, yes, you saw it.
Yes, yes.
The two islands.
That, right?
Yes, yes, the two islands.
Bam, bam, bam, bam, bam, bam, bam, bam, bam.
No, I don't care about that.
Yes.
Go on.
And then.
Where did you see it?
I said I saw it.
As a 9 o'clock.
Ah, that's right.
Koshien 6 times.
That's right.
Yes, yes.
And then, I saw it.
Then, what do you call that?
This.
Stockings.
There are stockings that look like, are you serious?
Yes, yes.
What are those?
Stockings.
Just like that?
Yes.
You noticed that I wasn't wearing stockings?
I noticed.
You noticed?
Yes.
You're really stupid.
Everyone was like, here's the representative of Hyogo Prefecture!
They were doing that.
Eh, you were called like that?
Yes.
The representative of Hyogo Prefecture, please come here!
They said that.
And I was lined up.
I'm going!
Ta-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da!
That's what I was doing.
What's that?
Ah, from the beginning.
The opening.
I was doing something.
And then, I was like, you're not wearing this?
Ah!
I was like, ah!
I can't do this!
Yes.
Right?
Because I didn't think I could do that much.
Ah, I could have done everything I thought I could.
Well, well, well.
Because you're a rocker.
But, you know, on a sunny stage like this, I thought it was not good to have only one person
wearing that.
So, I went to the rocker room.
I went to the rocker room.
Yes, yes.
Alone.
I went up to the end, and then, the monster of Koshien was there.
What kind of situation was it?
When I lifted it up.
I was shocked.
What kind of situation was it when you lifted it up?
Ah, I see.
There must be a lot of that minotaur.
It was that big?
It was really really big.
Ah, really?
Really?
What were you doing?
What were you doing on the floor?
I was drinking water.
Like this.
At first I was trying to drink it directly, but it was surprisingly hard to drink.
I was trying to hide it, but if I took a sip, I could drink it.
I was peeping through the window because it was summer.
That's right. It was hot.
I didn't care about the heat.
I was just drinking it.
What kind of person are you?
I know you're tall, but I don't know what you look like.
That's right. You don't know at all.
You can't draw.
I know you're tall.
That's right.
What kind of person are you?
I'm a boy.
Really?
That's when I was in high school.
That's right.
Yes.
You know...
Am I a bad person?
I'm not a bad person, am I?
Mr. Matsumoto, Yoshimoto Kitte's Pichu Pichu Gainer.
Yes.
Why do you always have to live like a log?
If you have any tips on how to live like a log every day, please tell me.
I see.
That may be true.
What makes you a log?
Well, in the end...
It's the same for everything.
I want to be a log.
That's why my car number is also a log.
What do you mean by a log?
It's a log, so it's a log, right?
You can't say that on TV, Matsumoto's number!
I can tell by looking at it. You can't read it as a log.
Your cell phone is also a log.
A log, a log, a log.
How can I always be a log?
You have to always keep a log in your heart.
I keep a log in my heart.
Then what are your goals?
Do you have a goal, someone you admire, someone you respect?
No, I don't.
Please say that.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter if it's Nagashima-san.
It doesn't matter if it's Antonio Inoki, the hero you admire.
It doesn't matter who it is.
I also have a log in my heart.
So in the future, the hero I admire will be a log.
Even if it's a dream, it's a dream that can be chased by a log.
It's hard to say that it's a log.
What is a log?
Where is it?
I don't know.
In the end, it's fresh.
Freshness is very important.
I think so.
What is your favorite food?
What is your favorite fruit?
I don't know.
I don't know if you're listening.
How many times have we done this together?
It's not yesterday or today.
If it was yesterday or today, I would know if you were listening.
We've been doing this for 20 years.
Sometimes I say one thing.
What is your favorite fruit?
Nothing.
It's such a delicious summer.
It's really delicious.
If you leave it for a long time, it will rot someday.
This is the flow of time.
The flow of time can heal people's hearts, but it can also rot.
I think so.
I can't speak clearly.
Being fresh is very important.
I think so.
I want you to understand this.
I understand what you're saying.
That's why Hama-chan will be fresh from now on.
That's why I said it at the beginning.
When I said, Hama-san, nice to meet you, he looked like this.
You didn't look like that when you were in the first generation of the NAC.
Thank you.
That's true.
You were amazing.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
How many times did you say sorry?
You don't say sorry now.
You don't say sorry even if you step on people's feet.
That's not true.
That's why your freshness is peeling off.
There's only this part left.
It's all peeled off.
That's not true.
I'm surprised by your freshness.
You're swimming in the sea of freshness.
I understand what you're saying.
That's true.
That's why you can't swim in the sea of freshness.
I can't swim, but I can't swim.
I understand.
It's dangerous to get used to it.
But if you think about it like that, it depends on the person's motivation.
What?
You can't swim in the sea of freshness.
You can swim in the sea of freshness.
Your way of swimming is fresh.
Which way of swimming is fresh?
Your way of swimming is like an old man's.
You swim like a young man.
Which way?
What do you mean by a young man?
You swim like Boku-chan.
That's what I'm saying.
I understand.
When I see people in trouble, I can't help them.
I ask Matsumoto, a man full of manliness.
I don't like it when people make fun of me at school.
Please tell me how to avoid trouble.
This is true.
You often say this.
Even if you are found cheating, the most important thing is not to admit it.
I see.
For example, if your wife finds you walking with a woman, that's a friend.
Even if you think it's stupid, you want her to be like that.
I see.
So you have to believe it this time.
This is the same with poop.
You poop so much.
I don't care.
But this is the same for children.
I see.
Don't say your name.
The name that fell on the toilet.
The name that fell on the toilet until the end.
You forgot it.
That's the thing.
I never poop.
Please say that.
But you're told to lie.
For example, if you're told to go to the toilet, you just want to look at the toilet.
But if you're told to go to the toilet, you just want to look at your pants.
If you're told to go to the toilet, you just want to look at your pants.
It's hard, but if you're told to go to the toilet, you just want to look at your pants.
Okamoto Osaki-san, Osaki-san!