What could it be?
Good evening everyone, I'm Masatoshi Hamada from Hikari.
Tonight, we have a fortune-telling quiz.
We have three panellists here with us.
We're going to ask them to tell us their fortune.
Let's get started.
First, to my left, we have a dancing fortune-teller, Mayuzumi Asumi-sensei.
Next, we have a fortune-teller, Nagisa Hoshi-sensei.
Lastly, we have this guy.
Hello, I'm a fortune-teller, Matsumoto.
What kind of fortune-telling do you do?
Well, when you pull it out...
Yeah, to see if there's meat on it.
What kind of fortune-telling do you do?
Here's the first question.
Here's the question. Where am I?
Please look at this screen.
There are a lot of people here, but I'm one of them.
First, the dancing fortune-teller, Mayuzumi Asumi-sensei.
Here we go.
Where are you going?
Okay, I'm going to roll the dice.
I'm very energetic.
When you sat down just now, your heart was shaking.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, right?
You're getting in the way.
It's usually on the top of the picture on the panel, right?
On the top left.
Around here?
On the left.
On the left?
This is the center.
This is the center?
Yes.
Around here.
Around here?
That's right.
Okay.
Now, Nagisa-sensei, please.
I see.
Wow, I got it.
I can feel the power from here.
I see, from this half circle.
Yes.
I see.
Judging from that,
Is it on the right side?
I can feel it on the right side.
Around here, right?
It's on the corner.
This shoulder?
Yes.
This shoulder is me, but it's this shoulder, right?
Around here.
Around here, right?
Yes.
Now, Masao-sensei.
This is that, right?
Probably,
Rather than fortune-telling,
My comedian soul gets excited.
Oh, rather than fortune-telling?
Yes.
The nose.
That's you.
The nose?
You can wear it.
Which one?
The nose.
The one in front of you.
This one?
Yes.
You can wear it.
I can wear it?
This is different from the nose.
What is it?
This is a person's shirt.
Haha.
No, it's the nose.
It's not the nose?
It's not the nose.
It's the nose.
This is the shirt's pattern.
Oh, really?
Hahaha.
This is that.
Which one?
That one.
This?
You can wear it.
The answer is this.
It's correct.
I'm here.
Please look down on them.
Hahaha.
I'm here.
So the correct answer is Maezumi sensei.
Hahaha.
Now, it's the last question.
Are you ready?
Yes.
The last question, VTR.
Here we go.
There's a picture on the darts.
Please look at it.
Ucchan, Nanchan, Bandage-san, Tamori-san, Matsumoto Hitoshi-san,
Kamio Kari Yutaro-san, Yokoyama Yasushi-san, Katsura Sanshi-san,
and our Suga.
Hahaha.
Now, this one, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
out of the eight pictures,
who am I going to target with this one?
Hahaha.
This is the last question.
Now, think!
Whose picture are you going to target?
This is the last question.
I got it.
You got it?
Yes.
Who are you going to target?
Katsura Sanshi-san.
Yes.
I got it.
Maezumi sensei is going to target Katsura Sanshi-san.
Now, Nagisa sensei, please.
Yes.
She is very kind-hearted.
She is kind-hearted,
but she has a strong power
when it comes to targeting people with a sharp tongue.
Oh.
Is that so?
I can feel her power.
And then,
Kamio Kari Yutaro-san.
Yes, I got it.
Who is the last one?
This is Yasu-san, isn't it?
Oh, Yokoyama Yasu-san?
Yes.
Is that so?
He was in front of the frame of Yasu-san's glasses.
There is a grudge that he was hit against the wall
at a TV show in the past.
Don't say such a thing.
Hahaha.
I thought about it from that day.
I haven't forgotten it yet.
Hahaha.
Sensei got all the answers.
Here is the correct answer.
Wow.
Hahaha.
The correct answer is
Master Sanshi.
As expected, isn't it?
As expected.
Hahaha.
I got it.
Ladies and gentlemen.
What is this atmosphere?
I got it.
Why did you come here?
If you didn't apply for it,
you wouldn't have done this.
This is...
But the staff said
this is the last time.
Hahaha.
It's disgusting.
Even if you say that,
I can't do it.
Oh.
I got it.
It's pretty good.
But there is no one who calls me Hama-chan.
I'm here.
Hahaha.
If you call everyone Hama-chan...
I don't feel good.
Just once.
One, two.
Hama-chan.
Hahaha.
I'll put in matcha.
I'll be on air.
Matsu.
Hahaha.
One, two.
Matcha.
Wow.
I can't do it.
It's disgusting.
But everyone is fine.
Really.
Men...
To tell you the truth,
you have to ask men to do comedy.
That's true.
Women...
If it's the next day,
you'll like a completely different person.
That's true.
If you like a man once,
you'll fall in love.
It's a long time.
It's fine.
But men...
Men's fans...
It's weird.
For example, what's weird?
Even if you're walking down the street,
if you say,
please shake my hand,
it's fine.
But if you say,
I'll hit you.
It hurts a little.
The other day,
I went to a disco.
I thought I'd go to the bathroom and go home.
My butt hit me from behind.
Hahaha.
That's...
That's not a hit.
It's just that I hate you.
I was angry.
I looked back.
Everyone looked like they didn't know.
I don't know.
Who...
Who told you to watch a mini-con at a disco?
I don't know.
I was angry.
I wanted you to stop kicking my butt.
It's not like you made a mistake with someone.
No, no.
That's not it.
There must be something.
You hate me, don't you?
Did you think about it?
Yeah.
When I went to a disco in Kyoto,
that was the scariest thing.
That thing.
Machan.
Let's go.
What?
Disco?
Let's go.
Take me to the bathroom.
Take you to the bathroom.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
There was a real one.
Hahaha.
This is...
That's what it looked like, right?
Here?
Yeah.
Hahaha.
When I said let's go,
I felt like I was going to take off my underwear.
Hahaha.
But there are people like that.
That kind of thing.
I like that woman a little bit.
I can't go to Kyoto.
There are people who say that.
I'm a little bit.
I can't give it to you.
But there are more than 100 people, right?
There are about 100 people, right?
Yeah.
After all, there are one or two people.
No, there are.
There are more people like that these days.
Is that so?
I think there will definitely be.
Hmm.
What makes you feel good?
So...
Hahaha.
It's nothing but a
I don't think so, but that's a butt, isn't it?
Hmm.
Well, the one who has a butt is weak.
The one who has a butt.
Hahaha.
Feelings.
What's going on here?
It's already flat.
Hahaha.
Why am I here with such a guy now?
That means the one who has a butt can't have another butt.
I can't.
Hahaha.
That's what I'm saying.
If that happens, it will be a circle.
Why?
Hahaha.
That's not true.
It's amazing, isn't it?
If you come this way with such a circle.
Hahaha.
Wow.
That's terrible, isn't it?
Yeah.
That's right.
It's a scary world, isn't it?
I don't know.
That's right.
Men are all bad.
Men in the world.
Well.
I'm sure everyone has gone to buy konjac when they were in junior high school.
Hahaha.
No.
That's just a special guy.
I went.
Hahaha.
That's why I'm saying it's just a special guy.
I can't forget it when I was in junior high school.
No.
It was when I was in the first year of junior high school.
Well.
I went to buy school uniforms when I was in junior high school.
I was really interested in konjac at that time.
Hahaha.
I was really interested in konjac.
Well.
I bought school uniforms and everyone said,
Mom, I'm going to go shopping.
I'll go home first.
I have an appointment.
Well.
I bought konjac.
You have an appointment with konjac?
Hahaha.
Well.
I'll put it in.
I baked tofu.
I said, give me konjac.
That's what you did.
Hahaha.
Well.
I'm laughing.
Hahaha.
Well.
You're laughing.
I'm laughing.
Well.
I did I'm cutting my wife in the middle of the sword with a knife.
Oh I'm sorry.
I think it's about as rushed as any woman.
Do not imitate anything.
Hahaha.
Come on.
What have I done it somehow.
Do it with a knife somewhere.
I did not.
To the middle of the sword.
Well.
I knew how to do.
I was sad about one thing.
Uh.
It is a very red red without
agar.
I thought he was Yota Kanwa.
I thought he was done with the fairy tale.
What are you talking about?
I completely forgot about the konjac.
You used it?
I completely forgot about it.
I left it somewhere and went to play.
It wasn't a story or anything.
When I went to play, I was surprised.
I left the konjac there.
Was it dangerous?
Of course it was dangerous.
Why did you leave the konjac there?
My mom and everyone came back from shopping.
I opened it and found the konjac.
I was like, what is this?
I know what this is.
I know what this is, but I don't think it's human.
I don't think so.
I got tired of playing and went home in the evening.
I went to the place where the konjac was supposed to be.
There was no konjac.
Where did it go?
I thought I left it there.
You forgot about it.
I forgot about it.
I thought I had to take care of it.
I opened the fridge and it was in there.
The konjac was in the middle.
It was in the fridge.
I was surprised.
I didn't know that.
I still don't know.
I knew.
I knew that there was no way to do it.
If you knew, you wouldn't have cooled it down.
I didn't know that.
What is that?
That's a problem.
Women are good.
What do you mean?
I thought women were bad.
There are people who talk to you when you're walking down the street.
If it's like that, then it's like that.
Men can't stand it.
But it can't be helped.
Even if everyone was there.
I want to think about it a little more.
I don't care if you don't like it.
That's what everyone thinks.
If you don't want me to do it, I can't help it.
Don't say that.
It's okay to be straightforward.
Women don't like it.
Don't say that.
What you don't like.
What I want to do.
Women don't like it.
What kind of reason is that?
Women don't like it more than you want to do it.
That's not true.
They don't like it that much.
Can I take a shit?
Women don't like it.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know this.
It's dirty.
If I had a woman here, it would have been a mess.
This is...
Your father's hair is long.
Amazing.
You pulled it out properly.
That's amazing.
I still don't know where your assistant is.
Death motive.
I fell in love with Hama-chan.
Hey!
What is this?
I'm a man, so I want to be sexy.
I see.
You're an idiot.
Thank you very much.
Hello, I'm a 21-year-old college student.
I see you every week.
Hama-chan's diving is so touching that I can't see the screen with tears.
Sosuke!
Please continue to do your best with your little finger.
This time it's a punishment game.
Oh, that's right.
You have to close your fingers.
Close your fingers.
That's why I'm doing my best with my little finger.
I see.
I remembered when I closed my fingers.
My father once closed his fingers completely.
That's a door or something.
That's right.
It's like a human finger.
When you go to the bathroom, there's a door in the bathroom.
It's slippery.
When you open it and close it, it's stuck.
It's like an echo in the bathroom.
Wow!
Did you make a voice like a foreign cartoonist?
Was it okay?
It was purple for about half a year.
Everyone was laughing.
Please give me a pen name, Hama-chan.
Okay.
Is it a man?
It's a girl. A 17-year-old girl.
Recently, I've been listening to my parents' sexy voice.
It's an old story.
It's an old story from a viewer, so it can't be helped.
The owner is a voice actor. It's not a big deal.
It's just a porn video that my father loves.
I have a big money and a porn that my brother loves.
I have a family weakness.
I wanted to tell this to someone, so I wrote it to Machan Hama-chan.
Don't show it to me.
When I was a kid, I was sleeping next to my parents.
I've been watching and listening to my parents' sex from the beginning.
Machan Hama-chan, have you ever seen and heard your parents' sex?
I don't have one.
You'll have a baby soon, so please don't show your parents' sex in front of them.
You don't have one?
You have one.
I really have one.
Really?
Yes, I really have one.
I have one.
That's a big deal.
Actually, I don't have one.
What do you mean you don't have one?
I really have one.
So which one is it?
That's why I'm not docking.
You're not docking?
When I was in the fourth or fifth grade of elementary school,
I forgot that I had a flute test today.
So I thought I'd take a flute test today.
You forgot your flute?
I forgot my flute, so I thought I had to take it home.
I had a little time before the first hour, so I thought I'd make it in time if I ran.
I ran, and when I opened the door, my dad was in his pants.
My mom was like this.
That's real.
Your mom's face was down.
My mom's face was down.
My dad's face was down, too.
It's a little half-laughing.
Why are you laughing?
What's wrong with you?
I didn't say anything, so I wrote it down.
The flute test that day is already worn out.
How was it today?
It was unusual for a boy to be so close.
It was unusual, wasn't it?
Yeah.
Well, I can't help but talk about it.
I can't help it.
Because it's all men.
I was just talking, and I thought, if there's a war now, Japan will lose.
That's as far as it goes.
What's that?
I don't know why.
Do you want to do something else?
But what are you going to do?
There's a lot of men.
There's a lot of stewardesses.
There's a lot of nurses.
There's a lot of nurses, though.
Yeah.
What's wrong with that?
It's all men.
I'll do it if we do it.
That's what I'm saying, but you have more than 100 nurses.
Everyone was smiling now.
Everyone was smiling.
But what do you say?
It might be better to limit it.
By profession.
Occasionally.
Yeah.
Every time, every time.
There's a strange teacher at school.
Mr. Hobo.
You're going in the wrong direction.
Why is Mr. Hobo wrong?
The teacher at school.
Mr. Hobo is not wrong.
You're wrong when you see Mr. Hobo.
What's that?
Let's think about it by profession.
That's right.
Nice.
I'll do it again next time.
I'll let you know at that time.
That's all for this time.
See you next week.
Good-bye.