Good evening, everyone. This is the first episode of the Chikichikyousero Meijin battle at the Gaki no Tsukaiya Ara.
Let's welcome the two Meijin.
Hamada Meijin.
Matsumoto Meijin.
Please roll the dice to decide who goes first.
Please roll the dice.
Hey! That's too early!
That's too early!
Matsumoto Meijin has 10 seconds left.
That's too early.
Gono-san.
What's that?
It's black.
What's this?
It's a water ball.
A black water ball?
Yes.
This program is brought to you by Sunluck and the following sponsors.
Tokuno-san.
Painless.
What's that?
You're pretty strong.
I can't see you.
Thank you very much.
Seven, five.
It's a love piece.
A love piece?
You call this a love piece?
Eight, five.
It's white.
Meijin.
What's this?
Huh?
What are these five lines from this corner?
What is it?
It's chance time.
Don't do that.
Are you going to lose?
I'll calm down after death.
This is the only one.
Two, one, white.
It's my win if I lose.
Is that so?
Yes.
I didn't know that.
Meijin is doing it.
What is it?
Five lines.
Thank you very much.
I don't want to come to such a far place.
This is the second time.
That's right.
Let's go somewhere closer.
You don't have to come to such a far place.
I can't do it in the neighborhood.
You can't do it in the neighborhood.
Whose convenience is this?
It's all over the place.
That's right.
We went to Yokohama.
Where did we go the other day?
We went to a very far place.
That's right.
This is the neighborhood, right?
Everyone.
Is this a neighborhood?
That's not it.
Yokohama?
Where is Yokohama?
It's the same.
I'm from Hamako too.
You're lying.
Hamako Yagana.
It's sticky.
That girl.
It's like a cartoon.
I'm sorry from the opening.
What?
Everyone, look at it today.
There's something that's changed, right?
What's changed?
That's right.
You understood.
I thought no one would notice.
That's true.
This is what changed.
This is.
That's true.
It changed.
It's been the same all the time.
The set has finally changed.
That's right.
Speaking of which.
The previous set was just like this.
This set is just like this.
It's the same as the previous set.
It's true.
I didn't dare say this.
I've seen the previous set.
This set?
That's right.
It's not funny.
This is the only set in this program.
I bought that shiny one.
It's a bugi-ugi band.
You're lying.
It's true.
Did you still have it after this?
I had it.
It's a bugi-ugi band.
It's true.
I'm telling you.
I didn't spend any money on this program.
We didn't spend any money.
LIkely.
You only spent money on renting the venue.
You must know such a thing.
ON SHOCK hoy...
It's cheap to write the name of regional manager in enthalpy.
It's...
It must be expensive like IOMA's name.
The show behind us.
They stole the money from the wallet that the chairman lost.
It's true.
Really.
It's pocket money.
It's not just pocket money, it's money that we slow down like we sucked.
Hey.
What should I talk about today?
Shall we talk about that?
What do you want to talk about?
What kind of story do you want to hear from me?
I want to hear everything about you.
Why? There must be something you want to hear.
If the audience wants to hear this, that's for sure.
But I don't want to hear anything about you.
Everyone who came here is the same.
Is that so?
Even when they told me not to take off my underwear, I took it off.
Yeah.
Right?
Yeah, but you know...
I remembered that I had to get used to Tokyo a little more.
You did?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Why did you remember that?
Osaka is already dead.
The other day, I thought I'd play in Osaka for the first time in a while.
But there was no one there.
That's just a coincidence, right?
No, I'm sure you don't know.
So you're hiding in a store somewhere?
No, I'm not hiding in a store.
Hey, Matsumoto is here.
I was wondering if you'd come if you got caught.
I'm not hiding in a store.
I went to 10K85.
Don't go to 10K after looking for a woman.
Show me the store.
I can't tell you the name of the bridge, but it's a crane car.
10K is...
It goes like this.
No, it doesn't break.
Oh, really?
It used to be called a hook bridge on the bridge of Dotonbori.
There was a signboard like this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There was a bridge and the river of Dotonbori was flowing.
It was called a hook bridge.
That's right.
There's no one there.
Oh, really?
When I was walking around, I saw a big marimo in the west.
It's quiet in front of the bridge.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know.
There's a big marimo in the west.
The round grass is breaking up in the snow.
Run and then bang, bang, bang.
What was the situation like before?
Oh, I was surprised.
There's always a young man walking in the south.
Yeah.
The strike zone is here.
They were selling it.
Well, it was about 12 years ago.
You're lying.
It's been three years since I started shooting.
I started shooting in the strike zone.
Well, when the time is late, the strike zone is...
I think it's okay around here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think so, too.
It's getting worse.
Well, it's already sold out at this time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There wasn't even that.
I was walking with three men, but at 5 o'clock in the morning, I couldn't even find a broken ball.
That's not good.
I thought I'd pull it out with a broken ball, but I couldn't find it.
There was no one to use it.
Because there was no one.
So where did your grumpy feelings go?
I have no choice but to go borrow adult videos that I've been doing until 5 o'clock.
It's empty, isn't it?
What are you guys doing? Don't pull adult videos.
I'll watch it.
What are you talking about?
Adult videos, too.
But Tokyo is a difficult place to borrow.
Oh, yeah?
Everyone's so tense.
Why is that?
Have you ever written it here?
I have.
Isn't it weird? Osaka is more like this.
It's like, yeah, it's bad.
You can say that.
No, it's like this guy is pretending not to see anything.
I'm sure he'll come back and hit me later.
It's kind of like this.
I don't want him to come back.
No, I don't get that kind of rain.
I went to the store, and my brother was a college student.
Yeah.
I went to the store and said, yeah.
I was wondering if there was anything nice.
Please come.
We went to the store together.
This is it.
Oh, yeah. In Tokyo?
That's right.
That's not true.
This is weird.
There's a place with a ranking.
It's called the best store of the week.
One on the shelf.
It's in the band.
Hey, is that true?
No, it's a lie.
That's the store manager's preference.
This is the truth.
I don't know why he said that.
Well, you know, I don't think he's as bad as people in Osaka.
That's not true.
Is that so?
That's the same for everyone.
Which man in Japan is the worst Osaka guy?
All of Osaka's alcohol is on rent.
Oh, is that so?
Tokyo is pretty much free to choose, right?
It's pretty much free to choose.
Isn't it?
That's true.
How many years have you been in Osaka?
It's not open at all.
Why is that?
Well, that's because I rent a lot.
One person.
You rent it for about five minutes a time, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, that's not true.
You.
Damn it.
You rent it for five minutes and you can't finish it.
That's not true.
What is this?
I'm listening.
Idiot.
No one is listening.
You.
I'm listening like this.
That's not true.
What is this?
You can't say that.
You can't listen like this.
That's not true.
Even if you're a student, you're a sushi restaurant owner.
But that's true.
That's not true.
I usually rent it for about five minutes.
But it's a waste more than you've rented it, so don't you think you should do it for the time being?
Isn't that something to see?
Shut up.
Then what are you going to do with five minutes?
What?
What are you going to do with five minutes?
I looked at it and it was 45 minutes.
That's not true.
You should have written it in the first place.
It's difficult to go back when you've rented it for about five minutes.
What's difficult?
I rented it for five minutes.
I have to return it in good health at that time.
If you go to a tired Kaose, you'll be like this.
I did something.
That's right.
You can't make a bear in front of you.
You have to return it in good health and say, thank you very much.
I've already rented it, but we're not that tired.
That's right.
We just saw it.
You have to return it in good health.
I don't rent movies that are completely different from dummy movies.
I often rent dummy movies.
If you rent three adult movies, you can rent one dummy movie.
Because it's normal.
There are many people who suddenly go to the adult corner.
That's right.
Even if it's a lie, I've seen a masterpiece once.
This is too obvious.
I know.
You came to the adult corner.
You don't have to say it.
What have you been doing recently?
What are you talking about?
I haven't been able to do anything recently.
You're lying.
Don't say anything.
You're more handsome than me.
I'm disappointed.
What are you talking about?
You don't have a rental video that you haven't seen in Minami.
I have a rental video.
You don't have an adult movie that you haven't seen.
You and I are cute.
I think I'm cuter.
What do you mean?
You often go to the adult corner.
That's you.
Where did you get the money for the adult movie this year?
What are you doing?
I'm going to Osaka.
You're worse.
I've never been there.
When he was in junior high school, he asked me to go to the girls' room.
I refused.
Wait.
That's what we planned.
Why is it my fault?
Did I tell you what happened after that?
I'm angry.
I'm going to get hit.
When I went into the girl's room, there were a lot of shelves.
There were a lot of clothes.
There were two girls who took a nero.
They said, hey, hey, hey.
There was a bra, but there were no pants.
I said, what is this?
I went up the stairs and saw a fat woman.
I hated her.
When I got out of the room, there was a table tennis table on the right.
There was a lot of dust on the table.
I went under the table.
As I went under the table, what did this girl do?
She took from that dirty shirt.
I thought, bring this.
When it is very hot in summer, who will bring this dusty woman?
This is a Mr. Hamada.
When you were in middle school, you went to see girls, didn't you?
That too!
When I was in elementary school
When I opened the window, there were about 50 or 60 girls. They called me Mr. Joe.
You look like Moroni!
Uwaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Mr. Joe was amazing!
Let's go to the post office.
Oh, hello.
Today, the general office came to see you.
They said you were preparing for the meeting in Inagawa.
What do you mean preparing?
Ms. Takada.
What is the contact place for you?
Is it a company?
You look like you are working for a big company.
Do you watch this program every week?
Yes.
Which one are you a fan of?
I like both of them.
It's obvious.
I'm not popular.
Which one are you a fan of?
Thank you very much.
Please keep watching.
I'd like to introduce you to my brother.
Which one should I choose?
Please listen to my story.
When I was working part-time at KFC,
I was taking orders for a drive-thru.
Suddenly, my aunt came into the drive-thru with a bicycle instead of a car.
She said loudly,
Give me five KFCs.
I asked her again,
Is five KFCs okay?
She said,
No, five KFCs.
Five KFCs.
I came into the drive-thru with a bicycle
and asked her to give me five KFCs.
I couldn't stop laughing.
That's right.
I thought that's the name of the product.
My aunt is really stupid.
I was talking to my friend the other day.
When I was a kid,
I went to my friend's house to play.
My aunt was angry.
My brother was more angry than my aunt.
What are you thinking?
She said,
Don't be angry.
My aunt was very angry.
She was very excited.
Don't be angry.
Bring me some butter.
Butter.
What do birds do?
What?
Birds.
Birds are very difficult.
Birds?
Birds.
I quit.
You quit?
I didn't want to be on TV.
I was told to fly from 10 meters above.
That's a plane you made, isn't it?
I wanted to quit.
So,
I said I would do it on TV.
I did it.
There are still many problems.
It's complicated.
So,
I said I would go to see it.
She said,
You did it very well.
You were very excited.
You didn't make a flying plane.
I was 10 meters above.
You said you would fly with your clothes on.
You were very excited.
So,
staffs.
You were very excited.
Sorry.
Staffs said,
Stop it.
You should have flown while you were wearing it.
You should not have done that.
Three people from the start will ride it.
Order them to do that.
They were saying they wanted to fly with it.
Yes.
They said no.
Just let them fly.
It was about 15 meters.
Order them to do that out there.
There're a lot of cars going over there.
I didn't think Hamada would be there.
What about the old man?
The old man?
Yeah.
Gyoza, is he here?
Well, I think he's here.
I don't think he's going to send the old man.
I wonder if he sent the old man.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to do it?
Not really.
Then don't do it.
I don't think so.
I think there's no end to making more and more of these things.
Yeah.
It's worth it that there's no end to it.
I don't know when it'll be.
There's going to be an event for Japanese television.
It's going to be the...
America's Greatest Ultra Quiz.
Yeah.
And in the fall, the
No, it's the Ultra Quiz.
I can't go.
You're not going?
I'm not going.
I can't go.
What do you want to do?
I don't know what to do.
I should think about it.
I'll answer you here.
Yeah.
That's it.
And today, the lady who came in the public.
I've been ignoring her.
I haven't been to the public in a long time.
I've been observing the public, so I've really been following.
I've been watching.
I've never been to the public and I've never.
I've been by myself.
I've never been to the public.
I've never been.
I've never seen her.
The day I saw her, I thought,
I'm gonna be so nice, my wife.
I'll always be here.
I'm gonna be so nice...
We haven't met before.
You're so pretty.
And then.
It was nice to meet them here.
Thanks for everything.
Thank you very much.
This program was brought to you by the sponsor of this program, Sunluck.