In the first episode, we're going to show you how to make a living out of this show!
What a mess.
Good evening!
What are we doing today?
We're going to make a living out of No No Jiman Tengoku.
You look like you want to see something.
I do.
The judge for today is Yoshida-ken!
I'm sorry, Yoshida-san.
I'm the judge today.
You're the judge?
I'm not just a judge.
Right?
And the performer is...
Mr. Yodo Yokomari!
There are songs that you can't play, right?
There aren't any, right?
Well, sometimes there are.
Oh, really?
You were playing the rumba earlier.
I was playing the rumba.
There are new songs, right?
Look!
It's amazing that you can play the rumba.
Since we're doing No No Jiman today...
That's right.
We'll play 10 songs each.
You're confident, right?
I'm confident.
Can I say it?
Go ahead.
What?
C-5.
C-5?
Garan-zu!
Where are you going all of a sudden?
I'm frustrated, but I'm in front of you
Garan-zu!
Oh!
My eyes are wet with tears
Garan-zu!
Dino!
Go!
I'm laughing at the past
I wish I could hate you
But I still like you
That's enough!
I was confident!
You put too much emotion into it.
What are you trying to say?
Why are you singing like that?
That's right.
It's not like that.
If you sing too much, the audience won't be able to hear it.
Mach-chan's part isn't his own.
He imitated it first.
I see.
It was good.
Who is it?
It's a white-winged Gatchaman
flying in the sky
If you run and jump out,
you'll be a bird of a golden bird
Go!
Gatchaman!
GQ!
Go!
Gatchaman!
That was the best!
'
Your body smells...
drunk like an alcoholic
You are a man, aren't you?
You have to live strong
Don't worry about me
I'm praying for your happiness
From the judge, Ken Yoshida
What do you think of the whole performance?
And which one was better?
When I sing, I have to be the only one who feels good
I have to be the only one who feels good
And I have to stand on the beat
Well, that's it
The winner is Hamamitsu
Did you know that we are releasing a record?
Really?
This is the first time we are releasing a record
Ladies and gentlemen
Hello
What are those dirty clothes you are wearing?
You look so poor
These are clothes I prepared
What is this?
You look like a gentleman
I don't look like a gentleman
I look like a man
I have to do my best to make you happy
What is this?
I have to walk with you
That's the regret?
I don't think so
Your face is so poor
Really?
I don't have money
I went to a night club for the first time in a long time
It's called night club business
You are a bad friend
Tobu Zoo
What a joke
I told a joke on Tobu Zoo
I have a condition of not saying this
I don't have a TV
I don't know what to say
It's cold
What do you mean?
And it's far
You're not going to say anything like that!
Right? It took 2 and a half hours for you to come back.
Right?
I'm so angry at you for having such a long day.
This is not good.
Rakko Panda!
You're not going to say Koala's name.
What?
It's a flying animal park!
I'm not going to say it because I don't have one.
I see.
It's fun. There are many things you can do.
The place you went to before was called Green Pier.
It's a small town in Hyogo Prefecture.
I can't forget it.
It was summer.
It was a hot summer.
It was an outdoor stage.
There were so many people.
There was a big fire.
The sun was burning.
It was like a new story.
I was doing a manzai.
The stairs were like this.
There was an old lady who was sitting on the top.
She was doing a manzai.
Suddenly, she fell down the stairs.
It was a long journey.
She was doing a manzai, but she fell down the stairs.
I thought I had to do it.
When I was doing it, a nurse came to me.
The nurse and the teacher at Green Pier ran to me.
The old lady was taken away like an alien.
I thought I had to do it.
I continued to do manzai.
It was like a fairy tale.
It was true.
When I went home, I saw the old lady wearing a hat.
She was wearing a straw hat.
I thought it was a joke.
I didn't believe it.
It was true.
It was like a new story.
We walked a lot.
There are many things like that.
I didn't like it yesterday.
I didn't sleep for two days.
I didn't like it.
I went to the theater in Oza for the first time in a long time.
There was a child who was surrounded by a car.
When I went home, there were many people in the car.
I didn't like it.
I pulled his leg.
He came to the car.
I think it's bad.
I didn't like it.
There was a car behind me.
I couldn't move forward.
I couldn't stop.
I was walking slowly.
He came to me.
I didn't like it.
It was true.
I was walking slowly.
I walked slowly yesterday.
I couldn't stop.
I went to the station.
I went to the station again.
There was a child.
What kind of child is this?
I didn't like it.
I didn't take him seriously.
I couldn't help myself.
But that guy who was screaming like that,
If he said something like,
It's still like that,
Screaming like that,
I don't know what it was.
But he really had the guts to chase after her.
It really hurt.
Even if you say that,
The car was screaming like that.
It really hurt.
He was with his friends,
And he was crying in front of them.
He had guts.
In front of people.
That's why he was screaming like that.
After he went home,
He was screaming like that.
It happens a lot.
Yesterday, it was really bad.
I was really surprised.
He was screaming like that.
One person.
And then,
He was screaming like that.
What was that?
Are you kidding me?
It was really bad.
It was like this here.
No, it was really long.
It was like this.
I think it was Roba-kun.
His shoes were really long.
I was really surprised.
Let's go to the post.
What?
Excuse me.
This is the assistant.
You have a big chest.
I have a big chest too.
That's right.
What?
Don't make fun of me!
What did you say?
So,
Let's do a drawing.
Let's do an imitation of a cat.
I've seen it many times.
I'm a genius.
When I discovered this.
Let's do it.
The cat was sleeping on the roof.
It was crying like this.
I know it.
Let's do it.
No.
I think it's funny.
Don't be angry.
It's funny.
It would be good if it came more.
It would be funny if it came in two stages.
It's like today's lunch.
Please say something.
Meow.
What is this?
I'm going to end my lunch.
I haven't slept for two days.
I don't know what's funny.
I bought something for lunch.
Is that so?
I can't help it.
Let's do a drawing.
Which one do you like?
The pen name is Bonobono in Kanagawa prefecture.
Please listen.
My brother Yoshihiro suddenly said something ridiculous.
He said he wanted to become a student in downtown.
I don't say that I can't break my brother's dream.
Please reply to my brother.
By the way, my brother is in the third grade of elementary school.
I look forward to working with you.
My brother's dream is that.
It's better to crush it.
Stubbornly?
Stubbornly.
I don't want to enter such a world.
It's not a good world.
This is the ninth year.
That's right.
I want to come out in one or two years.
The first three years.
I can't afford to eat.
Because you don't have money?
Because I don't have money.
I don't want to have such a terrible face.
You're starting to cry.
It's true.
I didn't have any money at all.
I thought it was broken.
You only have money in your bank account.
That's right.
I think people who came to play will understand.
I don't have money.
How far is it from Namba to Amagasaki?
I walked all the way to Amagasaki.
I don't have money.
Didn't you work 150 yen a day?
No, no, no.
I finished my part-time job in the morning.
That's right.
I walked all the way home.
When I came back, I was thirsty.
I drank coffee milk and went home.
That's right.
It was terrible.
I had no choice but to stay at home during the day.
I didn't have money to go out.
I didn't have money to go to the bathroom.
That's right.
During the day.
I had a life pattern.
That's right.
I woke up in the evening.
At night, I was thirsty.
I was thirsty at home.
If I had 300 yen, I would have gone to the all-night bar until morning.
I went home.
I haven't slept yet.
I was awake until the evening.
I saw Alemin.
I saw her.
I made sure to watch her.
Shiga-chan.
I know her name.
I fell asleep after watching Shiga-chan.
I woke up in the evening.
I went to the bathroom.
I came home in the evening.
I was thirsty at home.
I continued to watch it for two years.
That's right.
I went to wake up.
I slept until the evening.
That's right.
I sometimes found her.
Hey.
I don't like it.
I think it's good.
I often tell my grandmother.
I went to buy cigarettes.
My grandmother said,
Grandma, Mild Seven Light.
I said, yes, yes.
Don't say it on TV.
What are you saying?
What's funny?
I think it's funny.
It's funny.
I said it on TV.
What are you saying?
When I appeared on a quiz show of a TV station,
I was a student.
I don't remember much when I was in elementary, middle and high school.
In particular, I was only written as a broadcaster.
Did you spend such an uninteresting time?
If you have a story from the past, let me hear it.
When did I do that?
When I was in junior high school.
This guy.
He's a white guy.
I've been given a cutlet.
Cutlet.
It's everywhere, isn't it?
Two people.
In front of a candy shop.
Is this a smart ball?
In Osaka, it's called Janjan.
Janjan, Janjan, Janjan.
It's like a bat.
There's a guy who does this.
That.
I was doing it when I was in junior high school.
When I was in junior high school.
A guy who looks bad from the other side.
The same age guy.
I was walking like this.
Hey, don't you have any money?
I was told.
I had a fight.
Two people versus one person.
Two people are coming from the other side.
No, I've already taken the other one.
Oh, you took it.
I took it.
I was screaming.
I was grabbed by my hair.
I was pulled around.
I feel sorry for you.
What are you doing?
When I looked at it.
Janjan.
I'm still fighting.
With the other guy.
When I looked at it.
A chick ran here.
Janjan, Janjan, Janjan.
This is the slot machine.
It came out with a coin.
I'd like to ask you a question.
What would you do if something like this happened again?
What if your wife was kidnapped by someone?
At that time, the criminal's request was to kill your partner.
What would you do if you could only get one of your wives or your partner?
Well, I'd like to ask you a question.
I don't know why you asked me such a question.
I'll help you.
There's nothing to help.
There's nothing for me to help.
So you don't have to kill her, do you?
My wife won't come back.
This is already an emergency.
It can't be helped.
You're going to abandon your wife and take me?
That's right.
After all, I'm gay.
Do you get along with Nozawa Naoko?
I'm often told that I get along with her.
That's not true.
That's the worst.
Why?
If you're going to take a picture of me and Nozawa walking together, that's the worst.
It's really ugly.
That's not what you think.
What do people think when they see it?
Even the worst couple gets angry.
Is that so?
Of course.
Let's say I'm going out with her.
I'm going to have a meal with her.
I'm going to have a drink with her.
What are you going to do after that?
That's the atmosphere on that day.
What's going to happen?
It's going to be a noisy and fun night.
I'm going to have a meal with her.
I'm going to have a drink with her.
What are you going to do after that?
If you think about it, you're going to dance with her.
Today's opening is the Nozawa Jiman Competition.
That's right.
Are you Ryozo Nogomori?
That's the one I took last week.
Hey!
Thank you very much.
That's the one I took last week.
It was really fun.
I don't know how much the TV viewers will enjoy it.
That's right.
The assistant also came out today.
I'm going to recruit more people.
An amateur?
Yes.
Please send me your photos.
And also, the one who is in charge of the DJ.
The one who is in charge of the DJ.
No.
I can't gather them all.
And also, the questions.
I'm waiting for your questions.
The answers are all the same.
The questions of the assistant and DJ are the same.
They are all the same.
Please send more questions with your photos.
I'm waiting for them.
Thank you very much.
Is that okay?
Yes.
The one who is in charge of the DJ.
That's all for this week.
Goodbye!
What are you doing?
This program is brought to you by Sunluck and the sponsors you are watching.