While I tried my best, I wanted to learn to pa
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors
Good evening everyone
Good evening
What should we start with?
Let's start with the one with the eyes
What are you doing?
Hamada-kun
Okay
Wow
That's the way I do it
I finished one
Please eat it with lemon juice
With a little bit of lemon juice
It looks delicious
It's melting
Okay
I know this
Please eat it all
It's okay
It's good
Is it okay?
It's okay
It looks like eggplant tempura
Please bring a small bowl
I'm so happy
This is impossible
Okay
Do you have it?
That's good
Do you have any good memories?
This is a bit dangerous
It's okay
I don't care
Do you have some beans?
Yes
This is...
Okay
Please eat it with salt
It's good, right?
Yes
Do you need this?
That's good
Do you want a shirt?
This one?
It's new
This is...
Only one side
I see
Please eat it with lemon juice
Let's take it
He's shooting a gun
Okay
Let's change the place
Please eat it with salt
Okay
This is the first time to eat eggplant
Yes
Please eat it with salt
This is the first time
It's ready
Okay
Wait
It's hot
Please eat it with lemon juice
How about this?
That's good
Please eat it with salt
There's oil inside
This is the best
Thank you
Can someone give this to me?
Earrings
Please give me something that I can't take back
Please eat it with salt
Please give this to me
That's good
Please eat it with salt
Wait
That's good
You did a good job
In September
In September?
The customers have changed
Yes
Thank you
Ladies and gentlemen
That's good
This program is held in many halls
We don't have fixed time
Tomorrow is Kojimachi
Tomorrow is...
This hall has the worst air condition
Last week we started a little late
We were talking for a while
We talked for about 5 minutes
We couldn't stop
You can stop when it's time
Why?
It's until 10 o'clock
Last week we started late
It was already 10 o'clock
We were talking and sweating
We couldn't stop
It's already 10 o'clock
I'm sorry
It's hot
It's too hot
Everyone is hot
My nose is low
Let me see
Listen to me
You don't understand anything about human
You don't understand what I'm saying
You don't understand
You
You have a low nose when it's hot
I'm sorry
Why?
I don't know
In hot countries
In cold countries
What are you talking about?
Even if you say it twice
Are you in hot countries or cold countries?
Which one are you?
You seem to be proud
It's fine
What is it?
Eh?
In cold countries
In cold countries it's difficult
Why?
You're so mean
In cold countries
The temperature is low
If you directly enter your nose, you'll get a fever
By raising your nose
The temperature will be raised
And in hot countries
It doesn't matter if you directly accept it
And it will lower your nose
That's it
So, let's talk about the heavy stuff.
What are you talking about?
How have you been recently?
Recently?
Yes.
Oh, the other day, when I was watching TV, I was doing something like this.
In the middle of the night.
There were three guys hanging out.
Two of them looked like surfers.
I thought, oh, they'll get caught.
I said, I'll talk to them.
They were cute.
But there was one more.
He was wearing a black tank top.
He was wearing a jean.
He was torn around here.
He was wearing this in a fashionable way.
He was so fat.
He was hanging out with the two of them.
The reporter asked him why he was hanging out with them.
The cute guy said, well, I thought it was okay.
But the fat guy said, it's just a feeling.
It's the worst thing to say.
That's why I can't speak English.
I remember that.
The fat guy said, Popeye, Popeye made me laugh.
Now, the bad guy is cool.
It's exciting.
That's right.
Well, I'm a bad guy, too.
Well, if you look at it, it's about me.
I see.
Well, I'm in it, too.
Bad.
I'm very sensitive to the word bad.
That's right.
If you say bad.
What's wrong?
I'm the type to get angry.
If you say bad.
Why do you think it's bad?
It's funny, isn't it?
If you look at it, there's a lot of things.
A celebrity or a celebrity's girl is a bad guy.
It's written.
It's not enough to be kind.
It's like a curry day.
And finally, the bad guy couple in town.
I see.
The bad guy is going to be popular from now on.
I thought I had to be bad.
That kindness.
There's a picture.
The bad guy couple in town.
That's right.
This is what a man is like.
It's a little tight.
All the women on the side are the worst.
I'm a bad guy.
Don't be bad.
I'm not going to let you catch me.
It's like a life insurance number.
But isn't that what it is?
What?
I'm not the one to say, oh, that's great.
Yes.
What?
I laughed a little at Popai's special.
Oh, really?
Yes.
But I saw that fat guy moving around in a brown car.
When there are three or four women, there's only one.
That's right.
I can't help it.
That's what humans are like.
For example, isn't it true that you're a celebrity?
I don't know.
A celebrity?
A celebrity.
Yes.
On TV?
Yes, a celebrity.
A celebrity.
No.
Say it again.
A celebrity.
Yes, a celebrity.
For example, let's take a look at this.
Downtown.
It's ugly.
It's ugly and dull.
Right?
It can't be helped.
It can't be helped, it can't be helped.
It's totally the truth.
Here I come.
I have something I don't know about the train seats.
Yes.
For some reason, there is a color change for one person on the seats for eight people.
Ah, ah, ah.
There is.
Is it brownish or something like that?
Who is that for?
No, what is it made for?
No, if someone sits there, look.
Eight people can sit properly.
Somehow...
It's like a heat tire.
Ah, is it hot?
What is that? Did you think of it yourself?
Can you tell your mother?
Why?
I'm already 31.
Why, mother?
Did you come all the way here by yourself?
Yes.
Who thought of it?
Who thought of it? I was saying something.
Somehow...
I heard something bad about it.
What is that?
It's something wrong that has been input.
You remembered something wrong.
Really?
Please tell me.
That is...
Yes.
What are you going to write?
In the place where the colors are different...
Why are the colors different? At first, the colors were all the same.
However, there was an old man who sat there forever.
The other places were on fire.
It didn't matter that the colors gradually faded.
Because that old man was there forever.
Because that old man was there,
it became possible for eight people to sit properly.
Everything is different.
Right?
That's not true.
Please tell me the truth.
You want to hear the truth?
Yes.
You really want to hear the truth, don't you?
No matter what happens, you want to hear the truth, don't you?
That's true.
Give me a little more time.
Yes.
I'll announce it at the end.
Why are there no fat people among criminals?
That's not true.
Fat people are...
To put it simply, fat people are hard to deal with.
Is that so?
They don't kill people.
It's not just killing people.
It's a crime.
Who are you?
Why are you here?
I'm sorry.
There are various crimes.
It's not just killing people.
I'll announce it at the end.
Yes.
You won't be able to take your eyes off until the end of the show.
It's going to be a mess in 30 minutes.
I'll stop now.
Thank you.
I'm a person from Tokyo.
When I was a kid, I often went to my friend's house and called him from the outside.
Hamada-kun.
I shouted loudly.
The person who was called...
Ha-in.
I deliberately extended the word and replied.
How do you call your friends in Osaka?
Why did I have to extend the word?
That's why...
Hamada-kun.
I'm different.
Let's play.
And when I was in the second half of elementary school, my voice changed.
The soprano that had appeared so far...
It's gone.
That's when I thought of Hamada-kun.
That's too sudden.
The person who has a sense of rhythm is Hamada-kun.
Hamada-kun.
At the front door of a person's house.
Isn't it different?
Isn't it the same in Tokyo?
When I went to the bathroom, I was told to count 10.
The way to count that number is completely different.
We count 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
11, 12, 13, 14...
This is the saddest part.
Why is it sad?
It depends on the region.
Osaka is like this, but when you go to Kyushu or Hokkaido, it's different.
Osaka people are said to be the fastest to walk in the world.
Osaka people have a sense of rhythm.
If you go to Osaka and observe the people walking on the streets, it's different from Tokyo.
They walk fast, and sometimes they walk like this.
Hiragawa-san.
You can do backflip.
You have to look at those things carefully.
Let's go home.
It's okay.
If you say it, I'll answer it properly.
It's you!
It's dirty!
I didn't do that.
Answer quickly!
Say it again.
Say it again what you want to hear.
Say it.
You have to say it again.
The atmosphere is bad.
I'll say it.
On the train.
There's a seat.
Only one seat is brown.
Only one seat.
Why is that seat brown?
Isn't it cream-colored?
It's cream-colored.
Why is that seat cream-colored?
That's the question.
In the past,
I wonder if it still exists today.
Grandpas and grandmas had their own seats.
They had their own silver seats.
They had their own roles.
I see.
On the plane, it was first class.
It was business class.
Everyone had their own seat.
I see.
Why is it cream-colored?
I'll say it again.
It was the first class!
That's it!
I'm scared.
Okay.
I was really scared in the middle!
You?