Yakinokukai's famous Prank-Zen-Shu!
Today, we'll show you a super-duper-VTR of Machanama-chan's Prank-Zen-Shu,
and also a super-duper-VTR of Ahozura Manakuzero!
Prank-Zen-Shu
Target No.1
The first target of the memorable prank was Hama-chan.
I'm not Matsumoto!
This is my first time doing this, so I'm here today.
Ramen and...
The bento is terrible!
I've never eaten bento like this before.
Here it comes.
This is the first time I've been this nervous.
Thank you for the food.
The second target of the memorable Prank-Zen-Shu was Hama-chan.
Grandma!
Don't drink the water!
No!
My body!
What the hell are you doing?
Hama-chan!
Why did you come here earlier than me?
No!
What time did I wake you up?
I came here earlier than you!
I've been in that cold place all this time!
Target No.2
The first prank was Chikichiki-Terekura!
The next target was Takasu, the writer.
The man's desire was completely crushed.
If you really make a promise, will it come true?
I can feel it in your skin.
This is different from the usual opening.
The staff is like a tracking staff.
Please go!
Actually, this monitor...
Takasu, the writer, is in Room No.4.
That room is being shown now.
Because he likes sauce.
I think Takasu will keep it a secret from us.
I see.
That's why I asked the tracking staff to come here today.
I bought it.
It's Aoyako.
Where are you?
Where do you live?
I'm in Otsuka.
Otsuka?
Yes.
Really?
What are you doing now?
I'm taking a day off from work today.
I don't have much time, so I'm calling you.
Really?
Do you call often?
I don't call that often.
I've heard a lot of things.
Do you talk to everyone?
I'm in Otsuka.
Minamiguchi.
Minamiguchi?
Yes.
I understand.
Really?
Yes.
I'm in Otsuka.
Really?
Pink suit. Minamiguchi.
Minamiguchi.
Takasu is all alone.
That guy?
I'm sorry.
I'm still working hard.
Who do you look like?
You're so cool.
Who are you?
Taishu Kase.
What are you talking about?
I'm serious.
Do you really look like him?
I don't think so.
Taishu Kase?
I'm grateful that you call me.
Let's meet somewhere at 10 o'clock.
At 8 o'clock?
If you don't, I'll call you.
Taishu Kase?
I see.
I'd like to meet you.
Of course.
By the way, you might think it's a lie.
I used to be a fan of you.
What?
By the way, I...
Well...
I can't meet you at 10 o'clock.
It's okay.
Do you know where the station is at 10 o'clock?
Yes.
What are you going to wear?
I'm going to wear a white polo shirt and a navy skirt.
Takasu is excited.
Navy skirt.
You're going to wear it, right?
I'm going to wear it.
You have to come.
Yes.
I'm waiting for you.
All right.
Let's report the results of the one-person test.
I'm 20 years old.
How many tests did you take?
I took three tests.
Only one?
At 8 o'clock.
I'm here.
How did you do it?
Only one.
There are only two.
Welcome home.
What about you, Takasu?
I didn't have time.
I see.
It can't be helped.
Thank you for your hard work.
He's here.
You're singing with someone you know.
I'm desperate to find you.
I'm waiting for you.
You look like Tsukosu.
I look like Tsukosu.
You're stupid.
You're waiting for me.
I'm not stupid.
I'm going to expand the strike zone of Toshio.
I wonder if he's going to come out.
That's amazing.
I'm asking you.
I'm not going to pull you any further.
I wonder if he's going to come out.
I'm not stupid.
I'm going to look over there.
Which way?
That's not it.
Let's wait a little longer.
Takahashi.
I'm sorry.
I'm here.
He's running away.
That's definitely it.
Let's wait a little longer.
What's wrong?
What's wrong, Takahashi?
Takahashi.
You've been silent all this time.
I'm sorry.
Takahashi.
Takahashi, who was silent to everyone.
Let's not do this.
This is not funny.
Target number 3.
Next is Yamazaki.
Here's where the bad comedian comes in.
This is Takasu.
Actually, this time, Takasu.
He lent me his room.
Yamazaki.
With his girlfriend.
I want to get on with you.
Actually, that girl.
She was this woman.
First of all, please play her role.
What's your name?
I'm Asaki Misato.
Actually, Takasu.
I'm Yamazaki.
That's my room.
To her.
So I'm Yamazaki.
I'm Yamazaki.
Yamazaki is back while I'm running.
And she's gone.
And then.
This man will appear.
Please.
It doesn't look like elementary school students.
I'm Murakami, the villain introduction.
When I was defeated.
I wonder if Yamazaki will blow the night wind.
It's coming.
Good morning.
It's cool, isn't it?
Yamazaki-san.
Hello.
Is Yamazaki here?
It's me.
Hey.
You.
Misato.
I'll give you a joker.
Hey.
Who is Misato?
Don't say that.
Hey.
Say something.
It's too late, so hurry.
If you wait, it's there.
Hey, wait.
It's not nice to say that.
Hey.
It's too late, so hurry.
In early-night.
We don't Pierrot.
It's one of us.
Hey.
Wait.
Come on.
Hey.
What is Misato.
It's cool.
How is it?
Do you know Misato?
From where?
This?
I got a call.
From Murakami.
He said,
Wait a minute.
I'll be back in a minute.
That's right.
He said,
Wait a minute.
I don't know where he is.
It's the worst.
I'll get it from here.
Murakami.
Hello.
Hey, do you know Yamazaki?
Yes.
Yamazaki.
Your name is Yamazaki.
I'm Takasato.
Get out of here.
Yamazaki.
What do you mean?
I'm coming, so wait for me.
I'll be there.
I'll do it.
You stay here.
Excuse me.
You're scary.
Don't do that.
I don't know you.
I know you.
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm here.
Who is it?
I don't know you.
I'll go from there.
I'll go from here.
Excuse me.
I'm not the one.
What the hell?
Excuse me.
I'm not the one.
I'm really not.
Why don't you tell me?
I'm not the one.
I'm sorry.
He's talking crap.
I'm not the one.
Just wait for a second.
Where is your life?
nanレ
Konnichiwa!
You're wrong!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
I thought I was going to die!
Let's run away.
Wow, that's huge!
When you called me, you said you were fine.
I'm really tired.
Target number 4.
In the first episode of the Gaki no Tsukai series,
Chikichiki, Nakibokuro, and Okamoto
have a big surprise!
Next, Okamoto, who was the new manager at the time.
First, let's introduce the two people behind the scenes.
Kenji Tsugawa.
And next to him, the writer, Ichi Motoi.
The two of them are the set.
They're gay.
But this is a prank.
It's a prank to show Okamoto the gay part.
But the gay part is real.
Okamoto, bring me some clothes.
Hey, Ha, Ha, Ha.
LOL
I cannot believe
There are so many things
You are so beautiful
Come to me
Yama-chan
You don't know anything scary
I don't know anything scary
Yama-chan
You don't know anything scary
You got it
I got it
I am quick
I know how to grill
Two are
You are so black
The red color going on
Yama-chan
And I came for a phone call.
Here's our little Curly figured out hero!
D
If you don't say anything, I'll go this way.
Lower your head. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Otoichi is acting like that again.
What are you doing, sensei?
That was a tough prank.
It's a scary town.
Target number 5.
The world's new record.
The last one is a prank that we rarely see.
Please explain today's mission.
How many people can fit in here?
I see.
Let's start the practice.
You have to close it.
It's open here.
It's delicious.
It's delicious there, too.
You have to work harder.
Remember how you felt when you were thrown away by the coin locker.
Who?
I don't know.
You failed because you went from the big one.
You have to go lower.
I'm scared.
You came here to do this?
I didn't have to kill you to trick you.
I'm scared.
I don't like it.
I feel like I'm going to vomit.
I'm scared.
The smoke is strong.
Yamazaki-san.
You guys are scary.
You guys are funny.
Did you know that?
Then...
Don't blow your nose.
Don't be fooled like this.
Don't be fooled.