After all, after winning, curry is the most important.
It's getting a little hard.
Huh?
I'm hungry!
What a husky voice.
I'm hungry.
I don't know anymore.
I should have watched it at the best time.
Welcome.
Uh-huh.
Are you okay?
I'm good.
What are you talking about?
Here's the guest.
Guest.
I think you're better.
Excuse me, it's dance time.
What's this?
Excuse me.
Oh, my God.
Hi.
Welcome.
Hahaha.
Hi.
Welcome.
Uh-huh.
Hahaha.
I'm hungry.
Thank you.
Oh, honey.
Yes.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, me too.
Yeah.
Hahaha.
Thank you.
Oh, yeah.
Hahaha.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I got my nose, didn't I?
Hahaha.
Oh, yeah.
I've been kissing since then.
Honey.
Oh, yeah.
Hahaha.
Honey, I love you.
Not yet.
I'm hungry.
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
It's hot. I'm hungry.
Let me sleep.
I'm hungry.
You're such a wimp!
You're good.
Thank you for your hard work.
25,000 yen.
Everyone is putting out a lot of money.
If there's someone else doing it, it'll be a lot of pressure.
Suzuki will be doing it next.
That's the worst part.
It'll be next week.
It hurts!
It's been a long time since I've been to Osaka.
I was so drunk that I had to go on a typhoon.
I took a plane.
It's scary to take a plane in a typhoon.
It shakes.
It shakes even if there's no typhoon.
It was shaking all the time.
I fell twice.
That was dangerous.
From the back.
I fell from my head.
That was good.
I fell from my back.
You've seen it.
The tire was on top and I fell.
I'll have to bring it back.
I couldn't move my legs.
I hit my head.
I have a little cerebral palsy.
But I can still move my legs.
It's scary.
There's no point in going in from the day before.
There is.
Why are you so desperate in a typhoon?
If you're desperate, you should go to Osaka.
I fell twice.
There's no reason for you to go to Osaka.
I'll go to Osaka.
Why?
There's no reason for you to go to Osaka.
I want to cry.
Why are you crying?
Osaka has a lot of good food.
You went to Osaka at night.
I just wanted to eat something delicious.
I can't sleep in a hotel.
I sleep on the bed.
How do you sleep at home?
I sleep on a futon.
Do you sleep on a futon?
Yes.
I can't wake you up.
I don't sleep on a bed either.
But I can sleep in a hotel.
That's not true.
You can hear something, right?
What?
The sound of a refrigerator in a hotel.
Is that so?
You can hear it.
What are you worried about?
You can't say it all the time.
You don't know if you got the right answer.
You can calm down once.
This is it.
You don't know if you got the right answer.
You are worried about the second question.
That's good.
I'm not sleepy.
You are not sleepy.
There must be something.
Is that so?
I was in Osaka the other day.
I thought I was going to sleep.
Suddenly my nose.
My nose started to say.
This is about your body.
It has nothing to do with the surroundings.
When I went to Hong Kong as a kid, you were sleeping.
I can't sleep in a hotel.
I got a dream.
When Jimmy came in.
I was close to home.
What?
I calmed down.
You were close to home?
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
I was at the Nichio Theater.
Nichio Theater in Toshiba?
Nichio Theater in Toshiba.
I was there for a while.
Higashi.
The boy band.
That's cool.
That's right.
The legend of the big melon.
I don't like the song.
Higashi may be hard to understand.
Everyone knows Higashi.
It's easier to understand if you say the legend of the melon.
That's complicated.
It's not a legend.
It's not transmitted.
It's not transmitted to anyone.
He's the only one who says it.
It's a mess.
I was involved with Higashi.
I see.
We were rehearsing.
I went to see him for the first time.
I was involved with Higashi.
Everyone was looking at me.
I was wondering why.
Who were you looking at?
Itao.
I took a taxi.
A shirt came out.
Like this.
That's why everyone was looking at me.
Why?
I looked closely.
There was poop on my shirt.
That's not good.
That's not good this year either.
It's not over.
That's what it is.
I touched my dick.
Have you ever touched your dick?
I'm sorry.
There are many beautiful stories.
Matsumoto's beautiful story.
Everyone in America knows it.
Please tell me the story of when you rescued a child from a building in New York.
That's...
Hey!
What do you think the timing is?
I rescued a person.
Yes.
Why is your face different?
Rescue.
What kind of situation was this?
I went on a trip to America.
I was walking.
I didn't see anything.
Where were you walking?
The station building.
What?
The station building?
It's in front of the station.
What is a station building?
I was walking there.
Where is the station building?
I was walking.
Happen! Happen!
Happening! Happening!
I'm sorry.
I looked up and saw something amazing.
What?
What do you mean by amazing?
There was a child.
In front of the window?
Yes, in front of the window.
It was a miracle.
Why miracle?
Nothing has started and nothing has ended.
I was told to help me.
I didn't come to America with that intention.
I told my mother that I would go.
What did you say?
Rescue! Rescue!
When I said rescue, the child said,
Power down! Power down!
It's all words.
Game over! Game over!
Hey boy! Hey boy!
Why?
It's all words.
I was told to help me.
I said, Oh, it's great!
Oh, cutie!
A fool can't help a fool.
It was amazing.
It was a three-story building.
You can't fall down!
The three-story building is the scariest.
It's not scary.
It's a real height.
You're living with a fake family, right?
Go away!
Where did you go to the station building?
I've been stuck in the subway door in a stupid way.
It's best not to get stuck.
If you get stuck, please tell me how to escape.
You've never been stuck, have you?
I've never been stuck.
But if I get stuck, I can do this and that.
Please tell me how to escape.
How to get stuck.
Of course there's a cool way to get stuck.
Please tell me.
How do you get stuck?
If you go in like this...
Oh, like this?
I always get stuck.
I don't get stuck like this.
I have a hand.
I know.
You have to go in like this.
You don't even have to use a bow.
I think it's cool.
You're stuck and you're like this.
You're going to move like this, right?
That's right.
It's cool, but...
The people around you are crazy.
If you get stuck once, you'll be able to get out.
If you get stuck once, you'll be able to get out, right?
You'll be able to get out.
It's cool to get stuck.
That's right.
Because you're able to get out.
It's a way to get out.
You have to be careful not to get stuck.
What the hell are you talking about?
Wait a minute.
If you're going to get stuck, let's be honest.
That's not cool.
You don't know that?
It's the same with bugs.
If you put a bug in a basket and open it, it'll run away.
That's not cool.
If you're proud of that, you'll be like, what?
It's like a beetle.
But you really want to run away, right?
I really want to run away.
That's why I'm trying to go when it goes like this.
I can't close it.
I have to do it more.
Why does it hurt?
I'm fine like this.
You don't have to show it there.
If you get stuck, it'll open up.
It'll open up?
Yes, yes, yes.
It's better not to think you're stuck for the first time.
I'm like this.
Yes, yes, yes.
Do you understand?
If you get stuck, it'll open up.
Yes, yes, yes.
It'll open up, so go around the door and don't go back.
What are you doing?
This is a question for Komuro Tetsuya's assistant, Matsumoto.
Please write the school's chime in Matsumoto style.
There are lyrics in the book.
I'm not saying it's part of the song or lyrics.
I'm just not saying it out loud.
All of the lyrics are included.
But the school's chime isn't included.
It is.
There's something like pride of the throat, right?
You are great.
Wait a minute.
It's a bit of a shame!
It's a bit of a shame to talk about youth!
Yes, yes, yes.
What is Chaim?
Chaim is a bit different depending on the school.
King Kong, Kong Kong, King Kong, Kong Kong, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
Please teach me the C of this.
Ah, I will teach you.
You guys...
Why are you singing with a soft touch?
It's normal!
It's this kind of intonation, right?
Ah, well, yes.
You guys...
Right now...
What?
What does it mean by, now?
It's not even the part you'll sing yet?
King Kong Kong Kong Kong!
King Kong Kong Kong!
It ends at King Kong Kong Kong, right?
King...
Right?
That's it!
Really, really.
Really?
Well, that's fine.
Yes, yes, yes.
You guys, now is the time to go on a journey
Hey!
You're going to do the tatami, right?
Lupin is a man
Just like that
Fujiko is a woman
Please explain it clearly
There's that
Lupin is a man
Fujiko is a woman
Goemon is a man
Jigen is a man