Hama-chan's KIN-CHAN RACING MOTOKU!
Hama-chan, you're good.
I'm not good at all.
I talked about it last time.
You said it.
I got a letter from the viewers.
Just one?
I want you to appear in the Fuji TV program called KIN-CHAN RACING.
I'm not going.
I'm not ready for KIN-CHAN RACING yet.
That's enough.
It's enough just to wear a suit.
Put this on.
Makeup.
Why are you doing that?
I didn't expect you to do this again.
This is the suit I wore when I was a stuntman.
What?
I'm not good at all.
I'm getting old.
I'll put this on.
Why are you doing that?
My teeth are wet.
I don't like it.
I didn't mean to change it.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
I have to train.
Why?
Run.
I'm going to train here.
Let's go.
It's fun.
It's like this.
It's like a train.
It's fun.
Let's speed up.
It's coming.
It's fun.
More.
I see.
I'll put this on.
This program has 8 episodes.
8 episodes.
Are you serious?
Let's go.
It's coming.
Faster.
That was great.
Hey!
Ladies and gentlemen.
It's really hard.
As promised.
As I told you before.
We are going to meet the Minister of Culture.
It was really hard.
We had lunch, and we were late.
I wear a suit.
And you wear a tie.
Wearing a necktie, wearing pants, and wearing a plastic bald headdress.
With a red nose.
I went there.
I'm going to see the Prime Minister now.
The Prime Minister?
I'm going to see the Prime Minister.
I see.
What are we going to talk about today?
Today, we're going to talk about Yuka.
Yuka?
Yes.
Just one story?
Just one story.
What are you going to do if he's in a bad mood?
Him?
Yes.
If I give him a sign, he'll turn around and bully me.
Like this?
Yes.
I'll kick his belly and run away.
Then tell him to run away.
I'll tell him to run away.
You tell him to run away and I'll catch him.
Yes.
I'll tell him that.
I'll tell him.
Yes.
If I get caught, I'll leave the rest to you.
Leave it to me.
I'll leave it to you.
I can't be in this situation.
Oh, really?
I have a policy as a comedian.
I see.
I can't be in this situation.
Oh, really?
Yes.
I can't be in this situation.
I see.
I have a policy as a comedian.
I'm proud of it.
Oh, really?
Yes.
But people will think I'm a fool.
Good luck.
He has a scary face.
He's amazing.
He's a very popular guy.
I'll do my best.
He was amazing.
He was in front of the entrance.
It was huge police station.
And there were a lot of SP's.
And this guy was so scary.
I really wanted to entertain myself.
I did my best.
I was worried at first.
I held his hand and said,
Tashiro-san came to the entrance and said,
No!
Every time he said that, I said, No!
How many times did you say that to me?
That's not good.
I said, No!
Is it over?
He came out.
I said, I'll go.
I went down the stairs.
When I went down the stairs,
Kento Delicato said,
No!
What are you doing?
I tried to go down, but I couldn't.
I raised my hand and said,
Where do you think you are?
I thought you were going to run away.
I shook it off and went down.
SP said,
What are they?
I was scared.
It was the first time I held his hand.
Seriously.
The first time I saw them,
I said,
That's not good.
They pretend to be strangers.
They don't come close.
Right?
They have guts.
I don't do that.
I'm in the film department.
You guys are here.
Hanshin and I are here.
We're here together.
It's a popular show.
It stinks.
That's good.
Everyone came together.
It was a calm atmosphere.
The person who came was Gyo, so I asked him to take a picture.
He said,
There!
He was a little angry.
I went to his place and gave him a name card.
He was a secretary.
I knew it.
I was watching the servant of the child.
I was waiting for him.
He said a lot of things.
He left.
Let me introduce his wife.
His wife is still here.
His wife doesn't know much about us.
She doesn't know.
She's always watching us.
Get out of the way!
She's a liar.
Ask her about her job.
Right.
If there was a 2.26 incident, I couldn't write it at all.
Most of them were wearing a wig.
Most of them.
There was no discomfort at all.
It was hard.
There was a little left.
I should have hit him more.
I took it off.
I took it off a little.
The back is clean.
I hit him with a stick.
That was good.
After that, I kicked him.
That was no good.
I knocked down 4 SPs.
The fifth one.
My nose is open.
My nose was broken.
I was hit.
But he was really a good man.
I really wanted to meet him.
Right.
To be honest, I still don't agree with the consumption tax.
I wanted to tell him that.
If he resists, I'll use my fist anytime.
Right.
If he resists.
If he gives me a sign.
Right.
I have to beat him up.
At that time, he didn't understand us.
He gave me a sign to go.
I beat him up.
I told him to be Nan-chan.
He...
I went home.
He was like,
I'll be Nan-chan.
I don't like that kind of thing.
I don't enjoy it.
I don't want to do it.
Don't copy me.
If you like it, I'll copy you.
You know, the thing that comes out of the plate.
Like this.
It looks like a man.
That voice is cool.
Like this.
I'm scared.
I just want to say that.
I want to try that.
Can't you do it at the opening?
Can an amateur do that?
Do you have a license?
I do.
Do you want to get a license?
Go get it.
Do you want me to get it?
Yes.
Really?
Will you give me money?
Why?
You want to do it, don't you?
What kind of license do you want?
Do you want a boiler license?
Will it be useful?
Wouldn't it be better to weld it?
Do you want a boiler license?
I want a welding license.
Let's do it at the opening.
Do you want me to do something like this at the opening?
Do you want me to weld it?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Do you want a boiler license?
Let's get a license.
You don't have a license at all.
If you think about it.
That's right.
My car license was taken away.
Do you know why?
Because I stole gasoline.
No.
That's not true.
I only have a normal car.
Go get a license.
That's funny.
I can play at the opening.
If you get a license?
Yes.
You can only do it at that place.
You can't do that.
If you say yes from that place, the dishes will fly away.
Is that so?
Where does the dishes come from?
I've been thinking about it all my life.
Someone said yes.
Is that so?
I can't do that.
If you say yes, it's a violation of the law.
What?
That's a sign.
Really?
Is it okay even if it's not yes?
Is it okay to say yes?
Of course!
If you say yes, they will push the button.
Is it okay if I say yes?
That's hard to understand.
What should I do?
Is it okay?
I don't think so.
Well, well, let's think about it.
Let's go with Aragaki.
Yes, Aragaki.
Wow, I was surprised.
Thank you very much for promoting me on TV.
What happened?
Well, in the shop...
Well, if you're going to promote me anyway, please promote this one.
This one?
Yes.
Healthy curry?
Yes, we have a curry shop.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Walk straight to the left.
It's behind the first Toyota building.
We don't use water for our curry.
We cook it with yogurt.
Really?
That's right.
What?
What if we go to the kitchen and there's a curry prince?
No way.
That kind of curry is only in Japan.
That kind of solid one.
That's not good.
Well, the students are watching.
They're always watching this program.
Yes.
And they talk a lot about you.
What?
They don't talk about me.
So I thought I'd thank you today.
Did I say something?
No, I don't remember.
You talked a lot.
That's not true.
I'm a big fan.
Really?
Well, today...
I'm sorry.
Well, in the first place, I have a deep connection with Yoshimoto Kogyo.
That's the same.
I've been to Yoshimoto.
Yoshimoto Kogyo?
Really?
That's a mistake.
You're a senior here.
Well, that's...
I didn't say anything.
I've been there.
So, I'm a big fan of you.
Thank you very much.
Please promote it.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you very much.
This program has guests all of a sudden.
You'll be surprised.
I can't say bad things.
You can't say bad things.
Well, let me introduce the manuscript.
It's about a house near my house.
There is a house called Hamada and Matsumoto in Yamaguchi's house.
What is this?
This is Yamaguchi's house.
This is Hamada and Matsumoto's house.
This is Matsumoto's house.
Are these houses lined up?
Yes, they are.
There is an old man who is 73 years old in both Hamada and Matsumoto's houses.
We call them Hamaji and Matsuji.
The difference between Hamaji and Matsuji is that they are good friends and bad friends.
They often drink tea in the garden of Hamaji's house.
They often quarrel and talk about the past.
When I was a child, I often played with Hamaji.
Thank you, Hamaji.
I love Hamaji, but Matsuji has a bad breath.
I've quarreled with him, but I've been with him since I was a student.
It's rare to quarrel with a man.
That's amazing.
That's rare.
He is an old man.
Everyone is laughing now, but I don't want to quarrel with him.
He has a bad breath.
It's hard to quarrel with him.
What should I do?
It's hard.
There is a lever in the picture.
It's a pink plastic lever.
It would be nice if it was a partial lever.
The whole lever?
Yes.
That's hard.
When you get older, a lot of things come out.
I don't know if it's a lever or not.
What is it?
For example, an old man's eye.
I see.
What is an old man's eye?
It's an electron.
I can see far away.
I can see close.
It's like this.
An old man's eye.
If I were an old man, I would definitely enter the world of birds.
I can see far away.
Really?
That's good.
I can't see close.
I want to see close.
I want to see far away.
That's right.
What is the difference between what you can only see here and what you can only see in front of you?
It's better to see two kilometers away.
What is this?
I can't see it at all.
I don't like it.
It's better to be close.
Why?
I'm not interested in two kilometers away.
I don't know if that's true.
It's better to be close.
Why can't you see?
Two kilometers away again?
No.
I can't see two kilometers away.
I can see here.
It's better to walk two kilometers and see here.
So if you move, two kilometers away will move.
This is two kilometers away.
If this is two kilometers, I'm doing it here.
That's right.
I want to go from here to here.
If you want, two kilometers away.
If I move, this guy will move.
That's right.
So your eyes are two kilometers away.
That's why I'm a good boy.
I can see it here.
That's good.
I'm a good boy.
Two kilometers away is good.
My eyes are two kilometers away.
That's right.
So when you wear a T-shirt, it's two kilometers away.
I'm covering my eyes.
That's right.
Two kilometers further away.
Two kilometers away from your main body.
Another main body guy is looking at you.
Then who are you talking to?
It's like this.
But you guys are not worth hitting at all.
I can only see this side of you and this side of you.
Which side of you is good?
This side is good.
So the main body guy is better.
That's impossible.
Let's go home.
That's enough.
You talk too much.
Even if you say that, we can go home right away.
It's like a crescent moon.
We're stars, so we'll go back to the stars.
That's amazing.
Don't make such a noise.
It's scary.
Can you see it?
I ran with Kin-chan today.
What are you talking about?
That's decided.
Really?
You're lucky.
I'm not lucky.
I'm not lucky at all.
That's all for today.
Next week, we're going to show you the video of Kin-chan running.
Please look forward to it.
Goodbye.
It's over.