Chikichiki Chibikko at the Akinotsukaia area?
Anything is fine!
Applause!
Well done!
Then, I'll call two kind teachers who will answer your questions.
Hamada Masatoshi-sensei!
Yay!
Nice to meet you!
And Matsumoto Hitoshi-sensei!
Then, we...
Yes, please sit down.
Nice to meet you!
That was fun, wasn't it?
That's all for today.
Shall we start?
Then, please raise your hands and ask your questions.
Yes!
Then, I'll go first.
I'm Sugawara Yugo, 5th grade.
What's your question?
Well...
Humans are dead.
When humans die, they go to heaven and hell.
Is there really heaven and hell?
That's my question.
Ah, I see.
Thank you.
What's with this guy?
Heaven and hell...
Is there really heaven and hell?
Is there really?
Don't mess with me!
There's a difference between heaven and hell.
Ah, depending on the person's face?
Yes, yes.
What about his face?
It's hell, isn't it?
It's not like that, but...
You have to do something bad.
If you don't do something bad, you won't go to hell.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Let's go to the next one.
Then, I'll go.
10th grade.
I'm Akutsuryu.
I'm a second grader.
Hello.
Why is the Earth round?
Really?
I'm Kamaiko.
I'm a second grader.
What is a pendulum?
You have a father, right?
You have a mother, right?
Yes.
And your father...
really likes this.
Do you understand?
Other than my mother,
my father really likes this.
Most of the time,
your father likes women.
Since your mother is the only one,
it would be nice if you could focus on your mother.
But...
Even if you put it in your eyes,
your father really likes this.
Does your father come home from time to time?
No, he doesn't.
Really?
If your father doesn't come home from time to time,
raise your hand.
Yes.
He does.
That's bad, but...
That's for sure.
He does it whenever he gets the chance.
To put it simply,
if your father doesn't come home from time to time,
let's just call him Furin.
It's easy to understand.
That's how it is.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Okay, let's go over there.
Okay.
Let's go over there.
Stand up.
I'm Mayuko Doi. I'm a 4th grader.
I want to be a talent,
but please come up with a good name for me.
What was your school name?
Doi Mayuko.
I see.
It's Shoufukutei Mayuko.
Are you talking to me?
Stand up.
Touch me.
I don't want to.
Don't say you don't want to.
Come on.
Do you want a microphone?
What is it?
I'm Naoki Matsunaga.
Naoki Matsunaga?
Yes.
What is it?
Do you like Naoki?
I like him.
That's why you've been touching me all this time.
What?
Do you want an older brother?
Hello.
This is the first time I've been on a train.
I knew it was going to be crowded.
I took the Keio line.
You came on the train, but you were late.
Normally, if I came by taxi, I'd be here by 6.30.
But I came on the train.
What time did you arrive at Tokyo Station?
About 4.50.
What time did you arrive here?
5 o'clock.
Why did you arrive at Tokyo Station at 4.50?
Listen to me.
What?
You're not supposed to be here at 5.00.
Why did you arrive at Tokyo Station at 4.50?
This is...
This is the 5th most mysterious train in the world.
What are you talking about?
You're late again today.
I'm not late.
I was here at 5.00.
I'm not here.
I was here.
Are you stupid?
You were here at 6.00.
I was eating ramen in front of you.
Don't lie.
It's true.
I ate ramen in Sapporo.
You saw me passing by, right?
No, I really ate it.
Mushroom ramen.
You were late and you still ate ramen?
Of course.
What?
Give it to me.
What is it?
Juice.
Give it to me.
What is it?
The All-Star game.
The fan vote.
I'm showing the top players in each position.
This way.
Yes.
Right?
What are we going to do with this?
Yes.
So, this year's All-Star.
Which team will win?
Let's bet on this one.
Yes.
The one who loses will be punished.
But if I do this, I'll definitely have an advantage.
You don't know baseball, do you?
Chromaty.
Chromaty?
What kind of foreigner is this?
Of course.
Sorry.
Chromaty.
Chromaty, right?
I know him.
Right?
Yes.
I don't know him at all.
He's a top player.
Yes, yes.
So, we'll see who wins.
We have to make this clear.
And if you lose, what will you do?
I'll be punished.
This time it's amazing.
What is it?
It's a huge spectacle.
This punishment game.
That's right.
You always say it yourself, but you don't do it yourself.
I don't really care about that.
This time it's amazing.
What is it?
Right?
Skydiving.
It's really high.
This is it.
I'll do my best.
I don't want to.
I really don't want to do it.
If you lose, it's a punishment game.
You can't say, I did it.
I'll do something I don't want to do.
If you lose, I'll do something I don't want to do.
I won't stop.
I'll do it.
Really?
Yes.
I'll do it.
Alone?
Yes.
You'll do it alone?
I'll do it.
I really don't want to do it.
If I do it, I'll do it with a sheet.
You're really something.
This is interesting.
What is it?
If I do it with a sheet...
I don't go to high places at all.
Really?
If you do it, you can do that.
You can do it with a jump rope.
Moreover, you can open it with this part.
I'll die.
If you don't agree with it...
It's scary.
It's really scary.
If you don't do that...
There are wide places.
If you run like this...
There are a lot of fish.
Are you stupid?
There's a scene in Kamen Rider.
That's a dead horse.
If you just say, go through here...
You can run there.
That's not interesting.
You're stupid.
There's a road in the movie.
You can walk on the edge.
That's cool.
If you go to the toilet...
You have to poop.
It's dirty.
If you go to the toilet...
You have to poop.
That's cool.
It's not cool.
But it's not scary.
It's not scary.
But it's not cool.
I think that's better.
If you go like this...
That's better.
That's the opening.
You're stupid.
Why did you put them together?
This time, it's the best.
That's the best.
You're stupid.
What's the best?
The one who loses.
I don't want to do it.
It's impossible to do it alone.
Who's going to do it?
I'll do it.
The one who follows me.
And you'll do it.
I'll do it.
I won't do it.
I won't say it's okay.
But it's better than doing it alone.
Which one?
I'll do it or not?
Wait.
Don't say it like I'll do it.
If you lose, you'll do it.
If I lose, I'll do it too.
You really do it?
Yes.
I'll do it.
But in my case...
I can't bend my joints.
I can't bend it like this.
Why?
I'm a doll.
What?
Do it properly.
Well...
But seriously, let's do it together.
Let's do it together.
But it's not fun if we do it together.
It's fun to do it alone.
I'll do it with animals.
No!
I'll do it with a lot of animals.
Don't be noisy.
It's not scary.
I'll do it with a hand.
Yes.
It's still a little better.
I'll do it with animals.
In the end, we'll all be dumb.
We'll all wear pianos.
We'll all be like this.
You'll be the only one who can do it.
The difficulty isn't the highest.
It's just a little bit.
It's like a beginner class.
Let's do it like that.
So, let's start with one person.
Yeah.
Let's start with one person.
It's Suga or Saito.
So, sorry.
I said Suga or Saito.
All the staff will be 9 o'clock.
Right?
Yeah.
The staff will be 9 o'clock.
It doesn't matter if you're wrong.
That's right.
Right?
The sound engineer, lighting engineer, the artist, the cameraman, and Tokyo.
Everyone will be 9 o'clock.
Everyone.
Make-up artists and stylists.
If you're wrong, the crane will give you a sponge.
It's not a trial.
If you're wrong, I'll be waiting for you downstairs.
I'll put a lot of forks in the ground.
Hey!
I'll be waiting for you when you go.
That's right.
So, it's decided.
Yeah.
It's decided.
So, which one will win?
I bet that there will be an all-star this year.
That's wrong!
There won't be!
Definitely!
Well, this is the first place.
Yes, yes.
It's not certain that all of them will come out, but...
At first, these people will come out, and then the others will come in.
I got it.
So, which one will come out?
If I'm wrong...
Paris!
It's my turn.
Huh?
Paris!
It's my turn.
Now, it's your turn.
Definitely!
It's the first match!
Huh?
What?
At the end of the first match...
Why?
Why didn't you show it to me earlier?
While listening to the radio.
Ah, I lost!
Why are you holding the ribbon?
That's right.
I'll do it too.
You do it too.
The moment I know I lost, I'll jump down.
When is this?
Paris...
Huh?
When is the Japan Series?
Japan Series?
It's the All-Star!
You don't know anything!
When is the Japan Series?
It's the All-Star!
When is the All-Star?
July 24th.
It's soon.
It's already decided by the time of this broadcast.
Really?
That's right.
It's already decided by the time of this broadcast.
If that's the case...
Alright, the postcards!
Alright.
I don't like this.
I think I'll quit.
I have to introduce her.
I'm a bit late, but...
This person is...
I think I'll quit this program.
It's a rare name.
It's Chunko Chinonene.
She lives at Itabashi, Tokyo.
Are you siblings?
How old are you?
Who's your big sister?
Hamada is my big sister.
You...
Thank you.
Which one is prettier, you or your sister?
I see.
Thank you very much.
A college student.
When you went to a hotel with your girlfriend during your high school days, I heard that there was a fire at that hotel.
Is that true?
If it's true, please tell us more about it.
Please tell us more about it.
This was the first time...
It was the first time when I had a crush on someone.
There was a fire.
On New Year's Day, I went to a hotel at Umeda.
The name of the hotel was Diamond.
Don't say the name.
The inside of the hotel was very dirty.
When I went in, the stand was exposed.
There was no umbrella.
At first, it was strange that the stand had an umbrella.
But when I went in, the light bulb came out.
I thought I was going to faint, so I took a shower.
But the light bulb was shining, right?
That's right.
Because it was only the light bulb.
I hugged her with my strong arms.
I hugged her and said, come here.
Who is acting like that?
It's just a story.
I'm sure the girl was ready.
I know. I know.
I know.
It was a funny story.
Stop it.
I know.
It's a story.
Don't talk too much.
I know.
I understand.
You are so funny.
I know.
Let's go!
You're the one who said it
No...
That's why...
This is the first kiss I've seen with my parents
No...
What are you talking about?
Don't look at me
Aren't you an idiot?
I'm going to...
Don't talk nonsense!
We're going to be naked
Women are going to take off their clothes
Don't talk like that
I'm going to take off my clothes
Why are you taking off your clothes?
You're sweating
This is how you take off your clothes
It's very hard
It's a very hard way
This is very funny
I'm laughing but I can take it off more
That's enough
I'm going to take out the mannequin from my bag
It's not good if it breaks
I'm going to do it
You're going to do it
The girl is not talking
I'm going to do it
I'm definitely going to do it
The girl is gone
The mannequin is gone again
I'm done
You're going to fall
Then
The girl is going to say
She's embarrassed
That's right
Even if she says it
She's happy
She's going to say she doesn't want to do it
I convinced her
As much as I can
I like it when it's bright
I convinced her
With my strawberry talk
It's a sweet and sour talk
I see
Even so, the girl still doesn't like it
Right?
I couldn't help it
So I put on a new YG shirt
I put it on the mannequin
The YG of Gunse
It's just the right size
I see
I said, if I do this, I can leave it to you
Right?
So I said, okay, I got it
That's how our relationship started
Then, after a while
The girl started crying
I thought you had something good
I thought I had something good
I've never seen a girl cry this much
Right?
It's not like that
The girl said her eyes hurt
When I think about it, I'm crying too
The two of them are crying
Right?
Their eyes hurt
When I saw it, the room was full of smoke
When I stood up, my YG was burning
I opened the window and it was so bright
The sun was so bright that it could be seen on the bed
I poured water on it
I managed to hold it together
That was my first experience
What happened after that?
After that, the two of them burned
It's been a while since we played a game
We decided on a punishment game
You said something great
Now that I think about it
I'm really scared
But I have an idea
What?
When I go up and get pushed down, my body becomes like a ball
I don't want to go back
The All-Stars lost the first game
You go to Paris, I go to Céline
The one who loses will dive
Right?
Yes
So that's how it is
But it's so high
I'm scared
This is the first and last punishment game
I can't do it
You can't do it
What if the parachute doesn't open?
You
From now on, I'm going to go to the pet shop every day
I'm going to kiss a lot of my friends
You're going to ask for help?
I'm going to get them together
I'm going to jump with two people
I don't want to say it
Then you should stop
I have a letter, a question, and an assistant
I have a lot of letters
Thank you for watching
See you next week
Thank you for your viewing