The usual music shop, a small town with a calm atmosphere and a stop.
But today, there is a feeling of something.
Excuse me, somebody has blocked my man's car outside.
Who wants to know who it is?
Yeah, I gotta go somewhere. I got something to do.
You gotta go to work. His car.
BMW has been stopped.
Who has a wife?
Somebody is blocking my car.
BMW has been blocked.
Who are you to say that?
Okay, okay, I'm sorry.
What?
BMW has been blocked.
I think it's him, man.
You blocking the car?
Black BMW. White Toyota.
Sorry, sorry.
Very sorry, kid.
Let's go, let's go.
Very sorry.
What?
Let's go. Come on.
We're waiting too.
Hurry up.
Okay, okay.
You.
I left it there.
You're so pathetic.
You guys are so pathetic.
When was it?
It's been there all the time.
You're like, let's take it, let's take it.
You came right away.
You saved me.
You guys are so lame.
You can sing that song.
BMW has been blocked.
It's my fault.
I apologized.
Why are you apologizing?
It's my fault.
Hey!
What are you doing?
The picture, the picture.
I'm just saying I'm scared because a foreigner came.
Stop it, Masaki.
Stop it.
Hey.
Apologize.
Sorry, sorry.
Stop it, stop it.
What are you doing, Okamoto-san?
That's why I'm going to teach you Okamoto Hangar 5 Shinju today.
What?
The brief
Manager Okamoto is angry again.
Hangar 5 Shinju
Shinju development
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
I'm going to do it now.
Do it yourself.
What?
Why are you making it?
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
What are you doing?
Break the balloon with this.
Break the balloon?
With this?
Who are you?
You can't break it with this.
How to break it?
It's really hard.
You can't break it with this.
You have to be more energetic.
Be more energetic.
I'll show you how to break it.
You are fatter than Hong Kong.
It's different from Shinju.
I'm getting hungry.
Okamoto has changed.
Shinju development
Next.
I'll show you when someone attacks you.
Slowly.
I'll make it easy to understand.
Ouch.
I'm scared.
Are you ok?
Next.
I'll show you how to break a gun.
There is no gun.
Damn it.
What's wrong with you?
I'll show you how to break a gun.
I think you can do it.
I'll show you how to break a candle.
Ouch.
What's wrong with you?
My heart is beating.
I'll show you how to break a gun.
I'll help you.
With a hammer?
This is the only way to break a gun.
You can't do it with a hammer.
Cool.
I'll show you how to break a octopus.
It's a octopus.
Is it an octopus?
Is it a octopus?
I'll help you.
It's touching.
Why do you have such a voice sometimes?
Who is Shibattan?
It's an octopus.
Octopus is Shibattan?
Octopus is Shibattan.
That's enough.
You're mixing it with the hangar.
Why?
Where should I go in?
It's too far.
It's too far for a beautiful woman.
I'll go from here.
Yes, please.
You're passing in front of me.
Where is the hangar?
I forgot the hangar.
I'll fix the hangar.
You guys should try it.
What should we do with the hangar?
I'll fix the hangar.
It's too far.
It's too far for a beautiful woman.
No, it's OK.
You're using the hangar as a handle.
Yes, it's a handle.
I thought it would be a rope.
What's with that face?
Watch it.
Let's go.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Today's live is terrible.
It's the worst.
It's been a long time.
I have a headache.
I thought I was going to die.
I don't know what to do.
I woke up with a headache last night.
I have a headache.
The day before yesterday?
The day before yesterday.
I have a headache.
I know when it's raining.
It's been raining for three days.
Yes.
I have a headache.
No.
What you say and what you do are different.
It's like a scene play.
Let's go to the dentist.
You're fast.
I'm not fast.
This is my personal opinion.
Personal opinion?
You're here after the opening.
I see.
I had a fight with someone.
Who?
A member of the video?
Yes.
Can you go to the video?
Of course.
Can you write the address?
Can you write the phone number?
I can write the office number.
You can't write it.
I'm a talent.
But there are people who write the address in the video.
Yes.
That's enough.
You have a broken face.
You can't run away.
I was very angry.
You have a broken jaw.
Not only in the front, but in the side.
Please listen to me.
I'm a talent.
No matter how much money I have.
Of course, if I'm an amateur, I write everything.
I can't do that.
I became a member of Yamanaki.
That's good.
I took the money.
I was beaten.
I said, what?
I can't lend money to you.
I was angry.
I said, wait.
Why don't you understand that I'm not Yamazaki?
I know about you.
It's a woman, isn't it?
I know about you, too.
I don't understand.
It's a woman.
That's good.
I may be taking the money, so I probably have to say it.
But my face is cracked.
I know that I'm not Yamazaki.
Yamazaki is a talent.
You probably know Yamazaki too, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
Right?
Eh?
What?
Yes, yes, yes.
You know me, and you know Yamazaki too?
Yes.
Why don't you lend it to me?
Pah!
Moreover, there are so many down-to-earth videos in the world!
It's not such a bad thing!
I'll throw it away!
I don't want to live!
If you throw it away, you won't be able to grow up!
And then, I went out!
I'm already 33 years old.
When I went out, I was a little annoyed.
Why?
These days, the automatic door is like this, right?
The timing is bad!
Are you there?
Why?
You can't just go like this!
You can open and close the door like this!
Are you there?
What's going on?
Did you stop properly?
I lied a little, didn't I?
What are you talking about?
If you say it in detail, I think it's more correct.
That's right.
Right?
That's right!
What is it?
Did you sing?
No, that's not it.
It's strange, isn't it?
The part-time worker also has a lot of money, isn't it?
Even if you just go, you're smiling a little, aren't you?
I'm smiling, I'm smiling.
You're smiling, aren't you?
Can you tell such a guy his address?
It's a little funny.
It's a little funny, isn't it?
The guy in a different store also looks like this.
The guy in a different store is also a little funny.
What are you talking about?
I'm not talking to you!
I'm talking to you!
I'm angry.
I'm angry, too.
Even if you go shopping, if you order something big, it will be delivered, right?
What do you buy big things?
Do you buy such expensive things?
It's not expensive.
What?
It's very cheap.
Is that true?
It's true!
What is it?
It's very cheap.
Such as a toilet board.
What do you do with a toilet board?
You can't use it in such a situation.
You can't use it.
It's hard.
But you can't bring it to me.
That's right.
You can't bring it to me.
That's why I used to buy a phone once.
I went to the employee there.
You went to play?
That's right.
Wow!
Isn't it?
You played?
No.
What?
I played a little.
Don't pinch me.
I can't teach you.
What did you do with the past?
How did you bring the various things in your house?
I can't say that.
Then do it like that.
No, no, no.
I can't write my address.
I can't put it in.
That's a thing that can be brought home.
This is the sad part of talent.
Even if you want a sofa like this, you can't bring it home.
You have to buy a sofa like this.
Is it like this?
At home...
A sofa is fine.
Why did you come all the way here?
What are you doing?
I'm using the remote control of the TV.
It's so small.
It's really hard.
If you say that, what are you going to do about the delivery?
I can't even eat pizza.
But you've been ordering pizza for a long time, haven't you?
That's not good.
I like it when it's halved in the middle.
The taste is different.
I like it when it looks like it's been cooked.
I like it.
I eat it often.
You're a parasite.
What you're saying is different from what you're doing.
I remembered the delivery.
When you bring the delivery, you have to sing.
I can't sing anymore.
I can't sing.
It doesn't sound like the delivery.
The delivery was yesterday.
Who was it?
I brought the delivery.
I was on TV all morning.
You're on TV all morning.
You know, there are two guys who are obviously in a relationship with each other.
They have a little quarrel with each other.
They even accept each other.
Isn't that strange?
They are obviously in a relationship with each other.
Do you think the other guy is in a relationship with you?
And do you know that the other guy knows about your relationship with him?
No, but if they are in a relationship with each other, they should be able to understand each other.
That's strange.
Mr. Matsumoto is actually a single man.
What are the other five guys doing now?
As I thought, they are all in a relationship with each other.
I'm the eldest.
I have five more children.
One of them is a woman.
All of them are not men.
One, two, three.
I don't want to say two.
One, two, three, four, five.
What are you doing?
What are the other five guys doing?
I'm the captain.
What are you doing?
All of them are the same age?
Yes, all of them are the same age.
There are still five guys who are 33 years old.
That's right.
Are you the captain?
Yes, I am.
What's your position?
I'm the fourth.
Why did you suddenly change your position?
I'm the fifth.
You are in a relationship with each other.
What about your younger brother?
I'm the second.
I don't know if it's a family picture.
All of them have their own signs.
I see.
They go their own way.
What are you doing?
What are the other two guys doing?
I'm in a relationship with each other.
You can't do that.
You are in a relationship with each other.
I'm in a relationship with each other.
What?
I don't want you to say anything about the other two guys.
I heard it for the first time.
I'm sorry.
Don't say anything about the other two guys.
I will not say anything about the other two.
What's your position?
I'm the fourth.
You are in a relationship with each other.
What are you doing?
I'm in a relationship with each other.
Are you in a marriage?
Where did you do it?
At the JAL.
JAL?
JAL.
At the JAL.
At the JAL?
I'm sorry.
I turned the door mode on at the JAL.
That's because you were announced.
I'm doing it even though I'm not announced.
That's not good.
Everyone will jump out.
That's because you're great.
If you're great, you shouldn't do it even more.
That's selfish.
I think I turned it off.
It doesn't matter if you turn it on or off.
I'm doing it happily.
Mitsuko is a four-legged pilot.
She's a four-legged pilot.
She's the fifth.
She's amazing now.
Next time...
I don't know if I should say this.
I'll say Atlanta next time.
In the sushi restaurant, you can tell the order of the dishes by the order you order them.
What should I order first so that I can't be underestimated at the sushi restaurant where I go for the first time?
Do you want to go to the sushi restaurant?
I go there once in a while.
You only go there once in a while.
I like sushi very much.
You should tell me what you want to eat first.
Welcome.
First of all, octopus.
That's a new half.
First of all, let's eat a big fatty tuna.
Sushi is the same as martial arts.
It's definitely different.
Welcome. What do you want to eat?
I'll eat a big fatty tuna.
When I say the word, it comes out like this.
You said octopus earlier.
Octopus.
When I say the word, it comes out like this.
You can't underestimate it.
What kind of attack is that?
I see.
First of all, it's Otoro.
If it's Otoro, it means that I also pulled it out like this.
It's done.
What should I do next?
And then you dig it into the rope.
Why?
Because the next order is coming.
Digging into the rope.
What do you mean by digging into the rope?
After Otoro?
After Otoro, yes.
Digging, digging into the rope.
What's the next order?
Shrimp.
Shrimp?
That's what a masked wrestler would do.
Why?
You dig into the rope and then pull it out.
You're just doing it on your own.
I can't do it.
If it's a stubborn old man, he'll get angry.
What's that?
What are you going to do after you eat Otoro and get thrown out of the rope?
When I come back...
What?
Otoro.
This is unexpected.
What do you want me to do?
This is the hard part.
The person over there is scared.
I didn't think Otoro would come twice.
That's right.
I thought Otoro would eat a lot of sushi.
That's what I thought.
I see.
What's the third order?
What?
It's time.
It's not time.
It's not raw.
It's impossible.
It's not impossible.
It's not raw.
It's a gift corner.
What is this?
Hangar goldfish.
You're not going to wash it, are you?
Ouch!
What is this?
What kind of play is this?
Ouch!
Are you really going to do it?
I'm sorry.
Did you lose your shoulder again?
I'll do it underwater again.
I'm sorry.
I'm not going to dance.
You're not going to dance?
What?
It's in!
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.