Last week's broadcast
I happened to watch your broadcast last week
You talked a lot last week
You talked for almost an hour
But you didn't have 10 minutes for the broadcast
So, this week's Gaki no Tsukai is very interesting, but I can't broadcast it
I will show you a lot of unreleased talk
Gaki no Tsukai, the best unreleased talk show
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching
First of all, from this unreleased talk, there is an incident in Matsuo's room
I have something I can't forgive
There was a time when I moved
It's not a good place
It's my first time to welcome summer
I had a bad feeling when I moved
As summer approached, I watched Bokiburi
It's not a good place
What is it? Is it money?
No, it's a building
It's expensive
It's expensive, but it's about 200,000 yen
It's amazing if it's 200,000 yen
It can't be 200,000 yen
I'm listening
I understand
Let's talk about the house
Which one is amazing?
I want you to listen
You live alone
You don't live with your family
Let me explain
I was shocked when I saw a cockroach
Was it a big cockroach?
Yes, it was
I saw a few cockroaches
They were gone
I looked at the kitchen
It was huge
I had killed it before
It ran away under the refrigerator
I couldn't kill it
I don't live alone
I understand
But I can't communicate with it
I wanted to live alone
You killed it
I couldn't kill it
I saw a cockroach
I didn't like it
I did it for that
I did my best
I lived in a place like this
Why did I see a cockroach?
It's strange
I did it for that
It's hard
There is another house in the kitchen
It's your house
This space is your house
I spend money in his house every month
I don't know if it's good or bad
But I spend money in his house
You have money so you can move
Is that so?
What are you talking about?
I really don't like it
I'll move the refrigerator
It will move
What are you talking about?
I'm more sensitive to cockroaches than normal people
Everyone is
When I was a kid, cockroaches were amazing
My parents
The floor was moving
It was terrible
I put a water pillow on the pillar
All the cockroaches were hiding behind the water pillow
There is no mistake that the cockroaches live here
We gathered all the newspapers
All my family
My father said, let's move the water pillow
We moved the water pillow
All the cockroaches were hiding behind the water pillow
I was a good kid
All my family was crying
I was crying
I wanted to say goodbye to the cockroaches
So I did my best
But there are still cockroaches
It's scary, isn't it?
It's okay
You haven't seen it since then, have you?
It was two or three days ago
It's amazing
At night
I was rapping
It was moving
I have a great appetite
You know a lot
You were a good kid
My family had a lot of cockroaches and cicadas
I'm sorry I didn't say it
There was a cat, it wasn't a cat
It was a cicada
I said it was a cicada
It was a cat
It wasn't a cat, it was a cicada
Throw it away
In summer, I said it was a cicada
It was a cicada and I was wearing a collar
It was a black one
My brother was surprised
His face was like this
He said it was a cicada
It was a cicada
Because all the cicadas eat here
All of my family members were from here.
It was amazing.
So even if I went to the pool or the beach with my family,
they wouldn't recognize me even if I was looking at them from behind.
Oh, it's my dad.
Oh, it's my big brother.
I've never made a mistake.
When I looked at them, they were all eating.
What a poor family.
I don't have any drinking friends.
I'm sure you're okay.
I can't forgive the bugs in my house.
You might think, why are you here?
I don't know.
There are spiders here.
You shouldn't kill spiders.
They're all over the place.
I'm taking care of the spiders.
Let them go!
I don't want to kill them.
You don't want to kill the spiders?
Where's the time?
Where are the morning people?
I don't know!
You can come back and kill the spiders.
But the man in the bath is there.
I'll take the spiders away.
I went swimming once.
I got a spider when the water was too hot.
He was trying not to get caught, but he fell, and he was spinning in the bath tub where the hot water was flowing.
I said, no!
Why did you use that?
Because I wanted to kill him.
You shouldn't have let him go.
I shouldn't have let him go.
But he was spinning.
You shouldn't have let him go.
So I hit him on the other side.
Why?
And he was still in the bath.
He was still coming this way.
Why was he trying to die?
Because I wanted to kill him.
It's okay.
But I'm moving.
You're moving?
How much money do you have?
I have a lot of money.
You're so nice.
It's okay.
If it's like this, I'll open it.
The animal lover Matsumoto is taking pictures of a stupid dog.
I want you to tell me about animals.
I heard that lazy people don't get off the tree until they die.
But if you get off the tree, what will happen?
What will happen if you get off the tree?
I'm sure you've never seen a lazy person get off the tree, right?
I think I'm the only one who's seen it.
I saw it when I went over there.
Where?
When I went to Europe.
Europe?
A little further from Europe.
I saw it completely.
That's funny.
You saw it when you got off the tree?
I saw it when I got off the tree.
Do you know what happened?
I know.
I think I thought no one was watching.
When people are watching, they care about their character.
So they never get off the tree.
That's right.
Most animals are conscious because people are watching.
I'm a cat, so I have to be a cat.
I do this and that.
When people don't get off the tree, they're already dead.
Your face is just funny.
Yes, that's true.
You're a lazy person.
I saw a lazy person getting off the tree.
What are you doing?
I was getting off the tree.
Yes.
When I got off the tree, I looked around.
You looked around.
How long have I been doing this?
I got off the tree.
I was looking at the tree like this.
What are you doing?
I see.
I was hitting the tree.
That's about it.
It was really fun to see it live.
It's been a long time since I've laughed so hard.
I'm glad.
I went to the countdown TV the other day.
At that time, I and you...
I knew that the staff who had never worked before were scared.
That's not true.
There are five pipe seats.
Five is the number of members.
There was a soft sofa next to the pipe chair.
I didn't know that.
What does that mean?
The other members told me to sit in the pipe chair.
I thought I would go crazy if I had seven pipe chairs.
This is the end of the broadcast.
Actually, there's a talk after this.
I have to get rid of this image.
So don't make such a face.
That's right.
Let's stop it.
Even if it rains, when I get out of the car and go to the studio,
I'm only three meters away from the car, but I'm hit by an umbrella.
I'm hit by an umbrella.
You will be hit.
Really?
Can't you do that?
I'm sick while doing this.
Who sticks an umbrella like this?
Most people do it.
I always tell them to stop.
I always tell them to hold it if they want to stick an umbrella.
I don't want to talk about it anymore.
If I try to take it again, I'll be scared.
I don't like it when people on the other side pay attention to me.
I see.
It's amazing when I put on a microphone.
I've been told many times that I'm sorry.
There's nothing to be sorry about.
I'm really sorry.
It's true.
I've been told many times that I'm sorry.
But I have a little bit of a knife in me.
Yes.
I'm sorry to say this, but I have a knife in me.
The other day, I talked about Tsurube's show.
I don't have to say it.
I'm being treated like that.
I'm being treated like I'm trying to make a good image.
That's annoying.
I don't care.
I see.
Which side are you on?
I'm against it.
I don't want you to come here.
You should fight with yourself.
That's right.
I'll go.
Thank you very much.
I think her parents are watching TV, too.
I think they'll call me and ask,
Why are you on the show?
I don't know how to explain it.
I didn't do anything.
It's a flow.
You'll understand when you watch it.
I don't know her parents.
That's right.
The other day, there was a party at Itao's house.
What did her family think?
They were shocked.
That's right.
We're crazy, aren't we?
We talk about silly things.
I don't like that.
I don't know what it is, but Itao's wife has been taking care of her father.
I don't know.
I don't like that kind of clothes.
She wants to be sexy.
I don't like that.
I don't like her father.
I'm going to change my hair color.
I'll go back and see what happens next.
I don't like it.
I went to karaoke and changed my clothes.
Thank you for today.
I'll take this.
When the ticket was split in half at the academy and Cannes,
I asked Mr. Matsumoto who decided the prize by putting the ticket in the end.
The Hollywood version of Godzilla is a completely different thing from the Japanese Godzilla.
What kind of Godzilla would you like to see in the Matsumoto version?
I was asked a big question.
Is Godzilla completely different?
The face is completely different.
Godzilla is very aggressive.
Godzilla?
You've seen most of the video, haven't you?
Godzilla is very aggressive.
I want to see it.
I want to see the gorilla.
If you're going to shoot this time,
I'll be the director.
What kind of Godzilla would you like to see?
I imitated Tanaka Kakuen.
I just said, well.
I want to convey it.
I make movies while communicating.
It's hard to imitate someone you don't know.
But you want to use a person with a name, right?
If you think so, I'll ask you to do Mothra.
As you can see from the Hollywood version of Godzilla,
It doesn't matter.
If you don't reverse the previous one, it doesn't make sense.
If you're going to do Mothra, you're Mothra.
You don't have to do anything.
What do you mean?
Well, I'm...
No, no, no.
You're wearing something.
I'm wearing my own clothes.
No, no, no.
Wait a minute.
What?
Say Mothra.
I'll do it like this.
No, I'm...
I'm saying Mothra.
I don't do anything.
No, no, no. Wait a minute.
It's not big.
Just like this?
It's Mothra.
Mothra 3.
If everyone says Mothra,
It's Mothra.
You're Mothra.
I'll do it normally.
I see.
How about this?
It's okay.
Let's say I'm your version of Mothra.
Yes.
What about Godzilla?
That's a real Godzilla.
That's...
That's a little weird, isn't it?
Why?
I'm Mothra.
I'm saying Mothra.
Godzilla like this...
It's a big monster.
Godzilla vs. Mothra, right?
I'm saying Mothra.
Godzilla doesn't know Mothra.
That's why the shell is here.
It's okay if it's a big monster.
It's on the screen.
It's about the same as Godzilla.
There's a cut scene.
It's okay.
You'll take a picture of the same thing, right?
I'll take it.
For example, if it's an X-ray, people will say,
I'm Mothra or Godzilla.
I'm just walking around.
I'm not being told anything.
Look at Godzilla.
The person who runs away comes like this.
You're like this.
But I'm scared, so I don't run away.
That's Mothra.
Godzilla is like this.
But I can't do anything.
How interesting.
You've had a lot of women turn their backs on you.
Yes.
How did you get them to turn their backs on you?
This is amazing.
If this is true,
everyone is turning their backs on you.
You're just not aware of it.
Tell me how you do it.
You go like this.
You came from far away.
You get off the train and get off in front of Hachikoa.
You go like this.
This is Asakusa.
I understand that.
The way is like this.
You go like this.
I'm sorry.
Don't bite when I say this.
But I'm turning my back on you.
I see.
You're turning your back on me for a reason.
But that's what everyone says.
Hachikoa isn't like Asakusa.
I'm not turning my back on you.
Really?
If I were you, I'd be more stupid.
You're funny.
You're more stupid than I am.
I'm not like Asakusa in Shibuya.
When I'm alone at home, I'm really stupid.
When I was alone at home, I walked like this.
I'm totally free.
No one laughs.
I came here again.
It was very interesting.
Let's make a song together.
Fujiwara is amazing.
That's true.
He was working in our apartment.
He was noisy and hard to sleep.
But that doesn't matter to Fujiwara.
It's a normal conversation.
Fujiwara was noisy today, too.
It doesn't matter to Fujiwara.
It's a normal conversation.
I'm sorry.
This is the end of the broadcast.
After this, there will be unexpected developments.
I don't want to be treated like that.
I want Fujiwara to call me Machan.
That's not true.
If Fujiwara says that, I can't do it.
I can't do it.
That's okay.
After this, I can't be called Machan.
I don't care at all.
I want to be kicked in the ass.
This is the end of the broadcast.
I don't want to be treated like that.
You're biting me.
Machan, you're tired.
If you kick me, I'll kick you.
I wanted you to kick me.
Machan, you're tired.
I'm sorry.
Kick me now.
I want to be kicked in the ass.
I'll come to see you again.
If I have a chance like this again, I would like to come.
Thank you very much.