Aim for the ace!
In the previous episode, you said you could play both.
I said I could play both.
Yes, that's right.
Today, I will show you how to play both.
I think that you don't know what tennis is.
It's a game of violence.
Is that so?
Yes.
Tennis is a game of violence.
Yes, it's a game of violence.
The stronger you grab the ball, the better.
When I play tennis, I have a lot of violence.
How do you feel?
Can I play a big game?
Yes.
It's soft.
I'm serious.
Really?
Yes.
Let's do it.
Please show us.
Please come in.
I heard that if you play tennis for a long time, you will become a tiger.
No, I won't.
The program is different.
Let's do it.
Give it back to me.
When I play Wimbledon, you should shut up.
Shut up.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Shut up.
He is not good at imitating.
Hamada will do it.
When you come here, you have to break it.
Yes.
You have to take it back.
You have to break it.
Can I do it?
It's OK.
Really?
Yes.
Let's do it.
Move forward.
Take it by hand.
It's too fast.
Can you do it?
Take it by hand.
I heard that our passion to play tennis is connected.
The god of tennis came to us.
He is here.
He told us to aim for him.
Where is he?
He will be taken away.
What if we aim for him?
Even if the ball comes?
Yes.
It doesn't hurt at all.
Really?
Let's do it.
Did you say like this?
No, no.
It means that he is happy.
It's the god of tennis.
No, no.
It's a prank.
Where is the god of tennis?
Actually, that is the servant of the god.
Really?
The real god is someone else.
Is he here today?
Yes, he is.
Really?
Where is the god of tennis?
He is here.
I'm so happy.
Nice to meet you.
He is different from the servant of the god.
The servant of the god is proud.
Yes, he is.
It's strong.
It's enough.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
I'm sorry, servant of the god.
Where is the god of tennis?
He is still alive.
I'm the god of tennis.
I won't appear.
I declare it.
Then, I'll dance for a while.
What is tennis?
Ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you very much.
It's been a long time.
Yes.
This program has become popular recently.
Today, there are three groups.
Yes, there are three groups.
Yes.
I don't think so, but it's getting hot.
I don't say that because I want to relax.
I don't say that because I don't want to relax.
I can't rest in summer.
I don't like summer in this program.
Yes.
I hate summer the most.
Why do you hate summer?
Because it's sticky.
Yes, it's sticky.
My body is also tired.
Yes.
I think it's okay because it has a cooler.
My cooler isn't cool, but sometimes it smells like a Kintama bag.
I'm not Kintama bag.
Wait a minute.
I'm a Kintama bag.
There is! There is!
What kind of smell is that?
The smell of a golden egg?
What do you want?
Don't you know the smell of a golden egg?
What kind of smell is that?
Ah, it's so close that I can smell you.
I'm just kidding.
You don't know the smell, do you?
I know the smell.
Even the air conditioner in a car sometimes smells like that.
That's a different kind of smell.
Yeah, that's the smell.
That's the smell?
That's the smell of a golden egg?
Even in the air conditioner, it comes out and stops for a moment.
You're making fun of me, aren't you?
I'm so worn out.
No, no, no.
What kind of air conditioner do you use?
I use any kind of air conditioner.
When it comes out, it's kind of...
It has a bad smell, doesn't it?
Yes, yes.
A smelly smell.
That's the smell of a golden egg.
Is that so?
I think that the people in the electrical industry are very excited right now.
They seem to be using that bag in the material of the air conditioner.
What?
What is it?
That's why...
Maybe...
Why are you asking in such a small voice?
The bag is inside the air conditioner.
The golden egg bag is inside the bag.
Whose golden egg bag is that?
It belongs to the people who committed suicide.
What kind of...
The real golden egg...
Did you say that?
That's the material that comes out of the air conditioner.
That sounds good.
What are you talking about?
What are you looking at?
You...
Have you been talking for a long time?
Are you the king of Samurai?
You're wearing glasses.
You're a new comedian.
Get out of here!
That's dangerous.
You're going to get robbed.
That's strange.
You're going to get a tattoo on your neck.
That's different.
What were you doing?
What did you smell?
I was eating.
Really?
Let me see.
That's amazing.
What are you doing?
A group of hypocrites.
Matsumaru is like this.
Hamamaru is like this.
What are you doing?
I told you.
It's a special flash gag.
That's funny.
What is this?
It's like moving.
It's the same one that appeared in the last episode.
You're so cool.
I'm going to return this.
It's so frustrating.
I'm going to return it.
It's strange.
It's written here.
Please continue.
It's amazing.
Please show me your letter.
Hello.
Taiko Hoshino.
I'm 43 years old.
I'm 22 years old.
My hobby is to play with cats.
No.
You can play with cats.
Yes, a little.
It's amazing.
Is it a book?
It's a book.
It's broken.
Thank you very much.
What is this?
Well...
Marukome, the 8th generation.
It's a big reward.
Right?
I'm going to write it down.
Name, date of birth,
address, phone number, guardian.
I'm going to send you a picture.
The audition is on June 14th.
No.
It doesn't have to be me.
I said it doesn't have to be me.
You're completely different.
You don't speak a word.
The word doesn't have to be me.
What?
I don't care.
Write it down.
Look at this.
Write down the 8th generation Marukome.
I'm going to be on TV like this.
You're already on TV.
That's enough.
You're a healthy boy from 3 to 6 years old.
That's right.
Can you do this?
It's okay.
I don't know if there will be a special movie.
Choose a child from 3 to 6 years old as usual.
Moreover, when you stand next to him and run with that kid.
At the end of July.
I will become a bald man.
I don't know if I will be chosen.
Before I become a bald man.
I have to become a bald man.
Then you have to do something.
Right?
From the beginning.
I don't know if I can stay until the end.
Don't think about it.
It's okay if you go.
For the time being, let's go.
What are you going to do when I go?
I will go with you.
Your mother is coming.
What?
Your mother.
I will go with my mother.
I will put on makeup properly.
I will become a bald man.
I will go with you.
I want to go with you.
It's you.
It's okay if you become a bald man.
Are you kidding me?
It's true.
Don't make fun of me.
It's been 10 years since you became a bald man.
What?
It's okay.
Write it down.
Don't make fun of me.
It's your name.
Is it your real name?
No.
It's your real name.
It's annoying.
Write it down.
I will give it to you.
I brought it.
It's annoying.
I will put a picture next to it.
It's a guardian.
Who is the guardian?
Write my name.
I am protected by you.
I am fine.
It's okay.
I will put a picture next to it and send it to you.
Don't do this.
You should do this.
What will you do?
I will write it down.
You should do this.
You are an amateur CM character.
I don't do that.
I'll send it to Alusjin.
No, you can look at it.
No, no, no, don't say it.
I'm too old.
So, I wrote it down.
I'll send it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Now, let's go to the postcard.
This girl is pitiful.
This girl is a special girl.
She is from Tokyo.
Is it called Tatekawashi?
Tatekawashi.
You guys are too much.
Everyone knows that Tatekawashi is from Tokyo.
Tatekawashi.
This is the second time.
No, no, no.
I'll never remember it.
I'll call it Tatekawashi until I die.
I can't remember it.
Please listen to the story of the most unfortunate man in Japan.
This man had a surgery on the day before the important university exam.
That's the only thing that's unfortunate.
Even more so, the hospital where he was admitted to became a fire.
While he was evacuating, his wound opened up.
He was finally admitted to the hospital.
Finally, the wound was healed and he was discharged.
When he went back to his home, his house was burned down.
Really?
This is very unfortunate.
The hospital where he was admitted to became a fire.
That's amazing.
I don't know when that man is going to die.
That's why I always say this when I change my clothes.
You should stop wearing black bikinis.
That's just a coincidence.
I don't care because I'm wearing them.
You only look like you're wearing black pants.
That's the only reason.
I don't like wearing trunks.
Why?
Even when I change my pants, if I wear them normally, I look like this. But if I wear them, I look like this.
You look like this.
Even when I change my pants, if I take them off, I look like a bag of candy.
A bag of candy?
That's cool.
There's nothing like that.
There's no one in this world who doesn't want to see my candy.
There is.
I want to see it.
Everyone wants to see it.
Of course they want to see it.
I don't want to see it.
There's no mistake.
I know.
Let's laugh a little more.
I'm going home. Bye bye.
Please forgive me.
It's hot.
But please wait a little longer.
I don't want to buy it.
That's true.
I want to buy it.
No way.
You're kicking someone's butt like that.
What?
Your butt is filled with a very dangerous bomb.
Do you like to say something at the end?
Like, I'm really an angel.
That's a lie.
Actually, my butt is a bomb.
Where is the bomb?
What's wrong?
It's already in here.
In me?
This is a plus and this is a minus.
It's because we're touching each other.
I see.
It's in here.
That's right.
I'm going to light it up.
Ouch!
Wow!
I'm going to do something like that.
My butt is full of nitroglycerin.
I'm going to explode in one shot.
Really?
Is there anything more important than that?
If there is...
Don't make me angry.
What?
If you call me an angel like the other day, I don't know what to do.
I'm going to jump out of here.
Everything I say today is true.
Don't lie.
I'm telling the truth.
Are you an angel or a liar?
I told you before the bomb.
I didn't lie.
I'm telling the truth.
What?
What are you saying?
Ouch!
Don't open it.
Good evening.
I was surprised by the guy who was looking at the notebook today.
I was really surprised by that.
What are you going to do if you become an idiot like that?
You wrote it, didn't you?
The name of the audition paper.
No, I don't know.
Did you write it?
I'll send it to you.
I don't like Marukome or Boss.
I don't like it because it's a holiday.
What?
I don't like the name of the eighth generation.
I was the only one who noticed it.
I don't like it.
But the eighth generation and the first generation...
There are only small people so far.
Do you think my feelings are a little weak?
But you wrote it, didn't you?
I'll send it to you.
I'll do it.
You're going to do something, too.
What?
No, it's okay.
I'll do it.
I'm going to ride a roller coaster.
It doesn't matter.
From top to bottom, free fall.
I'll do it 30 times in a row.
Really?
What?
I got it.
I'll do it five times.
Really?
What?
I'll do it five times.
If you go to Marukome's audition.
I'll do it ten times.
You always say,
Come on, Sugakura.
I'll never do that.
Thank you very much.
It's okay.
I'll ride it all.
I'll do it properly.
Goodbye.
That's a lot.
Let's do it.
This program was provided by the sponsor you see.