A-Generation!
Hey, what's wrong?
My nails are peeling off.
Really?
Yes.
Really? Why?
It hurts a lot.
I got a team fight yesterday.
Really?
Yes.
You should have put something that's not here.
Stop it.
Just coming here is scary.
No, no, no.
That's why...
I'll do it here.
What?
You shouldn't put something that's here.
It hurts here.
I'm wearing a double.
My back hurts too.
I don't know about that.
I can't do it.
You really shouldn't be careful.
I shouldn't be careful.
I'll die.
That's not it.
You should be careful.
You shouldn't be like this.
I don't get it.
I'm worried about you.
When I was doing Ryoma, my nails were like this.
I cut my boots here.
What's this?
I put black magic on my boots.
That's...
You're a genius idiot.
There's a cover on your chest.
You shouldn't do that.
You'll get hurt.
Are you listening?
My back hurts.
I don't care about your black magic.
It's not black magic.
I don't know if you want to say that you did your best.
That's not it.
That's why you're a genius idiot.
It's not the era of Spokon.
Spokon?
It's okay.
Take it off.
I can take it off.
I'll take it off from now on.
You'll get hurt.
I'll get hurt.
You'll die too.
Why?
You're a genius idiot.
No, really.
It's hard.
I can't help it.
What's wrong with your back?
I don't know.
Are you too tired?
I don't use my back much.
What?
Are you a tuna?
That's right.
You're a tuna.
I'm a tuna.
Really?
You're a tuna too.
We're both tuna.
I'm just going to sleep.
My girlfriend is a super tuna.
Why are you angry?
I don't like it.
But I understand that you're a little angry.
It's like you were prepared.
You're saying that I'm not good enough.
I'm not good enough?
Well, well, well.
Don't you think it's a lie?
What?
That I don't have a mirror.
A mirror?
I'm sure it's a lie.
I get it.
I don't need a movie.
If that's the case, buy me a phone.
Tell me what you're talking about.
I'll cut it here.
If you get cut, don't talk.
I want to talk.
You're going to die.
I'm going to kill you.
I'm going to put you in a trunk and take you somewhere.
Mr. Nakamura.
I have a question for the younger brother of the Ultra Brothers.
Yes.
What did the Ultra Father say to his sons every day?
That's true.
If you were the son of the Ultra Brothers, would you call him your father?
My father.
My father used to say that to me.
My father was a strict person.
What was your name?
Ultraman.
What?
Look at your face.
It's not Ultraman.
Ultraman Curry.
What's Ultraman Curry?
I don't know.
I didn't do it on TV.
Ultraman Curry?
Yes.
Why didn't you do it?
It's hard to understand.
Ultraman Curry.
I was told it was okay.
No, of course, the people at the station came.
Always with that hand and this hand.
It's okay.
I'll transform with a pencil case.
Really?
Yes.
Don't do it.
I can't do it with a pencil case.
You can't do it with a pencil case.
I said, whoa!
I can't do it.
I'm bleeding.
It's complicated.
I don't understand why.
I don't have a TV station.
I forgot the name.
D told me.
It's not a TV station.
Curry-kun.
I'm sad.
I'll be there.
It's like a story store.
The boss kept telling me.
For the time being, no matter what you do,
where are you an Ultra?
No matter what you do,
when I'm flying,
I'm like this.
I thought it was like that.
It's different.
For example,
it's a long-distance call.
I'm on a long-distance call.
Hey!
At home.
I'm going to hit you!
That's what he said.
He's an old man.
Do you pay for it yourself?
Wait a minute.
He's an old man.
He's an Ultra.
Hey!
Do you pay for it yourself?
Where are you an Ultra?
That's weird.
I'm going to go blue.
If you tell me that.
You were hated.
You might have been hated.
You were hidden for a long time.
That's not what an old man does.
I'm going to look for it desperately.
That's not there again.
I'm going to look for it in the Ultra.
I don't understand the meaning.
I understand the meaning.
Stop it.
Who is that?
Only curry.
The mother of the Ultra says.
I'm cute even if I'm a curry.
I'm not going to ask you to look for curry.
I'll tell you clearly.
Actually, every year, 24 hours TV broadcast.
I have a question for Matsumoto-san, who keeps running alone.
When Akai scored a goal on 24 hours TV.
What did he say?
Did he involve Japan in the chaos?
I'm nervous when I'm laughing.
I have a lot of tension.
If I tickle him a little, he'll be in trouble.
That's right.
Do you have anything to say?
I have anything to say.
Tell me.
Let's start with the NG word.
I don't usually say this.
Don't say it.
Normally.
What's different about me from normal is.
I dare to say something that's not funny.
Don't say it.
I'll say it.
If you don't say it, you can't see the answer.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Let's go with the NG word.
Akai-san just came back.
When he came.
Peperoncino.
That's the NG word.
You can't say this.
But you can't say this.
I was going to say it before I said it.
Don't go home just because you got it.
Because there was that gesture.
Akai-san's answer is correct.
You can't say Peperoncino.
That's the NG word.
That's correct.
Let's go.
That's the NG word.
Don't you run like this and come up like this?
If you want to do that, it's okay.
I'm wearing a yellow T-shirt.
This is Budokan.
Who are you?
Tokumitsu-san.
I understand.
Okay.
Akai-san.
He hasn't started yet.
He's in the audience seat.
5 seconds left.
4, 3, 2, 1.
Akai-san has arrived at Budokan.
100 km.
Akai-san has finished his 100 km journey.
I'm wearing a yellow T-shirt.
This is...
NG.
That's the NG word.
This is wrong.
I was surprised.
I was surprised too.
I thought you were a magician.
Is that so?
I'm sorry.
I thought you were a magician.
I know you're wearing a yellow T-shirt every year.
I'm sorry.
Really.
I've become a queen.
Who are you?
Who are you now?
It's me.
I'm a live parent.
I thought you were a finished product.
I'm sorry.
Everyone, apologize.
Apologize properly.
I'm sorry.
That's the NG word.
Go back.
Masumoto-san, your feet are heavy.
No, it's okay.
Are you okay?
What?
Akai-san, are you okay?
Wait a minute.
There's something strange.
What?
I can't do it.
What is it?
It's coming from behind.
I don't know.
What's wrong?
I can't do it in a better situation.
It's okay.
Of course, the story has already been decided.
I want to take a picture.
I want to say it, but it's about to explode.
Wait a minute.
I'm begging you.
She's wearing a swimsuit.
Please.
Are you okay?
No one will kick you anymore.
Please.
What's wrong?
It's okay.
Does your stomach hurt?
My stomach hurts.
Don't say that to a junior high school student.
I hurt my leg.
I was treated like a transfer student.
What?