Chiki Chiki Staff Exhibition, Let's all make it together, Gaki Kalender 98!
What about this time?
This time, simply, let's make a calendar for next year from January to December.
I see.
That's what we're going to do.
We're going to go and bake what we've made.
Bake it?
It's bad manners.
Well, we should've made it.
We should've had it baked in a temple.
Since it's a calendar, it should be from January to December.
Yes, yes, yes.
We need a model for that.
This member should be in it.
If it's not enough, the staff should be in it too.
That can't be helped.
Yes.
There's going to be a hard month for a month, right?
A hard month.
There's going to be a really hard month.
Right?
If you say that, it's going to be a hard month from January on.
There we go.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Well, let's go.
There's only this person here.
He's our staff member for January.
Oh, really?
Since it's January, you're an octopus.
Yes.
If it's done well, we're going to make a calendar and give it to the viewers.
Is it done?
Yes.
Can't I open my hands?
Oh, like that?
Yes.
Come here.
Make more faces.
I can't do it.
I'm an amateur.
Make two different faces.
Let's make more faces.
Who's this?
He's a demon.
Why are there so many Sakamoto-chan?
In February...
Sakamoto-chan is in February too?
Sakamoto-chan and Yamazaki.
Oh, I see.
Sakamoto-chan, you should eat.
You can't bite, can you?
What's wrong with your body?
Yamazaki, you're wrong.
Yamazaki, it's not this way.
Yamazaki, your camera view is weird.
Look at the demon.
You're on the side.
That's why your nose position is wrong.
It's the opposite.
Really?
You're really not used to making jokes.
I think about it.
Which way to draw the mole.
The side without the camera.
You're all the opposite.
The mole and nose are all the opposite.
Cry once.
Ouch!
At that moment...
Go away, demon.
Is this all in March?
In March, there's a festival.
Four unique characters start shooting.
The picture is good.
Yanaoka is ugly.
This is the first time I've seen Yanaoka like that.
It's really funny.
It's funny.
It's ugly.
I can't lose to him.
Tanaka, let's make a voice.
Yes.
Hurry up.
Yanaoka, don't say anything.
Yanaoka, you can't make a voice.
Stop it.
Yanaoka, let's make a voice.
Yanaoka, look at the camera.
Make a voice.
Yanaoka, let's make a voice.
Next is Hama born in May.
It's funny.
Let's go.
Is that you?
If it's me, there's no bear.
There's only one person in May.
Let's leave the bear.
It's not his birthday or anything.
Who is the bear?
Who?
You're in trouble.
I'm sorry.
I think it's good that I won.
That's a little different.
Look over there.
Over there.
Yes, yes.
No, no, no, no, no.
I was taken by the string.
It's a post-it.
Who is this?
Kirika.
Okay, okay, okay.
It's Sato Koichiro.
Sato Koichiro.
It's going to cost a lot of money.
You're doing a good job.
What's this?
It's covered with a big one.
He's breaking his head in the middle.
That's a good one.
Here we go.
Roar, bear, roar.
Roar.
Did you get it?
Who is this?
It's covered with a big one.
Roar, bear, roar.
It's not a horse.
It's a human.
No matter how you look at it.
Roar.
It's still covered with a big one.
Let's take a picture.
June Pride in June.
It's ugly.
It's scary.
It's ugly up to here.
It's a muhen.
If you kill it.
If you kill it, it's a muhen.
Laugh.
Don't laugh.
Laugh more.
It's scary.
I envy your face.
If I was born again, I would have this face.
They look alike in some way.
Speak.
Hey.
It didn't work in July?
But these two.
Why are these two here?
I don't know.
They are Orihime and Hikoboshi.
But they can't bite each other.
Do it.
Do it properly.
Don't fight.
In August, there is a watermelon party at the beach in the middle of summer.
It's a situation where a crab that got caught in the water gets hit by a muhen.
It looks more like a crab.
Really?
It's true.
You can see it a little, right?
It doesn't matter who it is.
In September, Machan finally appears.
Matsumoto-san.
Yes.
Take this.
Wait a minute.
From this side.
Please jump here.
I'll jump.
If you jump like this, you will be in the same place as the moon.
I see.
You can do it in one shot, right?
That's right.
Let's do it.
Really?
Really.
Is that so?
I'm really sorry.
What?
I can't do this.
Do it more.
Yamazaki, show us.
Please.
Come from here.
You want me to do this much, right?
Show us something strange.
Yes.
Fight!
Try jumping.
More, more, more.
Jump more. Why can't you jump?
Jump more.
Personally, I jump a lot.
No, you don't.
Just try it.
I can't do it.
Like this.
That's right.
Dangerous.
Dangerous. You're working too hard.
Do you have a set?
Let's use this one in September.
Wait a minute.
Let me use this one.
Let's go.
Laugh. Laugh.
Laugh.
Don't say no.
Please.
Say no. Say no.
Say no.
Please.
My sweat is sticky.
Mago-san, please.
Doctor.
I'm sorry. Please.
What if I fall down this time?
You're falling down.
Alright.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
You're crazy.
October is an active image of the autumn sports festival.
Snap expressed a piece of obstacle relay.
Snap.
November.
An old lady is gathering in Urayama with the image of the deepening autumn.
There are a lot of people in December.
There are three of us.
Yes.
So, I'll introduce you.
Takahashi Oishi. Kuranosuke.
Okamoto is Kira.
Kira.
He looks like a bad guy.
Fujiwara is Horime Yasuke.
The fat of the liver is coming out.
This kid is funny.
But there's nothing to do.
That's right.
This kid is not funny at all.
Hey, Fujiwara-san.
Do you want me to dress you up?
That's a real face.
I tried to cut it.
Are you ready?
Kira is normal.
You have a more nasty face when you're booking.
You have a face when you refuse to do something.
Unfortunately...
Covered in full face.
Hey Fujiwara,
please look at the camera.
He just said Gero-Gero.
It's Circe who changes.
That's funny.
Today's opening was a bit long.
Oh, I see.
I could have cut the talk, but I didn't.
You should have come out and stopped me!
I've been angry since last week.
No, that's not it.
I'll tell you why I did the talk today.
You see, everyone is worried about Hamada-kun's health.
That's where my kindness comes out.
Hamada-chan, Hamada-chan, who are you?
That room just now, isn't that Hamada-chan?
I don't want to talk about the accident.
You don't want to talk about it?
I didn't know anything about the accident.
Oh, really?
It was on Saturday, right? When was it?
Friday night.
Friday night?
In the morning.
I had a job on Saturday.
Yes, yes.
When I had a job on Saturday, who was it?
Oh, it was Okamoto.
He came over.
I didn't know anything about it.
He said, Hamada-san, it's okay.
What?
I didn't know anything about it.
He suddenly said, Hamada-san, it's okay.
I thought, there's nothing to worry about.
Why? I didn't know anything.
There's nothing to worry about.
There's nothing to worry about for someone like Hamada.
He said, Hamada-san, it's okay.
I said, what?
Why is it okay?
He got angry.
I didn't know anything about it.
I was sleeping.
I heard a noise.
I was covered in glass.
It was pretty amazing.
It was amazing.
I wondered what it was.
When I woke up, it was windy.
All the windows were broken.
I thought you did it.
You did it.
No matter how you think about it, it's like a foreign car.
You look like a foreign car.
I thought it was you.
You look like a foreign car too.
No, you look more like a foreign car.
When you're on TV, you're a talent.
You're very attentive.
But when you're done, you're like a foreign car.
You're very frivolous.
When you're done, you're frivolous.
I don't know what to say.
I'm saying this because I wasn't on the show.
What do you mean?
I didn't get on the show, so that's what happened.
You didn't get on the show, so the accident happened.
Yes.
Why?
I have a lot of fear.
I'm like your god of poverty.
I'm holding you back.
I'm carrying a lot of things.
I have a different aura.
I can't do anything about you.
What?
You're not being protected.
The woman behind you is a Mongolian.
I'm not a Mongolian.
I can't do anything about it.
I'm not a normal Mongolian.
I'm a tempura.
You're being cooked even more.
I'm being cooked even more.
And I'm a little cold.
I can't do anything about it.
If I'm there, I'll protect you.
If you're there with me, you're being protected.
You have to be more careful.
I see.
I'm not a Mongolian.
Are you a good person?
I'm a good person.
I'm Elibis Presley.
Elibis Presley.
Elibis Presley and Bob Marley are mine.
Matsumoto-san once made a new opening song for Talk.
It was very popular.
Did you have one?
I had one.
What are you talking about?
I had a lot of them.
Please make a new opening song for Talk.
What about the previous one?
No, I can't.
That's where I am.
That's not a song.
It's not a song.
No, that's where I am.
That's no good.
This is hard to sing.
I can't sing.
It's over?
No matter how many times I hear it, I can't help but drink.
You can't help but drink.
So, please make a new song.
I'll make a new song.
This is the last one for this year.
Next year?
Next year, I'll make a new song.
If you make a new song here, it'll be recorded.
It'll be soon.
OK, OK.
Are you OK?
I like that.
I like the simple feeling.
If you're ready, I'll sing.
Are you OK?
OK, I understand.
I'll make a new opening song.
Everyone, please be quiet.
This is a recording.
Who's talking?
I'm going in, so I can't talk.
I can't talk.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Please do it.
OK, I understand.
Make a decision.
If you make a decision, it'll be soon.
OK, I understand.
Are you ready?
It's close.
This is the second year.
Mic.
OK, OK.
I'll sing a foreign song.
Are you ready?
Yes.
5 seconds.
4, 3, 2, 1.
Buse shibon.
Matcha matcha shibon.
Can you lower this?
I'll sing a foreign song.
Please.
It's OK now.
What's shibon?
I've heard this in Osaka.
It's a performance in the middle of the night.
Please do it.
Don't look this way.
I understand.
Let's change.
It's different now.
Are you ready?
Yes.
5 seconds.
4, 3, 2, 1.
Bagachiko.
Why are you laughing?
I'm not laughing.
5 seconds.
Do it like a black dream.
What?
5 seconds.
There's a way to do it like a black dream.
If you do this.
It's a song in the opening.
It's not about how to enter.
It's OK if it's a visual.
If it's a singing style, it's OK to enter.
Please.
Let's go.
5, 4, 3, 2...
Bagachiko.
Yes, Machan is Bagachiko.
Machan shouldn't be Bagachiko.
Bagachiko.
Mebachiko.
You are laughs
Bang!
Not
More
Also
Another
Cut
You're laughs
Go
Naa
Have go
At the moment
You are laughs
bang
Idiot waiting for trouble
Idiot!
you idiot!
no way out I am a blijday!
Get out!
Get out now!
You wanna play them??
No way out, idiot.
I'm not gonna!
what do I say?
Sh え え え え え え 偽 Wild
I can't get into it.
I did it because I couldn't.
No, no.
Bang, bang, bang, bang.
There's something about the previous song.
If you put it out, it's amazing.
I'll say it clearly, but Okuda Tamio is frustrated right now.
Ah, so this is what happened.
It's a new genre.
A man and a woman who fell in love are opposed by their parents, but they still want to be together.
It's a song that has the image of running away.
In the song, Machan is stupid.
Eh?
It has something to do with it.
Machan, please support our love.
Hana-chan, please support our love.
Stupid.
My dad is not stupid.