This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
It's all right to talk.
It ended suddenly.
I don't know when it will end.
Good evening.
Today is the 30th minute of the talk show.
Let me be clear.
I'm not feeling well.
Who are you talking about?
I don't like the song of taxi drivers.
I'm not feeling well.
Who are you talking about?
I was beaten this time.
What?
I was beaten.
From the North.
What do you mean you were beaten?
Did you cry?
What?
What are you doing?
That's dirty.
I didn't see it.
You didn't see it.
It's been a long time.
It's been three hours.
The second day is three and a half hours.
Did you cry?
I'm crying.
Let me be honest.
I watched the first episode twice.
I watched the second episode twice in the last 30 minutes.
I was shooting a video.
You were watching a video.
Yes.
I watched the second episode twice.
I wanted to cry again.
I was wondering what would happen if I watched the second episode.
Let me be honest. I watched the second episode yesterday.
Did you cry?
That's not true.
The theme of the second episode is death and marriage.
You'll see it later.
I've never seen that series.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
I don't think so.
Do you think it's better to watch it from the beginning?
But I think I can keep up with it.
Brother Sota is dead.
Who is it?
I don't know that.
Brother Sota.
I've never seen it.
You don't even know Brother Sota.
I don't believe it.
I've never seen it because I said it first.
Brother Sota is Koichi Iwaki.
I know that.
He's dead.
He's been alive for a long time.
That drama has been going on for 20 years.
It's hard for a person who's been alive to die.
That's true.
Hodaru is getting married.
Brother Sota dies before that.
His wife is going to give a speech, but Brother Sota was really looking forward to the wedding.
He was rehearsing for the speech.
He put it on the cassette tape.
He said he found it and wrote it.
A dead person congratulates him on the cassette tape.
It's like this.
You're a good customer.
That's what I'm aiming for.
He's dead this time.
There are a lot of strange things.
The wife of Kunie Tanaka is a great actress.
She's dead.
He's crying.
Kunie Tanaka is crying.
He said he was going to get a cold, so he put something in his kimono.
I saw a picture of Ayumi Ishida.
I see.
He's crying again.
I cried.
Did you cry?
But before that, Kunie Tanaka was dancing naked.
I asked him where he saw that picture.
There's a time limit.
He hid it here before he danced naked.
He danced naked and put it in his kimono.
You're crying because you said that.
I don't care.
He's crying a lot.
That's what happened this time.
He's the representative of the audience.
Masashi Sada's song is cowardly.
It's a song that comes out many times.
If it's a song, I'll cry.
That's not true.
I'll cry even if I run naked.
I'll definitely cry.
There's been a lot of things in the music industry, so I'll cry.
When he got bored of Masashi Sada's song, a trumpet came in.
It's no good.
That's what happened this time.
Can I watch that video?
I'll lend you the video.
What did you think of the next video?
It's six and a half hours.
It's three and a half hours.
If you watch it over and over again, you won't know which country it's from.
It's not a dirty country.
I have some complaints.
There's a strange scene.
I don't know the meaning of Jun and Miyazawa Rei living apart.
I don't know what you're talking about.
They're living apart and working at a convenience store.
That's right.
I don't know if you were an AV actress.
I was an AV actress.
I don't know why you're staying at home and working at a convenience store.
I don't know where you're going to go if you do that.
Why don't you go to Vinta?
I wonder if he went to a strange place.
Well, I'll take a look.
Please tell me.
Are you going to cry?
Thank you very much.
What are you going to say?
That's funny.
Life game.
I was bored, so I played a life game.
That's funny.
Do you choose the salaryman course first?
Business course.
I chose the business course.
I became a talent.
It's amazing if you become a talent.
When the payday comes, it's 100 or 1,000 times every month.
The salary.
It's amazing.
I thought I'd be a talent.
I've been making a lot of money as a talent somewhere.
I couldn't stop laughing.
Next time, if I stop at 3 or something, I'll be a best-seller.
If I publish a book, I'll be a best-seller.
That's why I started making money again.
I made a lot of money.
Suddenly, I started working part-time at home.
No way.
That's what I'm saying.
I thought it was amazing.
It's a part-time job.
That's right.
I was married before that.
My wife was next to me.
It's like a lie.
After I started working part-time, my wife started crying.
I didn't know I hated it.
I became a talent with you.
It's fun.
I was a little upset.
But I've been doing it for a long time, so I'm still doing it.
That's how it is.
It's a game of life.
It's fun, isn't it?
I'm not doing it.
I'm going to Okinawa.
What are you going to do?
I'm going on a vacation.
Is that so?
Yes.
Are you going on a vacation?
I'm going to change from this summer.
What's going to change when you go to Okinawa?
I'm going to be a comedian.
Why?
I'm going to be bold.
I'm going to be bolder than I thought.
What do you mean?
I'm going to be more masculine.
I'm going to appeal to people and walk.
Left, right, left, right.
That doesn't matter.
People who are watching TV and people who are wearing this today.
Yes.
It's summer.
It's very different.
What do you mean?
I'm going to change my hairstyle.
That's a good thing.
What do you mean?
That doesn't matter.
It's the left side.
Right side.
I'll reduce the length to about two millimeters.
What is your shape of the head?
It's not bad.
I shaved my head when I was in high school.
It's clean.
It's round.
I'm perfect.
Oh, is that so?
So, there was a time when I did it smoothly.
Well, it doesn't matter what you did.
What is that?
Well, I don't have a lot of opponents.
I don't have any.
I'm saying that, but if you really don't do it, you'll be called a liar again.
No, I'll do it.
Are you really doing it in 2mm?
I'll do it in 2mm.
I'm looking forward to it.
When I come back to Okinawa, I'll do it in 2mm.
Well, I think you'll be called a liar again.
You'll be called a liar by me.
Well, I don't know if I'll get a tattoo.
You can't go. You can't go.
Where should I go?
Well, you can go here.
What are you doing in a woman's house?
Well, really.
What are you doing?
It's like a devil.
What are you talking about?
Are you all well?
Right?
Are you going back to the countryside?
Well, I wonder.
It's mostly in the countryside, right?
Do you know anyone from Tokyo?
Look at this.
All of them are from the countryside.
It's terrible.
Aren't there so few of them?
Look at the face of a person from Tokyo.
Are you stupid?
Aren't there so few of them?
Raise your hand if you're from Tokyo again.
That's all.
But it's kind of like a countryside.
I'm going to watch this program and make a cup.
We're standing here, too.
Where are you from?
For example, where are you from?
I'm from Shibaragi.
I'm scared.
I'm from Ibaragi.
What are you talking about?
I'm from Hyojun.
I'm not from Hyojun.
I'm from Yojinbo.
It's Hyojun language.
Hyo-jin-bo?
I can't do that.
Isn't that right?
Why don't you send me something in a box?
Right?
That's right.
I'll send it to you.
You'll send it to me, huh?
It's summer stuff.
But it's not summer.
If you open it, it's not really summer clothes.
It's something you used to wear in the past.
I see, I see.
You can wear it as a dishware.
If you open it, it's just clothes.
You just changed it in the past.
I see.
That's how it is.
It's tough.
Let's do our best.
We have no choice but to do our best.
Right.
I'm starting to feel blue.
Then, from now on, I'll give you two minutes.
Everyone, think about your parents.
Besides that, play Masashi Sada's song.
I see.
That's how it is.
Then...
Let's start.
Stop it!
You were kicking a lot.
Matsumoto-san says his hobby is human watching.
Why do people shake the poor?
What is shaking the poor?
Please tell me the identity of shaking the poor.
Do you know the word for shaking the poor?
I don't know.
You can't do anything if you shake the rich.
I see.
I got it.
You were imitating it just now.
That's ridiculous.
If you shake the rich, it means that you have money.
But I don't want to be taken.
You don't want to be taken, but you have some money.
But if you shake the poor, what do you think will happen?
That's a big deal.
You'll be scared.
Even though you don't have money.
You're shaking the cap.
The rhythm is so bad.
The rhythm is bad.
Is that you're?
The rhythm is like that.
This is the rhythm of shaking the poor.
Even though you don't have money.
You're shaking the rich.
That's long.
Because you have money.
You're so noisy.
This is what I think.
Do you think that everyone is right?
But is it a lie to say that if you keep talking about poverty, you'll become poor?
No, that's not true.
I'm originally poor.
I see.
That's what it is.
So you're saying that a poor person who has been seduced by a poor person is a poor person who has been seduced by a poor person.
So please look at the people who are seducing the poor.
Please watch the people who are seducing the poor.
You can watch it at a coffee shop or anywhere.
The people who are seducing the poor are being seduced by a poor person.
I've never seen it.
I've never seen it. I've never seen it. I've never seen it.
It's in the rhythm.
Why do people seduce the poor?
I understand that.
That's right.
But now, I think there are people who do it.
I do it too.
Why do you do it?
Do you do it?
Sometimes I do it while eating.
Are you saying, I don't have it?
Wait a minute.
I don't do it because I'm poor.
I don't think you're poor either.
Normally, I don't have it.
You didn't have it.
Is it different for each person?
It's different for each person.
That's why I'm watching you.
Don't you do it?
I don't do it.
I'm raised in the United States.
How many times do you say you're in the United States?
What are you talking about?
It's okay.
My parents didn't teach me that.
Don't do it.
When you don't like it, use a knife and fork.
You put the rice on top of the fork.
I'll eat it.
You have to cut the steak into small pieces first.
Why are you hiding it?
My mother taught me that.
Watch your back.
My grandmother told me to eat.
Eat this.
Why are you hiding it?
Chew the food.
You're a fool.
What happens when you use Viagra?
How much do you know about Viagra?
I don't know.
You don't know?
You don't know Viagra?
You're a fool.
It's easy to understand.
It's a hot topic now.
It's hard to get it in Japan.
I went to buy it in Hong Kong.
It is said that drinking Viagra is good for people who have never had Viagra.
I'm still active.
I sell my pulse.
Red and blue are like this.
Red and blue.
The pulse of red and the pulse of blue are like this.
It's red.
It's coming out like this.
It's green.
You're the one who's talking about it.
What happens when you drink Viagra?
It's going to burst.
It's not like that in the world.
When you drink Viagra, it's going to burst.
It's going to burst.
After drinking it for 10 minutes, it's going to burst.
Till the morning.
What was it?
It means you hear it.
If you put it simply, it means you hear it.
Well maybe that's right.
For you, it's like this, but you can't do anything about it.
Why is that?
If you drink it, you'll get used to it.
Isn't there a way to drink it?
It's like you suddenly float.
That's funny.
When the wind blows, you float.
I want to drink it from the top.
The wind goes down, so you float.
It's Halloween.
If you come from here, you float.
It's entangled once, and it's like this.
In boxing matches, if the second throws a towel, it automatically means a loss.
What else does it mean to throw?
Boxing is a lonely world.
No matter how much the trainer or the coach says,
it's a lonely world when the game starts.
You can't do anything about it.
If you throw something, you tell your opponent,
I'm thinking like this.
You're thinking like this?
So please stop it.
You mean don't hit me anymore, right?
I've been watching a lot of matches, so I've seen a lot of throws.
What else?
I threw a newspaper once.
Does that mean anything?
That means read it.
Look at this article.
It's not like that.
I'll show you later.
Look at this article.
It's not good if it's after the game.
I just saw it.
I'm doing it seriously.
I'll say, go.
Look at this.
This child hit his parent.
I've seen a lot of things like that.
It's not related to the game.
You can throw something that's not related to the game.
It's a lonely fight, so I'll say it many times.
I don't want my players to be lonely.
I'll do a lot of things.
I dig CDs.
What?
I don't ask you to dig CDs.
Look at this roundness.
That's the game.
It's okay after the game.
You said it's the digital age.
You know that.
In this world.
I have something to do with that.
What?
I was hit.
What are you doing?
You can't see the digital age.
What do you mean?
Have you ever seen such a digital age?
I don't know.
I don't have the ability to understand.
There's no point in throwing it.
If you throw it, your players will think it's okay.
Then you'll understand.
You should think about yourself and throw it.