I've said it before, but...
Yes, yes, yes, what is it?
I'm still laughing at the opening song.
That's right.
The staff told us to change the opening song.
I thought it would be better, but I'm still laughing.
You're laughing, aren't you?
That's it.
I can't go to a drink this year.
It's been a while.
I've been saying it's been a while, but you're looking at me with such a clouded eye.
It's like, wow, really?
It's like Romeo and Juliet.
This program is brought to you by five sponsors.
I've said it before, but it's not a big deal.
Yesterday, I was driving around in my car.
It's really small.
It's like an L-shape.
It doesn't go all the way to the end of the car.
It's hard to turn, isn't it?
This corner is dangerous, isn't it?
You want to go like this, don't you?
What do you call it?
It's a big circle.
You want to go in a big circle, don't you?
A woman came from the other side on a bike.
She came like this.
She was waiting for me at this corner.
Oh, I see.
No, no, no, no.
You have to go like this.
I wasn't angry or anything.
If you don't come to me, the car is like this.
You have to get used to the car.
You can't do that.
Those are appropriate words.
I wanted to say that to that woman, but I couldn't.
I wanted to say that to the car's body.
I thought the car's body was strange.
Did you say that to her?
No, I didn't.
I thought it was a body.
It's a beaver, isn't it?
I don't care.
I don't know if it's a beaver or not.
When you're in a hurry...
I know.
When you're in a hurry, it goes like this.
What?
It doesn't move at all, so I hit it and went.
No, no, no.
I said, ah, it's a beaver.
And I signed it.
You're lying.
How many times have I signed it this year?
It's definitely a lie.
When you're in a hurry, something amazing happens.
What?
Have you ever had a dry throat?
That's different.
I have.
Have you ever had a dry throat?
What's wrong?
It's not that big of a deal.
Why did you do that?
When I go to the gym, something amazing happens.
It goes like this.
It happens after you exercise.
I was surprised.
My hands were shaking.
My throat was so dry.
I was surprised.
If you're too hungry, your hands will shake.
Ah.
It's relaxing.
It's not that.
It's not because you have a throat.
It's not like that in this day and age.
It's not because you're hungry.
It's not that.
It's because you're hungry that you feel sick.
You want to put something in quickly.
It's like this.
I can't take it anymore.
My wallet...
My wallet is like a check.
I don't know.
I put it out like this.
I put it in like this.
I push it.
I didn't push it and say, go down quickly.
I mean, it's better if you drink quickly.
I was doing it and it was close to me.
I have a broken hand.
I pushed it and it was close.
I was pushing it and it was close.
I was surprised and my coins went like this.
My coins went like this.
It was 240 yen.
Are you sure?
I'll never do that!
No no no no no!
This is true!
What the hell!
Ah, yo!
Did you make the yo?
You!
Are you stupid?
Only the stupid ones come out.
No no no no no no!
That, Volvic, Volvic.
I was expecting Volvic, Volvic.
5 yen, 10 yen, 5 yen, 10 yen, and so on.
I drank 240 yen.
Are you drunk?
You're not drunk, are you?
Wait, wait.
I'm not drunk.
Shut up.
You're not drunk.
No, but it really does make a sound.
Well, I don't know if you're in a hurry, but...
You have to be careful about that.
You have to be careful.
But you don't have to eat to shake your body, do you?
That's what I do.
But with that, um...
I feel like the punishment for this time was a hint.
What do you mean by punishment for this time?
They say to do it in the Japanese series.
Ah, yes, yes, yes.
Well, it could be this time.
By the way...
Which do you think will win?
Me?
I think Hanshin will win.
Really?
Why? Do you think it's Daiei?
To be honest, I think it's Daiei.
Then there's no need to play rock-paper-scissors.
That's right.
Is it okay to decide that?
So what?
The loser will be punished.
Why?
If you say that, it's a series of why's.
I still have something left in my ass.
Right, Takasu?
No, Takasu.
No, really, really.
I've been watching this on the radio.
No, I don't think so.
And Takasu said, show me.
I said, I don't have any.
Do you want to see it?
I'll see it.
I'm really gonna hit you.
I understand.
Then look at it.
Why?
Look at it.
It's just my ass.
I don't like it even if it's just your ass.
And it's a little bit of a
This is also a little bit.
What are you talking about?
It's a little bit.
No, it's okay to see it.
Then, go.
Stop it.
Then, what kind of ass can I show?
That's enough.
You, you, you're an idiot.
You're an idiot.
I'm just saying, look at your ass.
No, I don't want to see it.
I'm just saying, show me your ass.
I'm just saying, look at your ass.
I'm just showing it.
Shut up.
But why do I have to show it?
Actually, it's the other way around.
Why do you need it?
I'll show it to you!
I'll take it!
I'll give it to you!
I'll give it to you, so take it!
Why do you need it?
Why do you want to show my butt to everyone?
I want you to see it this much!
I don't want to see it!
Then look at it!
I don't know!
Feel my back!
Look at it!
Like this!
Look at it or don't look at it!
Look at it!
Then feel my butt!
Softly!
What are you talking about?
Be firm!
Feel my butt!
That's good.
You have a half-body.
Which is better?
If you lose, I'll think about it.
In the end, you don't have to decide.
What?
But I think you have a half-body.
I think you have a half-body.
I'm surprised.
If you get infected with the most troublesome computer virus in the world, what will happen to your computer?
Do you know about computer viruses?
Something comes in, right?
That's a rough way of saying it.
What will happen to your computer?
If you get infected with a really bad virus.
This is similar to humans.
What do you mean?
What happens if you catch a cold?
You'll get a fever.
Humans.
But what if you use electronic products for a long time?
You'll get a fever.
Humans are the same.
First of all, when I came back from work,
The computer that got infected with the computer virus is...
It's already...
From the top of the screen,
Oh, that's it.
But now the mouse is Claire.
It warms up.
The mouse becomes a tight way.
Which way?
You're droning
It's tight, now.
The mouse...
This is the mouse.
Why is it like this?
That's fine.
When you turn around, it's like this.
You're telling me a lie?
That's true.
Then if you have a fever, you should just go to the AC and take a look.
That's not good.
That kind of person will die.
If you don't cry, you'll kill yourself. That's what Hototokisu thinks.
I hate those kinds of thoughts.
I don't understand this idiot.
Then how do you fix it?
I taught you how to fix it.
Why are you asking such a silly question?
Then how do you fix it?
What are you going to do if your wife is like that?
You can take it off, right?
It feels good, it feels good.
Are you motivated, you idiot?
Yes, yes, yes.
That's a good example.
That's right.
That's how you do it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Excuse me, then how do you fix it?
The heated computer.
Yes, that's fine.
Excuse me.
Do you have a computer?
Of course I do.
If that's the case, I'll teach you.
Thank you very much.
Do you have a sweater?
I think I have one.
Cut the bottom of it into squares.
Yes, yes, yes.
First, cover it up.
It's going to make a noise.
That's it.
So open it up here and cover it up.
Yes, yes, yes.
Basically, that's fine.
And then put it on the side.
It's going to be hard to do this all the time.
And do you have any ginger?
I think you can find it if you look for it.
Cut it up.
You can eat it.
Oh, me?
Feel the computer.
I have a question for Mr. Matsumoto, who talks to animals and trees like humans.
Mr. Matsumoto, have you ever talked to tofu?
If you have, what did you talk about?
There's nothing I've never talked about.
Tofu?
Tofu and furisode.
I talked about furisode two nights.
You've ever talked about it?
Furisode?
Furisode.
What were you talking about two nights?
It's like this.
So it was easy to talk.
We usually look at each other the same way.
I talked a little like a rishoku.
It's not easy to talk.
What do you talk about two nights?
First of all, what kind of person have you been in love with?
There was a lot of that.
Well, furisode is fine.
Have you ever talked to tofu?
I have.
Tell me what you talked about.
You talked about tofu, didn't you?
I did.
Then tell me what it was about.
Basically, it's all about the bad things about soy milk.
What are you talking about?
What are you talking about soy milk?
I can't say this on TV.
I was talking about it a lot.
Soy milk is annoying.
You said it was annoying.
That's right.
It's all about the bad things about soy milk.
It's bitter.
I was talking about it.
Do you laugh at it?
No, I don't laugh at it.
I'll get angry if I laugh.
You're the one who's laughing.
That's right.
Why are you laughing?
There's a lot of tofu.
What is it?
Are you on bad terms with your parents?
My parents are on bad terms with me, too.
What are you talking about?
My son says he's a bad boy.
He's a bad boy.
Why don't you talk a little more?
You're talking a lot.
That's right.
It's the same for everyone.
I have a question for Mr. Matsumoto, the Indy Jones of Gotanda.
Who's Gotanda?
Gotanda didn't go to the station.
As much as you think.
That's the only thing I'm not happy about.
It's not as much as you think.
I don't know.
It's written.
Gotanda's Indy Jones.
That's all right.
I have a question for Mr. Matsumoto.
Please tell me why Neanderthals are extinct.
That's all right.
I finally got a real letter.
What should I do?
I've been reading all the stupid letters.
I'm sorry.
Neanderthals are really stupid.
I see.
That's really stupid.
Is that so?
What should I do?
I was stupid.
I see.
I can't help it if I die.
You were that stupid?
I was stupid.
For example, how can you say that?
What?
How can you say that?
I was really stupid.
I thought I shouldn't have pooped.
I'm stupid.
I thought pooping was the devil's servant.
I see.
That's why I've been pooping all the time.
At home.
At home or in the village.
It was amazing.
Neanderthals are really stupid.
I heard that I was pooping all the time.
They are old.
They can't even poop.
I said that.
Everyone said that I was stupid.
I couldn't do anything about it.
Everyone said, get together.
I thought I shouldn't have pooped.
I see.
You are amazing.
When I pooped, everyone was looking at me.
I was envious.
I said that.
I said, that's good.
Who said that?
That's right.
I said, that's good.
I see.
What do you mean, that's good?
It's like Haratetsuo.
Come here.
He said that.
I was about to poop.
Then he pooped again.
There is a long history.
That's right.
There are people who pooped before.
That's why I pooped.
But I was envious.
That's right.
It's all because of the bad anal.
Ah, is that so?
Yes.
But, everyone will slap Anaru.
Your Anaru...
It's not your fault!
It's not your Anaru's fault!
Who's that? Who's that?
It's Chorou.
Ah, Chorou.
Chorou.
Everyone, wait!
Eh, wait, wait, wait.
Chorou's not waiting for that.
Everyone, wait!
It's not this guy's fault!
It's this guy's Anaru's fault!
Bring me the pachinko.
Bring me the pachinko that you hid from Kanete.
There's no need to hide it!
Where did you put it?
There's no need to leave it there.
Bring it to me.
Chorou's a bit big.
The ball?
The ball.
The village guy's ball is this small.
Wait!
Here it comes!
This is my big ball!
It's not your fault!
I've been telling you!
It's your Anaru's fault!
I know that, that's why everyone's doing it!
Here I go.
Okay.
E, R, San.
What are you doing?
That was, that was a terrible thing to do.
You don't eat it much, right?
If I eat it, it'll come out.
If you eat it, it'll come out.
No, that's not it.
What I'm asking is why you're asking if it's rotten.
If it's rotten, I know that you think it's bad.
I know that Anaru's saying bad things and doing this.
Why?
I want to destroy it.
What?
That's right.
What's right?
You'll destroy it.
Why?
First, you can't eat it.
Yes, yes, yes.
If you don't eat it as little as possible, the devil's servant will do it.
That's right.
You can't use the devil's servant.
That's right, that's right.
If you have small hands, it'll look like that.
It'll look like that.
That's a terrible thing, if it looks like that.
That's right.
That's why everyone should eat as little as possible.
Right?
In the end, you can't eat anything.
No, that's not it.
What I'm asking is why you're increasing the number of ancestors.
Yes, yes, yes.
Right?
Yes.
No, but...
This is what I'm talking about.
No, it's not.
You can do it while holding back your poop?
Right? That's what I'm saying.
But you have to eat as little as possible.
Yes.
What are you going to do about this?
I don't know.
And the child that's born will be like,
The baby will be like,
It'll come out like this.
You just did it.
I won't forgive you even if you're a baby.
You hid it after it was born.
It'll come out like this.
That's right.
There's a way.
Let's just leave it there.
You don't have to hide it.
It's not your fault.
No, it's Anaru's fault.
I know that. I know that.
Mine is a big ball, so I'll hold back a little.
That's what I'm saying.
Bang!
And then the child, right?
It's too small.
You can't react to that, can you?
I see.
It's a real problem.
It's amazing.
That's why you died?
It seems that everyone came out of nowhere at the end.
It's a dirty story.
I see.
I don't really want to hear about it.
If that's the case, I'd like to hear more about Choro.
Do you want to hear about Choro?
Actually, I'll tell you now.
Choro was silent to everyone.
That's right.
I can't stand it until I'm that old.
Where do you do it?
Everyone woke up at 7 o'clock tomorrow and said, I'm going to sleep.
By the time everyone fell asleep.
Bang!
It's amazing.
There's a lot of boiled eggs.
Boiled eggs.
It's like Neanderthal.
That's right.
That's why it's connected to the opening.
What is it?
It's not good to put up with it today.
Yes, yes, yes.
If you put up with the thirst of your throat, you'll drink 220 yen.
That's what happened, isn't it?
I didn't drink it.
Do you want to say it again?
You said you drank a lot.
I didn't drink that much.
What kind of 220 yen do you think 220 yen is?
What do you mean?
I think it's 220 yen in total.
Don't think it's 220 yen for two 100 yen bills and two 10 yen bills.
Oh, is that wrong?
One 100 yen bill, two 50 yen bills, two 5 yen bills, and one 10 yen bill.
And the number of bills changes completely.
No, but you didn't drink it.
What I drank was very fine.
It's even finer.
There was 5 yen in it.
If you don't write that down at all, you're saying 220 yen, two 100 yen bills, two 10 yen bills.
I can't forgive you for that.
But it's not your fault.
It's your own fault.
This program was brought to you by five sponsors.