BAM-BARA!
Don't...don't...don't fall in love with me!
I...I want to go...I want to go answer for our mother hands...
BAM-BARA!
I'm going to be the wind!
Well, this is a new version.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Hanatan's earring.
I think it's very complete.
I'm thinking of making a CD of this kind of thing.
It's called the flower song series.
I think it would be nice if it was a flower song.
Oh, that's right.
It's a lyrics.
Well, that's right.
Well, I don't want to be told by such a crazy guy.
Really, it's the beginning of the winter.
It's already raining.
I'm shivering.
It's refreshing in half an hour.
This program is provided by the sponsor you see.
What do you want to say?
No, no, I was embarrassed the other day.
At the time of the drama.
It's a pretty serious scene.
There are times when you can't read the kanji, right?
It's a little bit like this.
It's about looking it up before you go to the scene.
I just happened to read it.
When I saw the next scene, there were surprisingly a lot of lines.
It was a pretty serious scene.
I couldn't read the kanji.
In between the eyebrows.
I couldn't read it.
It's not a comedy scene.
I was surprised.
It's over when I heard it.
It's called a crotch.
The core of the crotch is completely different.
You should have played the game with your crotch.
I was really embarrassed.
There's nothing to do with a crotch.
This is the core of the crotch.
I didn't mean to make you laugh.
It's a serious scene.
The scene is frozen.
What happened to everyone?
Everyone was surprised.
What is this guy?
This is no good.
I don't need this kind of crotch.
Say that.
Wait a minute.
I didn't mean to make you laugh.
I was really embarrassed.
That's no good.
I was embarrassed because I couldn't read the kanji.
I didn't know why I couldn't read the kanji.
I was embarrassed.
I put my crotch on my crotch.
And I'm a girl.
I'm a girl.
That's not a mistake.
I really don't like it.
It's finally over.
The drama is over, right?
It's over.
You're going to start next.
That's right.
How long will it take for me to end and you to start?
It depends.
That's right.
I'll take off my wings when I'm done.
Really?
What are you going to do?
I'm going crazy.
I'm going to cross the five continents.
You're going to cross the five continents?
You're making a mistake with your words.
Don't say it all the time.
I'm sorry.
I have a lot of things to do.
You have a lot of things to do?
Yes.
What exactly do you want to do?
Well, I want to be a hard gay.
Try it.
What are you talking about?
Who's a hard gay?
I'm going to sue you.
What part of me is a hard gay?
Do you have any qualities?
No, I don't.
Then what do you want to do?
But I'm sure there will be more gays in the future.
What are you talking about?
I've seen a lot of gays in the city.
Really?
Listen to my theory.
If there is no war, there will be more gays.
What do you mean?
After the war, there will be 50 years of war.
War may not have been a good thing.
But there was a war.
It was a time when men were strong.
Women were protected by men.
It's a complicated story that men protect women.
It's not a story to listen to like that.
You have to be a little more aggressive.
Come on.
You're like a waterfall.
I think so.
When the war is over, women will become stronger.
Men can't emphasize that they are men.
Then the relationship between men and women is reversed.
Women are getting stronger.
Men are getting weaker.
When men are all weak, they are looking for weak people.
When men are weak, the love between men begins.
Why is that?
That's where the hard gays come in.
There are a lot of hard gays.
When I went to Shibuya the other day, I saw a lot of hard gays.
What do you mean by hard gays?
I'll tell you how to distinguish hard gays.
First of all, it's a tank top.
It's a great tank top.
It's not all tank tops.
It's a tank top.
When I saw a man wearing a tank top, I thought it was a hard gay.
And he's bald.
He's got a lot of skin on his head.
I thought it was a hard gay.
And he's got a big ass.
I don't know if he's got a big ass.
If you look closely, you'll see.
He's got a big ass.
Where are you going?
There's a thing called city noise in the hard gay world.
If you listen with your ears focused, you'll be breathing like this.
You're an idiot.
That's how hard gays are.
That's what's been going on lately.
That's a lot.
That's what's happened.
It's not like I'm going to do anything.
I don't know about that.
I don't know if you're being targeted.
I don't know if there's a hard gay right next to you.
That's why I'm saying it's different.
Stop it, you idiot.
I'm going to run with the boss.
I don't like running.
I don't like running, but I'm going to run with the boss.
Why are we talking about this?
You started it.
It doesn't matter if you break it.
I don't know about that.
Why?
I don't know if you're being targeted.
If you're being targeted by five people, there's nothing you can do.
Then you should say it.
What do you mean by saying it?
Don't hide it from me.
He got killed.
That's what I mean.
You can cry.
I don't know if you're being targeted.
I'm not going to say it.
You're talking like this.
That's the way it is.
You're going to run, right?
If you're talking like this and I'm like, what?
I'm going to say it.
You said, go.
No, no, no. That's fine.
No, really. I'm sorry about this.
No, no, no.
Now, shall we go home?
Yes.
I wrote it down.
Is it okay?
That's a hard game.
I stuck it in.
When I stuck it in, it was 5.
When Matsumoto-san was in the Amagasaki era,
I heard that you once grabbed the flower of heaven.
Yes.
How did you feel about it?
I haven't talked about this before, have I?
I did say that I saw a kappa.
I didn't grab the flower of heaven.
I didn't say that either.
Why? Why can't you say something so amazing?
It's been about 10 years since it started.
It's okay to say it first.
That's right.
But if you don't listen to me, I can't say it.
Who would believe that I suddenly came out and grabbed the flower of heaven?
What?
Did you just fart?
It's okay.
I'll just fart.
Fart?
I've even been on the Asahi News.
The Asahi News?
You must be lying.
When I was in the fourth grade of elementary school,
I grabbed the flower of heaven.
The flower of heaven?
That's amazing.
You're treating that as one-sided.
It came out.
I don't know if anyone has it, but I looked it up.
I was in the fourth grade of elementary school, so I was about 10 years old.
Where? Where did you see it?
On a long-distance trip.
A long-distance trip?
A long-distance trip.
A long-distance trip? I didn't go on a long-distance trip either.
Well, you did.
We were in the same fourth grade.
What do you mean by the same fourth grade?
It's a bit double.
It's double!
It's four times more.
Well, you did.
At that time, I got lost on a long-distance trip.
At that time, something like that happened.
A mountain-like place?
A mountain-like place.
Wakakusayama.
Wakakusayama?
It's a place full of grass.
There's no place to hide.
It's Wakakusayama in Nara.
I was asked if there was a place to hide.
You saw it, didn't you?
I saw it.
What kind of situation was it?
It was raining heavily.
Yes, yes.
It was raining heavily, and I got lost.
I was walking down the mountain path.
You were walking down the mountain path.
I fell down.
At that time, I grabbed something.
When you slipped, your hand suddenly...
I grabbed my hand suddenly.
It was just a stick.
I don't think anyone would say it hurts.
That's your way of running.
If you grab a stick, you'll know I slipped.
I grabbed my hand suddenly.
I thought it was a stick.
I was walking down the mountain path again.
Suddenly, something hit my head.
I was surprised.
It was just a branch.
Do you understand the second time?
I think there's a second time.
When did you grab it?
It wasn't the second time.
My stomach started to hurt.
My stomach suddenly started to hurt.
I felt like I was going to puke.
You felt like you were going to puke.
Yes, I felt like I was going to puke.
I ran and grabbed the stick.
I didn't have any tissue paper.
I grabbed a leaf or something.
It was a leaf.
You knew it was a leaf?
I knew it was a leaf.
It was the third time.
Then can you do it again?
I knew it was a leaf.
Please touch it again.
I grabbed a leaf.
I was going to puke.
I found something that hit my head.
I thought it was a stick.
Then, here...
That's a bit too much!
It's too much!
It's too much for a video!
That's why you can't touch it in front of it!
What are you trying to do?
Is this how you do it?
From the back of the mouth...
That's why, leave it to me!
You're the one who's going to say,
I'm definitely going to do it!
This is weird!
Then, why don't you just walk out of the room?
You're the one who's going to do it!
You can't do it!
It's you!
It's my memory, and I'm the one who's going to talk!
You're the one who's going to say it from the side!
Isn't that weird?
Then, I can't do it here!
I can't do it here!
That's weird!
It's not here!
It's embarrassing!
Right?
You're so stupid!
I thought no one would see it!
You're laughing like, what?
I'm stupid!
Wait a minute!
You're clearly stupid!
You said that?
I said that!
There's someone who said that!
Who is it?!
If you say that, this is already a heaven!
That's a heaven!
Wait!
I'm chasing after a heaven!
Why?
You weren't scared?
I wasn't scared!
Because I was angry!
People were laughing at me!
I see!
Right!
I said, wait!
And I chased after it!
A heaven like this, huh?
I wonder if I can catch it?
You didn't even touch it!
No, no, no!
Even a heaven is stupid!
I should have run away like this!
I wonder if I can catch it?
I looked at it like this!
I caught it right away!
Let go!
It's amazing!
If it's like that, I won't let go!
Let go!
No, I won't let go!
It's a fight!
That was hard!
It's pretty long!
What's long?
The nose!
It's going to grow!
It won't grow, right?
If you pull it like this!
Really?
It's going to grow?
Then...
It won't grow that much!
It won't grow that much?
It's a little longer than I thought!
I can tell the difference!
Probably!
And then!
I said, wait!
I can make it a dog!
When I was young...
When I was young, I was doing stewardess, Mr. Matsumoto.
I heard that stewardess is trained when she's attacked by terrorists.
What kind of training is she doing?
I'm sure she's doing that.
Please tell me how to deal with stewardess.
That's right.
Then you're a terrorist.
Yes, I'm a terrorist.
Then I'm that terrorist's subordinate.
Alright!
You!
You bastard!
You're scaring me, boss!
A terrorist's countermeasure.
It's not like you're doing the old manzai.
If you're a stewardess, you won't be able to see any countermeasures.
I'm sorry.
I understand.
Yes.
What should I do?
I'll show you my Udon Desu Kai.
I'll show it to the audience.
I see.
What do you think, audience?
This is my Udon Desu Kai.
I'm doing it.
You're doing it.
At that time...
I'm not motivated.
I can't do it with someone who's not motivated.
It's more about how to deal with it than my acting.
I'm doing it seriously.
I'm sorry.
It's about people's lives.
I won't stop.
I'm sorry.
I won't stop this story.
I can't stop it.
Then, shall we move on?
It can't be helped.
Please tell us properly.
What is it?
How to deal with terrorism.
I'll tell you later.
I have a question for you, Mr. Matsumoto.
What is it?
When you go to the hospital when you have a cold,
do you put a stethoscope on your stomach and listen to it?
Do you also put a stethoscope on your back and listen to it?
What is the difference between front and back?
I see, I see.
Please tell me.
I have that.
You don't put it on your stomach, do you?
Don't you put a stethoscope on your back and listen to it?
But I think it's okay to have one of them.
Not the front and back.
No, no.
Don't you want to be more sure?
I see.
I'm sorry to hear the sound of my lungs breathing.
I think so.
You try to do this, right?
You do this, so you have to do this again, right?
You should have done this from the beginning.
You should have done this.
Come on!
As a doctor, you should talk properly.
You should have done this.
But isn't it too early?
That's fine.
Then I'll go to the bus.
The bus?
I'm sorry for the distance.
Where?
Where is the picture?
Why are you looking back?
Have you ever dried your futon?
Yes, I have.
Futon.
I do it to kill the mites.
When I dry this side, the mites run to the back because they don't like the sunlight.
So I have to dry the back side again.
It's the same as that.
For example, when the wind blows like this.
I don't want to go to the back, so I run to the back.
That's what it means.
So you have to do it quickly.
Old men's doctors do this.
They say, next is the back side.
At that time, the wind blows again.
Oh, it's the back side.
Actually, it's like this.
The wind blows like this.
Old men's doctors don't do this.
But can you find it?
If the wind blows like this.
I want you to put a lot of soul into it.
The doctor?
The doctor.
Like this, like this.
Okay, show me your back side.
If you do that, don't come out.
I know.
Oh, it's moving now.
Can I stop?
Can I stop the page?
I don't mind.
I don't mind that.
I'll take off my shoes.
Finally, when the terrorists were attacked.
It was the commander's order.
Terrorists.
Yes.
They're here.
Usually, they go to the chief or something.
They don't go to the station.
But we're not three.
There's no chief role.
You should be the chief.
Hey.
You should have done it right after you got on.
You should have taken off your makeup.
The chief is doing this.
Yes, the chief is here.
What are you doing?
I'm going to New York right now.
Turn back.
Turn back?
You can't do such a stupid thing.
Don't hit your back.
The more you hit your back, the more your back hurts.
If you hit your back twice, it hurts twice.
So stop it.
Hey.
What are you?
Turn back.
I have a job to do.
Even if you tell me to turn back, I won't.
At that time.
Don't do it.
Are you Udon?
Hey, you.
Open the door.
Are you Udon?
Hey, you.
Wait.
What are you doing?
Shut up.
This tree is hijacked.
This tree is hijacked?
The life of the king is on our hands.
It doesn't matter.
This tree.
Everyone was looking forward to going to New York.
You can't do such a thing as turning back.
Shut up.
No.
Return the sword.
Go over there.
Go over there?
Isn't that strange?
Thank you very much.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.