This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
It's been a long time.
It's been two and a half months since I last came here.
Oh, really?
I came here on March 11th.
Well, you didn't.
No, I did.
Well, it's the atmosphere, right?
What atmosphere?
Mentally.
No, no, no, no, no.
I did, I did.
It's been a long time.
Well, I missed you.
But I didn't change the set.
Well, that's...
Oh, is that so?
Otherwise...
Now that you've changed, you've become a bit of a hawaiian.
What's a hawaiian?
You're a hawaiian, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
Why are you making that face?
Don't you know what a hawaiian is?
Not everyone knows.
Well, I think you'll find out next week's Nakabakura.
I'll find out now.
Oh, really?
You didn't do that much?
No, I didn't.
That's kind of weird.
But if your legs are 100% healthy, what would you be like?
Well, I should be about 70 or 80.
Oh, really?
But I can't run.
You can't run?
Why?
Because it hurts.
That's very easy to understand.
The professor's staff made me something great.
What is it?
If you're tired from talking, you can talk like this.
You're the standing lord.
That's cool.
I'm not going to say it now, but you're the standing lord.
Oh, really?
That's very cool.
You're too sweet.
I'm already standing up and walking.
Why?
We've been friends for a long time.
You always say that your knees hurt.
That's terrible.
I wanted to talk and see everyone's faces as soon as possible.
There it is.
That's the worst part.
Why are you laughing?
It was a long time.
If it was just broken, it would have been faster.
This human body was broken.
I should have fixed all the bad parts.
No.
I can't take it because it's broken.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you full of scars?
The skin peeled off a while ago.
The skin peeled off?
There's nothing to peel off.
Why are you full of scars?
What's wrong with you?
I was shaking to see if I could play golf.
My hands were shaking.
You couldn't catch up?
I couldn't catch up.
You haven't played golf for a long time?
I haven't played golf for a long time.
I see. I should have fixed it.
What?
What's wrong with you?
I have to wear a headband.
You...
That's right.
You're angry at the headband, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
You're not angry at me, are you?
You're full of anger, aren't you?
Your headband.
You're angry at the headband, aren't you?
Me?
Both of you.
Next week is the last episode.
Stop talking.
You can look back.
It's one episode before the fire in the candle goes out.
I did it again, didn't I?
What did you do?
A prophecy.
A prophecy? That's a coincidence.
In the past...
There were many times, right?
Like when a meteorite fell.
It happened, didn't it?
In that incident.
That happened, but you still said I didn't have enough glasses.
I didn't say I didn't have enough glasses.
I was surprised when I heard this.
I thought you were wearing them properly.
No, I was preparing for it.
I was surprised when I heard this.
I...
What is it?
It's me, isn't it?
It's me.
The world is like the underwater world.
When I said something in the photo...
It was about two years ago.
At that time, there was a photo of Director Ogi.
Director Ogi had this kind of face in the photo.
When I saw that, I said, I don't have a house.
A few months after that, there was a disaster.
Your house?
Yes.
When I saw the city of Kobe, I said, I don't have a house.
It's really scary, isn't it?
No.
It's really cool, isn't it?
Why?
It's true.
That's why I can't say anything bad.
It's all right.
You're stupid.
Your fracture...
You're lying.
No, no.
Actually, I knew it.
Why did you say that?
Why didn't you say that?
No, no.
I didn't dare to say it.
If I said it, it would be bad.
But we've been together for more than 10 years.
It's been 6 years.
Yes, it's been 16 years.
When I heard that we were going to be together, I said, you have a fracture.
You'll have it someday.
It's not like that.
Since then, I've been thinking about having a fracture.
If it's going to happen someday, you should have told me.
Even if I told you, there's nothing I can do about it.
That's right.
What?
When will it heal completely?
In about a month.
Really?
Yes.
It's going to take a long time.
It's because you're getting older.
If you're young, it'll heal quickly.
It's not like that.
Really?
If it was a bone, it would heal quickly.
Is that so?
You've never had a fracture, have you?
That's right. I've never had a fracture.
Really?
I've never had a fracture.
That's not true.
I've never had a fracture, and I've never had a physical injury.
That's annoying.
If I were to tell you, including you, the audience, and the people watching TV,
if I were to say something to you, it would be,
bean sprouts.
It's bean sprouts, so it's not a fracture.
I wrote this down for you one by one, and gave it to you.
Really.
Why don't you train more?
Hey, you!
I don't know.
Do you understand?
For example, when I take off my rubber band, I don't just take it off.
I force myself to take it off even if I turn around.
If you do that, your body will be trained.
For example, it's easy to take off your rubber band like this,
but if you turn around and take it off like this,
this will...
This part will be trained.
If you're aware of it, you can do six of these.
You can do six of these?
No, really.
You're damaging yourself.
Damaging?
You're bullying yourself.
Damaging and lucky.
Do you understand?
If you don't say it, I understand.
It's better to train your body more.
Then you shouldn't drink milk.
I don't drink it.
If you drink milk, your bones won't break.
No, they won't break.
I've been trained to the point where I can do karate chop.
You'll understand when you see it.
I'll let you chop.
No, no.
You're not Masu Oyama.
Wait a minute.
If it's Masu Oyama, it'll break for sure.
But if it's me, it'll be fine.
There's no point, right?
It's fine.
Even though your leg is injured, you shouldn't do that.
It's fine!
Then do it.
What?
Hurry up and do it.
What did you just say?
You said, huh?
That's the sound here, right?
But it really hurts.
It's fine.
After all, the way you train is different.
Seriously, why do you all have bean sprouts?
The modern people eat too much English food.
That's not true.
What kind of food do you usually eat?
For me, it's senmai.
It's not senmai, it's genmai.
Genmai, genmai.
I'm sorry!
It's fine, it's fine.
You're going to say that to a real idiot!
Seriously!
I eat something like genmai.
Genmai, right?
It's a big mistake to think that sports are good for your body.
You shouldn't do sports.
What do you mean?
I told you to train.
Training is different from doing sports.
The exercise you do in your daily life is because your body was made to do it.
For example, taking an eraser.
Taking an eraser is normal in your daily life, so it's fine.
But if you take an eraser and put it in a bowl...
It's not good for your daily life.
Because of that, your body refuses to do it.
It refuses to do it.
Because of that, your body becomes more and more old.
Is that true for everything?
That's true.
Because no one can blame you for kicking so much.
Isn't that right?
That's how it is.
But even if you're a soccer player, your legs are like this.
That's because I'm trying so hard.
What are you trying so hard for?
My body is trying to catch up with me.
Really? Really?
If I use my muscles, I can do this at first.
But I use them in a strange way.
Really? Really?
It's like this.
You can't do it with your legs like this.
It's different. Everyone is doing it slowly, but it's getting more and more like this.
So I'm doing it, I'm doing it, I'm doing it, I'm doing it.
Don't say that.
At first, say it to a boy.
The second time, say it to a girl.
I'm doing it, I'm doing it.
It's not good.
Sports can be done on a Famicom.
You can't move your fingers on a Famicom.
Do you know Star Fox?
I know, I know.
It's like this.
When you defeat a big boss, it comes like this.
So when you defeat a big boss, you hit it like this.
It feels good.
As expected of a big boss.
It's not very stimulating.
It's like this.
I didn't make it for that.
Do it with that special thing.
That's it.
I'm going to defeat it.
I'm going to jump at first.
A nurse or stewardess will come out.
When I get rid of it, it's like this.
The enemy is coming while I'm doing it.
It's a boss, so if you defeat the boss once, there's a break for a while.
You don't have to do it in a hurry.
You can do it like this.
It's coming out like this, so it's just right.
If you defeat it while doing this, it will come out.
I'm going to go to the next stage with a clear mind.
You're really smelly.
Don't say that.
I'm going to do it while saying that.
Is that so?
It's a completely unrelated story.
Do you know how smelly the car in Tokyo is?
I've been saying it for a long time.
Why can't you see the mirror?
What do you mean?
Something's going on.
There's a T-shape.
There's a mirror on the T-shape road.
You can't see it, can you?
I can't see it.
What do you mean?
Are you going to come in with a mint?
No.
There's a T-shape.
There's a mirror over there.
If you go this way, you can see it.
That's it.
My bonnet is coming out.
I can see it, so it's okay.
It's not okay.
The car body is coming out.
Even if the car body comes out halfway, it won't get in the way.
It's okay if your face comes out of the bonnet.
You're going to be here for a long time.
It's okay if it doesn't get in the way.
Do you know the taxi?
The door opens.
If you close it, you'll get angry.
I did it with my hand.
Try it.
You'll get angry.
I'm doing it here.
Do you know why I'm so angry?
There's a door that opens.
If you close it, you'll get angry.
That's why I'm so angry.
Luigi Talent.
Is it similar?
That's right.
Was it Dentsu?
I don't know.
I'm looking it up somewhere.
It's the same kind of talent as this talent.
They're doing it on their own.
Tsuruya's Luigi Talent has three.
It's weird.
I want to know my Luigi Talent.
He'll tell me if I call him.
Really?
I think your Luigi Talent is Izumiya Shigeru.
It was on something.
I think so.
It's on the women's weekly magazine.
It's similar.
The face is similar.
It's not like that.
It's a character.
Matsutaka and Hong Kong are similar.
It's similar.
When I first heard it, I was surprised.
Then look at it properly.
This is the origin of curry udon.
I used to think it was curry udon.
It's so stupid.
Is it good?
Hong Kong and Matsutaka.
It's definitely like that.
I don't know about that, but it's similar.
It's similar.
Really?
I want to see it again.
I don't know about your Luigi Talent.
It's Izumiya Shigeru.
I know Izumiya Shigeru.
It's a rotten talent.
I want to see it every time.
Hong Kong and Matsutaka are similar.
It's definitely like that.
Everyone is being deceived.
I've been saying that there is no such thing as a rotten talent for a long time.
I'm going to make a movie.
Do you know the last movie?
It's a rotten talent.
It's scary.
You've never seen it, have you?
I've seen it on TV once in a while.
I'm surprised when I see it.
You've seen it, haven't you?
It's a rotten talent.
What are you doing?
Make a cute face.
Hey!
Wow!
It's nostalgic.
It's a cotton ball.
When you become like this, you will never open your own eyes.
I opened my own eyes.
You have a dirty temper.
You open your eyes and look at the atmosphere.
It's so dirty.
I can't open my own eyes.
I was found out.
That's right, but you can open your own eyes.
What's that?
I don't need it.
It's a bed sheet.
No!
It's a sleeping bag, but I don't need a bed sheet.
Thank you very much.
I have a question for Mr. Matsumoto.
Mr. Matsumoto is a super underwear collector.
In particular, he chooses his underwear from a collection of 1,000 pieces every morning.
Among them, there is a very special one.
If you wear this, you can take down any opponent in one shot.
It's a dream underwear.
Can you tell me about Super Hitoshi Magnum?
Sure.
It has nothing to do with underwear.
What is it?
You can take it down in one shot.
Isn't there a fashion that you can't show?
I know that, but I can't take it down in one shot because I'm wearing this.
But there is a fashion that you can't show.
It's a fashion that you can't show.
What is Super Hitoshi Magnum today?
Today, my side is a little knitted.
What?
My side is a little knitted.
My back side is a little knitted.
What is it?
This is not the kind of knitted I wore today.
It's the kind of knitted I wore when I wore it before.
It's a little knitted.
It's always knitted.
What are you talking about?
The one I like the most is the string.
The long string.
What kind of length is that?
It's about 2 cm long.
It's made of Persian carpet.
You don't buy it?
I don't buy it.
I wrap it like this.
That's sick.
Why?
It's not sick.
This is the most fashionable.
It's the ultimate underwear.
In the end, if you wear it, you can make underwear.
There's nothing around here.
And then, you can pull out your panties.
What?
You can pull out your panties.
And then, when it's time, you can make a woman lie down.
You don't do it when it's hot?
I don't do it when it's hot.
I do it when it's hot.
It's a little like this.
Sometimes, I do it like this.
That's...
Teach me how to make a woman lie down.
That's how to make a woman lie down.
I didn't say anything.
I just said it.
I accepted it, so I can't do it anymore.
The other day, I asked Mr. Matsumoto, who was active as a professional specialist in FBI psychological profiling.
What should you do to distinguish between a woman's acting and her true feelings?
It was a light conversation.
At least, the woman I've ever held has never acted.
Hmm...
Well, I'm...
I can't stand it anymore.
That's the worst.
I'm a legendary wimpo.
What?
That's why I can see it now.
That's...
A man should try it once.
No, I want to try it.
You say it's good, right?
When you say it, you say,
Yes, sir!
But when you're acting, you say,
What time is it tomorrow?
What did you do tomorrow?
I'm a professional.
But if you're asked if you're acting, what would you do?
I don't want to say that I'm scared.
No, I understand.
I don't understand anything, so I didn't ask.
It's not about the eyes.
For example, when you feed a cat,
When you feed a cat,
If it's a white fish,
That's the woman I've ever held.
That's not just you, is it?
The sofa will jump over.
This program was provided by the sponsor you see.