Please listen to me!
You're not good at it!
Why am I not good at it?
It has nothing to do with it!
There's a reason for it!
Please listen to me!
I'm really sorry about the other day.
I apologize.
What do you mean by the other day?
Ah, the super-dirty thing.
Thank you very much for telling me about the super-dirty thing.
I saw it with my own eyes, but it wasn't super-dirty at all!
That's not good.
It's not good at all!
Last time, Yamazaki's one-man show of affection didn't reach his opponent.
It ended in failure.
That's why, today, I'll do my best!
Your best?
My best!
I'll do my best with all my heart and soul!
You're so noisy.
People are passing by.
You don't know your position.
You're a good-for-nothing.
You're a good-for-nothing!
Today, I really mean it.
That's why, today...
Why are you here all of a sudden?
Today, I'll make you meet a wonderful person.
You'll make me feel good?
Yes.
And I'll make you dirty.
I'll make you dirty?
I'll make you dirty!
Dirty entertainer.
It's the end of a long journey in the entertainment world.
Everyone else avoids the dirty entertainer.
The second episode of Yamazaki Super Dirty.
Who will be today's opponent?
Please watch.
I'll make you dirty!
Why are you making me dirty all of a sudden?
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Why?
Excuse me.
Hello.
You're not cute at all.
I'm really busy today.
It's okay.
Just relax.
Wait a minute.
Nice to meet you. I'm Hosei.
You came before?
Really?
I've seen you before.
Yes.
Really?
Don't say anything.
Are you nervous?
Why are you nervous?
You have a wide shoulder.
What?
How tall are you?
42 cm?
I can't see.
I really can't see.
Who are you?
What character do you want to be?
Excuse me.
Really?
There's a lot of water here.
It's amazing.
Excuse me.
There's a lot of water here.
Do you want to see my nails?
Your nails are long.
Your nails are really hard.
You have a lot of hair.
It's funny.
What are you doing?
Excuse me.
First of all, I'd like to have a powder.
I'm tired.
Excuse me.
You're pale.
I have a lot of hair.
Don't laugh.
I don't want to laugh.
I have a lot of hair.
You have a lot of hair.
Excuse me.
It's been a while.
What do you want to do?
Excuse me.
Please sit down.
It's embarrassing.
I'll show you.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
It's beautiful.
Your butt is round.
What?
It hurts.
Are you okay?
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
I'll put it in your butt.
It's coming out.
What?
What's coming out?
What are you doing?
Excuse me.
Please sit down.
That's the thing.
It hurts.
Excuse me.
Please sit down.
I don't want to call you.
Excuse me.
Please sit down.
I took it off.
It's a mistake.
It's a good timing.
How was it?
You're wearing panties.
It was fun.
I did my best today.
I wonder if the people watching TV will laugh.
I'm not making them laugh, I'm making them laugh.
I see.
I hope there will be a next time.
Yes, I'll do my best next time.
I'm going to ask the child caretaker to do it.
Hello, I'm a woman.
No, no.
Yes, yes.
I'm going to watch TV from now on.
No, no, no.
That's rude.
I'm wearing panties.
It's normal to watch TV like this.
There are times when you wear slippers.
Slippers?
It's barefoot.
What is this?
It's a costume for buying Caster Mild.
Like this.
Let's take a burst shot.
Really?
I don't know what this is.
What is this?
It's the costume I wore yesterday.
The costume?
Only I know.
I don't know.
Is this the costume you wore yesterday?
No.
Why are you doing this?
I can't do foot acting.
No, no.
I said it from my nails.
I said it would be revealed.
You said it too much.
No, no.
The other person is wearing it.
What do you call that?
What do you call this?
How do you call this?
We call it Dotsun.
What?
I'm scared.
No, no.
How do you call this?
Say it again.
No, no.
How do you call this?
What?
Goodbye.
This is really hard.
You can't do this.
Why?
You said it from your nails.
No, no.
I don't wear socks.
I can't do this.
What is this?
It's a castor mild.
No, no.
I don't wear it at all.
It's a burst shot today.
How do you call this?
No, no.
I said Dotsun yesterday.
Well, I know it.
Everyone knows it.
What do you call this?
This?
No.
Why are you doing this?
I can't do foot acting.
I said it from my nails.
You said it too fast.
Well, I'm trying too hard.
You said it from your nails.
I don't know anymore.
I can't do what I used to do.
That's right.
I can't do it anymore.
You can't do it anymore.
It's true.
I'm going to be like Hamada Masato.
That's too fast.
I'm going to be like him.
I'm going to be like Hamada Masato.
That's true.
Congratulations.
Why are you clapping?
What do you mean congratulations?
I don't know.
Seriously.
I'm going to be like Joe Yabanzuke.
What?
Did you kill him?
Why?
You're number one.
Congratulations on being number two.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to talk about this.
But there's going to be another announcement tomorrow or the day after.
I was going to do it earlier.
Well.
Everyone, look at this.
This is number one.
Number one has a nose like this.
But next year, I'm not going to be in the top ten.
I'm not going to do anything bad.
I originally had that kind of income.
But something happened.
You're definitely going to be number one next year.
Why do you say that?
No, no, no.
I'm going to release a lot of CDs.
How many times have I said that?
Don't say that.
You're a fool.
You have a lot of money.
Is that true?
It's true.
You have a lot of money.
If you sell a million or two million copies, what kind of pose is that?
I thought it was a little hard.
I just did it like this.
It's like something's going to start from here.
It's scary.
When I was in front of you the other day, there was a toilet like this.
Don't you know?
Look.
It's like this.
Do you know?
Look carefully.
Don't look at me with thin eyes.
Look at me clearly.
I know.
It's like this.
There was blood.
Was that a man's toilet?
Yes.
What do you think?
Wasn't it a man's toilet?
No, no, no.
Was it a man's toilet?
Yes.
What do you think?
I don't know.
I looked at the toilet and there was blood.
I was surprised.
I was worried.
There was blood on the toilet.
Was it on this part of the toilet seat?
No, no.
I have to go to the toilet.
There are times when you go to the toilet like this.
No, no.
It's on the right side of the toilet.
You have to say that.
There was blood on this part.
I thought it was our joke.
There was blood on your shoulder.
There is no such thing as a scary thing.
What are you talking about?
There was blood on your shoulder.
I remember that.
If that was the case, you should have gone to the toilet.
What is that?
Did you look at the ceiling at that time?
Maybe the blood was coming from the ceiling.
I didn't see that.
Why was there blood coming from the ceiling?
Maybe it was leaking from the toilet space.
What is it?
Maybe it was leaking from the space above.
What?
The upper part of the toilet room is a toilet seen as a fact.
I see.
Why did you say that?
Something was on the up part.
There was something on top of the toilet.
Maybe there was blood on the upper part of the toilet.
You should not look at the upper part of the roof.
Maybe there was nothing there.
What do you mean by that?
It's a happy ending.
What are you talking about?
At that time, I can't be happy.
There are such strange things.
Is that so?
It's unimaginable.
I used to say this before, but I sometimes say this.
I went to the bathroom and came out.
When I looked at it, there was a lot of shit on my nose.
What kind of life are you living?
This is...
I'm sorry.
There are such strange things.
Wait a minute.
This is a little too funny.
Why did you go to the bathroom and come out?
I don't know, but there are such things.
I'm your...
What is it?
Are you a Satsuma person?
I'm doing a lot of rose-colored life right now.
I'm doing it now.
Is there anyone you want me to look for?
Why?
Tochi's mother.
You used to work part-time.
You were dug up.
Is there anyone you want me to look for?
There's only one person.
Who?
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
Do you know Shakutani?
I know.
I'm looking for Shakutani.
Why?
Why do you call me?
It's a good story.
I had a hard time saying goodbye to Shakutani.
Is that so?
No, there was a guy called Shakutani.
When I was in elementary school, I had a lot of friends.
You just want to say Shakutani.
No, no, no.
Shakutani was a little bullied.
But we were good friends.
For some reason, I couldn't bully Shakutani.
Is that so?
Shakutani was very...
You really wanted to say that.
No, I didn't.
Shakutani was very fond of me.
Really?
Shakutani and I were taking a dump on our way home from school.
Then Shakutani started saying,
I got a mole.
That's why I can't bully you.
Then we went to Shakutani's house.
Shakutani went to change his underwear.
I was waiting for him at home.
I said, I'm sorry.
Then I took off my underwear and wiped it.
Then I changed my underwear to blue.
I was watching it all the time.
Shakutani said,
Don't tell anyone about this.
I'll be bullied again.
I said, I can't say that.
I said a lot the next day.
Then Shakutani was bullied a lot.
He looked at me with a grumpy face.
There are children like that.
Yes, there are.
If I told him to stop there, I might be bullied.
I thought I had to apologize to Shakutani.
From then on, my relationship with Shakutani became strange.
That's right.
Shakutani was betrayed.
That's great.
Then I moved to Shakutani.
Shakutani couldn't catch up with me.
I don't like it when you say that now.
I don't know what Shakutani is doing.
I don't know where Shakutani moved to.
That's great.
I'm looking for someone like that.
I have to apologize to Shakutani.
Then let's go out.
I'm going to meet Shakutani again.
I'm a scary old man.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to be a yakuza from now on.
Shakutani.
I don't know who Shakutani is.
I don't know why.
Shakutani.
I have a question for Mr. Matsumoto, who produces all the CM songs, lyrics, and choreography.
I heard that there is a sequel to that song.
What kind of song is it?
Are you the one who choreographed the choreography?
Yes, I am.
I've been thinking about it for three days.
Really?
What kind of lyrics was it?
Let's choose a wife, Mirin.
Let's do it twice.
You chose that song, didn't you?
It's probably because it's me.
What?
You asked me to do it.
Yes.
I asked you to do it.
Hiromi usually says good things about me.
Hiromi?
I gave her my advice.
How many years ago?
You're an amateur.
Please tell me the sequel.
Yes, yes, yes.
This is the first version.
It's a regular Koterinko, right?
Yes.
Next is Koterinko Mini.
I see.
Next is Koterinko Curry.
It's Mirin.
Why does it taste like curry?
Let's choose a wife, Mirin.
That one, right?
Yes, that one.
Next is let's choose a wife, Mirin.
What are you talking about?
Do you know this one?
Wife.
You're just pretending.
Let's choose a wife, Mirin.
Koterinko.
Next one is a new one.
Let's choose a wife, Mirin.
What are you talking about?
Wife, wife.
Why is this a wife?
I don't care.
Please look at it.
It will be released soon.
Really?
Yes.
It will be released soon.
Did you just say hey?
Why do you keep saying hey?
Matsumoto-san, who won the first time in Koshien as a first-year ace, but left the baseball world for some reason.
When you lose in Koshien at 9 o'clock in high school, you take the soil home, but what do you use that soil for?
Did you take it home?
I didn't lose, so I didn't take it home.
There are many people who think that they take the soil home because they lost in Koshien.
I see.
I didn't take the soil home because I lost in Koshien.
Why?
If you lose, you have to take the soil home.
It's not because of baseball.
That tradition only remains in high school baseball.
For example, if you like a woman and she changes her clothes, you don't take the soil home.
Because it's a complete defeat.
Even if you lose in that sense, you don't take it home.
That's right.
It's not just high school baseball.
Where did you change your clothes and find out?
For example, when I went to her house and tried to do it, it smelled really bad.
I have no choice but to cry.
I cry a lot.
You don't have to cry.
I sing a song.
What?
There?
There.
While crying?
While crying.
Then I take the soil from the garden in that house and run home.
You have to run.
It looks like a nail.