Whether Selig wins or Parig wins, it's a punishment game if you lose.
This time it's amazing.
What is it?
Skydiving.
If I do it, it's Parig.
What about you?
Parig.
Then you're Selig, right?
Hello.
Are you playing golf?
Selig is going to win today.
One point, three points.
That's not good.
Who's next?
Parig, Parig, Parig, Parig.
What the hell is that?
What are you talking about?
Are you kidding me?
Thank you.
It's 0-0, right?
Yes, it's 0-0.
Do what you want.
J.O.L.
Let him go.
This program is brought to you by the first sponsor and the sponsor you are about to see.
Hey!
Don't just stand there!
Give me a double!
Bro, can you fly instead of me?
Hey! Don't just stand there!
Did it go in?
It went in!
Yes!
This guy is tough!
Hey, drink it!
Alright, alright!
I only have Hoshihuma left to drink!
Really!
Come on!
Why is this guy sweating so much?
He's fat!
That's right, this guy is weird!
His throat is dry!
Right?
Alright!
Oh no!
It went in!
Alright!
Out!
It's out, right?
It's out, it's out!
It's over?
It's over!
What is this crazy way to end it?
Hey! Come on!
You're so lame!
Hamada-kun, let's have you fly!
I'm sorry.
Good job!
This is my last show!
I don't want to see you ever again!
Hamada-kun, I think you're in a really good mood.
In the end, I just want to say that I have a lot of other friends.
Hello!
Hello, really!
How was it today?
What do you mean?
I thought about a lot of things from America.
When it came to skydiving.
I'm sorry to say this, but I don't need it!
Wait!
What?
I'm sorry.
I've been saying that I don't need it!
Yeah, so I don't need it anymore.
Is there such a reason?
If I don't need it, then I don't need it either!
No, no, that's a different story.
Why?
I...
Yeah?
You told me to do it, but I've been saying that I don't need it since I was in the dressing room.
I don't need it!
Then it's your fault!
Why don't you need it?
I don't need it.
I used to have a weird habit.
What kind of habit?
If you fly from high up, you'll have a weird feeling.
I don't need it.
You probably won't be able to capture it.
There are other things.
That's why I told you to be more detailed.
More detailed.
Yeah.
A little bit more.
A little bit more?
You don't have to zoom in and look like a crazy person like this.
Yeah, right?
You have to be shy and think about that.
From such a high place...
You really don't need to be shy.
I don't need to be shy!
What are you going to do?
It's scary.
Everyone does it.
You don't have the guts to jump in first.
You'll be pushed from behind.
That's right.
You won't be able to jump in, so the instructor behind you will do it.
Otherwise, it won't start, no matter how long it takes.
If I don't do it, I'll fall and get pushed in.
That's what I'm looking for!
Really.
It's unbearable.
It's impossible.
You have to get to your destination.
You don't know where you'll land depending on the direction.
Right?
You'll be scared.
You'll be scared again if you're at the yakuza office.
Why?
You'll be scared.
You'll be able to get out of the window cleanly.
You'll be scared again.
It's a double fear.
You'll fall and get out of the window cleanly.
But if you faint the moment you get out, it'll look cool.
That's cool too.
You'll come down and make a big noise.
It'll be scary and you'll be a white rock.
I don't know about that.
You'll be a white rock but what will you do if I fall?
That's not true.
I'll tie you up here.
Seriously.
What should I do?
I told you.
Skydiving...
Go home.
You said it.
I kicked you.
See? See? See?
So stop skydiving and get into the cage.
That's fine.
It's fine, right?
You won't be able to get in.
That's right.
If it's a cage.
But Takasu from Kosei said that if the shark is small, it'll get in.
That's scary.
If it's small, it'll be fine.
Well, if it's small...
If it's this small, it'll eat more than half of your mouth.
That's gross.
What?
And if it's a big shark, it'll be small.
It's big.
If you look at it from afar, it's big.
But if you look at it from close up, it's this big.
It's the type to sweat.
What are you wearing?
Are you wearing something?
If it comes in like that, it'll be scary.
But that's fine.
Basically...
If you talk to the staff, for example, if you're going to fly,
I'll be the instructor.
I'll make sure you get in.
I'll tell you where to go.
But you don't have a parachute.
If you just fix it here, your back and stomach.
The teacher's back has a parachute.
So...
Damn it.
I'm going to take off my glasses.
Don't be so modest!
If you lose your temper, you'll have to do a lot of jokes while you're flying.
If you lose your temper, you'll have only one finger.
I see.
This is bad.
I'm really happy to be able to do this in this world.
What are you talking about?
If you die in a variety show, that's fine.
At the beginning?
That's fine.
But when I die, there will be a lot of people who are in trouble.
Who?
No one can tell.
Even if you do something like that.
I'll be in trouble if I die.
If you die, the conversation between you two will end.
I'll be in trouble.
But...
But if you die in a variety show, you'll have to do a lot of jokes while you're flying.
I really hate it!
If I die, the funeral will probably be a mess.
That's too bad.
But if I lose, I'll be in trouble.
If I lose, the next day I'll be looking for someone who looks like me.
Even if I went to Thailand, I wouldn't be there.
It's hard to find someone who looks like you in Japan.
It's harder to find someone who looks like you in the Philippines.
Wow!
This is really bad.
I was looking for someone who looked like me on TV.
If you lose this time, you'll have to cut the pipe.
I want to lose.
Even if you cut the pipe, you can't get it back.
Really?
Really.
You can't get it back.
Why?
You're so detailed.
I've already tried it.
If you think I'm funny, you can cut it.
And if you think I want a kid, you can get it back.
Really?
Yeah.
Even if you do that, it's no use.
Where is the proof of the punishment?
Kyo-Boku, you said you've already cut the pipe, so you can't put out the pipe here.
I can't tell if I did.
Right?
I was like, let's see!
But they still came out
What are we going to do?
Eh?
How are we going to prove that they came out?
We're going to show them that we're good
Normally there would be people like this
But at the start everyone was like this
Everyone was like
I'm going to die
That's right
You have to be able to tell by looking at them
If you were given a prize, how many times would you be able to fly?
That one was better, the bungee jump
No, that one was worse
The one where you put a rope on your leg
There's that one, right?
From the top
To the very edge
That's from some country, right?
It's like a ceremony
It's like falling from a tree
That's right
There's also a country where you put a bone on your nose at the ceremony
Foreigners really don't know what they're thinking
But apparently that's how it is
Last year I was watching the news
About a dog raising an octopus
It's a dog that loves to raise octopuses
I was doing a VTR in the morning
The octopus was going up
The dog was forced to be tied up here
The dog was doing that
The octopus was going up like this
You don't know how many dogs there are
There was no reaction
It was normal
It was going up like this
I love to raise octopuses
Hello
You're smiling
I am
Let me introduce this person
What?
Is this really you?
You're not
You're mistaken
Why am I mistaken?
Shut up!
You're mistaken
This is rude
Let's ask him directly
What's your name?
I'm Kato Fumiya
Kato Fumiya
You have a nice bust
How many centimeters?
I don't know
You've never measured it?
Bring me a measuring tape
Are you putting something in?
I'm not
You're not putting anything in
See?
You're so full of yourself
You're really full of yourself
Do you have a boyfriend?
I don't have any friends
Friends?
I have a lot of friends
Are they your friends?
Thank you
I'm sorry
Let's ask him
Well then
This person
He's from Ibaraki
His pen name is Hide
I always watch your videos
By the way
In Nonno
What do you mean by Nonno?
There are 100 men you want to date
Matsumoto-san is in the 50th place
Congratulations
Hamaya-san is in the 69th place
So did you lose to Ucchan and Nanchan
Over your thoughts?
Where is Nanchan in the 10th place?
Nanchan is in the 10th place
Nanchan is in the 10th place?
You're lying
Nanchan was in the top of the list
Nanchan was in the top of the list?
Really?
Who else is there?
Then you said earlier
I'm in the 50th place
It's 50, right? That means there are 49 people up there, right?
Who's there?
The one who bought it from me!
And then...
This...
Which one should I go with?
Anything?
What?
Ah, I'll go with this one.
Nakano-kun's...
Kawawa Akira-kun.
That's dirty.
Your nose will come out too, right?
Since a while ago, Machan has been saying that he doesn't come to work.
But in the ending, I saw the two of you leaving.
I understood that Machan hates his job.
Hama-chan is acting cute in front of the camera.
But Machan doesn't even look at him.
Even when he gets close to the camera, he looks like he doesn't like it.
He ignores it.
What's the real thing? Please tell me.
At the end... that's right.
Ah, I'm that kind of person.
I'm that kind of person who looks at the viewers and...
I'm that kind of person who sucks up to them and...
No, it doesn't matter when you're talking in the ending.
When you're done and the show is over,
and everyone is going to the side,
the camera is facing you.
You can go home like that.
I don't need that kind of thing.
It doesn't matter.
Why?
Eh?
It's already over.
When the camera turns, it's the end.
Don't act like you're cute.
You're trying to look cute.
It's obvious.
Don't point your finger.
Really.
When the camera is facing you,
you'll Krishna how the staff is doing.
Then the camera is facing you.
I don't need that.
It's already over.
If it's an ending, I wouldn't eat it.
I don't eat it.
I don't need that kind of thing.
Why?
But you know, there's always a cut, a premeditated cut
I'll end it here. I wonder if you'll watch it tomorrow as well?
I'll say, I'm fine, and then there'll be a commercial
And by the time I come back, the commercials are usually like this
I'll be back soon! And suddenly everyone's like this
That's what I don't like
I said, I don't like it! You're doing it for fun!
Eh?
I'm just barely next to you
It's annoying
I said, I don't like it!
If you go to a commercial again, it'll be normal
Eh?
You know, that...
Don't do it again!
You'll be in trouble for a long time
Hey!
You'll be in trouble
What are you talking about?
Eh?
You're close! You're the next good friend, the premeditated cut, and you won't go wild
What?
Make a promise here
What promise?
When everyone's like this, you'll be in trouble
How?
Tamori-san will be next to you, and you'll be right next to him
What are you doing?
Right?
What?
That's annoying
If you don't like it
Do you understand?
Eh?
The last one
Adachi-kun, Machan and Hama-chan, is there anyone you don't like to be called by your name?
Ah...
No, I don't think so
But I don't really like it
Eh?
When I'm called
When you say I'm a bad guy, I get a little angry
Ah, but that's not true
But you know, when I was in Osaka, there was a car going south, in front of the Hori-ren
And the woman was in the front seat, and she said,
Ah, it's Hama!
That's not true
Men are the ones who smile and say, Ah, it's Hama!
So I thought, is there anything wrong with being a man?
You're good
You're flamboyant
Sparkle, sparkle, sparkle
I don't know that
But sometimes...
Ah, I'm not calling you by your name, but
From elementary school to middle school, there was a guy who bullied me
Morioka
It's a little different from calling you by your name, but
That bully, bully, bully Morioka
When I was about 20, I met him
It's been a while
But I'm an adult now
In the past, I was bullied
A man who became a good man, I met him on the street
I can't bully him again
In the past, I thought, let's just let the water flow
But Morioka came from the other side
So I said, Yes!
And then Morioka
Then Morioka replied, Yes!
This made me angry
That's what happened
The water flowed
Even if the water flowed, I would still be called by you
Then what should I call Morioka?
We're the same age and we're in the same class
Why?
That's...
What's wrong with you?
I don't care
I'd be angry if Morioka did that
I don't know what Morioka is
What Morioka?
I don't know what that is
Come here, Morioka
You bullied Morioka, didn't you?
I didn't bully him
You did
What?
Morioka is bad
Why?
He has a lot of things to bully
He plays and suddenly goes home
He goes home
It's annoying
He plays and suddenly goes home?
He doesn't say anything about going home
It's annoying
I don't know what Morioka is
He goes home
Morioka is stupid
Morioka is poor
That's ridiculous
Everyone gathers at the birthday party
Everyone
Minicar
Everyone gives presents
Everyone gathers at Kyoudo's house
I don't know
Kyoudo
He seems rich
Everyone gathers
Kyou-chan, I'm a minicar
Kyou-chan, I'm a...
I only know Takasu
Robot
Everyone gathers around 1000 yen
Morioka is poor
He wants to be late
If you open the door, Morioka will come from the other side
That's why he walks
Why is it Sparta X?
Morioka is beaten and walks
What is Morioka's birthday present?
I don't have money, so what do I want to bring?
Kyou-chan
Two pencils
Hello, I'm Emil
Nice to meet you
It's time for Kin-chan's photo album
Yes
Let's talk about the idea
There were some ideas
Really?
There were some ideas that we could improve
This time, we will definitely participate in the main event
The other day, when I went to drink at Roppongi, I met the producer of Kaso Taisei
Yes
I asked him
This time, we will participate in the main event
Thank you for the other day
Next time, we will participate in the main event
Thank you
Kyou-chan
Yes
What about the other side?
I will do it
I'm going to close my eyes
This time, I will do it
You will do it
You used to smile
Which side?
I will do it
I will do it like this
I don't know if it will be helpful
Yes
I will do it
I will definitely participate in the main event
I will do my best
Everything will be the same
Please look forward to it