This is the first time I've ever seen this kind of performance.
Oh, you're still in good shape.
Yes, I'm in good shape.
I'm glad I stood up.
I'm glad I stood up and did the Guts pose.
I'm sure the people who are watching this will understand.
There's no seats in the audience at all.
This is the first time I've ever seen this kind of performance.
Thank you. I'll hit you later.
The other day, we had a golf match.
I went to see it.
You went to see it. Was it in the middle of the show?
That's right.
We did it.
I want you to see it today.
I don't know the result until I see it.
I dare not comment on anything.
If you want to say it, say it now.
I think it's better to see it after listening to a lot of stories.
It's dirty.
This guy is really dirty.
That's all I'm going to say.
Wait a minute.
What's so dirty about it?
It looks like I'm going to have a bad temper.
But...
This guy is so dirty.
I'm going to play golf from now on.
When I'm scared, I'll do this.
Don't do that.
That's not good.
That's because you told me first.
I didn't say anything.
If you try to hit me like this, I'll hit you.
Then I'll say, I don't want to hit you.
You've been saying it all the time.
I don't want to hit you.
That's why you're doing it and I'm saying it.
That's all.
What's so dirty about it?
I don't want to hit you.
Is that true?
You said you didn't want to hit me first.
If you complain about that, you can't play golf.
Let's watch the game.
I'm sure there are various opinions.
I'll ask you later.
Please watch it.
Umekichi is...
Umekichi is a little...
It's the other way around.
Umekichi.
This is the golf course.
I'll be waiting for you.
I don't usually use the key.
So I'll play a penalty game.
Welcome.
Golf match play.
Let me explain the rules.
What is it?
I'll do it five times.
Okay.
The three I took earlier are hidden.
If you lose,
you have to go to the golf course.
And you have to wait in the dressing room.
So a professional will come to my house.
Yes.
Only two.
And I have to put it in the otaku's place.
You have to put it in?
Yes.
So today,
I've been staying in the parking lot all the time.
Umekichi.
It's about time you got your name.
Yes.
Has Umekichi ever played golf?
I've only seen it.
You've only seen it?
Yes.
I've never seen it.
You'll use Umekichi only once.
And you'll play until you hit the target.
Until you hit the target.
How many times are you going to hit the target?
But Umekichi is not an ordinary old lady.
I'm not an ordinary old lady.
You're not an ordinary old lady.
If you look closely, you'll see.
Umekichi has a little beard.
That's how Umekichi is.
Is this that?
Really?
I'll get a prize for this.
Oh!
Umekichi, you're really good.
What is that?
Hey, this is a serious sport.
You're going to miss.
Oh!
Here we go.
I wanted to say this.
Oh, it's out.
Hey!
Nice shot!
You're really good.
But this is going to be the seventh hit.
If it's the seventh hit, no one will notice.
No one will notice.
Oh, no!
Where did you hit it?
Don't fall!
It fell!
You're really good.
Umekichi.
Yes?
Mark it.
Yes.
What?
You're going to hit a 10-yen coin?
Hey!
You're the one who marked it.
It's a fox.
It's over?
It's not working again.
Oh, it went over there.
It's not going to work.
Hey, Ita.
Yes?
I'm going to use a chance card here.
I'm going to ask a professional.
I'm Go Meiges.
I'm sorry that this kind of person is on our show.
I'm really sorry.
Then, in place of Machiko,
Me?
Yes.
It's sudden, but...
It's the red flag.
I know!
I know.
Please don't sing this song.
It's easier to hit over there.
No, no, no.
I don't need that kind of joke.
Seriously.
Please listen to Haritomo.
Nice shot!
It's on, it's on, it's on.
Oh, it's falling, it's falling.
Oh, it's on.
Nice shot!
Thank you very much.
Hey, did you all see that?
Good, good, good.
Should I run a little too much?
There are six of us.
Three, four, five, six.
Right?
What do you know?
Oh, this is a complicated course.
It's not easy.
You're the only one left.
Stop blowing.
Seriously.
That's really dirty.
Yours is dirty.
I'll do something about it.
Demi, your blow is the most dirty.
No, you didn't cut it.
Oh, it's on.
Miracle shot.
It's on.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Good, good, good.
That really hurt.
You're doing it on purpose.
What?
You hit it five times.
I'll put this in.
What are you doing?
Let's use Umekichi.
Umekichi.
What kind of man are you?
You.
You were running happily.
Please, please.
Umekichi.
Without this.
I thought I had a bullet.
It's big.
I won't teach you.
Take your time, Umekichi.
Take your time.
How's your girlfriend doing?
I don't care.
I'll put this in either way.
Oh, even?
This music...
I left a good one.
This is difficult.
What if I put this in?
Why?
I can't put this in.
I'm in trouble next time.
Next.
That's it.
What?
It's dirty.
You're still doing it?
You're persistent.
It's really dirty.
So, Matsumoto-kun.
Penalty game.
Why do I have to get a penalty?
I just played golf.
I'm having fun playing.
Why do I have to get a penalty?
Please go to Sanshi-san's place.
Who's that?
Katsura Sanshi-san.
I don't know. I've seen him.
He's one of our seniors.
He's Katsura Sanshi's master.
I don't know.
Anyway, I'll get a penalty for Matsumoto-kun.
Thank you very much.
I won't do it again.
It looks scary, doesn't it?
You saw it, didn't you?
It's dirty.
What's dirty?
This is my first time playing golf.
I think I was pretty good.
You were pretty good.
Umekichi...
What do you mean by Umekichi?
You're telling me too many details.
That's not true.
You're a pro.
You're telling me to do what I want to do.
I was on the air for a while.
But before that, he was so annoying.
Umekichi, do this, do that.
He kept making me do it.
There was a group of foreigners who were playing before me.
When the group of foreigners were playing,
Umekichi said,
I don't think that's right.
The foreigners were like,
Hey, can I?
And they got angry.
They were so angry that
the foreigners started speaking Japanese.
The person I just introduced is
this person, right?
This is him.
This person is
Mr. Asano Chisato.
He has a driver's license and...
What is this?
What is a first-class driver's license?
It's a normal driver's license.
A normal driver's license.
Oh, I see.
It means you're in good health.
Why are you taking it off all of a sudden?
Just in case.
It's a matter of course.
Is that so?
I don't have any intentions.
I like sports and swimming.
Thank you very much.
Are you going to take it home?
Goodbye.
The other day, I was wiping the blackboard,
and my nails hit the blackboard,
and it made a noise,
and everyone told me to die.
I don't hate it,
but why do you hate that sound so much?
Do you hate this sound?
By the way, what I hate is
when I put a spoon on my teeth.
It hits, but you don't hate it, do you?
When you drink something,
you sometimes say,
Oh, you don't like it?
No, I don't hate the sound of the blackboard.
Why do you hate it?
I don't hate it.
No way.
And your blood vessels are also painful, aren't they?
What?
Blood vessels, blood vessels.
What does that mean?
There are many things that humans can't stand.
If you put ice here, it will be terrible.
So why do you do that?
Why do you put ice here in your normal life?
What?
So why do you put it here?
There are many reasons to put ice here.
Why do you put ice here?
What?
Don't ask me again.
Why do you put it here?
Putting ice here is a daily routine.
Absolutely.
Hello, I'm Sahanji, a daily person.
You know...
What?
What do you do to put ice here?
No, no.
I was just making a joke.
Oh, I see.
I'm a girl who loves you, Hama-chan.
I have a problem.
I have the same problem as you.
This guy is the only one who says it stinks.
Have you ever smelled my room?
This guy...
What?
I'm the only one who says it?
That's right.
You're the only one who says it.
What are you saying?
I'm lying, but I'm saying it.
You're the only one who says it.
Other people say it stinks.
I'm used to it now.
When I smelled your room for the first time,
I thought there was poop on my nose.
I thought it was strange.
You didn't feel that the smell was close to you?
It smelled so close to me.
I'm so busy with my nose hair.
What's wrong with your nose hair?
Something I've never been in before is trying to get through.
My nose hair is all over the place.
That's amazing.
It's all over the place.
Seriously.
That's right.
How many times have I said it stinks?
Foreigners can't speak Japanese at all.
It's the same as before.
When I smelled your room for the first time,
I thought it smelled so close to me.
That's your instinct.
My instinct.
You thought it smelled so close to you.
That's right.
I've never spoken to a child before.
I've never been born.
I've never been a mother or a mother.
I thought it smelled so close to me.
That's about it.
But I understand how you feel.
That's enough.
In the end, when something happens,
you'll show your bad temper.
For example?
For example, your grandmother is in trouble at the traffic light.
She can't cross the street.
You'll look at that and pretend not to see it, right?
Not at all.
What will you do?
I'll pull her hand.
You'll never do that.
I'll do it.
What?
What are you going to do?
What do you mean?
nei
What will you do?
You're telling me this.
What will you do if your grandmother is there?
What do you do if your grandmother is there?
What do I do?
What will you do?
What will you do if your grandmother is there?
If the traffic light doesn't come through?
What will you do?
If the traffic light doesn't come through,
I don't know
You said that
What did I say?
The traffic light is blue
You said that
That's why the traffic light is blue
You said that so I'm going home
I'm going home
It's a normal road
Sometimes the car goes like this
If you look at it like this
There's an old lady
I can't go
What if there's an old lady like that?
But there's no old lady trying to cross that road
I don't think there will be
You're so stubborn
I want to cross
No matter what
There's always something
Old ladies have a strong faith so it's okay
What do you mean by faith?
They have a lot of protection
That has nothing to do with it
What if there's an old lady in trouble?
What are you talking about?
What trouble are you talking about?
The stairs to the church are long
They're long
If you're young you can go up
But the old ladies
One by one
You can't go like this
You have to wear kimono
You have to go up
What if there's an old lady like that?
An old lady like that?
The stairs
But you can go up
I don't have any luggage
I forgot
I have luggage
One by one
How old are you?
I'm close to 70
60 something
When I say old ladies
I start from 75
Sorry I forgot
I forgot
75 old ladies
Stubborn old ladies
Genki
It's like someone's comedy
What if there's an old lady like that?
What are you going to do?
It's dirty
What's dirty?
What are you going to do when there's an old lady like that?
I'll help you
How?
I'll do this
What is this?
I'll hold the old lady
I'll hold her
I'll definitely do it
I'll do it
When I'm walking down the street
The old lady will say
My stomach hurts
I'm scared so I'll go
The game is over
It's time for the punishment
The punishment
This year
We can show it to everyone
And
In front of our school
We're doing
That show
A special show
We're doing
This is December 29th
Saturday from 2 to 3
Until the 25th
We're doing a special show
It's fun
If we win
We'll do a punishment game
We'll do
Dance, dance, dance
That's good
Let's do it
So for us
We'll go
This is
The first event
Please do your best
Please look forward to it
Let's do it
This program was sponsored by
KON why