The fifth time, Chikitsuki Gerojin Tsuri Senchiku!
This is the annual big event.
We've already passed the fifth time.
Let's introduce him right away.
He trains his body with a training machine every day and night.
Matsumoto!
Thank you.
I'll do it today.
Please.
I'll catch something I've never seen before.
Please say Basushu.
We'll do it today too.
Please come in.
There are rumors that you'll quit being a copywriter and become a professional.
Itoi Shinhano-san!
I'm not happy, but is it okay?
No, it's totally fine.
You're in a good mood today.
No, I'm totally fine.
Please take care of me.
The person who will make your life full of joy.
The king of the music world, Okuda Tamiya-san!
Thank you!
How is your confidence today?
I have confidence!
You have?
I have confidence today!
Really?
Then, please do your best!
Thank you!
The future happiness of the newly married couple!
Eguchi Yosuke!
You are married and you are tired of the work.
I think you're going to catch a good fish.
That's right.
I'll ask you a little more.
How do you call your wife at home?
Stop it.
Stop it. It's normal.
It's normal.
Soon.
I'll win today.
I won't wake you up anymore.
I'll call your name.
I told you to stop it.
Good luck.
Thank you very much!
Where did the cute guy from the debut go?
Recently, he has been very popular, Mr. Yamada Keho Asaya!
I will continue to help you if there is a chance to laugh.
I'm crying now, but...
Let's continue to help.
The man with a tall body who was shining in the drama, Samurai Ikki!
Hello!
Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you too.
Are you a fisherman?
This is my first time.
What?
This is your first time?
Everyone has fishing experience,
and they are all good at fishing.
Do you have any confidence in winning?
Yes, I do.
Then, shut up!
Thank you!
Please give me a big hand!
Recently, the taste of young women has become popular.
Today, we will show you the charm of young women.
Kato Haruhiko!
Do you fish?
I used to catch a crab.
You came here a while ago and you didn't fish?
I did practice.
35cm deep.
I'm fishing.
If it's over 35cm, it's big.
It's about my size.
I don't think so.
I'm sorry.
Please come.
Finally, the defending champion of the entertainment world, Masato Hamada!
Please, champion.
He's the defending champion.
Everyone is always looking forward to seeing him.
Yes, everyone is looking forward to seeing him.
I'm not good at it.
You're not good at it?
Thank you for your time.
Please do your best.
Now, let's start the meeting.
I'd like to ask Tanaka-san to give a speech.
Today, B-class people are here.
B-class comedian, B-class actor, B-class musician, C-class copywriter.
Copywriter?
I don't know what makes you happy, but I'll do my best.
I'll give you a lot of books.
I'll send you this.
This is the place where you can get money.
You should know where you can't get money.
Okuda!
Okudai, do your best in the gym!
Think about it!
Eiji!
What are you talking about?
Raw!
Good one!
Okudai!
Hey, Okudai!
Hey!
I'll do it properly.
Cut!
Put your ears out.
This is the last.
Ken Oro.
He's my father.
Be careful.
Everyone, do your best!
This program is brought to you by the sponsors.
For some reason, I always get good results in the down time.
Thanks to that, I'm able to hold a trophy in my heart.
I'm a very poor guy, so I think I'm the second crazy one.
I've had enough of playing around.
I'm going to show you how much I can take a break.
I'm usually in the lower half of the room, so I'm thinking of eating the top place.
He's aiming for the first place while asking.
I'll do my best not to lose to my rival, Kato.
If I win, I'll get a beer from Matsumoto.
I'll personally get a beer.
I've lost 35 centimeters.
Everyone around me is saying I'm out of luck.
But I'll aim for the number and size.
Please support me.
The celebrities' fishing competition, everyone is starting at the same time.
Nohaz is having trouble here.
Hey!
It's coming!
Okuda and Masaki are starting to get back to the start line.
The other members started fishing without worrying about the other members.
Hey!
Isn't it terrible?
What are you talking about?
Who is it?
Do you want to do that?
I'm sorry!
Wait a minute, are you saying that I did it?
That's right!
It's terrible!
Meanwhile, the boat that had its first time in the competition with its usual partner, started to fish at a different point.
I want to be the first one.
And in the boat of Hamada, Enuchi and Sawamura, he keeps saying that he is the first one to get on.
I'm getting nervous at first.
I'm not ready yet.
Don't be so hasty.
I have to win no matter what.
This time, Eguchi secretly makes the investment.
How many CDs do you want me to get?
About 30.
30?
If you get 30, I'll get the CD.
Okay.
Really?
Yes.
Alright!
I'll get 30!
I'll ask for a duet.
Why?
Duet.
Sawamura and Tsugisoya, the guys who started with Kato.
Ah, here it comes.
As Hamada predicted, Sawamura...
They look so happy.
Alright, alright, alright.
Wait a minute.
And Kato also hits.
You're going to be exposed.
This is pretty good.
It's true.
You're going to be exposed.
It's not coming.
Kato is the first one to get hit.
It's here.
Kawamura, who I just hit, hits again.
Kawamura also hits.
Did you get it?
That was a 50cm fish.
30 minutes have passed since the start.
Okuda's first hit of the day.
It's big.
That's the first one.
29cm.
And Hamada also got his first hit today.
Did you get caught?
Yes.
Damn it!
I'm happy when I get caught.
At the same time, Itoi fished another boat.
It's not a competition.
It's like a waste of film.
Matsumoto is the only one who is not caught in the same boat.
I'm in trouble.
There is no sign of the boat.
The captain Okuda gets the second one.
It's amazing.
This is smaller than the one before.
Here, the little boy comes with a sash for each boat.
How is the condition of the lake today?
It's dangerous.
It's a good one, right?
You know?
It's like a turtle.
Is it cool?
It's a turtle.
You're so naive.
It's cool.
It's so tight.
It's small again.
Okuda is fishing again
What if I catch 30 fish?
That's fine
Why?
I'll produce it
7!
Shut up, you bastard
How was it?
It's not your fault
You can't catch any
You mean you can't catch any fish?
It was a coincidence.
Samurai-san.
Samurai-san, how was it?
What?
Your face changed. Did you have such a scary face?
You should have had a more gentle face.
You were the second victim of the Seidama-no-Po, right?
That's right.
So?
Don't be impatient.
At that time...
Here it comes!
It's coming! It's coming!
It's coming!
Hamada-san is coming!
It's not that big.
It's not that big, but it's Hamada's yearning bus.
It's written that Shimano's commercial will continue.
It just came out.
Wow, oh!
Oh, Yippee!
Yippee!
That's the first time he's been hit in the face by Eguchi.
Oh!
Is that a punishment?
What do you think?
That...
That's a punishment?
No, no.
Eguchi's somehow holding back his embarrassment.
Small one.
Well, I guess I'll put on my lure, too.
You didn't put on the lure?
I did.
Why'd you do that?
If I wear it, I can catch a lot of fish.
He doesn't care about the others, but he catches fish.
It's a boring thing.
Yes! Yes!
And Kato...
Hey!
Haruto!
Don't get carried away!
Sorry.
But I can't help it.
The fish will come.
You're not going to tell me?
If you think it's bad
That night, Kato appears again
This is good
I'm getting caught
Sorry
Kato
Are you close?
Seriously?
How many are there?
It's raining!
I hate busses.
While the others are catching up, Matsumoto and Kisoukan are wandering.
Meanwhile, the Okuda-Yamasaki pair...
But my voice is good, right?
Which is it?
If I say it with a voice I like or I don't like, which is it?
I don't know the voice you're singing.
This singing voice is haaaaaa
Out
You don't have to wear this, Eguchi-san
You're not alone
You're fishing
It's not related to the movie
Downtown Lure Time
The famous downtown lure time.
The first person to catch a fish in 30 minutes will receive 100,000 yen.
This is a popular downtown lure in the past.
This time, the pros will be recommended.
This is a good one.
Oh, really?
This is Mr. Matsumoto's.
This is the shiny one.
Which one is better?
The one with the Matsumoto lure is more popular.
Oh, really?
It looks like a fish.
Something's wrong with me.
Start!
I'll take 100,000 yen.
I'll take it seriously.
The racing battle for 100,000 yen begins.
Then, Eguchi's car will die.
Is it here?
It's here.
100,000 yen!
Ah!
It's here! It's here!
Eguchi is frustrated.
However, all the members were satisfied with the improvement this time.
It's not like there's no chance of winning.
It's different from before.
I'm awake.
After 10 minutes, he's back to the starting line.
Will Eguchi be able to get the 10,000 yen?
Here it comes!
Eguchi is once again crying out in pain.
At that time, Matsumoto is in trouble.
Here it comes!
He's coming!
Matsumoto!
Matsumoto is a great guy
That was a great fight
What? You're a good runner
You're a good runner
And then, in the second half...
It's coming from there.
Hey, what are you doing?
You're making fun of me!
Okuda, who's maintaining the lead, hits it right away.
He's catching up to it.
And then, on the other side, Sawamura still has no catch.
A bit of air is flowing.
But then...
It's coming!
I did it!
I'm aiming for the victory
Yamasaki who couldn't catch another one also caught one here
The blood is coming out
Out!
The one who caught it is the boat's screw
There's not much time left, and it's the last spurt.
Here, the defending champion Hamada's determination is on the rise.
The score is getting bigger.
Who will win the championship?
Good work, good work.
We'll start with the Samurai one.
Thank you.
It's one.
It's two.
Tsutari-kun!
I'm Tsutan!
What are you saying?
It's not like I'm zero!
The winner is...
Yamada-san!
Yamazaki, what's going on with you guys?
Actually, Yamazaki is...
Tsutan!
I'm here!
You're the end!
Don't go after the end, Kimitsu-tan.
Oh, you're so energetic.
No, I'm not!
I'm over 60!
3.5
Hey, Kato-san!
This guy is pretty small.
That's right.
He's pretty small.
3.5!
It's huge!
It's pretty big!
No!
I've measured everything.
It's number 1.
It's 30.
Why?
It's 50 yen.
Ah, but it's 30.
30.5, huh?
30cm.
It's big.
This is also 30cm.
It's beautiful.
You're doing the same thing.
There are three.
It's not enough.
The last one.
Two.
You're surprised.
It's a big one.
Four.
Next is the last one.
This is...
Yo! The lid is closed!
You're forcing yourself to do it.
It's huge!
If you win this, what would it be?
Ah!
27cm.
27cm!
Ah, Itoi-san!
It's a big one.
How many did you catch, Itoi-san?
I think I caught four.
Oh!
That's a square.
Oh, it's Oyama-san!
29?
This is not 30.
29!
Oh, it's a top!
Now, Kamiyama-san!
Yes!
Oh, it's a tight!
It's the most!
Wait, count all of them.
I can't see it.
I don't know.
I can't remember.
This is 29.
29.
Then, how about this?
It's over 30.
It's over 30. Wait a minute.
But it's 30.
It's 30.
The one before.
I can't remember.
Look.
It's a little...
It's coming out.
This is Kato's mocha.
It's out.
It's about 2.
Then, 30.2.
I didn't think he would put that much detail.
It's not that much.
It's a big difference between 1 and 2.
Then, I want to eat meat.
Look, 30.5.
Thank you.
Wait, you can say it after you see mine.
Let's play 2-line game.
Oh, it's switched.
You're wrong.
You're so short.
No, I'm short.
24 seconds.
The winner is...
Kato Akanesaka!
Amazing!
He's still in the lead.
I'm so happy.
And the winner is...
The best T-shirt!
The best!
This is amazing!
This is the best T-shirt!
The 5th fishing competition closed with the following results
Here, we present the winner, Kato Haruhiko's 3mm T-shirt
And the help of Megabus, who helped us with the downtown lure
We present this lure to 10 people
Please apply to the next round.
I was thinking of winning the championship and then going fishing.
But fishing is just that.
This is the result I got.
My last miracle was a great talent.
I'm looking forward to it.
I was going to win next year, but I didn't have the intention to win today.
So I think it's just right.
I failed again this time.
Next time, I will win.
I will do it like this.
When I announced the combination, I was a little annoyed.
I was a bit shocked, but that's how I became like this.
I want to be like that, so next year I want to practice the release.
I want to change the rules.
I think animals can do anything.
I caught a lot of monkeys and peaches, but I couldn't catch any fish.
I would like to change the rules a little.
This time, I'm the gaming champion, so I thought I had to make a decision.
I didn't say it until the end, but I didn't put a lure.
Next time I will try to do my best with a lure.
Today I got to fish for the first time.
I got 3 baits.
I want to enjoy fishing while maintaining the beginners.
Thank you very much for today.