Youkai
They have a deep connection with the human world with many legends from the ancient times of Japan
We have been mislead at times and have received grace at other times
Just a year ago, we met several Youkai in downtown
Tonight, we went to the school that is rumored to be the best in Japan
Entering the Youkai, the school Youkai
What do you have for us today?
Well...
There is a lot of spiritual energy
I can't show it to children
I can feel the spiritual energy around here
I can tell right away
Really?
There are a lot of Youkai
Are they already out here?
Yes, they are
Really?
Yes
This is the school
This is a scary picture
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors
There is someone here, Matsumoto-san
They are already out here?
Matsumoto-san, I think I saw them last year
They are already out here
They are still here
They are already out here this year
What is this Youkai?
A cat girl
Youkai is a cat girl
This girl loves Temari and Yasuri
She is so energetic that her spirit has almost disappeared
A Youkai cat girl
Isn't this too violent?
This is a good Youkai
She is just playing with Maritsuki
Yes, she is not violent at all
She is not violent, but she has been lying down for a while
She is getting jealous
She doesn't want to go up
She is always like this
It would be a big deal if we took her down
Is it dangerous?
Yes
Are you going to do it?
I will
Are you sure?
Yes
Don't do it
I will
What?
We haven't had a big meeting yet
That was close
That was scary
Let's go to the next one
A cat girl for the first time in a year
Is it close?
It's really scary
Can you feel it from the bottom?
Yes
This is scary
What is this?
It's screaming
It's scary
It's really scary
What?
It's scary
Something is coming
It's walking
What?
It's scary
What is this?
It's a monster
Is it running?
It's a monster running
I was really scared
A strange drum is ringing
Many children were lured by the sound
A monster running
It was really scary
We should have put our hands out
What is this?
It's a monster running
It's said that it eats children
Is that so?
It's scary
That's why this elementary school...
It's okay because it's not interested in adults
That's why it passed by
Yes
What if it enters the school building?
It will enter the school building
It's suddenly hot
Is it here?
I can hear something
What is this?
It's scary
I can hear something from there
There should be no one
This summer vacation
From the music room of the elementary school
I can hear the piano
What is this?
It's scary
It's a monster running
We should have put our hands out
Let the wind blow
It's a monster running
You bastard
What is this?
It's a monster running
A long time ago
A young man was found by a man
It was a music room
Yo-kai Mo-tei
The teacher is coming!
Mo-tei!
The machine is scary.
Scary! Scary! Scary!
This is dangerous!
If you get caught in this, it's over!
Mo-tei!
Yamazaki, push it in! Push it in!
Mo-tei! Mo-tei!
Good job!
That's the only way to get rid of it.
That's right.
It was a great desire.
You're completely in the mouth.
It's coming again!
Where did you go?
Yo-kai Running has appeared again.
He's not a bad guy.
Really?
He's just passing by.
He doesn't do anything to adults.
Scary!
Is he looking for a child?
What?
He's carrying something.
Yo-kai Bo-in
Yo-kai Bo-in?
Bo-in
Don't say it to yourself.
With a guitar in his hand, he travels all over the country.
He's the number one bo-in in the Yo-kai world.
Yo-kai Bo-in
Bo-in
What are you doing?
He's the number one bo-in in the Yo-kai world, but he sings his own song.
It's like saying, I'm still 16.
I see.
Bo-in
You're still alive.
Are you still going to sing?
Actually, the boss comes out later.
The boss?
The boss is coming out of the health room.
Here?
He's really coming out.
I'm scared.
Yamazaki, someone's here.
Are you sure?
He's here.
He's calling.
Yamazaki, go.
What?
Go.
What are you going to do?
Hold him from the top.
He's coming out.
He's the number one bo-in in the Yo-kai world.
He's hiding in the health room bed.
The number one bo-in in the Yo-kai world.
I'm scared.
I'm really scared.
I can't do this.
Is this the boss character?
This is the boss character.
Yamazaki, do something.
I can't do anything.
I'm begging you.
Get the teacher.
You said you wanted to see the teacher.
I really like matcha.
Please forgive me.
Thank you.
Help me.
Run away.
I'm scared.
Help me.
I can't do this.
I'm scared.
I want to sleep.
This year was more intense.
I think it will be the same next year.
You managed to escape.
I'm desperate.
The Yo-kai world is full of evil spirits.
It's a real Yo-kai.
It's said that there is no way to deal with it.
It doesn't work.
Let's get out of here.
Let's go.
I'm really sorry.
It's been a long time.
I don't talk much.
It's been a long time since I've been here.
I lost my motivation.
What do you mean you lost your motivation?
I had a lot of fun.
I took a break.
I heard that you went to the beach and picked up girls.
I didn't.
I heard a lot of great things.
I went to the beach with a yoga mat.
I waited for you in the car.
These videos are useful.
You can watch it right away.
What are you doing?
Don't say anything.
I didn't do anything.
You went with me, didn't you?
I didn't go to the beach with you.
I don't like it.
You charged me with the battery of the yoga mat.
Don't say things that don't concern you.
Yamazaki picked up the girls.
He came back in the car.
He was fast.
He was telling me what to do.
It was like you were at the scene.
I said I wanted to go to the beach.
I want to go to the beach because I'm a summer guy.
I want to go to the beach.
I don't care.
I'm not doing anything bad.
I want to go to the beach.
I want to make memories of the trip.
I want to do something.
This is not common for an amateur.
You're making fun of me.
You're making fun of my sister.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I know her.
What?
She's grown up.
How many of you know her?
And then...
You're making fun of me.
There was a girl I knew.
And then...
I heard something interesting.
I asked the girl a lot of questions.
She came to Shonan last year.
She was a businesswoman.
She talked to you?
She said there was someone who was definitely there, so I asked her to come with me.
I asked her who it was.
She said it was a celebrity.
I said it wasn't a celebrity.
I asked her to come with me.
She said it wasn't a celebrity.
Hey!
It wasn't a celebrity!
Hey, everyone, come here!
That's how it went.
I see.
There were a lot of things.
But I really...
This is enough.
You're making fun of me.
I was at home.
I was basically at home.
Basically?
Yes.
But you did go.
Well, well...
That's right.
I didn't really go.
I just...
How do I say this?
To put it simply, I didn't go.
You did go!
To put it simply...
You didn't go, you didn't go.
You didn't go.
I got in a car accident.
What car accident?
It was a 5.2.
I don't know what you're talking about.
No, no.
This is just for the sake of the honor.
This is really...
Yes, Mr. Kazumoto?
Well, you see, when I work as a comedian,
I have to do a lot of research.
So, most of the girls I've taken pictures with are popular now.
What are you talking about?
That's because you went to the beach.
That's right.
Ah...
My comment...
My comment was wrong.
Yes, yes.
Really.
Yes, yes, yes.
Right?
Ah, the sand...
Ah, the beach.
When you're driving,
there's a soldier or a shoe in the middle of the road.
Sometimes there's a blanket on the ground.
Mr. Kazumoto, what does that mean?
What does that mean?
You're driving me crazy.
This is something you really have to think about.
Don't be so desperate.
You have to think seriously about this.
I have something I have to think about, too.
Really.
It's a big deal.
Mr. Kinpachi.
This is a big deal.
A blanket, a soldier, and a shoe.
What does that mean?
It doesn't have anything to do with the body.
Why are you so desperate?
You have to think seriously about this.
What does that mean?
A hand and a foot.
Okay.
Well, this is...
First of all,
have you ever found a soldier on the road?
Yes, I have.
You have?
You have, right?
No, I haven't.
I haven't.
You should have.
I should have.
Have you ever seen a soldier on the road while driving?
Yes, I have.
This is a message for you.
What?
Are you okay?
Everyone is a soldier, right?
That's right.
That's the difference.
Is that so?
That's right.
That's a message.
Why have you ignored it all this time?
That's annoying.
You want to come over there?
On the other hand,
I can't help but get angry.
I'm sorry about that.
Right?
Don't do that again.
Okay.
This is a long story.
Tell me the message.
Let's ask him.
Let's ask him more directly.
Did you use your left hand or your right hand?
I didn't look at it carefully.
Maybe I used my left hand.
Soldiers don't use their left hand and right hand, right?
That's not true.
When I was doing this,
I felt pain.
You lied to me just now.
I don't like this story anymore.
No matter how I look at it,
you lied to me.
That's not true.
No matter how I look at it,
I feel pain when I do this.
You used your left hand, didn't you?
Yes.
What?
Right?
Yes.
I don't know if you use your left hand or your right hand,
but I use my left hand.
Which one is better?
I got it.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to use my left hand or my right hand anymore.
I don't want to use my left hand anymore.
Which one is better?
I'm sorry.
All the things that were falling down,
they're all dead.
Are you okay?
What do you mean by that?
When you get out of the car,
a lot of things are falling down.
You didn't notice that,
but they're all dead.
Do you understand?
I see.
Yes.
For example,
a soldier's hand is falling down.
Right?
A soldier's hand is falling down.
And a lot of things are falling down.
There are a lot of things in between.
Of course.
A soldier's hand doesn't suddenly fall down.
And...
How do you explain that you did it?
That's right.
Why do you think that Shiritori is following you?
Yes, yes.
You think that, right?
I think so.
Wait a minute.
It's old.
I don't understand.
Why do you think that?
You don't understand that?
I don't understand that.
But you know that Shiritori is following you.
I know that.
That's great.
No one will notice that.
Yes, yes, yes.
After the military service,
they sell you a hand mirror.
What's next?
Well,
usually,
you know,
they sell you a pair of earrings.
And then,
they sell you shoes.
usually,
you know,
they sell you a pair of wings.
And then,
you know,
they sell you a mask.
And then,
usually,
you know,
they sell you a scarf.
Yes, yes, yes.
You know,
they sell you a scarf.
It's impossible.
The scarf is...
I have to finish it.
It's not a scarf.
Well,
usually,
they sell you a condom.
Oh, a condom.
And then,
they sell you a muumuu.
It's impossible.
They sell you a muumuu for adults.
What?
For children?
In your body,
there is a left-handed psycho gun.
It seems that there are seven weapons inside.
What are the other six?
And whose hands were they inside?
It's a sad past, but please tell me.
If I take this off, it's a psycho gun.
Then, take it off.
No, no, no, no.
I can't take it off.
You have to push and turn it.
Oh, I see.
That's right.
I can't take it off like this.
I can't wait.
You have to push and turn it to take it off.
Oh, I see.
You have to push both buttons at the same time.
Oh, there are buttons here.
Yes, there are two.
So, you can't take it off even if you push only one.
You have to push it hard.
Yes, yes, yes.
In the past, it was easy to take it off.
Tell the doctor to do it a little bit more.
Doctor?
Tell him to take it off in three actions.
It's a doctor's song.
Then, take it off.
No, no, no.
You can't do that.
What's this?
So, the bullets are coming out?
If you take it off?
Yes, yes, yes.
That's basically it.
And you can change about six more.
You don't have to sing.
So, I don't use that much.
In fact, I use something else.
Oh, there's something you use.
Yes, there is.
Even now?
The thing I use the most is the wine extractor.
You're so sad.
It's like this.
You're using my arm to make wine.
Is that your request?
Yes, yes, yes.
It's like this.
But you have to turn it yourself.
Why?
Turn this way.
What?
Why?
I don't want to do this.
Why do I have to turn it myself?
That's what you use the most?
That's what I use the most.
And there's something else.
If it's like this, it's like a mirror.
It's like the back of your teeth.
Leave it to the dentist.
It doesn't matter if it's there or not.
That's not convenient.
Oh, that was it.
That's not there anymore.
What do you mean?
It's like magic.