Please come in.
Where are we?
Today, we are here to celebrate the birth of Hamada's second child.
Is that so?
You are amazing. You don't do this kind of thing.
You are here?
This is my living room.
I see.
Please enjoy.
There is a kojirane.
It's a private room.
It's a small room.
No one can enter.
Is that so?
There is a kojirane.
It's a peeping room.
Madonna.
The fee is 2,000 yen.
First of all, I'll give you 2,000 yen.
What?
I'll give you 2,000 yen.
I'll give it to the manager.
Here you are.
Where is the squid?
Is it okay to broadcast this kind of thing on TV?
The director was surprised.
He was surprised.
I'm looking forward to it.
Here you are.
You are noisy.
What is this?
Number 3.
Let's go to number 3.
Is that so?
This is today's menu.
Let me introduce it to you.
A blonde ecstasy.
I don't like it very much.
It's a stew.
You can eat as much as you want.
This is good.
Wet lingerie.
A nurse's petal.
I see.
It's a stew.
I can't stand it anymore.
I don't need this.
I don't like stew.
Please give me a bag.
This is good.
I prepared only this today.
You can choose what you like.
Is that so?
Yes.
I'll see this first.
I haven't seen it much.
I'm looking forward to it.
This is a blonde ecstasy.
This is for you.
For me?
Yes.
This is for you.
Only for me?
Yes.
It's 3,000 yen.
What?
Again?
It's 3,000 yen.
It's 2,000 yen.
No.
It's 3,000 yen.
It's 2,000 yen.
It's a blonde ecstasy.
The bell rang.
What should I do?
Please enjoy it.
Idiot.
Why do you have tissue?
Thank you very much.
It's a blonde ecstasy.
It's nothing.
Is that so?
I've been waiting for a while.
It's a blonde ecstasy.
But it's a little expensive.
Are you kidding me?
This costs 5,000 yen.
This is...
It's a blonde ecstasy.
Please.
It's 5,000 yen.
Do you need this?
It costs 9,000 yen.
What are you doing?
Are you preparing it?
I know that.
It's time to start.
Grandma.
I've seen this grandma.
What is this grandma?
It's a blonde ecstasy.
Thank you very much.
It's wonderful.
Is that so?
I think it was very good.
Which one do you recommend?
Do you recommend?
Wet lingerie.
Thank you very much.
It's already wet.
Please.
The customer who came the other day.
He went home three times with wet lingerie.
Is that so?
It's wonderful.
It's 15,000 yen.
It's starting.
Wet lingerie.
It's already wet.
Thank you very much.
Hey.
It's not coming out.
Now, the customer.
It's time to cry.
I'm done.
No, no, no.
It's wet lingerie.
Wet lingerie.
How much is this?
This is about 6,000 yen.
It's starting.
Wet lingerie.
Attention, please.
What do you think?
Here you are.
Thank you very much.
Wait a minute.
Is this the end?
That's not good.
Wet lingerie.
It's so wet.
You're wet.
You've been wet three times.
I love it.
A nurse's firework.
What about a nurse's firework?
I like it.
What are you touching?
I'll take 16,000 yen.
Good luck.
Please be wet.
I want to be wet, too.
I can't be wet.
A nurse's firework.
It's a nurse's firework.
Here you are.
A nurse's firework.
Thank you very much.
This is...
It's a waste of money.
Look at this.
What?
It's a summer flower.
This is the last one.
Please give me a bag.
This is...
I can see your skin.
Really?
How much do you have?
What?
I'll give you 40,000 yen.
What are you doing?
Ladies and gentlemen.
Did you see Akko last week?
The opening?
Yes.
Akko's trial.
It happened, didn't it?
Yes.
I was there.
I was there that night.
From Lusden.
From Akko.
I just said from Akko.
I don't understand it at all.
I thought it was from an old man.
You didn't say his name.
I did, but I couldn't hear it because of the phone.
So I thought I'd ask Lusden.
I said hello.
Thank you very much for today.
It was fun.
Thank you very much.
Hey, old man.
What is this?
It's a long message.
Thank you very much.
I like funny things.
It was fun.
I don't think I can call you.
I'll put the phone number.
If it's bad, I'll call you again.
I forgot.
I'm not good either.
What is this old man?
I really like you.
I can't say it.
But I don't understand that voice.
I like funny things, too.
I'm a singer.
Singer?
What is this old man?
I still don't understand.
This man is really good at calling.
I'm watching you.
You should change your cell phone number as soon as possible.
I'll change it.
Hey, old man.
What is this?
I changed my voice.
I didn't have a bad voice.
You were famous.
I was famous.
I'm scared.
I met a man on Fuji TV.
He was a man.
I was talking to him.
I saw him.
I found him.
Oh, really?
I'm watching you.
I've been watching you all the time.
I didn't forget you.
You should have said,
I'm watching you.
You shouldn't have said,
That's right.
You shouldn't have said that.
Do you know that?
What was it?
Do you know the fighting game in the United States?
There's a video of it.
There's everything.
There's Kinteki Geri,
Kamitsuki,
Metsurushi.
There's everything else.
You said there's everything.
There are three things.
Why are you emphasizing the word?
I'm going to cheat you.
There are only three things.
I'm going to use my body.
Don't you think it's amazing?
What happened to your hands?
Of course I wear gloves.
You don't wear gloves.
There are people who wear gloves.
What are you talking about?
There's a karate.
There are a lot of pigs and karate.
When the pig said,
I said,
I said.
I said and hit himself,
and,
and he was plant
and then.
What kind of sword is that?
It's a tsui-ken, isn't it?
It's a katana.
It's like a pot.
It's like a turtle.
From here...
If you have a turtle, you can't attack.
That's right.
When you do it in Japan, you have to come out.
I thought I wouldn't be able to come out.
The people who just applauded...
...want to see the dead side of the comedians.
They want to bend down from their noses.
But, you know...
I...
As you can see,
There are many kinds of karate,
kung fu, kickboxing...
There are many kinds of karate, kung fu, kickboxing...
But the strongest one is the one who digs up poop.
If you dig up poop, you can win.
You...
What kind of karate is that?
If you dig up poop,
there's nothing you can do.
No, it's not like that.
Even if you say,
even if you say,
you don't want to dig up it's ok.
But if you were going to dig up a real one,
you would have to dig up it.
If you were going to dig up it,
you would have been holding onto something.
But, you...
your wife will run away from you to do such a thing.
Who?
Well, you know...
Even if will be told,
his wife will go home.
Even if people come to get poop, they don't sell one or two.
No, no, no.
There are so many.
At first, there are a lot of poop.
They come like this.
Nice to meet you.
It's like noodles.
It's like thin noodles.
That's not good.
No, no, no.
I thought I'd collect a lot of poop.
What do you think he's doing today?
He told me to go with him in the morning.
My car...
It's blue.
That's Takasu.
Takasu, Takasu.
What do you think he's doing?
Look at this.
There's a little bit of acne here.
It's so small.
I don't look good in anything.
Oh, Mitsuyoshi.
Why did you ask me to do it?
I'm surprised.
Is that so?
Don't step on the brake suddenly.
Wait, wait.
That was terrible.
When I went to the cafeteria, the old lady kept looking at my nose.
She didn't look at it.
Is that Karasaburo?
It's about what the old lady sees.
What's going on?
There were a lot of people.
It's okay.
It's not bad.
What is the effect of the second radio exercise?
Konimoto?
Yes.
Oh, yes.
This.
That's not cool.
What effect does this have?
It's like this.
It's like training the inner eye.
What about this?
You need to be more energetic.
That's not cool.
There were a lot of things.
What about this?
Like this?
I don't know about this, but it's like this.
Rather than going from here to there, it's better to go from here to there.
It all has a meaning.
I don't know what this means.
What is it?
You can see it if you look at it.
It's like this.
Right?
I don't look like a man who exercises.
If you look at this, you can see it, right?
No matter how you think about it, it's like this.
You can meet someone you've never met before.
Why?
No!
It's not good.
It's the opposite.
Matsumoto-san, do you often say that the mole on the inside is colorful?
Or do you say that the mole on the chest is not good?
Do you say that?
What kind of mole is good?
By the way, I have one on my waist.
First of all, there is a tearful mole here.
That's right.
There is a tearful mole here.
Is that so?
And the mole around the mouth here is a tearful mole.
And the mole on the neck is a tearful mole.
Wait a minute.
Everyone knows that it's a tearful mole.
That's right.
It's a tearful mole.
I'm sorry. I don't know if it's just me, but I don't know what it means.
The mole on the neck is not good enough.
No, it's not.
I can't go anywhere.
The mole on the neck is always satisfied with the mole on the neck.
There are people around me who spit out nonsense.
I have a hard time reacting to it every day.
What is the best way to deal with it?
It's hard to spit out nonsense.
It's hard.
And it's the person above you.
It's okay if it's an old man who has nothing to do with it.
Even if you say that, you can't help it when it comes to seniors.
I can't help laughing.
I can't help smiling.
The easiest way to deal with it is to pull it out.
Pull it out.
And put your hand in it.
It's not a burden at all.
It's 30,000 yen.
When I'm talking to Mr. Tamori, Mr. Sanma is doing a good job.
You can't help it.
I can't help laughing.
This is the easiest way.
Mr. Sekine has been doing it recently.
It's easy to laugh at Nakamura Tamao.
No matter what he says, I can't help laughing.
That's easy.
I can't help laughing.
It's not like me at all.
I'm having trouble with my upper lip.
How can I fix my upper lip?
You can't help laughing.
I'm having trouble with my upper lip.
I can't help laughing.
I know.
When I went to see the Sultine Bank,
I was a guest, but I was beaten up.
I was confused with a pilot.
My legs were shaking.
I can't help laughing.
I was nervous.
That's it.
I don't know how far I can go.
My face turns red.
I turn red, too.
What?
Really.
I don't know when I turn red.
When I turn red.
That's it.
I don't know when I turn red.
What are you reading?
I always think,
A word that's written under the car is
Kuhaha.
Moha.
What does that mean?
Where is it written?
No, no, at the corner of the lower eye.
Around the corner.
It's written on the vehicle.
Kuwa!
And there are numbers.
3 letters or 4 letters.
Why is it written?
That is...
If you listen carefully, you'll understand.
What did I listen to?
Whose words did I listen to?
It's just written.
No, no, no.
You're curious, aren't you?
Kuwa!
The train is a great thing.
Like this.
Gadan, gadan, gadan, gadan.
Kuwa!
Thank you for watching!