Chikishiki! Proudly, we have a big surprise for you!
Today...
Is it a surprise?
Yes, it's a surprise.
The story goes back to the players.
To put it simply,
Takogui Ikagui slipped.
As a punishment,
He was given a lesson from the god of comedy.
So he slipped.
Yes, he slipped.
The Tanaka of Kokoriko, who is doing the Maesetsu of Masayuki Uchi, is the big one, right?
This one is a little stupid.
Really?
Yamada-chan has a strange head.
It's strange.
Why is it strange?
Basically, this guy is also a fan.
Who is the fan of this guy?
No, I'm the same.
As a comedian, he is a fan of Okama.
I'm a fan of Okama.
So he is a fan of Okama.
I don't know.
He is one of them.
Yes, he is one of them.
Well, the yellow one is Endo.
He knows.
He also cooperates a little.
The audience knows everything about him.
What do you mean?
Endo also has a strange head.
He is a little weird.
This program is brought to you by the sponsor.
Yes, please join the program.
It's amazing.
What do you think that popularity is?
I have a feeling.
Did you see it?
Yes, I saw it.
I can't see the tree.
The tree was in full swing.
It was so strong.
It was like a gorilla.
I thought I couldn't go home.
I'm still alive.
I'm glad I saw it.
It's amazing.
I can't believe that.
What kind of program is this?
I can't believe it.
It's amazing.
It's really amazing.
Come on.
Yes.
What is it?
It's a little late.
We're working.
Yes.
I don't know what to do.
It will be over soon.
Wait a minute.
I've been waiting for so long.
I'm sorry...
Apologies.
It's almost future!
It's almost...
So, do something.
Let's do it then.
What is it?
Do something.
Give me the video correction.
Have you got tired already?
Does he get Only mod?
Skin color.
It's boring.
What is this, You've got money.
Right!
I'm sorry buddy.
Ok, I got it.
You should go home.
I'm sorry but I have to go.
Just go home.
What are you doing!
you stupid idiot!
signals of rest!
Hey, you!
Hey!
No, no, no.
I can't do this.
Don't do it.
You're like the ideal version of Riku.
I saw the ideal version of Riku.
No way.
When you were coming out, I thought you were going to stab me.
You thought you were going to stab me?
I thought so.
I thought you were going to stab me?
I don't know.
How was it?
Pretty...
His face was weird.
I thought he was going to stab me.
Did you notice?
When I was talking,
I thought you were looking at me.
Were you looking at me?
I was looking at you all the time.
I thought you were scary.
There were other customers.
Are you okay?
I was going to the toilet.
Did you go out?
Yes, I did.
I was wondering what was going on.
That's not good.
You shouldn't make fun of others.
I'm really scared.
I'm really nervous.
I shouldn't do that.
I'm weak against accidents.
Stop it!
I said stop it!
Why did you hit me?
I'm dead!
Cut!
That's not what I mean!
Okay!
You can't do that. You have to act.
Do it.
Cut! Cut!
The actor is waiting for you!
He's waiting for the next scene.
Can you hurry up and do it?
I'm sorry, Mr. Tatsu.
If you don't die, I won't be able to get out.
I won't die.
It's not a fight.
Why are you crying?
Don't cry!
It was really scary.
You were shaking so much.
I've never seen you shake so much.
It was really scary.
You were wearing socks.
Why were you wearing socks?
It was really scary.
I was really scared.
I could see you all the time.
I couldn't say anything because I was scared.
I could see you.
It was the worst.
It was really scary.
I couldn't understand it at all.
Your face when you came out.
I don't want to see it later.
It was really scary.
You looked like a small animal.
Today was really hard.
Thank you.
I'm sorry to make you feel uncomfortable.
My plate is broken.
Really?
Yes.
You can't walk.
What?
My plate is broken.
It's not broken.
What?
It's broken.
Are you okay?
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
Are you stupid?
My plate is broken.
It's not broken.
I'll ask you something.
Why are you quiet?
It's clear.
It's not broken.
Why do you say it's broken?
You're weird.
You think it's broken.
You think it's broken because it hurts a little.
It hurts a little because it's broken.
It's never broken.
You suddenly say something bad to everyone.
It's not broken.
It's not something you should say as a professional.
I don't want you to think I'm weird.
It's weird.
I think you can do 96% of your usual strength.
That's enough.
If you say that, I'll...
What?
I'm talking about myself.
I hit my ankle with my shin.
You said your plate hurts.
I thought it hurt because we were together.
I did it with patience.
My plate is broken.
I'm sure my plate is broken.
It's hard to tell if it's broken or not.
It's broken.
I'm sure it's broken.
It's not broken.
But...
What?
It will be in the future.
It's broken.
I'm really sorry.
This is completely true.
Our downtown shop seems to be on fire.
What's going on?
That's okay.
Really?
I'm selling a pencil case at a stationery store.
He posted a picture of me and said it looked like a match box.
I said, can you sell it?
I said that.
I should stop selling this.
It's not selling well.
It's true.
I should stop selling this when I open a shop.
What are you talking about with that look?
Stop it.
Don't you want to open a shop?
What?
No snacks.
Really?
Well, I think I'll do it at a pet shop.
Why?
Because I like animals.
That's mean.
Oh, you're trying to give me a good impression again.
No, no, no.
I like animals.
Right?
You're a kind person.
Yeah, I like animals.
Right?
I want to have a dog, but...
I want a dog that can fight.
You mean a big dog?
Yeah.
You don't have to obey me that much.
I want a dog that can sometimes fight.
About three wins and two losses.
That's a good match.
Isn't it?
Something like that.
But what if you lose?
Three wins and two losses is good, but...
What about those two losses?
What kind of situation are you in?
If you win, I win.
Then it's over.
What kind of situation are you in?
What kind of situation is that two losses?
Basically, it's a dead end.
Because I'm a talent, I can't get my hands out.
You can't hit your face.
I can't hit my face.
Basically...
Do dogs do dead ends like this?
Why do dogs use fists?
That's why...
It would be nice if there was a dog like this.
Well, that's fine.
I don't think there is.
Is that so?
Why do you hate dogs?
You don't like them?
You're so mean.
But sometimes I bring a dog to the studio.
Everyone loves dogs, so they always fight.
But you never fight.
No.
I always hold him like this.
Really.
I've never seen you do it.
You always do it like this.
That's not true.
You do it like this, and I do it like this.
That's a weird story.
But if you do it, I'll do it.
No way.
You're weird.
I think you have a problem.
A problem?
Are you stupid?
I always held him when he was a chimpanzee.
What is a chimpanzee?
That's scary.
I'm not that bad either.
I'm a chimpanzee.
There was a chimpanzee.
Where was he?
There?
I don't know.
I told him to throw away the trash he ate, and he threw it away.
In the end, that's how you treat him.
He's cute.
He's weird.
What are you talking about?
I'm writing a letter.
It's not broken.
It's a famous story that Mach-chan used to wake up the princess's sleep with a kiss.
He became a model for Princess Shirayuki in the fairy tale.
Why does Mach-chan sleep with a yellowtail every night?
I don't know.
Why does he sleep with a yellowtail?
To put it simply, he's a rising king.
I'm a human being, but I don't like people who are low-minded.
I'm a rising king.
If you're a rising king, you're a rising king.
He sleeps with a yellowtail.
Everyone doesn't care about his rise.
Does he sleep with a yellowtail?
That's right.
A rising king?
That doesn't sound like sashimi.
Is it just one?
No, one.
One.
Or two.
When did he have two?
Two when he broke up with his girlfriend.
And three.
Why?
I can't stand it! It stinks!
Stinks?
It stinks!
It stinks! It stinks!
Your kid, Nozawa, said the other day that he pooped in his underwear.
I can't stand it.
It's different from that smell.
He must have been surprised. He peed in his underwear and pooped.
He's a rooster, right?
There are still 4 or 5 of them.
I thought there were only 2 of them.
I was surprised.
It's not that kind of smell. It stinks.
Can you tell me about Buri?
What is it?
About his birth.
I'm sorry.
Really?
No, no, no.
Hamachi is in the middle.
Hamachi becomes Buri.
Really?
That's fine.
And below that is Kamasu.
What?
Please don't do that.
This is a rule.
Kamasu, Hamachi, Buri.
I'll go even further.
What? What do you mean?
Teri.
Buri teri.
That's after you've been judged.
It's fine even if I've been judged.
How many years do you have?
After you've been judged,
whether you're Buri teri or not,
it doesn't matter.
Is it over when you're alive?
It's not over.
Please tell me that.
What's next when you're alive?
Buri papa.
Humans cry when we cry,
so why don't we cry?
Men, what would you do if you crying rock?
That's a bad story.
Since first grade in 4th year school,
everybody has praised me
that I
am weak in rock.
Then, where is your weakness?
Well, I'm weak but the one is my neck.
As for ragdoll, the hardest part of ragdoll, the part you don't want to touch, is the back of your head.
The part you don't want to touch?
Of course. Of course.
Because if you don't have that, it's normal.
Normal?
It's really complex.
What's normal about that?
It's normal.
It's an ordinary animal, isn't it?
An animal?
It's really complex.
Is that the case with you?
Of course it is.
It's very complex.
There are some people who think it's nice, but that's a lie.
Ragdoll people already know what it is, so don't say it.
That's what they think.
So that's where it goes on.
That's where it goes on.
Are you going to cry?
I'm going to cry.
Are you going to shed tears?
Yes.
First, when you're in love with a ragdoll...
What are you doing?
Hey!
What are you going to do if I touch you?
What are you doing?
Ah, ah, ah.
Do it again.
Cross your arms and touch me like this.
You shouldn't do that.
Why would you do that?
I really don't like it when you do that.
Why would you do that with your right hand and your left hand?
I'm going to touch you.
What are you doing?
Right?
Stop it.
What do you mean?
That's what Ragdolls think.
Ah, I think so.
They say, stop it, ten times is one tear.
Ah, I see.
I understand what you're saying.
You really understand, right?
I understand.
So what's wrong?
Where should I start over?
It was good when you touched me first.
That's fine.
It's fine here too.
It was good, right?
I can do it too.
It's fine from here.
I felt like I was going to fall down in a huge crowd.
That was bad?
Yes.
Ah, so after this...
Wait a minute.
Do it like this, like this, like this.
After this, stop and go down.
Then...
Can I do it again?
What?
I don't mind, but...
What do you think?
It's the second time.
Ah, there's no more?
Am I fired?
Is Yoshimoto fired?
It's been seven years since you started.
I don't know what kind of face you should have when you go back to your family.
Please tell me the most natural way.
I think the best way is to go home empty-handed.
Well, yeah.
So you open your mouth and say,
Yeah, but...
What?
What are you talking about, Suzuki?
You say that, but...
I think the most natural way is to go home empty-handed.
It's been seven years since you started!
That's the kind of tension you should have.
I have a question for Matsumoto-san.
You say that there are as many women as there are stars.
What kind of number of men are there?
Well, you know, there are a lot of jokes.
And there are a lot of laughs.
That's a good thing to say.
And there are a lot of meals.
That's not the end of it.
It's not the end of it.
They say there's love in the wind of a kiss.
Only the number of tears is moving.
That's a good thing to say, isn't it?
Well, that's fine.
Well, if you're going to say that, there are a lot of men.
That's right!
There are a lot of men!
There are men in Japan!
So let's go get a picture here.
Well, you can't decide that.
No, the example of a woman is not so much a star.
That's right.
That's a strange example.
Oh, is it okay if it's beautiful?
It's beautiful, but it's not a man.
It's kind of like that.
It's okay if it's beautiful.
What's wrong with me?
Isn't it okay for a woman to be a rainbow?
There's no rainbow.
It's okay if it's beautiful.
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's okay if it's something like a number.
A number?
There are a lot of numbers.
A bowling ball.
A yellow bowling ball.
It's a bowling ball.
It's beautiful.
Have you ever thought that a bowling ball is beautiful?
No, I haven't.
It's a ball. It's a beautiful ball.
But there are three holes.
That's right.
That's a shame.
What?
It's a shame.
What's a shame?
It's beautiful.
What?
If there weren't these three holes, I wouldn't be able to say anything.
That's a shame.
That's right.
But there are three holes.
There are three holes.
It's beautiful.
I see.
You'll never get used to it.
Do you think that jeers me?
No, it's a shame!
It's beautiful!
That's a shame!
But해잇
It's beautiful!
That's a shame!
Butяс
There are three holes.
It's beautiful.
With its regional meaning.
Return?
Return, yes.
It's beautiful!
It's beautiful.