Next time, let's go to Gaki no Tsukaya and eat a lot of kaitetsu sushi and get 1 million yen!
It's 1 million yen!
This time it's a bonus project.
That's right.
Giri Giri Tsukasa said he made a mistake.
He said, let's go for 2 million yen.
Really?
If you say a little, you can still go for 3 million yen.
That's very generous.
The rules are simple.
The five of us can eat the most.
I see.
That's all.
You'll definitely get it.
That's right.
I'm drooling.
You're drooling.
Why?
Again, again.
You're drooling.
Try it.
It's the worst.
Today's project is also called a performance.
It's an old man's face.
Let's go.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Is everyone ready?
Yes.
The person who eats the most will get 1 million yen.
That's right.
Let's get started.
Are you ready?
Ready.
Start.
This is difficult.
You're definitely going to lose.
I'm a little hungry.
Excuse me.
What?
Outside, outside, outside.
There's a lot of eggs.
Look outside.
What's that?
It's Mr. Itao.
Really?
Why do you look like that?
What is it?
It's like a game.
Good morning.
What's the matter?
Well, I'm a little tired.
Oh.
I had a pain.
Are you shooting a program now?
Yes.
The person who ate the most will get 1 million yen or 2 million yen.
If that's the case, shall we do it together?
No, no.
I'm sorry we're doing it alone.
It's a program that's always done with the members of the kids.
Yes.
But 6 people out of 5 people.
7 people out of 6 people.
I have plenty of time.
Mr. Tsuga.
What are you doing in Yokohama?
It's 1 o'clock and 2 o'clock.
I still have plenty of time.
No.
Please sign it.
Are you okay?
Shall we do it?
No.
How about a confrontation with me?
Wait a minute.
What? Really?
There's no way to win.
That's right.
It's okay.
I'm so hungry.
But you can't do that to me.
No.
It's okay.
Are you going to do it?
No.
Let's do it.
Are you serious?
It's my seat.
It's a tight place.
Wait a minute.
Come on.
Okay.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
I'm fine.
I'm so hungry.
Then let's do it.
Please.
Let's do it.
I think it's easy.
What do you think?
It's easy.
If you're full, let's go home.
Good luck.
I'm ready.
Start!
I've always had a bad feeling about this.
Please.
I'm sorry.
I failed.
It's okay.
Okay.
I'm too slow.
It's okay.
Thank you.
But it doesn't matter if you don't have time.
I'll do it.
Let's do it.
I can do it today.
You can do it?
It's okay if I can eat it.
Here you go.
Thank you.
It says Meiji.
It's chocolate.
What's this?
You shouldn't eat that.
Here you go.
It's good for children.
I got a squid.
I'll eat that.
This is dried squid.
Dried squid?
It's so good.
This is a sea bream.
I don't think it's a sea bream.
It's a sea bream.
Let's go.
What's that?
Don't eat it.
What is this?
Glasses.
Wasabi is looking at us.
What is this?
Completely.
Completely glasses.
Let's pour it.
Pour it.
It's coming.
Let's go.
Let's pour this out.
Alright.
It's an honest band.
He's wearing a lot of glasses.
It's crazy.
I thought he would pass out.
It's coming again.
What is this?
What's this?
Cracker.
Hey.
Wait a minute.
It's crazy.
Let's go.
We're not supposed to eat this.
Pour it.
Let's get something to eat.
Here it comes!
Which one should I take?
I got it!
Here it comes.
What's this?
It's a student uniform button.
It's a high school button.
It's coming!
What's this?
I don't get it.
Let's eat!
What's that?
I can't see the rice.
It's hot.
I got it.
What's this?
There's rice.
It's hot.
There's a hole.
Let's eat this.
We have to eat this.
Why are you trying to escape?
Stand up properly.
Here we go.
This is the best.
Let's eat this.
Here we go.
It fell.
I think I can't eat anymore.
There's a dog.
This is the main dish.
It's really good.
I can't eat anymore.
I'll give it a try.
There's rice inside.
This is strange.
I can't eat this.
How about 10,000 yen?
No, we can't do that anymore, Nobu-san.
We can't eat 10,000 yen.
We can't do that at all.
We can't eat that.
There's nothing we can eat.
That's not true.
It's been going on for a while.
There's a part where we gave up.
Let's eat more.
Everyone is watching.
We can't eat that.
Let's see with our own eyes.
The sushi.
We can't eat that.
Let's take it for now.
The prize money.
What?
The prize money?
That's the rule.
How about you, Kusuga-san?
I don't have any.
I'm scared.
I'm sorry.
We can't eat that.
But I won today, right?
We can eat that.
Perfectly.
It's strange that you came suddenly.
Other than that, there's nothing.
For now...
Hey!
Take a look at this.
I'll take it for now.
Here.
It's a freebie.
It's strange.
The prize money is a freebie.
I'm doing it.
What's that?
It's a ballpoint pen.
I'm going to use a ballpoint pen next.
It's a gum demo.
Is he stupid?
You were doing it behind my back, right?
Of course I was.
I wore it.
It hurts.
It's strange.
Why is that?
I didn't do anything.
What are you doing in front of me?
What are you doing?
I'm scared.
Hey!
Nao!
Why don't you drive?
There was a driver.
It was a team.
There was another one.
Your wife was there the whole time, right?
She was there the whole time.
I don't know.
The staff will come, right?
Are you serious?
Are you a kid?
Gaki no Tsuken wa Tanoshii
Gaki Gaki kun Gaki Gaki kun Gaki Gaki kun Gaki Gaki
Gari Gari kun
Hello.
How have you been?
I've only been here for a week.
I see.
What happened?
I'm from the North.
What?
I've never seen anything like that.
Is that so?
I've never seen anything like that, so I don't know if it's interesting.
That's strange.
What is that?
I hate that kind of thing.
When people get excited, it gets more and more...
I have that kind of thing, too.
I cried.
You cried?
What?
You're the one who cried.
To be honest, this time...
It wasn't a big deal.
That's right.
What do you mean by before this time?
There's no way it was a big deal.
To be honest, before this time...
You're the one who cried.
If I had to express it in 100%,
I cried about 30% of the time.
I cried.
To be honest.
I'm laughing now, though.
I know that.
I'm not crying now.
It was fine until last time, but this time I couldn't go in.
What made you cry?
What?
What made you cry in that drama?
What are you talking about?
That kind of drama isn't funny.
What made you cry in the main?
What made you cry?
Was it about your family?
This isn't about my family.
It was about your love for your family.
What made you cry?
Well...
I don't know.
Was it about your family?
Yes, it was about my family.
I don't know what's good about it.
I don't know what's good about crying.
My favorite scene is...
when you take off your shoes.
What do you mean by that?
It's a sad story.
Really?
Jun and I are wearing worn-out shoes.
Goro bought them for us.
Goro?
Goro is a friend of mine.
He bought them for us.
We walked around in Hokkaido,
so they're worn-out.
They're already worn-out.
They're already worn-out?
I'm asking because there are people who haven't seen them.
What do you mean? They're worn-out.
Come here!
I'm Ishida Yami!
What are you talking about?
Pro-Radio Yokohama!
Pro-Radio Yokohama cheated on me!
What does Ishida Yami have to do with it?
What?
Pro-Radio Yokohama?
Pro-Radio Yokohama was a couple with an old man.
Who was that old man?
Kanaka Kuni!
I had a son with a lot of hair.
That's a lot of hair.
It's Jun!
Jun?
He has a lot of hair.
His younger sister is an old woman.
I can't help it.
Who would have seen that?
I saw it myself.
I saw it myself. I don't have 30% of it.
What are you talking about?
That's not it.
That's right.
Ishida Yami cheated on him.
There was a man who cheated on him.
Ishida Yami was dead.
But because he was his mother, Jun and Hotaru came to Tokyo for a funeral.
They were all worn out shoes.
They were all worn out.
Ishida Yami's husband,
He was a free man.
That old man said,
You guys are wearing dirty shoes. Come here.
He took me to the shoe shop and said,
Choose any of them.
He asked me to buy the shoes.
The shoes I bought from the old man.
I don't need this.
He threw it away.
He wore new shoes and came back.
I'm curious about what happened to his shoes.
We went to the shoe shop.
Why can't I explain this?
Buy the shoes.
Do you like it?
Don't talk like that in the dressing room.
Tell me what you like.
We went to the shoe shop.
The shoe shop was closed.
I looked at the back of the shoe shop.
There was a lot of garbage.
There were a lot of cardboard boxes.
I gave up.
I thought it might be in the shoe shop.
There was a lot of garbage.
The police officer came.
What are you guys doing?
Don't you think this is the worst?
It's still going on.
Okay.
I'm looking for a shoe.
What is this shoe?
I don't know what it means.
I said something like this.
The police officer said,
Come here.
Let's look for it together.
I looked for it.
I found it.
No way.
That's funny.
I don't even remember the reaction.
When I was a kid, my friend was a dog lover.
That's rude.
When I was a kid, I was bitten by a dog.
What kind of disease is it?
My pen name is Roro Choujin.
I've been told a lot.
That's a scary disease.
Really?
Have you ever seen anyone who's been bitten?
I've been bitten.
I thought you'd say that.
When I was a kid,
I was bitten by a dog I had at school.
Really?
I was bitten hard.
And?
At that time, I was injected with something.
It's like an infectious disease.
Did you get a fever?
No, I didn't get that kind of name.
What kind of disease is it?
I'm fine on that day.
I'm fine.
I see.
I can run a lot.
I can play the flute a lot.
I think it's just your imagination.
You're playing the flute a lot.
No, I'm not.
I've been bitten.
I've been bitten, so I can run a lot.
Matsumoto, you look good today.
Do you have any pain?
No, I don't have any pain.
When I'm 50 meters away, I'm like this.
You're so fast, Matsumoto.
Why?
No, I don't have any pain.
You're already playing the flute.
What do you mean, you're already playing the flute?
I'm playing the flute.
It's easy to understand.
It's a condition.
You used to work as a part-time worker at a power plant factory.
Yes.
What happens when you turn up the volume of the audio?
Mr. Odeo Taro.
Have you ever done that?
No, I haven't.
There you go.
Yes.
That's right.
In Japan, houses are crowded.
It's a nuisance, so we don't turn up the volume.
That's right.
But there's something about not doing it.
Well, when you do it.
Of course, I've done it before.
What happens?
An old man comes out of the speaker.
That's scary.
An old man comes out of the R.
An old man in a T-shirt called R.
Bang!
Can you do it?
What are you doing in there?
I'm trying my best.
I've come a long way, and I'm really frustrated.
But the old man is holding out.
But I'm still going to turn it up.
Don't tell me to shut up!
What about this one?
And the L comes out.
Well, well, well, well, well.
The L.
Well, well, well, well, well, well.
Stop it!
Mr. Tenosu, you lose!
But he's definitely setting it up on purpose.
It's better to wait for him.
On the contrary, it's scary.
It's like a detective investigation.
That's what it is.
The two of them are talking about it.
In the end, you're back, right?
I'll be back in the end.
But Tokitama is going to say something again.
Are you just watching?
Are you just listening?
This time, I'm just listening.
Bang!
It's scary.
From then on.
You can just throw it away.
Even if you're just listening, you're looking at it with your eyes closed.
It's close to you, so you can see it well.
You can't see it if you keep your eyes closed.
It's a loss if you keep your eyes closed.
You're looking at it with your eyes wide open.
I pulled it out once.
The cord.
From the stereo.
From the main body.
And then...
It was really scary.
How old are you?
You don't have to do it like that.
It's a little bigger than the speaker.
It's funny.
It comes out like this.
The shoulder width is amazing.
It's almost a right angle.
It's a little bigger than the speaker.
I don't want you to do that.
Please be careful.
Your stereo is big, isn't it?
It's not big.
The speaker is big and the old man is big.
Is it on the speaker?
Of course.
It's a really big speaker.
You don't have to do it like that.
The old man is listening to the CD like this.
Did you know?
I don't know.
You don't know.
The old man is a fool.
What do you listen to?
Mischel?
Let's listen to Mischel.
When I listen to Mischel, I look at it.
I think it's Mischel.
Can I listen to Mischel here?
If you do that, I won't forgive you.