Gaki no Tsukai Special Project Matsumoto vs. Hamada Kokoriko
The race between the two will finally begin!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
On the day of the race, the Hamada team, who will face Matsumoto, will enter the track.
What?
What's going on?
I slipped!
Matsumoto, you slipped!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Yamashita, you have a child.
You have to win this race.
Your father is strong.
I have a child today, so I'm going to win.
Are you okay?
Is it okay for me to do it here?
It's a big place.
It's a serious place.
On the other hand, Matsumoto, who is eager to take revenge, arrives late.
Matsumoto vs. Hamada Kokoriko
On the day of the race, Matsumoto vs. Hamada Kokoriko
The race between the two will finally begin!
The day of the race has come!
Unfortunately, it's raining.
The weather is bad.
I returned it to you a long time ago.
It was raining a lot.
It's raining a lot, so I can't go.
The rules of this race are...
Matsumoto vs. Hamada Kokoriko
It's a race between two people.
It's finally here.
I saw this for the first time in a long time.
I can go.
Really?
Yes.
I have a lot of room.
The place to jump out was behind me.
That's right.
This is the only place.
If you step out a little, it's over.
I'll take care of the details.
I saw it earlier.
He has a lot of jumping power.
That's right.
It's surprising.
Please look up.
It's amazing.
It's the same.
It was amazing.
It was too high.
I could see it right away.
I was scared.
It was crowded.
Where?
Around here.
It was crowded.
It was around here.
It was crowded like Komazawa street.
Please look up again.
It's a total of four times.
Matsumoto said he was confident.
As a handyman,
One of the four times is the world record.
I did it.
It's hard for me to jump four times this year.
Where did he go?
I don't know.
Matsumoto's team is the winner.
The winner is Heipo.
It's coming.
Where is it?
It's going up.
It's coming.
Heipo, burn.
I don't want to do it.
I used three days of strength today.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I feel sick.
You feel sick?
The viewers will feel sick even more.
Let's go over there.
One by one.
That's right.
Let's cheer for each other.
The four of us are fine.
The one that bothers me the most is
There's a young man in there.
I'm completely down.
Young man.
Don't you cheer for me?
I'm not cheering for you.
I'm making fun of you.
Each team has a coach.
Yes.
Let's go.
The coach of the Hamada team is
The one who can run and jump.
Mr. Masaki Morinaga.
Mr. Masaki.
Mr. Masaki is going to jump.
Please.
Demonstration.
I'm going to jump.
Wow.
What was that?
Are you an idiot?
Amazing.
About 7 meters.
What's the record?
The current record is
7.5 meters.
Wow.
Amazing.
What a great coach.
He was doing this in the air.
He was walking.
The air time is long.
Mr. Masaki Morinaga.
The record achieved in 1992,
8.25 meters,
hasn't been broken yet.
The top star of the track and field
will be the coach of the Hamada team.
He's a Japanese record holder.
You know what that means, right?
What?
World record holder?
The coach of the Matsumoto team is
this person.
He's already won.
What?
Wow.
You know what?
He's been laughing
the whole time.
He's still laughing.
What?
It has nothing to do with you.
Why are you so interested?
I failed.
Look.
The coach of Matsumoto is
the producer of Luminosa Yoshimoto.
The current record is
3.30 meters.
Why is it 3.30 meters?
I can't get close to him.
He's not naked.
I don't know.
I can't get close to him.
Excuse me, Mr. Matsumoto.
Yes.
Actually,
the World Cup is coming up.
The world is paying attention
to this match.
The Africa Central Television
is here to interview you.
He's here.
The director is the same.
He's the same.
He's here.
I believe you.
The camera of Japan is here.
He's here again.
He's here.
I told him
to do this kind of match.
I told him to do this kind of match.
He's fast.
You're fast.
He's angry.
He's not laughing at all.
He's angry because he doesn't have time.
I can't do this.
Today,
I'm in perfect condition.
I can jump 1.20 meters.
What are you talking about?
He's funny.
The West Indian International Television
is also here.
Yes.
Why is there music?
You're crazy.
You're in the way.
You're in the way when you're editing.
He's a timekeeper.
It's a picture of curry.
It's a TV show.
It's the West Indian.
It's a picture of curry.
You don't need to be in the picture.
Why are you in the picture?
Thank you.
It's our first time to be in India.
Welcome.
Why are you talking while you are waiting?
Are you wearing a wig?
Give me.
What the hell are you talking about?
I'm talking about America.
Don't argue with me.
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?
I'll do my best.
I've been talking about Africa.
What the hell?
I just want to do a mini skit with you guys.
Both teams go into practice under their respective coaches.
The Hamada team starts with a warm-up run.
On the other hand, Matsumoto starts with a jump training without a flexible workout.
No!
It's hard to keep your feet together, right?
The Hamada team goes on to the important point of practice.
The more you go up, the more your body goes up.
It looks like the floor is going to be loose.
See?
It didn't feel good.
It felt good.
It's okay.
Did you get it?
You're amazing.
I can do this much.
What the hell?
The Hamada team rests their body.
Can I check the rules?
For example, if you can't keep your feet together, you can't do this.
I don't think so.
Really?
If we burn out, it's over.
It's a great TV deck.
I'm done talking.
I'll ask you to get out of this tent.
It's a different place.
It's okay. I'll just burn it out.
It's the other way around.
The Hamada team gets ready for the real thing.
A massage with concentration.
My wife made it.
Your wife made it?
I can fly.
You can fly?
What?
It's not Hitoshi. It's Hiroshi.
It's me.
I'm just showing my love for the tent to my parents.
The real thing is coming up.
The Hamada team is in a relaxed mood.
The tension is starting to show.
Matsumoto is alone next to him.
What's the outcome of the match?
The race is about to begin.
It's about time.
We've been practicing.
I'm a little nervous.
It's hard to play tag for 48 hours.
It's like he has a lot of demons.
I've been bitten.
He has more demons.
It's hard.
The Hamada team has Yamasaki, Endo, Tanaka and Hamada.
The Matsumoto team is in the lead in the third place.
First of all, the Hamada team has Yamasaki.
Please give me a round of applause.
Let's go!
Wow!
Team Hamada's first challenger is Yamasaki.
What kind of challenge will he show in this tense atmosphere?
Let's go!
Nice jump!
Okay, okay.
Did I reach the ceiling?
The ceiling.
Did I pass the checkpoint?
No, there's no checkpoint.
The current record is...
4 meters.
Yes!
4 meters?
You did it!
No way!
Okay, Matsumoto-san.
I think it was the best practice.
Really?
Including practice.
I think it was the best practice.
I know, I know.
Wait a minute!
Wait!
Thank you.
If that's the case,
I have an average score,
so I can't exceed 4 meters at this point.
Are you serious?
Yes.
Matsumoto's expression
is all over the place
in Yamasaki's record.
That was a nice jump.
It was a really nice jump.
He jumped better than me.
Matsumoto's record is 4.5 meters.
He jumped really far.
I think it's about 4.5 meters.
It's about 1.0 meters.
That's amazing.
He jumped really far.
I think it's about 4.5 meters.
That's amazing.
Tadaiwa's record is 4.53 meters.
Yes!
That was a nice jump.
He was really focused.
It felt like there was no one else
doing it alone.
Let's go to the second round.
Let's go!
Hamada's team.
The second person is Endo.
How far is it?
It's about 4 meters.
Everyone, don't go!
Tadaiwa's record is 4.27 meters.
That's amazing.
He jumped really far.
Matsumoto's second jump.
He's just scratching his chest.
I'd like to extend the record a little
and make a difference.
Let's go!
He jumped!
Tadaiwa's record is 4.65 meters.
That's amazing.
It's a world of 6 meters.
It's okay.
Matsumoto's jumping really well.
It's amazing.
Hamada's team.
The third person is Tanaka.
Relax.
Heijyoshi
I'll do my best for the second round.
Let's go!
He jumped!
This is not good.
The current record is 4m40cm.
Wait a minute.
This is not good.
You didn't jump the most.
That's right.
I wanted to jump in a big way.
Why did you think so much?
You don't have to think about it.
You can jump normally.
I wanted to jump in a big way.
You didn't jump in a big way.
Everyone, be quiet.
I'm in the image training.
Concentration.
Finally, the problem is solved.
I'm going.
Go.
I did it.
The current record is 2m87cm.
Good.
As practiced.
It took a long time.
The drama of waiting was waiting.
This is amazing.
Hama, please.
Next is Hama.
The current record is 62cm.
So far, Matsumoto has jumped more than 4m50cm twice.
I can't let my guard down.
This is a place where I show my determination as a captain.
Please hold it.
I did it.
This is a very good game.
The current record is 4m16cm.
That's too hard.
I did it.
Matsumoto.
You can jump 4m80cm, right?
Yes.
I'm angry because I'm worried.
I'm very worried.
I'm doing my best for you.
I'm sorry.
Crying or laughing, this is the last leap.
If you jump 4m79cm here, it will be a miracle reversal.
4m79cm.
As far as I've seen the record so far, it's not an impossible number.
At that time, Matsumoto took a long run from the starting point.
Will this strategy succeed?
I'm going.
It's your turn.
I'm tired.
I'm doing pretty well.
I'm counting on you.
The current record is 4m56cm.
I did it.
I want to jump again.
I'm different now.
What are you?
I'm sorry.
Matsumoto will be punished.
I can't accept it.
The six men had a match.
The result was a victory for the Hamada team.
Matsumoto, who keeps screaming with his shoulders down, will face a cruel punishment game that no one has ever experienced.
This program was provided by the following sponsors.