The next day
Can you film?
No
What about the video?
I can't film the video
You can't film the video?
Yes
Oh, I see
Good morning
What's wrong?
You're panting
I'm tired
What?
Who are you talking to?
The police
What?
No way
The police
They wouldn't do that
No, they would do something
Right?
They would do something
No way
The police are really angry today
Why?
Now that I think about it, I feel sorry for them
How many years have you been in this show?
15 years
How many times have you done this show in 15 years?
Quite a lot
Have you ever filmed the police in a cool way?
If you say so
Have you ever filmed the police in a 180-degree angle?
No, I've never done that
No, no
I've done a lot of things that made me the main character
Yes
Right?
Are you not satisfied with that?
I'm not satisfied
I heard that only this year, the number of ENDERs has decreased by 6
But that's the last time
I've only done it 5 times, but the number of ENDERs has decreased by 6
In the end, what's the problem?
That's right
What's wrong with us?
That's why I want you to show us something cool on this show
I want you to show us that there's nothing cool about you
It's difficult
Even a little thing can be scary
That's right
Even if you do it
Suwa-chan, you don't have to do it
I don't think so
Right?
It's getting worse
I don't know
What do you mean?
I have to go to the Hollow, so I can't go there
I'll go to the Go Masuri soon
Please think about it
I really can't do it
K-POP is getting more and more popular
It's been 15 years since K-POP was shown on TV
Will he be able to show off his coolness?
To fulfill the wish of K-POP, which is the overall production of this program
4 men stood up
This program is provided by the sponsors of the 5th generation
Let's clean up
Excuse me
Thank you
Are you cool?
Of course
Of course, I'm cool
So I think it would be nice if I could show it as my whole body
Let's talk about it
I think a cool guy is a cowboy
In terms of appearance
I think so
I want to prepare all the costumes
Excuse me
What kind of person is he?
He's a cowboy
He's a rodeo
A rodeo
He's a man
What do you think?
What?
Are you sure you're cool?
I think he's cool
I think he's definitely cool
Say it yourself
It's annoying
What?
What if we've been friends for 20 years?
Should we do it? Should we not do it?
You've been talking for so long
We've been thinking about it
It's better to do it
It's definitely cool
Let's do it
What are you doing?
It's the same thing
We'll be waiting
Show us a cool uniform on the rodeo
This is perfect
It costs a lot of money
I prepared this
I had it set up like this
I see
Even if it falls, it's okay
I don't care
It's good
Thank you
It's easy
Anyone can do it
I'm getting excited
It's good
Shall we go?
Let's go
We can go anytime
Let's put it on
Just in case
It's cool enough
Let's do a pose
Isn't it good?
Anyone can do it
Please hold the camera
Let's go
No
Just turn around
Excuse me
I'm scared
We just turned around
From now on
I don't like it
It sounds bad
It's fun
Show us a cool one
Let's go
I don't like it
Excuse me
Remember this
Mr. Hemo
What should we do?
Why are you scared?
We just turned around
It's fun
Why are you angry?
Let's apologize
We can't do that
What's wrong?
What do you think?
Again?
I'm so excited
I finally calmed down
There's some improvement
Let's talk about it
Improvement?
We can't do it like this
I want you to explain it
Can you ask him?
Excuse me
Mr. Hemo
Can we talk?
Let's talk
Your appearance
You look like you're scared
Can you change your appearance?
What do you think?
I trust you
Really?
Thank you
If something happens to you
God's punishment will come
I don't think it's a punishment
What do you mean?
I think it's a good thing
We're friends
I'm glad you think so
You're reading an old book
Let's see your cool appearance
This is good
It's not scary
It's a flower field
The color is pink
It's here
I've been waiting
What do you think?
It's fun
I like it because it's cute
That's good
The machine was out of order
I think it will change the atmosphere
It's not just this
I've prepared this for you
Look
It's cute
You're smiling
I can't help it
I'm trying to talk
What do you think?
It would be nice if you could show your cool side
It would be romantic
It's like a compliment
It's like a joke
I said it as it is
I said the language
Heba
She's right in front
Are you okay?
Show your cool side
Let's go
It's here
Why are you coming back?
Heba
You've done too much
This is tough
Thank you for coming
I'm sorry
Thank you
I'm going
Go back
It's really bad
I told you
Don't be shy in front of a woman
That's what it is
You brought a woman
You were embarrassed
It's weird
Let me explain
I don't think I'll see her
Really?
You're lying
It can't be helped
What?
It's too early
I'm sorry
Heba
We're going to talk about it
This is a point of improvement
We've talked about it
I think machines are different
In that sense, if you try to do it with horror
It's a human's way
I understand that
He said he wanted to go to Shibaki.
Yeah, we've been doing it for a long time.
He said he couldn't make it to the next step without going to Shibaki.
Who was the most excited?
I'm sorry.
To be honest, I wasn't as excited as I usually am.
Show us some cool martial arts.
I thought he was really mad at you.
Yeah, I thought so, too.
But it's not the end.
It's almost done.
It's like this. It's not a machine anymore.
You'll see when you see it.
I can imagine what it'll be like.
This is a pretty gentle feeling.
That's fine.
Well, then.
Yes, please.
Please come this way.
This is okay.
It's like this.
Then, Mr. Hebu.
Please get on.
It's pretty heavy.
Mr. Hebu, it's pretty heavy.
It's coming.
Then I'll give you one.
You've been saying that for a long time, Mr. Hebu.
Wait a minute.
It's okay.
Let's go.
It hurts.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
You guys.
You're the devil who wears a mask on someone's face.
Mr. Hebu.
What are you doing?
Yama-chan, are you okay?
What's wrong?
That's a gun.
It's stuck.
Yama-chan, it's stuck.
I almost died.
That's the last thing I can do.
Please go home.
No.
Please go home today.
We've come this far.
We've done our best.
I'm really angry.
I'll explain it to you now.
It's definitely okay.
I don't think it's possible.
Please.
Please go home.
That was fast.
But it was better than I expected.
Excuse me.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Mr. Hebu.
Why did you come today?
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I did my best thinking about you.
Yama-chan, your ears are getting swollen.
How do you feel about this?
I'm not about that.
Who do you want to kill?
Who do you want to kill, Ebou-san?
I know, I know.
I'm sorry.
I think this is the last time.
We have to do it in a safe way. No fear, no danger.
And we have to look cool.
Can we really do that?
Yes, we can.
What are you going to do?
Really?
I want to kill one more person.
Who is it, Ebou-san?
Hama-san...
Who is it?
Hama-san, good.
Mimimi?
I'm counting on you.
Get Ebou-san right away.
Let's see cool Ebou on the rodeo.
If you complain about this, I'm sorry.
Why did you have to do this?
Honestly, I'm embarrassed.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, I'll do it.
Oh, it's running.
It's going well.
Ebou-san, you can see that it's not dangerous.
It's definitely safe.
What do you think?
There was a lot of trouble, but if the end is good, everything is good.
I'm very grateful that I was able to come to Hamada.
Is that so?
As for the end, I'm not satisfied yet.
Is this okay?
It's okay.
But really...
I'll leave it to you.
If you can do it with love.
We've been together for years.
I'll do it.
If it's okay, I can't do it.
That's right, you can't do it.
Okay, let's go.
Ebou-san.
It's going to be cool.
I'll show you something cool.
Okay, okay, okay.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Oh, that's cool.
Good luck, Ebou-san.
It's hot.
Do you want some more?
This is...
I don't know.
This week, we will have an unreleased talk.
What's inside Antonio Inoki's chin?
This is also an orthodox...
It's a fight.
I'll tell you what's inside.
That's a stick.
I'm just putting it in.
Screamer?
Screamer.
If you take it off, there's something like a caster.
It's like a piece of this.
Something like this.
That's coming out.
Yeah.
Why?
So, if you hold Inoki's legs, it's like that.
Once, it goes like this. If you suddenly can't do this, it goes like this.
Suddenly, it can't turn.
Inoki is also scared, scared, scared, scared, scared.
It goes like this, goes like this, goes like this.
That's right.
It's funny when you show the picture.
There's nothing here.
There's a caster.
Inoki, when he's about Inoki, he doesn't walk at all.
I think that's hard.
Why is that? Fujita can do it.
Anyone can do it.
When you can't do it, you want to hide it, so you put it in here.
That's right. When the road is wide, it's fine.
Fujita can also do it like this.
When it's narrow, if it goes like this, it goes like this once.
That's enough.
Recently, Fujita has gone out once and looked for it like this.
There's nothing here.
Fujita can also do it.
I understand that well.
So, when it's narrow, it goes like this.
In that case, it goes like this.
Everyone is trying to laugh.
I can't laugh at that kind of exaggeration.
It goes like this.
You're doing a lot of shurin.
I'm tired of it.
Shut up.
It goes like this.
I'm going home.
This program was brought to you by the 5-dan sponsor.