In the 5th episode of Gaki no Tsukai Arahen, Tsukitsuki Ogiri Daigasu!
I am Hamada Masatoshi.
Please introduce yourself one by one.
I am Yamasaki Bankaku.
Nice to meet you.
Sexy-san, please have fun.
I am Team Zero Noriasu.
Nice to meet you.
Today, I am invited to this place.
Don't be noisy.
Don't get lost.
Mo mo mo mo mo.
Nice to meet you.
What is that?
Golden Week is coming soon.
That's right.
Everyone will go to many places.
I will go to my favorite New York.
Nakamashi.
Mo mo mo mo mo.
Atakamo Reading!
The topic of today's Atakamo Reading is this.
Japan Passing.
Passing?
Yes.
It's about economics.
Japan Passing is about passing cars.
Passing is the first thing.
It's the first thing.
But this is not a hole-in-one.
The bubble burst and real estate prices rise and become cheaper.
Which one?
I will write about this in detail later.
I will go to the next page.
Until now, there was a lot of nonsense.
But from now on, let's work seriously.
Why?
Because...
What is the meaning of trade fraud?
If you ask what it is...
What is that?
According to the court, it's not worth 200,000 yen.
There must be more money.
The money...
It's not enough.
It's not enough?
Give it to me.
Japan Passing is dead.
But I don't know what kind of enemy will attack next.
Good luck, Japan Passing.
Japan Passing is dead.
Can I change the order?
Let's change.
Yamazaki, you can't.
Yamazaki and I will change.
This guy is the worst.
Yamazaki is the worst.
Then...
Yamazaki is here.
I don't know.
Then...
I don't know at all.
I don't know.
Hitoshi,
do you want to drink or not?
Give me a break already!
Hitojichi!
Is that so?
Of course it is!
Prank!
Give me a break already!
The answer is this!
Hitojichi no baka o kan!
This guy's way of saying it is a bit French!
That's strange!
The answer is this!
Now, let's have Pea and Noriasu do it together.
Yamazaki vs. Noriasu.
Ready!
That outfit suits you well!
Wait a minute!
You're admitting it!
If you give it to me, I'll give it to you!
Can I say it?
Yamazaki, ready!
It's like it's raining!
Your hairstyle is similar to Hamada-san's!
You're so funny!
Yamagata's girlfriend is Genki!
Your girlfriend is Genki?
What are you doing?
Konnichiwa!
You can't do that!
Good morning!
Speak!
I don't want to do it with this guy!
Now, Jimmy vs. Noriasu.
Jimmy, Noriasu is hard to do!
Noriasu, ready!
Jimmy, do your best!
You do your best too!
Jimmy, do your best too!
Everyone, are you ready?
From now on,
one by one,
here,
in the middle, put your head out.
I'll give you a topic.
If you can make a joke with that topic,
raise your hand.
Yamazaki-kun!
Yamazaki-kun's
topic is here!
Yamazaki-kun!
Put your head out!
What's going on?
I feel tired...
Pick up the ball!
Slow down!
I am a vomitting baby because of too much heavy spray.
It made me die but I did not give up and continued to fight.
Please appreciate my savage personality.
But I was rather surprised.
What the hell!
Ladies and gentlemen.
We have to think about the opening.
I have a bad feeling.
It smells too much.
It's strange. It feels like a little man is walking on the table.
The audience seems to be tired.
Time is time.
We have to get up early and go home.
What's the matter?
Everyone is going to take a break.
It's okay.
Is there anyone who is going to take a break?
It's like a poor man.
I'm going back to the Philippines.
Raise your hand.
Be careful.
It would be nice if everyone could take a break.
How long do they take a break?
There are many people who take a break for about two weeks.
They take a break for seven days.
I feel sorry for them.
They don't have time to take a break.
I don't know why they take a break for two weeks.
They don't have time to take a break even if they break the house.
I don't do good things if I break the house.
You are a man.
Everyone is having a hard time.
Do something.
I have to find a hobby.
Everyone tells me to do something.
You are telling me to do something.
I am doing something.
I only do what I have decided.
Everyone tells me to do something.
Everyone tells me to go camping.
I want to buy something.
Do you want to buy a car?
I want to buy a car.
What are you talking about?
You are a man.
I will wear a bandana at that time.
I want to go camping.
You nicht something with a knife.
In the fishing, it goes quickly.
The fish Chernobyl пример disappears in a second.
What are you doing?
I take a rest.
So you do not do anything else.
He told me to put some salt now.
You are the worst man.
What are you talking about?
I'm starting to get embarrassed
I'm starting to get weird
But you really want to go?
I don't want to go
Why?
I'm asking you to go
What are you going to do?
Fishing
I don't want to go
Why?
I like you
Have you ever been to a fishing village?
No
I haven't
But we all went to a fishing village
It was really strong
Everyone said to pull
It was amazing
Everyone was surprised
But we didn't get surprised
We were surprised that we couldn't go because of the tires
It was fun
Take everyone and go
If it was fun, do you want to go?
I'll ask and then talk
Camping is fun
It's a golf club
Don't do that
What is that?
Are you stupid?
I'll just say no
Just go
I'll tell you how much fun it is
There are a lot of fun things when you go to the mountains
Fishing and what else
You go to the mountains and fish?
Let's go fishing more
Do you want to go on a cruiser?
No
Do you really think so?
Buy a cruiser
Why me?
You have money
What are you doing?
You're making friends
It doesn't matter
You don't want to buy a cruiser?
If you don't want to buy a camping car, buy a cruiser
Cruiser?
You have to be careful not to sneeze
You have to take it off
If you have a big hole
You have to put a pot in
Buy it yourself
If you want to buy a cruiser, name it
Why?
I can't name it
You can name it Natsumi
I don't care
You don't care? What do you mean?
Don't say that
I think it's fun
You have too many hobbies
You don't do things that celebrities don't do?
You don't go camping?
I don't go camping
Otherwise, the range of the entertainment is narrow
If you go camping, it's natural
It's natural
If you go camping
What are you doing?
I'm just saying
You can use it
I can use it
Let's do that
There are women who date
There is a big difference between an out-door woman and an in-door woman
It's really tiring to date an out-door woman
It's annoying
It's annoying, I hate it
Women from the sports world are more fun than women from the culture world
That's completely different
Where are you going?
Did you take a break?
I'm licking it
Don't lick it
Are you stupid?
Take me somewhere
Where are you going?
It's getting late
Take the money and go somewhere
Go somewhere
I'll watch a video at home
Women are terrible
What should I do?
If you see a video of a jet ski on TV, you can say, ha
What are you doing?
Just like a jet ski
It's just like that
You stupid
I'm going to cry
I'm licking it
Do you have that kind of reaction?
A talent is licking an out-door woman
An out-door woman?
I'm licking it
I can't call it affection
I'll tell you
At the store in the morning, a salaryman puts his hand on his waist and puts the newspaper in his hand
He drinks juice with his hand on his chest and drinks it
Why does he put his hand on his waist and drink it?
Old men drink it like this
He drinks it like this next to Kiyosuku
What's the meaning of this hand on his waist?
I don't know
When I drink cold milk in the morning, it's bad for my stomach
When I drink it directly, it's bad for my stomach
That's why I drink it like this
What?
Your stuff goes in here and comes here
I'm playing with it
It comes here and comes out
There's a hole here
If it goes here, it's bad
That's why I want it to go here
Then it goes like this
There's nothing like this
It can't go through
That's strange
If you want to say something, say it
What is this?
Get rid of it
What is the most expensive thing you've bought?
I don't buy expensive things
You're really dirty
Why?
Because I've never seen you buy expensive things
You're a loser
Is that so?
That's right
You must have left a lot of money
I didn't leave it
I left it for you
I used it when it wasn't selling
You're a bad person
I didn't leave it
It's cool
Even if it's not expensive, I buy it
This is expensive
This is savings
This is a gift
This is my rent, this is my electricity bill, this is my monthly allowance
Wait a minute, I'll pay for this too
When you go to a family restaurant
I sometimes eat steak
When you say medium
I eat Young Hamburg
This has fried eggs
I eat
What are you talking about?
I'm happy when I eat fried eggs
By the way, give me back the 3,000 yen from when I was in middle school
I remembered again
I didn't borrow it
I definitely borrowed it
Because it's you
There is a restaurant called Nagasaki
I went there to buy clothes
When I was looking at clothes
I noticed that Hamada wasn't there
I went to buy clothes together, but Hamada wasn't there
I went to the top floor, but Hamada
Why?
Hamachon, Hamachon
I don't have enough money
Wait a minute, if you really don't have enough money, I'll tell you right away
Why did you go to the emergency room alone?
That's why I borrowed 3,000 yen
Is it okay?
It's okay
I'm ashamed to say it myself