Next time on Gachi no Tsukai Ara! Chikitsuki! Fukawa Ryoshichi Hengen!
This is amazing!
This is amazing, isn't it?
Fukawa!
The five of you are here!
Nice to meet you!
In the past, our talent and staff...
Well, most of them.
They came from other places, right?
Yes, so really...
I don't know what to say about myself.
Why?
As a comedian, I wanted to do what I had to do to get here.
I wanted to throw everything away to get here.
But it takes years.
That's right.
I've been watching him for a few years, and I thought,
this kid can't do what he has to do.
This is the current score.
Yes.
Where should we go today?
Well, for now...
I want to be in the top 10.
He doesn't seem very confident.
Before that, can you introduce the one who has changed his position?
Really?
This is probably the first time he's been on TV.
If you don't introduce him earlier, his eyes will be different.
That's right.
This is my brother.
See?
Fuka, don't do it like this.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
What should we do?
But Hamada-san has also changed his position.
Yes, I've changed my position.
You've changed your position.
Endo, you've also changed your position.
I'm not aware of changing my position.
What do you think about Endo's head position?
I've changed my position.
I want to make it short.
I'll stop.
I've been caught many times.
What?
Speak properly.
Has Kanaka-san changed his position?
Yes, he has.
You are really...
He has become straight.
Yes, he has grown.
Speak properly.
Kanaka has become neutral.
Really?
Yes.
He is 50 years old.
He is close.
Let's decide on the movie.
I can't say it.
Yes, you can't say it.
What is it?
Let's do it.
What are you doing?
It took me a long time to change my clothes.
But when I came back, they were normal clothes.
I just changed my clothes.
It was just a normal pose.
You can do it even if you change your clothes, right?
You have a car, right?
I don't have a car.
I'll go to the back seat.
Sushi.
Tuna.
Shrimp.
Is this okay?
I'm sorry.
The clay and the shelf were dangerous.
I was attacked from a distance.
I don't know if I'm scared.
Maybe it's because we're close.
I was attacked from a distance.
It's amazing.
Thank you.
I ate a lot.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what happened.
Have you decided on the meeting?
Have you decided on the project?
Do you still want to do it?
Fukawa.
Please say something.
I can't do it now.
Fukawa.
Please say something.
I'm in the middle of a meeting.
Fukawa.
Don't get angry because I used the corner of the eraser.
The corner of the eraser.
The corner of the eraser?
I'm sorry.
Don't get angry because I used the corner of the eraser.
The corner of the eraser?
Please say something.
Don't get angry because I used the corner of the eraser.
Put it in.
It's not a safe car.
I ate it.
Really?
It's tough.
Please do it.
What should I do to change this?
This way.
Put it in.
I thought he was stupid.
I'll give you 5,000 yen.
What the hell are you doing?
Damn it!
No way...
Stop!
I can't do it.
Do it.
You're so persistent.
I can't do it.
That guy...
Yama-chan is so lame.
He's so clingy!
I didn't do anything.
That's true.
Huh?
I didn't do anything.
If I did, would you call me?
I'm close to you.
You're such an idiot.
He's starting to get into it.
For example, if I did...
Yeah?
You did?
I got a message.
It's strange.
Huh?
Here?
Where is it?
What is this?
I'm doomed.
It's strange.
Hey!
It's done!
Fukawa-san's prize is...
It's 31,000 yen.
It's 31,000 yen!
Thank you!
To be honest, I didn't know how it would be until the third one.
It was terrible.
Is this...
Is this a step-up?
What are you talking about?
No, no, no.
It's not a strange meaning.
I wonder if it's okay to encourage yourself.
I don't want to watch it.
I'll watch it again next time.
I'm a kid's servant.
Gaki Gaki-kun Gaki Gaki-kun
Gaki Gaki-kun Gaki Gaki
When was it?
When we had the last talk.
The audience was terrible.
Terrible.
Was it today?
It was really terrible.
My heart was breaking.
I was really depressed.
I didn't do anything bad.
I was really angry.
Angry?
Speaking of angry,
I was having a meal at a bar.
And now,
I was young.
I was in third grade.
When I came to the bar,
the old lady was like,
What's that?
When I came to the bar,
it was strange.
The old lady was like,
Imai-chan.
You know,
she was ignoring me on purpose.
It was strange.
She pushed me away.
She said,
Imai-chan, shake my hand.
I felt bad.
Because I was a star.
I was a star.
You have a big mouth.
You were a star.
I don't have a big mouth.
She called me Imai-chan,
and I was like,
What do you think I did?
I was shocked.
What did you do?
I was like,
Yes, I'm a star.
And she was like,
Where are you hitting me?
This is what happens.
Basically,
when I eat a side dish,
I definitely want to eat rice.
I can't eat rice.
When I eat a side dish,
The balance is weak.
If you don't eat it.
There's still rice left.
Then eat more.
I can't eat rice.
Wait, Power!
I can't get angry.
Don't lie to me.
If it was you,
you wouldn't be living like this.
Why?
I don't know.
I was scared of doing nothing.
But when I got home,
I felt sick.
Don't you think
you should do something like that?
I'm so angry.
At times like that,
I can't help but envy you.
Why?
You can hit someone
without hesitation.
Even if I say it,
my heart is like a businessman.
I can't do that.
But the people at the store
are so considerate.
Even if I say I'm sorry,
I don't need any money today.
Even if you say that,
I don't need any money.
I have a lot of money.
If I talk a little,
my heart will be like this.
When you were young,
you used to run a business
in a village in Iga.
Please tell us
how to get rid of
Kunoichi,
who is forbidden
from falling in love.
If you can't get rid of Kunoichi,
that means
you don't want to get rid of him.
You don't want to get rid of him.
That's what he thinks.
But if you change the situation,
you can't get rid of him.
You can't get rid of him.
You're so particular about that.
You're so sensitive
about getting rid of him.
If you change the situation,
you want to get rid of him.
That's what he thinks.
Is that so?
So,
you think
you shouldn't think
like that, right?
You shouldn't think
that way.
That's also bad, isn't it?
Because you know
what's bad,
you shouldn't think
that way.
That's why
Kunoichi is bad.
Is that so?
He's a scoundrel.
What?
Kunoichi is a scoundrel?
Even with a katana,
he can do this
and that,
and he can do this.
He can do that.
What are you talking about?
Tell me how to get rid of him.
Shuriken
does this
really fast,
but if you look at him slowly,
when he comes back,
he does this.
That's why
Kunoichi is bad.
I get it now.
Tell me how to get rid of him.
For example,
let's say
I was targeted
by Kunoichi.
I was targeted.
I'm his enemy.
He's my enemy.
So I can't get rid of him
like I usually do.
I can't get rid of him
This is definitely
not good,
but I have one.
How did you get rid of him?
I was sleeping.
Then
I heard a bang.
So that's what
you're doing.
No, no.
I think I was being attacked.
I was being attacked.
That's weird.
I was aiming at him.
There was
a slight gap
and light was leaking
from the other side.
I think you were close.
It was leaking light.
I was sleeping
and I heard a bang.
I heard a bang.
Get ready!
Did he come?
I would be surprised.
You would be surprised.
All of a sudden.
He was wearing
a short-sleeved shirt like this.
It was a short-sleeved shirt.
Get ready!
This is where it starts.
You can't be surprised here.
I don't know.
I thought I was done.
Well, I really thought it was a yes, but I didn't want to say it.
I wasn't prepared or anything, but I said it.
You idiot!
It wasn't that easy.
You idiot, you can't do that.
It was easy.
It wasn't that easy.
I mean, I caught it.
It was right here.
Stop it!
I'm going to find it!
That was fast.
It wasn't that easy.
Well, he did it too.
You can't just do it like that.
What is this? It's like a ball.
What are you doing?
It's gone.
Tonight is the night.
When Anpanman sees someone who's hungry and in trouble, he tears up his face.
When Matsumoto sees someone in trouble, what does he do?
Basically, it's the same.
Anpanman really tears up his face.
I really don't tear up my face because I'm an Anpanman.
But you see, it's like he's smiling.
What is this?
For example, look at my face.
Why do I have to see your smile at this distance?
Everyone, look at my face.
You still remember my name, don't you?
Happy birthday to you.
This is Yamazaki Hosei's birthday.
That's right.
Happy birthday to you.
Everyone, look at my face.
Look at my face.
It's already out.