It's time for the staff free talk show!
They're not taking it off
They don't like it
I don't understand how professional they are
If they're just going to do free talk, they're going to ask for laughter
Since it's just the two of you, let's choose from here
Let's start with the first group
Since it's just the two of you
You have to come here
Yanaoka
About us and our family
No
And don't touch the audience
No no no
So you can see us from time to time
No
Let's start with the opening
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors
Let's go
First group, Yanaoka, Otomo
Ladies and gentlemen
Next month, you're getting married
Congratulations
I heard you got a young lady
No, it's not like that
I'm going to get married and come back
So that's what you're going to do
You're not saying anything interesting
Right?
You're all dressed up
It's warm
Thank you everyone
Thank you so much
What is that?
You didn't bring anything
What is this?
Seiza
You guys
Today's guest is warm
It's really warm
Let's go
Who's next?
This is no good
This
And
What is this?
No matter what it is, I have a lot of love for this program
Ladies and gentlemen
Hello
What is this?
I don't know much about this person
Even if I'm asked to be in the second team
Recently I've been walking around the city
And people say I look like him
But recently my concept is Kimutaku
Don't come back
What is this?
This is my strongest comedy
Who do you think looks the coolest?
I don't know
Don't say that
If you say that, then say it
Nozomu-san, shouldn't you have a postcard?
Without talking
I don't think so
You don't think so?
I still have to go to the bathroom
Why did you kick me?
I was looking at you and you kicked me
I was turning around
I wasn't turning around
Why?
I was just flapping
I'm sorry
This is difficult
This is hard
I don't do this
I think he can do it
So he's a good partner
I can do both otaku and house
I can do both
I haven't seen them talking
Ladies and gentlemen
There's not much to it
It's really our first time meeting
I think Okamoto-kun is a celebrity
That's right
Saying that's right is rude
But I think it's true
I've lost my regular job since fall
Is that so?
Even when I walk around the streets
I've become someone who doesn't have a job
I'm getting a pretty depressed reaction
It's rude
It's not like that
That's right
I sometimes see it on the screen
Sometimes
When this is on the screen
I might lose my only regular job
What do you do then?
I'm an idiot
That was the end
I don't think about it seriously
Thank you very much
Thank you
It was good to have you two
You had a chance to run away
Why did you talk about it?
We didn't talk about it seriously
Even though you were on the show
I was thinking about the costume
You should have listened to your partner
What do you call yourself?
Okamoto
That's rude
Everyone says it's rude
You want to show it
That's right
I've prepared it
Let's see it
Hello
It's 8 o'clock
Until now
I'm an amateur
I don't have the energy to talk
Do you want to write a letter?
This is hard
I don't have the energy to talk
Don't open the door
Hey, stop
Don't make my show dirty
I'll read it
I'm the man who came here to recommend
I'll read the first one
This is a question for Dea-san
Who is the next popular member of Johnny's?
I don't know
If you keep your nose hair long
What will happen?
If I keep my nose hair long
I'll look bad
Wow
It's a white towel
Leave the towel
Don't you play sports?
I'm a sports baseball player
What?
You threw a white towel
It's a knockout
Thank you
Oh no
Everyone
It's not like that
My partner is crying
Why are you crying?
I have to use the bomb
What is that?
It's been a long time
You look happy
I'm in trouble
You're in trouble?
He has muscle pain and fever
He has a cold
No one asked him to go home
But I think I can do it
Right?
I'll do it
I'm a genius
Mr. Jigashi
Yesterday we did a 50m race
I won
Wait
We didn't exercise
We didn't fall
I fell
You didn't fall
I was desperate
I won
You were desperate
Why did you run like that?
Actually
If you can't say it, don't say it
I made a mistake
Who is it?
It's Furuhata Ninjaburo
It doesn't look like you
I'm tired
I'm listening to the talk
It's not interesting
But today's guest is sweet
It's because of the atmosphere
Today was a good guest
I wanted to do it with a worse guest
It's not funny at all
But
What should I say?
You should say it yourself
You're good
Please listen
Even now
After the title match
Why did Matsumoto-san throw away his boxing gloves?
Don't take them off!
What is this?
It's like
I'm your partner
That's right
When I was boxing
What did you do?
I was Megaton Matsumoto
You were Megaton Matsumoto?
You were either a champion or a first place
You were the bottom
You were the champion
What was your name?
Megaton Matsumoto
You were the champion?
The champion was great
Who was it?
No, what about you?
Megaton
Coincidentally, we have the same name
The name is the same
You're so mean!
Well, that's true
But the champion was a while ago
Megaton came back
No, it was your debut
What's with that face?
Are you an otaku?
Change your name
You can't change your name
Megaton Matsumoto
It's the strongest name
Megaton Matsumoto vs Megaton Matsumoto
Well, we have the same name
Which one wins?
In the end, Megaton is the older brother
Megaton is the younger brother
That's mean
Well, that's true
Which one is the older brother?
I'm the older brother
Even though we're not siblings
How many rounds did you have?
Until the end
There was an extension
In the end
Basically, it was a fight
It's a boxing match
Why did you wear gloves
in the end?
He licked my lips
Who?
Megaton Matsumoto
Who are you?
My older brother
Your younger brother
We had a good fight
It was an exclusive
It was an exclusive boxing match
It was very spicy
He ran into the corner
Which one won?
I won
You won?
You're the champion
You quit?
I quit
Why did you quit?
The reason
It ended
Everyone was like
Megaton! Megaton!
Megaton!
It sounds heavy
Thank you, everyone
I said it about 8 times
You said it too many times
It doesn't matter how long
I said it
I went home
I was lonely
It was a beautiful stage
When I opened the door
It was full of gloves
I was so angry
I wanted to sleep
I don't need it anymore
It was written in the magazine
I thought the kogyal boom had calmed down
It was the young lady's
Komadam boom
The trend leader
What kind of boom
Will come next?
Do you know what the Komadam boom is?
I don't
You know the kogyal
Komadam boom
Can you put out your antenna?
Your antenna
And catch it
I've been hitting it
You hit the lack of glasses
I don't lack glasses
Everyone is wearing glasses
You said you lack water and rice
You said you lack glasses
I didn't
You did
Did you go to the Komadam boom?
I did
You didn't
You should have
I didn't
I think I said it
You will edit it
What's wrong with you?
It's an edit
Don't reveal what you don't need
I'm really angry
I'm cutting it
I'm not cutting it
What kind of boom
The next one is the Kominato boom
There's a little Kominato
You mean Minato-machi?
What's so exciting about the Kominato boom?
The Kominato
That's strange
What's so exciting about the Kominato
It's very exciting
What's so exciting about it?
This is amazing
Let me hear it
Okay
Can I say it again?
Why is the Kominato boom so exciting?
Okay
Why?
You should say it
What's so exciting about it?
I'm listening
Go
You should say it
You should say it twice
It's dirty
You should say it yourself
The Kominato is exciting, right?
It's exciting, okay
What's so exciting about it?
That's not it
You should say it three times
What's so exciting about it?
You said earlier that you're a high school girl
The Kominato is making
The Kominato is making a scene
They're selling their underwear
It's very exciting, right?
It's exciting, but it's very exciting
You should say it
It's actually very exciting
The words of the proposal that were in the magazine
Top 5
1. Let's get married
2. Let's get married and 3. Let's work hard together
4. Give birth to my child
5. I want to eat your food
Now, if Matsumoto-san is the age to fall in love
What kind of words would you use to propose?
The Japanese port is...
The Japanese port is... the kitchen
What?
The Japanese port is the kitchen
Hey, everyone listen to me
Anyone understand?
If you say that
That's your proposal
You don't know
What is that?
I was wondering what you were saying
And then you said yes
And then you said yes and your wife couldn't read it
I don't understand what you're implying
If there's something like that
What was I saying?
I was saying that I'd use my love to relieve myself
So that's what I said, right?
Yes, that's what you said.
So it's not me, it's you, Inari-san!
But it's already over, right?
You should've told me at least one proposal.
You often say that you want to drink the morning coffee, right?
That's a little...
There's a guy who says, please wash my underwear.
What is this?
No, no, no.
This is bad.
Ah, Te-chan!
What is this?
It doesn't make any sense at all.
I'll wash your underwear.
This won't be a proposal.
I'll tell you one proposal.
Yes.
Tell him, Te-chan.
No, really, Tamo-san.
How many proposals do you have? There are about six.
The second one.
If we do this, maybe...
Japan...
From the end of this year to the beginning of next year...
Maybe we'll enter the age of marriage.
The thing is...
The age of marriage?
A man and a woman who have never met before...
By saying these words that I'm about to tell you...
There's a possibility that they'll get married.
A lot of couples will get married.
Right?
That's the opposite.
You guys are laughing too much.
You're misunderstanding.
This movement...
A man and a woman...
What is this?
Well, it's fine.
Today is that kind of day.
Do whatever you want.
If you hear those words...
Yes, yes, yes.
It'll be a big deal.
The second one is fine.
Tell him.
Is that okay?
Yes.
What?
I want you to say it.
Japanese red.
Is that part of the sentence?
Yes, yes.
I'm sorry.
It's already over.
What?
No, no, no.
You're only saying Japanese red.
I thought it might be like that.
But it's not like that.
I don't know why.
If you...
If you love me...
Is that okay?
Yes.
If you call me to a restaurant.
What is it today?
I'll be like, okay.
What?
I'll put on a tie or something.
I'll call you to a restaurant or something.
I won't tell you that.
Say it quickly.
Is that okay?
Say the word propose.
I'll call you.