This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Mak-chan is so cute. Mak-chan is so cute. Why is Mak-chan so cute?
Thank you very much.
Hello.
Today is the first day of the festival.
Is that so?
Thank you very much.
This is the first time this year, right?
Yes.
If the first time doesn't go well, it's going to be a bad year.
That's right.
Can I entrust it to today's guest?
You don't have to entrust it to me.
I'm doing it on my own.
That's right.
When I came in today, there were a lot of these people.
What kind of reaction is that?
The stars are passing by a little more.
I wonder if I can meet them.
I don't care if you don't meet them.
I'm going to treat them badly.
I'm sorry.
Really.
Why are you ignoring me?
I don't know how to treat them.
Don't hit me too much. My skin will fly off.
It's burnt.
In the end, we didn't meet in Guam at all.
That's right.
It seems that there was a mistake once.
There was a mistake.
I avoided it.
I avoided it with a full hand.
Why do you avoid it?
What is it?
Why are you doing that?
You said you were going to the pool.
I didn't go to the pool.
I went to Kmart.
I don't know that.
We were going.
I was waiting for the car outside.
I saw it.
I was going to the front.
I was going to go to the front.
I saw it.
There was a taxi that stopped and came down.
I was going.
I drove the car.
I said, I'm here.
I was waiting for the taxi.
I don't think I was in a taxi.
You don't know the taxi or the car.
I don't know.
I've been to Japan Mart a couple of times.
Why have you been there three times?
I've been there once.
How many times?
You should have been there once.
I've been there, I've been there.
I've been to many places.
You've been to many places.
Oh, really?
I was wondering what I should do tomorrow.
I was thinking of going to the pool.
I heard that Hamada-san's family was making a reservation.
I thought I should go the day after tomorrow.
I knew it.
I didn't have to go there.
If I go with you, I'll be blamed for this.
You can see it, right?
That's right.
I've given up.
Is that so?
But...
What is it?
It's my first time.
I've been to many places during the New Year.
It's a bit annoying.
I heard that you were very rude.
What?
You've been to many places.
Everyone knows that.
If you say that, I'll tell everyone that you've been to many places.
One of your family members took a picture of you on a plane.
It was right after you arrived, right?
What did you take a picture of?
You shouldn't get so angry.
You hit Hamada's shoulder and looked back.
I heard that it was Tashiro-san.
That's correct.
I heard that.
What did you take a picture of?
Don't get angry.
He took me out.
What is it?
I took a picture of Tashiro-san.
I took a picture of you.
Tashiro-san said,
Did you take a picture of me?
That's right.
Why is the family in Osaka so bad?
I said that last year.
That's terrible.
What did you do?
What should I say?
The people in Tokyo came to me with a tone-deaf face.
They said,
Can I take a picture of you?
I said,
I'm sorry.
They said,
I said,
I'm sorry.
That family in Osaka is really bad.
They said,
I'm sorry.
I said,
What did they say?
They tried to teach me.
With a loud voice.
They treated me as a guest.
They said,
Come on, let's run away.
At that time,
They said,
I'm sorry, I can't do this anymore.
I'm not so good.
They said,
One old lady said,
Seriously.
You understand, don't you?
Young people are really bad.
No, no.
They said two things.
Seriously.
They said,
What are you doing?
You'll get hurt.
I said,
What are you doing?
They said,
You'll get hurt.
I said,
We're not together today.
They said,
What?
They laughed with their mouths open.
You understand, don't you?
What?
Why is that funny?
What's funny?
They laughed.
They laughed with their mouths open.
They were really angry.
They were in the pool.
They were swimming in the pool.
I thought,
That's easy.
There was a child inside.
He said,
That's from Tokyo.
It's true.
It's a bald man.
It's the same kind of thing.
It's okay to be bald.
It's a bald man.
It's like rice balls and rice.
It's okay to be bald.
It's a bald man.
Can you move your body for an hour?
For about 50,000 yen.
I want to go to the stairs of Duty Free.
I want to go to the second floor.
It's okay to be bald.
I want to go to the third floor.
I want to go to the seventh floor.
I really want to do it.
This is a real film.
Pretend to be catching his child.
He will catch it.
Obviously, you don't understand.
I don't know.
But if you go to the doctor, you'll know what kind of answer he'll give you, right?
No, I didn't take it.
You didn't?
I know that I took it myself, so I can't say it.
But he completely focused on me.
And when I opened my eyes, he was like...
I can't see! He was running so fast!
I want to do it.
I can't do it!
Shut up!
I'm so angry!
I know, right?
When we went to the doctor, he said a lot of things, right?
You'll know when you go to the doctor, right?
I know.
When we went to the doctor, he was obviously filming from here.
The camera!
He was like...
And when I noticed...
I was like, excuse me.
Can I talk to you?
I didn't take it!
What are you talking about?
Okay, go away!
Go away!
Your words are amazing too!
I didn't take it, so go away!
So you told him to go away?
Yeah.
I told him to go away, and after about 3 minutes, he got angry again.
He was angry, right?
Yeah.
He was like, I didn't take it!
I'm so angry!
I told him to go away, but he didn't want to show it.
He was really angry, so he was like this.
There was a table, so I couldn't give it to him.
But he was so angry!
And he was like this.
I was like...
I told him to go away!
He was like this, and then he came to the counter, and I was like this.
He was trying to stop me.
What are you talking about?
He was really angry.
He came in a polite way.
He didn't want people to notice.
He didn't want to take pictures, but he wanted to shake hands.
He didn't want people to take pictures, but he wanted to shake hands.
He didn't want people to notice.
Right?
I was really angry.
The kid was like...
What was that?
What?
He was just flying.
Why did he suddenly...
He was like this.
What has changed since then?
It's funny.
What's different now than a minute ago?
Suddenly, he was like this.
I was like this and that, and suddenly he was happy.
He was like this.
Why?
When he arrives, he jumps.
Then he jumps.
He puts it in his hands.
Why is that?
I can't help but laugh.
The plane was precious.
That plane was precious.
I quite like him.
Did he appeared on the shown TV show?
No, I didn't watch it.
Are you telling me you didn't do it?
What do you mean you didn't do it?
I did it when I arrived, but I think it was a mistake.
I think my parents didn't do it.
Oh, really?
My lower jaw was in bad shape, so I had to hold it all the time.
Oh, your chin?
My chin?
Something came off.
My jaw was in bad shape?
What do you mean?
No, no, no.
It's not like that.
When I came out of the plane, someone came and told me to talk to you.
My jaw was in bad shape, so I had to hold it.
Your jaw?
No, I don't want to talk about my jaw.
My jaw was in bad shape, and I tried to bite the back of the person in front of the plane.
I thought you didn't like it.
My jaw was in bad shape, so I said, I'm sorry.
I said, I'm sorry, but I didn't do it on purpose.
You said, wait.
I was told, I'll talk to you when I get there.
I said, it's okay. I didn't do anything wrong.
I walked a little, and there was a bus stop, so I thought it would be faster to take this.
I got on the bus, and I got to the exit.
I saw the back of the bus, and I was waiting for me there.
It's weird to go back.
I'm sorry.
I said, no, no.
What's wrong with you?
I'm a show-off comedian.
I don't know.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to kill you.
Mr. Matsumoto, who is a stylist for Sachiko Kobayashi.
Yes.
Please tell us about this year's Kouhaku's costume.
It's a long story.
Well, that's right.
It's already decided?
It's already decided.
What was the Kouhaku last year?
You're the Kouhaku.
What I'm saying is wrong, and what the stylist is saying is weird.
How was it, everyone?
How was it?
What was the Kouhaku last year?
Has anyone seen it?
Huh?
It's Princess Kaguya.
Princess Kaguya.
Well, if I say this, you might say, don't say it.
Maybe I'll cut it.
What?
Last year's costume is red this year.
What do you mean?
Huh?
Last year's costume?
Last year's costume is red this year.
You mean the color is different?
But this time it's L.
The size is different.
The size is different, but the color is different.
If the size is different and the color is different, it's completely different.
That's not true.
I'm looking at it.
It's Princess Kaguya.
No, no, no.
Last year's costume was like this.
It's a little rough.
Hey, have fun.
Last year's costume was like this.
I can't tell the difference.
Oh, is that so?
It's strange.
If I say this year's costume is like this, you might say,
Ah...
Skeleton.
What's skeleton?
I wear a skeleton.
You wear a skeleton?
It's all transparent.
Finally.
I wonder if NHK will forgive me.
There's no way they'll forgive you.
Why?
Because they'll take off your veil.
You're wrong.
They'll take off your veil.
Is that so?
Yes.
Matsumoto-san also experienced it.
The children in Hamada-san's house do it in a very unpleasant way.
They ask the people around them to do it.
What kind of way is it?
This is really unpleasant.
What is it?
How is your education?
After all, it's money.
What are you talking about?
Be the demon of money.
What is that?
That's unpleasant.
What's unpleasant?
What kind of way is it?
They'll jump out of the car.
It's a hit.
It's not a joke.
If I say, are you okay?
They'll say, good morning.
It's funny.
If you don't do it, it can't be helped.
That's right.
If you say, good morning,
they'll take off your veil in front of the car.
Do you really have to say that?
They'll take off your veil in front of the car.
Mr. Matsumoto, you've made a lot of talk shows.
I've noticed that all your shows are fake.
Fake?
If it's fake this year,
Morning Musume's Love Machine
or Hiromi's Goldfinger...
I don't know.
Isn't it a hit?
It's a hit.
For now, Mr. Matsumoto,
please make new shows.
There's a song called Pakurireki by Mr. Matsumoto.
Ian Bakan is playing the role of Mr. Haisai.
It's Bartle.
I've prepared a song for you.
Ian Bakan, that's no good.
Next, Taxi Driver.
This is totally original.
This is Tokyo Bus Girl.
Inaho ga Yureru
The inaho is swaying.
He is a taxi driver.
Pasta.
Alright.
Baku.
I'm the bus of the bus.
You can't say, ''Let's go!''
Buses usually say, ''Let's go!''
It's strange to say, ''Let's go!'' and then say, ''Let's go!''
There's no such thing. They're all the same.
What is it?
Machan baby.
This is completely original.
Kawaii baby.
Machan baby.
Hi, hi.
Machan is really cute.
Machan is cute.
Why?
Kawaii baby.
Hi, hi.
There's a slight difference.
What?
''Pakuri'' is a bit different.
If you fight in court, you'll definitely win.
No way.
I don't think you can win.
I think you'll win.
Either way, make a device this year.
I will.
So there's no Machan baby.
Why not?
I can't come up with anything.
If the reason is that clear...
I got it.
That's the most important part.
That's right.
So today, just give us a hint.
What kind of hint?
Before, when we did the Sharankyu, you made the foundation.
I made it.
If you do that...
If there's a musician watching on TV...
If that's the case, we'll do it.
Just give us a hint.
Really?
What would be good?
I want to start with WOW!
Wait a minute.
Maachan, Hayama-chan, this is fun!
I haven't said anything yet.
It's okay.
Maachan, Hayama-chan, Maachan...
Maachan, Maachan, this is fun!
Hama-chan, that's enough.
Why?
Put it in.
Ballad.
Ballad?
Let's start with ballad.
Wait a minute.
What do you mean?
Let's change it somewhere.
Let's do it like that.
Let's change it from ballad.
Is that okay?
It's okay.
It's okay to say that.
Should we do a counting song?
It'll be like this.
But isn't counting good?
One...
Two...
What are you saying?
That's not good.
If you do all the songs...
I will do them.
I wonder if I can do them.
What are you talking about at the start of the year?
I want you to decide on a title.
What is that?
Mamma Mia.
Mamma Mia?
Yeah.
I got it.
Mamma Mia.
The title is Mamma Mia.
Wait! Give me some time to think!
I'm from Osaka!
It's fine, but...
You just said the title.
The title?
Then I'll go with Mamma Mia.
Mamma Mia of tears.
Don't make me laugh!
Tears?
Then...
Osu!
Osu! Mamma Mia!
Really?
I don't know.
I got it.
Osu! Mamma Mia!
I'll release it soon.
Really?
If there's a musician watching this,
I'll ask them to make it.
Osu! Mamma Mia!
The title of the song is Osikko de manhenne.
No!
De manhenne is no good!