Kotonohottan was in the middle of recording last week's talk
There's that thing you open at the bottom of the kitchen, right?
There's that thing you put a bowl or something on there
The one I used before
The one you stick with double-sided tape, you can use four of those
But it's like this!
It's definitely red!
This is life! If it's like this...
No, I understand that
Congratulations! You're going to open it, right?
You're going to open it, right?
Matsumoto, who can't control his anger, began to draw more details at the next meeting
I wonder if it's like this...
I think I did four of them
And then...
It's like this
What is this angle?
Bang!
What are you looking for?
What's wrong? You're looking for this, right?
You're looking for this, right?
He decides to look for a solution to the problem
But his partner, Hamada, doesn't care at all
How are you going to look for it?
Like this
You're going to do it, right?
Will the Otamakake family, who have such a mediocre look, really exist in this world?
Matsumoto, with his sharp sense of observation and unrivaled insight, challenges the root of evil that lurks in modern society
Matsumoto, cutting off society, Otamakake's solution
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
All of a sudden, Downtown goes to look for Otamakake's solution
Matsumoto-san, isn't it around here?
There's a hook like this
It's different
It's like this
It's below
Around here
This is Otamakake's solution
This is terrible
This hook is...
The color is different, but the angle is close to mine
It's close, isn't it?
It's not like this
Look at this
If it's like this
This is good too
There's no problem
It's straight
Let's try this
What are you doing?
He decides to experiment with Otamakake's solution
The shape of the hook is different, but the angle is close to mine
What is this?
It's a useless angle
Let's try
Are you ready?
We're going to do a commercial here
Let's do it
He dropped 3
He dropped 2
But it can't be helped
When you're cooking
The enemy wants to do it well
You have to do it like this
This is not the right way
No
It can't be helped
It's good
You were saying this
Why am I saying this so strongly?
This is a matter of life and death
What are you looking at?
I got it
Let's buy this
No
This is the real deal
This is a disaster
Let's go
Where are you going?
I'll show you how scary this hook is
Why is this hook related to human life?
The car goes to a certain place
Mr. Machan
We've come this far
Isn't this enough?
Let's do it again
Please watch the shocking video from the back side
I'm not going to do any shocking
I'm just going to fall
Let's do it again
I'm going to fall
Why is this so small?
Let's zoom in on this shocking video
This is what happens when you zoom in
Camera man, shake it
This is what happens
There are two idiots
We've specially brought Jimmy
Why is Jimmy being caught?
We want you to experience it with your body
This is the last part of the problem
This is the part where we explain the problem in detail
This is what human life is like
This is impossible
We want you to see this
We've brought two people who don't have numbers
Hey, Mr. Tsuga
I'm a talent
If you use a talent with numbers, it will go in a different direction
This is not a punishment game
I see
This is an experiment
Let's open it
You can jump
What?
Why do you look so happy?
40 and 33
Let's do it again
Press this button
Let's go
Switch on
You fell
You fell from the screen
Hurry up
I saw the camera
Hey
You're a talent
Are you ready?
You have to raise your head like this
Look at this
This is what happens
I wanted to say this for two weeks
Say it in the talk
Everyone missed it
The staff are being carried
They are being carried
You did it
After this, there was an unexpected development for Matsumoto
Matsumoto
I found one thing
What is it?
This is a new truth
I wanted to surprise you
This is the same hook that I bought at the store
Yes
Look
The hook of this angle
As you said
I put it behind the door
The hook you are talking about
I put it here
What?
You can't put it behind the door
You have to put it here
He is saying something good
You have to put the hook here
I put it here
It's like an old NINJA bath
Wait
The maker told Matsumoto
The hook is wrong
So I have to put it here
Why?
If you have any questions, please ask
We will solve it
What is it?
There is a parking lot at KO Plaza Hotel
I can't park my car there
I see
I don't know how far I can park my car
I thought it was already parked
When I parked my car, I went to the wall
Let's go to see KO Plaza
There are a lot of people
There are a lot of people, why is it so noisy?
It's scary
It's not a very interesting day
We are so stupid
We can't do it today
What are you saying?
It's that...
Gakimizu
It's selling
It seems to be selling
It's just like my strategy
There is a sense of fear in people
It's selling, so I can't keep doing it
It's not good?
It's not good, but it's not funny
It's like a cold coat
No, that's...
I have one or two
I failed
You have it
I have it
What is this?
It's like a cold coat
I have it
Does it have anything to do with me?
You are really...
You are really, really, really, really
You are really stupid
I can't say it
You like it that much?
What?
Money
Why?
You really like it
You are stupid
If there is a 500 yen coin in a high place, you will climb it
It's hard to find it
If there is a 500 yen coin in a high place
If you are in a high place, you will climb it
I don't like high places
If you have money, you will do something
You will definitely do it
I said it in the opening
KO Plaza
Why did you go there?
A meeting
What is that?
What is a meeting?
It's like a meeting
Why did you have to go to a meeting?
What is that?
A reunion in middle school
What about me?
Why did you call me?
No, no, no, Hamada
Yuwasu?
I didn't come, I didn't get a call
Yukkira
It's been a long time since we had a reunion
I can't go
Even if it's a reunion
It's been a long time
Let's meet once in a while
Why are you laughing?
Why are you talking about that reunion?
It's been a long time
It's my story
I can see it
If you go there
The parking lot there is definitely strange
It's wide
When cars bump into each other
There's a parking lot
That's right
It's like this
Everyone is there
The wall is open
On the wall
It's like this
Wait, wait
Are you looking at Keio Plaza?
Say Jonathan
I want him the most
So
Do you think you can go like this?
You're bumping into the wall
There's no parking lot
So this is
My car's rear is hurt
It can't be helped
It's a driving mistake
Eh?
Macchan's driving mistake
You're making me angry
But it's a driving mistake
This is strange
You have to check it
Normally it's narrow and dark
It's narrow and dark
You can open the door and go back like this
Eh?
You can open the door and look down
Isn't it scary?
So you go like this
There's a wall, right?
You go like this
This is
It's really strange
That's Keio Plaza's fault
I'm amazing
That was interesting
Thank you, Ketsu
This is Ketsu's fault
Matsumoto-san is 84cm, 58cm, 85cm
It's a nice proportion
What's the secret of your beauty?
Do you know what my office is?
I'm a yellow cab
It's a huge army
I am
Yellow cab?
Yellow cab
I'm a yellow cab
But you don't look at swimsuits
That's because I'm 32
I'm getting old
I used to be amazing
I was popular around here
I was popular with everyone around here
It's interesting
I wonder if you know
What's that?
I'm getting old
Did you put silicone?
No, I'm getting old
I'm getting old
I was Bokkon
Bokkon Musume
It was a catch copy
I'm not good at it
You're not good at it
There's nothing
No
Let me tell you
I was Bokkon
From that time, my tongue was Bokkon
It was dented
I don't know if it's in
But it was dented
That's gross
So my Bokkon is like this
I understand
Bokkon Musume from the land of the stars
Why are you adding it?
You should've said it from the start
That's fine
I don't want to talk about this
84, 58, 85
I think this is my proportion
Why do you think it's 84?
This is my point
From the time of Kokutai
Kokutai?
I bought it
Yes
Why did you buy it?
80, 58, 85
My opponent is 83, 50
What number is that?
What is your opponent doing?
This is the final point
I understand
What did you do?
So I bought it
I decided to buy it
What?
So
No
Give me the paper
Why?
I decided to buy it so it's 85
You decided to buy it so what did you do?
So I bought it
You bought it
I bought it in a three set match
Three set match?
I bought it
So what kind of match is this?
What kind of match is this?
What did you do to get 85?
That's not a problem right now
I bought it
It has nothing to do with me getting it
I played a cross game
You played an ACI
That's right
So what did you do?
In the end, it came up to here
I managed to get it
You did it on purpose
I was in the middle and he was in the middle
So it was a competition
That's why I bought it
Why did you get it?
That's a strange story
You can't get 85
You don't know anything about sports
If you get it, it's a minus point
I'm telling you to tell me
What is it?
Are you running?
I'm not running
If I run, I lose
If I run, I'm out
Out?
I'm out
Where do you do it?
What do you mean?
Where is the bus?
Pool
Pool side
You're telling me a big story
Do you do it on the edge like this?
You can't run
It's on the pool side
You'll get in trouble
You can't run
You can't take it off
So you don't know
Is that okay?
In the end, I...
That's enough
Give it to me
In the end, I won with 84, 58, 85
I knew that
It was a tie
Why are you praising me for that?
It's not like that
My memories from when I was 29
Why are you trying to make it sepia-colored?
I don't know
I didn't mean it like that
I just wanted to congratulate you
So tell me how you won
You should have told me earlier
No, no
You should have told me
You should have told me earlier
What did you say?
I wanted you to say that
You changed your mind
When you were in your early 20s
You were an AD for a TV station in Osaka
Yes
Even now, there's a legendary trick
Please show us that trick
What kind of trick was it?
It was ad-lib-land
Everyday?
Yes, everyday
You only did it everyday
It was everyday
What?
I was told to do it everyday
You should have told my AD
I can't do it now
I don't know why
You do know
I don't have the courage to do it
With that?
Yes
Do you want to try it?
A normal AD
I can't do it
4, 3, 2, 9
I don't know where to start
You should have said 9
4, 3, 2
No, no
It's hard to understand
It's annoying
Why?
I can't do it
You look angry
No, no
I was like this
I can't move right away
Your hands are like this
Like this
I can move right away
I can't move
Why?
My legs
I can't move
You should have said
What?
You're slow
Why do you have to do it everyday?
You can do it from here
I can't move
I can't do it
Why?
Like this
When did you do that?
When I was watching the show
Applause
I don't know how to do it
It's hard to understand
You do it like this
It's weird
You don't know how to do it
No, no
You do it like this
I can't do it
Why?
That's why
I do it like this
I do it on my own
You should have said 3
It's an illusion
I forgot
I should have forgotten
Like this
Can I do it?
My legs can't move
You should have said 3
I don't know how to do it
My legs can't move
Like this
5 seconds
Go
I'm coming
I can't do it