After this, we're going to downtown Gaki no Tsukaya.
Don't do such a bad thing.
We're going to Gaki no Tsukaya for the second time.
It's going to be a hot and hot competition.
The temperature in this room right now is about 30 degrees Celsius.
In front of us, we have oden.
And this is a pot.
I'm sitting right now, but please put the futon on your knees and open it.
The kotatsu is also in the switch today.
And the person who's going to ask me a question today is...
An announcer.
Thank you very much.
I've been working hard until now.
I've been working hard on the news.
It's a variety show all of a sudden.
But the female announcer is eating a lot.
I see.
You're wearing a mask, aren't you?
Do you like women?
It's not good to say it's hot.
Everyone, let's eat oden.
Oden?
It's not good to eat oden.
It warms the body.
It's hot.
It's not good to be hot.
Now, Noriyaki, please ask a question.
The total population of the country is GNT.
What is the total population of the country?
Pure GNT.
That's right.
Noriyaki.
Go ahead.
Number one of B.
Hot.
What is this?
Are you ready?
I'm scared.
What are you doing?
Are you ready?
It's hot.
It's not that simple.
Are you ready?
It's hot.
It's not good.
Question for Matsumoto.
How many people watch TV?
500,000 people.
The correct answer is 1 million people.
You're kidding me!
It's not a joke!
That's the hottest one!
C3
Tatsura
It's quite hot
It's the opposite. It's Mayan
Yes
Yamamaki-san, please give us the question
Here's the question
Who is the first Zabuton Hakobi?
It's Matsuzaki Makoto
The correct answer is
Dokumamushi Sandayu
The correct answer is B-2
B-2
It's you
Idiot!
Matsuzaki-san, your hands are hot!
It's hot!
I'm always hot
Like Tetsuya
I can't move my weight
Here's the question for Hamada-san
Who is the shortest Zabuton Hakobi?
Well
Let's answer
Hey!
Makoto!
What?
Why are you laughing?
I'll call you again
Noriyasu-kun, please
It's a political question again
You know the weak points
This time it's America
What are the two major states in America?
Socialist
Socialist?
It's the Republican Party
I knew it
D-3
What?
What is the animal that looks like an elephant in the sea?
Let's go
Hey!
Please
The answer is
A seiyuchi
What is the number?
C-1
A stuffed animal
Hey, give me a break!
No way!
I don't like to hold it
I'm Tetsuya
Put it on
What?
Here's the question
Where is the famous Aso-san in Aldera?
Kagoshima
What?
The answer is
Kumamoto
D-2
What?
This is not a joke!
Shut up!
What is this?
I want to cry
I can't move
I'm so happy today
Today, there are many people wearing glasses
Isn't it?
I'm curious
This is like a game
Rui calls Rui
Rui calls Tomo
Well, it's fine
I know you're lying
I'm telling you
It happened in the song of Yosuke Tarawa
This is Rui
It's totally different
If you wear glasses
people wearing glasses will appear
Even if you say it's one of the 7 mysteries of the world
It's really good.
Well, there is such a belief.
So, in the family, everyone wears glasses.
There is such a thing, isn't it?
Before, when I was on the Shinkansen,
I had a family of five and everyone wore glasses.
I'm doing this until everyone arrives.
Don't take me away like that.
If it shakes a little, everyone does this.
So, when it shakes, I'll do it, I'll do it.
Then, my grandmother said,
Oh, it's Mt. Fuji.
Then, everyone does this.
Don't do this again.
This is really a strange thing.
Everyone gathers like that.
Are there only fat people?
Fat people are only fat people.
It's hot.
What are you going to eat this time?
That's all he has.
I'm thirsty.
Me too, me too.
Everyone gathers like that.
One of the fat people,
I don't know what it is,
A guy like a leader comes out.
The fat of the leader is hungry.
If you say that, everyone is hungry.
Everyone is hungry.
Everyone follows that pig.
Everyone, the pig moves.
This is really,
It's the law of fate.
Some people are convinced.
This program,
What I say,
First of all, from the head,
What do you say?
No, no, no.
First of all, from the head,
That's right.
It's stupid to deny it.
These days,
First of all, what I say,
It's been denied.
That's right.
I've been found out.
My plume has been peeled off.
That's right.
I'm not a plume.
No, no, no.
What you're saying is telling.
That's right.
Well, certainly, Kimura,
Including you,
I think all humans have a lower IQ than me.
I think so.
If your IQ is low, you can see.
Why are you being told that by someone who can't speak?
So,
You can see, you can see, you can see.
Don't say nonsense.
Isn't it strange at that point?
No, no, it's not.
When I hear it, I laugh when it's funny.
Of course.
It's okay if it's just that.
So there's something like that in there, right?
What are you doing now?
That's different.
No, it's not.
Why are you changing your pose?
You did this once. Why are you doing this again?
That's a brother.
Stop it.
That's different.
I'm a different person.
A guest.
Really.
Let's do our best today.
That's right.
What were you talking about?
What?
Yes, yes, yes.
That's what animals do.
There's a little fish.
In the sea.
There's only half of them, but there's a leader.
That's the one who's fighting.
That's right.
When the leader changes his direction,
Everyone follows him.
That's strange.
I don't know what you decided to be a leader.
I don't know who did what.
I see.
What did you say at the beginning?
Glasses?
A group of glasses or a group of fat people.
What do you mean?
You're a leader.
The one who's fatter is a leader.
That's completely different.
The one who's wearing thick glasses is a leader.
Glasses group.
It's absolutely different.
What do you mean?
Fat and glasses.
I don't know.
Why?
I don't know either.
Then it's different.
What?
Are you crazy?
I'm tired today.
I'm more tired than that.
I'm definitely more tired.
I'm just talking like that.
You're just talking.
I'm not talking.
You're talking.
You know what you're talking about.
I know.
What are you doing?
You're crazy.
It's our show.
What are you doing in front of us?
I don't like it.
Is that so?
That's right.
It's okay.
I didn't check the audio.
I don't know what kind of story it was yesterday.
I don't know.
My mystery is getting solved.
Yes.
I was surfing.
In the rough waves.
I carried a baby.
I went to the hospital.
It's a big lie.
I'm talking about that.
I wanted to say.
I talked about a lot of things.
I did a mushroom cut.
Is that so?
Yes.
Can you extend it a little?
Once again.
Like a long time ago.
It was around here.
It's like this.
It was from here.
It was like a big bond.
I was popular.
It was like this.
I've never seen it.
I've been with you for about 20 years.
When you came with me, you always had that kind of hair.
It was an ordinary head.
It was never round.
Is that a lie?
I've never told a lie.
Don't be ridiculous.
What's this hand?
You put it out.
I took it.
No, no.
It's okay.
It's true.
What are we talking about today?
What?
I'll tell you.
It's a big era.
You can't wear a yellow T-shirt.
I went to a meeting the other day.
I went to a meeting.
I'm going to wear a yellow T-shirt.
I'm going to wear it.
But the design has changed.
I don't want to hear that.
But it's a big era.
It's a big era.
What's that?
What's the position?
I'm the main.
Everyone's shaking hands.
Thank you.
There's a chorus.
Do I have to cry if I wear a yellow T-shirt there?
It's hard.
Nobody's crying.
I don't want to tell that.
Love saves the earth.
You know, even if you say it, even if you say it,
you get charity from everyone,
you take responsibility for the money you get from everyone,
where is it?
Cambodia,
you give it to people like that.
That's right.
You, who are the main organizer,
steal women's underwear,
steal gasoline,
and become an AV actress.
Can you save them?
Can you see the screen?
Don't ask!
Can you give them love?
Well, you know,
that kind of talk is fine, it's a lot of work.
Do you want to decide something?
What?
Something,
something that only the people who are watching this program can understand in 24 hours.
Keyword?
Keyword.
The last one, the biggest loss.
Where is it?
Do you want to go to the Nihon Budokan?
Probably.
Everyone is wearing a yellow T-shirt,
but one of them is wearing a Piongiji T-shirt.
What kind of T-shirt is that?
You wear a Piongiji T-shirt.
I'm wearing a B&B T-shirt.
Piongiji T-shirt,
well, it might be funny.
But you can also,
I can also,
while I'm going out,
do the gala,
24 hours gala,
I can do charity.
You're kidding me!
I mean,
it's just between us,
so even if I can do it,
it's...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're kidding me!
It's between us.
If you can do it,
we can do it together.
Why do you want to do it together?
It's your personal idea.
Don't say that.
It's just between us.
I mean,
this is just a note.
It's not a note.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Don't mind it.
I mean,
I think I've talked too much.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's your opinion.
Yes, yes.
This is just a joke.
What?
It's just a joke.
Today's person is a little...
Question.
Your hair grows wherever you go.
Why do you only grow your side hair halfway?
Please tell me.
Oh, I see.
I've been saying this since I was a young man.
Hair and talent...
Hair and talent are the same.
What?
So,
your side hair is ignored, right?
That's why it doesn't grow.
If you cut it,
what the hell?
It's so dirty.
It's so dirty?
Yes, yes, yes.
So, if you get a haircut,
you don't lose.
It grows.
I don't think you should lose.
But,
women's hair grows.
Women's hair grows.
So, if you stop growing your hair,
it grows without a stopper.
What?
What are you talking about?
It grows without a stopper?
It grows more and more.
It's a locale.
It's a whole thing.
Well, it's a press.
Yes, yes.
It's a press.
Judy Ong is like that.
It's wide, though.
That's right.
I see.
It's wide.
It's wide, though.
It's a chikun.
Yes.
Hmm?
What's wrong?
What's this?
It's a crotch.
But you can read it as a chikun.
I can't.
I'm talking a lot today.
You talk a lot.
Yes, I talk a lot.
It's coming to an end.
There are many things in the world that cannot be understood yet.
One of the many mysteries is this.
Grandfather, grandfather, you have a long nose.
That's right, mother also has a long nose.
What the hell did this lyrics tell us?
Please tell us.
That's what you often say.
Isn't it that everyone is equal?
Listen to the story of tomorrow.
What is it? Your nose is long!
No!
Listen to the story of tomorrow.
In the beginning, before listening to the song,
I have a long nose, so it's disgusting.
Why is my nose so long?
What is it?
At that time, with this song,
You are not the only one.
I also have a long nose.
Isn't that the case?
Isn't it the same?
That's different.
I thought so.
What do you mean?
This is the old Roman law.
That's enough!
That's different.
So the frog's child is a frog.
If your father is bald, you will also be bald.
That's why you look like your father.
That's because you are my son.
You are my son.
I am your mother.
It's a song to strengthen the bond of the family.
It's the same as what you're saying.
Why?
It's completely different.
What you're saying and what I'm saying.
If you have a long nose, I have a long nose.
It's the same as what you're saying.
If you have hair coming out of your ears,
I also have hair coming out of my ears.
It's the same.
Speak!
It's too early to tell you this story.
I'm sorry.