It's cold, isn't it?
Good evening.
What month is it now?
It's the opening, isn't it?
Yes, it's the opening.
It's strange, isn't it?
I heard that the players will be gone.
These guys are really annoying.
Why do you have to gather such a thing?
With a kotatsu and a yutampo.
It's warm, isn't it?
Don't mess with me!
This is...
There's nothing colder than a kotatsu without electricity.
This is the coldest, isn't it?
I prepared a kotatsu just for this.
It's cold, isn't it?
I heard that the strobe is short today, but it's not.
If you walk, it's long.
Look at this.
It's a good kotatsu.
It's cold.
It's funny to see the back, isn't it?
Oh, come on!
Here, here.
Tsunami Kuritsu.
Hamadayama Kaikan.
You guys are dangerous.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
I told you not to do this!
I got hit by a bat.
Hey!
My head hurts.
It's cold.
Let's put on the kotatsu.
I see.
Why are you still here?
Are you a woman?
Look at this.
What is this?
Is it a bath bomb?
It's a bath bomb.
I thought it would be like this.
If you say so, it's cold.
You guys should take a bath.
It's cold here.
Today's...
I don't have a bath bomb.
This is Hamadayama.
Hamadayama Kaikan.
Yes.
Let's start.
This program is brought to you by Sunluck, Soyou Suisan, and Oyama International Products.
Ojiichan!
Yes.
Everyone.
Today, I heard that a dangerous criminal is here.
What?
I don't know how scary he is.
Yes.
Be careful.
Don't look at me.
I got fired today.
Thank you.
Is it your first job?
Yes.
Did you press the time card?
I'm nervous because it's my first job.
I'm a veteran detective.
Yes.
If you have something to steal, steal it from me.
But stealing from a detective is a strange story.
Let's do our best.
Thank you.
But I have to give you a nickname.
What?
I have to give you a nickname.
A nickname?
Yes.
Why do you have a nickname?
It's obvious.
It's the same when I show Soyou Suisan.
Yes.
I have a nickname.
Oh, I see.
If I don't give you a nickname, it won't start.
Like G-Pant.
Yes.
Like Texas.
Soyou.
Yes.
What's your name?
Hamada.
This is Hamada.
Yes.
When you say something, say Hamada.
It's hard to say.
You can say it.
You can say it now, but you can't say it when you're nervous.
You can say Hamada.
What's your nickname?
Masatoshi.
Hamada Masatoshi.
You can't say it.
You can say it clearly.
What do you think?
I'll give you a nickname.
Hamada.
It's okay to say Hamada.
You can say it.
What's your hobby?
My hobby is reading records.
Reading records.
Anything else?
I'm young, but I play bonsai.
Reading records and playing bonsai?
Yes.
Okay, it's decided.
I play records.
Good luck.
Nice to meet you.
Yes.
It's better to say Hamada.
Where is the criminal?
I'm here.
You're here, too?
What a scary guy.
It's hard to do this position, so change the position.
I'm here.
I've been fooled.
I've decided to say Hamada.
You idiot.
Stop playing records.
What are you doing?
Don't call me Hamada because you've decided.
Let me go.
Shut up.
Don't come.
What?
Don't come close.
Shut up.
I'm angry.
Don't come close.
If you come close I'll shoot you.
Shut up.
I'll shoot him.
Hey.
Are you kidding me?
L disadvantageous situation.
Don't move.
If you move.
I'll shoot him with one shot.
I''ll shoot him with two.
Don't move.
It's better to shoot him by one shot.
I don't like your poker face.
I won't shut up.
Is this a conversation between a detective and a criminal?
Stop it.
Stay away from me.
Lend me your sword.
Stay away from me or I'll shoot you.
Okay, I got it.
Look.
As you can see, I have a big butt.
Shut up.
You have a big butt.
I have a big waist.
Stop it.
Lend me your sword.
I'll shoot you if you move.
What?
I'll shoot you if you come forward.
Lend me your sword.
I'll shoot you.
You'll shoot me if I come forward?
Do you think I'm scared of you?
I'll shoot you.
Stay away from me.
I'll shoot you if you move forward.
You have a big butt.
Lend me your sword.
I'll shoot you if you come forward.
I'll shoot you.
Stop it.
I won't shoot you.
I'll shoot you.
Lend me your sword.
Stop it.
I'll shoot you.
Don't do anything you don't like.
What kind of sword?
You're a scary guy.
It's you.
It can't be helped.
It's a good strategy.
Who are you talking to?
Nobody is talking to me.
I have no choice but to go with a good strategy.
I don't care.
You.
What?
Do you know what that is?
That's it.
What is that?
What?
That's it.
I don't know.
What is it?
Do you know Toure Carpet?
What?
You're wrong.
Do you know Russian Roulette?
I don't know at all.
What is Russian Roulette and Toure Carpet?
There is only one bullet in this pistol.
I don't know where it is.
Why don't we shoot each other with each other's rice paper?
The unlucky one will die.
How about this rule?
It's okay.
It looks interesting.
You first.
Why is it from me?
The first shot is less likely.
Please.
What are you afraid of?
It's dangerous the next time.
You.
Don't shoot me.
It's dangerous the next time.
You.
Die.
How many times have you been shot?
Do you want to die with a joke?
Are you serious?
Stop it.
What is it?
This is a real man-to-man game.
What?
What are you doing?
Stand facing each other and walk forward.
Don't step on each other.
Cut it.
Stand facing each other.
Walk forward.
Step forward.
Look back and shoot me.
Calm down.
Stand facing each other.
How many times have you been shot?
It's dangerous the next time.
Who are you talking to?
Who am I?
I'm Ryoki.
Let's go.
Stand facing each other.
Walk forward.
Step forward.
Look back and shoot me.
This is the rule that the slow one will die.
Don't step on each other.
Do you understand?
It's a walk.
That's right.
Yes.
If you make it clear, you're risking your life.
It's about two or three steps.
If you make it clear, it's a walk.
Yes.
It's a walk.
If you compete with the world, it's about three or mostly.
Tell me.
How many steps?
It's a walk.
Tell me it's a walk.
Yes.
Let's go!
Are you ready?
Yes!
Let's go!
One, two...
I said two, didn't I?
You said three!
I was thinking in the middle and didn't understand.
Sorry.
I said three.
Hey.
Am I going to die?
I didn't ask you.
I want to ask you one last thing.
What?
What did I do?
I don't know.
What did I do? I didn't do anything!
What did I do?
But you ran away with my hair, didn't you?
You were just jogging!
You should have worn a jersey.
Why did you come to me?
What did I do?
Don't do that again.
There are women who sleep with you.
Me?
What did I do?
You're a
Tell me!
I'm scared!
That's the end of the story.
Thank you very much.
Today's story is pretty good, isn't it?
It's good, isn't it?
You can do it anywhere.
It's been a big hit for a month.
We usually do it with four people.
We do it with two people.
So when we say, next is a good strategy, we're always here.
We don't say, that's right.
No one says that, so we say it in our hearts.
It was hard.
The other day, I took a taxi here.
I told the taxi driver to go to Tokyo Station.
There's another taxi story.
There are so many stories.
I'm sorry.
You may be watching this on TV, so it's hard to say.
He was a very energetic person.
I told him to go to Tokyo Station.
I'm watching.
It's Mr. Downton.
Really?
It's very high.
It's Mr. Downton.
I'm watching.
Thank you very much.
It's the best, Mr. Downton.
I'm not saying this because there are many customers.
I really like it.
There are many young people now.
But...
Mr. Downton is the best.
Why are you so high?
It's the best.
Mr. Downton is the best.
It's good.
I can praise him as much as I want.
I'm also shy.
It's not like that.
But...
Suddenly...
Why are you so high?
But...
Something is not right.
There is one thing that is not right.
What is it?
I'm sorry to say this.
You don't have to say that.
Please don't be angry.
Mr. Aikata...
Are you serious?
What?
Mr. Aikata is a little different.
Why?
I think you should do it alone.
If you do it alone, the next B and Takeshi will be you.
Is that so?
Mr. Aikata's bad words are...
The person who is taller is...
That's me.
The way you talk to your fans is good.
You are completely wrong.
I'm not wrong about B21.
Mr. Downton is right.
But you are wrong about B21.
You are a strange man.
Mr. Aikata is not here.
He is talking about me.
Let's introduce the postcards.
Is that so?
Yes.
Postcards?
The postcards...
Oh, thank you.
Well...
You were looking for an assistant, right?
Yes.
Until now...
There was a person like that.
Like this.
I was looking for an assistant.
I chose the person from the list for the first time.
You should be more surprised.
You gave me a letter.
That's right.
The letter...
Oh, you put it in a big place.
It's really warm.
I got this.
There is a photo.
Please send me more of these.
I really want to see it.
You wrote a history book for me.
That's right.
What is it?
The motivation of death.
I thought it was interesting.
Are you underestimating me?
Don't call me that.
I'm in trouble.
I thought it was strange.
It's strange, but you like downtown, right?
Which one do you like?
You like it, don't you?
If Hamada and I were drowning, which one would you like?
Which one do you like?
I like all of them.
You're crazy.
Your answer is always like that.
When I say it, you say it.
You always say it.
Where do you say it?
What is it?
The voice.
The voice?
You're underestimating me.
The voice is good.
Is that so?
What is it suddenly?
I've never said that before.
There are things you like and don't like.
That's totally fine.
Go over there.
Hey!
Thank you very much.
Please.
Please give him a round of applause.
You sent me more cute girls than I expected.
I'm surprised.
That's funny.
Yes, yes.
Now, I'm going to introduce the postcards.
I've been doing Osaka-Benkotan for a long time.
But there aren't many.
Well, then.
What do you mean, then?
When you say, then, in Tokyo dialect,
When you say, then, what do you say when you say, then?
Bye-bye?
It's just like that.
Well, then.
Osaka.
Then.
Osaka people say then.
Then, then.
It's cool when you say goodbye.
Osaka people say then when they die.
You say it?
You can't speak.
Have you ever heard it?
The guy before he died.
Then, then.
I said it at my house.
I said it after I died.
Well, then.
I have some more time.
You have some more time.
I'm watching UFO.
You're kidding!
I'm watching UFO program.
I had no time to write.
Me?
I'm watching UFO program.
It's quite serious.
Nittere.
Please come.
It's so sad.
Why is Nittere like this?
I don't think so. It's a serious program, isn't it?
That's right.
What do you mean, that's right?
You're talking about the UFO flying in and taking a shit.
The aliens are like this.
They're sticking their faces out of the disk.
The aliens are sticking their backs out from behind.
Who's going to believe it?
I saw it the other day.
Everyone's going to believe it.
A disk-shaped UFO.
It flew in like this.
A disk-shaped UFO?
At that point, it's already a disk.
There's a lot of things like the way it flies.
The UFO flew in like this.
Suddenly, it flew in diagonally.
There were about three holes, and the hot water was dripping.
It looks like he's going to puke.
What is this?
This is funny.
Don't laugh.
I remember this.
I invented something amazing.
When you lied, you said it was going to be like this.
I think I'm going to get an award.
This is serious.
In Tokyo, well, it's the same everywhere in the country.
There are a lot of problems with parking lots.
Parking next to the road.
It's in the way.
I thought of a way to fix it.
A way to fix parking lots?
That's right.
The road will never be blocked.
Never.
I'll say it.
What is it?
I'm going to make a car like this.
Like this.
I'm going to make a car that looks like a beetle.
Even if you park next to the road, you can't go up.
The car is like this.
Even if you connect five cars, you can't go up like this.
Is it open here?
It's not open.
I thought about it again.
What?
It's a roller coaster.
It's like a play hub.
World's first experience of fear.
It says Miracle Coaster.
It's like looking at an idiot.
Miracle Coaster.
Only one person can ride it.
The driver is also on board.
It's like a roller coaster.
What kind of experience is it?
It's pitch black.
It's a narrow roller coaster.
There's nothing to do on a roller coaster.
It's narrow.
I'm going to run.
When I started running, I felt like an actor.
Hey!
Get out of here!
I don't know if that's funny.
Don't say this on your way home.
I thought you were going to say it, but you grabbed the bell.
Why did you do that?
Let's repeat one thing.
Let's go with a bad one.
Let's go!
We're going home.
Let's go home.
Are you listening?
Let's do it.
Are you practicing?
Let's go!
I can't go home!
That's all for tonight.
Let's go!
This is the first time we've done it together.
How is it?
I'm always next to you.
There's a lot of criminals, so there's about four of us.
I had to do it while I was a criminal.
Next week, I think I'll do a short one.
A short one?
I think so.
Just one shot?
Yeah.
Really?
Two or three minutes.
Yeah.
The story's that short?
Really?
Yeah.
I don't think it's a bad thing that you're going to quit.
That's all for tonight.
Let's do it.
Let's go!
This program was brought to you by Sannaku, Toyosuisan, and Oyama International Products.