We are...
The water bugs of the entertainment world!
This year, the 11th Gaki no Tsukai Kourei Entertainment's Fishing Contest
In the slightly cold autumn of Kawamuchiko, the entertainment world's fishing idiots have gathered this year as well
But the ones who have been able to climb the Black Bucks so far are Okuda, Matsumoto, Tamada, Aikawa and the only 4 of them in the 9.
The ones who have been able to come to this mountain are...
It's sad.
It is.
In the first round of the first round, the fishing competition for the best of the best, the second half of the competition starts.
This program is brought to you by the sponsors.
The rules of the fishing competition are simple. The person who catches the biggest fish in the time will be the winner.
But, it's been an hour since the opening. This year is even more boring than the previous year.
Meanwhile...
Well, the people who are going to give us the tickets have brought them here.
So, shall we get ready right away?
Yes!
Then, please give us the tickets!
Thank you.
They are the people.
It's really cool.
That person is this person.
That's right.
It's Ishihara-kun.
Oh, you're here!
And this time, we'd like to invite everyone from the Itaida group to come to the stage.
What are you guys doing?
It's been a while.
What are you doing?
What's going on, boss?
That's not good.
Recently, you haven't gotten rid of your mischievousness, have you?
You should retire soon.
What are you talking about?
Please take a picture of the o-hagi.
This is pretty good.
It's like a hamburger.
Hey, hey, hey.
I'll take one.
Eat it.
O-hagi.
Sorry.
Oh, Tami-Tami.
Oh, long time no see.
I can't see anything.
Mr. Ishihara and Mr. Ishihara.
This is a dream-like photo.
Excuse me.
The mirror over there is completely invisible.
So, it's the same thing.
Please take a picture of the
I can see it completely.
Mr. Daimon, why are you so angry?
Every time.
Daimon is angry.
I'm gonna get angry.
You should get more angry.
Don't get angry.
Shall we go?
We're going to the next one.
I'm going to the next one.
Can I come in a moment?
Okay.
Please come in.
Nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Yeah, it's been a while.
How have you been?
I've been good.
Oh, I see.
Thank you.
Thank you for waiting, Machan.
Well, I'm sorry.
What?
I think you're a bit of a fanatic about cheating.
I was going to start a fire, but...
Asano-san, you're quite...
Recently, you've been acting like you have a taste.
Asano-san, you're a bit of a fanatic about cheating.
Hey, you...
Let's go.
What are you angry about?
What are you doing?
Why are you so angry?
What is it?
Daimon-san, please smile.
It's scary, isn't it?
Eh?
Well, well.
Mr. Yamamoto, you are Yujiro Ishihara. How long have you been doing this? Is this your first time?
No, this is my first time.
How is it?
I'm always so young, I'm a bit surprised.
Always so young, right?
Please leave it to me.
How is it? Is it fun?
Are you having fun?
Yes, I'm having fun.
Shall I sing?
No.
It's okay.
It's okay?
I have my own taste.
Hey!
It's Kotaro.
What?
Haruhiko!
Are you fishing?
It's a big fish.
What are you doing?
Tachi and...
Kotaro?
That's right.
Why are you fighting?
The captain is complaining.
Hey, watch out!
It's delicious!
The chicken is delicious!
Ichido regains his composure and goes to the second half.
Then, finally this person...
Please take me.
Go further.
How about this?
It's strange!
Itoi's miscommunication.
Today, it seems that he is hated by the fish
At that time, Okuda's boat was lost
Did he get a big one?
Did it fly away?
No, no, it's a Mew
Unfortunately, Blue Gill
Other than Black Bass, the rules over there
Hmm, it's close
On the other hand, even with this boat
Oh! Oh! Oh!
It's dead! It's dead!
Ah! Ah!
What are you doing?
But even so, I'm still envious.
Hey, you were watching!
I want it! I want something like that!
What's wrong?
Oh, the eyeliner was huge!
Somehow, I'm getting embarrassed like this.
Once again, he has to struggle.
Then, he changes his mood and starts this project.
Everyone, I would like to introduce you to the new project.
Downtown Tour!
30 minutes of time limit.
The first person to catch the bus on this downtown tour will receive a prize.
And the amount is...
Last time, nobody said anything.
This year, the carryover is 200,000 yen!
It's 200,000 yen with a special discount.
And the person who will make this down-down ruler is this person!
Eh, is it another woman?
White and black, ecstasy, Hepolarm!
Aikawa-san, black and white, let's go!
This is the cover of the book, Hepolarm.
I think it's hard to understand.
Hepolarm!
You'll be surprised when you see it.
This is the cover of the book, Hepolarm.
Don't take it off.
You can't take it off.
Kamata-san and Matsumoto-san.
Show me.
Which one?
What should I do?
I'll just go with my own way.
I'll go with the blue one.
The blue one is for Matsumoto-san.
Be careful!
What are you doing?
Hey!
What the hell is this?
Hurry up!
Be careful!
Don't open it!
Hurry up!
What the hell is this?
I'm going to tear it up!
Hurry up!
I'm so tired.
Hamada's floor is orange and Matsumoto's floor is blue.
Can you choose this one?
Yes.
After you do this, you have to do this.
What are you doing?
He's swimming! He's swimming!
He's swimming!
The hippo is swimming!
I don't like this guy!
Hippo!
The waves are strong!
Scary!
Let's go back to the starting point.
Sorry for the wait.
Hippo!
Hippo, look!
Where is he?
There!
He is heavy!
You are so cute!
You are heavy!
Rua!
Help me!
Your head is too heavy!
My head is too heavy!
What?
It's heavy!
It's not that heavy, is it?
It's heavy.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Young people all over the country, please study hard.
The first prize is 200,000 yen.
Ready, start!
All the members are throwing their lures at the same time. Everyone is aiming for 200,000 yen.
I haven't caught anything so far.
I feel like I'm going to catch something there.
And Yamasaki's boat, which was rivaled by Hamada, finally comes to the serious mode.
Oh, no!
No, it's a big loss.
Yamasaki and Kato's intentions are intertwined, and the atmosphere is very bad.
Meanwhile, the boys, except Matsumoto, are still...
What's wrong?
What?
This is...
Unfortunately, their voices are weak.
15 minutes have passed since the start of the lure time.
Who will be able to overcome this time?
Basically fishing is in Japan.
The owner.
Yes, yes.
I think he will spend the second round in a state where no one is fishing.
I think that's absolutely no good.
Please think about that.
If you think so, then you guys should have let someone else dive.
You should have let someone else dive because you like the hippo ramen.
And then, today's best friend Itoi.
I don't have luck or luck anymore.
He's completely out of it.
I don't want to see a Itoi like that.
I've never heard such a line before.
And the time limit is 3 minutes left.
What? What's wrong?
What's wrong, Pong-san?
You're still with Kotaro-kun?
You're so stupid.
Which is wrong?
It's Kotaro-kun.
It's definitely Kotaro-kun. You can tell by his face.
If you look at his face, it's Zaki-san.
It's 100% Zaki-san.
I think Kotaro is very irritated.
What is this?
And then...
It's huge.
Did you see it?
It's heavy!
It's heavy?
It's heavy.
What is this?
What?
Pet bottle?
The end!
The lure time prize will be brought back next year.
And the fishing competition is over.
The men who have finished the battle, are surrounded by delicious food and praise each other's skills.
But, the fate of victory is still worrying.
Who will get the award this year?
The result announcement!
Please look at my partner.
Please look at his face. It's crazy.
That's right.
Isn't it enough?
He's like a sour man.
First, Koizumi Koudaro.
He's here.
You won't see him anymore.
The next one is...
This one!
I'm so frustrated.
I want him to be on the show again.
Sato Haruko-kun, if I didn't have this, I might have graduated.
Don! High-Five!
The ship was bad.
What's wrong with that? I want you to work hard with this young power.
Now, Hosei-san, it's the same ship.
Let's go! Hosei-san, here you are!
Don! High-Five!
I think that the power of their anger is amazing.
Senpai, you are so annoying.
Next is Asano.
Don Bonne!
I'm sorry.
You were depressed all the time.
I'm sorry for the words I said.
I'm sorry for you.
When I was eating, I ate a lot of sweets.
What kind of combination is that?
Please come again next year.
Next, Shigesato.
Thank you for your time.
Ahhhh!
He did!
Here goes a fish!
This is a type of catfish called the mackerel welass.
This was a character And we need to let it go!
The screen cried again!
We couldn't
One day we landed
And caught the fish
She's fcéfé to get.
The next is Hamada-san
Here's the beefing champion.
Thank you!
applause
17.5
Well, it seems that you know it.
Yes, I do.
Let's see the third one.
Aikawa Sho-san.
Aikawa-san.
Sho-san looks like a cake.
But, he is so careful when he catches fish.
He is so careful when he catches fish.
Let's see.
Aikawa Sho-san, here it is.
Look, it's big.
That's Bluegill.
That's the biggest one.
It's a pity that the fish is so big.
How many centimeters is the small fish?
It's over 17.5 centimeters.
It's coming.
It's 20 centimeters.
The small fish is 20 centimeters.
It's the top fish now.
It's Matsumoto.
It's a big fish.
Let's go.
It's huge!
Isn't this the bus 3?
The bus 3 is the best!
Isn't this my bus?
Isn't this a small house?
This is huge!
But it's only one person.
26cm
Amazing
It's smaller than the normal one
There are many in the box
Okuda Tamiyo
Here it is
There are 8cm
I wanted your size
How about Kamiyo-san's 26cm?
What are you looking at?
Let's go!
23cm!
The winner is Matsumoto!
The winner is Matsumoto Hitoshi-dono.
You are the 11th champion.
You are a professional fisherman.
You never stop fishing.
He won the championship with his own style.
I will award him with this achievement.
On October 26, 2017, the producer of Nihon Television, KENJI SUGA.
Congratulations!
Thank you!
He's back!
This year's 3-win tournament closed with Matsumoto's 4th win.
Here's a present announcement.
5 special downtown lures used in the program
The winner, Matsumoto Hitoshi's crab-eating house will be given to one person
Please apply for the prize on the day of the prize
The deadline is December 12
Well, today I tried to do a performance called Donzoko
I have to make crabs.
I can't see any hope from now on.
I think it went well as a play.
There are many people who write 2 in the house.
I caught a lot, but I don't think it's reflected in the picture.
I'm happy every day with this tone.
Well, there's a rod, and there's a string attached to it, and there's a hook attached to it.
Well, the fish come up, and if you do that, the fish will come up on their own.
I don't think I'm great at all.
They can't do that, and they're...
Are they stupid?
Idiot!
Are you surprised?
It seems that I don't get along with Haruhiko-kun
Next year, it seems that Haruhiko-kun will graduate
Please let me and the younger ones do it
With the young weapons
Winx, Rage, Yamagami brothers
I want to do it
I'm waiting!
It was only the Yamagami brothers.
I don't know what to say, but I wanted to catch something.
I want to win against Matsumoto.
I'm sorry for that. I was too emotional.
I don't really say it like that.
On New Year's, I want to go to Tokyo with my family.
Please.
I've never thought about getting on other people's ship.
Other people's ships looked really cool.
I'm very frustrated but it was very fun.
I want to go out again and catch one more fish.
Next year, I won't be on the same boat as Shota Aikawa.
I have to be careful.
It's okay, Shota-san. It's okay.
What's wrong?
This is not true.
Look, you're really drunk.
Next year, you will be on the show, right?
Will you let me be on the show?
I will.
Next year, I will be on the show.
Excuse me.
I will do my best.
Then, I will introduce the last one, Haruhiko Kato.
I thought you would jump.
It's impossible.
I will do my best.
Next year, too.
So you're going to give him something again, right?
Yes, yes, yes, something like a murder.
It's a murder, so it's just a murder.
But thank you very much.
Please do your best next time.
And Uesugi's movie.
This stick happily
I always put it in my bag
Actually
l got a friend who was always good at Highcla
I can't say that TOO
except
The guy I met last year
That guy
He told me to cheer him up
Sorry
I was amazed
Right
Yes
Too
Sorry
How come