In the 1st episode of Gaki no Tsukai, Chikichi, the world's name, Anki Gasshoen, Gaijin-san, welcome!
Hello.
This is easy.
Gaijin-san will appear, so you just need to remember their names.
That's it?
That's right.
The person who remembers the least will be punished.
This is really simple and clear.
10 people will appear, right?
Yes, 10 people will appear.
That's how it is.
What about Anki Gasshoen, Yamaaki-san?
I'm really good at Anki Gasshoen.
I used to be an old man.
When I went to college, I was an old man.
I was doing all kinds of Anki Gasshoen.
If you were good at Anki Gasshoen, you wouldn't be an old man, right?
No, but I was an old man.
It's not fun at all even if you're a wife.
Endo Shodo-san.
Nice to meet you.
What's your name?
It's Ganjin-san's name.
Ganjin-san?
The last one.
Naoki Tanigawa.
Nice to meet you.
Wait a minute.
Your tongue is weird.
I can't talk.
It's okay.
Let's do our best.
10 people will appear.
After that, we'll randomly choose.
For example, I remember perfectly.
For example, Yamazaki-san.
Yes.
I think Endo lost this.
Please name it right away.
He probably can't say it.
He can't say it.
But if Endo-san can say it,
Yamazaki-san, who named it, will lose.
This is a minus.
I see.
Hana-san, are you okay?
You're still laughing like this.
It can't be helped.
I have to do more.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
The first one.
Go ahead.
Hello.
The first one.
My name is Mohamed Raju.
Please show us.
Mohamed Raju-san.
It's okay.
I'm okay.
Let's go.
The next one.
Hello.
My name is Edmond Bridgewater.
It sounds like a name with a lot of words.
Edmond Bridgewater-san.
Okay.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Hello.
That's good.
My name is Rainford Reed.
Rainford Reed-san.
That was good.
Is it okay if I ask you questions?
Are you wearing sunglasses?
I took them off.
They have nothing to do with me.
That was a terrible interruption.
Can I ask you something?
How do you pronounce my name?
We can't understand Japanese.
We can't ask questions.
I want you to have a good time.
My name is Mohamed Saad Kisra.
Mohamed Saad Kisra.
My name is Moni Hoshin.
This is good.
Moni Hoshin.
My name is Bernard Edrington.
Edrington.
Bernard Edrington.
My name is Joe.
What's your name?
I don't remember your name.
My name is Hasein.
I'm from Indonesia.
Thank you very much.
Next person, please.
Hello. Hello.
My name is Mishiwaki Twimasebe.
Mishiwaki Twimasebe.
If you remember, the one on top is Nishiwaki.
I remember.
That's good.
This is the last one.
The 10th person is this person.
Hello. Hello.
My name is Ahmed Griev.
What?
Ahmed Griev.
Griev.
It's a difficult name.
It's a difficult person.
It's like a nickname.
Is there a nickname like that?
Ahmed. Ahmed.
All of them seem to be difficult names to remember.
Who is the one who has forgotten the name of a foreigner in Yamazaki Kokoriko?
First of all, this person.
Hello. Hello.
Yamazaki-san.
Yes.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Endo-san.
Takakawa-san.
I'm okay.
Takakawa-san, do you think you remember the other two?
Yamazaki-san has lost his sight.
Yamazaki-san.
He has lost his sight.
Edward Bridget Water.
What is it?
Edward Bridge...
Bridge Water.
Is this correct?
Yes, it's correct.
I think both of you are incorrect.
It's Edward Bridge Water.
Oh, Endo-san.
Edmont Bridge Water.
That's correct.
That's amazing.
This person.
Hello. Hello.
Yes, Yamazaki-san.
I'm Endo Music.
Endo-san, are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Then please call his name.
Edward Water-san.
Hello. Hello.
Yes, yes, yes.
Then, Endo-san.
Tanaka-kun.
I think he has lost his sight.
I see.
Wait a minute.
I'm sure he has lost his sight.
The reason why they raised their hands like that is probably because they don't know each other.
Tanaka-san, please call his name.
Mohammed Saad Kisra-san.
That's correct.
That's amazing.
Endo-san, it's your turn.
Oh, it hurts.
Kiyo Sebak-san.
It's the same as mine.
Mohammed Raz-san.
That's correct.
Let's go.
This person.
Hello. Hello.
Hello.
Yamazaki-san.
Endo-san, please call his name.
Then please call his name.
Let's go.
Cornelius Savanna-san.
I think he has lost his sight.
But like Endo-san, he has the spirit to say something even if he doesn't remember anything.
That's what Kin-chan likes.
Hello. Hello.
Where did you get this from?
No, no, no.
Tanaka-san, it's your turn.
Endo-san, please call his name.
Andreda Giant-san.
No, no, no.
There wasn't a second one, right?
I don't get it at all.
Is it possible to reverse the last one?
Of course, it is.
It is?
Wait a minute.
Why is it of course?
If you don't get the next one right, you get 4 points.
4 minus.
The last one is this person.
Hello. Hello.
What kind of actor is this?
I really know this person. I really know this person.
I think everyone knows this person.
I see, I see.
Endo has no chance of winning if he doesn't say anything.
That's right.
Yes.
Yes, Endo-san.
I wonder if Tanaka-kun knows this person.
Tanaka-kun.
I think he has lost sight of it.
If Tanaka-san doesn't get it right, it's a reverse.
Then, Tanaka-san.
What is the name of this person?
Griez.
He did it.
Really?
No.
Kase-no-san.
What was Kase-no-san?
Then, Kase-no-san.
Kase-no-san.
I remember Serano.
Serano.
The punishment game is Tanaka-san.
Tanaka-san.
As a result of the name test, the punishment game will be decided by these 8 people.
Please take these 8 people home for the night.
A night spent with foreigners. The punishment game will be in the second half of the program.
Ladies and gentlemen.
I'm grateful that you're cheering for me like this.
But I don't know if I can respond to this cheering.
We are.
I'm sorry that I'm not feeling well.
Are you okay?
I have dry skin.
I can't help but scratch my body.
Are you okay?
I've been living here for more than 30 years.
I have a lot of phlegm.
Why do you say that?
If a person has phlegm once,
If a normal person has experienced phlegm 20,000 times,
I think I have a lot of phlegm.
That's because you happen to have phlegm at this time of the year.
No, no.
If you say you have phlegm, I have phlegm too.
I have phlegm.
I always have phlegm.
Wait a minute.
Do you always have phlegm?
I always have phlegm.
Really?
I still have phlegm.
I always have phlegm.
I have a little bit of phlegm.
That's how it is.
I see.
It's Christmas.
Christmas.
Do you buy something for your children?
Is it a gift?
I don't know what to say about children.
It's a child.
It's not a child, it's a child.
If you have a family, there are times like that.
Don't you give anyone a Christmas present?
What is it?
A Christmas present.
I'll give it to you.
Really?
Yes.
To whom?
After all,
To my girlfriend.
Well, I promised her in the future.
I promised her that I would run away with her hand in my hand.
That's enough.
Why are you running away?
What are you going to give her?
Well, I'm wondering what I'm going to give her this year.
Do you have anything good?
No, I've given her the same thing as before.
Well, I gave her a ring.
A gold ring?
Wait a minute.
What?
What is it?
Do you have it?
Yes, I have it.
It's not expensive.
If you give her something expensive, she'll become a star like me.
People often say that a diamond or a wedding ring is worth a few months.
Of course, there may be something like that.
I want to give her a diamond that is as bright as me.
A blue ring?
That's right.
There's a blue ring here.
I want to give her a ring that is as bright as me.
A blue ring?
A ring?
What kind of ring are you talking about?
You didn't know?
What ordinary citizens buy is a ring.
A ring?
From a certain point, she'll become a character.
A character?
She'll become a character.
A character.
A character?
She'll become a character letter.
I want to give her 30 character letters.
That sounds amazing.
Yes, it's amazing.
Is it big?
Yes, it's big.
It's a special order.
She'll eat noodles.
If you think it's a lie, you can go to a jewelry store and ask for 30 character letters.
If you ask for 30 character letters, she'll eat noodles.
She'll eat noodles.
What about this year?
This year, I want to give her a wine opener.
I want to give her a cork.
I want to give her two of those.
For me.
It has nothing to do with you.
You want to give her two?
Yes, a cork.
A cork and a wine opener.
That's it.
What are you?
You can't do it for your wife?
If you have time.
Time?
It's almost like my birthday.
It's not because it's Christmas.
You're thinking it's okay to be shy, right?
That's what I'm thinking.
My question to you, Masumoto-san.
You were working at a place where the bowling pins were coming out.
What exactly were you doing inside?
Also, what happened inside?
I worked part-time really hard.
How many did you do?
I don't really remember working part-time.
I'm sure you can tell from the way we're talking, but we have a different life experience.
It's like the thickness of a man's chest.
It's so thin.
We do a lot of things.
Is this one of those things?
The bowling thing. I did it.
What were you doing in there?
There's a triangle with a hole in it.
You put a pin in there and go gaga gaga gaga gaga.
Do you have that much time?
If you break it, it'll just fall off.
At that time, you drop it like gaga gaga gaga gaga.
This is 200 yen for a time machine.
200 yen for a time machine?
I also did the ball-pulling thing.
You pull out the ball?
There's a place where the ball comes out.
It's spinning, isn't it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's spinning down there.
If you pull out a little more, you can see it.
It's spinning like this.
That's a difficult way to do it.
And when the ball comes, it goes like this.
You can't get your hand out?
You can't get your hand out.
You have to train it first.
And when the ball comes, it goes like this.
When it comes out, the air is here.
It goes in and out.
Look at how it moves.
Like this?
Yeah, yeah.
This time machine is 800 yen.
That's too cheap!
This one is cheaper.
That was a lot of work.
You did a lot of things.
You did the ball-pulling thing.
The ball-pulling thing?
Yeah, the ball-pulling thing.
Oh, the ball-pulling thing?
What?
You mean the stainless steel thing?
That's a lot of work.
You're always talking about the ball-pulling thing.
Recently, many banks and securities companies have gone bankrupt.
From now on, please find a way to keep your money safe.
I don't know what's going to happen even if I leave it in the bank.
Who would do that?
It used to be safe a long time ago.
But the bank says it's going to collapse.
Who would do that?
It's accumulated.
Let's protect our money.
This is a spear.
We have to protect it with a spear.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
It hurts.
You took the gum, didn't you?
I didn't take the gum.
I didn't take it.
You always come.
You always do the ball-pulling thing.
You have to protect your money.
What are you guys doing?
How do you protect your money?
Why can't you guys talk?
Go home.
Die. Go home and die.
I'm being told to go home and die.
What?
Drink two different kinds of cold medicine and die.
What's that?
I don't know.
What?
In a way, you're worse than Yamasaki.
Why are you so angry?
I have a document on this show.
You read it and I'll answer it.
Really?
That's right.
Answer it properly.
You're being told to protect it with a spear.
What's wrong with that?
If you die, you die.
You'll be stuck in a compressor.
A compressor?
What's wrong with you?
You, you, you, you, you.
You're a little smart.
Just a while ago, I turned on the TV.
Oh, really?
I turned it on because the show was about to start.
Why did you turn it off?
What's wrong with you?
Die. Die.
If you have a lot of business cards, you'll have a lot of business cards.
That's not business card.
I'm trying to say something for people here.
That's right.
It's a good thing if you listen to it and accept it.
We have to reflect on it.
I'm sorry to apologize to everyone.
I'm really sorry.
Okay, okay, okay.
Bring me a hammer.
Why?
It's okay.
I don't need it.
You don't need it?
Please.
Okay, I got it.
Yutaro.
Please.
Money.
Stop talking.
If that's the case, I can't sell it.
Please.
You guys are really stupid.
I'm stupid.
I'm sorry.
Okay, okay.
How to protect your own money.
That's right.
That means you can't leave it in the bank.
That's the current situation.
Let's get rid of it. Let's get rid of all the savings.
Let's get rid of all the savings.
And let's put money in your own house.
Let's put money in my own house.
There's a thing called stealing.
There's a thing called money laundering.
It's dangerous.
It's because you go on a trip.
Don't say things you don't need.
How to protect.
How to protect is the best thing.
That's the point of today's talk.
That's the point.
How to protect.
For example, put it on your desk.
Right?
Put it on your desk?
For example, Yutan.
That's not it.
I'm sorry.
That's right.
I'm usually like, put it somewhere.
That's what I'm talking about.
How far are you going?
I want to walk along the road.
What is it?
Do you want to go home?
You're so harsh.
Let's go home.
I'm sorry.
I don't have money.
You're not resisting, are you?
Wait a minute.
You're so easy-going.
You know what?
If he tells you to go home...
I've been holding out my hand all this time.
I want to stay here and do it.
If he tells you to go home, you won't listen to me.
I wonder if I can get in.
What is it?
No shoes.
Hey.
Put it in the room.
This is Japan.
No shoes in the room.
It's hot.
Put it in the room.
Okay.
Oh, okay.
It's delicious.
It's beautiful.
Listen to me.
Delicious.
Delicious?
What will happen to them?
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.