In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai, we will be looking for Gekidotsu Tsukitsuki Kowamote-kun!
Please put a frame on this G.
It's Kowamote, not KowaOmote.
What's KowaOmote?!
Who ordered this?
Today, we will be looking for Gekidotsu Kowamote-kun.
How many times do we have to repeat the first episode?
Do we have to repeat it over and over again?
I don't know.
I don't know why we are still calling him Tsukitsuki.
Last time, we went to buy something weighing 10kg.
This time, we are going to look for Kowamote.
He has a scary face.
You don't want to talk to someone with a scary face, do you?
Well, that's true.
Why are you taking me with you?
I can only say that you have a scary face.
Isn't there a Yakuza office around here?
Isn't that just one shot?
That's not it.
You can walk around there.
If you go to an office like that, you'll be right there.
There are so many professionals.
If I get hit, I'll be Kowamote.
So, in 15 minutes, what was today's event?
What was it?
Well, Todoroki Plaza.
That's not it.
It's Todoroki something pleasure.
So, in 15 minutes, we'll take three Kowamote-san with us.
Sounds good.
Let's go.
This is a Kowamote town.
It's really cute.
Isn't this Kowamote?
It's Kowamote.
Kowamote's face is Kowamote.
Excuse me.
What is this?
Are you Japanese?
Where are you going?
Are you a Yakuza?
I'm going home.
That's right.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the ends of the earth.
What are you talking about?
Kowamote.
Are you Kowamote?
Don't talk to me like that.
I don't like it.
There's no one here.
Excuse me.
Father.
I'm looking for someone with a scary face.
Excuse me.
What is this?
That old man has a scary face.
He's 90 years old.
He's strong.
He has a scary face.
This program is brought to you by Sunluck.
Ooyama International Products.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
I did it.
I'm not good at it.
I was scared.
I have one.
I had a really scary face.
I didn't speak loudly.
That's right.
I was really scared.
So I was in a safe place.
I was a shopping guy before.
I don't think I lost, but I think I bought another one.
You bought another one.
So I'm definitely going to win today.
I see.
This is my first hand.
Yes.
Let's take a look at it.
This person.
What is it?
See, he's scary.
This is scary.
Let's go to the next one.
He's making a lot of comments.
It's scary, but...
It's okay.
This is okay.
It's scary.
Here you go.
Where is it?
You're being bullied.
It's scary in a different way.
I don't know what to do.
There's a fear of what to do.
He's this old, but he's wearing these glasses.
Right.
And his hair.
It's scary in a different way.
There's a fear of what to do.
That's true.
It's scary.
Let's go to the next one.
This person.
See.
It's scary.
But he's cute.
I was going to give up.
When he took off his hat.
See.
You.
Stop it.
See.
He's a old man.
He's wearing a helmet.
I don't know what to do.
I'll go home at night.
I'll go home at night in two or three years.
See.
How old is he?
He's 80 years old.
He has a pimple.
I don't know what to do.
He has a pimple?
He doesn't have a pimple.
He's angry.
He's not angry at all.
He's smiling.
He has a scar.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to go to the golf course with Ishikawa.
Really?
I'm going to go to the golf course.
This is scary.
See.
He's old.
I'm going to the golf course with Ishikawa.
Please wait.
The third one.
The last one.
This is scary.
I'm going to the golf course.
See.
Everyone will be surprised when they see me.
What are you doing?
I'm working.
I'm working on a bicycle.
I have no sense of humor.
You have no sense of humor.
Let me explain.
I'm preparing to work on a bicycle.
Outside.
See.
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, look over here!
This is scary! This is scary!
This is scary!
You're so cowardly!
Hey, you!
This is scary!
Hey, wait!
Stop with that name!
Endo-san.
Endo-san? What's your age?
26.
26? You're 26!
You're the same age!
What are you saying?
You've never been sold to a store, right?
No, I've never been sold to a store.
I didn't know that kind of people would come to the store.
That kind of people are really scary!
Seriously!
What's your name?
Yoshiyoka-san.
Yoshiyoka-san, what's your name?
26.
26?
You're so scary!
This is really scary!
This kind of people are really scary!
I can't stand it if you two come to a comedy club.
I'm going to lose this time.
Right?
Seriously.
You lost to that old man today.
Today, I...
What?
I have to hurry up and get on the Shinkansen.
What do you mean, hurry up?
Today, you shouldn't be talking like usual.
No, no, no, I'm talking really fast.
But time is time.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking really fast.
That's why...
I always talk a lot.
No, this program is...
It's being edited a lot.
It's always being edited.
I've been filming in the dressing room, but I can't hear anything.
That's right.
I'm editing, so today there's no way to edit.
This is going to be like the Kampake.
So I'm not going to put any scissors in.
I'm going to just let it flow.
I don't want to say anything stupid.
I've put scissors in.
I'll put it in.
I can't use this.
You're not going to say anything?
I don't want to say anything stupid.
You're the one who says it yourself, so time...
That's why...
The other day...
And now the time has come again.
I went to Bangkok.
Yeah, yeah.
I went there. What's so funny about that?
I went there.
At that time, I think everyone was watching it on TV.
Oh, really?
We went to Bangkok to look for Sokkuri-san.
Bangkok? Yes, yes, yes.
What's so funny about that?
I was Sokkuri of Matsumoto.
Matsumoto went to look for my Sokkuri-san.
Thai, Bangkok Thai, right?
We went there.
We did a lot of hot filming.
Yes, yes, yes.
What do you call that thing over there?
You know, there's a lot of humidity.
It's like Japan's summer.
It was so hot that I couldn't stand it anymore.
No, seriously.
It was really hot.
We did a lot of filming.
My Sokkuri didn't look like Thai at all.
That's right. It didn't look like Thai at all.
It's European style.
No, it's not.
There's no mistake.
I don't want to laugh.
No, it's not.
You're from the Philippines.
What did you say?
If you went to the Philippines, there would be a lot of them.
Is that so?
Yes.
There wouldn't be any in Thailand.
There were a lot in Thailand.
Oh, it's the beach.
That's too much to say, but mine was really similar.
It was similar, right?
Thai men don't know Japanese at all.
Yes, yes, yes.
But for some reason, Japanese women know a lot of Japanese.
They sing a lot of Japanese songs.
They sing a lot of Japanese songs at karaoke.
There are a lot of contact people.
You idiot.
Seriously.
Oh, it's hot.
Your wife said,
do you want to have a baby?
I don't have any, why?
I've never done this before.
I'm holding back now, I want to have a baby.
I want to have a baby.
We're going to,
soon,
we're going to start promoting Unacore.
Yes, yes, yes.
Don't say things like that.
It's going to be a promotion.
When it's good, it's going to be Unacore.
If you want to promote Unacore,
you have to go to Chinchinkai.
That's no good.
Is that so?
If you go there,
when you're a student,
you should learn English a little more.
If you ask me if I can speak English,
it would be a problem.
I should have studied English a little more.
When I was in junior high school,
I started learning English in the first year of junior high school.
It starts with,
This is a pen.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I quickly lost sight of it.
But look,
there are a lot of musicians coming to Japan now.
Are they called Gaitare?
Who came to Japan the other day?
What?
The other day...
Who was it?
Rolling Stones.
Yes, yes, yes.
What are they doing now?
You should go.
You can't study like that.
I didn't see it.
Have you ever been to such a fashionable concert?
What kind of concert is fashionable?
You!
Wait!
What?
When I was in junior high school,
there was only Mizue Takada who was taken by you.
What is this?
I was there,
but you went to Mick Jagger.
Well, that's...
You've never been there, have you?
If you want to study,
you don't have to be interested in it.
You don't have to force yourself to see it.
I've never seen it.
Mizue Takada was certainly in the front,
so I thought,
Oh, Mizue Takada.
I wish I had that kind of feeling,
but when I saw Mick Jagger in front of me,
I thought,
Oh, what a disgusting guy.
You shouldn't say that.
So,
tell me what you've been to.
First of all,
I've been to Mick Jagger.
You can think of it as Mizue Takada.
Mick Jagger.
Junko Sakurada.
What about you?
Mick Jagger.
I've been to Mick Jagger.
And then,
Madonna.
I've been to Madonna.
I haven't been there.
I really wanted to go there.
So,
I went to Osaka Stadium.
Madonna came to Osaka Stadium.
At that time,
I lived really close to Osaka Stadium.
I wanted to go there,
so when Madonna's concert was about to begin,
I opened the window and listened to it like this.
It's outside, so I can't hear it.
I can't hear it,
but it's faintly...
Fuu.
Are you kidding me?
I can't hear it.
No way.
Fuu.
I can't say Fuu at the Yoppo-no-Mukoro.
That's right.
I can't hear it.
I can't say Fuu until you come to me.
I couldn't hear the Laika version,
but I can hear Fuu for some reason.
I just put air in the gap.
That's weird.
So,
when I hear it, I'm like,
What?
Ah,
search for Morita.
What is that?
I really liked Moritemucho.
Are you looking down on me?
Go to the hell!
I had only been to Osaka's Festival Hall once,
and it was a drift.
You're nasty!
I watched it when I was a kid,
bam, bam, bam, bam, bam...
It was amazing.
Drift is the god of children.
When I was a kid, I was a kid who ran around in sports shoes.
I was a kid who ran around in sports shoes.
You were able to run from the audience seat at that time?
I was able to run.
Hey! The kids at the Festival Hall are delicious!
Here.
Ah, yes, yes, yes.
I have something to tell you.
I'll introduce it to you.
I'm having fun watching it every week.
Show them your face.
When I was doing the tricycle race, I went to the venue and watched it for a long time.
When the two of us were doing the race, we talked a lot with the manager, Mr. Nitta.
At that time, I was talking about the SM fashion.
Do you know how I feel when I'm dressed like this?
What are you going to do with an amateur?
I've been saying it all the time.
I don't like it.
Chikuri is coming.
I don't like it a little bit.
It's okay if you don't like it a little bit.
That's why I feel like SM is okay.
I'm tired of it.
That's why I'm thinking of a new corner.
Nitta?
It's called the coordinate corner.
It's clear.
I've been thinking about it.
Coordinate corner.
Yes.
I'm looking for what kind of clothes you want me to wear on a daily basis.
I'll recruit you.
I'll choose the clothes you want me to wear today.
That's right.
Let's do that.
Thank you very much for today.
I'll write it down.
Why are you twisting your neck?
This is from Saitama Prefecture.
Uchida Yuki-chan.
You two have been on the program from 1961 to 1962.
You were on the program.
Is it true that you were in the clothes of human hair?
It's true.
You were on the program, weren't you?
It's an imaginary program.
Don't you know?
I'm wearing a plush on such a big surface.
My tongue is moving.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Wait a minute.
You laughed at me.
I didn't laugh much.
What?
It would be more interesting if there was a story about your work.
If you did something like this.
If it was a commercial that aired in Tokyo a long time ago,
Mr. Donut.
Hey, Mr. Donut was on the show.
It's the first time.
It's the first time I've been on a commercial.
I don't know anything.
I was walking with such a big donut.
Don't you know?
That's why Mr. George and Mr. Hayashi Katagiri.
You shot it in Harajuku, didn't you?
In Harajuku.
With such a big donut in the back.
Donut, donut.
It's delicious.
I'm eating Yudotan.
I don't know.
Well, I don't know.
But I don't remember seeing it.
Do you know that there was such a commercial?
I know.
It was on the edge of the screen.
It was there.
To be honest, I can't see it in the morning.
Because the time comes out.
It comes out at 8 o'clock.
It was around here.
It was on top of Matsumoto's face.
I don't know.
I see.
And there was a line.
Matsumoto was talking.
We were sitting on the counter.
No matter where you look, the line is the line.
There was.
Oh, it's us.
It's so nostalgic.
I don't know much.
I see.
Well, that's right.
There are other things in Tokyo.
Well, there are various things happening in Yokyosaki.
There are various fun things.
Well, that's right.
Once before.
Where was it?
When we went somewhere.
When we were doing a manzai, a kid.
He was walking around us.
While we were doing a manzai.
He was cutting the front and the side.
The two of them came up and said,
Do something about this guy.
We caught him on the stage.
He took off all his clothes.
He took off his pants.
We were laughing together.
After that, the president there.
Please take a picture with us.
He brought his family.
That kid did that.
Then the kid went to Masumoto.
He said, Don't ever come here again.
Bang!
He said that.
Well, he was the president.
He was the president's son.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
He was like,
You idiot.
He held his head up.
He closed his eyes a little.
Well, in terms of the picture,
It was a warm feeling.
Until then, he took off his pants.
He took off his pants.
I thought of a new impersonation.
Well, if you don't have time,
How many times do you do it?
Tamaki Koji.
It's a new product.
Everyone is doing Tamaki.
Mine is a little different.
What's the difference?
Why?
Why do you say that?
It's a little different.
It's a little different?
What's the difference?
It's not that similar.
You can't say that it's an impersonation.
But I feel something attractive.
Are you crazy?
I'm a little crazy.
Tamaki Koji.
What's that?
Why?
That's my name.
What's a little different?
Why?
Shinichi Mori.
This is an impersonation.
I'm not confident at all.
It's not funny at all.
First of all, it's an impersonation.
Good evening.
Shinichi Mori.
Everyone has done this before.
It's certainly similar.
It's not similar.
Anyone can do it if it's a man.
But this is what everyone has done.
I don't want to do Shinichi Mori anymore.
Shinichi Mori in the morning.
You all know what I mean, right?
Good morning.
What's that?
This is a lie.
It's a lie?
Kusagari Masao.
Really?
Good evening.
Kusagari Masao.
You idiot.
What's that?
Why are you doing that?
This is a male teacher.
Well, let's go home today.
I'll do my Kusagari Masao impersonation.
Let's connect from the part where you say thank you very much.
I'll do that and go home.
I'm sorry, Kusagari Masao.
That's it.
It was pretty good, wasn't it?
I have a lot of requests for everyone today.
First of all, I want to ask you for an idea.
What kind of costume are you going to wear?
Second, I want you to think about the costume of Nitta Atsuo.
Nitta Atsuo costume big plan.
It's a big plan.
If you're good at drawing, you're good at drawing.
Yes.
I want you to draw with these clothes.
Nitta Atsuo, of course, but there are a lot of other staff.
I want you to do it.
What?
I want you to do it with Saito.
That's a good idea.
I always take you to a cold location.
I'm doing it in the car on my side.
I see.
I want you to do it with Saito.
Saito doesn't wear anything.
I'm going to take a car on a one-way street.
I'm going to leave Nitta Atsuo for now.
That's right.
I'm going to make my grandfather wear something like that.
That's also pretty funny.
It's funny.
I want you to do a lot of things.
I want you to do everything the same.
I'm going to leave Nitta Atsuo.
I want you to wear more and more clothes.
I want you to take it off a little more.
I want you to do it with Saito.