In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai, Chiki-chiki!
O-Mise-Taiko Spring Selection Sports Day!
Today, Wato-san...
Yes, yes.
There's a smelly shop here.
Today is the O-Mise-Taiko Sports Day.
Ah, that's right.
This is...
Pan-ya-san team!
The old man has been taking pictures of us for a while now.
There's a lot of money in here.
It's gold.
The popular Pan-ya-san team, San-Eto-R.
They've been working hard on their own business for 68 years.
Their son, Toshiyuki-san, has also grown a lot.
Their first grandchild, Elisa-chan, also wants to join them in today's battle.
What's that?
The Pan-ya-san team.
The Pan-Eto-R team.
And now, the Saka-ya-san team is...
Yamagata-ya-san!
Is that your son?
It's my son.
His parents are here.
Ah, that's right.
Your father is also hiding his wealth.
But if my father was here, he'd be in trouble.
The opponent, Omukai-san, is Yamagata-ya-san from Saka-ya.
His son, Masayuki-san, has passed on his father's legacy.
He will protect the 42-year history of the business.
Last year, he finished renovating the store.
He's also going to have a family meeting with his new partner, Datou-Paya-san.
So, Masayuki-san.
Yes, the first round is...
Tama-Ire-Gas-Sen-Me!
The four teams are...
Everyone, do your best.
Tama-Ire is a noble game.
Do your best.
Let's go for one minute each.
Yes.
The first round, get ready!
Go!
Okay!
I'm lonely.
Then, Nasai!
Tama-Ire-Gas-Sen-Me!
Tama-Ire-Gas-Sen-Me! Do your best!
Yamagata-ya, you're a bit late!
Yamagata-ya, do your best!
Is your father a bit far away?
Okay, okay.
They're all in.
35, 36, 32, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47...
49 to 44!
This game is...
Tama-Ire-Gas-Sen-Me!
The second round, get ready!
This is a second round!
Okay, let's go!
The second round is...
the series mode!
Okay!
The series mode!
Let's introduce the runners.
Who are they?
First, the Veya-san team is...
Yome-san!
Hiroko-san!
Are you attracted to the bakery?
The baker came with me.
Really?
Well, this is quite the opposite.
Yamamata-san's team is Oga-san!
This is a match between a wife and a husband, right?
Yes, it's a match between a wife and a husband.
We're quite far apart though.
It's like the husband is making the wife feel weak.
This is also a three-round match.
Even so, if it doesn't work, we'll do a T-back-janken.
I'll be wearing this today.
Let's go!
I think I learned this somewhere.
Where did you learn it?
Let's go!
What do you think about this?
I feel like this one fell earlier.
Let's watch the previous one again.
Let's replay it.
Please watch.
That means Oga-san wins.
Oga-san wins!
Yamamata-san.
Yes?
At the end, we'll do a kiba-sensei.
Really?
I can't believe you're doing such a fun thing.
No, it's not fun at all.
What are you talking about?
It's a 21st century joke.
It's too bad.
Now, face each other!
Whether you cry or laugh, it's decided.
There's no one who will cry.
Now, let's go!
The final match, get ready!
It's not broken yet!
Are your glasses okay?
Is it broken?
This match is Yamamata-san's victory!
The winner of the first two rounds is Yamamata-san! Congratulations!
The winner of the second round is Yamamata-san! Congratulations!
It's wonderful.
No, no, no, thank you.
It doesn't smell at all.
No, no, no, thank you, thank you.
Your face is red!
No, no, no.
It doesn't smell at all.
You don't look sporty at all.
No, no, I don't know what to say.
No, no, it's not like that.
Well, I went to New York the other day.
You're lying!
You didn't go!
In the end, you went to New York, didn't you?
You said you went.
I've never talked to you about New York.
Oh, I see.
So that's why you fought.
That's right.
Are you going to throw it again?
So how was New York?
Well, I went to New York to look for Nozawa.
Nozawa-kun is getting married.
I went to see him.
Nozawa is in a band called Chimpanzees.
What are you doing?
I told you not to say it!
I told Inoue-chan.
It's called Chimpanzees.
The eyebrows are connected.
You said you wanted to study comedy in New York, didn't you?
Yes.
Then you're a level down.
You're a mere coach.
You're dancing in a park somewhere.
You're dressed like a monkey.
There's a live performance of Chimpanzees.
I finally found Nozawa.
When I arrived at the live performance,
I saw him with pink hair and drinking coffee.
He looked like this.
It was a little strange.
I said,
That's Nozawa's husband.
Nozawa's husband's head is pink.
His head is pink.
It's dirty.
He's wearing shorts.
It's dirty, isn't it?
It's fine.
It's not like that.
I watched the live performance.
Everyone was in the back of the hotel.
We were talking in the back of the night view.
My husband is coming today.
I called him.
It's called Bob.
It's Bob.
It's a tough name.
Bob came in and sat next to Nozawa.
I was surprised.
I looked at Bob.
What?
Bob...
He's really like that.
Everyone knows it, but they can't say it.
He knows it.
He doesn't think about anything.
I said,
Is that so?
I have no choice but to say it.
I don't know Bob.
He's laughing.
When we were talking,
He was flying.
He's a good guy.
In America,
There are many people who are flying.
In that sense,
He was flying.
Bob was flying in many ways.
But he looked good in two shots.
That again?
That looks good again.
I think that was a mistake.
During that time,
Matsumoto went to Hakone's hot spring.
That was sudden.
It was definitely more fun here.
In the sense that you can do it slowly.
Hakone is the best.
I'm a little self-absorbed.
Why?
It's really amazing.
Why are you self-absorbed?
Women are free to live.
Women are blooming.
You do it.
When I went there,
There was a cable TV on the hotel's TV.
Bang!
Man.
This kind of man.
Bang!
He took off his shirt.
His butt is sticking out.
Bang!
As expected, 99 channels.
That's a big one.
What will happen to 100 channels?
That's a memory.
Hakone is amazing.
It was amazing.
What was amazing?
When I went to the station, women were blooming.
Bang!
Who said that?
Women.
Why did you say that?
Bang!
Are you kidding me?
I'm sorry.
I was lying.
Are you a pervert?
Actually, there wasn't a single woman.
That's the worst.
There should be a woman I can call.
There was an old lady who prepared food.
There was no place for young people to play.
There wasn't.
I thought I shouldn't do that.
There was a sculpture museum.
There wasn't.
Of course there was.
I said there wasn't.
Really?
Of course there was.
There wasn't.
I searched.
Why did you lie?
I still don't get it.
But the sculpture museum was quite interesting.
You don't know much about art, do you?
When I was a student, I got full marks in art.
I don't care about that.
Really?
I don't care.
What are you talking about?
That's enough.
I was always walking around.
I was taken to Harlem.
It was scary.
I couldn't see anything on the subway.
I was told to get on.
But suddenly there were black people.
When I was filming,
people said,
Hamada, what are you doing?
Why can't you do that in Europe?
I couldn't do it.
Why?
It was scary.
I went into the middle of the subway.
I was in the sky above.
When I looked at my face,
my face was like this.
I was told to sit down.
We were sitting together.
We were in a completely different place.
In front of me,
there was a child looking at me.
That was scary.
If I was in Japan,
I would have been killed.
How old were you?
I was in junior high school.
I was in the sky above.
I was scared.
The child was staring at me.
I didn't want to see it.
I was scared.
Do kelp, seaweed, and seaweed soup come out of the sea?
No.
Kelp doesn't come out of water.
Why can't it come out of seawater?
Because it's salt water.
Oh.
You are quick to understand.
But it's strange.
Why can't it come out of seawater?
Why?
Because when you make a pot,
you put salt in it, right?
The seawater comes out.
That's about a teaspoon.
It's different.
Is that so?
That's right.
It doesn't come out.
I think it comes out.
That's how you took it.
It comes out.
It comes out, but you can't tell with salt water.
Because it's amazing.
The sea has a bonito flavor.
It's kelp soup.
It's amazing.
It's all erased by seawater.
It's too strong.
That's right.
I see.
That's absolutely right.
What?
If you're convinced,
you're being made fun of.
No, no, no.
That's about it.
I'll read it and make fun of it.
I don't really make fun of it.
That's about it.
When you show a very large area,
you often say,
how many Tokyo domes are there?
It doesn't come to mind.
I see.
Please make a new unit.
Oh, when you show a large area.
How many Tokyo domes?
You say that.
But the size of the Tokyo dome
doesn't come to mind.
I don't know.
Even if you say 100 Tokyo domes,
you can see how large it is,
but you can't imagine
how large it is.
That's right.
For example,
if you say,
how many Mild Seven Lights are there?
It becomes a huge number,
so you don't know how many there are.
So you have to take a little more time.
I see.
Well,
how about Ota-kun?
It's better to do that.
Wait a minute.
Let's ask everyone about this.
Ota-kun?
Ota-kun, 50 people.
It's very easy to understand.
Ota-kun, 50 people,
are laughing in my head.
You have to be Ota-kun.
Why?
Isn't that right?
You have to be Ota-kun.
When you say,
Ota-kun, 50 people,
doesn't it come to mind?
It doesn't come to mind at all.
When you say Ota-kun,
it comes to mind.
It's a side-division.
I don't know.
It doesn't matter.
You can't think of anything
with your name.
You can't think of anything with your name.
Really?
When you say,
Mr. Otagaki,
it's a bit...
It's ugly.
It's a bit ugly.
You don't have imagination.
If you laugh,
you can't imagine
to the point that you can't draw.
I see.
That's no good.
You're very fast.
It's a side-division.
This is a side-division.
Do you understand?
Did you see it?
What kind of teacher is it?
Mr. Sawada.
You have to be Ota-kun.
You have to be able to imagine.
I see.
That's what it is.
I have something I'm curious about.
Please tell me about it.
Is there really a Tokugawa Plastic Surgery?
When did you finally find it in the newspaper?
Find?
That's the question.
It's written,
but you haven't seen it.
Is there any other program
that can attract viewers?
Mr. Raundan,
please tell me the truth of the incident.
This is that.
I was doing it at Gimiya Break.
I've been pulling it all the time
since I was a kid.
This is TBS.
TV-do.
What is TV-do?
It's a personal attack,
but you're attacking a big organization.
Don't you stop it?
If you get hit by everyone, it hurts.
That's right.
Itoi told me this story.
It's okay because it's an individual.
Why does Itoi have a hole in his nose?
Just because he's a normal kid.
It's because he's a professional.
I have something to say.
What is it?
I'm getting angry at the talent.
You're already the next one.
You said it first.
I didn't say anything like that.
I'm the most angry right now.
I'm the most angry on TV these days.
Don't underestimate me.
Inoki.
I'm angry.
I don't even know the name.
How about the spiciness?
It's as spicy as oolong tea.
I'm sorry for the tea, too.
I'm sorry.
My face is really annoying.
I want to hit you.
I don't think so.
It's really annoying.
I want to see your face.
What's wrong with him?
His commercials have a lot of dancing.
It's really annoying.
I'm not that angry.
I usually don't think about anything.
As long as it's a commercial.
His face when he dances is really annoying.
It's like he's being made fun of.
I didn't do it.
I can't do it.
It's personal.
My face is really annoying.
There are people like that.
Of course.
Is that so?
His face when he says something is annoying.
What are you talking about?
I don't know if there's anyone who talks like that.
Is that so?
I don't remember that tea commercial.
You don't remember?
Seriously.
I thought I had to say it when I was a kid.
I can't remember.
Seriously.
The Michael Jackson commercial that was fun to watch on TV was fun.
The Michael Jackson commercial.
That was really fun.
His face is turning white.
The interviewer asked him a really stupid question.
He asked,
Are you doing something with your skin?
It's a stupid talk.
I should have asked that!
You're the one who should be asking.
I was more excited to see it.
Are you doing something with your skin?
He's a little angry.
Then Michael said,
This is a disease.
That's what I heard.
You've done plastic surgery many times.
I haven't done it many times.
I've done it many times because the media wrote it up on their own.
I've done it only twice.
It's definitely a lie!
His face is completely different!
It's completely different.
There's a rumor that you're a virgin.
I asked, What do you think about this?
Why are you talking like that?
I wanted you to hear it.
Why do you want me to hear it?
There's a rumor like that.
I asked, What do you think about this?
It's private, so I don't want to say it.
Don't say it like that.
You're a superstar, Michael!
Please look at my garden.