The history of the club activities of the kids.
The first club.
The high speed spinning spinning club.
The small and small club.
And tonight...
The fourth club activity.
The
I've done many things, but I was only a second seat.
What?
I was only a second seat.
Second seat? What do you mean?
I was doing stupid things to do this Hikizurare Club.
Hikidome Club?
Furufuru Club?
That's right.
Kocho Bashi Club?
I've done a lot of things.
But I really wanted to do this Hikizurare Club.
Is this your real name?
This is my real name.
What do you mean?
It's simple.
There's a car with a bar.
You hold it in your hand and never let go of it.
It's a very simple story.
Let's measure the time.
Think of the bar as a TV show's regular.
I see.
You're right.
Well, Yama-chan, you're doing your best.
He's getting too close.
How many regular ones do you have?
I have two regular ones.
He said, I have two.
So, who are we going to fight today?
Let's get started!
Let's go!
Here's our opponent!
Who is it?
It's me!
This is...
Stop it!
You're too fast!
I'm sorry, but I'm not good at this.
Hurry up!
The last one is the opponent, Watanabe Entertainment!
We are Watanabe! Watanabe! Watanabe Entertainment!
You should have said that earlier!
You're doing well.
Can you do it?
Thank you!
I was able to do a live show
I thought I shouldn't be late
I gathered young people
Why did Michael and Fuuka come?
Wait a minute
I'm the one who should be the one to say it
Michael!
Yes!
Michael
What about Red?
I don't have Red
No, you don't
I'm curious about the red one.
The red one is really good.
You're really good.
I'll tell you this.
I've been clinging to this entertainment industry for 12 years.
So last month, I let go of that hand.
Please.
What?
I'm not going to let go of it.
Don't pay attention to the pen.
What's going on now?
I'm so hot.
My stomach is hot.
Let me explain the rules.
The first person to play will decide the order of the team, and will be dragged off in a 1 to 1.
Each person will have to count the time until their hands are released, and will decide the winner in that total amount of time.
Lastly, there is a team match where five people will be dragged off.
The chance of winning is...
Let's decide the strategy first.
Let's decide on each one.
Our team is...
This guy is amazing.
Who?
Yamane!
Really?
He's the best!
He's really powerful.
How many do you have?
32-30.
That's a lot!
What should we do?
When I do this, I always do it first.
You've decided, right?
After that, you can change it.
I'm already burning with drama.
If you do it here, there will be no connection.
I'm a little angry with Mr. Tachihiro.
The battle of the attention of the
Let's start the first round!
Let's go!
Go, Endo!
Three!
Go!
Ready...
Wait a minute!
Oh no!
He's fast!
Endo missed!
Endo is going to get it!
He's fast!
Endo is fast!
Yamane is fast too!
Hey, are you okay?
Endo!
Hey, it's broken!
It's true!
It's broken!
No!
Yori-san.
I won't say anything bad.
What?
I should have withdrawn.
I withdrew.
I'm ready to ride a bicycle.
That's the spirit.
I withdrew.
It's so fast!
This is the curve.
The curve is so fast.
Yes, it is.
He won!
It was good.
He is so good.
He won.
Everyone is doing the same thing.
That's right.
The feeling is amazing.
It's amazing.
It's really fast.
It's fast.
I feel like I'm going to do it.
Let's do it.
Everyone is doing their best.
Have you decided?
We have decided.
We are going to do it.
Really?
Fukawa.
Please.
I have to cut here.
I have to drink it.
What should we do?
I'm a little scared.
Do you want to go, Hamada?
I'll go.
Let's go.
Good luck, Hamada.
I had a different image.
I'm sorry, but isn't that Hosei?
The first one is Masatoshi Hamada from the Gaki team.
The second one is Ryo Fukawa from the Watanabe team.
I'm a little nervous about the standby.
He's really fat.
I'm scared.
Are you ready?
10 laps.
Ready.
I'm going to speed up a bit.
You just won!
Seriously?
You lost by 1 or 2 seconds.
Hamada-san!
What is this?
What? What?
The curve...
I was thrown out of the corner.
I'm scared.
I'm sorry.
I lost in 1 second.
I was almost at the same time.
I was caught by Hamada-san.
You won't fall if you don't stand up.
You pulled me a little, didn't you?
Who pulled you?
I was pulled back a little.
All kinds of comedians have been pulled back so far.
The final match is the double Tanaka match between Kokoriko Tanaka and An Girls Tanaka.
Now, the double Tanaka.
I won't lose in the inside.
I'm going to show you who's the best at the C-BDog.
That's right.
When we join the same youth club, we will be like this.
Too slow.
I'm counting on you!
Ready.
Go!
This is bad.
No, no, no. It's making a strange sound.
Tanaka, go!
Tanaka!
Don't give up!
Where did Tanaka go?
That was Tanaka again.
That was a bit too early.
What happened, Tanaka?
I got hit by a car over there, so it hurts.
What happened? I'm scared!
You should stop the outside.
The weeds are amazing.
The weeds are amazing outside!
The weeds are coming out!
It's scary!
It's outside!
It's good to be outside!
I tried my best!
What was that?
The moment you talked, the balance changed.
Ah, I was out of balance.
You were out of balance.
You're a poor guy!
You're really excited!
The junior team is the one who will be the leader of the 9 second round.
Will they be able to turn the tables?
They can do it, right?
Well, even if you say it, it's 9 seconds.
Hey, you!
Who are you?
Next is...
Michael!
Yamasaki and Michael!
I don't want to see Michael!
The special match is Yamasaki vs Michael.
During this match, the two's evolution will be questioned.
Who is that?
It's Professor Injiki.
It's also Mr. Ito Shiro.
Are you okay?
I'll do my best.
If you end up losing, I'll have you think about it.
If I win, please change the regular.
You guys are talking about such a big thing.
I thought it was a lego!
I thought it was lego!
I'll go get it!
Go!
Let's go!
Please!
Ready!
Go!
9 seconds left!
There's still a lot left.
But you're doing your best.
Good luck!
Michael, good luck!
He's still silent.
What are you saying?
He's not saying anything.
This is it.
Michael!
This is a bit fast.
Michael's a bit slow.
Here it comes!
Good, good, good.
You lost, but you're still a ball.
I don't even want to go.
I won, I won.
Good, you're out.
Nagasaki, stand up.
Stand up and run over here.
What's wrong with you?
Run, you!
What did you do?
I wish you could show us a little more.
That's right.
Michael won perfectly.
Yes.
You did it.
Good job.
Yes.
Well, look at this.
What?
Here.
The sword is strange.
Well, it's amazing if you have a sword.
That's right.
It's not good.
It's a sword.
You didn't do your best at all!
I did my best! I'm the winner after all!
Well, well, well...
I'm not even close to Hamada-san!
The distance is...
Right?
Before the final match, Watanabe's team is 10 seconds ahead.
The match is left to the grand prize.
That's right! That's right!
10 seconds!
I lost.
No, no, this is the final match.
Ouripts are still the свобод!
You went through, Gol-Gol!
Next is Wataru and you!
Seeing his face must hurt!
It certainly hurts!
We'll be playing the same Matsumoto game!
Hi, Matsumoto Ganryu?
You might get a
The team that won the battle with Watanabe's 10 second lead is the new Matsumoto team.
Will they win?
Look at this.
There's no Shiro, but he's taking this dog with him.
Dog? It's not a dog.
It's a human.
I don't feel like I can win.
Stand by.
Please do your best in the battle.
Go for it, Goro-san.
You're really fat.
Let's go!
Ready...
Go!
The first one!
It's still fine.
It's hot!
Ouch!
The first curve is coming
It's coming
It's accelerating
Matsumoto is also scared
Matsumoto is really scared
It's a long distance race
It's coming
It's dangerous
This is amazing!
This is great!
How was it?
You did it!
I beat him!
You beat him!
Amazing!
You did it!
It's your first win!
You should take this off.
Golgo!
I did it!
I got it, I got it.
Golgo!
Why? Why?
Two rocks were in my mouth.
That's not good.
One of them swallowed it.
Really?
It hit my mouth.
But I can still breathe.
How many seconds?
Ah, but you lost 4 seconds.
I lost!
After this, it's finally a team battle.
The final battle will be decided by...
In the group battle, all 5 teams will be dragged away.
The remaining time will be added to the individual battle's total time.
The winner will be decided.
However, 4 people will be separated from their loved ones.
The remaining person will be dragged away.
First up is the 4 second lead team, Watanabe.
Here, we'll reveal the results of the first round.
Now, in the group battle, the first team is the Nabe team!
Watanabe! Watanabe! Watanabe! Watanabe!
Team up!
Alright!
Cut!
He's using his useless strength.
Who's going to be in the middle?
It's a good balance.
I see.
We have to make it a double.
It's a bit like a mudokan.
Are you ready?
Yes!
Let's go!
Let's do this!
Ready...
Come on!
Push your chest!
You can do it!
Hang in there!
It's beautiful.
It's amazing.
It's vivid.
Taro!
Oh, he's coming!
He's running!
Who is it?
Tanaka!
He's still running!
But there are four of them, and he's still good!
Look out!
Tanaka!
Who is it?
The last Golgo.
You were close.
You did your best.
This is how it feels.
One by one, they fall.
The balance is broken.
I see.
What's wrong?
Are you okay, Tanaka?
I'm okay.
The field is wider now.
There's a lot of grass.
It's weeds.
It's like a body bath.
So, as you can see, the results of the Watanabe team are as follows.
The Gaki team wins if they can get past 1 minute and 1 second.
The man in the middle, you and I will read it together.
Well, I know it well, but I haven't read it for two weeks.
I'll definitely read it for two weeks.
The minimum.
How many times?
The most beautiful thing is that all five of us read it together.
I don't like it.
Like a Dutchman.
Why not?
Please.
What?
What should I say?
How many times?
Like Dutch.
Sorry.
Let's do it.
Let's go.
Let's go!
I knew it would be like this.
It's like a downfall.
It's the final round.
We'll do our best.
I don't understand the meaning.
Will the Gaku team turn the tables?
Finally, they will challenge the last battle
Now, whether you cry or laugh, this is the last battle
Yaki no Sky Team
According to the calculation, if you don't go more than 2 laps, you can't win
That's right, there is a 1 minute difference
It's hard because it's the second time
It's a little hard in this era
It's thick, right?
It's thick
It's scary
It feels like it's being shaken
It's like a finger
Then, please
It's the water from the river.
Let go of me!
Who is this?
He's coming from here.
It's like he's coming from the mountain.
If you let go of someone, it's hard to deal with it.
And then, boom, boom, boom.
Let go! Let go!
Speed up!
100 km per hour!
Wow, that's strong!
What?
The balance is off!
Look!
Watch out! Watch out!
It hurts!
Two people!
They're pushing!
Two more!
Wow, it's so hard!
It's so subtle!
Who's the winner?
Time!
Is Mr. Hanabata the third one?
I did it!
Mr. Matsumoto is the last one.
It's so subtle!
This is a bit strange.
Wow!
It's hard!
This is a bit scary.
I can't do it.
If I quit now, it would be like I'm thinking about something like TV.
I definitely didn't quit, but it was really impossible.
Let's see the results!
Gajiska team 1 minute 2 seconds!
Nabeburo team 4 minutes 29 seconds.
Gajiska team 4 minutes...
30 seconds!
Team victory!
We lost, but oh my god!
Endo, don't lose!
We won!
This is crazy.
If you're crazy, you're a real kid.
It's not foreign ha ha ha ha