Can the Bibi scare people?
Today's guest is the world's best ghost!
It's been a while since we've seen you.
I've been on this show for 10 years now, but I have a bad feeling about this.
What is it?
It's been a while since I've seen you, and you're the worst opening.
It smells like poop.
Was it bad to have a Heipo opening in the past?
I'm sure the viewers have a good feeling about this.
It's been a while since I've seen you, and you're the worst opening.
I didn't participate in the show at all today.
I'll just say this.
Today's guest is the world's best Heipo!
Why are you dressed like this?
I don't have an aura at all.
I think I should cut this and make it into Tsuki-yaki.
Tsuki-yaki?
I think we should all eat Harami.
This one?
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
First of all, let's see how scared Heipo is.
Apparently, Heipo has gone to a scary place.
I was really scared.
I'm sure it's Harami.
I didn't think it was Harami.
The world's best Heipo.
This man, who has made many mistakes as a scary man,
is going to challenge an even scarier legend tonight.
The world's best Heipo, a scary experience report.
Good evening, I'm Saito.
I'm now at the famous Sendagaya Tunnel, a ghost spot in Tokyo.
The best ghost spot in Tokyo, the Sendagaya Tunnel.
It's a ghost tunnel where ghosts are said to have been awakened by moving the grave to open it.
It's a very scary place, so I'd like to experience it right away.
I'm going.
Why is it so creepy here?
There's something like a rake over there.
I can hear a woman's cry.
I'm scared of this picture.
Huh?
The staff who was supposed to be there...
Why?
Take it off.
I was surprised.
What is this?
The next destination is Hachioji, which has many ghost spots.
It's now turned into a ruins without a trace of people.
But this is a little scary.
In the back of the suspicious Zoukibayashi,
there is a headless statue of the dead.
Good evening, I'm Saito.
I'm going.
I'm really going.
I'm scared.
What, what, what?
Come with me.
I'm scared, I'm scared.
It's pitch black.
It's really creepy.
It's cold.
Actually, I was told by the manager.
When you get a cold,
tighten your butt and say,
Hey, hey, hey.
It's good to do it.
What, what, what?
Let's go.
It's really close.
Where do I put my luggage?
I was surprised.
What is it?
No, no, no, no.
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
I'm scared.
Are you crazy?
I heard a sound there.
Let's stop it.
It's the entrance.
It's true.
It's not the entrance.
Look, look, something fell.
Stop it.
I don't like it anymore.
What?
What is that person?
I don't like it.
Let's go home.
I've never done anything like this before.
I'm sorry, please give up.
I'm really scared.
Please.
Let's go home.
Stop it.
Good evening, I'm Saito.
I'm at the haunted house in Fuji-Q Highland.
The haunted house in Fuji-Q Highland.
It's a haunted house with the image of the abandoned hospital.
This is the most terrible haunted house in Fuji-Q.
Let's go.
Do you know where the ghost is?
That's right.
I can smell the ghost from inside the hospital.
It's scary.
It's so hard.
What are you doing?
What?
It's so hard.
It's too hard.
It's already hard enough.
Please, I beg you. I have a heartache.
He's giving up.
He's in the hospital.
He's not giving up yet.
I have a heartache.
That's how scared he is.
I wonder if he can scare people.
I'm confident about that.
I'm good at scaring people.
He knows what he's scared of.
That's right.
M is the most S.
He knows.
That's right.
It's M, right?
Yes, it's very M.
The first ghost is Yatsuhakamura Heipo.
The first ghost is Heipo.
Is Yatsuhakamura scared of the guests?
He's here.
I can't wear glasses.
But he's a little scared.
That's right.
What is it?
Heipo.
Yes.
Vibrate properly.
I'll do it properly.
He looks like Tanaka.
He's here.
He's a professional.
He looks like Tanaka.
He's scared of the girls.
He's here.
He doesn't notice.
He's laughing.
Yatsuhakamura.
What is it?
It's like the title of a movie.
He's here to make a video.
It's no good.
It's not scary.
He doesn't say it himself.
He's scared.
It's a little different.
He's wearing glasses.
He's small.
If he says that, it won't start.
Next is Heipou the mouse man.
He's here.
This is...
Is it okay to look at it from the front like this?
This is good.
When I saw it when I was doing it earlier, the degree of perfection was low.
This is a child.
This is definitely a child.
What kind of timing is this?
There is no scary thing if you remove this timing.
It's a mouse, isn't it?
It's a child.
He's saying bye bye.
Why do you say that the mouse man is a child?
I don't need to.
I want you to be a Dracula.
I'll be a Dracula.
What should I do?
If you don't become a Dracula, you'll be a mouse man.
You can be a mouse man.
Mouse man.
I'm getting goosebumps.
Don't call me a mouse man.
I've said it many times.
Try to be a Dracula.
I'm a Dracula.
Please.
Pretend to be a frog.
What's wrong with you?
You sound like a mouse man.
Next is Heipo Dracula.
But he changes his strategy here.
He sends that old lady as a guest and surprises Heipo.
This is the target of this time.
Please turn around.
He doesn't talk.
He doesn't talk at all.
I was surprised.
It was as I expected.
I'll never do this again.
I'm a mouse man.
Is that so?
I'm sorry.
I don't think I'll ever come out again.
It's a long time ago.
Really?
I wanted to explain it to you.
I understand.
Don't fall in love with me.
Hamada's ear hair.
The wind is blowing.
It was short.
The opening was short.
It was short, but it was long.
It's long.
I don't know why the audience is sinking.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with me?
You don't want to talk.
You know that long hair?
Yes.
You broke your arm.
You're on a bike and you're on your way to work.
That's not good.
If you think about breaking your arm, you can't do anything.
I can't do anything.
You can't do anything.
It depends on where you broke it.
You two are still on the bike.
I'm sorry.
It's fixed, so you can take it off.
But I can't do that. It hurts.
Even if you poop, it's like a toilet seat.
It's okay.
If you grab it, it'll be okay.
I don't care about that.
That's why I'm trying to attack Yoshimoto today.
That's why I'm telling you to send it.
It's a toilet seat.
Even if I'm not bad, if a car comes from the other side and hits me, I'll be out of work today.
That's why I'm bothering you.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with me?
Is it because of the button?
That's not funny.
You can't laugh at anything.
Of course, the office will lend us an apartment.
They'll lend it to us.
Really?
That's right.
It's like an idol, right?
Well, we're like idols.
That's what I think.
It's a middle-class idol.
He won seven gold medals in the Olympics seven times in a row.
Mr. Matsumoto, who has won the title of King of Olympics.
That's right.
Please tell me how to avoid doping after a competition.
That's okay.
What?
That's a urine test or a blood test.
That's right.
There's no way you can't get caught.
There is.
If you get caught, it's over.
Please tell me.
Then I'll try to get it.
I'll try to get the urine.
Are you a prosecutor?
I'm a detective.
My nose is high, so I don't care.
Then...
That's okay.
Then I'll take it out like this.
No, this.
What?
This.
No, no, no.
No, no.
Please take this.
Okay.
No, no.
No, no, no.
No, it's not okay.
Don't take this.
I can't do the test.
Then...
No, no, no, no.
Then I'll do it.
No, it's not drinking.
No, it's for a fool!
Get it out here.
Why!
I don't want to get caught.
If you get caught, damn it!
You stand up, don't do that.
If you get caught...
You get caught!
No, no, no, no.
So I'll justify it.
Are you stupid?
Put your voice in here.
I'm not letting you film me.
You're so stubborn.
That's fine.
I don't think there's anyone who's as stubborn as you.
I'll take this with me.
No, no, no.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
No, no, no.
You're stupid.
You're really stupid.
You shouldn't have had a check-up.
What are you doing?
It's a check-up.
It's a check-up for your eyes.
What?
You're stupid.
You don't understand that?
You shouldn't have had a check-up.
You're really stupid.
You're not qualified.
You're so stubborn.
No, no, no.
You're stupid.
You're in a lab.
You're probably doing tests.
No, no, no.
What are you doing?
I'm done.
Run!
I'm sure you are.
I am confident to do it.
What do you mean confident?
I am confident that I won't get caught.
Even with blood test, I will be caught in the end.
What are you doing?
Don't do the test.
I'm not asking you.
You can stab me.
Don't do the test.
You can't stab me.
What are you doing?
I'm doing a check.
Then take it off.
Why?
You can definitely do it.
If I can't do it, will everyone do it?
But you can't do it that far.
You don't have the guts.
If you stick to it, you'll think it's crazy and stop.
If you don't let me do it, I can't get out.
You can get out.
Why? Before you do it.
There's a doping test before the game.
There's a doping test after the game.
No, no, no.
No, so even if there's no such thing.
Even if you're a extremeENT, you can't get out of the play.
No, no.
You can't get out.
I can't play.
No, no, no
No, no.
I can't play.
Please, can you pick up the flow.
No, no, no.
Oh, no, no.
I can definitely do it.
He wouldn't do it.
K 뉴스
It's yours.
They go like U Paul
Gold medals like...
And they don't even realise
And the other ones go like
No no no no no...
Definitely
retarders
I don't want that
They stick to her
That makes no sense
And this goes for women too
They're alwaysnehmen
They can pull it off
Huh? How so?
How so?
When people say no
What do you do?
No no no no
Hey hey hey
Hey okay okay
Stop it
I'm gonna cuss
No, no, no
He means it
I said stop it
Please stop it
No, no, no
Are you absolutely gonna do it?
Are you gonna do it for sure?
You could fight a cancer or something.
I'm really sorry but it's cancer
I said what's cancer?
what's cancer?
so yes, it's cancer
what?
Nononono...
I'll show you.
To the person in question.
He's a cute little guy who can keep his cuteness like Bambi.
In the news, a deer's horn was cut off with a saw.
What does a deer look like?
Please tell us how it feels to be a deer.
Ah, well...
I'm sure there are some people who have become deers.
Rebirth?
Well, there are some people who have been reborn as deers.
Among them?
Yes, there are.
Rebirth of a freezer.
I feel sorry for that kid.
A freezer?
Rebirth of a freezer.
A freezer!
I didn't do anything!
Rebirth of VHS nails.
There are a lot of them.
But I don't remember them.
You don't remember them, right?
I remember them.
What do you remember?
What I did.
I remember up to 50 of them.
What did you do one year before Matsumoto Hitoshi?
I was wearing a cover.
I thought you were wearing a cover here.
I was wearing a cover a long time ago!
To be honest, it was so funny.
I was so depressed.
I thought I was in the way.
I thought I was just making a fool of myself.
You became a human being from wearing a cover, right?
I did my best.
I didn't do much around my body.
The feelings of a deer.
Surprisingly, it's big.
It's a psychological pain.
Because at one point, it was like...
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
You can't do that!
The shock at that time was a psychological pain.
Really?
I didn't know what I was doing.
But your friends did it too.
But wait.
When you were a deer,
your friend,
your friend who was so close to you,
was suppressed by an old man wearing work clothes.
He was like,
But, after you cut them off,
it'll get up again
and it'll be hurt.
Yes,
but it's the same as the line by the car.
You think,
What happened?
I'll wonder if it hurts.
Until the day before,
we were like,
We're friends.
He said,
I don't like you.
A little different
That Mo appeal was...
He said you must catch the ship by tomorrow
We went home, he fell asleep
And when he ask me to sleep I picked him up
I woke up and still hesitating
Earlier we had so much fun together
And then everyone holds me tight
But now they are kicked out
Something like that
No, no, I got it.
I can't see your face.