THE END
Good evening
Today has finally come
We have invited a lot of people
Today, we have invited a lot of people
We have invited them to come to America
It was a shocking event
For the entertainment world
Isn't it a bomb statement?
His statement that he is going to America
Even so
There is no program to find a spot for this person
He said that he looks like Geno
If we don't leave him like that
Isn't it pitiful?
Even so, he is our senpai
That's right
If we broadcast this
I think a lot of people will buy it
Why are you looking for a spot?
Let's have Shirakuri appear
Please
It's a gorilla
Isn't it a gorilla?
What is this?
Today is a day to go on a trip
I told you to look at the nose
As I said before
There is no program to say goodbye to Jimmy-chan?
There is no program at all
Really?
Don't laugh
Our program didn't have a lot of guests
There were 310 times
The number of times that Jimmy appeared was 15 times
This is the most
It can't be helped if we don't find a spot
It's a great contribution
This is a summary of Jimmy's activities
Please look at it
Thank you
He doesn't say anything funny
I was surprised
You know that
He doesn't say anything funny
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
Jimmy Onishi
His real name is Onishi Hideaki
He is a unique Japanese comedian
His love for comedy continues to give us peace and dreams
He is now saying goodbye to us
He is going to travel to America
This is a great miracle of a comedian
He is good
In 1992, Jimmy Onishi appeared for the first time
This is the first time that he is going to travel to America
Your face is chubby
Hello
This is Jimmy Onishi
What?
He is a comedian
I don't know him
Look at him
He is doing it
He is famous
My younger brother is a comedian
I want to show him
Come and play with us
What should I do?
Don't run away
He ran away
A lot of things happened and he finally came
I didn't think he would run away
This is Jimmy Onishi
Thank you
Hello
This is Jimmy Onishi
You know him
Excuse me
Can you touch here?
He is wet
Why is he wet?
Really?
I don't know
He is really chubby
Really?
I don't know why he is wet
He is going home
Thank you
He is really fast
I want to do it
You want to do it?
Yes
There are a lot of things
My character is Taiyaki
Look at his face
Thank you
My character is Taiyaki
I think he will get it
Excuse me
I am not a manager
I heard that you gave him the gala
I was wondering what you were thinking
He also asked me to do it
I didn't think it would be this easy
I am not a manager
I thought it would be easy
I didn't think it would be easy
I was wondering what you were thinking
I thought it would be easy
He gave a big applause to the three fighters.
If you sell, what do you want to do?
I'm good at singing, so I want to release a record.
You're good at singing?
Can you sing?
I can sing, leave it to me.
But you said you were good at 180,000 yen.
Kiyoshi Nakajou's lie.
Then let's ask the audience who is coming today.
Where are you coming from?
Kiyoshi Nakajou's lie.
Today's topic is...
Japan passing.
That's because...
What is that?
According to the court, 200,000 yen is not enough.
You have more money, don't you?
Money...
Softly...
The second topic is...
Ogasawara...
Ogasawara style dating.
Miyuki is...
I'm scared.
One foot first.
Ogasawara style dating.
Moutakuto and the Cultural Revolution.
Edison was...
On Moutakuto's knee...
Why are you talking about Edison?
We were talking about 2039.
It was a story that I haven't seen yet.
Kokon Tozai.
I'm so scared.
In the masterpiece Kokon Tozai...
It is a dialogue with Matsuo, who remains in the Japanese comedy market.
Something is shining.
It's a Japanese character.
I'm scared.
I'm going to be scolded by my mother.
Matsuo.
Matsuo is crying.
And then...
The name of the member of Pintosu changed.
Golbatto.
I'm sorry.
It was amazing.
It was smelly.
What?
Buttocks.
It was my first time using it.
There were many things.
I was surprised.
I was surprised by the dog.
It wasn't a special dog.
But a clever dog just três walks along.
There are a lot of dogs.
His house is just across from here.
It's surprising that he barked at Jimmy.
It's amazing that I won't be scolded by a dog.
He barked a lot.
I found out later that he was a good dog.
I thought he was a good dog.
After I found out that he was all prepared.
What is he talking about?
I don't know what he is talking about.
Dogs are not prepared.
They are just born.
That's right.
It's difficult.
What is difficult?
The dog.
You were wet.
You were caught in the net.
Were you scared?
I don't know where the pee leaked.
When I touched it, I saw it.
It was wet.
It's more interesting to see Jimmy in the V.
What is that?
Jimmy in the V is interesting.
When did you do that?
In 1994,
Yamazaki Hosei and his team
released a big hit series.
The talent of Jimmy Onishi
became popular at once.
He became one of the top ones with a big success.
His cross between the Jimmy vs. Yamazaki
and his
A bit difficult.
igramm
I hate you!
I hate you too.
What's with your face?
I'm not going to give you anything.
I don't know you! Look at me!
If you're going to do it, then do it!
Hey!
Look at me!
It's hot!
The tweezers!
The tweezers.
That's what I'm talking about.
Hold him!
If he comes out, it's over.
Stand up!
Do it from the inside.
Why are you letting go?
Let's go!
It's hot!
What is this?
You're a human!
You did it!
Look at the camera!
What?
What are you doing?
It's hot!
It's beautiful!
In 1995, the talent of Jimmy Onishi, who was born in Yamazaki, entered the entertainment industry.
He developed his mental state.
Musical Adventure 95 Summer I
You did it, didn't you?
It's a bubble.
Amazing.
The light is leaking.
Whose room is this?
Oh!
Romeo!
Why are you Romeo?
Come up here.
And hold me.
Right now.
Romeo!
I don't know!
What?
Aucha Mardin!
And they all barged in.
O-Ri-Kai-San
He's a monster!
Scary, scary, scary.
In the Gaginotsukai special, the life of the child is revealed.
At the Hong Kong hotel, Hamada Masatoshi's report shows his honest charm.
He made us feel a familiar face.
He's a monster!
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Good morning.
He's a monster!
That was the best way to fall for it.
Ouch!
He's a monster!
For four years, the Gaginotsukai has been walking with Onishi.
We will never forget the joy of spending the shining season with you.
That smile, that voice, that warmth.
Even if you're far away, I hope you don't forget.
Jimmy Onishi.
Because you're an irreplaceable friend.
Jimmy is really funny.
Yamazaki and Jimmy thought it would be a long time.
That's what they said.
They were so excited.
Jimmy really hated me for that.
He hated me for acting, acting, and playing.
So when I went to America, he said,
I'm going to go play, but I'm not going to come alone.
Really?
Yes.
But I don't want you to come.
Why?
It's okay.
That was just a comparison.
But it's okay.
Ouch! My chin hurts!
My chin hurts!
You can't do that!
It hurts!
I don't know what's going on.
But it's okay.
It's time to leave.
Thank you very much.
Jimmy, it's time to leave.
It's time to leave.
I'd like you to run through Virgin Road.
Take care and go to America.
Thank you very much.
See you again.
Hey!
Jimmy!
I knew this would happen.
Hiro! Hiro!
Why would you do something like this to me?
I'm so happy.
I thought it was an egg.
I can't leave an egg.
Do you want to put it back next year?
I'm done with you.
It's cold.
This is a big deal.
We don't have that kind of money.
I'm glad it wasn't that much.
What a way to say it.
It's cold.