It's a hot day for all the viewers of Gaki no Tsukai. How are you all doing?
Tonight, we have a special gift for you all.
This is a recording from downtown Gaki no Tsukai Yara.
It's been 7 years since the show started.
There are more and more friends of Gaki no Tsukai.
Let's take a look at the memories of that start together.
Gaki no Tsukai Kouyuuroku, where old friends come back to life.
Now, let's begin.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
First, a scene from when Gaki no Tsukai was still young.
The first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Yara, Chikichiki Gentenpappa!
Good evening.
Please welcome the children.
Please come in.
Please look to the side.
Your father is a yuakashi pot.
Father, please come out.
What is that?
Is that so?
They look alike.
Let's introduce them once again.
This is Harada Daichiro.
What does Kotaro think about his father in the variety show?
He thinks it's wonderful.
What?
There's no way he would think that.
This is Kotaro's opinion.
Everyone's opinion.
I got it.
People pull.
No!
The second episode of Gaki no Tsukai Yara, Jicchan Bacchan Gakurenbo!
This is Namikoshi-sensei.
He's here again.
He was hiding in the car the other day.
And this is Komori no Obajama.
Hello.
He's here for the first time.
Downtown is looking for Jicchan Bacchan hiding in the model room.
He's definitely looking down on me.
He's here.
He's standing up seriously.
He has a three-dimensional look.
That's amazing.
But he never moves.
He never moves?
He doesn't even put his fingers in his nostrils.
He's really tall.
The third episode of Gaki no Tsukai Yara, Jicchan Bacchan Gakurenbo!
He's in this room.
That's amazing.
Huh?
I hear something.
What are you looking for?
What is that?
So, Jicchan Bacchan Gakurenbo.
That was hard.
It was a huge success.
Jicchan Bacchan did it for me.
Thank you.
Say something.
It was fun.
I'm glad.
And this year, he appeared on this program and took on this challenge.
Just by looking at this house, I get the feeling that it's an inn.
Yes, it is.
Let's go.
Did you really come here?
Is that an inn?
Hey, you.
You're dressed funny.
Thank you.
I heard about you.
Did you really come here?
That's funny.
That's nice.
Then, let's run.
Please run.
Let's do our best.
Can you show us once?
We're practicing.
Please.
Then, let's go.
I'm nervous.
Let's go.
4, 3, 2...
I'm nervous.
You're doing too much.
Thank you.
Then, we'll wait for you next time.
What?
We'll wait for you.
From this point on, Gaki no Tsukai will advance to the Golden Age.
And they're going to challenge themselves in many different projects.
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Ara, Chiki Chiki Jicchan Paachan Gesture Tournament!
Good evening!
Start!
It's quite detailed.
Ah!
It's the Olympics.
You can say whatever you want.
You really can't say anything.
You have to look here, not my face.
I'm angry!
Here is the question.
What is it?
Well...
Devil!
You're right to choose this one.
That's fine!
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Ara, Chiki Chiki Jicchan Paachan Gesture Tournament!
And the special episode, Omae So Chan Ka Grand Prix.
The memorable first episode started with these talents.
First, this is Kenji Nagira.
Thank you for coming.
Then, Tenme Sano.
Thank you.
This is Matsumoto Hitachi.
The last question is this!
What a big-looking entertainer!
Let's see.
Nonio-san.
This is a big-looking one.
Right.
No.
Which one is it?
Matsumoto-san, stop putting them together.
Kenji Nagira.
Masabuchi.
Wada Akiko-san.
Matcha.
Norio Nishikawa.
Matsumoto-san.
It's Matsumoto-san.
It's a big-looking one!
Matsumoto Hitachi!
The famous lyrics and this kind of drama.
It's been three months since she left this house.
There's no sign of her leaving.
I've become like a princess.
I don't like it.
You!
Put one on me.
I don't drink anymore!
Shut up!
I got it.
Just one.
You!
You stole my money again!
You idiot!
I can't take that money!
Shut up!
You!
Actually, I have something to tell you.
In my belly...
...is your baby!
In a nameless town in the north...
...snow falls like tears.
A happy woman is crying...
...as the cold night breeze passes by.
I want to live with a man who has left.
Even such a small dream...
...and this unreachable body...
...are painful.
For my sake...
...I chase after that dream.
What are you doing?
I brought the finishing touch.
Oh, you're taking it out!
And now, there are these three people...
...who can be called illusions.
I'm Matsu-chan!
I'm Omo-chan!
I'm Ichidai Juunichi!
We're three Maito!
We're still rookies, but...
It's almost time.
I'm telling you to do your best, but...
But, you know...
...you can't be a comedian.
You can't be a comedian.
You can't be a comedian because...
...no matter what you say, the car you're driving...
...is amazing. It's amazing.
Is that so?
Do you know what Sen Masao-san's car is?
It's a Rolls-Royce.
That's amazing.
It's amazing, right?
Do you know what Katsura Bunchin-san is driving?
What?
Ferrari.
Is it a supercar?
You can't be surprised by something like that.
Badan-san from Chaos-Bodan.
The car you're driving is...
...a fire truck.
That's right.
It's hot! It's hot! It's hot!
Hey!
What are you saying?
No, no, no, no.
You can't be a comedian.
What do you want to do?
Well, I'm good at singing.
I want to release a record.
You're good at singing?
Can you sing?
I can sing. Leave it to me.
What's your favorite number 18?
Nakajou Kiyoshi's Lies.
Then today, let's have our guests listen to it.
Please listen to it.
Where did you guys come from?
What?
What are you talking about?
Where did you come from?
It's a little confusing.
I don't know.
It's confusing because we did it in Paris.
I see.
I'll do it next time.
He's the only one who dances.
Yes.
I'm counting on you.
It's broken.
How many times do I have to tell you to sing?
After the end of the show, the memorable problem will appear.
Please look forward to it.
Next time, let's have a special program to make Yamazaki stand up.
Yamazaki's mini-prank.
After this, it will be a talk show with a Yamazaki host.
It is not known that a scary star will appear.
Let's have a special program to make Yamazaki stand up.
Can I do it here?
Yes.
It's Yananobo.
Hobby.
Yananobo-san, what kind of hobbies do you have?
Alcohol and women.
Alcohol and women?
It's a good hobby.
Do you think it's a good hobby?
Yes, it's a good hobby.
I see.
What about you guys?
I'm scared.
Hey.
What?
Let's stop the tape.
It's a different story.
Who is responsible?
I'm sorry.
Call him.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
What's next?
Why are you doing this again?
I'm sorry.
Can Yamazaki stand up now?
Can he?
This year's special program has more than 20% ratings.
Let's introduce the first user.
Let's introduce him again.
First of all, Murakami Shoji-san.
Nice to meet you.
Next to him, Dave Spector-san.
Hello.
Last but not least, Matsumoto Hida-san.
Let's listen to him.
When did you start?
We've been watching TV for a long time.
Are you the king today?
Where am I?
The chair here is a change.
I don't know if you're going to sit here.
But it's comfortable to sit.
It's good, isn't it?
It's expensive, isn't it?
I'm already in.
It's comfortable to sit.
I didn't notice it.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
Jaka-chan.
ZO.
I'll go with ZO.
Welcome to Kamu-de Kamu-do.
Who said it's a joke?
ZO-san.
What's this?
It's a soap.
It's not good.
Goro-san.
Take a good look at this mirror.
What's this?
It's a light bulb.
It's a diamond.
In the fourth episode of Gaki no Tsukai Ara Hende Tsuki Tsuki,
Dachio Club Ryu-chan's coordinated strategy.
Let's call him right away.
First of all,
Aina.
Retsuzaku.
Hino-chan.
Ryu-chan's coordinated strategy.
Let's call him right away.
Let's take a look at his coordinated strategy.
Ryu-chan, go ahead.
It's not good.
Everyone.
He's wearing a jersey.
It's a helmet.
It's not good if it's written like this.
Go home.
I don't know.
Let's go home.
Good work, Ryu-chan.
I'll be late for school tomorrow.
After the CM,
The Gaki no Tsukai's best ratings project has appeared.
It's not good if it's written like this.
It's a helmet.
It's a hit project to hit the point of the guest who was called without knowing anything.
What is this?
But, but.
It's a helmet.
Everyone was dead.
Well, it's called Cinderella.
Is it a dead person?
I'm not excited to do such a thing.
I change the color every day.
How is it?
Don't you wear earrings on your nose?
Do you wear earrings on your nose?
Do you open your nose?
No, I don't open it.
How many kinds of shoes do you have?
I think I have about 70 or 80 pairs of shoes, including the ones I don't wear.
Turn around and show it to everyone.
Turn this way.
You did a good job.
You're a weird guy.
What are you doing?
No, no, no.
Thank you very much.
You're a weird guy.
What are you doing?
I have something here.
It's something like this.
I'm not going to play with it.
I thought I'd do it.
I'm sorry.
I have something here.
Thank you very much.
I'll announce the results.
You only had 10,000 points for your one shot.
After that, Kaga's father touched it.
You only got 50 points, right?
That's right.
I threw away my shoes.
Kaga's father touched it.
What is it?
You have a lot of savings.
I have a lot of savings.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
And this is the famous program of the staff.
Downtown Dinner Show.
Please listen to Yugeyuke Humor.
Burning red.
The center of the night.
The star of the year.
What is it?
Run away.
Who is it?
At the end of this year, Sakamoto from all over the world came to the program as a fan.
He made that star debut in New York.
We got the teacher girls.
Get in the show.
Coming out here from Japan.
Take it to our tan-tan.
Y'all ready, boys?
Make some noise.
Make some noise for him.
All right?
Let's go, grandma.
With the warm cheers from the various stars, the downtown kids continue to run today.
Attractive guests gave the program dreams and spread.
We look forward to seeing more interesting dreams with you who are watching TV.