It's been a long time since I've seen you.
Me too, George.
Yama-chan, I want to see George too.
In the back.
Yes.
Only George.
Let's see George.
No, there's only one.
There's only Miho.
This is the old book.
I like George.
It's cool.
I don't want to see George.
What are you going to do next?
Let's do it again.
Let's do it without water next time.
We can do it for about 5 minutes.
We can do it.
We can do it for more than 5 minutes.
I don't know if that picture will last.
If it doesn't last.
Of course we'll add water to the opponent.
We can't win.
Excuse me.
Something terrible has happened.
Iie-chan.
What are you going to do, Iie-chan?
It's not the time to be excited.
Mr. Suga fell down.
Is that Irie's job?
It's unusual.
Can you come here for a moment?
What?
Mr. Suga fell down.
Why?
Please come here.
You're talking nonsense.
Irie was taken to the scene without knowing the reason.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
What happened?
Irie-chan, what happened?
I was working.
I don't know why, but he asked me to help him.
When I hit him, I hit him in the head.
Did you hit him?
Yes.
That's not good.
It's an accident.
It's Irie-chan's fault.
Hey, what are you going to do?
Excuse me.
Old man.
Mr. Suga.
Hey.
Get up.
I was surprised.
I didn't know you were coming.
I'm glad.
What happened?
What's wrong?
Where are you going?
He is very enthusiastic.
I'll do it, too.
Who?
No.
Isn't it Mr. Matsumoto?
It's already on air.
What is this camera?
Shooting?
Do you know the camera?
Mr. Suga often uses it.
It's a child's camera.
It's not for recording.
No.
What?
What is this?
Is it a camera?
I don't know.
It's amazing.
It's not a camera.
Who is it?
What is your favorite TV show?
Metropolitan TV.
Where is it?
What is it?
I've heard of it.
It's not here.
Bring the music.
Yes.
Please.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
This program is sponsored by the following sponsors.
You don't remember?
I don't know.
Is it a program that doesn't use musical instruments?
No.
You don't know?
Does your head hurt?
A little.
A little?
This is a serious problem.
Hey, Heipo!
Really?
This is Heipo.
What should I do?
You've been dating for a long time.
We've been dating for 20 years.
Yes.
Don't you know?
Heipo.
What is that?
The way he laughs now.
It's a characteristic.
Something.
What should I do?
The door of memory.
Did you open it?
What is that?
Something.
The way he laughs.
Let's play the tatami in Heipo.
That's right.
Let's show a lot of the best scenes of Heipo.
Then you might remember.
You remember, right?
How is it?
It's coming.
Hang in there.
One more push.
A little more.
I want to do one more push.
One more push.
A little more.
Oh, there it is.
There are so many.
This is Heipo.
That's right.
It's Heipo.
Absolutely.
I'll definitely do it today.
This person is also a box artist.
That's right.
What are you doing?
I'll do it properly.
That's enough.
This, this, this, this.
That's right.
You remember a lot.
Hey, hey.
Stop it.
I won't do it anymore.
This, this, this.
Why are you feeling it?
I'll do it.
You remember.
Stop it.
How is it?
I feel like you remember something.
What are you going to do?
Heipo, really.
Stop it.
I don't want to do it anymore.
Heipo-san.
This, this, this.
How is it?
Heipo, what are you guys doing?
It's fun.
What should we do?
What else was there?
Heipo...
Sorry.
Can you change your clothes?
Heipo, change your clothes.
Change your clothes.
I think it's better to actually do it.
Definitely.
I understand.
I'll change my clothes.
Thank you.
You guys, stop it.
It's fun.
Even if it's just for show.
Then, with this...
Yes.
Let's see it in front of us.
It's a name.
Yes.
Thank you for waiting.
This is hard.
What is this?
Give me the gun.
The gun.
I'm scared.
He said he's scared.
He's already been shot.
He's scared.
What is this?
It's different.
He's still alive.
Do you really think so?
In this situation.
It's a small one.
I don't want to die.
He's still alive.
What's going to happen?
He's dead.
Okay.
What's going to happen?
I don't know what's going to happen.
He was thinner than before.
That's right.
He was like a rice.
I can't remember.
Just a little more.
Really.
Is he here?
Yes.
He's here.
Let's put the tatami on him.
This should do it.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Okay.
He's here.
I'm not good at this.
Bo-chan.
It's moving.
Wait.
Bo-chan.
Aoya.
What are you two?
It's done!
I'm starving!
Ho-rum! Ho-rum! Ho-rum! Ho-rum!
Ho-rum! Ho-rum! Ho-rum! Ho-rum! Ho-rum! Ho-rum! Cage!
Ho-rum! Ho-rum! Ho-rum! Ho-rum! ho-rum!
No ~~~
Amazing!
That was the pilot episode.
To put it simply.
Sorry.
We did the pilot episode.
That was the pilot episode.