In the pouring rain, Ikko has come
Today, if we talk about the amusement park in Tokyo
Gokurand
What?
Yomiland
Yes, Yomiland
Even if we don't say it, we have come to Yomiland
Let's have fun together
Can we have fun?
I don't think we can have fun
If you look at the weather
What kind of weather is this?
Today, we will also have fun
Yes
The other day
Mr. Tanuki
Yes
It's a great opportunity
It's a great battle
Yes
Chiki Chiki Heisei Tanuki Neri Gassen
No matter what happens around
Two people who decided to go to Tanuki Neri
Can Tanuki Neri be done as if nothing happened today?
The attractions of Yomiland are waiting for them
I'm looking forward to Tanuki
I brought it
It just appeared
I'm sleeping
Even if you say something
Even if you are sleeping, I think you will wake up
Let's have fun
These two
Tanuki here
I think you will be surprised to see
Married
Who is it?
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching
It's heavy
Isn't it very heavy?
Maybe
Let's leave this
This is a little better
What should I do with this?
Take this Tanuki
This is not Tanuki at all
What are you doing?
I hate this Tanuki
This is not Tanuki
What are you doing?
Tanuki
Tanuki is gone
It's dangerous
Why?
Do you want to kill me?
Rock'n'roll
This is very useful
I'm OK
This is a good one
Hurry up
You guys are too much
You are too much
This is very hard
Masumoto san
It's better to ride this than riding a merry-go-round
Is that so?
That's right
It's better to ride this
Rock'n'roller
First of all, it's a rock'n'roller that spins in the sky
Everyone is going to enjoy riding it
What kind of Tanuki will it be?
If everyone rides it, you can't turn it
We have to broadcast it
We will do it
We will broadcast it
You can't hit me
Have fun with Tanuki
Yes
Please
Rock'n'roller start
He has a scary face
Tanuki from the east has a scary face
Scary
He's back
Tanuki from the east has a scary face
Why?
If you don't ride it again, you won't know Tanuki
Only Tanuki from the east?
Tanuki from the east
If Tanaka rides with you
Tanaka
Are you Tanaka?
I'm Tanaka
Please say Tanaka looking at me
I don't know which one
You have a habit of reflecting
What are you doing?
Say Tanaka reflected in Endo's eyes
Do you understand?
I don't understand
Let's go
Rock'n'roller start
Wait
Why is he doing that?
He can do it many times
He has a scary face
Tanuki from the east is coming
He's coming
He's enjoying it
Tanuki from the east is dangerous
He's dangerous
He has a weird face
What should we ride?
This is
This is cute
Merry-go-round is good
This is fun
Next is Merry-go-round
They will go to Merhenchik
Let's go
He's so fast
He's hitting the iron ball
Hold it in front
You can lie down
Lie down
Down
It's over
This is good
Be careful
He's looking at you
Let's go
This is good
He's hitting the iron ball
What are you doing?
This is fun
Next is Tanuki
Two Tanuki are singing
I don't think I can sleep
Did you ride this?
This one?
And the scary machine
You can't get up even if you spin in the air
Why don't you get in the back?
Let's get in together
This is weird
Everyone thinks it's weird
You and I are different
Let's get in together
Let's have fun
The main character is Tanuki
Don't forget to raise your hands
Tanuki remembers
Please
Let's have fun
Cool
Tanuki raised his hand
Let's have fun
Tanaka raise your hand
It's raining
Are you having fun?
Tanuki
Tanuki from the east, raise your hand
Here he comes
Tanuki
He's fast
He did his best
They look happy
You can't go twice
I'm not going
Why?
I want to go again
What is this?
It's not fun at all
Your face is even worse
I'm going to shoot from the other side
I'm going to shoot from this side
You're going to get wet
Think about the rain
Have a good day
Why?
Why are you laughing?
It's raining
It's raining again
They are exhausted from the rain
They made a suggestion
It's cold, do you want to eat something?
Yes
It's time
There are pork balls
I wanted to eat
It's warm
It looks hot
It's good for a cold body
Who is it?
It's coming
What?
Why did you pose like that?
It's fun
They prepared hot ramen to warm their body
Tanuki
It's coming
Wake up
It's annoying
Drink a lot
He is completely awake
He drank the soup
It's good
It's coming
Noodles
It's good
He is a child
I want to put the soup
It's ramen
He is awake
What?
What did you do?
Yes
Finally, they moved the place to the room and had a fun bowling competition
The two raccoons decided to play with the raccoon
Can you do it?
It's a rare opportunity
I'm going to take you out
The bowling competition showed unexpected excitement
The winner is Hosei Yamazaki
I did it
He is in his 50s
The winner is
This is the last
You should have done it before
Let's play with Tanuki
Let's do it together
This way
Stand up
What are you doing?
Let's play bowling
This is dangerous
I put a bowling ball
Let's have fun
What is this?
Thank you
Let's help