In front of the stage of Gaki no Tsukai
Your dad is a fisherman, right?
I'm a fisherman, not a fisherman
You're lying
No, I'm not
That's a weird lie
I'm going to put on a character
Thank you
Can these two sell?
I think they're going to sell
I'll have to do my best
I'm sorry to interrupt, but
You have a channel called Nittere, right?
Koho
The manager of Downtown asked me to do it
The one with the hat?
Yes
Nittere-chan
You're Nittere-chan too
Nittere-chan is the best in the world
Okamoto-kun or him
Isomata
I don't remember
Okamoto did it before
He did it
What was it?
That
He did it
Isomata can do it
The two of you can choose
Thank you
I'll do it
No, Nittere-chan
I just said it
You did it before
Grand Prix Okamoto
I won't give you a chance
Last time, the Japanese TV spot CM
The manager Okamoto
He ignored the theory
He came up from the bottom of the sea
And shouted praises
It was an amazing scene
And this is what was completed
That's Nittere-chan
Isomata will be back soon
He was kicked out
Yoshimoto's company is in Osaka
Wait a minute
You talked to me
Talk to me
Let's do it at the end
Let's do it
What are you doing?
It hasn't started yet
Don't get angry
Yamazaki
Stop it
Stop hitting each other
Yamazaki, stop it
You're good at it
I like it
Stop fighting
Stop it
Who are you?
Listen to your opinion
Stop it
You guys are ***
***
It doesn't matter
What are you talking about?
You guys
Yes
If I do it, you can't do it
Isomata can accept it
I don't accept it
It's an order
It's a company
It's not
Okamoto-san has been in many movies
I don't know if there's a movie called Mataya
Don't talk like that
We're working
I read the news every week
I read the news
To be honest
I always say, I'm tired of Okamoto-san
If I win the game
It's not to my liking
Let's start
I'm wearing this hat
I'm fighting
Apparently it's going to sell
It's not going to sell
It's 4800 Yen
That's expensive!
But you can buy it for 2,000 yen
Yes, you can buy it for 2,000 yen
I think people around the world would want it
I'm sorry but I'm going to wear it
That's good
Is that good, everyone?
I'm going to play 3 games
Please tell us
First, the first game
Cool!
Wow!
You're really good
As you can see
The cat is the same
The cat is cool
What is this?
Start!
It started
What is that sword?
I'm just stretching
Get down!
One, two, fight!
That's amazing
It's not working at all
What are you doing?
I thought you were going to attack continuously
What is this?
Get back!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight
You're still standing?
That's good
This was the ideal situation
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten
What is this program?
You lied!
I was listening
What is this program?
I'll do it
If you stop now, it will be Isomata
I'll do this
What is this?
I'll hit you
Stop it
Shut up
You're the worst
You have a great body
Your upper body
It's okay, you can win
Binta no Binoji wa Big no Bi
Aiue Okamoto vs Babi Bube Binta Taiketsu
That was fast
Defend
Good
That was painful
What was that?
It hurts
You can't do that
That was good
What is this program?
How should we judge this?
I won
I lost
What are you looking at?
Look at it
I'll look at it
You can do it again
Why do you have to do it again?
It's hard to understand
Do it again
Binta Taiketsu
That was good
That's the end
Binta Taiketsu
Okamoto
I'll give this hat to Isomata
What are you looking at?
It's not working
Which one did you like?
What?
What are you laughing at?
You liked it?
Okamoto liked it
That's right
We didn't see it like that
It's a fighting game
It's a variety
That's right
There's no picture
We took it in Japan
If you don't take it in Japan
It's a loss
What do you think?
Aosu's picture is cool
It's cool
That's cool
The last one
Yoshimoto Meibutsu Mogitate Pants Mogitori Taiketsu
The total of the 3
Which one was the best?
That's what it means
It's changing
There's no choice
You have to look at the total
I see
Fight
Ok
It's different from before
Do you have stamina?
He's using his legs
That's good
Ok
Thank you
Shake it
Oh no
What do you want to do?
Is there such a thing?
It's getting more and more
Ok
I don't need a manager like this
Sorry
Ok
Rest
I didn't sleep
I did it a little bit more.
Hey, you look like Bulma.
Okamoto.
There is no winner in this game.
I'm a loser when I'm playing.
You're so stupid.
What is this show?
I'm still in the pot.
This year, there will be 20 people like this in Yoshimoto Kogyo.
There will be 2 people like this.
Just now, I was saved by Gong.
Let's do our best.
Fight!
What's wrong?
You look like a salmon.
What are you doing?
I see.
This is not good.
This is embarrassing.
Break time.
I was saved by Gong.
It's OK.
Fight!
You look like Kamikaze.
You look like Koumon Marumi.
You're too low.
Okamoto-san, you look like...
Winner!
This hat goes to Isomata.
Thank you.
Isomata is OK, right?
Isomata, the manager who defeated Okamoto, will he be able to film safely?
What is this behind you?
Okamoto-san.
I thought it was a joke.
It's cool.
You wanted to do it like this.
It's because you want to win.
I see.
But it's OK.
I'll do it.
Why?
I'm sweating.
It's not like that.
It's not like you're sweating.
What did you do until now?
I'm exhausted.
You're sweating, so you're the one who's exhausted.
Don't say things like a quiz.
No.
You're the one who's excited.
Well, well, but...
You all agree with what I'm doing, right?
What do you mean by everyone?
The people who are watching, the people who are here, the camera-san, the lighting-san, everyone.
That's a great opinion.
I don't want to do it.
It's OK.
I'll do it.
I did my best.
I did my best, but in the end...
I'll do it.
I'll show you that kind of look.
It's the time when you shouldn't show it the most.
Yes, yes.
Since you've said it so far, I'll do it.
That's right.
The set is ready.
It's already prepared.
What was it like?
That's right.
It was like this.
You too, Nittere-chan.
Right?
It's cool.
But can you show us the one until now?
Yes.
It's a location, right?
The glass shoes are Nittere-chan.
The program name is Nittere-chan.
Nittere-chan.
It's like this until now.
It's not that big.
You made a set like this.
That's right.
It's not that big.
It wasn't that much of a fight until the end.
It's 3 seconds.
3 seconds, 3 seconds.
It seems to be 3 seconds.
You have to say the line within 3 seconds.
In one shot.
What should I do?
The servant of the kid is Nittere-chan.
You don't need the servant of the kid.
What?
You said it in the program.
You don't need the servant of the kid.
What kind of comment is that?
Nittere-chan is Okamoto-chan.
It's not Nittere-chan.
That's right.
If you still say Okamoto-chan is Nittere-chan.
You'll know it again.
Nittere-chan is Okamoto-chan.
What?
It's not the part where you get caught.
It's huge.
So it's equal.
Nittere-chan was absorbed.
That's right.
I got it.
You can say that.
What was that again?
What was it again?
Nittere-chan's red tea
You're funny
Why did you do that?
What happens when it's 9?
It's too late!
It's already 3 seconds
You're drinking it now
It's not like that
That's the shop of the doctor at the university hospital
Yamazaki, can you run away? It's only 3 seconds
I'm fine
Really?
I've prepared a set
You don't have to do that
This guy...
I hate him
Why do you have to do that?
I don't think so
Let's go
Ready
Nittere-chan, Okamoto-chan
That's strange
You have a different face
It's because of the atmosphere
The atmosphere here
You're making a role
Can you do a cheerful pose?
I'll do that
Ready
Nittere-chan, Okamoto-chan
Don't stand up
His hand is cut off
The frame is like this
Are you stupid?
What's with the cheerful pose?
You can't do that
Let's go
Ready
Nittere-chan, Okamoto-chan
Cut
Is it okay?
Wait
You can't do that
I don't like it
You look fine
No
I want to look more flashy
What do you want to do?
Why are you doing that?
I like to drink
You can't do that
It's cold
Nittere-chan, Okamoto-chan
You should make a character
Like an impersonator
An impersonator?
You can't do that
Do you want to try?
Ready
Action
Nittere-chan, Okamoto-chan
Okay
Thank you
I'm not satisfied
Who did that?
Tamura Masakazu
I knew it
Do you want to try again?
Again?
Ready
Action
Nittere-chan, Okamoto-chan
Okay
It's good
Let's go
It's not good
It's okay
I'll do it again
I'll do a bigger one
Let's do it
Get ready
I have another one
He wanted to do that
Okamoto-san
You did it
Isomata did it better
What are you talking about?
What did you see?
I did my best
I
Isomata did it
No
You'll see
Ready
Action
That's
Wow
Okay
Thank you
It was good
It was great
It was okay in many ways
It was okay
That's
That's from before
It's old
You can do it
Let's do it again
It's okay
Thank you for watching