The first episode of the show, Hikari Umeda's Emergency! Tonight, you will witness the miracle of the thousand-year-old god!
Good evening, I am the host, Shigeru Kajiwara.
And I have gathered everyone here today to witness the miracle.
We are the downtown's children's
Well, Mr. Hikateri Umeda, you have been the champion of fortune-telling, magic, and big-mouthed.
You have been the champion of fortune-telling, magic, and big-mouthed.
But, in fact, you were the man-biki-jimen of the great-master.
This time, it became clear.
Man-biki is easier to catch than before.
After five, even the boss who is busy and can't be caught at all can be caught easily.
That's all.
I don't know anything about him.
I don't think he's from Canada.
That's right.
He's been called to Canada for an emergency.
Let's call him out.
No blinkers while tracking.
No eye ball fatigue.
If you have a great skill, you'll be a G-man.
Hikari Ueda!
The world's most powerful man is 8.0.
He can be seen with the naked eye.
Next, the technique of the Kageyama Umeda will be exploded.
I found it.
He is the one.
Please.
The perfect shari is here.
If you get a full-drawn, this one is low.
It's a final line.
Now, what is the situation of full-drawing in Japan?
I want you to see this graph.
Over 10,000 cases a week.
This is the number of cases.
By the way, by the way, by Mr. Piccadilly's coming next day,
How much will the number of full-drawing cases decrease?
This was expected by the experts.
It will be like this.
But...
Heный...
It is a conjecture that almost all public complaints from Japan will disappear.
Does that mean this is only linear?
That is a great thing.
My sense of justice is not silly.
Er?
My sense of justice is not over.
Ah...
We have succeeded in filming a part of the scene of the work of Mr. Umeda Piccadilly.
It looks like it's amazing.
Let's take a look at the shocking video.
ZOA and Ileva G-Men's
The attack of the two sides.
A crime lurking nearby.
The attack.
Don't do it.
I did it.
I just did it.
Is this a disease that the modern society is suffering from?
A momentary malice.
But the price is too high.
I've seen this before.
Please help me!
I'll do something.
I'll use that footage.
The man is facing the crime that's repeated.
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
The dark is coming.
This is not the place.
There is a supermarket in the neighborhood of Tokyo.
The total damage of this store is 1.5 million yen per year.
This man who received the SOS of such a store is the man who appeared.
Let's go and feel it.
There is always a blind spot in the supermarket.
That is the workplace for the manbikikan.
Piccadilly is breaking down the workplace one by one.
But that is because his arm is called his arm.
That's great.
After a while, Piccadilly's sense of smell started to
I'll do it like this.
I'll definitely do it.
The back of my head is going to be swollen.
The incident right after the earthquake.
It's a bomb. It's a bomb.
The night of the tsunami hit.
Certainly, the product disappeared in the woman's bag.
She doesn't even have time to take out the products from her bag.
And then the woman goes out of the store.
She is successful.
Let's go.
Piccadilly follows the woman.
Hey, Mr. Hoshiguma.
You are early.
You should have taken a bath.
What?
If you go there, you have to take off your clothes.
You have to take off your clothes.
The match was visible.
The woman, who was convinced by Piccadilly's words,
obediently agreed.
A wonderful fight.
Please put the things that ladies can't pass.
An unacceptable moment.
The stolen item came out of the bag.
That was the reality.
When she heard this, she was 48 years old, and the mother of two children.
I will teach you the tricks of the master's daughter.
Please forgive me.
The mother who doesn't want her family to know about her own sins, Piccadilly bites her.
Don't talk so much.
You don't know the difference between this and a handkerchief?
What would the child think if he knew this?
I'm too old to be here.
I'm not coming back to this place.
You're coming back?
You're going home?
Yes!
What's that?
The word of Piccadilly has fallen on her mother.
She wrote a promise that she would never do it again.
The woman has arrived at her home.
The manbiki g-men sometimes change their appearance and become normal.
The appearance of the woman who is patrolling the world is a familiar sight to anyone.
Suddenly...
They are suspicious.
Two girls are standing in front of the lady's eyes.
The bag is opening its mouth.
Be careful!
And the next moment...
I put it in, I put it in, I put it in!
The girl's product in her right hand is in the bag.
It disappeared.
Immediately, Piccadilly stands up to the girls.
Hey, girls.
It's a security thing.
There is a new product, right?
Even if the bugs in the
bowl are deceived, my eyes are not deceived.
The girls who found out that they could not escape do not run away for some reason.
Even if caught, the girls who show a playful mischief are said to be 13 years old together.
Did they intend to dress up as a thief?
That's not the problem!
You're not in the mood to do it!
I'm not going to reflect on myself at all!
What's so funny?
Is this game for the girls to enjoy the thrill?
Piccadilly is not the type of person who would dry his tongue in this manner
Girls
Here I come
I'll write a letter to you all
But I'm writing to all of you
Is it okay for me to take you all?
It's not going to be good
The sound of the girls' adoration for the adults disappeared when Piccadilly threatened them.
Hey!
And Piccadilly got the phone call.
Hello?
I'm at the supermarket.
I caught two people with a slingshot.
Please tell them to come over.
It's so delicious!
You're not eating it!
The end of the story was so bad that Piccadilly was in the modern society.
It's so good!
That was the moment when Piccadilly returned to heaven.
I'm scared!
That big guy is so annoying!
The foreign man that Piccadilly marked as 2 meters tall
The product is in his hands
Immediately Piccadilly follows the foreign man
And he dives into the perfect position
It's always a scene that makes me feel sad
Stop it!
We heard that, but the wish did not reach him.
He put it in.
The item disappeared into the hat of a foreigner.
It was a crime that took advantage of a large body.
There are many such things.
Are you okay?
Yo yo yo yo, my name is Piccadilly.
Piccadilly is a name that comes from Kanagajikomi.
Piccadilly!
Piccadilly's brilliant self-confidence.
I'm a man! I'm a man!
The men who heard the noise are holding the foreigners back.
I'm a police officer! I'm a police officer!
The three men are always in danger and side by side.
The story of Piccadilly's decision was a flash in the pan.
But after this, the greatest trial awaits Piccadilly.
How was it?
I want to know how Piccadilly became Manbiki G-man.
I want to know that.
Actually, Piccadilly himself was the head of Manbiki.
Oh my!
So, he knows how much he should pull if he gets pulled.
Pulling hard.
Pulling hard?
He says pulling hard.
Pulling hard.
You say pulling hard.
Shut up!
You're too much.
It's because I'm stuck!
I'm so mean!
We're going home.
Wait, wait!
Can we go home?
We can go home, we're not angry.
We can't go home.
Sorry.
We're a little disappointed in the scene where you call out for a guy.
We happened to be out of the scene, so...
What do you do if he's not there?
We made him go home.
Until you call me a man, that's the truth.
What?
What is it?
He's calling you a man.
Until you call me a man, that's the truth.
He's a man.
Hikarerii Jikiden
Let's reveal the truth.
As a 2 meter tall man,
as a man with a blind eye,
could you grab Hikarerii's chest?
I see.
Please.
Oh!
I'm a man! I'm a man!
I'm a man!
That's enough.
I saw it on V.
I'm a man!
Mr. Kanegi, I understand.
We have just witnessed a miracle.
The one who is the most popular in the entertainment industry, the one who is said to be the most powerful, Yamazaki Hosei, has also been defeated in one moment.
Day 2 of the infiltration.
The person who was entrusted to Piccadilly that day was the manbiki Joshu who has been running the store for many years.
I wonder if it's okay to take off my clothes this time.
Let's go!
The reporter was surprised by Piccadilly's disguise.
What is this?
But that was the target.
He thought that a guy dressed like this wouldn't be able to win over 10,000 people.
It was a brilliant strategy that caught the opponent's attention.
It's crazy!
There's a limit to what you can do!
And finally, that time has come.
There she is! That woman!
This one?
Don't get it wrong!
Our reporter also took a look at her.
She was a woman who was surprisingly beautiful.
Certainly, the handbag is the same.
There is no doubt about the noise.
Hikaderi takes a distance from the woman so that she is not noticed.
I was noticed...
What is this?
It was at that time.
I was noticed.
I was noticed in front of Hikaderi.
I was able to say it well.
I'm not going to do anything bad.
I'm not a woman.
Will the woman leave the store without making any money?
Hurry up. Hurry up.
Hurry up.
Piccadilly is about to eat her.
Hey, brother.
I have something I haven't finished yet.
I didn't finish it just last night.
I made a mark on your back.
I see.
Then, shall we go?
It was a very bad situation.
The woman who was repeating the same thing for three months.
My life didn't go well at all.
I was stressed out.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
Okin.
Yes?
You're not saying anything.
What?
I'm not saying anything.
Then, I'll give you a massage.
That's not necessary.
I'll give you a big welcome in the future
You're so silly
The husband who received the call comes running
I'm sorry
The woman who kept her head down in the wife's mistake
Proved the bond between the couple
I'm sorry
Master
If you don't do it everyday, you'll get weak.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
I'll do it everyday.
Thank you.
Piccadilly solved the problems of the couple without even a single problem.
How amazing is his skill?
That was a wonderful scene.
How was it watching Matsumoto-san?
Well, there was a bit of a sexual harassment scene.
I think that was because he was winning the role that I was playing.
If you're going to dry your hair, I'll make you wet.
That's a low-class compliment.
I think he's trying to be cool.
I wonder why he's so hard on his shoulders.
Endo.
Yes.
You're a bad guy too.
No, I'm not.
You're right.
You're a good guy too.
What?
Are you angry?
This is a Pikachu.
You can't do that.
Say something nice.
Sorry, Endo.
I don't know.
Well then, Kiyaki! I love you!
Kiyaki is also a pervert.
Actually, this time, a guest has come to Piccadilly.
This person, please!
Piccadilly, my friend!
Actually, this is the first time that Piccadilly has been caught by a manbiki G-man.
He's a long time G-man.
Long time no see!
Piccadilly, how are you?
Because everybody loves you over there.
I know, I know.
But, you know, we gotta take my friend, yeah.
Okay.
Oh, you're going to take him?
Yes, sure, no problem, honey. Whenever you want.
But you know, seriously, really, please don't.
But in Canada, shall we go?
You know, we have a lot of friends.
That's all!
What?
Well, that's terrible.
If you're in snow, you're a man-bikini man.
The day of the emergency has come.
See you again.
Goodbye!
You've closed it with force.
I want to know how many times you'll do it.
Can I ask you a question?
Sure.
As usual,
there are times when you put seeds in the umeboshi of the onigiri, right?
You don't understand what I mean, do you?
What does that mean?
It's absolutely wrong!
Shut up!
It's absolutely wrong, isn't it?
No, no, no, no, no.
Hey, you know, that...
What? Are you angry because there are no seeds in it?
I ate a delicious rice ball the other day and there was a seed in it.
There are many people who get angry at that.
I will never get angry.
Shut up!
I go to the gallery sometimes.
I go to the front door.
I will never get angry.
You are very angry.
Why are you all angry at me?
I will never get angry.
Why?
I'm not angry at all.
Do you have seeds in convenience stores?
Where did you buy them?
There are many rice balls like udon or delivery.
Seeds.
Delivery?
Like delivery rice balls.
Udon, rice balls, salmon, plum, I ordered a lot of them.
You can't do that.
Don't I look like a student?