I'm standing in front of the signboard of the one-way street.
I've just heard that Hamada-san is in that hotel.
I'm very nervous right now.
I'd like to hear the truth about Natsumi Okawa.
There he is! Hamada-san! Hamada-san!
Hamada-san!
Let me ask you something!
What is it?
Is it true that Natsumi Okawa is good at playing the flute?
That's none of your business!
What is it?
What song is it?
Let me ask you something!
Is it true that Natsumi Okawa's nipples are black?
That's none of your business!
Did you hit me? Did you hit me?
Hamada-san! Let me ask you something!
What is it? What song is it?
What is it?
What program is it?
What right do you have to say such a thing?
It's Ruk Ruk Konnichiwa!
Move!
Ruk Ruk is over!
Let me ask you something!
Is it true that you broke your front teeth and made Sonoda-san pay for it?
That's none of your business!
What is it, Sonoda?
Don't move your eyes!
You idiot!
What are you doing?
Hamada-san!
Is it true that Natsumi Okawa's nipples are black?
They're not black!
What are you talking about?
Hamada-san!
Don't move your eyes!
Do you really have to say such a thing?
As you heard, Hamada-san acknowledged everything.
I'm glad.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Good evening.
Actually, I was supposed to do a skit here today.
But I had a lot of things to do.
So I changed the subject.
Why do you have to do skits?
I've already given up on the name Dandan.
Really?
It's Nikonsha Kikonsha.
So I thought I'd give it a try.
It's your time from now on.
You know what?
I've already figured out how to deal with people.
Really?
Just now, I had a letter on my desk.
I opened it.
It said, congratulations.
That's not good.
Well, from now on, do your best at work in Tokyo.
Well!
It doesn't matter how you read it.
Even Mutsuru's letter says, well!
Well!
To be honest, this program is a little messy, isn't it?
Actually, we're already shooting on Tuesdays.
That's right.
There's supposed to be a long one.
But we'll have to postpone it to next year.
You don't have to do that.
Just let it go.
Today's part will be released next week.
Today's part will be released next Tuesday.
It's like I was chased by a reporter during the opening.
Don't go that far.
It's a waste.
But it's warmer than you think, isn't it?
It's my first time today.
That's right.
I had a hard time, too.
I'm a partner, so I knew it.
The fact that the ceremony was held in October.
But this is a top secret from the company.
Don't tell anyone.
The staff here knew about it, too.
That's right.
The staff here knew about Yuya Nittere's news.
I don't know if Yuya got a little bit of it.
I don't know if it was a joke, but they kept it a secret.
I kept it a secret from my close friends, too.
Nevertheless, your couple is a little weird.
What?
In Osaka dialect, the weak ones here are called Itai.
Your couple is Itai.
I don't want to hide it.
I'm trying my best not to tell anyone.
It's pretty proud.
I'm sitting side by side with the Shinkansen from Osaka to Tokyo.
What are you talking about?
I don't know what you're talking about.
We're not on the same train.
There are a lot of fans in Osaka.
I ran to them and said,
Hamada-san, what are you doing?
I'm sitting side by side with Natsumi Ogawa and the Shinkansen.
We're wearing the same clothes.
That's why it's Itai.
It's Itai.
That's not true.
It's not true, but I don't cry.
It's just a matter of time before they find out.
But like you said,
I didn't really try to hide it.
You didn't try to hide it.
We're wearing the same clothes.
What kind of clothes are we wearing?
We're wearing the same leather jacket.
We're sitting side by side.
What is this?
It's hot.
That's not true.
If you do that, they'll find you.
I don't know why they found me.
Why did they find you?
That's because your father is Itai.
Everyone in my family is Itai.
Your father doesn't like to hide things.
But if they find out, they'll think it's not true.
He must have come from somewhere else.
What?
He must have said something.
My father is a painter.
He's bragging about how he painted the Soviet Union.
Do you know about the Soviet Union?
It's red and white.
You painted that, didn't you?
It's just two colors.
Anyone can do it.
You're a big idiot.
I painted it from top to bottom.
You could have painted it beautifully.
I gathered my colleagues at work.
When I told them not to talk about marriage,
I said, I'm going to Tokyo tomorrow.
My colleagues at work asked me why.
I said, I'm going to marry my son.
That's a different story.
It was a lie.
I thought it was bad.
From October until now,
I thought it was a pity.
I thought I didn't know anything.
Everyone knows you're not a virgin.
This is amazing.
At this point?
At this point.
It's not true.
It's true, but it's not true at all.
I don't know.
It's a lie.
I don't think I'm 100% wrong.
I can't say anything.
I don't think you're wrong.
I'm wearing a bra.
Why?
What's wrong?
How many girls do you have?
I don't know.
It's a pity.
What's wrong?
You're 26 years old.
What?
Why are you in such a hurry?
There's a lot of things.
What?
It's not that I'm in a hurry.
There's a lot of things.
Yes, that's right.
It's not that I'm in a hurry.
Why is it not that I'm in a hurry?
What?
Isn't it?
I don't care about your story.
I heard it.
I knew you were married, but I didn't expect you to be called P-chan at home.
I felt sorry for you.
My back was broken.
What do you mean P-chan?
What are you talking about?
I didn't expect you to be called that.
I didn't expect that.
You don't have to say that.
But I heard a lot of things about you.
I heard that you were called as a single.
When I was with my girlfriend?
Everyone called me Matsumoto-kun.
My girlfriend is very strict.
Like Matsumoto-kun.
Matsumoto-shi.
It's written in the book.
It's not Matsumoto-shi.
But you didn't say anything.
What?
You wanted to talk about it.
About what?
I'm really strict.
I'm more strict than Golgo 13.
I don't talk at all.
But you two are very soft.
That's enough.
I thought it was amazing that you didn't come out of your house.
I thought you would go somewhere.
I thought the world was cold.
I was on the radio in Osaka yesterday.
It was late at night.
There were a lot of fans in the cold mountains.
At the gate.
I was wondering how many people would come to my party.
I got in the car.
There were only two people.
There were less people than usual.
There were less people.
We are completely separated now.
Did you see it?
I talked about it the night before.
At 10 a.m. on the next day.
I was working at Yoshimoto Kaikan.
I was the only one there.
I got off the taxi with my manager.
A reporter came to me.
I said congratulations.
A girl was in the outside car.
Liar!
Screaming.
I was talking.
Liar!
It was amazing.
I was watching.
I don't think you can cheat.
I don't think so.
I see.
You don't like girls when you are married?
I don't think so.
What do you think?
It doesn't matter.
Liar!
I will get angry again.
In a sense.
For a fan.
When you are married, you are calm.
I don't know.
What do you mean?
You are calm.
There is a monitor.
You can watch with peace of mind.
If you are not married, you are not calm.
You can say that.
You are not calm.
I am not calm at all.
Liar!
What?
That's good.
Liar!
I have been writing fan letters.
Mr. Matsumoto.
Don't blame me.
I don't blame you.
I won't do it for 10 years.
The girl I like is in elementary school.
How do you know that?
What kind of school do you want to go to?
I don't know.
I want you to be happy.
Let me introduce the letters.
Please bring it.
This is the assistant girl.
I feel good today.
She applied for this program.
How old are you?
22 years old.
You are cute.
You are an amateur, right?
You haven't done this before, right?
This is the first time.
You are brave.
Who was your ex-girlfriend?
She was my ex-girlfriend until the day before yesterday.
I don't know what you are talking about.
I'll tell you later.
Thank you.
Later?
You are brave.
You are a model.
Let me introduce the letters.
What are you doing on your day off?
This is a simple question.
How is your day off?
What is that?
What is your day off?
Leave me alone.
I have a letter.
I have been sleeping until the evening.
With whom?
Who is sleeping with me?
I'm sleeping alone until the evening.
Are you sleeping alone?
Aren't you sleeping together?
What?
You don't have a girlfriend like that.
You are sleeping alone, aren't you?
What?
Are you sleeping apart?
Your wife is 18 years old.
I don't understand.
Why are you sleeping apart?
It depends on the situation.
Shut up.
Let's move on.
This person is from Yokohama.
His pen name is Frillman.
Frillman is a fun program.
Why did it end?
I don't know.
This program is good.
This is a story I saw on the 5th of December.
I thought.
The reason why fans come to Matsumoto's house.
Matsumoto is a good person.
Even if he is angry, he is not powerful.
If he is angry, he will be beaten up.
He knows his girlfriend is there.
So he can't enter the house.
Did you know that?
Why?
Because Matsumoto is a good person?
No.
Why?
But I will be bullied in the future.
You have been bullied, haven't you?
I haven't told you yet.
If I tell you, you will be angry.
You will say, I want to do it too.
I couldn't tell you.
I haven't told you in Osaka.
I hated Matsumoto the most.
I was tired and went home.
I didn't sleep well for two days.
I thought I would sleep at home today.
I was sleeping alone.
At about 2 o'clock in the morning.
There was a fire somewhere.
I was getting closer.
I went to the 10th floor of the apartment.
It was very noisy.
I thought it was a big fire.
I opened the door and looked down.
There was a fire truck lined up.
In your apartment?
Yes.
I was wondering if it was upstairs or downstairs.
I thought it was in this apartment.
The fire truck came up.
Firefighters came.
Matsumoto.
It's a fire, isn't it?
I said, I'm coming.
There was a report.
The fire truck came in.
The fire truck came to the window of my house.
I couldn't do that.
I don't know what I should do.
I thought the fireman should come home.
I called him.
Yes.
He said, if you get in through the window, you'll be surprised.
I said that's wrong.
Then he said, the fireman wouldn't come out.
I said.
That's right.
Even though it's meaningless.
I didn't mean to come out.
It just came out.
I was shocked when I heard that.
I couldn't sleep for a while.
Do you want to go to Osaka-ben?
Osaka-ben?
That's right.
I'm wearing a postcard like this.
I don't know if it's going to decrease from now on.
Because there is such a thing.
It's increasing for you.
What are you talking about?
You're definitely right.
Even if I get married, I'll still be popular.
You should think so.
I got it now.
I can't do it.
My staff said,
No, you can't do it anymore.
If it's a staff,
I'll say, no, it's not like that.
There are fans of Hamada.
I'm going to give you a gift.
I'm sweating.
My friends told me to talk.
I went to the internet to talk.
I don't know.
I was wondering if you were curious.
Nan-chan
I don't know what you're talking about.
I feel like I'm sleeping.
You talk clearly.
You're really sitting down.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Nan-chan,
You should practice your pronunciation.
I've known Nan-chan for a long time.
I've talked a lot.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Don't say it with your face.
I don't know what you're saying.
I'm not good at it.
Sometimes I think,
But I'm not good at it.
You're aiming.
I'm going to Osaka-ben.
I'm going to Osaka-ben for the last time today.
I don't know what to think.
Today, we have a lot of things that are thick.
For example, there are thin things, right?
Thin.
Thin things are thin here and in Osaka, right?
What is really thin?
Thick and thin.
We call it thick and thin, right?
I think everyone knows by now.
Even thinner than that!
What do you call it?
What do you call thick and thin in Tokyo?
Super thin.
Super thin?
What do you call it?
Super thin!
This is super thin!
We call it super!
Super!
We call it super in Osaka.
The health teacher calls it super.
Super thin.
And on top of that you call it super thin.
What do you call it more thin?
What do you call it?
Super!
We call it super thin!
Ah, is that so?
So thin, super thin.
And then we have super thick!
We call it super thick.
Super thick!
Super thick and thin!
I don't know much about this, but I'd like you to remember this word, monogotsui, today.
That's right, monogotsui.
That's all for today.
Okay.
How should I answer this?
That's right. How should we answer this?
If we ask, what is thin?
It's thin.
Why?
It's very thin.
It's gotsui hosoi.
Okay, then.
What is thin?
Why aren't you saying anything?
What?
I think there are a lot of Hamada fans here today.
Why?
What is thin?
It's thin.
Say it properly.
What is very thin?
It's gotsui hosoi.
Say it properly.
What is very thin?
It's gotsui hosoi.
Say it properly.
Thank you very much.
Let's see you next time.
I've wanted to do this for a long time.
It's been a long time.
But I don't know what to do.
This is...
When I say it once, it's like this.
It's okay, right?
That's right.
I think we'll break up by the end of next year.
But both of them are stupid.
But there might be someone who thinks so.
I think so.
Oh, you don't think so?
How much do you think so?
That's right.
Next year, I want to do as much as I can.
As I said, next year is the first day of the new year.
I want to show myself in front of everyone.
I'll take a break once a year.
That's right.
From the next week.
From January 9th.
I want to show myself in front of everyone.
That's right.
Maybe you can do it.
What?
It would be fun if it was like this.
Thank you very much.
Let's meet again next January 9th.
Goodbye.
Thank you very much.
This program was brought to you by Oyama International Products,
Sunluck,
and Zoyosui.