Where are you going today?
I don't know where, but I'm going to cut my hand off from Nittere next April.
This year, right?
Yes, this year.
Today, I'm going to Yokohama.
I'm going to be 3rd, so I'm going to be Mineshitero.
I don't need this kind of thing.
Don't mess with me.
I'm not good at carrying things like that.
I'm sorry that I was here before.
I'm not going to be fooled by this kind of thing.
Hey, don't you guys have an appointment?
Why don't you do it with just one T-shirt?
It's snowing, so don't make a mess.
Goodbye, rotten Gedo Taku.
Well, if the guest is also a rotten Gedo, the staff is also a rotten Gedo.
Here it is.
Today's venue, Sōtetsu Honda Theater.
Yes.
Let's go in here.
Bring this set to this small place.
Look at the staff.
What are we going to do today?
Today, we're going to do a skit.
It's a little nostalgic.
I'm going to do something nostalgic.
It's a skit that used to be popular.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's a skit from that time.
I'd like to do it.
It's just the right feeling.
After that, I'll send you a lot of live broadcasts in three and a half hours.
Please look forward to it until the end.
This program is brought to you by Sunluck and Oyama International Products.
Sponsored by the sponsor you are watching.
I've already won.
What?
What are you doing?
Stop it.
I've already won.
What?
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Stop it.
It's too early to get excited.
I've already won.
Who are you?
Stop it.
What are you doing?
Who are you?
Stop it.
Die.
You shouldn't do such a bad thing.
You are weak.
I'm not afraid even if you look at me like that.
Go away.
I won't look at you.
Thank you.
It was hard for you today.
What?
Thank you for coming today.
It's snowing for the first time in four years.
I've never seen that much snow in Osaka.
I was surprised.
It's hard to find the place.
Here?
Are you all from Yokohama?
I always come here by taxi.
I don't know where it is.
I don't think it's on the third floor.
I was walking alone.
I became a hamako in five minutes.
Are you kidding me?
How can you get used to it so easily?
Hamako?
When I came here by car, it snowed a lot.
I stopped driving because it was snowing.
So I came here an hour earlier than usual.
I was in the pachinko shop of the president.
Don't do that.
It's embarrassing.
Don't do embarrassing things.
I came here as soon as I finished work.
No one noticed you were in the pachinko shop.
No one noticed me.
All the shop assistants were there.
They were from different departments.
Departments?
Some of them were from different departments.
It was snowing a lot.
There were about 80 ambulances.
For that?
For that.
There were injured people and people who fell down and had to go to the hospital.
I saw it on the news.
It's embarrassing.
It's in the neighborhood.
It's all in the neighborhood.
There are old people who die every year.
It's cool.
But I can't stand it.
It's not good.
People know the end of their life.
God has decided it.
Who said that?
I did.
Why?
It's decided.
It's not decided by others.
I can't believe what I said.
If someone said it was written in a book, everyone would accept it.
It's all decided.
Who said it?
I didn't.
I didn't come here to see this.
It was decided when I was born.
It can't be.
You think so, don't you?
Why do you say that?
Why do you think so?
I did research like that.
Where?
When?
I read the book.
I know it.
Is there such a book?
Yes.
I'm better than Tanba Tetsuro.
There is a spirit world.
There is no hole.
What is there?
When humans and animals die, they go into the egg bag.
Are you stupid?
Why do they die?
Why do they go into the egg bag?
I don't know.
This is a serious story.
Wait a minute.
What kind of state is it to go into the egg?
It's a human body.
It becomes a soul and goes into the egg.
It goes into the egg in this way.
You were born as a human being.
If you die, you will be born as a dog.
Then you go into the dog's egg.
Then you will be born as a dog.
The dog will mate and then I will go into the egg.
That's how it goes around.
Tanba Tetsuro is lying.
I want to talk to Tanba Tetsuro.
About that.
I will win.
Animals say they feel sorry for animals.
If the lion eats the animal, it will be a wild kingdom.
If the lion eats the deer, it will be a great deer.
That's right.
The deer will eat the lion of the animal.
It's a brave deer.
If you look at the wild kingdom, the lion runs and goes to the deer herd.
If my mother sees it, she will say,
I feel sorry for the deer, run away.
I feel sorry for anyone who sees it.
I feel sorry for the human emotions.
Who are you?
Even if the deer is bitten by a lion, it doesn't hurt.
That's right.
That's what you think.
If you are bitten by a lion, it hurts.
The deer doesn't hurt just because you think it hurts.
That's not true.
If you are bitten by a lion, it hurts.
The deer is like that.
Why doesn't it hurt?
It's an animal, so it doesn't hurt.
There is no feeling of pain.
That's not true.
If you hit a dog or a cat, it will hurt.
No one says it hurts.
That's what you think.
If you look at the face, you can see it.
That's not true.
They don't care about the face.
That's what you think.
Are you laughing?
Is that so?
When the lion bites the deer,
Does the deer look like this?
That's what you think.
If you are bitten by a lion, you run away.
There is no reason to run away.
Why?
The deer is awake.
Let's go.
What will happen?
The deer is awake.
That's not true.
If you are bitten by a lion, it hurts.
If the deer dies and becomes a human,
It will enter the human body.
That's why the deer is running around.
That's not true.
I don't care.
When I got on the Shinkansen,
There was a man sitting behind me.
He was reading a book he wrote.
I thought he was reading a book.
I have a letter.
Today is great.
What is great?
The content of the letter is great.
There are two people today.
This is great.
Oh my god.
Are you brothers?
Which one is your sister?
How many siblings do you have?
What are you guys?
I'm scared.
How many siblings do you have?
Really? Why?
I have an aunt.
You have an aunt?
Look at me.
Really?
I think I saw it.
Dad.
You have an aunt.
I don't know.
You look like a bad father.
Thank you very much.
If you can wear this, please come out.
I'm sorry.
Let me introduce you.
I have a request for you two.
Please make me your disciple.
It's not a joke.
It's a lifelong request.
I really ask you.
I watch all your programs.
I'm a sixth grader.
That's right.
Disciple.
It's about time.
Why?
It's been eight or nine years since I entered this world.
It's been nine years.
Disciple.
I have nothing to do.
I'm just a disciple.
That's right.
Yes.
I go buy juice.
You're a bad boy.
I have nothing to ask.
I go buy juice.
I'm just a disciple.
I have nothing to teach you.
That's right.
I can't teach you to talk like this.
Well, you can think about it.
Next?
Please tell us each other's habits.
If there is anything you want to stop with that habit, please tell us.
Habits! Habits!
What about me?
You have a habit of sleeping anywhere.
No, I don't.
This is not an exaggeration to say that you have a habit.
That's not true.
It doesn't matter where you can sleep.
Well, I sleep too much anywhere.
I sleep in the dressing room all the time.
I can really fall into a deep sleep.
I think that's amazing.
Oh, really?
It's deep.
I also snore and talk in the dressing room.
Are you kidding me?
I do.
I sometimes sneeze in the dressing room.
I can't do that.
I also sneeze in the dressing room.
He is happy when he sleeps.
He usually sleeps like this.
But he is like this.
If you don't like it, don't sleep.
You are like that.
What?
You are snoring but your eyes are open.
It's disgusting.
Your eyes are open.
He is like this.
He is sleeping.
This is true.
Right?
Don't you snore?
I sometimes snore.
My eyes are open.
Yes.
My eyes are completely open.
It's true.
It's scary.
It's the first time.
It's true.
When I sleep with a girl...
It's scary, isn't it?
Over there.
Yes, sometimes.
Even if I say, right?
Yes.
It's true.
I was told,
What?
I couldn't say,
but when I woke up in the morning,
my eyes were open.
That's true.
Even if you didn't wake me up,
I was scared.
Yes.
My eyes are open.
I thought my eyes were open.
Yes.
At that time,
I wanted to stare at you.
Don't joke with me.
You're a fool.
I was scared.
And you two were hot.
You're a fool.
Don't joke with me.
Yes, it's true.
What else?
There was one good thing.
What is it?
I couldn't imitate you.
What are you talking about?
You can do it.
What?
I have a hundred of them.
You have a hundred of them.
You have more than I do.
I don't have a hundred of them.
Everyone knows that I imitate.
I don't know.
I've never done it before.
I've never tried to imitate.
It's easy to imitate.
Teach me how to imitate.
Did you teach me?
Yes.
Good.
How to do it.
What do you want to do?
What number do you want to do?
Number 35.
It's Lupin.
Is it true?
It's true.
It's Lupin.
Teach me.
This is...
How do you do it?
What?
Do you do it with your mouth?
Yes.
How do I say?
It's a wave.
I've done it before.
It goes up and down and up and down again.
It's like this.
I didn't put the energy into it.
You let out your hand.
I let out my hand.
If you let out your hand, it goes up.
I said, Lupin!
Then, you can't laugh.
I'm not laughing.
It goes up.
What do you do?
I said, Lupin!
Does it look like it?
I let out my hand.
It looks like Lupin.
I really wanted to imitate Lupin.
It's good.
It goes up.
FUJIKO-CHAN!
Oh my!
Oh my! FUJIKO-CHAN!
You're funny!
You can't get money!
Number two!
This is a gift from SAIJO.
Really?
Really!
What did you do?
This is a bit difficult.
I have to put a lot of pressure on my throat.
Really?
Then try it.
It's frustrating!
Are you watching?
That's right.
What is that?
That's what I'm saying.
It's frustrating.
What did you do?
This is a bit difficult.
It's good.
Really?
It's frustrating.
FUJIKO-CHAN!
Are you watching?
It's fine.
You do something!
What did you do?
It's fine.
It's a new one.
There are a lot of people who can only be seen in Osaka.
For example?
Like NOSUKE from ASIAKAN.
You don't know him, right?
UME-SAN!
Who is UME-SAN?
He is the best.
He is number one.
The first person I remembered was UME-SAN.
From here, I started to walk the royal road.
I want to walk!
The royal road.
UME-SAN.
Everyone, close your eyes.
Don't draw UME-SAN on your head.
Let's draw UME-SAN.
Let's go.
Let's draw.
HIIROSHI!
What is this?
From the first time.
Have you done everything?
I've done everything.
What was the last thing you massaged?
The 108th one?
The 108th one means最近.
Yes, yes.
I don't know this anymore.
What is it?
He is my relative.
You are doing such a repertoire.
Of course.
You can't do that with 1 million yen.
Who is it now?
He is my relative.
I was told.
UME-SAN, you can't do that.
What?
What do you want me to do?
What are you talking about?
HANA-CHAN, what are you talking about?
Why?
What do you want me to do?
You can't do it properly.
Don't say that to others.
HIIROSHI!
What?
You don't have anything.
That's not cool.
That's why I said HIIROSHI.
I see.
HIIROSHI!
What is it?
I want to cry.
That's all for today. Thank you very much.
It's over.
Yes, it's over.
What happened?
It was cold today.
It was cold, wasn't it?
We only had one tough day.
It was hard.
I thought we were going to retire.
Next week.
What are you going to wear next week?
I'm going to wear an SM school uniform.
Yes!
I want to knit.
That's why everyone wears glasses like this.
It's not dirty.
I don't know if the camera can take it well.
That's because I have a whip in one hand.
The image quality is good.
I'm going to knit.
Let's let NITTAR drive.
Our manager NITTAR.
I'm going to put it on Twitter.
Next week, NITTAR ATSUO,
Downtown's manager NITTAR ATSUO,
He's going to wear an SM school uniform.
We'll be on the same team.
When NITTAR ATSUO's downtown manager was decided,
The head office told him,
You're in trouble from now on.
I know what that means.
That's what I'm going to do.
I hope you understand.
That's it.
That's it for today.
Thank you for watching.