The first episode of the Gaggenau Skyar episode!
The 24 hour round interview!
We've done it with Jimmy-chan too.
Yes, what was the name of this?
It was the first time with Yamami-san, right?
Yes, we did it with Jimmy-san.
And with Suzuki-san.
Yes, yes.
Earlier, the main character of today, the camera was coming this way, so I told him to move.
And he had this kind of face.
Yes, he was like this.
I'm sorry but I'm a bit scared.
I have to call them.
I've already booked them.
Let's go.
Today's star is Nadal!
Hello!
Please stop being so close.
No, no.
You're going to be like that.
No, no. You're a weirdo.
Weirdo?
I was really worried about what you said on the show.
I feel like I'm going to wait in front of my house after I get rich.
Like a door to a yakuza.
Don't say that.
Scary, scary.
Are you okay?
Do you think of me as your senior?
I think of you as my senior.
I respect you.
I want to be like you.
I want to change.
Then, please apologize to the downtown on Wednesday.
This is bad.
The 4th year of the group, the Chikichiki Peppers have conquered the King of Contest.
But, if you ask if they are currently in a great success, they are not.
There is a problem with Nadal in the first episode.
To find out the truth, Nadal's true face will be revealed in a long interview.
On the day of the interview, the sky was blessed.
The hotel in Shiodome, Tokyo.
Nadal will be naked for 24 hours in a day.
But...
After the scheduled time, Nadal came.
Nadal, you're so sudden.
In the end, he came an hour later.
So sudden?
You're really something.
He was late, and he was at the scene of the drama.
We're late for the show.
I'm just a little late.
Thank you.
You're late.
The rain...
What?
I'm not kidding.
I don't know how it's going to be.
I can't take it anymore.
I've been waiting since 9am.
Right?
The interview is based on this year's report.
He will talk about his life and future.
I'm really happy.
It's a chance to get to know myself by saying 24 hours.
I'm looking forward to it.
Your face is like...
Today, we will ask you everything.
Yes.
Please answer honestly and without lying.
I will tell you everything that I have been told.
Yes.
The 24-hour curtain that Nadal talks about openly has opened.
What was it like to be born as Nadal?
I was told that I was cute
Like a baby?
Yes, like I don't want to be seen
In 1984, Nadal was born as the eldest son of three siblings
Oh, Nadal!
What is your real name?
My real name?
Well, I have a reason to do it.
What is it?
I'm doing it in Nadal, so I have a reason to do it.
I think it's a bad idea to do it in Nadal.
I think it's okay.
I don't know how many times I've done it.
I'm doing it in Nadal as a comedian.
Can I ask you a question?
Sure.
What is your name?
My real name is Aiu-ra Hideki.
Aiu-ra Hideki?
That's a pretty unique name.
That's right.
It's a common name.
I heard that I was the vassal of the Uesugi family of the Uesugi family.
Really?
The ancestors of the Aiu-ra family are the vassals who served the great name of the Sengoku family, the Uesugi family.
My dad told me that.
Really?
I don't think so.
I don't know if he really said that.
But I heard that he said that in the lyrics.
I don't need to doubt him anymore.
He was originally from a military family.
He was a soldier, but he was a soldier.
He was a farmer.
What is that?
His family is from Minami-Yamashiro village, the only village in Kyoto.
It's a small village with a population of about 2800 people.
Minami-Yamashiro village.
The new town in this village.
New town?
It's developing in this village.
It's a new residential area.
What is new town?
In Minamiyama Shirobura, there are various districts.
There are Dosenbo, Tayama, and Takao.
There is a place called New Town.
Is New Town a famous place?
Everyone calls it that.
It's not a famous place.
Please do it.
Since he was young, he has been a scary father to Nadar.
His name is Seichiro.
He looks like his father.
Father, do you have any memories of the first episode?
Can I say it now?
But when I was born, my penis was pulled out.
When I was ready to do something, I used to wash my penis with soap.
I had no feelings.
But when I looked around, I saw that my penis was not washed properly.
I thought I could wash it by pulling out my penis.
I said, it hurts!
I thought, oh!
I was pulled out when I didn't feel pain.
Don't make a self-reflection!
If this male child is born,
When I was born, I wanted to wash my eyes clean.
Speaking of your father, there is a TV show about something and a topic called Inaba no Monoki.
Naderu, whose father Seichiro collects something and keeps it in his storage, is teased on TV every now and then, but he never tries to break his mouth.
What's in that?
I said it's impossible.
It's impossible.
It's scary.
I have to interview.
Why are you so beautiful?
Do you know what's in it?
Of course I know.
Why?
It's a promise.
I don't know why I'm wearing this.
I'm scared.
But now it's like that.
If you can stop the camera.
The people behind the camera are like new.
They're like, don't do it.
Since he became a man of his word, he has always liked living things.
He was attracted to the turtle that was raised in the pond and decided to go to a nursery.
At that time, in the nursery, did you feel uncomfortable about the environment?
I was so stupid that I was crying when I found out that there was a rule.
I didn't know what the rule was.
I didn't know there was a sound.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know what I'm saying.
I have to do something.
I'm crying all the time.
He was a child who was running away from difficult things.
When he was in elementary school, he became bright about other problems.
I'm a little tired.
Did you get good grades in elementary school?
I think it was better.
I think I became more intelligent from the 5th grade.
I didn't feel calm until the 4th grade.
I ran around during my break time.
I ran naked when I noticed.
You ran alone?
I said, wow!
You were cute like that.
I climbed the highest part of the hill.
I was a little bit nervous, but I was able to get up and help my grandmother.
I felt that my life was not normal since I was in elementary school.
I'm annoyed.
I was a college student when I started teaching comedians.
I didn't know anything about comedians.
Did you watch any new comedians?
I didn't have a chance to watch them.
Did your father stop you?
Yes, my father.
Why did he tell you not to watch it?
Because I would become a fool.
He spent his childhood with no interest in comedy.
He eventually became a teenager who was aware of his opposite sex.
I hardly talked to girls in middle school.
You didn't realize it?
I was simply rejected by all the girls.
What are you talking about?
I raised my hand during class and the teacher said to lower your hand.
I raised my hand and the teacher said,
You know what I mean, right?
You don't even have to raise your hand.
I was disappointed.
I was disappointed when I was wrong.
Why did you raise your hand?
I went to the toilet and there were no shoes.
I was a real Izumi.
The reason was a test soon after the entrance of the school.
The seat in front of the hallway is mine.
I said, let's start the test.
When I said, let's start, a girl said, wait a minute, teacher.
Even though the chime is ringing, a female student who came to the classroom late.
Yesterday I said, I'm not studying at all.
I said, no, no, no.
I said, Chaimu, you shouldn't be in the class.
You're the one studying, right?
She said, yeah, but I'm sleeping.
She was acting like she was having fun.
I got angry.
Everyone was waiting.
So I said,
You, stop it.
You, everyone's waiting for you.
You, you're the one studying, right?
I don't know if you're doing this because you think it's funny, but you should quit studying and go to school.
I said that a lot.
Then, the girl suddenly grabbed the textbook and hit it on the hallway.
She looked at me and said,
I was going to go to school now.
I thought it was my fault.
I was nervous and I was testing myself.
But I started to be bullied from the next day.
I was the leader.
The 100-day competition was really hard.
There was a 100-day competition after the winter break.
If I could win the competition, something might change in this.
I remember 100 people round very well.
And the 100 people round competition started.
I was so excited.
I was the first one.
I was like, what the hell?
The moment I took the picture, the girl touched my hand.
I took the picture first.
The girl said, no!
The gym was full of people.
No!
They were all going crazy.
There were three teachers.
What did you do?
I said I didn't do anything.
I've been doing this for 100 days.
I don't think I can do anything.
I said I didn't do anything.
Why did this happen?
I didn't do anything.
As I was talking, I realized that the woman touched me.
I said I didn't do anything.
It started again.
There was another woman.
He was looking at me, and he was looking at me.
He said, I'll wash you after I get out of the soap.
I was like, what?
I couldn't say anything.
I was so angry.
You were so angry.
I'm glad I was able to enter.
It's so hot that I might get caught.
That's terrible.
3 and a half hours have passed since the start.
With the hope of being able to continue, they head to the next stop, which is their hobby.
A hobby?
Of course, while they're on the move, the interview continues.
The weather is...
How do you refresh yourself in your room?
Not outside.
I put my face on the pillow.
I'm tired.
It's been 2 or 3 hours.
What do you want to do after 2 or 3 hours?
I'm sorry.
I might be sleeping.
You are sleeping.
He has a hobby of fishing.
He is a real man.
Wow, that's amazing.
Thank you.
It's perfect.
Yes, it's all in here.
Here, we hear stories from his university days.
After graduating from high school,
he wanted to work in the fish farm,
and other related jobs related to fishery.
He decided to study fishery at the university.
Were you interested in comedy at that time?
I got interested in it when I was in college.
That's why I started it.
The first time I watched it, it was an all-darts comic.
But the giraffe comic was so funny.
I thought, there are so many interesting people.
At that time, did you want to be a comedian?
This is not good.
He is always in the mood and asks many questions.
You're so mean!
At least if you can catch fish, you can draw pictures.
You like it, don't you?
Even after 2 hours, he can't catch anything.
You can't catch anything, can you?
Well, I can't catch anything during the day.
Was it better at night?
Yes, I think I was better at night.
If you want to be a night person, then you should be a night person.
I want to calm my back and do an interview.
Looking at Kirin's comic, the university era began to be interested in comedians.
I wanted to go to the Department of Fisheries, especially the aquarium.
I wanted to be a comedian, but I didn't have enough money.
So I started to work as a waiter.
You were a waiter?
I worked as a waiter in the kitchen.
He spent his days in a daze because of his job.
But when he was 25, he suddenly found a way to be a comedian.
I didn't know that.
We were all in the same class, and we were going to go out for a drink and then go home.
One of my friends told me,
I want you to try acting as an entertainer.
He was my friend from college.
If you don't want to do it, you can try it.
You can do anything if you want to get a job.
Just try it once.
That's how I started.
Why did you start acting as a comedian?
I don't know why, but I was told it was fun.
It's important, so please tell us more.
I had a friend who had a ostrich.
I went to get the ostrich eggs.
They said, please get the ostrich eggs.
I said OK.
There were about 20 ostriches in the cage.
All the ostriches followed me.
No matter how much I tried to get them,
they all followed me even though it was night.
I couldn't get the eggs.
That's how it was.
As far as I know, he was 25 years old and entered Osaka NSC with a very comfortable feeling.
Of course, he was not so sweet as a comedian.
In 2010, he entered Osaka NSC at the age of 25.
I knew that there were many interesting people when I entered Osaka NSC.
I wanted to do the opening ceremony.
I thought that it was not so funny if it was the opening ceremony.
This is a terrible thing to say.
I was talking to Mr. Ueda of Cream Chou.
This is bad.
This is a good thing.
I was doing the opening ceremony when I just started to enter the entertainment industry.
I had a car, so I put a prop on it.
I went to Hoshimi.
Is that what you call a break?
That is also a break.
After learning various break and laughter, Nadal gradually gained strength.
In 2012, he formed Korochiki Peppers with his 7 year old classmate Nishino.
Nadal talked about the making of the story of Korochiki in an interview in the daytime.
I'm doing half and half for the story.
We fight and fight and fight.
There are times when it's hard, but something is connected.
It's hard to do that much story.
I can't do it alone.
The two of them are struggling to make a good story.
In just four years of formation, they conquered the King of Contest and broke it at once.
I was really happy
The next year, he moved to Tokyo and continued his activities
But Nadal is still not satisfied
I don't think I can be satisfied with my current state
I can't laugh
You have to think about your laughter all the time
I heard that Matsumoto-san went somewhere and said that he was still in the second round.
Are you thinking about it?
I thought about it and I didn't think about it.
What are you talking about?
I think that Matsumoto-san should go through this.
You're proud of that?
I think that he should run on the same path.
I think about the kind of laughter I can get.
What kind of laughter do you want to hear?
I think about that.
At the beginning, the entrance was very wide. There were many kinds of laughter.
I made a lot of mistakes.
I was making a lot of mistakes.
That's why I'm in the DL.
I was caught in such a moment.
It's scary.
It's that difficult.
The interview is still less than half an hour.
The first time the show started, he lost his energy and his expression is still the same.
What are you doing?
The 24 hour long interview will be broadcasted on the second half of Zaiharan.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
And the one who followed Ueda's down.
I think that's a bit far.
It's really weird.
I've been cut off somewhere.
There was a part where I could do it even if it wasn't funny.
There's a Ueda-san from the cream shop.
In the meantime, there was a very rich story.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
To check, when I look back on the vtr.
I don't think it's that funny if it's just Shikiri
If you say Shikiri...
Well, Ueda-san from Cream Chou
He didn't edit at all
But Nadal's life continues
So, Shikiri can be funny
But there's a ridiculous Shikiri, Ueda-san
It doesn't have to be funny
As long as there's poop
No, no, no
It's not funny yet
Wait a minute!
I'm sorry!
I didn't say anything that was good enough to explain!
The 24 hour long interview is over!
The alcohol is in, and Nadal is attacked by the water horse.
This is tough.
Eh, it's red!
It's dripping from the front!
Nadal-san?
Will he be able to do the 24 hour long interview?
Oke, Nap time.