In the 1st episode of Gaki no Tsukaya, we have the staff of Chikishiki Beauty Otose, Kudoki Tekugasse!
Today, we have the staff of Kudoki Tekugasse.
I see.
He's from the industry, so he should be very good at seducing women.
And he likes women.
He likes women.
He's from the industry.
That's right. So today, I wonder what the men on TV will say.
I see. I've never seen a woman like this before.
It's like a model.
I see.
That's what I wanted to show in the opening.
In that sense, the people sitting over there are the staff.
They're sleeping lions.
But Mr. Matsumoto, the person on the far left is sleeping.
That's right.
The staff of Kudoki Tekugasse, Kudoki Tekugasse.
Ouch.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
First, we meet at the hook.
We meet.
We meet and we try to get her to come over for a cup of tea.
We take her out for a drink.
And then from here...
The last one is this way.
We have to take her to our room.
There's a bed.
That's right.
There's nothing in the room.
But I think there are two steps.
I see.
I took her to my room.
It's a problem until she comes here.
It's probably impossible for her to come here suddenly.
That's right.
This is what you usually do.
It's okay if you do it.
It doesn't matter if you don't do it.
Mr. Matsumoto.
Yes.
Top batter.
That's right.
I was thinking about who to choose.
This is Mr. Yamazaki.
I see.
I think it's best to teach her.
Let's go to the top batter, Mr. Yamazaki.
Ready.
What are you doing?
Do you know me?
I don't know you.
It's dirty.
Do you know Downtown?
Downtown.
Haven't you seen that kid?
Haven't you seen him?
I've seen him, but I don't know him.
He was cheering.
That's me.
Is that so?
Don't you want to go for a drink?
A little.
Just a little.
Come here.
You're beautiful.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm not looking at you.
Don't look at me.
I'm going home.
I'm not worried about you.
Why?
I don't need to worry about you.
I'm serious.
It's polite.
It's not polite.
I'm serious.
I'm not worried about you.
Really?
I'm serious.
Just a little.
Let's play a game of cards.
If you take this card...
I don't want to.
What?
You're going to say something weird.
I'm not going to say anything weird.
Your eyes are like that.
I don't want to.
You don't have to do anything.
Go over there.
I'm drunk.
I'm not drunk.
Suddenly.
Just a little.
I'm not going to say anything.
I'm going home.
Why?
This is the worst.
I'm going to do it.
This is a big deal
No.2 batter
Next is Otomo
Otomo
What?
I don't know
Have you met him before?
No
You've met him before
Have you met him before?
No
Can I ask you something?
What?
I don't know
Can I ask you something?
What?
He's laughing
Sit down
I'm here
Can I ask you something?
What are you doing?
I have something to do
I'm waiting
I have something to show you
It's a bad thing
It's not a bad thing
I have something to show you
I'm just drinking
I have something like this
Are you playing alone?
I don't play alone
Are you not holding it?
I'm not holding it
Do you want to do it?
Show me your hand
Can I see your hand?
Can I see it?
Yes
Can I see your hand?
Wait
He's laughing
He's laughing a lot
How is it?
It's an adult mood
I think it has more tempo
Yes
It has more appeal
In that sense
It's a good thing
Good morning
What are you saying?
Oscar
No
This is a special edition
I can't go to the industry
Are you a model?
Just a little
Right?
Yes
There is a special edition
Sit down
Let's play rock-paper-scissors
What is it?
I don't want to do it
Let's play a game
I don't like games
Let's play rock-paper-scissors
Hamada
Are you two friends?
I raised them
I'll be your assistant
Go to my room
Why?
Look at the calendar
I forgot the date
Let's go
Thank you
Why are you going home?
I don't know
What is this?
I'm going to smoke
You smell good
No
I don't smell good
I don't think so
I'm just looking for a model
I'm just an agent of the model
What is your occupation?
I'm a model
Really?
I'd like to talk to you about the contract
and join the actors' world
OK
Do you like it?
Let's talk about it in the bar
Who's coming?
What is your name?
Lucy
Where are you from?
I'm from Thailand
That's cool
Do you like it?
It's not always cold
The last one
I'd like to talk to you about the contract
and join the actors' world
He said
Let's go
Hello
Nice to meet you
Where do you come from?
I come from Ireland
Are you lonely?
Let's drink together
OK
Just a small drink
Who are you talking to?
What would you like to drink?
I'll have lemonade
Lemonade?
Is it your country?
Yes
I like America
and Japan
Are you a Japanese boy?
I have a boyfriend
You have a boyfriend?
Your English is very good
Very good
Thank you very much
Are you a student?
Yes, I'm a student
My home is near
Really?
Let's drink together
OK
Just a short drink
Please
Thank you
You can sit there
Finish, stop
You can get somebody else to do this
What?
Heibo-san is angry
He's the worst
He's so cool
He's angry even though he can speak
Ladies and gentlemen
Why?
I'm so sweaty
It's hot
I don't want to be sweaty
Women can be sweaty
But this man...
He's good at it
There are a lot of women
I don't know about women
But men are good at
the tightness of their thighs
This is...
And it's itchy
It's itchy
It's itchy when you roll
But you're a trunks
That's why it's itchy
What?
You have a lot of hair
I don't have enough hair
So it's itchy
I think trunks are itchy
Right?
There are a lot of people like this
It's itchy
You can't do this
I remember that
Trunks are itchy
You can't do this
So it's itchy
It's itchy
Are you an old man?
It's not itchy
It's itchy sometimes
You can't control your body
I can do it
No
When I was wearing a jersey
I was doing this
I thought I was finished
But when I relaxed
My body went down
And my trunks were like this
You don't have trunks
But when my trunks went up, it was itchy
It's like Yakuzan
Do you know that?
No
When I was washing my face
There was a person who was doing it
I was doing it
It was over
He was like this
I was like, that's enough
It's not over
Then he went back
It's a cataract
What is that?
There is a cataract in a cat
It's a cataract
It hurts
That's why I try to shake it
You can't shake it that much
I can't shake it that much
How should I say it
There are people like me
What are you talking about?
There are times when I do it
What kind of times?
When I'm pooping
No one is there
If someone comes in
I don't know why I'm holding my breath
I know that
Why am I a lowly person?
Everyone is like that
Why are you hiding?
If I do it now, I can do it in one go
I can't even use the toilet paper
I really hate that
When I'm alone
I'm like this
I know that
But sometimes I'm like a man in the sea
I fall in love
A man falls in love with a man
I want to go out and wait
In charge ofidol
To become a children
What do we learn?
I have a little face
Help me
Narrow it
I was thinking of a different Hamada-san.
When I said, Oh, I got it!
I was like, Oh, I got it!
That's right, that's right.
I was thinking of a different Hamada-san.
Even if you say it, 24 hours have passed.
Ah, that's right.
Are you still looking for a letter?
I heard that a lot of people came.
Really?
I heard that only those who have done it before choose.
Oh, really?
What should I do?
I'm fine with saying that, but...
In a sense, it may be harder than a ostrich.
Well, it's a different nature.
And it's like ostriches.
If the camera chases you for 24 hours and tells you to do your best.
That's worth it.
It's worth it.
I'm not doing it for anyone.
I won't tell you to do your best.
I won't send you a fax.
What should I do?
Who are you asking?
Let's say you fall down.
What would you do?
I'll do it like this.
It's really hard.
I can do an impersonation show even if you fall down.
I'm really good at Senma Sao.
Is that a croquette?
Is Senma Sao doing a croquette?
No, I'm Senma Sao.
It's a croquette.
I've been doing impersonations for a long time.
It's an automatic vending machine at a cashier.
It's like an automatic vending machine.
It's like a vending machine.
It's really similar.
What about my money?
What are you doing?
What is the small window on the corner of the toilet door?
What does it mean?
Where is it?
It used to be like this.
Wasn't it around here?
It's not attached to the ventilation.
It's for ventilation.
It stinks.
It's not for ventilation?
It's not for ventilation.
But I need it.
I don't know.
You don't know?
Why is it attached?
I want you to tell me.
I can tell you.
At night,
everyone in the house is sleeping,
so if I don't open the window,
the poop that was playing outside...
Is that really true?
Yes, it's true.
What?
Why are you talking about old people?
Are you talking about old people?
Don't tell me you bought it.
Don't make a fool out of me.
Everyone thinks so.
Let's study one by one like this.
You can't reach my world yet, can you?
Well, yes.
One by one.
That's true.
Is that so?
Yes, I'll study it.
In the survey,
which one do you think is the sexiest?
When I saw the survey,
Matsumoto-san was in the first place.
How can I be sexy?
You should have told me.
Well,
the audience who came here last year,
85% of them are my fans.
Well,
I think most of the fans will notice it.
I don't want to say this because most of the fans noticed it.
I'm talking to you like this,
and I'm thinking you're concentrating on this.
But it's time to emphasize the urn.
It happened, didn't it?
It happened before.
It didn't happen.
Wait a minute, I don't have a head right now.
I think the people around here noticed.
This is the first time you've done this.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, Yamada-chan.
I'm in a bath right now.
I hope I don't get in your way.
Thank you very much.
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.