Next time, we will install a cooler in Kokoriko Endo's room.
It's hot.
I'm suddenly excited.
It's close.
It's hot.
But there's no cooler in his room.
Tanaka doesn't have it.
I had a cooler in the apartment.
Originally?
Originally.
But there's a hairball on it.
This is not good.
There's a hairball on it.
I can't use it.
That's not true.
It's okay.
I'll take it off for now.
That's a mistake.
And then we all said,
This is kind of us.
Really.
I'll give you a cooler.
It's for that.
And it's by hand.
It's like this.
It's cool.
And this is type A.
What's type A?
It's type B.
It's type A.
It's so hot.
Good morning.
You're sweating.
Why are you sweating so much?
Popular
So this time I'm going to install a cooler in Endo's room.
I'm here for you.
There's no cooler in this room.
There's no cooler.
Look at this.
It's a big cooler.
Put it on for me.
Really?
We'll put it on.
Thank you very much.
Shall we go in?
I'm sorry.
Can you put it on for me?
It's so hot.
This is a joke.
There's no cooler.
It's narrow.
It's thin.
It's hot.
This is the outside.
If you get a call, I'll open the drawer and touch it.
I'll do it.
Really?
I can't help it.
Let's do it.
Wait for me at the cafe in the neighborhood.
May I?
Sure.
There's no cooler in this room.
Really?
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
Let's put the blanket on.
Shall we move this?
There's a lot of dust.
Endo is grateful for his seniors' hard work.
It's fast if four men work together.
We can do it, right?
We can do it.
That's right.
I can't get it on camera.
Okay.
It's done.
Tanaka, call him.
Okay.
Tell him I'm here.
Tell him it was hard.
Okay.
I should have let Endo do the first one.
That's right.
I did it.
Really?
I'm sorry.
I'm a senior now.
I'm serious.
I finally did it.
Really?
I'm serious.
I want to do it.
It's done.
Thank you very much.
You did a good job.
There's a remote control.
You put the switch in first.
That's right.
It's cool.
Okay.
It's coming.
Look.
It's working.
It's really cool.
Wait a minute.
Hey.
It's the other way around.
Why?
Nothing.
There's a cold wind outside.
This is the heat.
This is for outside.
What's wrong?
Tell me.
I don't know.
I want the room to be cool.
Really?
There's a cold wind outside.
It's the other way around.
You're young.
It doesn't matter.
Let's do it again.
You should think about it.
I'm sorry.
Even though it's a senior's action,
Enzo can't afford to make a mistake.
It's done.
Okay.
I'll call him.
Let's press the button.
Is it about 24 degrees?
24 degrees.
If it gets cold suddenly,
you might catch a cold.
I see.
Is it really what he wants?
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
You don't have to thank me.
Okay.
Switch.
You do it.
First, cut the tape.
Look.
It's coming.
It's set at 24 degrees.
It looks good.
Why is your face so sharp?
It's not the other way around.
What do you mean?
It doesn't matter if you catch a cold here.
If you don't catch a cold here,
it will be here again.
Is this okay?
It doesn't make sense.
Young people these days are like this.
Are you sure?
It's difficult.
Young people these days are polite.
Is this a joke?
I was so happy when Mr. Oshiro Chaburo was with me.
If the hose is broken,
I can't fix it.
Please fix it.
I'm begging you.
I'll remove it.
It doesn't matter.
The hose is broken.
I want to fix it.
Endo is annoyed by the work that doesn't go as planned.
It's done.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad to see you.
What will the result be?
I wanted you to do this.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
It's done.
Come here.
Look.
Look at this.
Hurry up.
Look.
It doesn't matter.
Look at this.
Push it.
It's open.
The door to happiness has opened.
All right.
OK.
Let's go home.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong with this hose?
It's open.
It's in the middle of the room.
I don't know what to do.
Hey.
What?
What did you just say?
Are you crazy?
Hey.
What?
It's for everyone.
Everyone is working hard for you.
What?
What are you thinking?
You are crazy.
Are you crazy?
What's wrong with this hose?
What are you thinking?
What's wrong?
Stop it.
You are crazy.
You are difficult.
Sorry.
What should I do?
What do you want me to do?
The room is narrow.
And I can't install a cooler.
Can you install a compact one?
I'm sorry.
I'll do it.
Remove the hose part.
Understood.
The cooler that finally came true.
It's done.
It's okay now.
Really?
There's nothing left.
Let's go.
It's finally done.
I brought it.
Let's go in.
I'm sorry.
It's done.
There's nothing left.
It's better to use that.
It's compact.
Sit down.
This is your seat.
Press this switch.
Press it.
It's cool.
Why is it cold?
It's hot.
Put it in.
What is this?
What?
Give me a break.
That?
I don't know what you're talking about.
That's not the problem.
That's right.
That's not it.
Sit down like this.
It's pretty good.
Stop it.
What did you do?
Just me.
This room is cool.
That's all I need.
I'm not going to do this.
If you don't care about the coolness,
I have something for you.
Is that so?
You want to make this room cool, don't you?
That's right.
I want to make this room cool.
I'm not going to do it for you.
Thank you.
This is what Kogoriko does every time.
Today's guest is not feeling well.
Do you have a guest?
Do you have Kogoriko?
I'm not feeling well, but I'm Kogoriko.
How are you doing recently?
What?
I'm doing well.
I have a big house.
I haven't built it yet.
I want to build a house.
Is that so?
Go ahead.
But it's hot.
What?
It's hot in the summer.
You can park your car in the parking lot.
Who are you talking about?
I'm talking about you.
That's not true.
It's just one car.
You're a fool.
That's not true.
What?
I'm not sure if it's going to be popular.
I'm talking about you.
You're a fool.
You can't park your car in the parking lot.
I'm not talking about you.
But it's popular.
What?
It's not going to be popular.
That's not true.
You're a fool.
Where do you want to go this summer?
Where do you want to go?
No, no, no.
I'm not going with you.
Why do you want to go with me?
It's okay to go with you sometimes.
I don't want to go with you.
Why?
I'll get kicked out.
I won't get kicked out.
I'm not that kind of person.
I'll get kicked out either way.
That's not true.
I'll get kicked out if I get kicked out.
By the way, do you stand up when you see my butt?
No, no, no.
I'm not that kind of person.
I'm a general person.
Oh, really?
I'm not going to get kicked out.
I'm not going to get kicked out if I get kicked out.
Today's guest is not going to talk.
I'm not going to talk.
Then what do you want to do?
You're going to go somewhere, aren't you?
I don't know.
Oh, really?
I just remembered something while I was talking.
What is it?
Around October, this year...
If I talk about this, everyone will turn blue.
I don't think so.
I heard it from someone I can trust.
Around October, it's going to be really bad.
What?
Japan.
There's a rumor that Japan is going to disappear after leaving Shikoku.
That's going to be really bad.
No, no, it's true.
Alright!
Let's do something.
It's really bad.
It's bad.
Of course, not only Japan, the Earth is going to sink.
The Earth is going to sink?
The Earth is going to be really bad.
It's not something to laugh about.
No, no, no.
I know. I'm listening.
You know it's going to be really bad, right?
It's not going to be bad.
It's a lie.
Why don't you trust me?
Do you think aliens are going to attack us?
That's part of the world of movies.
You don't trust aliens?
I haven't actually seen them.
Do you know?
There are a lot of people who have been kidnapped by aliens.
Maybe you've been kidnapped too.
No, I haven't been kidnapped.
That's not true.
I haven't been kidnapped.
You've been kidnapped and beaten up.
I haven't been beaten up.
You've been licked all over your body.
What do you want to do with an alien?
But he doesn't realize it because he lost his memory when he returned it.
Sometimes he's planted something like a microchip.
Sometimes he's not planted.
When you plant something, you plant it on the top of your mouth.
There's nothing on my mouth.
When I put it down like this, there's a microchip.
What's a microchip?
Where are you going?
When you buy clothes, you have to take it off.
When you go out, the clerk asks you how it went.
You always say, I'll take this.
He doesn't notice it.
What would you answer?
Please tell me.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What?
What would you answer?
I don't care, but the customer is interested in it.
That's all right.
If the customer isn't interested in it, I don't care what I do here.
At that time, I'll be the one to take care of it.
The customer is not interested in it at all.
It's hard to say.
I want everyone to be more excited.
What are you talking about?
If you have such an attitude, I won't be told.
I'm sorry.
Please look back.
When you're done reading, don't do this.
Like this.
My body...
It's good.
Wait a minute.
When you're done reading...
Are you done?
Yes, thank you.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'll read the document.
When you buy clothes, you have to take it off.
You have to wear it properly.
When you go out, the clerk asks you how you feel.
You always say, I'll take this.
Please give me this.
You don't get the point.
Mr. Matsumoto, what would you say?
Well, I'd say...
I'm sorry.
I'm done.
Please open it.
I opened it.
How was it?
What do you mean how was it?
What is it?
Which is it?
Well, well...
It's a good feeling.
I'm glad.
Now I won't be able to slide.
I don't want to slide anymore.
I don't care.
In the race where Ayrton Senna won...
Mr. Matsumoto was always in the front of the F1 car.
What were you doing?
How did you get into the circuit?
Is it the system?
Well, basically...
Wait, wait.
You can't watch TV.
You have to watch the scenery.
That's not it.
I can't do that.
You can.
More.
That's why...
There are a lot of cameras on the track.
There are no cameras on the track.
There are places where you can't see the camera.
Senna always tells me.
It's hot. It's hot.
I'm sorry.
He always tells me.
Basically, I'm like this.
When the camera isn't on, Senna says,
Are you okay now?
I open my eyes and close them for a while.
I'm like, this is bad.
When Senna steps on the accelerator,
it's like he's stabbing my butt.
The bar.
When Senna goes like this,
it stimulates my front wheel.
What do you think?
When I do that, I go like this.
You!
You're just struggling in the front.
I'm not struggling.
There's a hole in the middle.
It's a turbo.
When Senna goes like this,
it stimulates my front wheel.
I go like this.
It's like this.
When Senna got into an accident,
he wasn't in the car.
What?
When Senna got into an accident,
he wasn't in the car.
What?
You were okay?
That's right.
It wasn't you who pushed him into the car, was it?
It was a big deal.
I didn't think it was a big deal.
It's okay to say that Senna got into an accident
because I jumped out.
Senna lost his balance.
He said,
Mazumoro!
Senna jumped out of the car.
No, Mazumoro, no!
Why did you jump out?
I thought it was a big deal.
I said, Mazumoro, no!
Because Mazumoro wasn't there,
I lost my balance.
Don't talk too much.
In such a short time.
No, I don't know.
You're still talking.
I don't know the last word.
When I was in elementary school,
I stopped the train running to save the puppy sleeping on the tracks
with bare hands.
Bare hands are too much.
I don't drive.
Why are there so many stones around the tracks of the train?
To fix the bar of the track,
you have to fix it.
I can't fix it with such a thing.
It's fixed.
I think it's better to fix it a little more.
Do you know how much money it costs to fix the track?
I don't know.
How many meters do you think the track is in Japan?
No one has ever thought about that.
The track is several times as big as Mt. Fuji.
It costs a lot of money.
Why do you have to do that?
I want to do it.
What are you talking about?
I didn't have any money this time.
It's terrible.
I want to take a bath.
Yes.
I don't want to.
I'm sweating.
I can't do it.
I can't do it at all.
I'm sorry.
Please tell me.
Are you thinking about it now?
Are you thinking about it?
What do you mean?
I'm thinking about it.
Please tell me.
I don't have the courage to tell you today.
Why?
Something is wrong.
What's wrong?
I feel like I'm going to slip.
I'm scared of today's guest.
That's not true.
Something is wrong.
Please tell me.
What's wrong?
I have a lot of thoughts.
Why?
Then tell me.
Tell me.
I'll tell you.
I can't do it if I don't have money.
Why?
Yes.
That's why.
I heard your opinion.
Do you have any other opinions?
No.
I've never talked about it.
I can't think of anything else.
I have an answer.
Then tell me.
Yes.
Tell me.
I'll tell you.
If I don't have money, I can't do it.
I see.
Think about it.
It's scary.
What do you mean?
There's only one way.
That's amazing.
What do you mean?
What?
What kind of question is that?
Oops.
This is the reason.
What is it?
It's messed up.
Bring it to me.
What are you saying?
What is it?
It's messed up.
What's messed up?
I didn't say anything.
You're lying.
Why are you angry?
What is it?
I don't want to draw.
You're lying.
It's messed up.
Why are you angry?
You're lying.
It's messed up.