What will be the punishment for the one who bites the opening title?
The opening title of the first half of the month,
Coming soon!
However, the title call was not as easy as it looks from the outside.
So, as before, he calls various titles out loud.
If he bites even a little bit, he will be punished for his fear.
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Ara,
the manager of Down Town,
Chikichiki Nakibokuro Okamoto...
Yes!
3, 2, 1, go!
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Ara,
Chikichiki...
Yes!
How many times will you say the word Chikichiki?
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Ara,
we will play a game to decide who bites the opening title!
Who will be the victim this time?
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
This time, it's a double pie throwing game.
Here is the punishment for the one who bites the opening title!
Let's go!
When I looked at the light,
the light was so bright that I couldn't see the time.
Let's go!
3, 2, 1, go!
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Ara,
we will play a game to decide who bites the opening title!
Let's go!
Next to Tanaka is...
3, 2, 1, go!
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Ara, we will play a game to decide who bites the opening title!
He's drooling.
His hair is in the middle.
Next to Matsumoto is...
Here!
Did you really do that?
No, I didn't.
You said it so easily.
I remember most of it.
I didn't do it.
Let's go!
3, 2, 1, go!
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Ara,
we will play a game to decide who bites the opening title!
Amazing.
I'm sorry that I didn't get excited.
I'm shaking.
It can't be helped.
Amazing.
Next is...
It's huge.
Is this French bread?
It's really big.
It's good, right?
It's French bread, right?
It's French bread.
What is this?
You got a big one again.
My hands are hot.
It's hot.
Next to Matsumoto is...
It's easy.
3, 2, 1, go!
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Ara,
we will play a game to decide who bites the opening title!
It's hot.
Alright.
It's really hot.
Let's use the long one instead of the round one.
Let's use the round one or the long one.
This is good.
If it sticks to your skin, it's bad for your liver.
It's hot.
Let's start.
Here are the questions.
Let's see.
3, 2, 1, go!
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Ara,
we will play a game to decide who bites the opening title!
It's hot.
Good job.
Keep going.
Okay.
Alright.
3, 2, 1, go!
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Ara,
we will play a game to decide who bites the opening title!
It's hot.
Who is it?
I'm holding it.
I'm begging you.
Mr. Hamada.
Are you okay?
How many people are you?
You're holding it well.
Let's start.
Here are the questions.
Here we go.
3, 2, 1, go!
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Ara,
we will play a game to decide who bites the opening title!
What is this?
Let's end this with a show.
What?
I'm risking my life.
What is this?
It's hot water.
I think it might be good.
You're all going this way.
If you can say it, it's okay.
Here are the questions.
Here we go.
3, 2, 1, go!
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Ara,
we will play a game to decide who bites the opening title!
3, 2, 1, go!
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Ara,
we will play a game to decide who bites the opening title!
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
The other day, you were talking about the manager of the house.
The manager of the house?
Yes, yes.
Our raccoon father, right?
He's terrible.
He's always in the picture book.
Yes, yes.
He's the manager of the raccoon family.
Do you know him?
The father of our pig.
He hasn't arrived yet.
How many months has it been?
It's been about 3 months.
I think he's still in the picture book.
He's still in the picture book.
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
How many times does he apologize in a day?
I'm sorry.
Yesterday, I was at the toilet.
I said, I'm going to the toilet.
He said, yes, go ahead.
He's always at the toilet.
He's at the toilet in front of me.
There's a lot of distance.
That's right.
He's good at that.
It's embarrassing.
To other managers.
Matsumoto is a king again.
What are you talking about?
I was walking normally.
There was a guy like this in front of me.
That's strange.
There was a toilet.
He said, go ahead.
He went into the toilet.
I don't want you to think it's a joke.
He's not in the toilet at all.
I know.
He went into the toilet and said, go ahead.
There's a person who pees in the toilet.
He opened it and looked at the toilet.
He said, go ahead.
You're the one who pees.
I thought it was strange because I was in the toilet.
I thought he peed in front of me.
He peed in front of the toilet and said, go ahead.
I laughed a little at that time.
This is what happens when you always lead people astray.
He said, go ahead.
Where is the interview room?
Go ahead.
He opened the door.
I thought it was a meeting.
He looked at me.
He looked at me from behind.
He said, go ahead.
Give me the phone, Fujiwara.
Yes.
He was sweating.
That pig was sweating all the time.
That's strange.
I'm sure he's here.
He's here.
He was laughing like this.
That's strange.
After work, I sometimes bring something to give to someone.
Do you know what that is?
I put it in the car.
I took it and looked at it.
I brought it.
I gave it to someone.
I put it in the car.
I'm sorry.
That's strange.
Where did you take it?
That's right.
When I came to work, I didn't have anything to eat.
I shouldn't get angry here.
Fujiwara, I live alone.
I'm a man.
I can't eat breakfast and come to work in the morning.
I don't know.
When I came to work, I should have something to eat.
You should have something to eat.
I said that.
I said, I'm sorry.
The next day, I was asked if I wanted spaghetti napolitan or bongole.
I said, I don't want it, so I'm doing it properly.
I don't want it.
I can't eat all the food on the menu.
It's hard.
I said, I don't want it.
But I'm doing it.
I went to buy a new pair of slippers the other day.
Why don't you wear shoes?
It's easier to wear slippers.
I went to Ise for a summer trip the other day.
I went to Ise.
Did you wear slippers that day?
I did.
But it was a summer trip, so it was good.
The bad thing was that it was in Niigata last winter.
I was wearing slippers when it was snowing heavily.
It was hard.
Did you go to buy slippers?
I went to buy new slippers.
I only had shoes, slippers, and an umbrella.
The old man there was so stupid.
He asked me to give him a pair of slippers for 2,300 yen.
I gave him 3,000 yen for 2,300 yen and a receipt.
I gave him 2,500 yen.
I gave him 2,200 yen.
Which way?
How many pairs of slippers did you give him?
What?
I gave him 1,500 yen.
You're lying.
You gave him 2,200 yen.
I gave him 2,500 yen.
You gave him 2,500 yen.
I gave him 3,000 yen, and the old man said yes, but he didn't move at all.
He didn't move at all.
There was an umbrella on top of him.
The umbrella was a little stuck.
That's strange.
I know the owner of the store, so I'm sure he'll give me a discount.
An old woman came out of the back of the store and asked me what I was doing.
I don't know what you're doing.
The old man said, I have 2,500 yen, so I'll give you a 300 yen discount.
The old woman said, go back to the store.
The old man said, 300 yen.
That's what the old man said.
I gave him 300 yen at the end.
I never saw him again.
I don't know if I'm going to make a fool of myself.
You have a family.
If I make a fool of myself, no one will take care of me.
No one will take care of you.
When I really make a fool of myself, I want you to take care of me.
Why?
Because I don't have a family.
You don't have a family?
After that, I'll make a fool of myself.
If you make a fool of yourself, your wife and children will take care of me.
If you make a fool of yourself, you'll be in downtown.
I don't think you should take care of your wife and children.
I don't think you should.
I'm lonely in the world, so I can't help it.
I don't know what you're talking about.
That's impossible.
If you two make a fool of yourself, it'll be a mess.
If you make a fool of yourself, you'll make a fool of yourself.
I'll be fine.
When you feel good, your brain goes like this.
What do you mean?
The back of your brain goes like this.
That doesn't make a fool of yourself.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I was drowning.
I was trying to make a fool of myself.
I've been dating her for three years.
I pay for all the dates.
I can't say I don't have money.
Is there a way to make her pay for all the dates?
I've been dating her for three years.
I've never said I'd pay for all the dates.
If that's the case, she's a crazy woman.
Do you pay for all the dates?
Yes, I do.
When you were single?
Yes.
Do you pay for all the dates?
Yes, I do.
Oh...
You have a hole in your stomach.
You pay for all the dates, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I'm older than her.
Older than her?
Yes.
How old are you?
I'm not that old.
I've never dated an older woman.
I see.
If I dated an older woman, I'd be much older than her.
If that's the case, I don't know what will happen.
I don't know if she'll pay for all the dates.
I've never dated an older woman.
Right?
I don't think she'll pay for all the dates.
It's like I'm the one who pays for all the dates.
I don't think the one who pays for all the dates thinks that way.
I don't think so.
You're lucky, aren't you?
There are many ways to do it.
Really?
Yes.
I don't want her to think,
Oh, I paid for all the dates without knowing.
But I don't feel bad about it.
There are many ways to do it.
You should have told me that.
The man I want to ask is Yamamoto.
Is that so?
That's right.
Let's tell him.
Let's have a meal together.
What do you mean by a meal?
That's right.
Let's have a meal together.
That's fine.
Oh, that's a good idea.
You should do it too.
Let's have a talk and wine together.
That's good.
I'll do it.
That's fine.
It's true.
Well, it was a joke.
That's right!
That's ridiculous.
I don't like it when people say that.
Isn't it?
Only once or twice a year.
That's right.
You can't use it.
It's only once.
I see.
Don't say it!
Please tell me how to make her angry.
What?
Please tell me how to make a woman angry.
Yes, yes, yes.
I understand.
Men watching TV...
This is a checkpoint.
...to make a medicine.
This is a great place.
That's right.
This is for you.
Yes, please.
Thank you.
Well, let's get started.
That's right.
What kind of wallet do you have?
What?
First of all, don't say what.
Wallet...
There are also gifts.
What kind of wallet do you have?
Something like this.
Let me see.
Do you have something like this?
Yes.
Then, let's go.
You...
That's...
It's a word.
Stop it!
It's already over.
Not only airplanes...
Yes.
...but also things that fly in the sky.
Is it true that you always say hello to her?
This may sound like a lie, but it's true.
If you were walking in the studio...
Yes.
...and your senior was walking in front of you...
...you would say hello to her before she said hello to you, right?
Yes, I would say hello to her.
This is the flow of the world.
That's right.
After all, from the lower door to the upper door...
...you show respect.
I understand that.
Yes.
But you always say hello to things that fly in the sky.
That's right.
Even things that fly in the sky...
...they know that I fly in the sky more than I do.
For example, if I were to fly a jumbo jet...
...I would fly like this, but Matsumoto-san...
...would say, if Matsumoto-san were to fly, it wouldn't be like this.
That's something that even Jumbo knows.
Matsumoto-san is the only one who can't do that.
Jumbo knows that I can't say that.
I'm drowning.
That's a lot.
You're asking too much.
Judgment Matsumoto's Which is Great?
Yasawa Eikichi and Nagamichi Tsuyoshi.
I'm sorry, I'm not good at studying. I don't know either of them.
Hey!
Which do you think is great?
I have a lot of opinions on this.
Don't react like that!
Well, for me...
I think it's...
And...
Well...
I think it's Shino Okan.
Jumbo Ozaki and Jumbo Jet.
This is Jumbo Jet.
That's true.
Ashika no Sho and Ashita no Jouma.
Well...
This is Ashika no Sho.
That's true.
It's not Ashita no Jou.
Nittere's 24-hour television is Fujii's 27-hour television.
This is Fujii's 27-hour television.
Why?
But if you run on Nittere's 24-hour television, your image will improve.
You should run next year too.
Why?
If you run on Hamada's 24-hour television, your image will improve.
You should run next year too.
I can't.
Why?
I can't take off my clothes.
Take off your clothes?
I'll think about it next year.
You should do good things sometimes.
I'll definitely run.
Let's run together.
What do you mean?
Even if we run together, it's different.
What's different?
Our pace doesn't match.
It's like this.
Here we go.
Start.
It's completely different.
We run at the same pace all the time.
Do you understand?
Do you think you can run at the same pace all the time?
Why?
At such a fast pace.
Start.
You can run at the same pace all the time.
It's impossible.
I can't keep up with you.
It's hard.
Do your best.
That's why.
Why?
If you want to run, tell me.
I'll do my best to support you.
You don't do anything?
No.
You don't do anything else?
I don't do anything else.
It's hard.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.