Next time on Gaki no Tsukaiya, we'll be doing a 24 hour long interview with Sanshiro Okobiya!
This is a bit scary.
Scary?
I've had a few drinks with him before, but he's really dark.
Is that so?
If he didn't become a comedian, he'd be making a time bomb.
That's about it.
That's dangerous.
Let's welcome our guest today, Mr. Haizawa!
Good morning!
How do you feel about this project?
When I first got the offer, I was really happy.
But when I tried it, I didn't want to do it again.
It was really hard.
I don't remember it because I've been doing it for 24 hours.
I think I said something ridiculous.
I'm doing a great job in the end.
Sanziro, Komiya. 24 hours long interview.
The challenge stage is a hotel in Asakusa.
The next day
Money...
What's wrong?
I forgot my wallet.
You forgot your wallet?
Yes.
How are you feeling today?
I'm feeling good, but the pollen is a bit...
It's a bit painful.
I think it's a medicine for the liver.
I feel a little dizzy.
I thought it was 24 hours.
It's hard to check.
Sorry.
A 24-hour long interview will be held in this hotel's medical room.
Please.
I'd like to hear your story.
I'm Kunikado.
I'm a media person.
The interview will be based on this year's report.
They will talk about their life and future.
Today, we will ask you to answer honestly.
Thank you.
How are you feeling today?
I have a little bit of a hard time with pollen.
I don't take any medicine for pollen.
But it was really hard to drink, so I felt sleepy.
And I felt tired.
I think I was in the school.
You are crazy.
I'm from the countryside.
How was your first child, Komiya?
I wonder how it was like when I was a baby.
I was told that I was cute.
Hironobe Komiyama was born on September 3, 1983.
He was a little boy, so I was happy to have him wear a high-heeled kimono.
What kind of house did you live in?
I lived in a one-bedroom apartment.
I also ran an apartment.
I have a house and 6 apartments.
It was a rich family environment.
When I asked about his parents,
What was your father like?
Not so much.
I don't have memories with my father.
I didn't talk much at home.
Your father was scary?
He wasn't scary or anything. I didn't talk much.
I kept a distance.
Why?
I don't know.
I didn't talk much.
Now, I'd like to ask about your mother.
My mother.
What kind of person was she?
I didn't talk to my mother at all.
You didn't?
I lost my mother when I was in the first grade of high school.
I was told to study all the time.
You don't have much memory with your parents.
Did you live separately?
No, we lived together.
Yes, it's the same.
My grandparents' house was about 20 meters away from here, so I always went to my grandparents' house.
His parents were busy working together.
He couldn't shorten the distance between his parents and his children, so he went to kindergarten.
Did you have many friends in kindergarten?
No, I didn't.
I remember I was always with the head teacher in kindergarten.
Why?
I was alone in the school's health room and crying.
What did you talk to the head teacher and the health teacher?
I was very angry with the female teacher.
I started to hate him since then.
What are you talking about?
He didn't talk to me like a woman.
I thought he was my friend.
But he was totally different.
I really hated him.
From then on, I became a woman and a man.
What is that?
A woman.
He became a man and entered elementary school.
Did you have any trauma in elementary school?
Yes, I was bullied.
How should I say it...
Since when?
Since the second half of my elementary school.
What did they do to you?
They put a land cell in my generator.
I couldn't take it out.
So they took out the land cell by
I was asked to come here and take a picture.
The girl you were bullying may be watching TV right now.
Please say something to the camera.
Well, at that time, everyone was higher.
I'm already higher.
Thank you for your hard work.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I feel bad.
I hope you live happily and take care of your family.
Are you okay?
I feel strange.
I'm scared of the ending.
If you don't like it, look at me and laugh.
I'll let the past go.
I'm an adult now, so I'll go with this.
I thought he'd use only good parts, but he used all of them.
He did a lot of patterns.
Two hours have passed since the start.
The interviewer will now take over.
He will have lunch with me.
Oh, it's coke.
Huh? Is it coke?
Say something.
What? Which one is it?
Hey, hey, did you drink coke?
You shouldn't ask such a thing.
It's a special type of food.
Please try the steamed chicken and the maitake salad.
Please enjoy.
I don't like this.
It's so good.
What kind of food do you usually eat?
I eat soft food.
I don't have teeth.
I don't eat much.
You don't eat much?
Oh, really?
Eh?
Wait a minute.
I don't have a tooth.
You're really slow.
He's going to the right.
He doesn't have a left.
I don't have a tooth.
Wait a minute.
I have an interview.
See you later.
He's getting a little annoyed.
You should have made it curry.
No!
I like it.
I like chicken.
I'm being teased.
I have to do an interview. Can you eat a little faster?
I can't do it.
It's the worst.
Next, let's talk about the middle school days.
After the junior high school entrance exam, Komia entered a famous private junior high school.
In elementary school, you were bullied badly.
How was the bullying in junior high school?
There was bullying.
I was told that I would not be able to eat the eraser.
I was given an eraser and I was allowed to eat it.
During basketball time, I was given a pass.
I didn't know that I would not get a pass.
I was being teased a lot.
I was teased a lot.
Komiya became friends with a teased character.
In the school event held at the beach,
he was shocked by his partner Aida.
At the beach school, everyone was doing something.
I think of the parody of Mr. Beta from Downtown.
The parody was really interesting.
It was amazing.
I don't know if it was because my parents were strict, but
I watched Downtown's program because there was no scene until high school students started.
No, no, no, it's my parents.
I like Uchiyama-chan, but I like Downtown.
And then, I started talking to him and we became friends.
Why did you not like Downtown's program?
There are no pieces of the heart.
It's my parents.
Even if your parents say it, you have your own way of saying it.
Did you have a crush on anyone?
In junior high?
I was in love with a class teacher, Madonna.
Did you approach her?
I was in the third grade of junior high school.
I was in the first class.
There were only four boys in the first class.
Three out of four girls had a girlfriend.
I was left out of the class.
I said, I want to be in it too.
She said, you're not in it.
So I said, I am in it too.
But I was really there.
The class's madonna.
I said, then confess.
Of course, I like it too.
I went on a school trip to Okinawa.
There was a male cottage and a female cottage.
There was a big tree in the middle.
I said, let's meet there at night.
To the girl.
The girl came and I went too.
I went to see her, but she said,
What?
I said,
Just enjoy your trip to Okinawa.
That was it.
I was looking at the footage from the cottage.
I didn't know what was going on.
So the girl went home, and I went home too.
Everyone was at the cottage.
I asked, How was it?
They said, It was nothing.
They said, You were dating her?
I thought, I could go.
I said, I dated her.
I thought I was dating her.
I thought I wouldn't be found out because we weren't that close.
I thought I would be found out someday, but I was fine.
One day, it was about six months later,
There are girls who come to class with their faces in any case.
That person was crying next to the window.
We came to the ground together.
All the girls in the class were there, surrounded by circles.
I said, get inside the picture!
In the middle of the picture, there was a liar, a scumbag, an idiot, a scumbag
One person said bad things about me
I said I would never talk to them again
And from there, I became a member of the group
You were watching it?
I was watching it
From above
I was watching the people surrounded me
You said you lied for half a year, but all the men were lying, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
In the end, I lied because I wanted to join the first army.
In the end, it's the same for everyone, both men and women.
So I never talked about it, but I've never talked about a fat man in the 5th army.
You said 5th army.
I'm really fat in the 5th army.
You're so discriminating!
Three hours have passed since the start.
After the meal, Komiya heads to the city of memories from his school days.
I'll continue to talk about the car.
Please tell me about your hobbies from middle school.
Hobbies?
My hair was really curly.
So, I think it was my hobby to read magazines and see their hair.
Was it like that around you?
It was like a city school in Tokyo. There were many kids who were mixed up.
The place where he came was Chetagaya-ku, Seijo, where he spent his high school days.
At the coffee shop in front of the station, he gave an interview from his high school days.
I heard that you had a big shock when you were in the first year of high school.
Yes, my mother passed away.
It was quite a shock.
Well, yes.
After all, my grandparents were closer to me, so I didn't get that much shock.
It was so sudden that he couldn't realize what was happening.
Yes.
I thought that people would die any time.
So I stopped studying.
I thought that if I studied, I would die.
So I thought I didn't have to study.
Because of his mother's death, he stopped studying at all.
As a result, he was in high school for two years.
Were you embarrassed?
I'm not embarrassed. Everyone was satisfied with me.
I was called in the shadows.
What kind of story was that?
I was hungry, so I went into the living room.
I was sorry that I was coming out very quickly.
I was in a coma, so I couldn't say anything.
I couldn't get out of there.
It was awkward.
He was a member of the National Police Department.
He was chosen by the Tokyo Metropolitan Police and was working hard.
But there was an incident when he was in the third grade of high school.
Shukichi was a student from kindergarten to university.
Everyone used the playground.
It was a school playground for elementary school students.
There was a club room next to it.
I felt sorry for changing clothes in the club room.
I was changing clothes in front of the club room.
When I was changing, a boy came through the door.
He took off his clothes and smiled.
He chased me in the trunk.
He ran away.
Two days later, he came to school with his mother.
He said a reporter had appeared.
He chased me in the trunk.
I had a blonde hair and had fox eyes.
I wanted to catch it.
I was asked to gather the blonde eyes.
My mother told my child,
I was the last one.
I was able to twist my face.
I told my brother,
I was doing something like that.
Then, the rumor was revealed to the whole school.
Everyone misunderstood and scolded me.
I fell down and I had a toothache.
Six hours have passed since the beginning.
Interview at the park of memories in the hope of Komiya.
Wow, the pollen is amazing. Why did I choose this place?
It's a memorable park, isn't it?
This place is a bit...
That pollen...
It's a bit of a
What is this place?
Oh really?
This place is...
Oh, I see. It's just my imagination.
I just thought of it.
But this park is amazing.
Is this a memorable park?
Yes, it is.
This is the place where I went into the fairy-tale castle
and we had a meeting to discuss the ideas for the live show.
At the high school festival, they performed comedy and comedy.
That was the reason why they became comedians.
After graduating from high school, they went to the comedy school of the people who had the talent.
They were the most talented in the school.
However, Yoshimoto's combination made the situation different.
What was the most popular show at Yoshimoto's request?
Oriental Radio.
It was 3 against 3, Oriental Radio.
It was like a multi-battle.
We did the story and thought we got it.
But then Oriental Radio came out and we were defeated.
Oriental Radio was the momentum of Hachiku.
I thought I didn't have a good sense for it.
So I decided to quit.
However, he didn't give up on his dream of becoming a comedian.
He became a freelancer and worked at Trio.
Trio was closed for about a year, but then Aida and Sanshiro were formed again.
After working for about 5 years as a freelancer, he went to Maseki Entertainment, his current agency.
9 hours have passed since the start.
We return to the hotel and ask about the reason why Komiya broke up.
What was the reason for breaking up?
It was a TV Tokyo program where comedians were chosen.
It was a program where comedians were chosen.
They were ranked first and they voted for me.
Could you tell us more about the recording?
Two days ago, I fell down and hurt my teeth.
I also had a bone fracture in my knee.
I was in the wheelchair.
I was going to do a full-time job, but I couldn't do it.
I felt like it was over.
I think it was good to think of it now.
It was a very good student.
The appearance of the impact and the excellent performance called for a reputation, and gradually the TV exposure increased to the rep game.
And the longing from the school days, the co-star of Downtown.
What kind of existence is downtown for you?
Hmm...
Oasis.
I was bullied in high school.
I watched DVDs and they made me digest them.
So, Oasis.
I was a real pervert in class.
I was laughing at the very sharp downtown DVDs of that time.
I'm not a criminal who is against society.
That's not true.
You don't get along with the members of the group.
No, I don't.
Mr. Kawada.
What?
To be honest, I'm sorry to say this, but...
I look like the person who bullied me when I was a student.
His face is so similar to mine.
Matsumoto-san, how do you feel about this?
This time, you're drinking with a person you've met before.
Ah, but now that you mention it, I thought I said that before.
Anyway, I'm talking about the lack of quality of downtown.
You said that before.
But I feel like I was told that before.
There are times when you don't have the quality.
I bullied him when he was a student.
The person and Hamada-san's visual, hair, and body position are all the same.
Isn't that me?
The way he throws the land cell in the train, that's the funniest.
It's the same, right?
This part is the most funny.
Next week!
That's not cool.
24 hour long interview, the end!
I'm going to be a monkey in the morning and night.
A storm of bomb remarks.
I'm going to die now.
Will it be possible to do it for 24 hours?