The idol group of 150 hours left directed by Takeshi Yamamoto
On the 200 hours
Takahashi Yamamoto
So...
We don't need to waste any more time using Kennedy today, right?
It's just one week since we last talked to you.
One week just passed?
Last week was also like that, right?
Yes, it was like that.
The last time, Kin-chan...
You saw everything about Captain Kazuo today.
That's right.
The other day, I got a phone call.
You made a phone call in Okinawa.
The last time, it was Arasuji.
Arasuji made a phone call in Okinawa.
You came in with a lot of things to say.
And while you were doing that, you went out onto the veranda.
And then...
You should have said it sooner!
And then you finally passed.
We went to the main event.
How many points did you get?
What happened?
That's a big deal.
You saw everything.
That's right.
It's been a while since you dressed up as Jiro-san...
Ah, not Jiro-san, Kin-chan.
I wanted to see Kin-chan, so I went.
And now you're calling me Jiro-san!
I went to see Kin-chan.
It's been a while since you and Kin-chan...
How do you say it?
Free talk.
It's such a good thing.
Let's take a look.
Please look at the monitor.
Here you go.
I told you to look at it.
Did you hear that?
It was all a lie.
It's divided into two parts.
Into two parts?
Let's start with the first part.
From the edge.
I'm scared.
Let's go to the center.
Wait a minute.
Matsumoto-san, come on.
That's Kin-chan.
That's right.
I can't see Matsumoto-san at all.
I'll turn it white in the back.
Is that so?
Thank you for your hard work.
Are you okay?
I did my best.
I'll bet on tomorrow.
Thank you for your hard work.
What did you say?
That's Kin-chan.
This time, it's rare to challenge a talent with an ordinary person.
Will there be a work that only responds to this cheering?
I'm looking forward to it.
Good morning.
I've reached a million subscribers.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm nervous before the show.
Don't you need this?
If I don't have this, I can't run away.
I can only see the line.
You!
You're a slippery woman.
Go home.
Go out quickly.
Hey!
I'm doing my best.
What's this?
You don't have a single pencil.
I'm going.
First of all,
We were the last.
At that time, I didn't have much confidence.
I thought it would be impossible.
What do you mean?
If it's more than 15 points, it's a success.
If it's less than 15 points, it's a failure.
I thought it would be impossible.
I thought it would be 7 or 8 points.
The only judge was Mr. Kanpei.
He was the only judge.
Mr. Kanpei is like a disciple of us.
I taught him how to write.
That's right.
Mr. Kanpei was there.
He didn't see it because he was nervous.
There was a lamp in front of him.
He didn't see who was the judge.
Who was there?
Mr. Masanobu Takashima.
Mr. Yamamoto.
Mr. Yukio Aoshima.
Mr. Yumiko Fujita.
The actress.
There are only people who don't understand.
Let's take a look.
You can't just forget the sound.
Do it yourself.
I can't do anything if I do it myself.
I'll do it.
This is the last work.
This program is the same as the general audience.
Please take a look.
And I passed.
Actually, I came last time.
I was angry because there was one more work.
I passed this time.
There may be judges and friends.
Please give me a high score.
Let's go.
He looks very nervous.
He is also the 40th.
I'm nervous.
Let's go.
No. 40 passed.
What happened?
What is the score of the judges?
What?
I'm sorry.
I'm glad.
Please give me a high score.
Are you doing it alone?
Yes.
I'm doing it alone.
Did you make it alone?
No.
What?
Who made it?
Yes.
Did you make it alone?
Please give me a high score.
I made it.
Don't fall.
Congratulations.
I'm glad.
I passed.
But I can't win.
You want to win, right?
Yes.
Please give me a high score.
Why are you looking up?
Please.
Don't step on my foot.
No.
I have plenty of time.
I made it.
I passed.
Please help your partner.
You don't have to put on makeup like this.
You did a good job.
I have three makeups.
Toshi still has three.
I did my best.
Thank you very much.
Look at the judges.
Mr. Kanpei.
You put on two makeups.
Yes.
I didn't do it.
I did it.
Mr. Aoshima and Mr. Takao.
Everyone is looking at you.
No.
You are making fun of me.
The director is noisy.
Thank you very much.
You have a good idea.
You are using your strength.
Thank you very much.
You are not losing strength.
Yes.
You are using your body.
I can feel it.
I felt the same way when I was judging.
I did it.
I'm doing it with my brain.
There was no music room.
Yes.
I said it all the time.
I said that there was no music room because I wasn't a guest.
I watched it again.
I'm glad.
I applied for the audition.
I passed the audition with everyone.
I will talk to you.
I have a wonderful friend.
I'm angry.
I'm very angry.
I'm very happy.
I'm embarrassed.
If I had one point, I would like to give it to you.
It's wonderful.
But don't give me 1 million yen.
It will be expensive.
Congratulations.
I passed the audition.
I'm very happy.
I'm going to win the 3rd place.
I can't see it.
It's in here.
I think it's in the 2nd place.
Announcement of the 3rd place.
3rd place.
No. 35 Waka Hana.
Congratulations.
That means, Kin-chan.
There are two more.
Are you going to win?
I was surprised when the next door came out.
There are two more.
I'm going to win the 3rd place.
No. 9 Polaroid.
There are two more.
That means, Kin-chan.
This is the last.
Thank you very much.
Let's hear the announcement.
Who will be the winner?
Announcement of the winner.
No. 13 Hanako.
The winner is Hanako.
There are people who lost the championship.
Finally, I realized it.
Thank you very much.
There are two more.
I'm going to win the 3rd place.
He is a bit of a joke.
Thank you very much.
Are you going home?
Go home.
Thank you very much.
There are people who lost the championship.
That's it.
This time, the level was higher than usual.
That's why it was bad when I came out.
The three or four people who won the championship were amazing.
I'm going to win the championship.
Why didn't you team up with him?
It was amazing.
I got 19 points.
It was good.
Give it to me.
I have a medal.
This is a medal.
This is amazing.
This is KIN-CHAN's signature.
It's hard to get.
It says line 40.
I have this.
Why did you bring this?
It's a gift.
This is a gift from our staff.
This is a gift from the commander.
I'm sorry.
This is the medal you were wearing.
You were pooping in brown before.
I don't know if I re-painted it.
I got 19 points.
I didn't win the championship.
I didn't wear the medal before I won the championship.
I won the championship once.
I don't know who won the championship.
If it was FUJITA, I'd forgive him.
AOSHIMA-CHAN...
CHAN!
AOSHIMA-CHAN!
I think he's wearing it because it was a good chance.
I'll check the video.
You'll see who didn't wear it.
The one who didn't wear it.
That guy!
There was no one who got 20 points.
That's right.
There was no one.
I don't know if I got 20 points.
I got some awards.
I didn't get any awards.
It's all because of FUJITA YUMIKO.
What are you going to do next time?
Next time...
How many times are you going to compete?
As I said before...
I'm going to do a bird-human contest.
Really?
I was surprised.
Why are you going to do a bird-human contest?
You didn't do that last time.
Why?
You're going to fly from 10 meters away.
You're going to die.
You're KIN-CHAN flying in the sky.
What?
Do I have to do KIN-CHAN's make-up again?
Are you stupid?
That's not it.
That's too much.
Next time, do JIROU-SAN.
I'll do it.
You should do it.
You're going to die.
I was flying in the sky the other day.
Which do you think is more difficult, skydiving or this?
Me!
Are you stupid?
How difficult is this?
You're going to die if you say it's hard.
I'm really scared.
You're not scared.
That height.
You can only fly this high.
I don't understand you.
I don't understand you at all.
It was amazing.
When I went to the top, my mouth was dry.
That's me.
I really understand you.
Are you stupid?
Next time, we're not going to do bird-human.
What is it?
One letter.
Are you going to do it?
I'm going to do this.
I'm going to call the people who are watching this on TV.
Let's do it together.
I was going to do it together.
What are you two doing?
You can't see it, right?
I don't want to do this.
What are you two doing?
What is it?
You're saying strange things.
If it's hard to see, I'll get you a big pair of sunglasses.
It's hot.
If the weather is good, let's burn it.
My throat is dry.
Let's do a simulation.
It's on the show, right?
The one-letter one.
Are you going to do that?
I'm going to do that.
And before that...
Practice.
Let's practice.
Let's try it.
Have you decided what to do?
I've decided.
What?
What are you going to do?
This is one-letter.
Let's play a lot.
In a different sense.
Let's gather everyone.
Let's go somewhere.
What are you going to do?
Everyone is a goldfish.
That's right.
Everyone is dressed like a goldfish.
About 1,000 people.
While doing this.
I'm going to walk around the river.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to take it from above?
I'm going to take it from above.
It's disgusting.
When I'm walking, the soccer ball comes flying.
About 1,000 people will kick it.
About 10,000 foreigners will come running.
Jogging.
When I shout, I'm a goldfish.
That's good.
That sounds interesting.
I'm going to beat up the guest, Kato Masaru.
There was a scene where I beat him up.
You are my student.
I'm going to beat him up with 5,000 people.
I'm going to break.
Let's do that before the show.
That's right.
Let's do it.
It doesn't matter if you're a goldfish or not.
Is there anyone who wants to be a goldfish?
There is.
It's not cool.
Really?
Please.
If you have short hair, please grow it out.
I can't do that.
I have something to bring.
A mouse-colored jacket.
And a thick tie.
I'm going to bring this.
I'm counting on you.
If you have time, practice like this.
Next, let's interview you.
Make an appearance.
I actually looked up a word.
It's a lot.
And it wasn't goldfish but thunder seal.
Thunder seal was very terrible.
I don't care about that story.
I'm not too sure.
It was fun.
That's enough!
How many people do you think I'll need to hire?
I don't know.
I'll see you next time.
Bye!
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.