ANTON MOI MATSURI!!!
The super special project, the first appearance of Moe Toukon Hakone Inoki!
I really hate it too!
In the familiar Oogiri Dai Gassen, the unpredictable happening takes place over and over again!
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming!
It's coming!
And now it's a big boom in the entertainment world!
Eguchi, Tamio, Ujiki, Itoi, are throwing firecrackers at the fishing competition with downtown!
Give it back to me!
In addition, there are tears to see, and tears to talk about!
The star is challenging with his life!
Furiko Bungee, the five-faced special of tears!
Oh, hello! It's been a long time since I've seen you!
And finally, the kid's special, Mazui Juice, is completed!
I'll give you anything you want!
Eat an egg!
What the hell is this?
It's October 15th, 9 o'clock, 11 o'clock, 2 hours.
I want to do a special with a kid.
This time I want to do it with just V.
When I look back on the past, I can bet on how flashy it was.
Are you betting on money?
I don't say that I spend a lot of money.
Is that so?
Yes.
There are more people on the screen.
It should be like that.
It's like I'm doing it.
It's a special.
It's flashy.
If it's not, I can't stop it.
What do you imagine a big one to be?
What?
What do you mean by big?
It's lively.
It's flashy.
It's like a festival.
That's fine.
When I went to Spain last year, I saw the Ushioi festival.
It was amazing.
It had an impact.
There were a lot of people.
It was flashy.
It was like a festival.
I think it's a good image for a special.
Ushioi festival.
It's like that.
It needs something that changes to Ushioi.
Something that changes to Ushioi.
Something flashy.
Even if you say so, it's not strong.
That's right.
I don't think it's scary.
It comes out and runs away.
It's strange that it runs away.
It's strong.
It's dangerous to take one step at a time.
It's like the end of the line.
It's like a tension.
It's flashy.
7 a.m.
A large bus is lined up in front of the Japanese TV.
And the young comedians are gathering one after another.
They are about to face the biggest challenge of their lives.
They are given a contract.
No matter what accident happens, no one will pick up the corpse.
Schoolday
The capital of passion, Spain.
It is a three-dimensional festival held every year in this country known as Tokyo.
They release a military ox.
And touching it is a sign of courage.
The most dangerous festival.
There is fear that goes beyond.
For the first time, the camera has entered the mysterious festival.
The first group has finally arrived at the festival's venue, Fujinosusono.
What is the fate of waiting for them?
From four buses, the young comedians get off one by one.
There are 200 of them.
And the costumes they wear are all red mufflers and red waistbands.
What does this mean?
There is no one to open their mouths, and they are covered by an invisible sense of anxiety.
And finally, the time has come.
Hello.
I've never seen you before.
Thank you very much.
Welcome to the traditional festival.
I hope they won't get hurt.
You've participated in the festival many times.
I was worried that you wouldn't be able to do it.
I wonder if you've been deceived.
Please explain the purpose.
Today, we're going to...
What's that?
It's a cage.
Isn't it a festival?
Something amazing is going to jump out.
There's a token towel here.
Who is it?
Everyone, please jump out and take it.
If you take it, you'll be the one with the most guts.
I want you to admit it to everyone who doesn't watch TV.
But it's a festival, right?
It's a festival.
It's fun, so don't say it.
Please listen to me.
Of course it's a festival, so I have a stall.
No way!
You can have as much fun as you want.
Now, please welcome the player, sensei, to the ostrich club.
Sensei!
We comedians have come here today without knowing what we're doing.
And I think it's a sign that the co-star and the staff are here.
But since we're here, the camera's position, the gun's position...
We're going to calculate everything and make a delicious reaction.
Please give him a round of applause.
Applause!
Why didn't you practice at home for three hours?
It wasn't like a meeting.
I was going to do something delicious.
Do you think you're the only one who's going to do something delicious at a place like this?
Ryu-chan, don't do that.
How the hell are you going to do that?
Now, without further ado, we're going to have an opening ceremony.
We're going to invite this person.
What are you doing?
Haru.
It's a cockfight.
What are you doing?
What is it?
Scary, scary, scary.
That, that, that.
It's a festival.
Yeah!
Let's go.
Yes.
Where are we going?
Let's go to the kid's special!
Anton Festival!
After the opening ceremony, you start walking down the path to the nurse.
Even if I get sick, if I can meet your smile and kindness, I'm looking forward to it.
It's a little complicated.
I look forward to working with you.
For the time being, I look forward to working with you at that time.
To a higher degree, to a warmer medical care.
It's a reliable medical device, Nipro.
Pickle Nessa.
Noebiya.
Yosenabe.
Grilled meat.
There's another wave plate on the grill.
Grilled meat is also delicious.
Delicious.
Tiger grill pot.
One more.
It's Tiger.
It's reliable, isn't it?
My second one.
There's another wave plate.
I can do it.
My third one.
Tiger hot plate.
One more.
It's Tiger.
Anton Festival.
Mr. Matsuo, Anton Festival has just begun.
It's amazing.
Will Inoki be able to do it?
It's terrible.
Inoki, Inoki.
I lost in front of the pool.
It's amazing.
Yamazaki.
It's a terrible festival.
It's terrible.
Everyone, let's fight.
Mr. Matsuo is serious.
It's terrible.
You often complain about the distance from the venue.
Where is the most dangerous place?
Distance.
In Chikichi.
Chikichi?
There's a cleaning lady.
Lady?
It's a tunnel.
I'll just tell you.
What?
Wait a minute.
I want to fall in love with you.
Do you know Takayama Kiribasami?
It's Takaeda.
I don't know.
I don't know at all.
I have a question for you.
Why do you look at the clock?
I don't know.
A clock?
My name is Kalimen.
Kalimen?
It's not easy to say.
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
Why are you a clown?
Ouch.
What is that?
What was that?
Are you okay?
You have a friend who is a talent.
What?
He is a talent.
A talent?
What about you?
What?
What is the difference between you and Chonan?
This is a plane.
Speak clearly.
Where is your foot?
It's one centimeter square, right?
It's one centimeter square.
Please check it.
This is also strange.
Chikishiki.
This is Hamada Masatoshi.
Let's have a special guest tonight.
One by one.
Don't look at the person over there.
Please introduce yourself one by one.
Last night, when I was at home, I was told to do my best.
So I opened the window and said thank you.
Then the two boys happily went home.
This morning...
What is your name?
My name is Yamasaki Hosei.
Nice to meet you.
Next.
I'm Jimmy Onishi.
I'm Miyagi.
Nice to meet you.
The other day, I watched the video of the boy's talk for the first time.
He was very kind when he was talking.
I'm Matsumoto from Shantan.
Nice to meet you.
Let's read the Atakamo book.
This is also familiar.
Atakamo book.
It's not written like that.
It's just an English book.
Let's proceed with the story as if it's written.
The first topic is this.
The happy friends with Elizabeth.
This is the book.
This book is called The happy friends with Elizabeth.
It's about when we were having a party in a garden in England.
Who is Elizabeth?
It's the queen.
The queen?
Who are the happy friends?
Please explain that.
The happy friends are like this.
The party was a dinner party.
Where did the friends go?
The friends gathered at the dinner party.
What do you want to say?
Francesco Zabien was born.
What is that?
What is Francesco Zabien?
The friend of Elizabeth.
The friend of Elizabeth?
Francesco Zabien was born.
The friend of Elizabeth.
We danced.
We danced happily.
At that time, the president came and kissed us.
What?
At the end, we all went somewhere to play.
Let's talk about Zabien.
Zabien is a wonderful friend.
Zabien is dead.
Don't kill such a good guy.
A letter came from Zabien.
Another friend.
Another friend?
Pe...
Then the bicycle broke down.
What the hell are you singing?
Yes.
The space shuttle.
Please don't look at it with cloudy glasses.
What are you talking about?
No one looks at it like that.
That's enough.
Yes.
Let's get on.
Let's get on the space shuttle.
Yes, yes.
There is a deep chair.
Oh, is that so?
Yes.
And by pushing this lever, the space shuttle starts.
I see.
When I saw that lever, I thought it was obviously a lever.
Huh?
I thought it was that.
Well then.
Well, it's just a circle.
It has been used by various individuals of the 18th century.
What?
For example, the butt of the space shuttle is shaped like a lotus root.
The lotus root was the same shape no matter how much I cut it.
Don't move it!
There is an on and off button.
It's easy to understand.
Yes, it's easy to understand.
And I pushed the on button.
I pushed it hard.
And then the sound of the space shuttle started to echo.
Yes.
Before the space shuttle started to move, I pushed the lever forward.
And then the space shuttle...
Hey, the phone is ringing!
After the commercial, Hama-chan is in trouble.
The biggest pain in the world.
I think that hair is important to take care of every day.
Shampoo and treatment of the plant story.
It was finished with amino acid ingredients.
I want you to use it for a long time.
From the Lion.
It's delicious to eat freshly cooked rice.
How much is it to eat freshly cooked rice?
Why don't you say something?
Stop it!
I see.
Freshly cooked rice is delicious because of the strong firepower of the IH.
It's delicious.
Tiger IH.
Freshly cooked rice.
You can remove the lid and wash it.
It's Tiger.
Big Challenge Toyota
Today, we're going to ride it.
Yes, we're going to ride it.
Speaking of riding, we're doing a big market campaign where you can ride various cars at the Toyota store.
We're doing it.
I'm going to go too.
10,000 large market campaigns nationwide.
What Toyota has done for OneBox in the future.
For example, the safety design of the large indoor space.
Granvia is here.
Head-on!
I'm going to play the music.
Please tell the other person with the movement of your mouth.
First of all, the topic.
The topic is this.
What?
One ear?
Mouth.
That's why.
Show me your mouth.
So-re-te-ni-te-re.
I don't know.
Please tell him now.
What is it?
I don't know.
What?
Did you say it?
That's right.
Don't say it in a weird way.
I don't know.
The whole sentence is very natural.
That's right.
Wakasanagi.
What did you say, Miyagi?
I don't know.
You don't know.
Wakasanagi.
Watatakayagi.
Now,
I'll do my best.
The last one is Kokon Tozai.
Omatani Monmari.
Since it's a special,
I'll pay for it.
Now, let's see the Monmari doll.
Here you go.
Wow.
The rules are explained.
The two players who sit side by side
will compete in Kokon Tozai first.
But if they can't answer,
a smelly crotch will come from the front.
And this time, there is a new challenge.
And this time, I'll open the back.
When the players sit here,
the person who came out of this box
will go to you.
The Monmari member will be decided here.
Now, Matsumoto-san.
Which box will you choose?
Mari.
The member of the fourth box,
the Monmari member, please come out.
Wow.
You're the worst.
I choose Mon.
Now, the third box.
Here you go.
The Monmari member, please come out.
I saw it.
What is this?
Wow.
I can't breathe.
Now, let's open it.
I'm talking.
Who is this?
A foreign band.
A foreign band?
Ready.
Cisco.
Abba, Abba, Abba.
Wow, Abba was taken.
I only had Abba next.
Why?
Ah.
You, you, you.
You too.
Eagles.
I don't know.
Wow.
It's like a moss.
It's true.
The next song is an anime song.
An anime song.
One phrase is enough.
Let's sing.
Let's start with Mr. Matsumoto.
The first human, go, go, go.
My father is a salaryman.
The train is my life.
I raise my head.
50 years of my life.
Long.
Wait a minute.
Why is it so long?
Famous gag.
I'm doing it.
What?
I'm shocked.
My brother is black.
I was surprised.
What?
No way.
I'm Goku.
What?
Don't look at me.
Who are you?
I'm Genji Sawada.
What?
I don't know what you're saying.
My father.
Who is Tsukie?
I don't know.
Don't ask me anything.
Who is it?
Rice.
Don't look at me.
Ultracute.
Dobby.
Taro.
Ultraman Ace.
Ultraman from space.
What?
What number is Yamazaki-san?
No.1 box, please.
Over here.
It's a line.
Open.
It's so hard.
Your pants are pink.
Is this a live show?
Pe-san, this is the setting.
Yamazaki-san vs. the president.
Let's start with the easy part.
The name of the fish.
Tuna.
Mackerel.
Kamasu.
I said it.
Sake.
Fish.
I don't know.
I said it.
Yamazaki-san vs. the president.
Tell me the name of the glasses.
I don't know the name of the glasses.
I'm sorry.
Sushi.
Tuna.
Mackerel.
I said it.
Time's up!
Let's start with the easy part.
You sit here.
Who's next?
I'm next.
You can't do that.
You're not allowed to do that.
What's wrong with you?
You can't do that.
You sit here.
Who's the classical composer?
Who's next?
You can't do that.
You!
Beethoven.
Schumann.
Tchaikovsky.
You can't do that!
Sorry.
Let's go to the third floor.
Again?
What floor?
You're laughing.
You should laugh.
Should you laugh halfheartedly?
If you're laughing like that,
you should laugh loud.
You should laugh halfheartedly.
That's a silly face.
The members of Candy's!
Candy's members!
Dan-chan
Su-chan
Miki-chan
Okay!
Wait, wait, wait, please don't do this
This is a big deal
Wait, hey!
Wait a second, hey!
I'm starting to feel really bad
I'm starting to feel anxious
Open more, open more
From Akure-san, let's go! Three members!
Wait a second!
Jun-san, okay!
Cho-saku
Okay, Cho-saku, okay!
Shoji-san
Shoji-san, okay!
Okay, last one, please!
I really don't like this either
It's still hot, it's hot!
It's hot!
It's cold!
It's really smelly!
There's a problem
If I'm late, the show will be canceled
That's just what you think
If I come on time,
the show will be canceled
That's just what you think
It's really hot!
If I'm late, the show will be canceled
Why?
That's why you're late!
After the commercials, it's time for the show to get hot!
Now, the heat is getting hotter
This is the hot flavor
Asahi Super Dry
The second bottle!
Alright!
One more bottle!
Hey, Kiki!
Dad, one more bottle!
It's really good!
It's Asahi Dad's name
One more bottle!
Yes, did you have a good time?
I've been a nurse for three months
I'm not a full-time nurse yet
But from the patient's point of view, I'm also a nurse
Even if it's hard, I can laugh at the patient's smile
I'll do my best not to betray your trust
What's wrong?
Excuse me!
With Yoriko, we'll take you to a warmer place
Cosmetic LUNESSA
Noevia
Is it still good?
Even if it's cut in half, it's not that big
If there were two, it would be enough
I think so too
No, that's impossible
It's only two hours
Also, there are a lot of specials coming up
I see
In that sense, I want something fresh
Like casting
That's right
Then, let's do it outside
Let's do it outside
Outside is good
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Arai, we have a special
Celebrity Tsurikichi
Hello
We're back
When you think of downtown, you think of a black bus
Everyone in the world thinks that
Today, we have a special
Celebrity Tsurikichi
Let's gather
We're going to do it
It can't be helped
I want to do it
First, Itoi Shigesato
Nice to meet you
I think it would be nice if you could do it
If it's something you don't understand, you can do anything
Yes
It's hard
Is this season hard?
When we did it last time, it was fine
But this time, we can do it even in Hamada
Anyway, I was overwhelmed by that big one
Yes
That's big
Look, 46? 47?
There are 47
I think it's the biggest I've ever caught
Your face has changed
You were kind until now
I want to be a kind uncle
That's why I'm going to catch it
If you can catch it, please catch it
Next, Mr. Ujiki Tsuyoshi
It seems to be a good one
It's good
This is important
When you come to Kawaguchiko, you have to buy an entry ticket
This is connected to the maintenance of Mizuimi and the protection of fish
I recommend fishing cooperation
I really like to be fashionable
I'm not fashionable
Please do your best
Next, Mr. Okuda Tamiyo
Hello
I was fishing without a job
When you come here, you have to fish a little
When I first started, I couldn't fish in Kawaguchiko
When I first came here, I couldn't fish
It's a lie
I met my wife in Kawaguchiko
Don't say nonsense
Please do your best
Finally, Mr. Eguchi Yosuke
Eguchi is fishing
I came here about two years ago
I haven't been fishing recently
Kawaguchiko is like a pond
Are you tired of fishing here?
I'm tired of fishing here
What are you talking about?
What do you think of this member?
He is a strong opponent
Who is the strongest?
I heard a lot of rumors
I went fishing with Mr. Itoi once
How was it?
It was amazing
Eguchi doesn't care about downtown
That's not true
I will explain the rules
If you catch a big fish, you win
It's a big fish
Let's start
Thank you
Let's go
Can you bring me a boat?
You can bring me a boat
Are you ready?
Let's go
Let's do our best
I'm happy to think this is my job
The competition is about to begin
I've been fishing since last night
I want to fish twice as much as yesterday
My rival is Hamada
I hate Hamada
I hate him
I'm doing this as a science teacher
If I catch fish at my usual pace, I can fish
I have my own will
If I win, I will win
I have a long career
I can't lose
I wear a hat to fight
I won't lose
I'm going to fish
Everyone is strong today
I'll do my best
Thank you
Everyone is going to fish
But the temperature is 15 degrees
You need advanced techniques to lure the enemy
The same goes for downtown
I'm wearing a hat
Hamada's first fish is...
I'm sorry
I should have fished
Eguchi's rod is too big
The pot is a magic pot
It's a magic pot
It's easy to cook
It's easy
Tiger Magic Pot
It's a tiger
The pot is small, but it can cook a lot
It's electric, so it's easy to cook
The pot's mirror
Tiger Electric Pot
It's a tiger
It's smooth, shiny
From the lion
I'll take a walk later
My head hurts
The buffalo is gentle and fast
I'm going
I want to heal my headache quickly
From the buffalo
I'm going to catch a fish
This is the news of the fall
Takeyuki Asahi's harvest sale
Asahi cultivation festival raw beer
This fall's delicious beer is
Asahi's cultivation festival
A new appearance!
In the shadow of the battle of Sekigahara, another battle between the two women unfolds.
In Sengoku Allcast, Jishu Yoru Kuji no Shitteri Tsumori is...
The joy and sorrow of a woman who has survived a turbulent life.
Toyotomi Hideyoshi's Wife, Nene, A Disaster of the Heart
Here it comes!
Ah, I missed it!
I missed it!
I'm so disappointed!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey!
You look so sad and happy!
Hey, hey!
As for me...
It's getting a little hot.
Ah, I took it off!
I took it off.
I took it off and spread it out again!
I'm so disappointed!
On the other hand, the designated combination is really at my pace.
As soon as I got to the jighead, it came.
It's the speed of the season.
It's pretty nerve-racking, isn't it?
At this time of the day.
Did it come?
What a surprise!
It hit Matsumoto right at the start!
Ah, it's coming!
It's coming!
The first hit is Matsumoto.
It's not that big, though.
But I can see the impatience.
I can see the color of impatience.
No, no, no.
Patience! Patience!
The downtown team caught it.
This is bad.
The Itoi-Ujiki combination doesn't even know that it allowed Matsumoto to take the lead.
Ah, it's coming!
Liar!
Masuka!
It's still hooked.
Look at this! It's huge!
Look at this!
Look!
It seems that Hamada is hooked today.
Oh!
It's coming!
It's coming! It's coming!
45 minutes have passed.
I'm curious about the other boats.
Is Hamada finally hooked?
I carefully approach him.
For a moment, I thought so.
We met again.
I hope it doesn't become zero for the program.
The Itoi-Ujiki boat is approaching while changing the point.
It's too big.
It was amazing.
It's big.
It's a rabbit.
I'm hungry.
It's been an hour.
Only one of the Matsumoto's boats is still hooked.
Everyone!
Let's move!
Why aren't you all moving?
I'm sorry!
We're moving!
Let's move!
I'll take you to the next place.
The two of us are going to the next place.
Let's move!
It won't end like this.
Taking pride in Tsurikichi,
I head to the shore of the lake to change the point.
Anxiety and anxiety make everyone nervous.
Is there a black bass at this point?
It's coming, isn't it?
Yes.
I think it's coming.
It's coming, isn't it?
It's definitely coming.
It's coming.
It's slow.
It's a good transfer.
It's definitely there.
Eguchi is...
...going crazy again.
I have a bad feeling about this.
I'm so frustrated.
Itoi and Ujiki are one step away from each other again.
Alright!
And finally, Itoi hits it.
That's good.
Grab it!
It seems to be in a bad shape.
Itoi seems to have caught it.
Egiichi!
What is this?
What did you do?
You should be more excited.
On the other hand, Ujiki, who has no chance at all, is in a strange mood.
I shouldn't have been impatient.
Shake, shake, shake.
You're good at playing.
What's wrong?
Hey, hey, baby.
Baby.
What's going on?
Eguchi Okuda is hit by a bus pro.
That's a pro.
It's quiet over there.
It's talking.
It's like...
It's like a friend has died.
It's raining.
It's raining non-stop.
It's the worst condition.
Hamada is still...
Oh, it's you again.
You come often.
Hey, look again.
You're good at it.
Hey, you're here.
Welcome home.
Okuda and Egiichi have come to the abandoned Kansai.
The sound of the reels echoes lonely.
And Hamada...
...is in a big trouble.
Something's stuck.
It's stuck.
Okuda is finally hit.
Damn it.
Did you get it?
I got it.
I'll get it.
I got a reel.
Damn it.
I don't think I can do this no matter how many times I do it.
Anyway, they can't catch it.
There's only a little time left.
I got it.
Did you get it?
They've already caught a blue sea urchin.
I got it.
Itoi has finally caught the second one.
What's that firework?
And the sign of the end rang.
I just heard a strange sound, but I don't know.
I don't know.
I wonder if they're waiting for something.
It's over.
It's over?
It's over now.
Really?
It's over.
After 120 minutes of fighting, the fishermen have returned.
It's cold.
The results are out.
Everyone has a cooler box in front of them.
First of all, it's Itoi.
Itoi.
What is it?
It's a little plain.
How much is this?
It's small.
This is different.
How do you know this?
It's about 27.
27?
27.
Let's open Tsuyoshi Ujiki's.
It's not here.
It's good, it's good.
I'm really happy.
Let's open it gradually.
This was caught by Mazumoto.
I can't hold it.
Endure it and put it in here.
I'm not a girl.
I'm scared.
What are you doing?
Hold it down.
It's big.
It's like this.
It's over here.
28.
Let's look at Yosuke Eguchi.
It's not here.
It's in.
Let's look at Okudatami at the end.
It's here.
It's big.
It's not here.
It's small.
It's just right.
This is 28cm, Mazumoto's.
Thank you.
I'm going to give it to you.
I want this.
This is the dream of a fisherman.
Everyone, thank you for your hard work.
Let's eat.
This is delicious.
Today's winner is Mazumoto's.
It's amazing.
He signed it.
It's big.
It's rare to see this size.
It's good.
I want to do this.
I want to win.
This first tournament closed the curtain with Mazumoto's victory.
I realized that I didn't have enough conversation with the fish.
Before the tournament started, I caught some fish.
I lost.
I'm glad I caught it.
If I can catch it, I can't catch it.
It's a big deal.
Next time, let's catch a big fish.
Thank you for your hard work.
Next time, let's catch a small fish.
After this, I won't be a kid anymore.
When is this going to be broadcasted?
It's going to be broadcasted in two days!
Two days?
Two days? I can't say it sideways!
Who are you asking?
Sideways?
I can't say it sideways!
Let's do it!
After this, I won't be a kid anymore.
When is this going to be broadcasted?
In two days!
After this, I won't be a kid anymore.
This is similar, right?
Right?
They're all similar!
After this, I won't be a kid anymore.
I'll be a mysterious transfer student.
I won't be a kid anymore.
After this, I won't be a kid anymore.
Let's start with the old man.
What are you talking about?
After this, I won't be a kid anymore.
I'm scared!
You guys aren't good viewers!
After this, I won't be a kid anymore.
I'll do a new gag.
A new one?
Yes, a new one.
It's my first time doing it.
After this, I won't be a kid anymore.
I won't be a kid anymore.
Watch me!
After this, I won't be a kid anymore.
Don't watch the opening!
Nice to meet you.
What was that? I forgot.
I'll do it again.
After this, I won't be a kid anymore.
I won't be a kid anymore.
From 5 seconds ago.
5, 4, 3, 2...
Wait a minute!
Your seconds are weird!
Let's go with a sharp taste.
5, 4, 3...
5 seconds ago!
Please.
5 seconds ago.
5, 4...
Let's continue.
5 seconds ago.
Just once.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1...
That's it!
A special episode with the kids!
A nostalgic reunion with the stars!
Hello.
Today, we have a special episode with the kids.
From now on, we'll have the stars appear.
There are people you want to see, right?
We've invited people who want to see us.
They're here to see us.
Then, let's have the first guest appear!
Please!
Haru!
I'm sorry for being such a star.
Haru Ichiban.
He was 16 when he started working for Amaguri Taro.
Back then, he didn't know what to do.
But he was kind and strict with his parents.
His name is Misao Watanabe.
Today, he'll be seeing him for the first time in 11 years.
What will you do if you see him?
If I see him, I'll tell him that I brought him to this world for 11 years.
He's been doing this a lot lately.
I want him to do this with me.
With Inoki?
With Inoki.
I don't know if I'll be able to see him or not.
For now, let's have him set up.
What do you mean, set up?
There's a setting to meet him.
Let's set it up.
Please set it up.
What does this have to do with meeting him?
A special episode for the kids.
The star's long-awaited meeting.
Let me explain how to meet him.
We've prepared 3 cranes that are 30 meters high.
Today's guests will be lifted up to the top of the mountain.
They'll be released into the windmill.
After that, they'll be able to meet him.
Please lift him up.
You don't have to see him anymore.
Let's start with Haru Ichiban.
Let's have him meet his boss, Watanabe.
5 seconds to meet him.
5 minutes to meet him.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5 minutes to meet him.
Watanabe!
What's going on?
His boss is going home soon.
I don't think he'll be able to meet him.
1 or 2 seconds to meet him.
Next, let's have the guests come in.
This is Mr. Manman.
Who do you want to meet?
He's my first partner.
What's his name?
Oscar Mescal.
That was bad.
I don't want to say it, but it's embarrassing.
I'm Oscar.
Thank you.
I want to meet Mescal.
It's embarrassing.
He's from the east.
His first partner when he was a student, Shinichiro Kodama.
He returned the 20,000 yen he borrowed from a poor student for the first time in 13 years.
I was so frustrated.
I'll be better than him.
Someday, I'll return the 20,000 yen.
That's a great chance today.
Really?
I can see it from above.
Can you see it from above?
I can definitely see it from above.
Let's go give it back.
Let's set it up.
What kind of setting is that?
It's the setting of the 5th generation.
What do you mean, please?
Is this a situation where you're going to return the money?
I have money.
I have money, but this is cool.
I'm waiting for you.
Wait a minute.
Stop it.
I'm really scared.
I can't be funny. I can't be funny. I can't be funny.
I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared.
I'm scared.
Help me.
Up to this point, we have provided you with reliable daily necessities, Tiger magic bottle,
Nipro Lion,
Asahi Beer, Noebiya, and many other sponsors.
Our journey is super hard all day long.
Uno
Kiseido Uno Super Heart Booth
Welcome.
I'm coming in.
1.5 times chunks of
Welcome to the new Pablon.
This year too, a new minor has been released!
For the first time, choro choro chi-pappa, chi-pappa, chi-pappa!
That's what I said!
Let's get it right with a quiz!
Let's eat it!
Delicious Mori Mori campaign, in progress!
This year too, Hokkaido is delicious!
It doesn't matter if it's serious or not
I want to embrace the punishment of fishing
With two faces, I'll fall in love
Last One
Ginza Jewelry Maki, Robinson Sapporo store 1st floor
Let's go!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Cheers!
This is my hobby
Ah, green gum!
Let's chew on the aftertaste
A green ticket in your mouth
Dotte Green Gum
Please treat me well
The night in Sapporo was cold
The sea in Ohotsuku was harsh
The cold winter was cold
5 seconds to answer
Stop it!
Answer!
What are you doing?
I'll give it back!
Give it back! Give it back!
Don't dig the wall!
I didn't return 20,000 yen!
Your face has changed
What is this movement?
What is this?
This is the Washington Convention
What kind of life is this?
Koda Shin
He wants to meet his best friend, Naruko
He wants to sing a song for him
Koda, are you ready?
Sing well
Koda Shin
5 seconds to answer
Shin-chan!
Please welcome the next guest!
Thank you for coming today
He wants to meet his best friend, Tooru Tsuboshima
What should we do today?
We don't have a reunion
Let's have a reunion
We can do this
We can shoot a movie
Let's do this until we can have a meeting
Are you sure?
I feel like I'm going to cry
Right, Higashi-san?
You should have a stiff neck
Let's go to the setting
It's not here?
What is this?
It's called a harness
I'm used to it
How many times have you put it on?
I don't think I need to put it on
I'm already moved
I feel like I'm going to cry
I'm the vice president of the PTA
Are you okay?
You have a sports meeting tomorrow
I don't need to sit in the PTA seat
Please get in
This is really scary
Stop it!
What is this?
Tsuboshima-san, let's have a meeting
5 seconds
Time's up!
Tsuboshima, long time no see
I've been trying to contact you
I'm going to make a phone call to my mother!
Hello?
How are you doing?
Long time no see!
Brother, did you talk to Yoko?
I talked to her very briefly.
I'm so embarrassed.
I said, long time no see.
You said, I'll call you later.
I said, I'll call you later.
Oh, I'm scared.
I'll call you later.
Hideo Takamatsu. He wants to meet Mr. Sukematsu, a teacher from elementary school.
It's been 50 years since the last time they met.
Please welcome Mr. Sukematsu!
Let's go!
5 seconds!
4!
3!
Stop it!
2!
1!
He's not here!
I'm looking for him!
Mr.Skema, we are sorry for your loss.
Please come back again.
That's terrible!
You guys are too terrible!
You guys are not human!
Please come back again!
You guys are too terrible!
Rock music, refreshing.
Rikka Molto Club, 1880 yen.
Please come back again.
This is a shampoo shop, isn't it?
Yes.
I finally found it.
I think people are weak.
Shiseido
New Super Mild Shampoo
Do you like hair?
The aroma has become new.
I think it's better to be new.
Take a new aroma.
It's a lie.
The campaign is in progress.
I'm going to dye my hair.
Don't pull it straight.
Don't hurt your hair.
Easy straight.
It's easy, isn't it?
Maxim
Do you choose coffee because of the aroma?
If you don't have this aroma, you can't call it Maxim.
The masterpiece of aroma.
Maxim
New Super Mild Shampoo
Do you want to talk?
Hey
What are you doing?
New Super Mild Shampoo
What are you laughing at?
power
Beemer Baby
What the hell is this?
10 yen!
Here you go.
Thank you.
Idiot!
He wanted to be a policeman.
What the hell is this?
Well, well, well, well.
Even with such a look, he's a bastard.
Then when you're done with the evidence, go home right away!
Oh, that's right!
See you later.
Even with such a look, when you're done with the evidence, go home right away!
Idiot!
That's right!
What the hell is this?
Idiot!
Can you leave?
By the way, where are you from?
I don't know.
You're so mean!
What the hell are you eating?
Shall we go home?
Yes.
What the hell are you eating?
You.
It's my first time.
It's your first time?
What the hell are you eating?
Die!
There are three foreign guests today.
Even if you do this?
It doesn't matter.
Please tell me what it is.
Mr. Enzo.
Mr. Enzo?
Speak clearly.
You can't sell it like that.
There's a date course near Port Pier Hotel in Kobe.
It doesn't matter whether you know it or not!
He's wearing a full-blown Soviet mask.
Do you know?
I don't know!
Get out!
What time is it now?
Four o'clock?
It's a little less than four o'clock.
It's about half past ten.
It's a little past ten.
It's a little less than four o'clock.
What are you going to do?
What should I do?
Something that's connected to the regulars?
It's a special for the regulars.
That's right.
What's connected?
That's what I've been talking about lately.
Juice?
Is that kind of thing connected?
I've been telling you, but you're not listening.
It's juice.
It's really bad.
This commercial is bad, too.
It's bad for your health, too.
It's really bad.
Get out!
A special for the regulars.
A bad juice project.
The annual production volume of our country's juice is 12.72 million kiloliters.
Last year, 873 new products were introduced.
The juice industry is in conflict with the 4.5 trillion yen market.
While each company is working hard to make it delicious,
our users dare to make bad juice and sell it.
We immediately asked each beverage company for cooperation.
I'd like to make a bad juice and sell it.
Would you like to cooperate?
Yes, I understand.
While each company was struggling with the phrase, bad,
we finally got a response from a beverage company.
The staff went there without taking anything.
Thank you very much.
I got it. Let's do it.
But I can't make anything bad for your health.
And after the negotiation, we got the president's approval.
The five causes of badness are
sweetness, spiciness, bitterness, sourness, and smell.
It's in these exquisite blends.
It's hard to make a juice that goes against the world.
After many trials and errors, we finally got a sample.
Let's start with today's order.
This is Matsumoto family's water.
Matsumoto family's water.
It tastes like iron-smelling water.
There are many people who drink this kind of water.
It doesn't look good.
If you go to a restaurant, you'll see this.
Squid ink beverage.
It tastes like sweet and sour with squid ink.
It tastes like hot cake syrup.
It's not good.
This is not good.
Super carbonated beverage.
Let's soak the taste and drink up to the limit of carbonation.
I like this.
Spice juice.
The combination of wasabi and chili pepper creates an unexpected bitter taste.
It stinks.
This is not good.
It smells like poop.
Stinky juice.
It blended the flavor of Dorian and challenged the ultimate smell.
It stinks.
I already smelled it.
This is Matsumoto family's water.
It stinks.
This is not good.
It smells really bad.
What are you doing?
It stinks.
Get out of here.
And the candidate juice is...
Dorian flavored stinky juice.
It is cultivated in Southeast Asia and is praised as the king of tropical fruits.
However, for some reason, it is forbidden to bring it to the first-class hotels in Southeast Asia.
It is to make the inside of the river smell like rotten onions.
Dorian is addicted to stinky juice.
The project was supposed to proceed smoothly with this juice.
I'm sorry, but there's a problem with the juice.
What is it?
The situation is not good.
Help me.
Are you kidding me?
The third boss of the tourism industry.
The seven-seater GT Chariot has various uses.
It is powerful.
Mitsumishi New Chariot.
Okaidoku Resort Runner MS is here.
My, my curry is with rice.
Three minutes in the microwave.
Otsuka's new recipe.
The name of the product is...
I don't need anything.
I'll throw it away.
I'm looking for you.
With my soul.
Don't stop the time.
Shout it out.
I can't stand it.
I'll give you all of me.
It's time to dye it.
Dye it.
It's easy to dye.
It's beautiful.
It's time to dye it.
It's easy to dye.
It's night.
Good morning.
A new elixir that prevents dullness of the skin.
Dramatical Essence.
How do you feel?
Why didn't you say anything?
Hello?
I...
I know.
I like it because it doesn't change.
Suntory New Chariot 1880 yen.
New Chariot 1880 yen.
I'm sorry.
It's about the juice.
There was a problem.
It was a harsh reality that was waiting for us.
Due to Dorian's terrible smell,
the production line will be unusable.
Due to the factory's production prohibition,
the project was approved.
New sample production became urgent.
New Chariot 1880 yen.
Hello.
Good morning.
A very spicy juice.
Two red peppers in one.
It's so spicy that you can't drink it without water.
First, drink it.
I don't know if it's spicy.
Is it spicy?
It's spicy.
What is this?
The feeling is strange.
What kind of feeling is this?
This is amazing.
It's a fire.
It hurts.
If you drink one, you can eat two red peppers.
How many lemons can you eat?
It's a stinky juice.
It reduced the smell of the previous one to one-tenth.
We have to be careful when producing this.
Is it a stinky one?
Yes.
It's much thinner.
It's bad.
It's a tea without sweetness.
It's famous as a diet drink.
I don't know if it's a little bitter.
It's not normal.
It's not sweet at all.
Drink it.
What is this?
It's not sweet at all.
It's the final decision.
I think it's the first one today.
It's either the first one or the last one.
What happens if you warm the first one?
I think it will work.
It will be warmed.
It's normal.
I'm sorry.
I think it's okay to drink it all at once.
I'm going to drink a bad juice.
I don't like it.
It's burning.
What is this?
It's not sweet at all.
I don't like it.
I'm getting numb.
In winter, the mouth gets warm.
It's only the mouth that gets warm.
It's like I'm getting cold around here.
A bad juice that shocked the members.
What is the truth?
It will lead humanity to a new world.
It's called Gakimizu.
What is this?
It tastes like the tears of a dragon or the sweat of a fox.
It will make the world go crazy.
It's the worst taste that mankind has ever tasted.
Gakimizu in downtown.
It will be on sale this year.
After the commercial, something will happen at the children's meeting room.
It's true. It's delicious.
Mineral water for dry skin in dry season.
You can use it anytime, anywhere. It feels good.
It's just right for the dry skin to melt a little.
Natural mineral water.
Let's use it.
Shall we do it?
It's Yu-mai.
Look.
It's delicious.
Welcome.
What is it?
That hat doesn't suit you.
I'm worried about my hair.
Then it's Adelance's Pinpoint Cyber.
Strong and light nature. Pinpoint Cyber.
Call me.
Where's your father?
I'll start with this coffee.
I like Nescaf Kusada.
A driving feel that has never existed before.
Invex II Sports Mode 5 speed AT.
I'm sure it will change the sedan.
New Diamante.
A new special user, the new 25X.
The new liquid is moist and sticky.
It feels good.
This is non-oily.
It's moist, but it's not sticky all the time.
Optune Liquid Foundation.
It's big.
Do you want that one?
That's not what I mean.
How is it?
Only the delicious part is the best.
It's delicious.
That's right.
Nescaf Kusada's Pinpoint Cyber.
Come on out.
No chicken!
I'm wearing this skirt even though my legs are like this.
It's so cold.
It's cold.
It's okay.
The cats gather and start to fight.
When that's over, the next one is...
I understand.
I haven't said anything yet.
It doesn't matter when it comes back.
It doesn't matter at all.
I'm going to run away quickly.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter at all.
It doesn't matter when it comes back.
The step is so hard.
This is all I can do.
Why is Matcha so beautiful?
What are you doing?
What do you want?
You're so big, but you're still so small.
What are you doing?
I think there's one more.
Can you spend money again?
What?
Money? I don't have any money.
You don't have any money?
I don't have any money.
I don't use it anymore.
So, from Hama-chan,
I'd like to ask Matcha if she can do skydiving.
Skydiving?
After the commercial, something happened to Matcha.
What will you do?
The real Honbushi Honkatsu.
The new Honbushi Honkatsu.
The bubbles are...
Do you know?
Suntory Hops Dry
HONDA COWBOY
For example,
It's a chocolate like kinu.
No matter what, it's kinu.
Glico
ENRICH
When you apply for ENRICH,
500 people get the product they want every month.
We are doing a gift sale.
For more information, please see the back of the product and sign up.
ENRICH
This year's Observe is...
Adding Kubuteka Kurumi and adding more ice...
Adding Kubuteka Kurumi
Observe of Kubuteka Kurumi
Toyotaiya
The customers not only taste the rice, but also check the quality of the rice.
Yes, we only serve good rice.
It's good, isn't it?
We deliver delicious rice from all over the country.
All rice
What did you say?
Skydiving and...
Heipo Torimonocho
What?
Skydiving and...
Heipo Torimonocho are listed.
What are you doing?
Ema-chan.
Skydiving and...
Heipo Torimonocho are listed.
Which one is good?
I think it's better to close it with you at the end.
What do you think?
Well...
It's not good to do it.
Hama-chan's overseas trip is good.
It's good.
It's hard. It's a goal.
It's a strange story to go abroad without a purpose.
It's overseas.
It's been a long time.
But 30 minutes...
Okamoto-chan did it.
It's not good to go.
It's a long time ago.
It's better to close it gradually.
At the end, it's us.
It's a long time ago.
What should I do?
I don't know if it's okay to do that.
I wonder if it's okay.
That's the idea.
I don't know if it's okay to do that.
I don't know if it's okay.
I don't know.
It's hard.
I wonder if it's okay to do that.
Ok, I'll do it.
You must watch it.
I wonder if it's okay to do that.
What should I do?
Did you sleep well?
Do it.
What do you think?
Like a splash.
Um.
What to do.
We've done a lot of patterns.
What do you think, Seiko?
Right now?
Like a splash.
What do you think?
Um.
What to do.
What?
Let's do it like that.
Good.
Good work.
What to do.
Get the car in the car.
Yeah.
Good work.
Thank you very much.
What the hell is going on here?
I took a dump in the morning.
Hi.
It's been a while.
Don't do that.
I feel sorry for you.
These are new shoes.
I bought new shoes because I thought they were really new.
It's only a few seconds old.
It's not old, is it?