Manager Okamoto.
His unceasing anger has taken over many of Ikuta's adventures.
It has knocked us into the depths of fear.
And now, once again...
The brief
Manager Okamoto's anger!
Umazuma-san.
Yes?
That's the one with 21.
Ah, that's the one.
That's the one.
That's the one with 21.
That's the one, right?
That's the one.
I thought that was the one with 21.
So, what is it, SHUIMI-san?
What's your name, Okamoto-san?
How's Okamoto!?
I've been calling you.
Again?
So, you've been calling me?
No, it's not that, but...
You're not angry?
Not much.
Is it soft?
He's been calling me when he's not angry!
Why have you been calling me?
Where are you?
Over here.
Over here?
Ah, inside the studio.
In the studio?
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Isn't there a place to shoot?
Oh, there is.
Huh?
Oh, there he is.
What are you up to?
Oh, good morning.
Good morning.
Hey, hey.
Huh?
I can't hear you.
Hey.
I'm here.
I'm here for work.
What are you doing?
Sorette Nittere.
Sorette Nittere?
That's right.
Many people have done it.
Oh, I see.
Sorette Nittere.
I'm here.
I'm here for work.
What do you mean?
It's not me or Yamazaki.
It's not?
I refuse that.
Why do you refuse it?
You can't accept it.
You're not a talent.
Sorette Nittere.
Sorette Nittere is a Japanese TV program with many celebrities.
Okamoto joins them.
It's one set today.
Are you going to sleep together?
I'm going to sleep together.
It's been a while.
Don't cry.
The person in charge is here.
Where?
That person.
He's the real one.
The real one?
Sorette Nittere?
The person who made it.
Oh, really?
Is it okay?
It's not a talent.
I think it's funny.
Is it really okay?
Everyone, get ready.
This is the camera.
This is it.
It's the end of the take one.
I'll do it right away.
Let's go.
Really.
Ready.
Yes.
Sorette Nittere.
Spring Special.
Yes.
That's it.
Okay, okay, okay.
That's good.
Damn it.
What's that?
It's okay now.
This is normal, right?
Normal?
Normal.
Sorette Nittere.
Then I'll do one more.
Yes.
Please do it again.
Normal version.
Ready.
Yes.
Sorette Nittere.
That's it.
The cat is perfect at the end.
Yes.
That's it.
Sorette Nittere.
It's perfect.
It was perfect.
Thank you.
Wait a minute.
It's a happy job.
Hey.
Why are you doing that?
Is this a good thing?
Sorette Nittere.
I'll do it.
Everyone, be more nervous.
Be more nervous.
There's something like this.
Sorette Nittere.
The atmosphere was good.
You're the one who's in a bad mood, right?
I got it.
Yamasaki is good at this.
He gets hit and goes from the waist.
What do you want to do?
Be more dangerous.
I don't know.
Wait a minute.
You're a professional.
A big producer.
What's a big producer?
I'm not a big producer.
Stop it.
I don't know.
Shut up.
I don't have a job.
I don't know.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
It's funny.
I know.
I'll stop.
I'll show you the bottom.
Did you make the bottom?
I made it.
It's underwater.
I have to hold a fishing rod.
I'll do it underwater.
It's funny.
You're drinking wine.
This is the first one.
Is it like this?
Yes.
I don't think it's possible.
Cool.
Awesome.
Put your feet on it.
A dolphin.
I'm sorry.
It's a dolphin.
You can swim.
It's amazing.
Why?
This is the first one.
Cool.
You can hold it like this.
Yes.
You'll do this?
I'll hold a grumbler and a fishing rod.
And I'll do a waltz.
Please do a waltz.
I'll do this.
It's underwater.
I prepared it.
Really?
Yes.
You're doing it again.
What do you do?
You go in.
After 30 seconds.
You come out.
You do this.
You do that.
That's one.
You do this.
You do that.
Can you do that?
Yes, I can.
I can do that.
It's a little hard.
He's saying it's hard.
I'll do a waltz.
You have to have a sense of crisis.
That's right.
You're risking your life.
I understand.
I'll leave it to you.
Yes.
I'll start from Shizuoka.
What?
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
You have to have a sense of crisis.
You have to be strong.
You have to run.
I'm not running.
I don't know what to do.
You have to be strong.
You're a good guy.
Are you ready, Okamoto?
Let's go.
Ready.
Start.
You look terrible.
Are you trying to get up?
You're not good at all.
You look like a man.
Look at your face.
Let's go.
Ready.
Start.
What are you doing?
There's still 15 seconds left.
10 seconds.
10 seconds left.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
I'll do it.
Okamoto.
You did it in 30 seconds.
You have to say it properly.
Yes.
Ready.
Start.
It's hard to get down.
It's hard.
15 seconds.
5.
4.
3.
2.
My nose is running.
Okamoto.
Your nose is running.
I can't hear you.
You're pathetic.
This is the last one.
Yes.
Ready.
Start.
5 seconds.
You did it.
Okamoto.
Good job.
I don't want to say it.
Okamoto, do it.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
Thank you.
Hello.
Why are you laughing?
I'm not laughing.
The audience is fine.
They are fine.
But you know what?
What?
The hub is hard.
The hub?
Do you want to talk about the hub?
I don't have much data.
It's ok.
What is it?
You know what?
My woman was kicked by a ***.
I don't like it.
That's because there are a lot of people.
There are things like that.
I don't know what's going to happen.
I think I should go and call her.
That's impossible.
I was worried about that.
I felt sorry for her.
I'm a wolf.
What are you?
Lonely wolf.
How old are you?
What are you doing?
Basically, I don't get kicked by people.
There are mothers and fathers like that.
But they are not my real parents.
You look like them.
I was born with a backache.
You don't look like your parents.
It doesn't matter.
I didn't run away.
I just happened to run into them.
For example, the guy with glasses?
It doesn't matter.
If he runs away, I'll beat him up.
You're the only one who can do that.
I see.
I'll tell him to stop.
I'll tell him that.
I'll ask him what he's doing.
I'll stab him.
He said that.
I'm the guy with glasses, right?
Yes, you are.
I'm the guy with glasses.
Don't lie to me.
I can't do anything.
I can't even tell him to stop.
I'm the guy with glasses.
I don't care if he stabs me or not.
It's a two-step process.
Don't lie to me.
You don't know anything.
He'll stab you if you get close to him.
It doesn't matter.
I can't do anything.
But you were hit by your own woman.
I shouldn't be angry.
Your bones are broken.
I always hit them.
Why?
I hit them.
What kind of situation is this?
How should I put it?
It's an expression of love.
It's like this.
Instead of that,
it's like this.
What?
There's a high-spirited expression.
It's like this.
A woman should be calm.
I'm not calm.
I have a lot of scars.
You have scars?
Don't you think about what to do if you get hit?
I do.
I don't know what to do.
I met her somewhere in Shinjuku.
I was walking and she was following me.
I was waiting for the traffic light.
There were two people.
I could hear them.
What should I do?
Should I stab her?
No way.
I was doing it normally.
You weren't doing this.
Should I stab her?
I don't know what to do.
It's mostly a blade.
I don't understand that.
You don't understand that?
What about a windmill?
It's fine.
I can stab a windmill on the back.
Let's try to find the windmill.
Let's just run.
What kind of death do you have to do in order to be released?
If there is something clearly wrong, you will be released.
By appearance?
By appearance.
For example, an elite salaried man of some class was killed.
Right? At this point... Ah, he was killed?
He was killed?
If he was killed, you will understand.
You will understand why he died.
He was dead when he woke up in the morning.
At this point, there is no need to release him.
That's why you should investigate why he died.
That's because he didn't wake up in the morning.
No, no, no.
You can't wake him up in the morning.
You should investigate why he died.
No, no, you already know that.
He was sleeping.
He was sleeping, and he just left.
So the reason he left is...
That's a sixth-degree sleep.
In a sense.
Rather than a second-degree sleep...
It's not a second-degree sleep or a third-degree sleep.
It's a sixth-degree sleep.
Right.
At this point, there is no need to release him.
But if you look at him...
He was wearing a bra.
That's strange.
You should try to release him.
Do you understand?
There's no way I understand.
Let's keep that a secret.
Why?
He was wearing a bra, so it's not good to release him.
It's too pitiful.
It's strange.
He was wearing a bra.
It's strange, but...
Let's keep that a secret.
But it's strange.
It's obviously strange.
It's strange.
But if you don't clean it up as a hobby...
He was wearing a bra, so I'll release him.
That's the feeling of a family member.
But...
Your father was wearing a bra?
Don't say that.
It's pitiful.
But if he was wearing a bra...
As a family member, you'd be worried.
Your father.
When your father takes something expensive...
He'll fix it later.
It's obviously strange.
Let's keep that a secret.
But it's not like...
It's not like he understood it after he died.
If you look at his daily life...
He'll do this when he does this.
He must have realized that his father was strange recently.
If he was wearing a bra, it's fine.
Maybe before the police came...
Everyone was taking off their bras.
You can't show this.
His family?
His family.
But there's a mark.
You can't wear bras like that.
I don't know why.
But bras are fine.
Don't take off your bras.
I won't.
Someone's station manager was killed.
Right?
You can't be killed.
Your boss...
The station manager died in the station manager's chair.
He died peacefully.
I don't know why.
He died like this.
You can't be killed.
If you do this, you're not Kiri anymore.
That's not the problem.
But from the station manager's nose...
The collar was sticking out.
It's not a collar.
It was sticking out from the station manager's nose.
This is strange.
That's strange.
If it was sticking out from one side, I would've put it in.
But it's sticking out from both sides.
Where's the inside?
It's alive.
It's alive?
I'm scared.
I'll go get it.
It's cold, Matsumoto-san.
Is that it?
How to get warm without a stove?
There's that.
Please tell us.
It's yesterday.
I see.
Yesterday, everyone was walking around saying it was cold.
I'm cold in a way, but I don't think I'm cold in a way.
Which is it?
It's cold, but I don't think I'm cold in a way.
So...
So what?
What are you trying to end with?
Give her a key holder.
I don't have one.
I don't have a key holder.
Downtown key holder.
I don't have one.
Matsumoto-san,
Please tell us a way to get a key holder that you can't figure out.
This.
This is...
It's nothing.
There is a perfect place to get it.
It can't be found.
Isn't that good?
The key holder can be found by peeping.
I see.
Don't peek.
It's a respect.
Don't peek, don't peek, don't sleep.
I can't sleep.
I'm sick of it.
When I was in high school, there was a guy who was really smart.
His name was Miyoshi.
That's why he didn't write Matsumoto Hitoshi.
He wrote Miyoshi instead.
He wrote Matsumoto and Kake for Miyoshi.
Matsumoto Hitoshi got 90 points.
So what about Miyoshi?
Miyoshi only got 20 points.
No way.
But if Matsumoto is good, it's all OK.
I wonder.
I was listening to this and thought it was AI.
Do you know that?
How to win a marathon.
Do you know?
Who are you listening to?
1500, trunk, that.
Trunk?
It's a truck.
It's a truck with four laps.
Do you know how to win a 1500 marathon?
I don't know.
Start.
There's no way it's a guy who has no stamina.
Why do you look so far?
I was looking at the picture when I was in perfect shape.
For a woman, I have a question for Matsumoto Teio who is said to have beaten up Ms. Umemiya.
I sometimes call her by the name of the woman I'm cheating on.
It becomes a very bad atmosphere.
There's no way to call her by her name correctly.
When you're dating multiple women, you can't call her by her name.
I see.
If you call her Keiko or Yoshiko, it's a mistake.
You have to unify them.
Anything is fine.
For example, Nikita.
You can't call her by her name.
Right?
Why Nikita?
There are many other names.
For-e-va.
I understand the meaning.
You have to unify them.
That's for sure.
I'll be honest with you.
I'll only call her by her name.
Why are you laughing?
I'm a little embarrassed.
But it's wrong to call her by her name.
You have to match her.
Nikita.
The problem is that when you call her Nikita, and she finds out,
you have to talk to her.
I understand Nikita, but I don't know how Nikita feels.
When that happens, you have to call her by her name.
You can't call her by her name.
You have to match her.
The problem is that when you call her Nikita, and she finds out,
you have to match her.
I understand Nikita, but I don't know how Nikita feels.
How do you call her?
How do you call your wife?
I'll call her by her name.
You're scary!
Do you want to get bitten?
Say it like that!