At the foot of Mt. Fuji, there is a lake full of water called Kawaguchiko.
This lake is also famous for being a place where people gather for fishing.
But deep in the lake, there is a legend that there is an imaginary giant fish that has defeated many fishermen in the Korean War.
In Downtown, he challenges the imaginary black bus that travels around the world.
What is it?
I heard that Mr. Ito is fishing here.
That's right.
When I came to the program before, I said,
If you don't have a hobby, how about fishing?
You said that, didn't you?
That's right.
I didn't think so.
You said that, didn't you?
Mr. Ito said,
Then let's do it.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
I came at 6 o'clock this morning.
It's real.
Yes, it's real.
It's a real Itoi.
What are you doing?
Itoi Shigesato, a man who is a man and a fish.
He is a man who is shown to be a black bus fisherman who demands high strategicity.
I'm sorry I'm early in the morning.
No, no, no.
I'm sorry I'm so early in the morning.
It's Mr. Itoi.
It's not early at all.
I'm sorry I'm so early.
Can you fish here?
I can.
Do you see what I just caught?
I can see it.
Can I brag about it?
Yes, go ahead.
Wow.
It's mine.
That's a really big one, isn't it?
Just now.
Just now?
Just now, just now.
I dropped it on purpose.
It's fresh.
I don't hate it that much.
I have it this time.
No, no, no.
I don't hate it.
You don't hate it?
It's lure fishing.
We're going to fish for bass using lure.
Yes.
Can I?
Yes, yes, yes.
I'll put this between my middle finger and ring finger.
Between your middle finger and ring finger?
Here, here, here, here.
Oh, like this?
Yes.
It's a different one.
You don't even know your middle finger and ring finger.
You don't even know.
No, no, no, no.
That's right.
Can I?
What?
Wow.
That's the worst.
I don't think you're a bad person.
The clock is 12 o'clock at the top, right?
Yes.
Think that you have a clock.
Do it until 2 o'clock and talk at 10 o'clock.
This index finger.
It's going to fly away.
Well, I'll do it badly.
Yes.
Can I?
Do it until 2 o'clock and talk at 10 o'clock.
Do it until 2 o'clock and talk at 10 o'clock?
Well, it's not bad.
It's not bad.
Do it until 2 o'clock and talk at 10 o'clock.
I'm doing it until 4 o'clock right now.
Oh, until 4 o'clock.
I was talking at 9 o'clock.
Oh, really?
Oh.
What?
I was surprised.
Thank you.
It's dangerous.
No, no, no.
I was talking from 2 o'clock to 10 o'clock.
8 seconds, 8 seconds.
It's dangerous.
At last, the battle between downtown, Itoishigesato,
and the black bus, a mysterious lake, is about to begin.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Two times a week, itoishi, who goes to Kawaguchiko, gets to the point of the black bus.
Ito-san is coming. It's coming. Oh, it's coming. It's coming. It's coming.
It was a big one. It's coming. It's coming.
What is it? It's coming. It's coming.
It's coming. It's coming. It's coming. It's coming. It's coming. It's coming. It's coming.
But if it comes, don't be impatient. I know.
Can we drive with the electric motor after the shootout?
I'm scared.
I can do it. It can do it.
Does this have something like a second engine?
This is what I'm stepping on with my feet. This is called an electric motor.
If you have a driver's license you can ride with them
That would be fun
It's coming
That was big
What a waste
You hit yourself
That was big
That was close
It's coming
Don't panic
His face is panicking
He did it
Wait
Put your thumb in here
I'm scared
This is fine
It's fine
How do you get the needle?
Put it a bit forward
He's an idiot
Why did you get caught by me?
Look at his eyes
It's coming
Why did you get caught?
It's strange
It's coming
I saw it was 28cm
It's a good size
Mine is better
It's coming
I'm happy
It's small
Why did you put it in the net?
I forgot
I'm sorry
I quit
I'm going to be a gill
It's sad
It's the worst when you say it
It's coming
It's a fish
I couldn't eat it
I knew it
I didn't have anything
Let's change the worm
We need one person to do the comedy
From here
You idiot
That's not it
Did you get caught?
Put the rope
The time is tight
It's coming
Wait
It's big
What is this?
It's coming
It's big
It's huge!
You have to catch it!
Don't let it escape!
Raise the rod!
This is huge!
What is this?
It's hot!
It's huge!
46cm?
47cm?
That's amazing!
It's the biggest I've ever caught.
I caught it in the U.S.
Is that so?
This is not a bad thing.
This is a good size.
It's coming!
It's huge!
But it's not as big as the one before.
It's not as big as the one before.
It's small.
You can catch anything!
I'm sorry.
This one is smaller.
Hold it like this.
The bottom is good.
We caught two fish.
I don't want to complain.
I'm going to put salad on it.
What is this?
It's wrinkled.
It's huge!
Can I wind it?
It's wrinkled.
Did I hold it?
I'll wind it.
It's huge!
Stop it!
You're not interested, are you?
I thought I'd stop fishing.
I'm sorry.
It's coming.
It's big.
Don't be impatient.
I didn't see it.
It's so big that I don't want to fish.
Why?
What should we do now?
My hand stinks.
It was wrinkled in the opening.
It stinks.
What is this?
It's a different smell.
Especially around here.
I came back from the back.
It still stinks.
It stinks even in the car.
I can smell the cigarette.
You're wrong.
Who is it?
Now
It's a round latte!
Did you start to like fishing?
Well, you know, it's a show like that.
They do everything for us.
You have to get the right people.
If you ask me if I want to go fishing...
I think that...
What?
I don't like that kind of thing.
What do you mean?
You have to get the right people and give them back.
Yes, yes.
I don't know if it's a kind license or something.
Everyone has that.
I think that's no good.
You can't give them back.
You...
You've been giving them back to a few people like this.
Well, well, well, well.
I can't help it because you told me.
The reason why you can't give them back is...
If you give them back, he'll tell everyone, right?
Yeah.
Be careful.
Whoa!
He gave them back!
Right?
I think that's true.
Are you serious?
That's what he'll say.
Did you just give them back?
No way.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
You can't give them back.
I was swimming, so I was hungry.
So he went in fast?
He went in fast, but he got caught.
You're there, you know that.
I told you to give them back.
And this is serious.
The police are coming, we need to be careful, we need to be careful.
We'll learn from it slowly.
You should never give them back.
I caught them myself, so I'm going to catch them myself.
It's not good.
It's the same as rag-a-bye.
No.
He said, if we caught them ourselves, we should catch them ourselves.
What?
You went fishing, didn't you?
Yeah, I went fishing
Ahhhh!
You were like this, you put your hand in your mouth and grabbed it
Ah, please do it already!
It's disgusting to touch things like that
It can't be helped, at the end
While you're saying that, you should wear a shirt like this
Today, it just so happened that I went fishing
It just so happened that I went fishing
You're saying things that you don't understand
Well, it's fine
Do you know that?
The new manager
Eh? That's Akutagawa, right?
Akutagawa?
He seems to be having quite a crash here
Quite a crash?
He seems to be having quite a crash
Right now, he's still in Higashino, right?
Yeah
When I asked him, he laughed
Even now
He said, I'll make curry for lunch today
I said, yes, understood
And when he came to the dressing room
He left a curry roux
You're laughing, aren't you?
No, I'm not! I'm serious!
He said, I'll make curry for lunch
He left a curry roux
He left a box of curry roux
He said, I don't know what you're talking about
What is this?
I'm so angry
I said, oh, it's curry!
He said, this is it
It's hot, it's hot
I said, what is this? It's this Hyorokudama
I got angry
You said it yourself?
I said, what is this Hyorokudama?
I said, I don't understand
I called my girlfriend
I was told by Hamada-san that it's Hyorokudama
Can you look it up in the dictionary?
It's written here
Isn't this terrible?
I shouldn't have asked my girlfriend
Why are you talking like that?
I'm talking like this
It's annoying, isn't it?
You've been going to university for 4 years
But you're helping a guy who went to a prison
Right?
A guy who was called by his number
I wasn't called
Number 1526
Who? Me?
The guy who said, come on!
Come on!
It's funny that you didn't get called
That's right
I'm not feeling well today
Why?
I don't know the reason
Do you have the courage?
I don't have the courage
Why is that?
I feel like I've done it 3 times
I can't help it
But recently I've been doing it 1000 times
You did it everyday before
I did it everyday
Did you feel good?
Yes, I felt good
That's good
Thank you
It's the second episode of Yuichi Jungle
Why?
My back hurts so much
Your back hurts, your ears hurt, your stomach hurts, what else makes you feel sick?
It's because of my appearance
It's because of your appearance
What else?
I think I'm starting to feel sick
Is that so?
When I go home, I take off my socks
The shape of my socks is hard to cut
That's because you're wearing tight socks
It's hard to cut after 5 minutes
I'm happy that you said that
When I go home, I take off my socks because it's hot
I'm always watching TV like this
Why are you bored at home?
I watch TV and go home
I watch it all the time and I still feel sick
I'm about to cry
I'm fine
Really?
But...
Wait, hey!
Stand up
It's like that
It happens
If you get a tattoo next time, what will it be?
What do you mean next time?
I won't get a tattoo next time
It's fine
It's fine if you don't get a tattoo
I won't get a tattoo
Do you want to get a tattoo?
I don't want to get a tattoo, but I already got one
You already got one?
But it doesn't mean anything if everyone gets a tattoo
Why?
Like a rose
It doesn't mean anything
If I get a tattoo, it's more meaningful
It's useful
Wait, it's a tattoo, so it's not useful
No, so...
I'll make this a calendar
What do you mean?
When will it be a calendar?
How long will it be a calendar?
Next month, next month
Even if it ends like that, I won't get a tattoo
What are you doing?
It's more meaningful
Or you can write your name here
It's not pants
Let's change it to Sambi Matsumoto
You're not Sambi
Why did you try to get a tattoo again?
No
I didn't
You have a lot of admiration for Yakuzas
That's the thing I hate the most
You really like Yakuzas
Why?
You have a live photo of Yakuzas
Why is the end of the toilet paper in a triangle?
But that's a woman's
Men don't have it
That's a woman's hatred
A different woman came
Long hair falls off
That's normal
Long hair doesn't fall off
While I was going to the toilet, she was peeing
I know what you're up to
And she was rolling around
I know
I thought I'd hold her down
And open it
And then
I dropped the napkin's seal
I dropped it
You should have noticed and done it
I did the earrings
I did it on purpose
When I went to the bathroom
I said, wait a minute
I did it
I thought I'd forget about it
And then
I said, wait a minute
I didn't feel it at all
And then
That's business
I said, I'm glad you did it
And then
I said, I forgot
Don't say it with the same tone
That's your tone
I said, wait a minute
It was so hot
It's not like that
It's summer
Really?
What season do you like?
I like winter
I always ask you
What are you doing?
And you always say
What is this?
You say something ambiguous
If I can catch you
I'll catch you
With high heels
Running on the beach
I don't know
No one will catch you
You try to act like a little devil
What's wrong with your head?
If it's winter, say it
If it's summer, say it
You're acting like a little devil
Say it
If it's summer, say it
Don't interrupt me
Wait a minute
Don't talk too much
You're the one who talks too much
I'm so energetic