Matsumoto Hitoshi's famous song, Taxi Driver, was made in Sokkyo.
This song, which brings back the mood of the early Showa period, is currently used as a talk show.
But at first, Matsumoto said something like this.
I'm not the type of person who sings by myself.
I see.
I'm the type of person who provides to others.
Even if you're watching this program,
Who do you want me to come to?
Anyone is fine.
This is the recording of Matsumoto Hitoshi's famous song, Taxi Driver.
Thank you very much.
Finally, the day has come.
Finally.
I went to the toilet and peed.
I have a tingling sensation.
That's bad.
It doesn't matter. Let's do our best.
Finally.
I don't want to lean on you.
Finally, a musician.
I'm glad to hear that.
Really?
Taxi Driver has nothing to do with Debaishi.
At first, when I came to the opening, the audience was excited.
It's getting more and more autumn.
It's early.
Last week, the audience didn't laugh at all.
So this time, I'm going to make a decision.
I'll have someone else do it.
That's right.
Let's have him on the stage.
Please welcome this person.
It's Sharankyu.
This time, he's going to sing.
Sharankyu is a unique group of musicians.
What kind of song will it be?
Osaka is a comic book.
Don't be happy.
Mako's eyes are swimming today, too.
Mako, you don't have to come here.
I'm going to record drums today.
I don't want to fight.
I'm glad to hear that.
Have you heard of it?
I've heard of it.
I've prepared it.
Let's hear it again.
Let's use this device.
The sound of the prelude and the beginning of the song are completely different.
It's so good.
There's a lot of relaxation here.
Komuro is a manager who can be used.
That's right.
I'm going to use Komuro.
This program is provided by the sponsor you see.
Let's do it.
Please do this.
Please do it.
Why?
Who are you?
Are you excited?
Listen to me.
Who are you?
Yamazaki.
Yamazaki, I'm sorry.
It's a song.
Hey, you guys.
Yes.
Why are you making us sing?
Why are you so arrogant?
Do you want to die?
What do you mean?
How many years have you been doing this?
You guys are a lot.
Do you want to die?
I'm asking for a taxi driver.
Don't let such a cheap guy do it.
Who are you?
What do you want to do?
No.
Why are you making us sing?
Why don't you let Yamazaki sing?
Is that so?
We want to sing for three people.
I'm a regular singer.
I'm not a regular singer.
You guys are making fun of me.
That's not true.
You're a musician.
Was there such a joke?
Don't you know?
Look at me.
Hey.
Let's go to the theater.
I'm thinking about going to the theater.
What are you saying?
I can't make you sing.
You are fast.
BOROME!
NARUTO!
It's true.
It's really low.
You have a lot of moves.
So, let's do this.
Please decide which one has more talent.
We're going to compete now.
It doesn't matter if it's funny or not.
We're going to compete.
Let's compete!
Let's go!
Who should we choose?
Why are you doing this?
Tell us the truth.
We don't know what to do.
If you don't tell us, we don't know who to choose.
That's true.
We don't know who to choose.
We don't know.
We're going to compete with the three of us.
The one who wins this competition, please sing.
Please sing.
The one who wins has to choose.
Then, shall we have him choose?
Of course.
Let's do that.
I'll buy his passion.
Okay.
You have to say that.
That's why.
I'm the cute one.
Makoto!
We're going to compete.
It's a high tension competition!
This is it!
What is it?
After I showed you this, you said it's a high tension competition.
It's a high tension competition.
Who will be the winner?
You did it again.
This is annoying.
This is hard.
I'll sing!
I'm counting on you!
Do you know the rhythm of the samba?
Why doesn't anyone know?
If you're the winner,
who will be the winner?
Hyoil did it three times.
Can you do it?
Can you do it, Makoto?
Watch me.
Do your best.
Can you do it?
I'm leading.
I'm doing it.
What was that?
This is a high tension competition.
Let's make a decision.
It's a high tension competition.
What is it?
I'm going to compete.
Go!
This is a high tension competition.
Who is it?
Taisei!
It's me.
Taisei and Makoto are competing.
Who will get the right to sing?
If you win,
we'll get the right to sing.
You can decide that?
The judge is here.
What is it?
I'm going to sing.
Ready, start!
Taisei is strong.
It hurts.
It hurts when it flies.
How much does it stretch?
More, more.
Why are you using rubber?
Taisei is strong.
It hurts.
What is it?
Where did you go?
I can't decide.
You have to turn around.
Taisei is strong.
It's a high tension competition.
It's amazing.
It's hard to decide.
In the end,
I'm going to sing.
It's me.
My competition is
me and my character,
Hatake.
It's been a while.
Both leaders,
Yamazaki and Hatake,
will decide the winner.
What is this?
Soccer.
Stop it.
This is really amazing.
I'm going to start.
What are you going to do?
What is this?
APJ!
That's why you're
a Brazilian
craftsman.
It's a skill.
Stop it.
Hatake, try it.
Who's going to do it?
I'm not going to do it.
There's more.
Don't treat me like this.
Next.
I'm going to do it.
Are you okay?
Look at this.
This is amazing.
I'm scared.
Let's go.
It's not broken at all.
It's broken on the ground.
That's great.
The atmosphere is different.
No matter how many times we do it,
it's still the atmosphere.
That's great.
The last match.
There's more.
There's more?
Wari basuke.
What is it?
Yes.
Wari basuke.
Anyone can do it.
It's a fun service.
What's the difference?
It's a private lobby.
Wari basuke.
Please make a decision.
I'll make a decision.
I think you already know this.
Sharankyu wins.
Why did you do your best?
Why did you decide on Sharankyu?
There's nothing like that.
The recording is about to begin.
Let's check the lyrics and the song.
It's about time.
I'm counting on you guys.
Why are you so proud?
I tried to do my best.
Up to here, it's la la la la.
Who's going to do this?
la la la la
Everyone?
Except for Tsunku?
I'll start with Tsunku.
Ito is a taxi driver.
You can go straight in.
Close the car door.
I'm going to be the driver.
It's a taxi company in Kyoto.
There's a third one.
He puts in gear and attention.
He's a taxi driver.
la la la la
Why are you going there?
Lovers are...
It's like a taxi driver singing to his lover.
Lovers are around here.
The lyrics are coming in.
Japanese after the war is like this.
This is an instruction.
I'll record it.
Please give me an instruction.
The lyrics are like this.
The basic lyrics are like this.
If you don't do it perfectly, you have to sing it at the concert.
I have to sing this at the tour.
I'll sing this at the beginning of the opening.
I'll sing this twice at the encore.
I'll sing this three times in total.
I'll sing this.
Let's do it.
They are playing the guitar.
They check the keys.
The field is in a bad condition.
What's wrong with this?
This is interesting.
I tried to play the guitar in the field.
He is serious.
Let's listen to the original song.
One more time.
Where is the master?
Look at this.
This is cool.
This is a field.
Really?
He is a great man.
This is a field.
This reminds me of GOKUTSUMA.
He is singing.
SHARANKYU.
Yes.
What's going on?
I'm checking the lyrics of the song.
I've never seen this before.
I'll play it again.
I see.
It takes time.
I'm sorry.
Don't ruin my image.
I think I should start from the 3rd bar.
What?
Which one?
I think I should start from the 3rd bar.
I don't know.
This is the first part.
Please play it.
I was the strongest.
I don't know what you're talking about.
That's not true.
He is a great man.
Mr. Matsumoto.
Yes.
Can I ask you about your image?
What?
What is your final image?
I want to be democratic.
You want to be democratic?
Leader.
I know.
What?
I want to be democratic.
What is your final image?
He is a taxi driver.
This one?
Yes.
He is a taxi driver.
I think I should start from the 3rd bar.
Mr. Azaki.
Yes.
This sound.
I got it.
That's not the sound.
This sound.
I got it.
It's a little different.
Matsui, can you play it?
It's difficult.
It's difficult to sing.
This is difficult.
Can you play the F7 in the 6th bar?
I don't know.
What?
F7.
This is F7.
It's hard.
I can't move it.
I don't know what you're talking about.
He can't hide his confusion.
He seems to be struggling.
This is B flat minor.
I got it.
OK.
Minor.
Let's change it to minor.
Thank you.
Matsui, can you play the F7 in the 6th bar?
I got it.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Matsui, can you play the F7 in the 6th bar?
All OK.
You're fast.
Thank you.
That's it.
Really?
Yes.
It was a little strange.
I'm sorry.
Basically, try it.
I got it.
Matsui, can you play the F7 in the 6th bar?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Believe in yourself.
Next week, we're finally going to see the taxi driver car basketball version complete.
Look forward to it.