On the night of the show, that man came to downtown to tell us that an unexpected visitor had arrived.
Excuse me.
Could you tell us what you're looking forward to?
Please tell us.
Actually,
a man came to downtown to tell us something.
Could you stay there for a moment?
Thank you.
Good morning.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you.
Last month,
the chief director of this show, who is said to have been a big fan of him, Toshihide Saito had a date with Jaguar whom he admires.
At that time,
Heipo tried to make Jaguar his girlfriend.
However,
Jaguar, who is more skillful than him, had to go home.
I told you to wait.
Why is she here?
Good morning.
What's the matter?
I had a date with Saito.
Oh, I see.
Well,
I feel like I'm stalking him.
Who is it?
Is it Saito?
I think so.
That's not good.
Is that so?
Well,
after the shoot,
I accidentally exchanged my cell phone number.
So,
he kept calling me.
At that time,
I saw a black shadow.
A black and small shadow.
I think it's small.
Oh, I see.
What should I do?
Let's call the police.
That's right.
But,
I think it's better to ask him.
That's right.
I don't like it.
But,
What do you mean?
Do you like me?
Well,
I had a date with him.
I don't like his appearance.
But,
I think he is kind.
if I have a stalking affair with him,
I feel like I'm jealous of him.
I see.
So,
I like strong men.
I see.
I don't like weak men.
Thank you.
Good morning.
He's here.
Good timing.
Good morning.
Heipo.
Yes.
Did you call Jaguar?
I had a phone call with him.
So, I asked him to call me.
That's good.
Did you go near his house?
Well,
I thought he liked me.
Did you have a stalking affair with him?
You don't usually tell him your phone number, do you?
No, no, no.
Why did you give me a light wave?
But,
Jaguar,
I don't think he doesn't like you.
Really?
His attitude.
His attitude?
He's like a stalker.
Jaguar says that Heipo is not manly.
That's not true.
He's quite manly.
I don't care what you say.
Jaguar likes strong men.
Yes, he does.
I'm able to protect him.
Yes, yes, yes.
For example, there are many strange men.
If Jaguar attacks them, I help him.
That's natural.
He's so weak.
What are you talking about?
You know he's manly.
I don't know.
Why do you say like that?
That's not manly.
For example, Jaguar was a wrestler.
How about this?
You two team up and fight with your opponent.
That's not true.
I can do it.
Let's do it.
That's fast.
Leave it to me.
Really?
Really.
I'll do it today.
For Ai.
For Jaguar.
If you can protect him.
I'll definitely protect him.
That's right.
I'll protect him.
I'm not a sweet guy.
It's okay.
It hurts.
I'm a lion.
It's okay.
What is this?
I'm a lion.
Jaguar is a lion.
What?
You're like a father.
The next episode
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Finally, Heipo and Jaguar's tag match will begin.
It's starting.
Is Toh's opponent, Heipo, okay?
I don't think so.
I have a chance to win.
Heipo is confident and says he'll fight.
But Ichido is worried about him.
Will Heipo be okay?
What are you doing?
You don't have any strength.
I don't have any strength.
I just ate something that went through my throat.
It's coming up soon.
Are you okay?
It's okay to stop.
I'm a man among men.
It's a question of whether you can show your manliness.
I think I can.
I was born as a man.
I have to protect women.
I have to be a man before I become a director.
You're a man.
Yes, I'm a man.
After this, Heipo talks about what a woman can do and the true strength of a man.
Everyone listens to different Heipo.
A man can stand up to any woman he likes.
Do you understand?
Is that so?
It seems so.
It's Heipo's opinion.
The alarm clock called love woke up my sleeping master.
You're talking like a poet.
After that, Heipo continued to talk about what a man should be like.
And...
Today's main event, Heipo and Jaguar's love tag match.
It's a 60-minute one-on-one match.
From the red corner, Heipo and Jaguar enter to prove their love.
I'll sing for my children.
I'm Heipo.
Next, from the blue corner, two mysterious wrestlers, Maskman Brothers enter.
Is this okay?
He seems to be strong.
It's open.
He's strong.
Really?
Is this okay?
Let's go!
The first challenge!
Go!
Go, HENKO!
Kill him!
He's telling you to kill him!
What's wrong?
HENKO, show us something cool!
What are you doing?
Hey!
Help me!
HENKO!
What are you doing?
If a man doesn't ask a woman for help,
he has to risk his life to protect her.
Eh?
HENKO!
Let's go!
HENKO, let's go!
Touch me!
What are you doing?
Let's go!
You can do it!
Help me!
What are you doing?
Don't mess with me!
Heipo!
Chaga-san, you're in trouble.
Don't mess with me!
Heipo, go!
What are you doing?
Heipo, grab his neck!
The character for man is the character for power.
It's not a man without power.
Don't you know that?
Heipo, grab his back!
Heipo, touch his back!
Heipo, get it!
Go!
Do it!
You're not helping Chaga!
Heipo!
Ah!
Now!
Give back the A-line ball!
That's a new one!
Give it back!
What are you doing?
That's bad!
Go! Take it!
What are you doing?
Go! Go!
It's coming!
What are you doing?
Give me the A-line ball!
Men are usually good-for-nothings.
Even if you're a loser,
if you shine a golden light
when you're in trouble,
that's good enough.
What are you doing?
Give it back!
Help!
Turn it more!
Turn the back side more!
Help!
That's scary!
That's bad!
A-line ball!
Now's the chance!
Chance!
You only have one chance!
A-line ball!
What was that?
Are you okay?
Aren't you supposed to protect me?
I love you!
What's wrong with him?
I'm sorry!
You're going home?
I'm sorry I'm sorry!
Let's go!
He's mad.
What is it?
You're strong!
Strong?
I'm strong?
What's your reason for it?
I ate too much.
You ate too much!
Hey, hey, it's already over!
Don't fall in love with me!
I'm Hamada's, I'm Hamada's, I'm Hamada's earring!
I'm going to be the wind!
I saw something interesting yesterday.
What did you see?
It's hard to watch.
I was driving around Meiji-dori, Shibuya.
A fire truck came.
It came like this.
I think the fire truck was in front of the big camera.
I wanted to make a U-turn around there.
It's big, so I can't make a U-turn.
A young fire truck came down.
From top to bottom, it was silver.
It was a big fire truck.
The fire truck came down and I couldn't make a U-turn, so I had to back up.
But I was in a hurry because it was a fire.
I had to do it quickly.
I backed up and went like this.
I was left behind.
No way!
I don't know what to do with that young fire truck.
What are you doing?
I can't watch it forever.
I went, but I felt sorry for it.
No matter how much I think about it, it was chasing me.
That was a game of Senna-Mitsuho.
I was left behind in that outfit.
It was because there was a fire truck.
I thought it would be fun, so I went.
You knew the scene.
I knew the scene.
You came later.
Please forgive me.
I think it was because of that.
I did it.
How was it?
How was this winter?
This winter?
It's delicious.
I know Shionoo.
Do you know him?
Yes, I know him.
He's a bit like this.
I heard you can't watch TV.
My TV?
No, a man's TV.
It's like this.
That's ridiculous.
There was a big guy.
I said, look, look.
He said, no, I'm fine.
I was watching.
Everyone was chasing him.
He said, it's okay.
He ran away like this.
Really?
It's not like that.
I went to Disneyland.
It's amazing.
Have you been there recently?
I haven't.
It's fun.
Did you go there?
Honey.
It's called Honey Hunt.
Honey Hunt?
It's Pooh's.
It's so much fun.
I love honey.
That's right.
I don't think so.
It's fun.
It's better to have kids.
They'll be happy.
It's like this.
I'm shaking a little.
It's a lot of fun.
You're shaking a lot.
You said you had a fan for 380,000 yen in your house.
I said that.
Rumor has it that you have a kotatsu for 380,000 yen.
What kind of kotatsu is it?
Do you want to hear this?
I want to hear that.
I've never seen a kotatsu for 380,000 yen.
What do you think it is?
Is it that?
Is that the feature of the heater?
Final answer?
No!
Really?
Ouch!
100,000 yen.
I don't usually buy a kotatsu for 380,000 yen.
I don't buy it.
I have a kotatsu for 380,000 yen.
Where is it?
I don't have one or two.
I have a few.
Please tell me the feature.
What?
Feature?
First of all, the kotatsu futon.
You can see the legs, right?
Wait a minute.
It's sexy.
It's not enough.
You can buy a kotatsu for 380,000 yen.
Why?
When I want to play the trumpet, I scream.
I scream at the green futon on the back.
It's an old kotatsu.
It's green on the back.
Trump is a king.
If I don't say anything, I scream.
I scream at the old man.
You look like you grew up in the wild.
How do you grow up if you raise a giraffe like a human child?
If you grow up to a certain extent, you will realize.
What is good?
I'm a giraffe.
What do you do if you find out?
If I find out, I pretend not to be a giraffe.
What do you do?
What is wrong with the decision?
It's like this.
The child next door is like this.
I try to do something about it first.
I always tell my friends to do this.
The moment this is separated, it's like this.
I can do something about it.
The problem is this.
It's definitely different.
When I take a picture with everyone in class, I feel like I'm taking a break even though I'm wearing it.
Is it a problem of wearing it?
Is everyone accepting it?
Let's accept it somehow.
I think the language barrier will be solved.
Will it be solved?
Yes.
Just a giraffe on the trash.
No matter what you say.
But only this wall.
It's difficult.
I have to do something about it.
Can't you solve it?
It will be solved by making an effort.
I don't know how to do that.
But it's basically impossible to make a long neck short.
But I can't do that.
So I think about it.
I think about wearing it.
What do you mean?
I'm going to roll it.
The neck?
The neck.
I'm going to roll it.
I'm going to completely roll it.
If I roll it again, I can make a big roll.
I know.
I'm going to make a few more of them.
The neck will be very short, but the weakness of this will be a little sideways.
That's a little creepy.
It's creepy.
If I think about it, I'm going to put a vertical line in this long neck.
And then I'm going to do it.
It's like konjac.
And the weakness of this is that it's facing the other side.
That's pitiful.
I can't help it.
What?
And if that's solved, there's this.
I can't help it.
I'll say it when I feel like I have to stand up.
What do you mean?
Someone.
When you feel like you have to stand up?
It's like this.
I'm going to do it like this.
Basically, you're a teacher.
I can't help it.
I can't help it even if I'm a teacher.
I can't help it if I have a lot of friends.
I know.
I can't help it.
It's pitiful.
Don't be depressed.
You don't have to be depressed.
It's pitiful.
It's pitiful if you look at it silently.
I can't help it.
What are you trying to do?
Can't you reverse it?
I can't help it.
Do you want to do it like this?
What are you doing?
I'm swinging it.
Do you want to do it like this?
There's a hook here.
I'm going to hang this on the hook here.
Put your face up here.
No one's coming.
If you cut it here, it'll blow up.