I am the master of Zura Miyaburiman, Mr. Masahoto.
Nice to meet you.
Do you know who Zura is?
I have never worn a Zura.
Do you always wear a Zura?
Yes.
Do you shave?
I shave once every two days.
Do you want to be a yoga master?
No.
I am the master of Zura, Mr. Okajiro.
Today, as I said, I will see through Zura.
Leave it to me.
Are you OK?
I'm OK.
Do you have a pot for hair?
Yes, I have.
Where?
I have a pot.
That's why I have a pot.
Here is the first question.
How many of you are wearing a wig?
If you have a question, please answer it.
I see.
Three.
No, no, no.
What?
I have three.
I know the number.
Three?
I can't answer yet.
You are fast.
Any questions?
Do you sweat?
Sweat?
Do you get wet?
Do you sweat?
Of course.
Of course, I do.
Sweat?
Yes, I do.
What are you talking about?
I'm just walking.
I can hear you.
What are you talking about?
Teacher.
Please write down the numbers of the people you think have the same wig.
Mr. Director, please show your answer.
Number one, number three, number five.
No.1 and No.2 are wearing the wig.
No.1, No.2, No.5.
Now, Zura Mihamuriman.
1, 2, 3, 5.
Let's start with No.1.
No.1, please.
Wrong!
No.1 is correct!
No.2, please.
Wrong!
No.2 is wearing the wig.
No.1, No.2, No.3, No.4.
That's strange.
No.3, please.
No.1, No.3, No.4.
No.1 and No.3 are wearing the wig.
No.4, please.
Wrong!
If the last one is Zura,
No.1 is correct.
Perfect.
No.5, please.
No?
The last question.
5 people will appear.
Please come to the front.
Are you ready?
Among these 5 men,
only one of them is wearing the wig.
Let's guess who it is.
No.5, please.
Do you play sports?
I play baseball.
Do you head-slide?
No.
No.2, please.
Can you show us the atmosphere?
I'm surprised.
No.3, please.
I'm a diver.
I'm diving.
Diving?
I play volleyball.
Volleyball.
Time is up.
You can use this flip.
No.1, No.2, No.3, No.4, No.5, please.
Go!
Let's start with No.5.
Show us.
No.5.
No.5?
I'm drenched.
I can't get that hair into my face.
This guy is ridiculous.
I see.
No.5, please.
It's the most correct opinion.
No.2.
I think this part is a little too much.
Ah, this part?
Yes, yes, yes.
Now, the person with the correct answer, please take it off.
Now, from 1 to 5, what number is it?
The person with the correct answer is the winner!
That means everyone, take it off!
What's so funny about me?
Teacher, how about wearing that?
It suits you, doesn't it?
Now, let's do our best today as well.
Hey, you!
What?
I'm asking you!
Go and shave your beard!
You're so dirty!
I got a cold from you!
What's with that?
I can't do it anymore, it's really hard.
In your case, if you don't get a cold, it's fine.
In my case, what do you mean?
Why?
The fever in your throat is about to go down, but you...
It's about to collapse.
What is he saying?
I don't know, Marshall!
Hey, are you Medaka-nii-san?
Marshall, where are you?
What did you say?
Sorry, I was sleeping until now.
I don't know what to do!
What should I do?
I'm going to get a cold.
I'll do my best.
Do your best, do your best.
You can't do it because you talk like that.
That's right.
But it's getting colder.
Yeah, it's cold.
From now on, it's the hot pot season.
The hot pot season is good.
When you say hot pot, what kind of hot pot do you mean?
Hot pot is...
Fugu, right?
Ah, Fugu...
It's a dream.
I went to Fugu at the end of my dream.
I was talking to Nan-chan.
There's a Fugu sashimi, right?
It's a thin sashimi that's spread out.
I don't usually use it.
It's expensive.
I don't have my own money.
I took a lot of Fugu sashimi with chopsticks.
I was saying, let's eat it.
And when it came out, I didn't know what to do.
It's up.
I couldn't eat it.
I took too much.
It's a little fluffy.
Did you take too much?
I took four or five pieces.
I'll eat it in my mouth forever.
I don't think it's that good just by saying it, right?
Even if it's Fugu, even if it's Matake, even if it's caviar, is it that good?
Right.
It's crab miso.
Ah, crab miso.
I don't think you're crazy to eat that.
When you break the shell of a crab, it looks like a beard.
You're crazy to eat that.
You're crazy.
You're so mean.
I didn't know how to eat it, so I thought I was poor.
One day, a crab came to my house.
What's that?
It's the first time a crab has come to your house.
When I was shaking my legs, my dad opened the shell of the crab and ate it.
My house is so poor.
How far have you gone?
What kind of person is my dad?
I don't know.
You don't know, do you?
That's not true.
I don't want to go to eat with this guy.
It's a child's idea.
What is it?
When I go to eat with this guy, it's a hamburger steak.
It's a child.
That's not true.
You don't eat that, do you?
I eat it at home.
You don't eat pickled radish, do you?
I eat it. I really like it.
You must eat it.
I eat it.
It's like fried chicken.
What is fried chicken?
That's a child.
That's not true.
You don't eat that, do you?
I eat it.
You eat a lot.
I'm talking to a yakuza.
I don't spend money on food.
That's not true.
I don't spend a thousand yen.
How many chickens do you think I have?
When I go to a family restaurant, I always have a set.
I also have a set.
I don't ask for a single dish.
I don't have to brag about it.
Let's change the topic.
Since this program started, the number of customers has increased, hasn't it?
That's right.
It's doubled.
Is it increasing?
It's increasing, but there are many people who don't want to see it.
How many people are there in one sheet of paper?
Three or four people, right?
That's why I really want to see it.
I want to see it.
There are four people.
I don't care about the other three people.
I don't care.
I'm a fan of Ucchanan.
That's right.
I'm also a fan of Ryuta Mine.
I'm the best at making money.
If you make money, people laugh.
I can't make money.
I can't laugh for 41 yen.
I was like that, too.
When the Drifters came,
Did you go to the Drifters?
That's right.
What?
When?
I went there when I was in high school.
You went to see the Drifters when you were in high school?
I went with a girl.
That's cool.
You went to see the Drifters when you were in high school?
Yes.
When I went to see the Drifters, there were only kids.
Of course.
I was the only adult there.
There was also a suburb.
When I was sitting down,
Mr. Chou was wearing sports shoes.
He came to me and said,
Hey!
People around me said,
I was like that, too.
I saw that.
Don't you often go to concerts like that?
I didn't.
You took me to the Takadamizue concert once.
I went to the Takadamizue concert.
It was at the opening of Garasuzaka.
Garasuzaka.
Shut up!
I went to the Takadamizue concert.
I said, Takadamizue.
I went to see the concert.
I said, Garasuzaka.
I said, I'm going to meet Takadamizue.
You said that, too.
You said, I'm the idiot who was watching it.
You're so cool.
When I was little,
I was taken away by my aunt.
Saigo Teruhiko.
I like you, but...
Hello, Dan-dan.
I have a question for you two.
Why do you always choose weird bread?
What do you think?
I don't know.
It's like, if you roll it, it's okay, right?
Their Parma is amazing, isn't it?
One year ago,
my mom said,
I'm going to clean up the Parma shop.
I said, really?
I took the class,
and I thought you were coming,
so I looked at you.
You look like a Mongolian.
I don't know what Mongolians are like.
It's amazing.
It's a big lot.
It's big, isn't it?
And I can't believe it.
You shouldn't do it as a human being.
It's like this.
The bottle is so tight.
I don't see it that often these days.
It's like Kabuto Kouji from Majinger Z.
In the past,
when I looked at the Parma shop,
all the women were wearing capsules like this.
That's right.
It's like a brainwave test.
They were lined up like this.
It's not like that these days.
It's really tough to be a mother.
Didn't they give you a hard time?
When you were in elementary school?
When I was little.
Did they give you a hard time when you were little?
They said they liked me.
They said they liked you.
It's so annoying.
I can't stand it.
I thought you were going too far.
What are you talking about?
I'm fine.
When I looked at the finished product,
it was like a dance.
Why are you making fun of me?
Even if you think like that,
you're still a man.
What are you talking about?
You're still a man.
You know what I mean, right?
You know,
I thought you killed him the most.
you go home sometimes.
So,
I asked you to sign it,
but you didn't sign it.
Right?
I don't care.
You didn't sign it when you went home.
I'm counting on you.
Don't say I'm counting on you.
Your face looks good.
Call me by the name you gave me.
I'll say it.
I'm interested in a girl.
When I followed her,
there was a dog at home.
The dog's fur was covered with poop.
There were eggs in the flower.
It was blue.
What should I do?
I don't know.
You don't like the girl you like, right?
Right.
It's hard.
I often see a girl's shoes.
The shoes look like a bottle cap.
It's stuck.
It's broken.
It's true.
If you boil it with soy sauce,
it will be fine.
I have one.
Right?
And the sneakers.
This area has been
beaten many times.
It's thin.
It's like a mini bomb.
I have one.
I used to wear a mini bomb.
Here and there.
I don't like men.
When I was in elementary school,
I wore sneakers all the time.
This part is broken.
Because it's beautiful.
When I was training,
I was doing this.
When I looked down,
this part was broken.
And my shoes were broken.
I thought it was cool.
My toes were like this.
Like this.
I was like this inside.
And I had tight clothes.
When you were in middle school,
you had tight clothes.
You didn't know that.
That's right.
I couldn't stand it.
I wore a white T-shirt.
It was a short sleeve.
What kind of design is that?
It's different.
It's a short sleeve.
It's tight.
It's winter.
It's a short sleeve in winter.
It's a lie.
It's obviously small.
If you wear it like this,
what will you do?
It's cold.
I like women.
I don't like women who have hair on their head.
I feel sorry for them.
If you have hair on your head,
you're not lucky.
You're like this.
That's why it's hard.
When you have hair on your head,
you're like this.
That's what I thought.
It's not like that.
That's why it's hard.
It's cold.
I always say that.
It's time to eat.
That's what he does.
Here.
It's been three days since it was made.
I was there.
It's cold.
I was angry.
I said,
It's cold.
I like women.
This is America.
That's also hard.
He did it, too.
What?
All of them.
He did it, too.
The hardest thing is
his nose.
That's not good.
His nose is like this.
He does like this.
Is there such a big animal?
If you do like this,
you won't notice it.
I was swaying.
You were swaying.
I don't know if you think of yourself as Hamada,
but you were Hanakuso-Soyoga.
I was swaying.
You went to the toilet.
When you looked in the mirror,
you noticed Hanakuso was swaying.
I was Hanakuso-Soyoga?
But this is hard.
You were swaying, but you didn't notice it.
But that's not good.
What should we do?
Let's leave it for now.
Let's go home.
Pretend you didn't notice it.
If you take it,
while we are talking,
what should we do?
Let's take it while we are talking.
The opening was amazing.
Did you do your best?
Mr. Namikoshi Tokujirou.
He is a really fun person.
Amazing.
Was it intense?
It was, but it's enough.
If you want to see more,
please send us your books.
All the books are the same.
If you have any questions,
or if you want us to read them,
please write them down and send them.
We will continue to write.
Until next time,
goodbye.
We are really waiting for you.
Thank you.