The first episode of Chikitsuki!
Nagashima Kazushige's complete production!
Karta Soda-Sensei!
Ah, Karta-san
What is it? It's a cy-break
It's really busy
We don't have time
The guest is a lazy person
Let's go!
There's a butt
You were busy.
Mr.Kajisaki, sorry for the inconvenience.
What do you mean by your ass is cut?
I'm busy.
I didn't decide it.
The schedule is the producer.
What do you mean?
It took 2 seconds to come out and kick ass.
This is the first time.
I was kicked in the ass suddenly during the recording.
Why are you kicked?
It's a nose.
It's over!
It was hard, right?
I thought about 44 or 45 patterns.
You thought about it seriously.
Did you draw it properly?
Of course.
You have a good sense of drawing, right?
If you look at it, you'll know how much I have.
Kazushige Nagashima
I'm talking to myself.
With his free spirit, he appeared in 272 TV shows last year and took over the industry.
Yes, I'll buy it.
Now, the most passionate man's unexpected appearance will be revealed tonight!
The rules are simple. The one who gets the most number of cards will receive a luxurious gift from Kazushige.
Is this the same as usual?
The person who gets the most number of cards will receive a prize.
You've written the guide carefully, haven't you?
Yes, I've written it seriously.
I'm not bad at drawing
You're checking it out
No, I'm not checking it
I'm just looking at the quality of the drawing
Nothing else
It's a pass
Thank you
Let's start
From the butt
What?
It's fast
You were looking
I was looking
I think I saw it clearly.
I'll read it until the end.
He is more of a boob than a butt.
I see.
What did you say?
No, no.
He is more of a boob than a butt.
Bigger?
Bigger is also okay.
Hamada-san, which do you prefer?
The butt or the boobs?
I think it's the boobs.
It was on the internet.
Hamada-san loves boobs.
I love boobs.
It says that you love boobs regardless of the price.
Hahaha
Regardless of the price.
Even if it's small, it's boobs.
That's right.
What about you, Matsumoto?
I'm not that particular about boobs.
The problem is the nipples.
Hahaha
It's no use if you don't have nipples.
I'm quite a maniac.
What kind of boobs do you like?
As long as it's big.
For example, who is the old idol?
Ah, if I had to say an old idol, it would be Kawaii Naoko-san.
Ah, that's true.
And, Sakakibara Ikue-chan.
Well, if I say that now, my son will get angry.
Ikue-san, and...
That's a bit...
I'm looking at you with that kind of eyes.
I wonder if there are people who hate boobs.
Kanaka-san, really...
What's wrong with you? You're so gross.
I feel bad.
What do you mean?
You don't have any sense of that.
I'm not a teacher.
It's about the butt.
About the butt?
You have to go in with your butt.
It's printed.
It's better to have a big one.
Who? Who?
Momotaro Kawaii-Nago.
He's a big fan.
When I was a kid, I thought, wow.
I thought so too.
If you fail with your neck, then your butt is better
But I don't fail with my butt
You don't fail with your butt?
But sometimes there are people who are really stiff
You're a genius
I've seen someone who is really stiff
You can't see it
Then, let's start
Unexpectedly, the middle name is Paolo
You're a bit off
That was fast
I don't know what to say.
What is your middle name?
I was baptized.
I am Catholic.
Paul?
My real name is Paul Kazushige Nagashima.
I am baptized and enter the middle name.
Christ's 12th century.
I haven't heard of it.
Is this a family name?
My mother is Catholic.
So my siblings were all baptized.
I was baptized when I was in the second or third grade of elementary school.
Isn't Paolo the most amazing place?
It's like a blessing place.
It's a moon-like place.
The moon is coming more and more.
There is no middle name called the moon.
I know it.
I thought you didn't know it.
He didn't know it.
I didn't know it.
Let's start.
He complains to cover himself.
It's fast.
I just saw it.
It's in front of you.
I'm not a Hamada-san.
You're a Hamada-san, right?
You always say something.
When we have a meeting, you always ask,
What do you think about that?
You don't want to do what you're told.
You want to oppose something.
Do you have such a thing with Hamada-san?
No, no.
You do what you're told?
Really?
What kind of town is this?
You know what Hamada-san is like.
I don't know.
Everyone's face is so pale.
It's like oil.
He's nervous.
That's true.
Do you have a crush on Matsumoto?
Not really.
I just want to try it.
I don't know if I should try it.
So you want to try it when you think it's boring?
I want to try it.
I think your way of talking is good
I've never heard that before
It's good
How do you do that?
Really, really
Unexpectedly
When I go to your dressing room, I hear that you are a former producer and you work a lot
That's right
Why do you come to my dressing room?
It's fine
Really?
You do that on purpose
I will definitely go to my senpai.
You're not a senpai.
I am a senpai.
You will go to Hamada-san's place, right?
Of course.
Are you coming?
I don't know.
This conversation is very troublesome.
The guest is very troublesome.
Please choose one.
You guys will come to the kid's place, too.
It's really troublesome.
Wait a minute.
That's our job.
Let's do it together.
Then we'll do it at once.
That's right.
If we do it together, it'll be like a curry show.
What's that?
Curry show?
Let's start.
Looks are thinner than slender.
It's RU!
You said it so suddenly
It's here again
It's always here
It's here!
It's like Masatoshi Hamada's Karuta tournament
It's like a big match
Let's mix it
This is also a woman's choice
It's a bit similar to boobs
I have that feeling.
When you have legs, it's not sexy to have a gap between thighs.
That's right.
But there are also people who like it to be rough.
That's right. There are people who like it to be rough.
There are?
Everyone is flat.
Eh? Tanaka?
I'm more of a flat person, and my butt is relatively flat.
Because you're a butt skin?
That's right.
But before, I liked a person from Slender, right?
Who?
The ex-wife of the previous one.
I only talked about that.
But if I only talked about that, I wouldn't like it.
I'm like that.
I want to talk about many things.
You mean women.
What do you want to do with your butt?
I look at their drawing like this...
You don't like that?
Yes I do.
But I don't have the urge to hit them.
But Hamada-san?
I don't usually do that.
If it happens I do this sometimes.
I have never hit then.
What happens when you hit them?
Nothing.
....piano
There is only puttingSt reportedly
Say but lotis for example
I have something tell.
I want to say something from the bottom of my heart WH внутри
It's allhaven'tbefine
Have Up
Don't add more
Ok leweat
Realistically, No.1 is Omi beef shatou-buri
D
It's D
It's here again
It's not a coincidence
It's all mixed
Your tobacco shop is also a bar
All of them are here
It's easy to get
When did you start?
Really?
I'm talking about Shiga's food.
You've been eating a lot of good food since you were little.
I think it's delicious.
I think so.
I think so if he says so.
I think Matsumoto-san's food is the best.
It's the best in this.
That's true.
For example, the stars go to listen to classical music or to watch ballet through year-end.
This is serious.
I think it's completely different from you guys.
It's a lie.
It's true.
What ballet did you go to watch?
There is no ballet.
There is.
Like the lake in Hakujyo.
I can't go to see such a thing.
What is it?
What ballet did you go to watch?
There is no ballet.
There are also those with a lot of muscles.
And the one with Kumakawa-san.
All of them.
All of them?
All of them are the best.
What are you talking about?
Not the cow, the best.
The best.
Amazing.
Not the beef.
You couldn't eat cup noodles when you were a kid.
When you were a kid?
I ate a lot of cup ramen.
Really?
I don't like it.
Chicken ramen came out when I was in elementary school.
And potato chips with Calbee's consommé flavor.
That's very normal.
That's the first one.
What about the Rider card?
I forgot the Rider card.
And the Home Run card from Calbee.
Oh, baseball.
Like baseball.
That's right.
So you get a lot of them at home.
He sends me money.
What happened to your allowance?
My allowance?
When I was in elementary school and middle school, I was given a lot of money.
So for a year...
Do you usually give money to others?
I gave it to myself.
Of course, I gave it to myself for a year.
So everyone,
In New Year's greetings, the relatives of the parents give greetings.
I don't know what to bring.
I will show you where I give my drop balls.
It's a little complicated story.
Well, there will be 40 people.
Well, it's not 1000 yen per person.
It's not.
Well, 100,000 yen is always...
400,000 to 500,000.
Wow!
It's not much for a year.
I wonder if it was really 2000 to 3000 yen.
Even if you collect all.
I collected all of them.
You collected all of them?
I'm about to cry.
I remember the scene of the sand.
Why am I in the scene of the ghost?
Let's start.
Hebi-Rote, Seiko's red sweet pea.
He, He.
He, He, He, He.
Oh, Hamada-san
It was there
This is originally your boyfriend's
No
Ebirote
Seiko-chan
Seiko-san
It's a big hit for Seiko Matsuda
I debuted in middle school about two years ago
Didn't you say you liked Kawai Naoko?
How about boobs?
I like the body
I like songs.
You like Seiko's songs.
I like Gai Sweet.
You like Seiko more than Akina.
Yes.
I like Akina too.
I was born in the year of the star.
I remember Akina's songs.
I like Yua Matsumoto's songs.
I like Yu Hayami's songs.
You were born in 1982.
Everyone was in it.
Akina-san was the only one who had a lot of production.
I still remember most of the production.
What about Chuu-san and Torio?
It's definitely Momoi-chan, right?
That's right.
Momoi-san and Junko-chan, right?
And Masako-chan.
Hey, that's not it.
It's not that kind of person.
Everyone is lined up.
That's right.
Kama-san's idol?
But they're about the same.
They're the same.
But I think it's Mako-chan.
Mako-chan from Ishida.
Yaeba.
That Yaeba is cute.
Mako-chan is still pretty.
She's cute.
She's still the same even after watching commercials.
Who's your idol, Matsumoto-san?
I think it's Momoe-chan.
Yamaguchi Momoe-san.
If I get invited to Momoe-chan's house, what should I do?
I was worried to the last minute, but I couldn't go.
I probably said,
Sorry, I can't go. I'm going home.
What are you worried about?
Are you still thinking about it?
I'll go to the front door, but...
Tomokazu is noisy.
That's impossible.
He's noisy.
It's still going on.
It seems to be easy.
That was a little faster.
Right?
Ah, that's fast!
Kazushige's even more honest side is revealed!
That's amazing!
That's strange.
I heard you won a karate contest on a different show.
Yeah.
What?
You're still doing it?
Yeah, I am.
You're not interested in karate?
Yeah, when I was in elementary school, there was a show called Karate Bakai Ichidai.
I wanted to do it, so I started to get interested in karate.
I'm not sure if I should do it or not.
I think you should try to get a blood test done.
You mean I should do it?
I'm scared because I don't want to do it.
The man who is scared of the man who is scared of the woman.
I don't like women who put perfume on their body.
I want to smell the body.
I don't know which one.
Do you smell the body?
I don't smell it.
You don't take a shower at all?
Yes.
I don't need a shower.
Hamada-san, this is becoming a strange Karuta.
Up until now, Hamada has been the one to win.
Who will win?
I'm starting.
The battle between the dreamy monster Egao.
Yes
What should I do?
That's what I'm talking about
I'm not motivated
I want to hear this story
I don't know
The reason why I don't know is
In the year when Mr. Egawa retired
It was the last year of Korakuen
The year I entered
I was a big fan of Ega.
I had a dream to fight against Ega.
I wanted to enter the pro-wrestling world.
Really?
I didn't have a partner who entered the pro-wrestling world.
I didn't have a partner.
That's right.
When I was 25, I was in the Giants after moving from Yakult.
Matsui was in the Giants.
At the Miyazaki camp, Matsui and I were newbies.
Of course, the newbies are the last ones to bat.
I'm not a regular, so I'm close to Hikari.
I practice batting with Matsui.
At that time, Ega-san was throwing the batting gauge towards Matsui.
Oh!
Hey, hey, hey.
What does that mean?
Ega-san, of course, retired and it's been years, but
In the TV program, Ega-san threw the batting gauge towards Matsui,
and Ega-san probably had a plan to explain it.
I see.
Why is it Godzilla?
I'm fine with that.
Even though you want to fight so badly?
Even though I want to fight.
And then,
after Matsui finished his batting practice,
he immediately jumped in to get in.
And then Ega-san might do it.
And I immediately got out of the game,
and Ega-san was still there.
I thought I'd get in, but Ega-san didn't even look at me.
He went in.
And he got off the ground.
That was really a trick.
Matsui was J?
No, I didn't jump properly.
Oh, I see.
You were pushed.
I was pushed.
I thought, Egawa-san is amazing.
I was watching, but why did I jump?
You didn't?
Let's start.
The famous director of Miyazaki Hayao, Mukarinai.
Mu.
It's Mu.
Yes.
It's your first time.
Ah, this side
Miyazaki Hayou-san
I once did voice acting
In the movie, Ponyo on the cliff
Ponyo's father in the movie
The one on the boat
Yes, the one on the boat
I was surprised
In short, you have to match the voice and the picture
But it doesn't match no matter how long it takes
Because he's blue.
No, no, he's not blue.
It's difficult.
Eventually, the teacher said,
It's okay.
Then, you can talk as you like.
He's not blue.
Everyone can match.
Do you do that alone?
I do it alone.
Whether there is a partner,
It's a partial shot.
Why don't you match?
It's blue, isn't it?
I didn't know it.
It's a good match.
No, no, no. It's a good match.
Miyazaki sensei said,
this is not like Kazushige-kun.
So, Kazushige-kun, read this line to your own sense.
I read it.
Then, I said, that's fine.
Then it was over.
I thought, this is not good with the picture at all.
I thought it was okay to finish it.
But later,
I changed the drawing after that.
You changed it?
I changed it.
Wow, amazing!
It's a lot of trouble.
That's what happened.
Since then, I've been calling you.
Really?
I don't know if it's alive.
I think it was pretty good.
What?
What's that?
Don't you have that kind of thing?
Ateleco?
I've never done Ateleco.
Don't you have Hamas?
Oh, Mr. Matsumoto.
I have it.
Shrek
But in Shrek, it's not done properly
The pencil
The line of Shrek is just moving
Sometimes it's done properly
The people over there all have their voices taken first
So they have their voices taken first
All of them have their voices taken first and then the animation is made
Is that so?
Then it's the opposite
Have you ever been called Shrek while walking on the street?
No.
No?
Shrek?
But I've played it before, so maybe I've played it once.
Next episode!
I'm late because I'm sleepy.
The second episode of the long-awaited Karta growth battle!
I went to the kitchen and found a knife.
He confessed his biggest slump in his life
And his thoughts about the 9th round
I don't want to be the coach of a baseball player
It's impossible
Hamada-san, you don't understand
It's obvious that no one knows about this victory
I'm going to practice
anges완