Before the performance, I can't see that man again
Good morning
Okamoto-san told me to come with you
Please
He told me to come to Haneda
Haneda? It's really far
Why?
I want to stay here
I'm sorry
What should we do?
Let's go home
Please change the manager
Okamoto is angry again
Manager Okamoto has been angry many times
The origin of his anger is always unknown
Why are you giving me a bungee?
Bungee?
3, 2, 1, go
His anger doesn't go down like a bungee
The second time he got angry towards a giant guillotine
It's the third time
Giant guillotine
I don't want to do it
Why?
Okamoto gets angrier
The third time he asked for a human cannon banana bird
Human cannon banana bird
I'll do it
The strongest adventurer in the entertainment industry
Manager Okamoto
Where will he go?
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching
What is it?
It's money
For what?
It's just a picture
What is it?
Where is it?
Over there
This is bad
Okamoto, this is the airport
He's angry
What's wrong?
It's not cool
What's not cool? It's always like this
What's not cool?
The cat has changed
It's true
It's in the hospital
Your cat is in the hospital
I'm going to Okinawa
It's sudden but I'm going to Okinawa
Why?
I'll do it like this
Why are you looking at the camera?
Why?
I'm going
Get ready
Okinawa is the southernmost part of Japan
The blue sky and the blue sea
The sun is burning on the white beach
What does he want to do in this resort?
Do you know why I came here?
I came to Okinawa
Everyone, come to Okinawa
Okinawa
It's hot
I'm the only one here
It's very hot
Everyone should dress up like this
Let's go
Who is it?
It's you
I'm going to take it
The cat is scared
It's not scared
Let's go
Do you hate it that much?
I don't hate it
I'm doing nothing
Let's go
Let's stop
I'm doing nothing
Are you going home?
I'm not going home
Let's go
I can see you
No
Let's go
This is it
Without any explanation
The boy is on the bus
Where is he going?
Where are you going?
I know
Don't smoke
Why?
Because the cat hates it
He calls me every time
He looks surprised
I've been watching him
Where?
You'll know when you get off
How many times have you been to Okinawa?
Stop smoking
Are you stupid?
Are you really stupid?
We're here
What's this?
It's hot
Okinawa is hot
Come here
What is this?
I don't know
It's hot
Do you know what it is?
It's a grand
I don't know if you're stupid
Why did you change your clothes?
Because it's hot
Because I came to Okinawa
Here
I know
It's a cattle farm
A cattle farm?
What are you doing?
I came to Okinawa to have a cattle farm
He wants me to have a cattle farm
What is this?
It's hot
When did you get this?
Look
It's Okamoto
I'm saving this
Do you want to be like this?
Yes
It's dangerous
It's okay
I'm not going to hurt you
I came here to do this
I brought you here
Manager Okamoto challenges Okinawa cattle
Okinawa cattle
The cattle are afraid of each other
Sometimes the attack of the thick horn is fatal
It can kill people
The intensity is the best in Japan
It looks like a cow
I'm motivated
Cow
Okamoto
Did you see it?
I saw it
I'm going to do that
What?
Are you going to do it?
I'm going to do it next
Your nails are sharp
You have long nails
It's huge!
Take a look at it.
It's huge.
It's not anything.
Why don't you go closer and take a look?
Just as we planned.
This is it.
It's coming.
It's looking at us.
It must be a 751.
It's dangerous.
It's scary.
It's coming.
It's in front of us.
It's a meteorite.
It's over.
It's pushing.
It's going to break.
How about you hit it from above?
You're different today.
Come back, Okamoto-san.
Does that mean we won?
It's amazing, Okamoto-san.
We fought.
We won this time.
You're satisfied, right?
Let's go to the Mayakawa Shimbatsu.
Let's go.
We still have 30 minutes left.
I'll do the opening.
I'll do it.
Let's do it next time.
I'll do it next time.
I'll do it all the time.
Are you sure?
Okamoto's anger that doesn't know how to stay.
Who will wait for the next one?
I'll drag you around a lot.
I'm going to sleep.
What are you doing?
Wake up.
I'm awake.
Okinawa is fun.
Let's have fun.
You guys don't usually come.
Why are you laughing?
There's not much to use at this stage.
It's about half a year.
I'll have to work hard from now on.
It's okay if you do a talk show.
Really?
We're playing.
You look like a new man.
I was big back then.
Is this the place?
Yes, this is the place.
Okamoto said he'd do it for 30 minutes.
He went to a private beach at a luxury hotel.
What is he going to do at this beach?
Look at this.
It's getting cloudy.
The weather is not good.
You've never been to a place like this.
Is this my type?
That's...
I want to hear it.
He's got a cat on his back.
Hug him.
It's like a handmade tea.
I'm going to ride that.
That?
You're all happy, right?
You can't come here.
This is funny.
Is this how it's going to be?
You're going to dive in.
You're going to break the watermelon with this.
Mr. Okamoto, we've come a long way and we wanted to see this
We've come a long way and we wanted to see this because I want to see it.
No, it's because I want to see it.
Manager OKAMOTO.
challenge to breaking watermelon in the water.
It's an ancient art that may have been passed down among the people.
Okamoto will attempt this fürthe in the water 5m deep.
How much do I have to pay you?
That's three hundred fifty.
All cash?
It's cash.
It's a card.
It's here
Okamoto san
I'm gonna do this for 30 minutes
If this doesn't work we're gonna go to Kanda Pans
It's only been 30 seconds
It's been a minute and a half
Okamoto san
You can think about it later
Don't say it here
I'll cool down
Okamoto san
I'm gonna blow from the water
This is
I'm gonna blow this
Is it okay to jump in?
The water got wet
Hey
Are you okay?
What's wrong with your face?
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
It's hot
What do you mean it's hot?
Okamoto san
Bye bye
You can't go back
Okamoto san
Hey
It's hot
It's scary
What are you doing?
Dive from there
Here
It's cold
What are you doing?
You're just putting on a face
Dive
It's hot
Don't say it's hot
Dive
What's wrong?
It's not funny
I can't say it's really hot
Come here and hold the end of the bamboo
We'll go down
I'll push
Let's go
This way
Okamoto san
It's hot
Let's go home
We'll take you to the middle of the field
Are you going to do something else?
I'll do it again
You can do it
Take the rest
Are you going to do it again?
I'll do it again
Put your energy in
I don't know
It's the same
Is this the human arrest we did before?
Yes
That island over there
We'll go there together
I'll go first
I'll tie the rope myself
Everyone come with me
What is this?
This is anger
I'll stab you
Let's play together
Let's play
How much can we play in this space?
Okamoto san
Your ideal image is too big
It's really cool
Manager Okamoto is going to Okishima to challenge the human arrest
Last time in Tokyo, Okamoto failed to catch the human arrest
He chose the human arrest in the ocean in Okinawa
The distance is 50 meters
Will Okamoto's body make it to Okishima safely?
Okamoto san
I've set it up as you wanted
Is it okay?
It's okay
I'll stab the island that came out from here
Everyone came later
They came with ropes
I'll stab you with this
I got it
What?
What is that?
He's angry
It wasn't in the picture
It's sweat
It fell into the water
I want to play over there
Let's play over there
What are you doing?
Let's have a barbeque
I've never been to Hanoi
Okamoto san, can you hear me?
He's saying oh
I'll close it
Oh's pattern
Lift it
It needs to be at the right angle
It's at the right angle
Let's go
5 seconds before take off
4, 3, 2, 1
Start
5 seconds before take off
4, 3, 2, 1
Start
5 seconds before take off
4, 3, 2, 1
It's fine
You're wearing a robe
Your head is off
Okamoto san, what's wrong?
What?
My head
What's wrong with your head?
Where did it go?
It's fine
I won't be on TV anymore
What did you hate the most?
Let's look back
Reality
The picture over there
It's a dream
I saw it in my dream
I wanted to be a mother
5 seconds before take off
4, 3, 2, 1
Where are you going?
I'm sorry
I don't know
What?
You should talk
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
I'm having fun
Ouch
I'm tired
I can't do it
I'll get angry
If I do it too much
5 seconds before take off
4, 3, 2, 1
What's wrong with you?