Good evening.
Do you know where we are today?
We are in front of a Buddhist temple.
That's right.
We are in Tawara-machi today.
Tawara-machi.
Asakusa is right there.
We've been there before.
That's right.
As you can see behind me, there is a Buddhist temple.
This is the Buddhist temple you mentioned earlier.
There are many Buddhist temples about 1 km away.
It's called the Buddhist temple street.
So it's safe to say that this is the Buddhist temple street.
That's...
That's a long story.
From the temple.
I see.
Look at the name of this shop.
What is it?
I just happened to see it.
Hamada Shoten.
Right.
They're doing bad business.
It's the same here.
That's right.
It's all the same.
Look at this.
It's closed.
It's like when Umekawa was arrested.
It's like the Mitsubishi Bank.
Well...
It's been a while since I had oden there.
What? Oden?
Oden.
Radish and egg.
And my father's love.
I heard something earlier.
They're doing bad business.
This is the 5th floor.
That supermarket over there.
Where are you going, old man?
What?
Where are you going?
I'm done for today.
Idiot.
What?
We don't have any money.
We don't have any money to pay the children.
It's on the 5th floor.
You can try asking around at Place 24.
That's the plan.
Enjoy until the end.
This program is brought to you by Sanraku, Toyosui-san, and Oyama International Products.
Please come this way.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Good evening.
Today's guest is famous.
Why?
Today is the 9th day.
The 9th day?
Yes, today is the 9th day.
The most uncooperative guest.
Why?
I don't know what makes you laugh.
No, no.
He has been working hard until now.
Really?
I don't know why you say that.
The weather is bad today.
I don't think everyone is in a good mood.
Oh, you got a watch today.
What?
Bandai or something.
I got a watch.
An Ultraman watch.
Yes, yes, yes.
I don't need it.
Who is the 26-year-old man?
I threw it away.
I don't need it.
I'm grateful that this program is popular.
These days, TV is not interesting.
It's being pushed to movies.
Really?
Video is the same.
You can watch movies on rental.
But there is no Japanese movie.
I don't like it.
These days, there is no Japanese movie.
You like it.
There are a lot of movies that I liked.
Really?
I used to watch a movie called Ogata Ken Shuen.
I was impressed.
KAI.
It's a difficult word.
I don't know if I should write it.
I don't like Japanese movies.
I don't know the meaning of the title.
I don't want to watch it.
I don't know what KAI means.
But it's Ogata Ken Shuen KAI.
And there is a Ketsu on it.
Why?
What kind of movie is Ogata Ken Shuen KAI?
It's funny.
There is a Ketsu from Ogata Ken.
It's over when the blood comes out.
You are stupid.
I've been writing Ketsu all the time.
What do you mean it's over when the blood comes out?
KAI is interesting.
I don't like the title.
There is also YASHA.
Takakura Ken.
YASHA.
Yakuza movie.
Takakura Ken Shuen YASHA.
I don't know the meaning of YASHA.
But there is a KANAWANYO on it.
It's WA-SHA.
WA-SHA and KANAWANYO.
It's an action movie.
I think it's a good movie.
Takakura Ken Shuen WA-SHA and KANAWANYO.
What kind of movie is it?
It's funny.
There are many strange movies these days.
But the title is interesting.
What is strange?
Orgol.
It's Tsuyoshi Nagaguchi.
Orgol is the first main character.
I don't want to watch it.
What kind of movie is it?
It's RURUGORU.
That's right.
This is a picture of the stupid Tsuyoshi.
He is saying,
I want to go!
He is eating the butter.
RURUGORU?
What is RURUGORU?
I don't want to watch that movie.
I'd like to watch it if it's a movie.
But I think the radio is more interesting.
The radio is interesting.
It's a child's phone call.
He's quite popular.
He doesn't listen to his friends.
He doesn't understand what his friends are saying.
He doesn't listen to his parents.
He calls them.
Hello?
What?
He was busy.
That happens sometimes.
Hello?
What's wrong?
Be quiet!
It's like a phone call for a child.
Hello?
You speak too fast.
Don't talk to me like that.
A little more.
A little smaller.
Hello?
What's your name?
Matsumoto.
Sato.
Sato?
What's your name?
Matsumoto.
Matsumoto?
Yes.
What's your name?
Sato.
Sato?
Matsumoto?
Yes.
Where's Sato?
What's the meaning of that?
Matsumoto Sato.
Matsumoto is your name?
Yes.
This is ridiculous!
Don't think of me like that!
What's the meaning of that?
I'm sorry.
Why didn't you say Sato?
Hello?
What's wrong?
I have something to ask.
That's why you called me.
I'm a Buddhist monk.
What?
Why are you concerned about children?
I don't care what you are.
I want to know what you are.
Ask me something child-like.
You're a Buddhist monk.
Why are you worried about this?
I want to know something more.
Something child-like.
Hello?
Yes?
I don't know how to say it, but it tickles my tongue.
Maybe I should drink some water.
What should I eat?
Ask your mother!
Don't call me all the time!
If you do that, your mother will be angry!
If you want to say something, just say it.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
It's better to ask your mother.
I'm going to ask something childish.
Why is a giraffe's neck so long?
That's a good question.
It's my first time.
Say it again.
Why is a giraffe's neck so long?
It's not a neck.
Don't call me a giraffe.
I don't want to call you a giraffe.
A giraffe's neck is very relaxing.
That's why you can't wait for a snack at 3 o'clock.
That's why it has a long neck.
That's true.
It's true.
Who is the turtle?
I'm not a turtle.
I'm a bear.
I'm not a bear.
I'm a turtle.
What?
I'm a snake.
I'm a bear.
What are you talking about?
I'm a woman.
You're a elephant.
You're a fool.
If you say such a complicated thing, I'll be in trouble.
I'm a child.
You're a man.
Brrrr.
Hello? I'd like to ask you something.
What do you want to ask?
I'm a stone.
A stone?
No one calls a stone.
Brrrr.
Hello? I'd like to ask you something.
I'm a fax machine.
A fax machine?
I'm sorry.
Why do you call a fax machine?
Hello?
I'd like to ask you something.
What is it?
I'm a child.
I'm a fax machine.
I'd like to ask you something.
What is it?
I'm...
Sorry. A fax machine just came in.
What?
I'm waiting for a fax machine.
Why don't you play the recorder?
Don't use Kachiyo!
We're talking politely to each other!
Hello? What's up? It's Onii-san.
Is it okay?
Yes, it's okay.
Is Kachiyo okay?
It's okay.
Hello?
Yes, what is it?
You know...
Yes.
I have something I want to ask you.
Yes, yes, yes.
How can a baby be born?
Ah, I see. How can a baby be born?
Yes.
A baby is born.
Ah!
What kind of phone call is that?
A baby is born?
That's not how it works.
What do you mean by a baby is born?
What?
Think of a way to say it!
You're talking to a child on the phone.
You should say, a baby is born!
You shouldn't say that.
You should ask something childish.
Childish?
Childish.
Hello? What's up?
Hello? Onii-san?
Yes.
I have something I want to ask you.
Yes, yes, yes.
How can a baby be born?
Hmm.
That's a great question.
Is it a great question?
Onii-san is very tired.
I see.
Yes.
How can a baby be born?
That's right.
This is a very difficult question.
Is that so?
So, Onii-san, I'm going to look it up.
Don't hang up. Wait.
Ah, yes.
I'm sorry.
I'll be out soon.
Yes.
Wait for me.
Does he know the answer?
I think he doesn't.
I think he doesn't know the answer.
How much longer?
Don't hit me!
Shut up!
Hurry up and play!
This is a very difficult problem. Can you wait a little longer?
I'm sorry!
I'll wait.
It's already fallen.
I'm sorry.
Can you wait a little longer?
It disappeared!
I'm sorry.
This is the first time you've seen a new story on TV.
Everyone doesn't understand this tension.
You can't experience it for the rest of your life.
I'm an amateur.
I said this before, but it's like you're driving for the first time and getting a license and getting a high speed.
You're good.
I don't know if I'm good or not.
It's like that.
I have a sense of tension.
It's hard.
I don't know how to react.
I've never done it in front of anyone.
I'm in a very bad condition physically.
Yesterday in Osaka, the radio was over, and today I came here by car.
It took seven hours.
The manager was already out, but no one came home.
My butt hurts.
What?
Your butt.
It hurts!
Suddenly I'm like this.
I saw your butt.
Even if I can't see it, I can't see it.
You're sick.
You're doing the ultimate choice in the middle of the car.
Choice?
Ultimate choice.
Speak clearly.
Which one do you choose?
I don't have a name.
You don't have a name.
I don't have a name called Hamada Masatoshi.
No one calls me.
They only call me Oi or Kimi.
Even my mother calls me Masatoshi.
They only call me Anta.
I can't even call the woman I like.
I don't have a name.
Even the manager doesn't know my name.
Because you don't have a name.
That's right.
Also,
I have a name called Piyo Piyo-man.
I knew it.
Piyo Piyo-man.
I wouldn't have known if I didn't have a name.
There are a lot of cool scenes with that name.
When I become a crab in a mental video, I look cool, right?
No, you don't.
You look cool even in a hospital waiting room.
When you go to the doctor, you say,
Piyo Piyo-man-san.
Even then, if you wait in the waiting room,
it's better than being called Oi.
Hey, you there.
Right?
It happens in traffic accidents.
There are a lot of things that happen.
In traffic accidents.
You crash your head.
You can't see the whole machine.
There's no spare machine.
No one has a spare machine.
You're covered with a transparent mat.
That's a machine.
You can't see the whole brain.
You crash your head.
You have a hat like a ping-pong ball.
You drew the bear's picture.
And you have a ball.
Oh, that's right.
You're a ping-pong ball.
You're a bad-looking guy.
I can't stop thinking about everyone's brainwaves.
When I think of something, I can't stop thinking about it.
Oh, he's thinking of something now.
And when I exercise hard, I can't stop thinking about it.
I'm going to introduce a little bit.
I'm sorry, Akiyo.
Why did you catch a cold again?
Yeah, I caught a cold.
I'm sorry.
I can't go home today.
I can't go home right away if I catch a cold.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to introduce a little bit.
I'm Masami Takatani from Chiba prefecture.
Good evening, Masumoto-san.
Thank you for your hard work every time.
There is a saying that there is a different way of saying the word eat on the radio.
There are only two people who eat.
I'm sorry.
I'll give you a little bit of food.
It's the same for girls.
I gave you a little bit of food yesterday.
I gave you a little bit of food.
Why are you so quiet?
I don't know if it's a little different from Osaka-pen.
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
There's candy.
Candy ball.
What do people say about this?
Do you call it candy?
What do you call it?
Just candy?
Do you eat candy?
I don't have candy, but I don't eat it.
I can't say I don't eat it.
Osaka is different.
There's a candy in Osaka.
Candy-chan.
You think this is a lie, don't you?
Really?
It's true.
This is definitely true.
It's not just young people.
Old people are overbearing, too.
That's right.
There was a yakuza last time.
He's got a lot of eyebrows that look like they're going to break.
I'll give you a punch.
A yakuza came and said,
I caught you candy-chan.
It's true.
You're lying!
It's really candy-chan.
If you have any relatives in Osaka, ask them.
It's not really a lie.
The poop is also called poop-chan.
It's true!
It's true.
This is also true.
It's true, right?
This is true.
Everything is chan?
Everything is chan.
What else is there?
Huh?
Ame-chan.
Ame-chan, right?
Poop-chan.
Huh?
This is...
Hama-chan.
This is match-chan.
Huh?
This is te-chan.
This is match-chan.
It's obvious that it's poop-chan.
Touching dirty things.
Everyone runs away.
This is true.
This is true, right?
Right?
What is this?
Huh?
En-gato.
En-gato?
What was Osaka again?
Oi.
Huh?
Bebenjo?
This is...
This is too dirty.
Bebenjo, Kanjo, Kage, Shimeta, right?
Which one is better?
Kansai.
Kansai, right?
Bebenjo is better.
This one is dirtier.
There's a coffee shop, right?
When you go to a coffee shop,
what do people ask you to do?
In Osaka, they ask you to eat char siu baku.
When you go to eat gyudon.
When you go to eat gyudon, do they ask you to eat gyudon?
That's interesting.
In Osaka, they ask you to eat gyu shi baku.
Gyu shi baku.
Today, we'll ask these two questions again.
We'll ask them to answer.
That's right.
Today, we'll ask them to answer.
Here we go.
When you go to a coffee shop?
Char siu baku.
When you go to eat gyudon?
Gyudon.
I'm sick of it.
Gyu shi baku.
I can't go home.
That's right.
Let's do it again.
When you go to a coffee shop?
Char siu baku.
When you go to eat gyudon?
Gyu shi baku.
What about this?
That's right.
That's all for today.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
That was fun.
You know,
I don't like it when people misunderstand me.
But next week,
I'm thinking of doing a comedy show.
What do you mean?
Why did you get misunderstood?
You know,
I don't like it when people misunderstand me.
It's not like that.
It's not like that at all.
It can't be helped.
You're right.
You know,
we've been talking all the time.
Right?
We don't use our bodies
so much in the free talk.
That's why people who are watching
think of us as lovely people.
It seems that the opening
will be canceled next week.
Really?
I'm so happy.
It was hard in the rain.
It's amazing.
It's so cold.
It'll be much easier if it's canceled.
It'll be easier.
I can concentrate on the next time.
That's all.
That's all for today.
Goodbye.
This program is brought to you by
Tohyo Suisan