Next, let's watch the final pro-wrestling match of Ritton Mizuno!
Tonight is the last day of Mizuno's solo life.
Let's watch the match!
Let's go!
Let's watch the final match of Ritton Mizuno!
Ritton Mizuno
I'm already slipping at this stage.
Human nuclear power!
The power of art is not just nuclear power.
Ritton Mizuno, also known as human nuclear power.
Today, Ritton Mizuno is going to have his first solo match in 37 years.
Will he be able to get a wonderful girlfriend and have the best summer in his life?
How old are you now?
I'm 37 years old.
You're 37 years old?
Yes.
You're 37 years old, and you don't have a girlfriend yet, right?
I don't have a girlfriend.
I'm already slipping at this stage.
You're slipping at this stage.
I see.
You have to do your best.
Today, we're going to have a pro-wrestling match.
Her name is Hanatabajo.
I see.
Let's see how much you can appeal to her.
All right.
This is your first match.
Your opponent is Hanatabajo!
What kind of beauty is she?
What?
Wow!
I'm so happy!
I've never seen anything like this before.
Let me introduce you to her.
Her name is Rei Morikawa.
She's currently a female pro-wrestler.
She's going to make a lunch box full of love for her husband.
Are you good at cooking?
Yes, I am.
You're good at cooking?
I see.
That's great.
Let's start with Hanatabajo.
Yes.
Hanatabajo, please give her a present.
All right.
Good luck.
Good luck from now on.
That's great.
I want to sleep with you tonight.
All right.
That's great.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Let's get started.
Are you all right?
That's great.
That's a real name.
I just thought of a name.
That's great.
Good luck.
Personally, I didn't feel
like I could sing this song.
Thank you.
It was great.
It's you!
This is not about winning or losing
I've already said this to her, but how much water can she drink to appeal to her?
Now, Morikawa Rei-san, please make your judgement
Okay, I'm ready
The judgement is...
Please! Please!
Why? Why?
I think she did her best, but I like strong people
That's not true!
You're overreacting!
Please say it again
I don't understand anything
Please do it one more time!
Now that she's been asked to do it again, let's have her back on the stage
Ningen Genshi-Ryoku Ritton Mizuno is here!
She's back on the stage again!
That's enough
Please welcome Yamato Nadeshiko-san and Fuwa Marika-san!
She's the type of person who always makes me laugh
I see
Is it hard?
No, it's not hard
It's okay, it's okay
Now, please give her a bouquet of flowers
Let's do our best!
Thank you
Let's go eat after the show
Let's go to my restaurant
Please sit at the back
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Let's go, Ritton Mizuno!
Let's see the pro-wrestling match!
She's here!
Hey, Mizuno, are you okay?
Your opponent is Takano!
We will now begin the first match of today's main event, the time limit
In the red corner, the 300 pound fighter, Kenji Takano!
In the blue corner, the 140 pound fighter, Ritton Mizuno!
Kenji Takano!
It's been 4 or 5 years!
It's been 2 or 3 years!
Mizuno!
It's okay, it's okay
Are you going to hit me with all of them?
Is this a down?
Yes, it's a down
3, 4
Fight!
I can't breathe
Really?
He's wearing a mask
It's a down
I don't need that
Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go!
Now! Now!
The top rope!
Go! Go!
Top rope!
What's wrong?
It's a fall
What's the matter?
From the top rope!
Go! Go! Go!
He's being surrounded!
He did it!
Mizuno!
I can't do this anymore.
You can't do this anymore!
You're dead!
There are a lot of you!
He's dead!
But!
Please give me a judgement!
The judgement is...
This time too, his nuclear power was unexpected.
I was just looking at him.
He's a taxi driver.
Everyone!
I'm glad that there are a lot of you here.
Actually, I'm seeing this for the first time today.
Now, let me introduce you to everyone.
This is the new Mizuno!
Hey!
Wait a minute.
What do you want to be?
I like you a lot.
Really?
If that's the case, I think I should be with you even though I'm 25 years old.
As a stranger, what kind of person do you want me to be?
First, let's talk about the person who was more popular in the past.
Just ignore that!
No!
Is that person better than me now?
That's good, isn't it?
That's because it's a human voice.
It's really wild.
To be honest, I thought it would be even weirder.
When I got home, I was just looking at the mirror.
It's not wild anymore.
When I had hair, it was wild.
Now it looks like a fur.
No way! It's really cool!
It looks like I'm being bullied.
I wonder if it's true. If I get hit like this, I think it's really worth it.
But it's not like I'm doing this all the time.
When I'm doing it normally, your eyes are big.
It looks like Boku-chan.
It's not cute anymore.
It's not scary anymore.
It looks like it has a lot of hair.
Hey!
I really like it.
But the people around me don't like it.
That's true.
But today, I went into the opening scene.
I was in a different room.
It's finally here.
Yuta-san said,
It's a great voice.
What is it?
I really wanted to see it from afar.
I've been wearing a towel all the time.
I'm used to it.
I'm not used to it myself.
I'm going to the bathroom.
I'm afraid it's going to come back.
You have to show the back of the deluxe before you show it.
I don't know.
When I'm in the bathroom, I usually forget.
I'm not wearing my own hair.
I'm sure I can't do it.
I'll be in a hurry.
Why are you making that sound?
It's like you have an enemy in your head.
I have beautiful hair, so I had no choice but to go like this.
But I can go like this, right?
No, it's not like that.
Everyone says it's good, but I want you to say it's better.
But the shape of the head is good.
It's really good, right?
The shape of the head is good.
I can't do that, because I'm perfect.
I'm just easy to hit.
Also, you're a little too burnt.
What do you mean, too burnt?
The sun...
Yes, yes, yes.
Your face...
It's even more like that.
It's like I'm a botamochi.
Botamochi...
If you're an amateur, you can't do that.
Um...
Are you a botamochi?
Are you a botamochi with a Regula 4 and 5?
You're really cool when you hit.
Cool?
I don't know what kind of person you are.
I don't know your nationality.
That's why you're mysterious.
Because you're Machan.
You shouldn't be called Machan.
You're mysterious.
It's not that you and I admire each other.
It's called a double pose.
No, it's not.
Change your name.
It's called a double baldness.
Baldness?
How about that?
It's not good.
No, it's not.
The shape of your head is good.
Yes, yes, yes.
I can't do that.
Is that so?
If you look from the front, your head is like this.
It's like a spearhead.
This is hard.
If you look from the side, it's like this.
The tip is sharp.
You don't have a baldness.
I don't have a baldness.
Why?
Because...
It's beautiful.
I was raised with great care.
It's true.
I was born at 5 o'clock.
I was born at 5 o'clock, so I don't have time to shave.
I don't have a baldness.
It's beautiful.
Thank you very much.
It's true.
If you look from the front, your hair is like this.
It's weird.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's beautiful.
It's true.
Thank you very much.
Would you like to be my partner?
I have a question for Matsumoto-san, who has been watching Hotaru's wedding scene from the North since the last broadcast.
I see.
The famous song of Masashi Sada.
It's la la la la la la.
I see.
There are lyrics, but what kind of lyrics are there?
This is really new.
Really?
Masashi Sada and So Kuramoto are...
Sada...
Are you stupid?
It doesn't fit.
You're thinking about it, right?
This...
No, it's not like that.
I don't like it that much.
Please tell me.
What is it?
I'm saying it from the side.
The lyrics...
Well, it's okay.
What was it like?
You know the most.
It's la la, not aah, right?
It says la la here, so I'll just say it.
Aaaaah.
It's a little embarrassing to do this.
Although I can pretend to be asleep.
Okay, Masumoto-san.
Yes.
I'll sing a different song for you.
What?
Oh, you have one?
Yes, please.
The pure firefly is la la.
Lala
Jun Hotaru is a la-la
Hokkaido is coming out
Really?
Is the conversation going well?
Yes
Did I stop it too soon?
Yes you did
I'm sorry
It's just that, Jun Hotaru is a la-la
You should show it from here
This is too much
Yes
I'm sorry.
Please.
Jun, Otaru, wa-ra-ra
Tanaka, Kunie, ra-ra
Jun and Otaru are called by their nicknames.
Why is your father called Tanaka Kunie?
Don't just call me by my nicknames.
What's your father's role?
He's the muscle of the year.
What's Tanaka Kunie's role?
What?
I'm going to do it from now on, you idiot.
Don't call me Tanaka Kunie.
I'm sorry, I couldn't think of Tanaka Kunie's role.
What was his name?
Gorou.
It's Gorou.
I don't know if it's Tanaka Kunie.
Are you ready?
Please.
Jun, Otaru, wa-ra-ra
Gorou, ra-ra-ra-ra
Kuramoto,
No matter what I say today, everyone's eyes are on me.
That's right.
It's kind of hard to do, isn't it?
When I talk to strangers, I can't look up, so I look down.
That's how I feel right now.
Wait a minute.
You're the farthest from strangers.
I prepared a few strangers in front of me.
Today, I'm going to do it with this hairstyle.
Come to the set like that.
Sometimes it's this long.
Kimura Takuya's long hair.
Sometimes I shake my head like this.
I can't grow my hair for the rest of my life.
If that's the case, I'll think about it.
If I don't get caught,
I don't know if I'm doing this.
If I don't remember,
I'll make my head look like this.
Who's going to say what first?
I want you to do that.
Like that ***.
It's hard!
Strangers are usually nice.
When I drink alcohol, I don't know what's going on.
I feel like I have to be nice.
I don't forget that it's hard.
It's going to be okay.
When I went to drink with someone before,
I saw a man next to me.
He drank a lot of alcohol.
He's writing it down with his hand.
I don't want you to know.
Emergency announcement.
The eternal rival, Moriman and Yamazaki, will finally meet at the venue in Tokyo.
Will it be Moriman or Yamazaki?
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.