Next time on Gaki no Tsukai Ara!
Chiki Chiki!
The end of the year!
Kouhaku High Tension Gassen!
Good evening everyone!
Good evening!
Chess is back again.
Yes, I'm the only one who's a little blue.
I've been in the top 10 before.
That's right.
It's the end of the year.
We're going to have a match with Kouhaku.
We, the red team, will do our best.
Thank you for coming!
What are you looking at?
The white team can't lose either!
Let's take a look at everyone's recent events this year.
Animal's monkey.
He earned a lot of prize money on the show.
I don't know at all.
There was a TV show last year.
He earned 1 million yen in 1 minute and a half.
Wow!
1 million yen!
He went to drink with Kouhaku.
I was invited right now.
I'm just kidding.
Thank you very much.
The content of the fan letter is mostly about the route.
Should I get a job?
Should I go to high school?
I'm not the real thing.
I can't do that.
This program is sponsored by the following sponsors.
The top batter is the red team.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Animal.
Mr. Monkey will do it.
Yes, Mr. Monkey will do it.
Mr. Kohara will cheer for you.
That's right.
I'm sure you're nervous because you're the top batter.
I'm nervous.
What's the title like?
I'm Kato Manager.
I don't know what you're talking about.
The title is Kato Manager.
That's right.
Let's get started.
The top batter of the red team is Mr. Monkey.
I'm Kato from the Asai Project.
What are you doing?
Who are you?
You're pathetic.
My ex, my ex, my ex.
Have a love affair.
I'm gonna pull out your nose and hands.
It's gone.
It's awesome.
Of course you're the top batter in terms of height.
Thank you very much.
It must be hard for you guys.
That's a good point.
It's time for you guys to try something.
I will do my best for my wife
Miyasako will do it
And 4000 years
It's hot!
Everyone, come forward!
Da da!
That was good!
While you are the enemy
No, but
I'm not going to lose like this either.
Let's continue with the next team.
Kokoriko Tanaka Naoki!
What's going on?
They've shown us a lot of things.
We can't lose as a team!
We can't lose. We have a lot of power right now.
Let's continue.
Kokoriko Tanaka Naoki's...
Otero De Bungee Gaku Bungee!
Hurry!
More!
I'm scared!
Stop! Stop!
Hurry and stop!
Jump! Jump!
Jump!
Hurry and jump!
Bungee!
Jump!
I'm scared!
No!
Alright!
Thank you!
At first, I thought it was a trick.
Tanaka-san has his own theme.
I understand.
The first team is Jyodanzo!
Jyodanzo!
It's Yutem's first time on this show.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
Can I change my clothes?
Wait, let's do it together.
Why?
Let's do it together.
All of us!
After we do this,
we'll do the jump.
Let's go!
Jyodanzo's last shout in 1998.
Summer Power!
You're the best!
I'm very excited.
I'm very excited!
Thank you!
I see.
Okay, thank you!
That's why we lost.
The secret influence of the red team.
Are you okay?
Let's continue.
The next red team is Ritton Jyodanzo!
Ritton, this is your first time in the studio.
That's right.
You've been out all this time.
And on the phone.
I understand.
That's a self-portrait.
Really?
What kind of self-portrait is that?
It's a pajama for women.
Okay, Ritton Jyodanzo.
Please do the human power rescue!
Human power rescue!
Rescue!
Is it a holiday today?
I feel like I'm going to bump into a police officer in Shikoku.
Curry bread! Curry bread!
Do you have a police officer?
I'm going to marry a girl next door.
I'm in shock right now.
I'm getting a lot of natto.
I found a hot rice.
I'm going to eat it.
I want to eat natto.
I'm going to lay an egg.
Sometimes it's like a shogi.
I want to be a mischievous woman.
I'm going to lay an egg.
If it's funny, it's just the end.
I bit my tongue on the way.
That's because it's cute.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to get cold.
The end.
This is the end.
You're a normal person.
I'm counting on you.
I don't know if I can do it.
I'm going to change my name.
Fujii Takashide
HENPIN 98
Sir.
I'm sorry.
HENPIN 98
Sir.
I can't.
HENPIN 98
HENPIN Vibration
I can't do it.
Cooling-off!
That was good.
I won, didn't I?
You won.
I won.
Yuta, you're always like that at the end.
Finally!
Why is that a bird?
The red bird!
I got it.
Your face is weird.
The red team will finish it off with this.
Let's go.
It's Yamanagi Hosei.
It's a bird.
Whether the red team wins or loses, it's up to me.
Let's do our best!
Well, even if you lose a little bit now, you can make up for it with this bird's effort.
That's right.
Let's do our best.
Let's go.
Red team's bird, Yamanagi Hosei.
The 17th edition of the Prondet Competition.
I was born a small bird.
I was a small bird.
The song is over.
It's the best!
It's the red team's bird.
It was a little dangerous in the middle, so I added it.
What do you mean the bird doesn't know the sushi?
Good! Good! Red team!
Red team!
Good!
It's my bird!
Komori Goen!
It's up to you.
But I've already won here.
The last one is no good.
I added it.
The face is different.
That's right.
It's easy.
The other team was up and up.
That's not true.
It's still the same.
This is my bird.
It's the last one this year.
Komori Goen!
Good!
What are you doing?
One, two, one, two, three.
Do you believe in the Nostradamus?
In 1999, the earth will be destroyed.
That's why I want to go to the forest with you.
So please make me a bento.
Please make me a bento.
Good!
Both of you have the same bird.
I thought it would be no good.
We were surprised, too.
Let's go!
High tension battle!
Please announce the result!
Good!
Hiromu wins!
Next year, I won't lose to anyone.
He is a taxi driver.
Good!
The song came out when it wasn't over yet.
It doesn't matter.
It was a little interesting for me.
This year, the countdown is approaching.
One year is over.
Did you participate?
I don't care about that.
I don't care about this year.
Do you know?
I've been a long-seller for a long time.
But I change the taste every year.
So I don't get bored.
What?
It's a long story.
Why am I compared to ramen?
In your case, you've changed a lot.
I've changed a lot.
Why do you always change the taste every year?
You're like an Ukrainian.
I don't change the taste every year.
You've changed the taste every year.
But you suddenly change the taste every year.
This year's news.
Where are you going this year?
Next year.
I'm going to the Netherlands next year.
Are you going to the Netherlands for an interview?
I was the only one who didn't want to take a plane.
I went to Hokkaido last year.
It's hard in Japan.
Why did you want to take a plane?
I've recently realized that I'm a big guy.
Can't I walk in a big way?
You can't walk.
Please walk.
I want to walk in a big way.
I'm going to the Netherlands.
I see.
I don't care.
I hate Christmas the most.
Why?
It's not a good thing.
If you had a lot of fun last year, would you raise your hand?
I can't.
You can't, can you?
It hurts to be here.
You're being introduced.
It's a little dirty.
What do you call it?
A solid meal.
Don't say that.
What do you call it?
Grilled meat.
Stop it.
I've been booking a hotel for about a year.
You don't do that these days.
But there are still a lot of people.
I've already made a reservation.
What about you?
What?
Why are you making a fuss?
I'm not making a fuss.
Do you celebrate Christmas?
No.
I'm being honest.
I usually work on Christmas.
I do.
Did you come down from the mountain?
You're a bandit, aren't you?
I say it every year.
Merry Christmas.
You said you were going to exchange gifts.
It's a story that ends in five minutes.
What are you doing there?
I don't know if that's strange.
You're persistent.
It's okay if you don't buy it right away.
It's okay to pull it out at the end.
If you don't buy it right away, you'll get into an accident.
It's not good to cause an accident on the highway.
You'll lose your driver's license.
I'll tell you something.
Listen carefully.
When you have an accident in a car,
don't leave the car in the police car.
It's a murder scene.
Stop the car.
You shouldn't leave it like that.
Shut up.
You think so, don't you?
Everyone thinks so.
You should not leave it like that.
You should wear gloves.
You should buy a card.
Are you stupid?
The other day, I turned left after crossing the crossing.
When I was about to turn, he came from behind.
I stopped.
He went in front of my car and hit me on the left side.
In your car?
That's right.
By bicycle?
Yes.
Are you a human being?
No, no, no.
It's obvious that you're a human being.
I stopped.
I don't know if you're really stopped.
You think you're stopped, but you're not.
I stopped.
What happened?
I turned and stopped.
I was waiting for him to come.
I was surprised.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I stopped.
I looked at him, but nothing happened.
Did you hit me?
That's strange.
I'll tell you a good thing.
I'll tell you what's wrong with Japanese drivers.
Don't think that safe driving means slow driving.
You can't say it's safe because you're driving slowly.
For example, be careful not to fall because you're driving slowly.
It may be safer to drive slowly.
It may be safe to drive slowly.
But it's not safe to drive slowly.
I'll tell you a good thing.
I don't understand it at all.
I can say that.
I'm confident that I'll get into an accident in a car for the rest of my life.
I declared it.
You went into the parking lot, turned around, and hit me.
That's a little random.
It's not random.
You went into the parking lot, turned around, and hit me.
There was water on the smooth iron plate.
But you didn't understand the iron plate.
You should get out of the car.
Because you are a fool.
Thank you very much.
You two are the people who drive a luxury car.
Both of you.
Human desire is really amazing.
Please tell me where you have fallen in love with each other.
I can't beat you.
You're a pervert.
I'm not more than a normal person.
I've done this in a double bed.
I can't beat you.
I thought I'd say it one by one.
I thought I'd do it little by little.
Suddenly I was surprised.
There's no next time.
Why?
If you go from Hantoubu, that's what happens to the iron plate at home.
I went to a strange place.
I went to Yoshimoto Shinkei Station.
You're an adult.
I'm in elementary school.
I'm in junior high school.
You're wearing the same suit as me.
I'm in Yoshimoto Shinkei Station, so I'm making my debut.
There was no video or anything like that.
I found it in an erotic book in the back of the gymnasium.
I was naked in Goro's Mizusawaki.
Did you do it?
When we went to the book store together, I didn't think Mizusawaki was naked.
When I saw Goro, he was just a little boy.
We were just little boys.
I remember it well.
Mizusawaki, take it off.
Give me this.
This program was provided by the sponsor you see.