On this day, the member of the kids' group was heading to a certain place with black mayonnaise.
Masamatsu-san, what is this?
Well, Kosugi is wearing damaged jeans, but he's already been damaged enough.
He's not damaged enough to wear jeans.
This is not fashionable.
Well, well.
Everyone, today we have a letter from the mayor of a town factory.
A letter for two people?
I'll read it.
Nice to meet you.
It's a letter from a sudden person. I'm sorry to bother you.
I run a small town factory in Tokyo.
A Moroccan man who works in a residential area recently, Muhammad,
has been homesick.
He hasn't been able to leave his room.
But Muhammad is a big fan of Black Mayonnaise, especially Kosugi.
When he saw the two of you on the show, he got back his energy.
I hope you won't let Muhammad down with your own power.
Why are you here again?
Because there are other shows on Black Mayonnaise.
I heard you were on the show recently.
Yes, I was on the show.
I wonder if you watched it.
I'm not the one who said you should do your best.
It's Ega-chan.
No, no, no. I was the only one who did the first 6 changes.
You can't make a mistake.
Do the 7 changes.
Are you kidding me?
You can't even get the rules right.
It's not me.
I'll tell you.
You can't do it.
That's not true.
The first step is to encourage Muhammad to go out of town.
Oh, isn't this the factory?
Suddenly, the factory appears.
Oh, wow.
Good evening.
Oh, thank you very much.
You're from the same company?
Yes, I am.
I'm Yamashita from the Ministry of Commerce.
Oh, I see.
Nice to meet you.
I heard you're from the same company.
Yes, I am.
I'm from the upper room.
Oh, really?
Yes, I am.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
It's a bit dirty.
Oh, no problem.
Well, excuse me.
Hello.
Please put on your slippers.
Yes, sir.
Please come in.
I live around here.
Here?
You don't come out all the time?
That's right.
I'm not very good at it.
Why don't we try asking him?
That's right.
He'll be happy if we do that.
I'm going to ask him, but...
Let's ask him.
It's easier to come out like this.
Muhammado!
The two of you from the drama world are here!
Ah, there he is.
Ah, Muhammado.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
I'm Black Manez.
I'm Black Manez Kosugi.
I heard that you liked us.
I thought it would be nice if you could help us.
I'm fine.
That's strange.
I can't get a reaction.
It's you, right?
Is it because I was there?
No, no.
It's not like that.
But it's a Brahma 4.
I saw it with my eyes that there was nothing in it.
From the back.
I saw it with my eyes that it was black.
I can't help it if you laugh.
Why don't you do it like you always do on TV?
Put in a switch and throw it.
Make it look like a funny party.
Hey, Hagio-dori.
What?
Hagio-dori.
What's with the sudden change?
You're not feeling well, right?
You're worried about me.
What are you talking about?
I'm thinking about my feelings.
I don't care about your feelings.
I'm not doing this to make you popular.
Who are you doing this for?
For Mugamage.
I'll bring him here.
Excuse me.
No, no.
It's okay.
Excuse me.
You can't just come in like that.
It's fine.
What's with him all of a sudden?
Right?
Well, Kosei-kun really...
He's been working since he was a kid.
Oh, okay.
Oh, oh, oh.
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
The sound is coming from the radio.
Muhammad, your beloved Cosumi-san will do something for you.
Oh, here it comes.
Hageodori! Hageodori!
Tetsuougei no hageodori!
Not at all.
You were laughing?
No, no.
I thought you'd laugh when I opened the door.
But I thought, well, I guess I was right.
And you started dancing, no doubt.
I'm angry.
What's with that hageodori?
What?
It's clearly fire troubling me.
No, I'm having all the fun.
Fire again are you?
Yeah. I do.
You think you can take all day without dancing once?
You got to watch the sound.
This is all a mistake, period.
How dare you moisurge me!
What was that?
Not a problem.
What made you make so much noise there?
An occurred scene.
I am having fun.
Beat it!
Hey!
You've lost tough inside.
What chunk of wood is sticking?
What a shame!
What the hell?
You're not supposed to touch my body!
Don't touch it!
This is not a good idea.
Why are you fighting?
Wait, wait, wait.
This is not good.
Muhammad is...
You're scaring me.
Who is it?
Muhammad.
I'm not going to do it.
Who do you think it is?
Stop it.
Stop fighting.
If you keep asking questions like that, I won't be able to finish it.
You are definitely more...
I thought you were more beautiful.
I'm not beautiful at all.
You're not beautiful.
Are you doing it?
The Eurobeat version.
You're 10 years too early to judge if it's slippery.
What are you trying to do?
You're not even a bit different from me.
If you're not even a bit different from me, you're a bit over the top.
Be careful.
You can still say, what if I do it?
Why don't you say, do it?
What if I do it?
My friends said it was fun.
Eurobeat version.
Really?
Who's that?
What's up?
What's up, Madoh?
I heard that Mr. Kosugi will do something for us again.
The last one is the last one.
It's over.
It's a really good place.
It's good.
Don't give up.
It's coming out.
What the hell?
I'm already tired.
It's coming, it's coming.
Hey.
You've been dancing for yourself since the beginning.
What?
I saw you were going to get a lot of likes.
Are you still saying that?
What's with that way of saying it?
You don't have the right to say that!
What?
Excuse me, can I talk to you for a moment?
You don't have the right to say that!
What?
I don't know what's going on, but I'm always in a bad mood when I dance.
Are you jealous?
Do it!
I don't know if I'm jealous, but I'm always told that I can't do it.
I'm trying to do my best, but if you look at me from above and see that I'm trying, it's harder to dance.
You're a con man!
Why are you talking to me like that?
I don't understand!
Try to understand!
Just dance once!
If you win, dance!
I can't dance!
You can't appear on TV because I'm naked!
You're so young!
What's wrong with you?
Stop it!
Why do you keep making trouble?
Let's be friends.
Let's have fun.
I'll do it a little bit more.
You don't know.
It's a little bit more.
You guys do it.
It's impossible.
You are doing it on a TV show, so you don't know if you don't do it properly.
Fukuwajitsu.
Can you do it?
You said that you could do Fukuwajitsu.
Why can't I do Fukuwajitsu?
So, you're going to break it?
You're going to do the same thing you did when you were a kid?
What are you so obsessed with?
I've never laughed at a bald man.
Let me try.
I have a doll.
What?
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Kozuki's got a
Really?
It's so big.
I've never seen this before.
I didn't know you could do this.
Muhammado, Kosugi-san will do something for you.
Come on out.
This is difficult.
He's a beginner.
Hello, Muhammado.
Today I'll introduce my friend.
Taro, introduce yourself.
Hello. I'm Toramu.
You're always sleeping.
There's a baritone snake over there.
Who's a baritone snake?
It's hiding in the room.
It's hiding in the room, so...
Why is it hiding in the room? Let's go cut it.
That's right! You should have listened to me directly!
Hey, Masa-kun!
Why didn't you leave the room?
I was stuck in there for a year!
The one who brought me out of there was the world of Fukuwajitsu!
Hey, can you stop saying that?
Your life as a fukkaku might be our own.
That's enough!
If you come back, I'll be a fukkaku doll!
What?
Oh, man.
I was just about to go to the bathroom, but I got a little angry.
I don't think you need a helicopter match now.
What?
I heard the sound of a helicopter.
Do you think there are people like that now?
Hey, I'll put this on. If you don't want to turn it, it's useless.
Why are you waiting for the helicopter with your judgement?
Just now, in the bus, you were playing with the damaged jeans of Mr. Matsumoto.
When I tried to face the camera, you said you didn't need it.
Learn from there.
What?
The way you learned to shoot in the morning, you don't need it here.
Why are you making him say that?
Because you don't know.
I don't know!
What the hell are you talking about?
Nothing is better than me!
Nothing is better than you!
You don't know anything!
I don't care what you did or what you got done!
I only taught you how to do Kagami Junsa at the event!
If it's not enough, then do more!
You can't do it all at once!
I only did it once at the event!
I didn't know you were going to do it.
You only did the Ironton Senna thing, right?
That was funny.
What?
No one did that.
What's with the Ironton Senna? Don't be so cocky.
I'm not cocky. You're always a little bit cocky.
You don't have any love.
What?
You don't have any kind words.
You're just pressuring me.
I don't understand.
If I talk to you, my brain will go crazy.
What are you talking about?
Try to understand!
You can't do anything because you're doing something you can't even do a single GEP!
I'm doing GEP!
If your GEP was a Sakuya stage, I wouldn't be doing this!
You're the one who saw me get into trouble with GEP!
Why are you saying that here?
I'm really sorry.
It's probably because of the times.
It's a big deal.
You should show your ass in front of your wife!
You can't do that!
I can't do it.
Show your ass!
Who's the unlucky guy?
Don't call me unlucky!
Show your ass!
I can't do it.
I took off my underwear.
Hey, Anmado! Yoshida-san is coming to see you!
Come out!
Odamazu-kun.
I know you're lonely.
I don't know if you want to see your father.
But I think you should think of your teacher as your father.
And what is the most scary thing about your parents?
You're talking so nicely.
I think you're most afraid of not working in Japan.
What's the problem?
Speak clearly.
So your father...
Hurry up and give me a break! What are you doing?
I can't do it!
You're talking about the body of a leech!
Why do you want to get a cold from your cheeks?
Let me see your cheeks!
You shouldn't mess with my cheeks when I'm depressed because of my body.
You shouldn't have two complexes at once.
Why?
Why don't you just do it?
I told you to get the shoe that you gave me.
That light one?
That's the one.
Why don't you get it?
Why can't you get it?
Well...
Okay, okay, okay.
That's enough.
That's enough?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, no, I can't.
You can.
I can't take it anymore.
I don't know what to do. I have to get this out.
Just do it.
That's right.
Sing.
You're the only one who can sing.
If you say that, it'll be hard to sing.
Are you trying to crush me?
I know I'm always in your way.
When I hear your high ratings, I know I'm always in your way.
But I'm not a man who would pull you down and try to make you fall.
Believe me.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Is something wrong?
The rice cooker's assistant will do something interesting this time.
Yes, yes.
Excuse me.
Sure.
How about a song about a mother who's worried because her child is homesick?
Oh, that's good.
What is it?
It's good.
My baby, are you crying?
I want to hold you.
I want to wash your baby's shoulder, baby
I want to cook your dinner
I want to wash your pajamas
Baby-chan! Baby-chan!
What will happen if I put my sleeves through your pants?
It's almost there.
It's almost time to cook dinner!
Baby-chan!
You're so oppressive!
Hurry up and take another look!
Baby-chan!
The time of the ring is approaching!
Mom loves Dad!
Baby-
Ah!
One more step!
That was close!
I almost fell.
That was close.
I don't know why.
You stepped into Muhammad's family too much.
I didn't step into his family.
I became his family.
You were washing your pajamas.
If your mother washes them, they'll get even dirtier.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, my father...
You should have sung!
Why did you do that?
What?
When I was...
Yeah?
...working on the 7th edition...
...I was doing something else...
Yeah?
...and you called me a fool!
What are you talking about?
I was singing my best and you called me a fool!
You're a f***ing a**hole!
Stop it!
Stop that!
Stop it! Stop it!
Let's go home!
Is it impossible?
It's impossible.
I want to save Muhammado-kun.
Even if he tries to persuade her with such pure feelings, her feelings won't reach him.
Can he not break the barrier in his heart?
No way. I'll do the hakeodori one more time.
You're going to do the hakeodori?
Yes. I brought a hakeodori that's easy to dance.
Really?
Yes.
I'm not good at dancing with my hair up.
Really?
I've never seen a man who dances so easily.
Yes.
Please come out, the dining room.
You can't dance!
Why are you so popular?
You have the answer!
You can't dance?
You're a big ass.
You're a big ass!
You have that kind of thing?
You say such bad things sometimes!
You idiot!
What the hell are you doing?