Well, I guess it will fly.
It's a strong tree.
Well, it's a celebration of the 5th anniversary.
Many famous people have sent us flowers.
Thank you very much.
That's right.
I also received it from overseas.
From Michael Jackson.
I also received it from Starono.
It says Starono over there.
Well, it's nostalgic.
Maybe his face is young.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's been 5 years since the 5th anniversary.
Let's start from the age of 20.
Let's take a look at this.
Well, I heard it the day before yesterday.
Is that so?
Hey, watching the Golden program,
It was decided the day before yesterday.
That's what it was like.
That's what it is.
In the world of TV.
When the world of TV is decided, it will be decided quickly.
Do you edit it like this?
Yeah.
The history of Japanese entertainment history.
The first page started with this kind of talk.
But Kohaku was amazing.
Yeah.
I wonder which one won.
What?
People who watch TV know.
Let's bet.
What?
Which one won?
I'll go first.
Red wins.
I'm white.
Yeah.
If I lose,
I'll be like this behind the zoom-in in the morning.
I'll be dressed like this.
I don't think it's funny.
You're that.
It's a little different song.
It's a refreshing morning.
Good morning.
It's Wednesday, January 17th.
The first thing in the morning is to go to Shizuoka.
Zoom-in.
The number of people who went to Shizuoka is 146, and 154 people were injured.
It looks like a strange person is coming from the morning.
It seems that you will be able to fly to the scene somehow by wrapping the anti-fog material around the runway.
I feel like it's going to work well.
I think I can fly today.
However, if you go into the shade, it will slip, so I would like you to be careful.
Let's zoom in on the smile of the Nippon Red Orchestra.
I'm a sharp-tongued person, and I can return anything with vinegar.
Watermelon.
Crab.
Shiasu.
Yuta.
The Shiasu I mentioned earlier is the Shiasu of the day before yesterday.
It doesn't matter.
I'm going to lose.
The end.
Wait a minute.
Don't eat it.
It hurts.
It's noisy.
First of all.
daí
for
40 always
Gaki no Tsukai
Well uh
Rlook
voodoo
All the stars of the world ranked Eric
I'm going to Paris.
What about you?
Yeah, right.
Don't just stand there.
Hey!
Give me a double.
This is it!
I'm ready.
Let's go.
What?
It's 3500rpm now.
3500rpm.
It's almost there.
Can they land safely with both feet?
The landing is the problem.
It's raining!
I can't express it in words.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
Please come again.
I'm very moved.
Thank you very much.
Did you see that?
Hmm?
Never mind.
playing
Hello, hello, hello.
Hello.
Are you Sanyo-san?
Come in.
If I open it, the real Sanyo-san is inside.
You idiot.
I'm going to say something stupid.
Come back.
It's okay. I'm still doing it.
Who did this when you first did Sanyo-san's makeup?
I'm sorry.
Welcome.
I love the beat.
I'm sorry.
Welcome.
Let's start the game.
He throws the ball.
There are brave men.
Look over there.
They are just idiots.
Look at that rough wave.
From now on, you will go to that rough wave.
Okay?
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
My body hurts.
I'm scared.
Bring it.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Don't lose to that rotten Hamada.
The game has started.
Nagachoba has 30 minutes.
He passes the ball.
Look at this.
Go, Hamada.
I can't take it anymore.
It's 40 meters.
It's so high.
I'm scared.
This is the scariest game.
It's so scary.
We have all the players for the 42nd NHK.
I'm writing them down.
I think Shiro is the best.
I think Akai is the best.
Shiro is the best.
15 seconds left.
10 seconds left.
5 seconds left.
4, 3, 2, 1.
I'm the best.
I'm the American Kid.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Hamada.
I'm going to introduce you to my friend, Hii.
Hii, come on.
Stand up.
Hii, he's your friend.
Say hi to him.
Hii.
This is the 40th episode of 1989.
I'm Shiro.
I'm the best.
Am I stupid?
I'm...
It's pretty long.
Am I stupid?
This is my first job this year.
This is J-O-A-X-T-V Channel 4.
This is Japan TV.
This is Hayami's American Kid.
Watch it.
Hi, everybody.
Am I...
Am I stupid?
Hello.
I'm glad you invited me to come to Yoshimoto.
Matsumoto is running out of patience.
I want to clear this in one go.
Nice jump.
It's a jump of fate.
He jumped into the water.
But he failed.
What's wrong?
I want to jump into the water.
Hamada has left Japan.
He's on his way to Mont-Moulin-Saint-Germain.
I don't think I need to drink water here.
Excuse me.
There's no water here.
There's a waterfall down there.
We're going to build it there.
Am I stupid?
What's wrong with you?
There it is.
Let me introduce you to the shrimp.
You're annoying.
The sparkling water is now pouring into the bottle.
I got it.
Congratulations, Hamada.
His dream has finally come true.
It's going to be a relaxing trip.
What about Evian?
It's a town.
I didn't say anything.
The water of the Alps is the water of the Alps.
The water of the Alps came out of Evian.
That's why it's called Evian.
If you come to Evian, there's no Evian.
That's right.
It's out there?
If you get off the plane and come here, you'll get hit.
It's a punishment.
The sparkling water is now pouring into the bottle.
I got it.
It's true.
Congratulations.
The dream has finally come true.
What is it?
Are you in pain?
I'm fine.
Fukuyama.
Fukuyama Masahara.
Checkers last year.
Thank you very much.
Hello.
It's me.
Were you sleeping?
Listen to my mother's cry.
Then look at the life of the parents and children.
It's been a long time.
It's dangerous, but it's fun.
Where are you?
You have a son who is in the second grade of elementary school, right?
I have a sixth grader.
How did you do that?
I'm embarrassed.
It's not funny.
Bring me some money.
I'm the second son of Masumoto.
I'm the second son of Shioe.
What are you going to do with your own family?
Thank you very much.
Let's do our best next year.
Let me think about it next year.
It's a battle and punishment game that made a lot of headlines last year.
In addition to that, there is also a famous project that challenged such a thing.
What are you thinking about now?
I'm thinking about the costume of Kin-chan.
I'm nervous.
Good evening.
Nice to meet you.
I'm number 67, Hitoshi Matsumoto.
The title is Chameleon.
Thank you very much.
I'm lost.
Come on.
Thank you very much.
I will announce the result.
I'm going to make up for the loss I made last time.
I'm sorry.
I did my best.
Please give me a high score.
I'm the captain of the costume of Kin-chan.
Thank you very much for accepting the application the other day.
Thank you very much.
I will announce the result.
Is that so?
Thank you very much.
Where are you going?
How did you do it?
Don't laugh.
Everyone wants to know how you did it.
What is the result of the costume?
I will tell you the result.
This time, our costume is a success.
This is the last work.
Let's get started.
You look very nervous.
I'm nervous.
This is a terrible work.
Let's go.
No. 40, pass line.
How did it go?
How many points did the judges give?
I'm sorry.
Please give me a high score.
Are you doing it alone?
Yes.
Please give me a high score.
You can't go down.
Congratulations.
You passed, but you can't win.
You want to win, right?
Please give me a high score.
Why are you looking up?
Please.
You passed.
Please give me a high score.
Hello.
I'm ready.
Start.
Ready.
Hurry up.
I don't know where to go.
In the back.
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
This is a train.
Ready.
Start.
Standby.
This is funny.
Please give me a high score.
The first two to listen to the song prepared by Mr. Sakamoto.
The lyrics are about two high-tension manzai.
The day of the New York live debut has finally come.
What is the reaction of the New Yorkers?