Ladies and gentlemen...
After 24 hours...
It looks like it's going to break today.
After 24 hours of TV, this program is over.
That's how it is.
24 hours was hard, wasn't it?
You were crying.
Oh, really?
It's that time of the year?
It's that time of the year.
It's that time of the year, isn't it?
The titans...
Yes, yes, the titans.
...became fans.
What did you say?
What?
You're not interested in baseball?
No, I'm not.
What do you like?
I used to like Chunichi.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Now you like Chunichi.
I like Chunichi.
When I was in elementary school, if there wasn't a club I liked,
I wouldn't be able to play against them.
Well, everyone likes baseball.
That's right.
So I forced myself to like Chunichi.
You're wearing Chunichi's hat while saying that.
Yes, yes, yes.
I kept saying that I liked him.
And then...
After I left school, Shakutani transferred to my school.
That's good.
I had to apologize for that.
Why?
It doesn't matter.
But there was a player called Matsumoto.
Matsumoto Rukitsura.
I really liked how he threw the ball at a very fast pace.
That's the only thing I remember.
It was amazing.
So there's a catcher, right?
If you throw it and there's a ball, it goes straight to the next one.
It was really amazing.
You should have thrown it slower with the catch ball.
Why?
That's what I thought.
It's a batter, right?
No, it's not a batter.
I liked him, but he's gone somewhere.
Oh, really?
He's not here, is he?
He's not here.
Maybe he was here in the past.
No, he was here.
I'm worried.
What's wrong with my brain?
That's right.
Well, baseball is...
Well, I think baseball is...
Well, if you like baseball, you can like it.
You always play baseball, right?
That's right.
Well, it's usually until 9 o'clock.
It's 9 o'clock.
It's already 9 o'clock.
You should have started 30 minutes earlier.
So I'm making a reservation, but I don't want to see it.
Stop that.
No, no, no.
That's...
It's really annoying.
I rarely do that.
But when I come back after making a reservation, I don't want to see it.
I can't help it.
I often hear that kind of story.
I've been doing it since 9 o'clock.
It's been about two and a half hours.
If that's the case, you should have decided that the picture would end at 9 o'clock.
No matter how many times you do it.
Then you can get a lucky face again.
Because it's early.
I don't have a lucky face.
I'm sorry.
I didn't listen to you.
Right?
Don't you have any lucky faces?
Well, I don't care.
I don't care.
It's a broadcast situation.
That kind of show will be a big deal.
It's not a big deal.
It's about 30 minutes.
No, no, no.
So I want to make the late-night show one minute and one second faster.
But I'm doing it because I can only get a good picture.
Why is it a roll situation?
It's a roll situation.
Right?
That's the only show I can do.
That's why I'm broadcasting there.
If I can't do it in Golden, I'll do it from the beginning.
Huh?
All right, all right.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to ask you.
If you think so, switch on.
Wait a minute.
There's nothing on the page.
The atmosphere, the atmosphere.
I'm looking at the movement here.
I don't know if you're going to do it or not.
No, no, no.
That's not right.
That's funny.
I want to see it.
If you say you're going to extend the Aikyu broadcast as it is.
I think that's right.
I don't think so.
What are you going to do when it's over at a place like this?
What kind of place is this?
What's that?
I can't see Nagashima.
If that's the case, I'll do it a little more.
Nagashima.
Why don't you show Nagashima?
Nagashima is like this.
Wait a minute.
If you say it's over at 6 o'clock.
I'll call you.
What kind of sign is that?
Hey.
What kind of sign is it at 2 out of 10,000?
It's not similar.
Other than that.
I'm imitating Keisuke Kuwata right now.
I've been doing it for a while, but it doesn't look like it.
Why is Keisuke Kuwata Keisuke?
Right now.
It's halfway through, isn't it?
Like Sen Masao.
Right now.
Baah.
It's like a croquette.
What kind of sign is that?
You can't do it at all, can you?
I can't.
Why?
My partner is doing this much.
We're eating the same amount of food.
Why can't you do it?
I can't.
Why?
You can't do anything, can you?
I can't.
You can't do it at all, can you?
Do it again.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You really can't do it, can you?
What's number 18?
Yumi.
That's the first time I've heard it.
I can't do it at all.
Next.
And Chuck.
Huh?
Chuck, Chuck.
Can you do that?
I can't do that.
San-san.
Can you do that?
I can't do that.
Do something.
Teach me.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm an impersonator teacher.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Yumi-san.
You're like a CD player.
I think it's better to be a cool guy.
Let's go with the red sun.
The red sun?
Peperoncino is here.
Me?
Of course.
Who is it?
You told me.
I've been talking to you all the time.
Since the first broadcast.
Since before that.
What's Peperon?
Peperoncino is here.
Have you ever seen a show?
Excuse me.
Wait a minute.
You're late.
No.
I thought you were in the show.
Peperoncino is here.
You should have seen the situation.
You're one step late.
What did you do?
Peperoncino is here.
Okay, I got it.
Who are you?
Like this.
It's cold.
Peperoncino is here.
Who are you?
Is this okay?
I'm sorry.
I'll pay you back.
Matsumoto is the most famous fortune teller in the world.
Yes.
What is your profession?
I don't know my past life.
Have you ever done fortune telling?
Of course.
Before that?
Yes.
Tell me.
Me and Matsumoto.
I don't think you should ask.
It's dangerous.
Is it dangerous?
I don't care if it's dangerous.
I don't like it.
I'm depressed.
Are you depressed?
Tell me.
I knew you were doing that.
What?
Wait a minute.
You shouldn't have done that.
You knew that.
I knew it a long time ago.
Everyone knows my staff.
You're not here.
But you have a good atmosphere.
Tell me.
I don't care if I'm depressed.
Okay.
Don't be surprised.
Don't hate me.
I'm a bright red winner.
I'm very depressed.
I don't eat.
I used to be told that you were a familiar in your previous life.
That was before that.
Before that, I used to put eggs in the refrigerator.
I shouldn't have said that.
That's the whole story.
I was doing that for the first few episodes.
But the winner is the third one.
The third one?
The middle one.
There are four below.
That was tough.
I'm sorry.
Who are you?
If I were a winner.
I used to say that I was a regent.
That's cool.
Where are you from?
Why are you doing this on someone's head?
That's enough.
I have a question for Mr. Matsumoto.
When I'm singing in karaoke,
but no one is listening to me,
what should I do to make them listen to me?
That's a good question.
When I'm singing in karaoke,
I can only see the people who are singing.
I can only see the people who are not singing.
It's not that sad.
That's true.
It's a matter of persuasion.
For example, what should I sing?
I'm praying.
You're praying?
How many times are you going to sing?
I can't think of anything.
That's fine.
What was it again?
I'm embarrassed.
It's because you're a regent.
Be careful of your health.
Seriously?
You're praying?
But the song is still going on.
It's okay.
It's okay to be late.
Be careful of your health.
Seriously?
Don't drink too much.
This song was good.
I'm glad I sang this song.