After this, it's time for the 6th episode of Gaki no Tsukai!
The 6th episode of Gaki no Tsukai!
The 200th anniversary of Tsukiji!
Oogiri Daigassen!
Today is the 200th anniversary of Oogiri Daigassen,
and we have one more guest.
The host is me, Hamada Masatoshi.
Now, let's have the talkers come up to the stage.
Please introduce yourself.
I will never lose in a fight! I'm Yamasaki.
Nice to meet you.
Next to you, please.
What's your name?
I'm Jibin Onishi.
Today, when I got on the train,
a passenger on the train put gum on my head.
Didn't you say anything?
I thought, what the hell is he doing?
But I bit him.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Next to you, please.
Today, I went to the cultural festival of Seijo Gakuen,
and there was a guy who said,
I know, I know, I was written by Noriyasu.
You did it?
Yes, I did.
Next to you, please.
What?
Hey!
What's going on?
We've been thinking about it for a long time.
First of all, the Dengon Game!
Everyone, please put on your headphones.
I'm going to make a lot of noise.
I'm going to say the words that I have in order.
Please say them in order.
First of all, the first topic is...
Here!
You got it, right?
Yes.
I'm sorry, Ramos.
I'm a foreigner, Ramos.
Don't move your mouth!
You got it, right?
No, I don't.
Can you hear me?
I'm a foreigner, Ramos.
That's enough.
What?
Let's move on to the next topic.
The next topic is...
Read the Atakamo!
Here is a book.
Yes.
Atakamo.
I hope you can read it as if you were writing it.
Yes.
Please read it.
The first topic is...
My long-distance love story.
Let's go.
When I was in middle school,
I was surrounded by everyone.
Because of that,
my beloved Michiko
was trapped.
I went to help her,
and I was surrounded.
But I managed to escape.
Don't make me laugh.
Here you are.
I asked her,
What is that?
I was surrounded.
I asked her,
Do you understand?
Yes.
She was a child of Hamamatsu.
I told her,
Hey,
are you...
My love...
Did you say something bad?
I went to help her.
I didn't say anything bad.
I said I went to help her.
She was saved because she was convinced.
Why were you convinced?
That's too easy.
I'll make it easy.
That's what happened.
I can't do it.
What should I do?
Let's go to the second question.
Let's change seats.
Yamazaki-san and Oni-san.
The second question.
Here you are.
Ogasawara-ryu date-jitsu.
When you go on a date,
you do this and that.
This is how you do it.
Let's read it.
Miyuki...
Well, well, well.
I'm doing it for you.
Miyuki...
One foot first.
Go to Ogasawara-ryu.
Read this book.
I got it.
The way to fall in love with Ogasawara-ryu is written here.
That's right.
First of all, kiss.
Good.
That's what it is.
This is called A.
And then...
Well, various things.
Well, neckline.
Well, it's going to be.
I don't like them.
It's difficult.
It's going to be.
But more important than that.
If you write it, it's...
Mood.
Equal.
Place.
I see. That's what it is.
That's what it is.
Yes.
There is a place to bring on a date.
One is a coffee shop.
And the other is a park.
The spring park is...
Peaceful.
After that, a boat came out.
Three birds.
At the edge of the pond.
As if they were looking at us.
Embarrassed.
I was taking a walk.
What?
I got it.
When we were looking at the birds.
We were too immersed in the pond.
We're both wet and naked.
It's cold, isn't it?
That's right.
There was a hut.
It's like a novel.
What's wrong with me?
The air of love is flowing.
I don't have a normal edge.
I'm Ogasahara Ryu.
I used three flowers.
One is kiku.
The second is tulip.
The third is rindou.
How do you use it?
First, I put her on the bed.
In rindou.
She...
Like this.
The two of them...
As they are.
They look like flowers.
What are you doing?
They look like flowers?
What kind of flowers?
And then the two of them...
They closed their eyes quietly.
What?
Goodbye.
I'm sure there's no one like this.
Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen.
You look good today.
What are you doing today?
There's a special occasion.
There's nothing.
Today's lunch is katsu-don.
Oh, really?
Thank you very much.
There's no such thing.
There's no flower.
I don't know.
After it's over.
When I go back to the dressing room.
There must be something.
There's no sign of that.
But that's how it is.
I haven't changed at all.
You've gotten stronger and stronger...
Why?
As a souvenir for the second time.
I thought I'd say that to you.
Why did you say I'm great?
I wanted to say it off the top of my head.
I wore a tie too.
No, it's always that way.
You've changed a lot since the show began, right?
I haven't changed.
I haven't changed at all.
I've changed.
I really haven't changed since my debut.
No, that's not true.
I haven't changed at all!
No, no, no, no.
If your attitude is good, I don't think there's anyone on your right.
In the entertainment world, it's either Yuji Oda or you.
No, it's...
Young people also hate each other, right?
What do you mean?
Well, I'm not sure what to say myself, but we're pretty popular, aren't we?
And there are a lot of young comedians these days.
They have their own followers.
Yes, there are.
Right?
I get angry when I see it.
When I see it, I say,
I'll pull it out now.
I don't say it out loud.
I want you to stop it.
When I was a kid,
Where was it?
Sun Mall.
When I went down the stairs of Sun Mall,
I was called Shetsu.
It means forever.
It's Shetsu.
I was called Shetsu.
Did you say that to me?
Is there such a thing?
If you're my fan,
I can't help it.
Why?
Well, that's what it is.
I don't like young people chasing me.
I'm really angry.
That young man in Osaka is amazing.
Even if I'm walking around,
I'm screaming.
It's so annoying.
I'm Hamachan.
Soccer was good, wasn't it?
What do you mean?
I hate it.
I was going to watch it to the end.
I was like,
I did it!
I jumped up.
How was it?
Everyone was disappointed.
You know what?
It's the preliminary round.
Don't you all forget that?
If you didn't make it to the final,
you wouldn't have made it to the main round.
Look, it's a comic book competition.
What are you talking about?
But we all feel the same way.
The preliminary round is amazing.
The comic book is...
Even if you make it to the preliminary round,
you can't be proud of yourself.
But it's a small town.
It's Osaka.
You...
Where are you going?
What's the point of the preliminary round?
What's the point?
When you fight for the championship in the main round,
everyone gets excited.
I know that.
But in the preliminary round in Asia,
you have to fight so many fights.
How many fights are there?
There aren't that many.
Iraq, Iran, Korea...
What is it?
There aren't that many.
And to win...
There were so many in my time.
There was Tomizu.
There was High Heel.
There was also Ginji Seiji.
There are so many.
When I was in high school baseball,
when I was in high school,
I would cry and cheer for them.
I told them to cheer for me like that.
When I was in the preliminary round,
when everyone was practicing hard after school,
I would say,
bye bye.
Then I would say,
I miss you.
I know that.
But I don't know the rules.
I don't care if you get angry at me.
That's your fault.
What is offside?
It's scary.
I don't know at all.
It's not scary.
When you say offside,
I'm like, what?
I get excited.
And the old man,
he's like this.
He's like this.
It's hard to move.
It's like a character.
It's like a woman is being hooked.
What's that?
What's the big mole on Hamada's neck?
This?
What's good about Hamada?
There's nothing good about him.
For example,
if you hit him with a highjack,
the mole on his neck will break.
That's not good.
Why is there a mole on my neck?
What's that?
It's like Nacchan.
It's scary.
Why?
There's nothing good about him.
There's nothing good about him,
but he's like Hifupyo.
There's nothing good about him.
The audience is going crazy.
What did you say?
She's going to cry.
What?
It's quiet.
That's your idea.
You should laugh.
Why are you serious when you talk about your girlfriend?
Nacchan is hiding that he graduated from Harvard University.
Hey.
Don't talk to me.
This is really funny.
What?
If I say that,
I can't say anything.
She's going to cry.
It's the second time.
Who is that little man on Nacchan's right shoulder?
He's drawing a picture.
He's an old man.
He's small.
But everyone says that.
Like Shigorei.
Shigorei.
Everyone says that.
But I'm not Shigorei.
I'm an old man.
How old are you?
Are you that old?
What?
What do you mean by that?
Are you this old?
No, I'm not that old.
I'm this old.
Right now, I'm at the top of my head.
I'm sorry.
Your glasses will move.
I'll do it myself.
Did you do this?
Don't do that.
Well, well.
Get out of here.
My house has been in trouble for about three years.
When I went to the police for help, they said it was stolen from the outside.
They said that if you dig in the house, it won't be stolen.
I really want to catch this thief.
What should I do?
But if they say that, you can't help it.
That's why I did it when I was in middle school.
What?
You stole my underwear?
I don't know.
We met together, right?
Leader.
Leader?
You always come to ask me out at night.
You said, let's go.
So I went to look for you.
You're really dirty.
Am I really dirty?
When I was in elementary school.
I'll tell you our failure at that time.
So I went to Kawata's house.
You have a dog.
That's right.
Kawata had a dog.
There was a dog under the bed.
Yes.
I don't like this dog.
He was in the way and I couldn't catch him.
I like dogs.
But I wanted to kill the dog of Kawata.
Don't call me Kawata.
At that time.
You should have prepared a fishing rod.
It's like this.
Like this.
You put it on like this.
You think I'm lying, don't you?
No, it's true.
You two took it like this.
I'll do it now.