In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Ara, Tsukitsuki, Dajare-yo, Gorou no Uchi wo Uchimakase!
Hello
Good evening
Today's opening is Dajare-yo, Gorou no Uchi wo Uchimakase
Why is everyone smiling like that?
First, let's introduce the challengers
The challengers are here!
Please sit down
Yes, that's it
Let's introduce them
First, Murakami Shoji-san!
Nice to meet you
You're confident in winning, right?
Yes, but I'm also confident in losing
And next to him, Dave Spector-san!
Hello
I want to do my best as the American version of Wada Ben
American version of Wada Ben?
What about Dajare-yo?
I don't like Dajare kidnappers
Why don't you say it?
I don't care, but what is this jacket?
What is this?
I'm going to say it, but I think it cost 10,000 yen at Shinjuku Pepe
10,000 yen?
And last but not least, Matsumoto Hisa-san!
I'm not very good at Dajare
I don't like it!
If I say Dajare, will you look at me with a normal face?
It's like a king
Let's have this person challenge
Is it a king?
Dajare-yo!
Please give it up!
When did I start?
We've been watching TV for a long time
Dajare has been on many TV shows
It's wonderful!
Today is the king's seat
The chair here is a change
Maybe the chair will sit here
Is it okay to say that you're happy?
For now, Goro-san
But the seat is good
It's good, right? It's expensive
It's already in
It's already in!
The seat is good!
I didn't notice! I'm sorry!
Dajare-yo!
There are points and themes
You have the right to choose one by one
If you choose one, you can say it one by one
If someone chooses 20 points, can I eat it?
That's right
After the three of you finish Dajare
The king will say a word
The person who says Dajare closer to the king gets one point
Close
I don't know the criteria
That's right
The king isn't wearing it right now
It's already in!
Let's start with Shoji-san
Please choose
Let's aim for a high score
Animal number 10
That's right
You have a high score
I'm scared, it's difficult
Animal number 10
Let's go
Elephant
I'll go with elephant
Who are you?
What?
It's elephant, not Dajare
I don't think I can say it
I got it!
It's elephant, not Dajare
I see
Where do you want to bite?
It's elephant, not Dajare
Who said it's because it's a gag?
You have to add elephant?
Of course
What's the theme?
Let's go with this
Elephant has a long nose
It's all a gag
What is the most popular food for an elephant?
It's elephant
It's better for this person
I think it's difficult
For example, when you're angry
You can't say it as a pro
I can't say it
That's why I want to add it
I'll give you this
Give me that
That's all
Please say something
It's an animal
It's easy
It's not elephant
It's elephant
I got it!
Thank you
Please choose the theme
Let's go with 30
30 for talent
It's Izumi Pinko
It's Izumi Mito
You're making it up
Shomi
It's Asadachi Pinko
It's Izumi
It's Pinko
It's Izumi Pinko
I'll do my best
Please say something
I got it
This is difficult
If you're a man, do it like a man
Do it like a man?
That's all
Please choose the theme
Last one
I'll give you 20
I can't see
What is it?
Put your feet in
But if you look at it from the bottom, the feet are flat
Do you understand?
The feet are flat
I see
Put your feet in
0 or 100
You're making a joke
Who said Ayu-e Osamu?
Please say something
I'll sing
Put your feet in
Shoji wins
The final round
I'm sorry
That's good
Otokoro
This brush is wonderful
I've been watching you since the time of KAKKURAGI
This is it
I don't like this kind of ear cleaning
Otokoro
I have a futon
That's good
Otokoro
I don't know soap
That's good
It's not good
Goro
Look at this mirror
That's good
As expected
Goro
Do you want to do it again?
That's good
I got it
Ryu writer
I'll do it as it is
I'll do this
Kebukamu
I hate it
10 times Goya
As expected, the champion is Goro
What is this?
Light bulb
I don't know
Ladies and gentlemen
Thank you
This is
What is this?
This is the best way to start the show
Is this the first time?
What are you talking about?
That means
It stinks
It smells
It's the new year
How many hours after the show ended?
6 hours
6 hours?
After 6 hours, there will be a punishment game
The people who are watching this show know which one is the light bulb
We don't know at this point
When that is decided
Hamada
Hamachan's punishment game
That's right
Everyone, please watch
I don't know which one is the light bulb
I don't know
You can't do it today
Last year
At the end of the year
The last bird was around this time
100 is a bit heavy
They are always smiling
No, no, no
I felt bad when I came out
No, this is
To be honest
Hamada and Matsumoto are doing downtown
When I came out
The audience
When there are a lot of Hamada fans
There are a lot of Matsumoto fans
It doesn't matter
It's not good at all
When there are a lot of Hamada fans
I don't like it
I'm not happy
I expect Hamada's punch more than my punch
What do you expect
Why did I notice that
When I came out
I punched him to make sure
At that time
Hamada is a Hamada person
Why do you decide
Because he is a Hamada person
So when my punch came out
No
I'm not saying that
I was laughing when I was punched
But this
No
If Hamada comes out
I will
This audience
It's disgusting
What are you doing
It's like an opera
This audience is different
This audience is different?
This audience came to listen to the conversation
It doesn't matter if you come out
It doesn't matter
If you come to listen to the conversation
You laugh
It doesn't matter
The audience of Gaki
It's different
From the normal audience
Even if you show it on other shows
I think it's just the people who can't accept it
This is just you
It's just you
Even if you say bad things
It doesn't matter
Even if I say bad things
They will laugh
In that sense
It's a unique audience
It's not a unique audience
It's an audience that we have trained for years
You mean
It was terrible at first
It was terrible
At first
Who are these people?
It's okay
What? Is he happy?
Why did you do the same thing?
I want you to blur all of this
You have to do the broadcast
I can't do it!
The face you hid in front of me is like this
But what happens if you do the broadcast?
Actually, if you do this
Everyone doesn't know but
You can't do it if you do it in the dark
If you do it like that
You can't tell if it's a big deal
It's not like that
Because it's like that
It's like a kid's s**t
Why is it a kid's s**t?
It's my s**t
It's a kid's s**t
But you can't change it like that
I can change it!
Is it okay if I shave my head?
Then tell me
Why is it a kid's s**t?
Wait a minute
Tell me that
I think that
It's not good to watch
If you think about it
There's a kid next to you
This guy is shaving
You're shaving too
If you see it
You'll be surprised
You're an adult
I want to shave my head
And shave my head
If I shave my head
I can't change it like that
You don't have to shave your head
If you can do that
The width of your hair will widen
What width?
I don't know why it's not good
Why is it a kid's s**t and why is it not good for adults?
This is discrimination
If you say that it's a woman
Why?
The baby boy is shaving a lot
It's not good for a girl
It's good
It's a boy and a small kid
It's not good for a girl and it's not good for adults
It's not good for a grandma
It's not good for a man
I want to see a grandma
No!
I want to see a scary thing
I want to see a smelly thing
I don't know why it's not good for a girl
Hey!
Why?
I'm going to die soon
I don't like Japanese people
They are older than me
They are kids
They are animals
It's a hot spring
And food
If you do it on TV, the ratings will be good
Hide-and-seek game
That's a number again
It's good
Hey!
What I don't like is
There are special points
That's right
Let's look at the special points
10 points, 9 points, 8 points, 10 points, 9 points
I don't use 2 points
If it's like this, let's make the whole triangle a square
I see
Why is the whole triangle a square?
Sorry
This kid
This kid is a genius
Something
Right?
He came out
He is a genius
What is it?
I don't know
This genius
This kid
What is it?
What are you saying?
I lost sight of him
I lost sight of him here
Don't go there
What is it?
10 points, 9 points, 8 points, 10 points, 9 points
Next, soccer genius
That's enough
Soccer genius and soccer kid
They are different
That's a different thing
Soccer genius wins
Soccer genius
That's enough
Next question
Question
What is the punch in Punch Parma?
Does it mean the same as the punch in John and Punch?
That's not true
When you translate punch into Japanese
It means
No, it's true
It's the sound you make when you punch
No, no, no
It's all the same
Punch Parma
Parma
Potato chips
Consomme punch
Consomme aura
It's punch
Punch means aura
A date with punch
A date with aura
That's scary
It means let's go on a date
What are you saying?
No, no, no
What is he saying?
Punch is an aura
That's a lie
It's punch
When you say that, I feel like that
What I'm saying is not a lie
You used to do punch kick
Punch kick
With a toy
Yes, yes, yes
If you say it's an aura, it means it's an aura
All punches are an aura
Chimpanzee
That's not true
I'm saying punch
Osmo Quiz Part 2
I used to do Osmo Quiz once
Yay, yay, yay
The peace treaty and the Sarajevo agreement have been settled
Which one will win?
Thinking time
Osmo, I will defeat you
The answer is the peace treaty and the Sarajevo agreement
Yay, yay, yay
Part 2
Osmo Quiz Part 2
Which one will win?
Thinking time
Osmo, I will defeat you
The answer is the peace treaty and the Sarajevo agreement
Yay, yay, yay
Do you want to go home?
It's a bit tight
Let's take a close-up
5 seconds
4, 3, 2
What?
Hey!
I'm sorry
4, 3, 2
You should say Kan
You shouldn't say Kan to the camera