A 24 hour long interview that was close to Nadal's human nature
And then Nadal
I'm not that funny
I don't like it
I don't know
And as a result of searching for the truth
My Heipo is a different type of person
I don't know if I can do it
I'm a man
And so, the punishment game is decided
The first time, the one who doesn't know how to use the instrument
The punishment game is the world's Heipo and man
Daru-chan
It's out!
What kind of comedians meet that often?
It's only been 2 years.
It's just been 2 years.
That's right.
Why is it a punishment game?
It's a little bit of a lie.
That's right.
Why am I going to the punishment game with you?
It's not related to punishment.
Because there's no one who acted deliciously with you.
This is a punishment.
The harsh, harsh, and harsh punishment game is about to begin.
It's so hot.
Good morning.
Today, we're going to have a 24 hour long punishment game.
Punishment game?
Why?
It's like a punishment game.
It's a lie.
Because, it's been announced that you will be going on a trip with Heipo in a punishment game.
I should have said it in advance.
Please stop it.
It's a lie.
Heipo is going on a journey in pair-suits.
I see.
You're going to the punishment game today, right?
You did something bad, right?
No, I didn't do anything bad.
You did!
No, I didn't.
I'm scared.
Why?
A heavy-duty director who has been in the show since the beginning of 1989.
He's so thin.
He's not a demon, but he's extremely scary.
Sometimes, he says,
What a ridiculous story!
And sometimes, he says things that are out of the ordinary.
He has a personality full of problems, but he has never been married, and he has been married 63 times this year.
Is this your first time with Heipou?
No, this is my first time with him.
I've seen him on TV.
He's a very open person, but he's also very selfish.
We met in Yoshimoto, right?
Yes, in Yoshimoto.
You don't remember?
At the theater.
No, at the office.
Sorry.
It's like a useless relationship.
The punishment game.
World peace and two men traveling.
The rules of the trip are to perform the commands that are given to you in different places, so that you don't get any bad parts.
In any case, make it a fun trip full of smiles.
The first command is this.
Immediately, the first command is announced.
Command?
It's the opposite.
Find each other's humanity through private conversation.
While you are talking to each other, please understand each other's personality.
In that car over there.
The private conversation is inside the moving car.
Wait a minute.
This is a little too frivolous.
No, it's too frivolous for me.
Do you go with this?
Do you go with two people?
I drive with two people.
Let's go with everyone.
Nadori touches the cage, rents a car and goes on a trip with the soldiers.
This compact Jimny is his favorite.
Even though it's a punishment game, if he can have fun on the trip, it might help Nadal improve his image.
The two of them are finally starting their journey. What kind of journey will it be?
I've never done a marriage with Aiko-san.
I've been doing it with Ayako-san in Michigan.
It's been a while since we met.
After the show, I met him by chance at Asakusa 10th.
I was a little...
Did you have sex?
No, no, no, I didn't.
There was a scary looking guy behind me.
I said, don't pose!
You used to play with him, didn't you?
I used to play with him.
I was a girl-lover.
There were times when I hated even humans.
You are being made to do that.
You are the one who gives the orders.
I have been doing bad things recently.
But when I do bad things, I don't enjoy it when I don't have any fun.
You don't enjoy it?
I don't enjoy it. So it's better to throw away the orders.
When everyone is gathering, I get bigger.
I don't get bigger.
You don't get bigger?
Oh, so the tits are bigger than you.
It's not that it's bigger than my tits.
So the tits are bigger than you.
It's because my tits are bigger than my tits.
Oh, that's how it is.
That's why it's fun.
Yes, that's why I'm a man.
That's why I'm half-life when I was young.
I think the Shimonota Talk is over.
I'm sure there are a lot of people coming.
No, I don't think so.
I can't get 15,000 yen on TV.
I thought you could get 100,000 yen.
I don't get it.
I'm an actor. I'm doing my best.
I just want to act.
I don't have money to buy a ticket.
I don't have money.
I'm going to throw up.
I'm a little shocked.
I thought I was laughing more
While talking about this, we came to Mother Farm
The mission here is to have fun with animals
The two of them are in a special vehicle to visit the farm and experience feeding
Nadal, who likes animals, is very active
Ah, scary!
I don't want to give it to you! Take it yourself!
Stop it!
Take it!
I'll leave it here and say, eat it!
Eat it!
This time, the main character is just a ghost.
Heipo doesn't care about the body, but shows the presence of the main character's body.
Wait, wait, this side too!
Ah, scary!
NADARU is in a good mood.
Are you okay?
I'm not okay!
Here, here, here.
This guy is scary!
Ahhhh!
Here, here, here.
No, no, no.
What's so scary about this?
What are you eating?
I'm telling you the reason why I'm scared.
You're cute, NADARU.
Ahhhh! You're not cute!
It is hard to say that Nadal had contact with animals in the past.
Seeing this, Nadal gradually changed.
The next command is...
It's over, isn't it?
Spend the night at the campsite.
No, I can't do that.
Everyone should go camping.
It won't end.
I said I would start at 7 o'clock tomorrow.
I will start at 7 o'clock tomorrow.
I'm really looking forward to Takahashi-san's summer live concert
You can just pass it
I can't do it
In the car on the way
I can't pass it
Takahashi-san is really worried and he's practicing a lot
Everyone is really worried
What is that?
He's telling his seniors that he's dissing them
To be honest, I'm the type of person who doesn't say much
Who says that?
I can't believe you're selling your senior.
It's okay.
Poor guy.
Mr. Diane and...
What about Diane?
Mr. Yamauchi from Kamaitachi.
I'm sorry, but I'll have you pay for this.
I'll pay for this.
You can't pay for this.
Waiting for the sun to set,
the two are taken to the campsite,
which is far from the crowd.
Are you okay?
I don't want to.
I've seen you so many times.
You've seen me so many times.
I'm going to sleep.
Please take a picture of your faces.
We'll take a picture of our faces.
Can we turn our faces this way?
Hey, it's scary.
It's so scary.
Please, I beg you.
It's pitch black.
It's scary.
The Hei Po show has begun.
I don't want to do this.
What should I do?
What are you doing?
Please wait, Seibo-san.
From here on, there are only a few cameramen left on the set.
Many staffs are watching from far away
Let's go inside
I'm scared
I'm really bad at this
I'm not good at this either
No way
I have to take off my shoes
It's slippery
I'm surprised
Don't scare me
What is written here?
It's a medical session
There are many bugs in summer
You will spend some time in this tent with Nadar and Heipo.
When the alarm goes off, open the envelope with the map.
Go to the marked spot.
Since there are cameras on the spot, stand in line and take a commemorative photo.
Wait...
Ah!
Don't scare me! What's wrong?
So even Navarre can't do it?
It's no good.
It's the worst of typhoons.
The first time he was able to get a job
After an hour, he regained his composure and started to worry about his job
We've never filmed a regular program in Tokyo
Oh, you've never filmed a regular program?
If I could count the morning, I would have a job every day
It's amazing that you go out every day
So you're that Kato-san, right?
You're called a mad dog.
That's right. But I'm still a mad dog.
You're a mad dog?
I'm a mad dog.
We were together before, when I was working.
If I'm a little silly, I'm a strong puncher.
Oh, you're a strong puncher.
I'm a little weaker.
You look so strong, I don't want to see you, Hamada.
What do you mean?
You're already weak.
No, that's not it.
Like Hoshi.
The real view is that you have to get a little older.
It's just the beginning.
My heart is beating so fast. What should I do? Should I stop?
Okay, okay.
What? It stopped.
It stopped?
I'll open the lid.
You're going to open the lid?
What's with this Japanese poem?
Make it a copy of the A4 paper.
Let's go to Hokora and take a series of photos.
You don't want to go to a place like that, right?
I don't want to go.
Hokora, Hokora.
They are aiming for the treasure map for the memorial shooting.
You are always complaining.
It's dark.
I'm scared.
Mr. Heibo.
Wait, Dan.
I'm supporting you from behind.
I'm getting older and I'm even more scared.
I'm scared every time you touch me.
I got it!
I'm doing my best to avoid it.
I see.
Tei-bou, you're doing it quietly.
The water is ringing.
What?
It's ringing.
Something is coming out.
It looks like a monster.
I'm scared of trees.
I want to go to the boar zoo.
Seriously?
The boar is really scary.
It's a matter of life.
But you can sleep.
What is this?
I don't know.
I'm scared.
What is this?
Huh? What is this?
No, no, no!
I'm scared, get out of here!
What is this?
I don't know!
Hei-Po-San, it's a tree!
Tree!
It's a tree!
What's scary about it?
I hate trees.
If you are afraid of trees, it's full of them around here.
It's a tree!
It's a hat!
Heipo-san, you're really tired yourself.
Yes.
I'm also tired of Heipo-san.
It's my punishment game, but it's Nadara-kun's punishment game.
Let's stop complaining.
What's with these footprints?
The position is...
The point is...
But I'm a little scared, so I'm scared if I don't do it to you.
Let's do it to you.
It's Nadara-kun's fault.
What are you doing?
Don't say that.
I don't know.
You don't know?
Ah, I'm so angry.
You're so big.
The two of them are in front of the shrine.
I'm really scared of the tree.
There's only a tree.
It's a big tree.
Typhoon! Typhoon!
Heiba-san, it's a tree.
Please forgive me.
It took a long time, but they completed the order and returned to the tent safely.
I'm tired.
There's a crow.
Heiba-san, let's stop saying normal things.
Let's go to the forest.
There are also trees in the forest.
That's right.
I'm scared of trees.
I'm going to the forest.
There is an uneasy atmosphere in the tent.
At such times, the two people are filled with vulgar stories.
I've been dating, so I've never had a good time.
I thought I'd be a celebrity.
Are you a celebrity?
You were so popular in the past.
Who?
Laura.
Wow, you're going to a great place.
And Manami Hashimoto.
No, not her.
But at that time, I thought it was a dream to win the King of Contest.
But it wasn't.
I wanted to see what it was like.
What do you mean?
I don't want to say it, but...
I want to see it.
I want to see it too
What a stupid story
The next order is to take a photo at the cemetery
The director will be happy if I do it
What did I do?
What did I do wrong?
I didn't do anything
I did my best for 24 hours
Meanwhile, the next order is
Why are you sweating so much?
Ah, I got it!
Pull it!
I'm pulling it!
Ah, I got it!
Why can't I eat this?
Let's go over there
It's a red one!
I want you to forgive me
Look at the back
This is not something to laugh at.
No one is laughing.
Wow, look.
It's a red one.
I saw it just now.
Where are you going?
Let's go.
Are you still going?
Wait, there's something.
It's a red one, over here.
What is this? Red?
It's a pet bottle.
Let's calm down.
If you look at it, it's a pet bottle in an instant.
The two finished the commemorative photo shoot in a short time.
He's so excited that he's going to the tent
How much did I fly?
He's angry
I don't know, please forgive me
Please forgive him
It's a crow!
What is this?
I'm not going to do it.
I couldn't do it!
I'm so sorry.
I didn't see it coming.
You have to do it.
Please, please.
I can't do it because no one said OK.
How many years have you been doing this?
I'm begging you!
It's not expected that Heipo will start to talk.
As usual, the location has ended.
But tonight, it's not over yet.
The tent life continues after Heipo has started to talk.
What do you want to do?
You guys are doing it so well!
Can I take a break?
I'm really doing my best!
Let's take a break.
I'm a good director.
This is amazing. How many times do I have to do this?
It's more than last time.
You guys are so annoying.
The
truth is, I heard that you were popular, Mr. Heibon.
It's a long time ago.
How many times did you do that?
No, I don't really know because it's a wind-up.
How many times did you put wind-up?
There is a wind-up of 5 times.
I don't know.
But the wind-up is 5 times.
Well, that's right.
No matter how many people are there.
I'm not talking about that, but I'm not having fun.
Let's stop the pre-recording.
Everyone, hurry up and become 63 years old!
You'll know when you're old.
I don't want to do it again.
I've been holding my teeth for a long time.
I can't go on like this until the alarm goes off.
Mr. Heipo is saying it's hard.
I'm going, so let the alarm go off!
I'm not going.
I'm not going either.
Ahhhh!
Ouch!
The next order is a memorial photo at the ruins.
Someone please say something like,
Good work!
Is there anyone who doesn't get a good score?
It's just an S.
S is not a good director.
It's not that kind of director.
I thought S was a good director.
Let's go to the special number.
Who taught you that?
Shut up!
It's a mess.
Ah! It moved!
It moved!
It's really energetic.
I can't do it anymore.
Just like before,
he arrived at the abandoned house,
afraid of the shaking tree.
What are you doing?
Let's just get out of here.
The only thing they want to do is to take a commemorative photo.
Here is the only scary story tonight.
I wonder if it's okay.
There's nothing.
It's scary.
It's a secret.
Scary.
I'll kill you.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Wait!
Ah! The spider's web!
Let's end this!
Every time they smile,
Nadal and Keiko set out with such a goal.
The first two people think of each other as a joke.
On the way, they ate together.
That's disgusting!
They didn't care about the way they ate.
Because they were similar.
However, when they met animals, their relationship became broken.
At night camp, the two completely lost their smiles.
At least at the end of the trip, they will smile.
I'm so sorry.
At least the last part of the trip is a smile.
Where is this?
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
You're so mean.
I'm sorry.
What's going on?
Help me!
Are you going to win?
So this time it was like this.
Is it okay?
That's right.
What the hell is that?
What the hell is it?
It's too funny.
I saw the second part.
What's the punishment?
Well then, you two, see you in the second part!
Thank you very much.
It's really hard.
I'm nervous.