Tadakata!
It's been a while since I've seen...
What is this?
My voice is getting hoarse.
It's been a while since I've seen Akasaka...
Bwa...
I don't like this guy.
I don't want people to laugh at me for saying things that I don't mean to say.
I'm laughing at you.
It's like a theater in Akasaka.
Oh, that's right.
The dressing room is upstairs.
Yes.
But it's like it's coming down.
It's coming down from the top.
It's coming up on it's own.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
I'm a bit tanned, right?
You went to the court?
I went to the court.
It's summer vacation.
It was a summer vacation. But on the first night, when I was sleeping at the hotel,
I remembered that Saipan was really famous.
Ah, the ghost.
I remembered that and was really scared.
From the second day, I went to hug Yamazaki.
I was really scared.
Don't lie to me like that.
I didn't mean to hug him, but we slept together in Yamazaki's room.
I was a little scared.
How many times did you hook up with her?
I didn't hook up with her. Because Saipan wasn't there.
She wasn't there.
It was just my family.
It was true.
My acquaintance found you.
Ah, in Saipan?
Yes.
What was the situation like?
I went into her room and saw her.
She wasn't there.
You must be lying.
Don't lie to me like that.
I heard it.
I've been lying to you for a long time.
You're married and have children.
You shouldn't lie to me like that.
I don't know if you're saying this because you're single.
But if you're single, you'll have a lot of dreams in the future.
You'll meet a lot of people in the future.
You'll crush them all.
No.
If I'm found out, will there be someone like that?
What?
It's not that I won't be found out.
I don't want to be found out by this guy.
You understand, right?
I'm the one who has a lot of dreams in the future.
It's not that I won't be found out by this guy.
You're a fool.
So why don't you want to be found out?
That's because...
I'm not single.
I don't want to be found out.
You should have told me honestly.
That's right.
What is this?
Let's say there's someone who's about to get caught.
It's just an example.
You don't need an example.
If there's someone who's about to get caught,
and they ask,
Are you playing in the court?
And you say, I don't want to.
What will happen to my love?
I want to tell you that.
That's right.
There's no way that your partner will crush your love.
You're a person who needs to help me with my love.
And if my love goes well,
I'll work harder.
If you're a jockey,
you'll have to kick my ass.
If you do that to my love,
I'll be flustered.
I'll be like, that's enough.
I'll be like, do you want to go abroad?
Do you want to go abroad?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
That's not true.
That's not true at all.
Why are you laughing?
I'm sorry.
That's not true at all.
Why is that?
If I knew about your relationship with your girlfriend,
I would have said,
thank you very much.
And I would have called the staff.
Hey, cut that part out.
What?
I don't have a staff member.
I want to do anything for you.
So please go home and watch the show this Sunday.
The things I've said so far,
I'll cut a little bit of it.
That's just a matter of time.
It's the opening line today.
I don't want to say too much.
Who is that?
A friend from high school.
A man?
Yes, a man.
That man saw me taking a woman into my room?
Yes, he did.
It's connected.
The trial will come out after all.
What?
I don't know.
You guys went in normally.
Did you see me doing this?
I think you saw me going in from behind.
It's completely connected.
It's scary.
The trial is scary.
I don't know if it's like that.
I don't know.
I was scared.
I went to the casino.
Have you ever been to the casino from the trial?
No.
It takes 50 minutes by boat.
Really?
Yes.
I was in a bad mood, so I went to the casino.
It takes 5 or 10 minutes by boat.
You have money.
What are you talking about?
It's not like that.
You have money.
It's a dirty casino.
A casino?
No.
It's like gambling.
That's fine.
The pilot was an old lady with a bow and arrow.
Old lady?
It's really scary.
It's just a bow and arrow.
It's true.
My hands are covered in blood.
The old lady's bow and arrow is interesting.
A black man took me there.
I thought he would ride with me.
But the old lady was riding with me.
I thought he was a candidate.
When I got on the boat, I was like a fool.
The old lady was riding with me.
My hands were covered in blood.
The old lady's bow and arrow is interesting.
It was really scary.
When I got on the boat, I was waiting for a taxi.
I was waiting for a taxi at the airport.
The old lady was waiting for a taxi at the airport.
I took out an aluminum foil from my bag.
I ate something.
It was really scary.
I didn't think I would die because of this old lady.
But she was a great old lady.
She was a great old lady.
It was really scary.
But there was nothing.
I'm glad there was nothing.
How long were you there?
About three days.
About three days?
Yes.
There were a lot of Japanese people, right?
There weren't many Japanese people.
Tourists?
There were a lot of tourists, right?
What do you want me to say?
Can I say something?
But can I speak as I am?
The audience is small and I can't say anything.
I can't say anything.
If I speak as I am, it's not interesting.
It's not fun.
I'm serious.
Are you kidding me?
Don't be so cocky just because I took you to my room.
What do you mean?
Oh, I did it!
Everyone, look at this.
My sweat.
I'm standing on my knees, aren't I?
Don't be so cocky just because I took you to my room.
My sweat.
Wait a minute, is that all?
Really?
What?
What's with that face?
Dirty. You're dirty.
If I had to rephrase it, you're dirty.
It hasn't changed.
It hasn't changed at all.
I'm going to take a dump.
I'm sure you're getting better at editing.
You're going to pee?
Isn't that obvious?
How are you going to pee?
When I took a dump, I peed!
If that's not good enough,
I don't understand a thing you're saying.
Even someone who hasn't been trained properly would understand.
Once again, I have a question for Mr. Matsumoto.
What would you do if someone took your bag?
What would you do if someone took your mount?
I see, I see.
I don't know how many of you know what a mount is.
They say that if you take a mount, it's the best thing for you.
If you take a mount, you can't do anything from the bottom.
You can't do anything.
That's right. You can't take my mount.
I'll let you take it.
What should I do?
Please take the mount.
What is this?
Let me take it.
Let me get on top of it.
Please take the mount.
Can I just cross my legs like this?
There's something like this.
Like this.
How did you take it?
This isn't a mount.
There are people who misunderstand this as a mount.
This is a mount.
This and this are completely different.
If you do this, you can't do anything.
I'm doing it like this.
I can't do anything.
It's not like I'm holding your hand.
I can hit it from below, but it doesn't work because it doesn't have a waist.
I see.
That's why I have to do this to make it hit me.
But if I do this, I can't do anything.
That's why it's hard.
What do you do when you get hit?
I got it.
Please remember this situation.
What are you doing?
Wait a minute.
Stand up once.
What are you doing?
You have a really amazing face.
Do you understand?
Please remember this situation.
You can't do anything.
What do you do when you get hit?
I got it.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
This is hot.
Let's go.
What are you going to do?
I'll let you take the mount.
I'm taking the mount.
Let's go.
Come on.
Take the mount.
Can I throw it?
It's a tackle.
You want to take the mount, don't you?
Yes, I want to take it.
You can't do this.
You can't do that at all.
That's...
Were you able to do that?
You bastard.
Because...
You can't take the mount.
You'll get hit.
That's not right.
You said you want to take the mount.
That's a molecule and a molecule.
What is that?
I don't get it.
You said you want to take the mount.
What is that?
That's not right.
It's like this.
When you take it...
It seems like you're cheating.
What are you doing?
You were really fast with just your hands.
Please tell us how to take care of your ears.
How to take care of your ears.
If you've heard anything about this, you won't lose anything.
I won't lose anything.
There's nothing that doesn't work.
What?
You mean for illness?
Yes.
Really?
For example, bald people get hair.
That's difficult.
People with a broken jaw won't lose anything.
What?
I don't know how bad it is.
Compared to before.
Really.
That's definitely true.
I want to be like that.
I want to have a better body.
It works for everything?
It works for everything.
For example, people who are fat want to lose weight.
Of course.
That works the best.
You should have said that first.
It's too obvious.
I didn't want to say it.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I like this shirt.
I don't like long sleeves.
I want to wear short sleeves.
I thought it would work for that.
What should I do?
It doesn't work for me.
It works for that.
Please tell me.
I don't have an earpick.
I can't do it.
It's okay to have one.
You have an earpick.
What are you doing?
It's okay.
I'm not an amateur.
Yes.
What are you doing?
What are you trying to do?
It's a rhythm.
What about an earpick?
I don't have an earpick.
What are you doing?
I have five earpicks here.
If you don't have five or ten earpicks, you can have one.
I don't have an earpick.
What should I do?
Let me hear your opinions.
I'm just singing.
Think of it like a radio exercise.
What was it?
It's like a folk dance.
It's all rhythm.
It's an exercise for earpick.
You have to remember the song first.
I got it.
What are you talking about?
I don't need lyrics.
If you don't remember the lyrics, you can't dance.
What are you talking about?
I'm not talking about music.
You're talking about something.
I'm talking about the atmosphere.
I'm talking about the rhythm.
You don't have to say anything.
I don't care.
If you don't have to say anything, don't say it.
I don't know if it's the same thing.
If you don't know how to say it, you'll remember it.
I can't say it if I don't have to say it.
It was a little funny.
You can't say it.
I can't remember it.
What are you talking about?
You have to remember that first.
Sunomono, sunomono, sunomono.
What is that?
It's called sunomono.
SU.
NU.
Suno.
Sunomono, sunomono, sunomono.
I'll do it.
Sunomono, sunomono, sunomono-san.
I didn't do anything.
Let's start from here.
Sunomono, sunomono, sunomono-su.
Don!
Sunomono, sunomono, sunomono-san.
What is that?
I just pointed it out.
I'll ask the person in charge.
You have to say it's just like that.
Yes.
Sunomono, sunomono, sunomono-san.
Yes, don!
Don!
You have to say it's just like that.
I did it too much, so I'll do it again.
It's hot.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday dear my darling.
Good job.
Let's toast as usual.
There's one person who's looking down.
He seems to have forgotten.
On behalf of everyone, Mr. Yamasaki, please.
Happy 37th birthday.
Well then, I'll leave it here.
What do you mean?
From now on, Yoshimoto Ninawa Kokoriko will...
Are you ready?
You don't have to be Ninawa anymore.
I'll give up.
You can't do that anymore?
Yes.
No.
What?
So...
Shouldn't it have ended like that?
Well then...
Why?
Kokoriko...
It's like a cake.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.