What's so funny?
There's nothing funny.
From now on too.
What's so funny?
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
I was driving in Daikanyama.
I was driving in a car.
The car in front of me is a Donkusai.
Yes, there's one.
There's one, right?
It's not even a traffic light.
What is it?
When a pedestrian comes, it stops one by one.
There's one.
It tells you to go faster.
How long are they going to wait?
Until it completely disappears.
It's impossible.
The main street of Daikanyama.
But it's there.
It tells you to go faster.
Then a car comes from behind.
Let's stop.
Then it stops again.
I wasn't in the car behind me.
I was in front of it.
In the end, it went away.
It went away.
I thought I was in front of it.
Then it opened the window.
It's a foreigner.
It's 100% a foreigner.
It's in beautiful Japanese.
I thought it was a lie.
If you think of Tokyo as the center, you're obviously far away.
But that doesn't matter.
It was said clearly.
It's a really bad foreigner.
I'll never lose.
It's a foreigner.
I was told by a guy who said,
What's this?
I'm from the countryside.
I came from Osaka to Tokyo.
You're definitely from New Jersey.
It's a corner, isn't it?
You're just saying what you know.
I'm angry.
Why did you know it was small?
Because the seat is like this.
It's like this.
Shut up.
I'm from the countryside.
They're really proud.
Well, I guess so.
If I go abroad.
You can't say that.
I'm sorry for about a year.
Right?
I can't say that.
You can't say that.
If you say that, it's a foreign word.
If you say that, it's going to be a big deal.
It's a close-in.
It's too close.
It's so close that you can wash it off.
It's a strange thing.
That's right.
There's no such thing.
They're really...
They're proud of me.
I was drunk in Roppongi.
There's a foreigner selling things.
That foreigner told me to go home when I was drunk.
That's...
I'm coming from a place that's obviously far from you.
No, no, no.
Don't worry.
I'm drunk.
That's right.
It's easy, isn't it?
What do you think?
What do you think about the drama?
I don't intend to complain.
Well, for the time being...
Otaku-san is...
We're just two people.
We're just messing around.
That's right.
What do you think?
Well, but...
I'm nervous.
Who?
Everyone.
It's red, isn't it?
The East is red.
The East...
It's like a period drama.
The lines change.
Tanaka said it yesterday, too.
He has an acting plan.
In the East.
I'm thinking about it in my hair.
I'm thinking about it under my hair.
This scene is like this.
I'm going to move in this way.
That's what he thinks.
But it's going to be red.
That's why it's a period drama.
Sometimes he walks like this.
If you think about it...
He moves with his bare feet.
If you think about it, he has a long acting career.
He's never done a drama before.
It's a standard language.
It's like he's doing a skit.
Is that a standard language?
No, Kogoriko and Fujii are all standard languages.
Really?
Fujii is a standard language.
But Fujii is sweating all the time.
He's been acting for a long time.
I don't know if it's okay to act like that.
He's sweating all the time.
He's like a drinking heart.
Even if it's a real deluxe car, he's sweating like this.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
He's sweating like this.
It's like he's stuck in my hand and it's coming out.
That's not good.
But his acting is a little strange.
Sometimes his standard language is strange.
You don't know the scene.
When I came, there were only two of us.
I've never seen anyone else acting.
To be honest, I'm scared.
Wait a minute.
Have you ever done this before?
I've done it once.
The set on the first day is set in the 8th floor of Higashi.
He's sweating all the time.
I don't know what's going on.
If you say that, it's your line.
If you say it, I don't know what to do.
I'm nervous when I see it.
I'm used to it.
Are you okay?
I'm nervous about the first and second episodes.
If I get used to it, I'll add some ad-libs to the lines.
But I don't think I can do it now.
I can't do it now.
There was a scene in the tobacco space.
I said something to Higashi at the end.
But Higashi is cold.
Then...
You didn't hear it.
Obviously.
Cold?
I said okay.
Did you say okay?
He appeared in a movie.
I didn't watch it.
There was a bed scene.
There was a woman on the bed.
She wanted to rub her father.
I can't do it like this.
I'm scared.
Please look forward to it.
In that sense?
I'm nervous.
Are you okay?
You haven't been free yet.
I'm nervous.
I can speak standard Japanese.
I can do it.
But I can't do it because everyone looks at me strangely.
You look like a standard Japanese.
I can do it if I speak standard Japanese.
Please say something weird.
You guys don't talk to me.
I don't want to listen to you.
You don't like to be called cold.
He doesn't like it.
I don't like the feeling of a hole in my butt.
I don't like that.
That's why I don't think it's a problem.
Oh really?
I don't know.
Even if you say it, it's already over the day before.
That's right.
Ah, it's a troublesome story.
It's a troublesome story.
I'll write it down.
What?
No, it's just that...
I wonder if it's there.
Ah, but I don't know, Hamada.
What is it?
If you talk too much about drama.
Why?
It's just that Yamazaki is already blue.
Just now in the dressing room.
After all, it's going to be a story like that.
How did you get it?
How is it?
There's a little story like that.
I'll tell you, right?
What is this feeling?
I can't get it!
In a sense, I'm saying that Yamazaki is the main character.
What kind of feeling is that?
It's not out yet.
Even if you say it, it's just Yamazaki.
Everyone else is out.
If you say it as a member of the kids, it's just Yamazaki.
It's not out yet, so it's okay to have a role.
It's hard.
I'm looking at Yamazaki right now.
It's no good if it's this story.
I'm looking at it from there.
It's going to be a story like that.
I don't know what Lee Japan went crazy about.
It was number one, right?
It was number one.
It's true.
Yamazaki is here again!
I want to see it with a face like number 62.
This is a question for Matsumoto-san, who is enjoying the thrill of living or dying.
Please tell me the story of how you managed to escape while being attacked by a giant ant hell that drags humans into the Sahara Desert.
This was hard.
Really?
What kind of ant hell do you know?
I don't know.
Do you know what happens in the end?
I don't know that.
I don't know that at all.
Really?
Let me tell you a little bean knowledge.
What is it?
There's something called Nagoya Kochin, right?
Yes.
Nagoya Kochin is a famous bird.
Like a chicken.
It's really stupid.
Why?
If you surprise it, it will die.
Really?
Nagoya Kochin.
It's really hard to raise it.
Don't surprise it.
If you put it in like this, it will die.
That's too much.
It's true.
You have to feed it gently.
That's annoying.
Such a bird.
You're angry, aren't you?
The door will open and bang.
It will die.
Why?
Don't surprise it.
It's true.
Like a chicken.
A chicken is dead because it can't breathe.
But Nagoya Kochin is dead when it is held.
It's true.
It doesn't matter what happens at the end.
When it is held, it will die.
That's not true.
What do you mean?
It's dead.
What are you talking about?
Why does it die?
It's surprised.
It's a fool.
Nagoya Kochin.
It's true.
It's really a fool.
It's surprised that the guy next to it died.
That's strange.
When the guy next to it died, I was surprised.
It's true.
You can't raise such a thing.
It's a big deal.
I was talking about when it ran away.
It ran away.
It's a big deal.
We don't know what's going on.
We don't know.
I've never been addicted to it.
Is that so?
Please tell me what happened.
Do you want me to tell you?
It's not over with Nagoya Kochin.
You said it yourself.
If I didn't say it myself, I wouldn't have died.
Even now, Nagoya Kochin is dying.
That's fine.
I want to hear this now.
That's true.
It ran away.
I was addicted to it.
In Sahara.
It happened in Sahara Desert.
That's right.
Please tell me what happened.
I arrived at the Sahara Airport.
Not in the desert?
Yes.
Is the airport like that?
Sahara International Airport.
I arrived at the North Wing.
It's a big place.
The Sahara Airport.
When I got off the plane, it was like this.
That's not true.
Why did you get off at the airport?
It's a huge place.
Is it in the middle of the desert?
What is it?
The airport is in the North Wing.
It's in the North.
Is it in the middle of the desert?
It's not standing.
I don't know.
When you got off, it was like this.
Is it in the middle of the desert?
The airport is like this.
Is there an airport in the middle of the desert?
No.
Listen to me.
It's like this.
What is that?
It's like an ant's hell.
It's like a fish bowl.
Yes.
What were you thinking about earlier?
What's more important?
I don't know.
It's like this.
What are you doing?
What's this?
It's like this.
It's getting bigger.
It was this small at first.
That's what a big one is.
It's going down.
It's getting bigger.
Who is this?
I'll tell you later.
There's someone doing it.
You know, in the Sahara desert, there's a plane that goes like this, and you think it's easy to land there, right?
And then you go like this.
At first, it was fine, but when you get into the landing zone, it goes like this.
Right? It was fine before, but it's bigger than you think.
You don't know that, so when you say,
I'm waiting for your arrival with all my heart.
What's that?
That's later.
When you land, it goes like this.
Well, it's fine. It went like this.
It went like this.
What happened? Only one leg went like this.
At that time, I was wearing pants, so I didn't know what to do.
It's called the Sahara.
The Sahara?
When you go to the Sahara, you wear something that's a little different from usual.
A bell bottom.
I was wearing a bell bottom that was more than necessary.
It was fine normally, right?
That's right.
That's why it was easy to grab.
Who is it now?
Who is it?
This guy.
Do you want to know who it is?
You want to know that, right? You've been doing it for a long time, haven't you?
After all, I can't talk about this without his story.
This is surprising.
Who is it?
Who is it? What is it?
Well, how do I say this?
Simply put, it's a foreigner.
It's not Japanese, is it?
It's a plus.
It's not Japanese.
When you go to the Sahara, you want something that's famous.
It's a Sahara, right?
It's a Sahara, right? It shouldn't be about Ali Jigoku.
Do you understand?
I understand.
That's why I vote every time.
What do you vote for?
The Ali Jigoku role.
I see.
The guy who was chosen at this time.
There was a time when I was a grandmother or a child.
By the way, when I was in the Sahara, I was 31 years old.
It's about 40 years old.
Even if I was 31 years old, I had a lot of upper arm muscles.
I had a lot of muscles.
You were 31 years old.
I was 31 years old.
I had a lot of muscles.
I was beaten by that guy.
I was grabbed.
Do you know what happens when you're dragged in?
I don't know.
I had to do it with the guy inside.
I had to do it with everyone.
There were about 50 people.
The other day, Mr. Matsumoto went to the department store with a monkey, a dog and a knight.
There are red and blue demons in the demon.
What's the difference?
This is complicated.
Is it complicated?
It's complicated.
There are only blue demons.
What do you think is the difference?
The color is different.
The demon is a demon.
Is that all?
I feel sorry that you don't have knowledge.
Please tell me the difference.
What is it?
Simply put, red is a punch.
Do you always come with me?
Red and blue.
It's difficult to be friends in the world of demons.
It's not good to be with blue people.
Because they are stupid.
I see.
Why is it not good?
They are stupid and stupid.
On the contrary.
On the contrary?
Red has to be blue.
Red always says a lot of things.
It's a demon's punch.
Don't laugh at me.
Red and blue must always be together.
It's not good in the world of demons.
I can't even go to the pool.
Pool?
If it's red and blue, it's a split.
There are days when it's red.
On the contrary, it's blue.
There are days when it's blue.
I don't think I deserve to be treated like this.
You don't deserve to be treated like this.
I want to say more.
It's a stupid punch.
Simply put.
There are many other things.
It's a stupid punch, right?
The two red horns are different from the one red horn, right?
There is a difference.
Oh, it's different from Japan.
How is it different?
The two red horns are the same as the one blue horn.
What's the same?
Feelings.
I don't know that.
That's why I say it's complicated.
It's a stupid punch.
The two red horns are...
I got it. It's complicated.
I got the difference now.
You got it, right?
I got it.
I wanted to say more about that.
I don't know that.
We don't know that.
That's right.
There's a slight difference between the two horns.
The one that goes like this is a little bit of a joke.
The one that goes like this is red.
But the one that goes like this in blue is something I really hate.
I see.
And the ten-par is not ten-par.
It's a little bit.
Ten-par is a little bit of a cheeky joke.
A joke that doesn't even laugh when you tickle someone.
That's funny.
With poker face.
There's something like that.
Is that so?
And the one that doesn't have horns is red.
There's one that doesn't have horns?
Really?
Yes.
The one that doesn't have horns is red.
Your...
Your demon talk is basically a play.
From now on, I'm going to keep messing around.
Is that so?
I'm not just going to have red and blue anymore.
What?
What color are you going to have?
There's a lot of things.
Red and blue, horns like this, like that, no, ten-par.
I'm going to marry whoever I want, so I'm messed up.
Is that so?
Yes.
What color are you going to have?
Recently, I've had paisley.
I'm not scared of that.
Even if a demon with a paisley pattern comes out, I don't think I'll be scared.
You're scared if a demon with a paisley pattern comes out.
I'll just watch it.
What is this?
That's scary.
If a red demon comes out, I'll be scared, but I'll just calm down and watch it.
There's also a lot of woodpeckers.
This program was provided by the following sponsors.