What should we do?
Excuse me.
Good morning.
Yamasaki-san said,
If you can come, then come.
Who are you talking to?
Who?
To everyone.
What are you saying?
If you can come, then come.
Who cares?
What's with you guys?
What's wrong with you?
Who are you talking to?
Who cares?
If you can come, then come.
Who are you talking to?
Don't tell me you remember the second one from before?
Oh, really?
That's right.
There was one like Yamazaki Quest.
That's an illustration.
That's not Yamazaki Quest.
Please come to the center.
It's been a long time since I've been here.
This time, I came to the Golden Land of Gizu, Jibang, rather than Harubaru France.
I'll give you a chance to be lucky.
This is the first time I've been to the Golden Land of Gizu, Jibang.
It's been a long time since I've been to the Golden Land of Gizu.
I'll give you a chance to be lucky.
You can meet the Golden Gold Coins from the Golden Land of Gizu, Jibang.
Golden...
You have to solve the mystery I thought of.
I'll give you the first hint.
I'll help you solve the mystery of the veteran ninja who is injured.
It's better to mix it up.
This program is brought to you by the sponsor you are watching.
You'll be surprised.
Good morning.
I don't need money.
I'll give you money.
It's warm.
It's warm, but it's hot.
The white thing that's been injured.
It's true.
It's a big deal.
I don't know if it's that injured.
What's wrong?
He died because he was hit by a kappa.
What is it?
Oh, that's it.
There's a kappa.
My father was hit by a kappa and fell down.
That's what he said.
There's a kappa, right?
That's right.
Do you fly kappa?
It's a big deal.
Are you okay?
I'm in the mood to do this.
Do you want to fly?
It's a big deal.
Get on the kappa.
It's pretty cold.
It's cold.
That's hot.
Get on the kappa.
It's very cold.
It's a big deal.
Get on the kappa.
Did you do it?
It's a big deal.
Let's go!
How many do you have?
I have four.
I have three.
I'm sick of it.
I want to go home.
I can see the monitor.
I'm sick of it.
It seems that the samurai got the first piece of the coin.
I will tell you the way you should go.
I'm sick of it.
Okay.
Was it scary?
Yes.
No, it wasn't.
This is teamwork.
The letters are probably different.
Right?
I'm scared.
No, stop it.
No, you can't do that.
You can't take the coin.
I'm scared.
How many are there?
Four, right?
Four.
It's the last one.
It's over.
Go and get it.
It's the last one.
You're not going to do it, are you?
I'm going for the third one.
Look.
What?
Children can also enjoy it, right?
I'm scared.
What are you talking about?
I'm not going to run away.
Was it that scary?
It's like a horror movie.
That's right.
How long have you been waiting here?
You're trying to make me do this.
Stop it.
I'm going to run away.
I'm not going to run away.
It's going to take about 10 minutes.
I'll follow you.
Should I lie down?
That's right.
Either way is fine, but lying down is faster.
I can't run fast.
What are you doing?
I don't like that kind of ad-lib.
Please watch it.
It's coming.
Don't run fast.
Did you see it?
You saw it perfectly.
It's a pirate.
That's it.
It's definitely a pirate.
I called you a pirate.
I don't know.
It's a pirate.
I'm looking for coins like this.
I don't know.
It's coming back.
It's a pirate.
It's coming.
The castle is full of rumors about you.
I want to see you.
But I can't go out.
I'm already 14 years old.
I'm a great man.
I'll tell you what's going on in the castle.
What's in the box?
There's a lot, but I wonder which one it is.
Please put it in.
Let's play the Chichi game with four people.
The loser will find the treasure box.
What do you mean Chichi game?
Chichi no Ichi
That's amazing.
Did you think about this game?
Chichi no Zero
Chichi no Ichi
End
The game is called Hayakidori.
That's the worst.
It's shaking.
That's great.
I'm going to die if I get on it.
It's shaking.
Are you okay?
I'm not okay.
Can you see anything?
I can see it.
Please do your best.
I'm scared.
What's this?
I don't want to go alone.
Wait a minute.
It's raining a lot.
It's going up to a very high place.
Wait a minute.
I'm dead.
What's this?
There's no end.
The game is over.
End is crying.
Can you see it?
Can't you see it?
I saw it.
What was it?
I'll take you there.
Did you see it?
What did it say?
Let's move to the place where we saw it.
Did you really see it?
I can see it.
Are you sure?
I'll tell you.
What did it say?
I can't see anything.
Please give me a hint.
It's a sparrow.
I saw a sparrow.
Please check it out.
Why?
I'm serious.
What is this?
This is a sparrow.
I want to choose a sparrow.
I can only choose one.
Please open it.
Let's choose this one.
This is a sparrow.
This is not the size of the box.
This is the opposite of the box.
Please choose this one.
This is the third one.
This is the fourth one.
Please choose this one.
This is the fifth one.
This is the sixth one.
Please open it.
It's not easy for you to come this far.
You smell like a beast.
Is it a sparrow?
I'm a long-time rival of the sparrow.
A sparrow?
I was attacked by a sparrow two years ago.
This old wound has healed.
He is a rival.
I said something like this then.
The spirit of hell dwells in the corner of the old man's hair.
The golden color of the child's teeth is shining.
Please go to the future.
This is a sparrow.
It's not easy for you to come this far.
It's annoying.
That's where it is.
I know.
It's on the right.
It's really narrow.
That's right.
It's here.
It's narrow.
It's all the same.
I can't see anything.
I don't want to.
I'm scared.
Why are you here?
Hide a little more.
Let's go.
I don't want to.
I'm scared.
Please go ahead.
I don't want to.
You can go ahead.
Please go ahead.
I don't want to.
Go away.
You can't go.
I'm going home.
Where are you going?
I don't want to.
It's the exit.
It's dangerous.
What are you scared of?
I'm scared.
It's not a ghost.
There are four.
Come here.
There's a monitor.
There are 10.
Congratulations, everyone.
You've got a gold piece.
Then,
take four pieces and put them in the event hall.
When the event is over,
you can meet the new king of the century.
I've seen this last time.
This is it.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
That's right.
That's it.
It's a piece of wood.
It's in.
It's a key.
I can make it.
The key to the event hall.
It's open.
I can see it.
It's amazing.
It's quite big.
It's fast.
World.
Thank you for waiting.
Now, let's welcome the six beauties
who are left for the final assessment.
Now,
Ladies and gentlemen,
the announcement of Miss World Grand Prix.
The Grand Prix goes to
Japan's representative,
Yama-chan.
Congratulations.
I can see a tear in her eyes.
Now, the winner, Yama-chan.
Who do you want to convey this joy to?
Of course, to my parents.
To Yukippe, who secretly applied for this contest.
I see.
Do you have a message for Yukippe?
Are you watching, Yukippe?
I won the Grand Prix.
She even has a balloon.
Now, the winner of the Grand Prix,
Yama-chan,
will sing Vacation,
which she showed us in the second round.
Here you go.
I can't do that.
Amazing.
V-A-C-A-T-I-O-A
This is fun.
What's wrong with me?
Shining brightly
In the summer sun
My first swim
V-A-C-A-T-I-O-A
Let's go on a fun ski trip in the winter
On a white snowy road
What was that?
I don't understand.
What is this?
You're amazing.
Good night
Your gaze is too hot
Thank you