Happy New Year!
Gaki no Tsukai, ah, 2000, Gaki no Tsukai, Omochiro VTR Best Ten.
Today, I have been chosen to be the host for three consecutive years.
My name is Yoshimoto Kogyo Fujiwara Hiroshi.
I look forward to working with you.
This year too, I'm sorry, the 21st century too.
What are you saying?
I'm sorry, I don't understand what you're saying.
The 21st century has started.
It's my job, but last year, I'm sorry, I got married.
Why are you sorry?
I got married last year.
Congratulations.
Yes, thank you.
I think I have to do my best.
Why are there five people?
That person is...
Why are you acting like a new character?
The more cards you get, the more gay you are.
The 21st century has started.
This program is brought to you by the sponsors you see.
I was chosen on my own and by prejudice.
Gaki no Tsukai, Omochiro VTR.
Why is it that every year you are chosen on your own and by prejudice?
For some reason, yes, I'm chosen on my own and by prejudice.
By prejudice?
First of all, I would like to announce from 10th to 7th place.
VTR, check it out.
It's funny.
In the past, Itao has appeared on the set of the show.
This time, Itao wants Gaki no Tsukai to be his wife.
Yamazaki, Kokoriko and Itao's wives.
Which of them is more suitable to be a wife?
Itao's wife's high tension, please.
Can you do Samba rhythm?
I want to go to Goose and Dandy.
What is this?
And the match between Tanaka and Yuusaku Matsuda.
You said it there.
You didn't say it there.
Bring it on.
But after this, Itao said something beyond our imagination.
What is this?
It's you.
Hey.
Wait a minute.
Isn't this a true story?
What?
Hey, are you okay?
There's no way this is real.
But this is what it actually looks like.
Are you going to die?
I'm in a coma.
Is it your husband?
My husband is Yamada.
Until what place?
Until 7th place.
It's just a prank on Yamada.
It's not a prank.
It's real.
It's a real story.
It's a big success.
It's real.
It's a documentary.
It's weird.
But at that time, there's a scary thing about Hamada.
Last year, Tanaka was washed away.
It's that time.
It's been 2 months since he was washed away.
And...
And Yuta.
This is Yamada.
Good morning.
It's the same tone as the anime.
What is that?
Wait a minute.
What do you mean you were washed away?
Is this 4th place?
I chose it.
There's more.
There's no place to laugh.
Did anyone laugh during the video?
You laughed.
This is Yamada.
Thank you.
Thank you for saving me.
Is this 2nd place?
I'm not sure.
So is Ogiri.
This 3rd and 2nd place have a bad image.
Even if you become a user and use 1 million yen to buy fireworks, you'll still be called a joke.
At that time, I wanted to cut it even more.
But my ribs were broken.
It's not broken.
It's not in the video, but...
What is it?
It's a skateboard.
It's a skateboard in the air.
That's right.
On December 10th, I broke my ribs.
It's not broken.
It's really broken.
I'll show you.
The moment it broke...
The moment it broke, you just fell from here.
It's dangerous.
Next year, I'll do that video 12 times.
12 times?
What does that mean, Fujiwara-kun?
It's 1st place.
1st place?
It's probably that.
I see.
I understand.
This is 1st place.
This isn't a punishment.
Every year on New Year's Eve...
No, no, no.
I'm in trouble.
I'm really in trouble.
If you look at it, it's not that big a deal.
No, no, no.
I think I'll do this in a movie.
In a movie.
A kid's movie.
But if you look at it up to 10th place...
There's no Heipo project at all.
That's true.
The other day, with Jaguar...
It's been a while since I've heard number 15.
Oh, that's right.
Then, I hope for the further development of the 21st century's kid's use.
I'd like to ask the old lady to dance.
I see.
It's been a while.
I'd like to ask the old lady to dance.
It's been a while since I've heard number 15.
I don't want to cut anything.
You did it right away.
This is going to be the end.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.