This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
I'm looking forward to it.
Like this?
I went to see it.
What did you see?
I went to see David Copperfield.
The one with magic?
Yes, the one with magic.
It was amazing.
I don't know how much I can say about this.
Anyway, what I can say is...
It was gone.
That's his business.
It suddenly came out of nowhere.
It disappeared again.
It came out again.
A busy man.
David said,
The husband has disappeared again.
But I saw some seeds.
I saw the seeds.
That's what I think.
Which one?
You didn't see it, did you?
It's your idea to talk now, isn't it?
I didn't see it.
What do you mean?
I don't know why it disappeared.
I don't know either.
But when it disappeared,
It appeared in the middle of the audience.
It disappeared immediately.
This is amazing.
I saw it.
Why?
He is a twin.
There is no mistake.
This is not a place to laugh.
They are twins.
There is no mistake.
You understood me immediately, didn't you?
What?
Are you a fool?
No.
It came out immediately.
On the contrary,
I want to say it's amazing.
They say,
You shouldn't do it.
You should do it because it's amazing.
But I found out that they are twins.
If I have a little more time,
I think there is a trick.
I can't believe it.
If I pull the cloth,
It will fall.
It's definitely David Tepperfield.
What does that mean?
It's my brother.
Your brother is Tepperfield?
Tepperfield.
This is the name I gave him.
It's not Sadako.
And he is jumping.
He is jumping.
That's what they do on the piano, right?
I think that's the first thing.
Because there is no way.
I went to Yamazaki with him.
He is a fool.
I thought he was joking at first.
I understood.
What is going on with the twins.
What do you think he said?
It's a magnet.
Where are you trying to go?
He is crazy.
A magnet is just right.
If it's a magnet that lifts a human,
Tepperfield goes up to the ceiling.
Tepperfield is under the iron.
There is a big magnet on the ceiling.
Tepperfield goes up to the ceiling.
And everyone turns off the lights.
He is sweating.
I'm not sweating.
He is helping.
His bag and wallet are flying.
That's right.
The cover under the microphone is also flying.
That's bad.
When I came here before,
He didn't clean the building.
Did he come here before?
He didn't come here before.
He was the goddess of freedom, right?
He cleaned the building, right?
Who are you?
He came here today.
I don't know you.
He is wearing a suit.
Is that so?
Did he come here before?
He didn't come here before.
Is that true?
He was surprised.
That's not true.
Everyone knows that he is amazing.
I don't know how much to say.
He was a cherry blossom.
Everyone else was a cherry blossom.
I don't know how much to say.
The timing was too good.
After the show,
It was a standing ovation.
Everyone was standing up.
I was standing up.
I thought it was wrong.
But I was surprised at one thing.
Really?
At first, I was given a piece of paper.
I was told to cut it.
I cut it into eight pieces of paper.
It became a card.
I see.
Only one of them was a picture of the moon.
The rest was white.
Everyone told me to put it out.
I told them to put it in the shape they wanted.
I was waiting for the right shot.
Telling everyone what he said.
I told them to look at the top.
That was wrong.
Same with the second one.
And the third one.
This is the picture of the moon.
I was surprised.
3,000 people were surprised.
You were fooled, too.
Everyone was surprised.
You were surprised, too.
No no no no.
Not everyone was like that.
Oh, really?
Yamazaki wasn't like that.
Yamazaki was like, what?
You should've waited for me somewhere.
Really?
Because I'm an idiot.
I didn't even get hit, but Kappa failed.
What are you talking about?
I wanted you to hit me.
He kept coming down.
Like, who should I hit?
I think it was obvious.
He was in love.
There was a magic ring.
Fujiwara was there too.
Fujiwara gave me a pair of glasses.
I looked at it, and he was like, no.
I didn't understand why.
I thought he was waiting for me.
I was like, where is he?
Really?
Fujiwara was like, no.
I looked at him, and he was like, no.
I think it was obvious.
He was really angry.
I've never seen a Kappa fail face like that.
I've never seen a normal face.
I was surprised by the card thing.
But he wasn't next to you, was he?
He was definitely doing something weird.
I think he was excited.
At the end, he shook his hand like this.
To Yamazaki's Kappa field.
He went out like this.
He wanted you to take him home.
It was really amazing.
He came out like this.
It wasn't very interesting.
Is there anyone?
If you don't know, don't tell anyone.
I don't know how he disappeared.
I want you to tell me before he died.
He cut his stomach with a razor.
It wasn't a real razor.
He cut the membrane like this.
It was cut off.
It was moving like this.
What do you think happened?
He was beaten.
You're addicted to him.
I'm not addicted to him.
I'm just a little addicted.
That's enough.
Yesterday,
I went to see him.
There were a lot of people.
There was a guy who asked me to take a picture with him.
Yesterday,
Everyone wanted to go to the bathroom.
So I went to the bathroom.
It's far from the bathroom.
He was holding the camera all the time.
He asked me to take a picture with him.
I told him I was watching him.
He never let me take a picture with him.
Do you know why?
If you don't know, don't tell anyone.
I'll tell you.
If you're a real fan of me,
You should ask for a handshake rather than a picture.
I don't know.
It's okay.
If you really like me,
You should want to touch me first.
Right?
First of all,
I want to touch your body.
That's fan psychology.
And then,
The next is a picture.
You don't have to be a fan to take a picture of me.
I just want to show you.
I don't know.
What are you doing?
I'm so scared right now.
You're acting like a woman.
How can you say such a stupid thing?
This is an insult.
It's true.
Please take a picture of me.
I hate it.
Well, well, well.
Right?
What is it?
He is insensitive.
The tuna is your partner, right?
Come on.
Well, well, well.
I heard that something terrible has happened.
What is it?
Mr. Matsumoto, please tell me.
This is...
What is it?
Well, well, well.
When the audience heard it, they were surprised.
What happened?
Well, well, well.
Everyone panicked.
I don't care.
Why are you panicking?
What's wrong with you?
The audience, the cameraman, and Suga-chan are all here.
Suga-chan is here, too.
Only Irie-chan is left.
Why?
Everyone is here.
I want to protect you.
What's going on?
Well, well, well.
It's my butt.
My anus.
Everyone ran away.
What's wrong with your butt?
Well, well, well.
I don't know such details.
You were wondering what happened to Matsumoto's butt, right?
But when I asked what was going on, everyone was surprised.
I don't like it.
I'm embarrassed, too.
I won't tell you.
Tell me.
Tell me what's going on with your butt.
Well, well, well.
I'm not in the mood today.
I'll be the bad guy.
You can't be the bad guy.
Your butt is weird.
What's wrong with you?
Why do you want me?
Tell me.
What's going on with your anus?
Well, well, well.
I don't know what you're doing.
You can see the atmosphere of this audience.
I'm jealous of you saying that.
You're a fool.
I know that.
You were shaking your butt a lot.
That's right.
I'll tell you why I shook my butt.
I shook my butt many times.
I was thinking what to say while shaking my butt.
You shouldn't say that.
I know that.
If you say that, I'll...
It's okay.
You can ask me anything today.
Well, well, well.
It's okay.
Tell me.
Tell me what's going on with your butt.
My butt is...
It's a star shape.
It's half and half.
It's your fault.
Why did you shake your butt?
Why did I shake my butt?
Wait a minute.
I don't know what you're doing.
You were shaking your butt so much.
I thought you were holding something.
That's right.
What's wrong with you?
I was scared when I saw you.
I don't know what you're doing.
I thought you were holding something.
It's your fault.
Next.
This hand is next.
How many times have you done this?
I'm a professional.
I've been doing this for 17 years.
It's not here.
It's here.
The man with the sweetest voice in the entertainment world.
Thank you very much.
Just talking on the phone.
The other woman.
I want to be hugged by this person once.
Please tell me how to talk.
I see.
When a man is trying to impress a woman,
He wants to have fun with conversation.
He wants to compliment the other woman.
But this is a big mistake.
It doesn't matter what you say.
Is that so?
It's a woman's bio-rhythm.
There's a woman's...
When the woman drops a little,
It's the time when the woman is at ease.
I see.
I have a way of doing it.
I know that.
No, I don't need that.
Please tell me how to do it.
How to do it.
You're gonna stick it on, right?
I'll touch it a little bit.
Touch what?
Please tell me how to do it.
How should I say it?
Can you do a female role?
I'm the only one who can do it.
You've been doing only female roles recently.
You're a bastard!
What do you want me to do?
Women have weak ears.
Women who don't think much even if they're attacked by their ears.
Even Kimusume can do it.
That's just a word.
It's like blowing a breath into your ear.
In a conversation,
when a person wants to do it,
Do you understand?
Yes.
Hello?
What were you doing?
I was watching TV.
What TV were you watching?
I was watching a news program.
What kind of news program is it?
The one that Kume-san is talking about.
Like this?
Your face is funny.
If you do that in front of me,
it's not a face.
It's not a face. What are you talking about?
What is this?
Don't say that.
I thought you were tricked.
I said, try it.
You said, try it.
So you went home and told your wife to try it.
I had a hard time today.
If you do that,
I'll give you another bowl of rice.
Don't you think it's okay to be hugged like that?
I think it's okay.
Women have weak ears.
If you do that in front of me,
I'll understand.
But if you do that in front of me,
women are scary creatures.
Right? I remember that.
But you've never been hugged directly.
I just got it.
I got it the day before yesterday.
What is that?
It's the same sex.
I get it.
There are a lot of women here today.
I don't think I can laugh.
Really?
I'm serious.
But you're laughing a lot.
I'm laughing, but I'm laughing in my upper mouth.
You're stupid.
Right?
You're crazy.
In my lower mouth,
You're a old man.
Excuse me.
Yes.
May I?
You seem to have a lot of confidence in golf.
I don't have confidence.
My staff told me a while ago.
Yamazaki, me, and Kogoriko.
Four of us.
Can you do it alone and win?
He said he could win.
Me?
Yes.
I didn't say that.
Are you done talking?
Let's say you hit one.
I'll hit four.
You hit four.
What do you call that?
It's a cup in.
How many times did I hit it?
I hit it 16 times and got the same score.
Yes.
It was a par-4.
I said, can you do it?
You said, it's easy.
I got the information.
I didn't say that.
But you can win, right?
Which one?
You can win, but...
You guys...
I can't...
I can't lose to this guy.
That's true.
That's true, but...
It's okay, right?
It's okay.
Really?
I'll do it.
What?
A match.
A match?
Why a match?
It's four against one.
If you lose, you'll die.
What?
If you lose, the four of us will hold a knife and...
If you're still like that, I can run away, too.
If you grab it like this, I'll grab it.
I'll prepare a punishment like that.
What if you guys lose?
If the four of us lose, the four of us will do something.
Let's do that.
It's okay.
I'm glad you came to this match.
On the other hand, you're being made a fool of.
In order to tell the history of the instrument user,
a match that can never be written and a punishment game.
Sometimes it's a shame.
Sometimes it's a life-threatening skydiving.
A serious match where you throw away your pride and put your body on the line.
I'm sure many of you have even learned how to be moved.
Various challenges with courage.
There were so many early plannings that no one thought they would do.
And in the history of such a confrontation and punishment game,
I'm trying to write a new page.
Matsumoto, Yamazaki, and Kokoriko, who challenge Hamada, the master of golf.
Can we get emotional again in this confrontation?
I'm pretty moved.
Please look forward to it.
I'll give you a gift.
Yamazaki-kun.
I've never seen him before.
I'm going to write a new page in Hamada.
I want to drink while I'm at it.
Let's go.
Ha!
I've been living my life to the fullest.
I'll do my best.
Thank you for your hard work every day.
Da!
My favorite person more than anyone else!
Are you going to continue?
Ma!