This is the 5th year anniversary showdown between Kouhaku and Katsunen
In the past, we've had 12 showsdowns
That many?
This is the 5th showdown between Kouhaku and Katsunen
So you've been doing this for 5 years?
Yes
No matter what channel you watch, it's all about showdowns
We've been doing this for a long time
It's like this
If you lose, you have to wear underwear
That's what our producer Sugaka says
The 5th showdown between Kouhaku and Katsunen
This show is brought to you by these sponsors
We've done this 4 times in Kouhaku
Yes
White or white
This is strange
I've lost all of them
You've actually lost
This reminds me of something
The flow is fast
I am
Am I stupid?
It was popular
This is what happened in the past
This is the members of this year's show
Matsumoto-san
Let's look at the red team
What should I do?
You're a man
You're really persistent
You have to check before the show
You're wrong
You're a man
You made a mistake again
That's not what I meant
It's this
Please take care of me
This brother again
How many times do I have to tell you?
What about TRF?
I don't know TRF and Ryoko
What about Matsuda Seiko?
I don't know
I'll do that
I think the red team is weak
Is the man stronger?
Do you know the story of Go Hiromi?
Koudashin
The back of the father
I know the back of the father
I don't know the song
Let's listen
My son
He's talking
Sabu-chan can sing anything
TOKIO
What is this?
I don't know
Let's listen to TOKIO
You have to go out
I can't think of this
Only you
That was good
I have a plan
Shirofumi Tori
Yajirobe
I think
If it's like this, it's better to include Geisha Girls
I don't know
It's your turn
This year is especially difficult
Difficult
I don't know
Let's listen to your opinion
Why do you always ask me?
Which one?
Me?
I'm Shiro
I'm Shiro too
No
This is Shiro
There are too many people who don't know
Even if you say Shiro, you don't know the song
Everyone knows
It can't be helped
Let's decide something simple
A game?
Let's decide
I prepared something
I remember Badminton for 24 hours
It's a little blue
Anything is fine
What should we do?
Let's do Kero Kero Pick
Okay
It's easy
Really?
Let's do this
This?
What is that?
You have to put the ball in
How many times?
Once?
The first three times
Let's do that
I'll go first
You're good
This
Stop it
It's weird
No
There were two
I know
It's weird
Let's do this
Okay
You can do this
You do that
Wait
What are you going to do with this?
Even if you jump
If you do this
The person who threw the ball has to shoot
That's right
If you miss, it's over
Okay
I'm getting nervous
Let's do this
I don't have to do this
If you do it, it's over
That's right
He's not in the mood
I told you to shoot
You're going to shoot
I can't do this
You have to do it
Wait
I have to shoot
I'm scared
It's here
It's definitely here
Why
It's here
It's definitely going to come next time
Thank you
But I'm really bad at games
Why
I don't know
I don't know if it's red or not
I tried to shoot
I don't know if I'm stupid
Then you should go home
But I really don't know
That game is weird
I've been thinking about it for 30 minutes
It's weird
You said it
It's better to float
You can shoot
But if I suddenly get shot, I won't be shot back
The moment you came out, I was like
I was scared
I won't be shot back
I really want to avoid it this year
Who's going to decide?
The judge?
And the phone?
The phone?
The judge?
The one in the front
No, the one in the audience
The one in the audience
I can't control it
I'm going to ask the audience
Why are you asking the audience
I'm not happy if you ask the audience
Do you know the person in the audience?
I don't know
I'm going to eat this
But
You saw the results
He's wearing white
It's hard to wear white
NHK is controlling it
They might say it's not good this year
It's possible
But it's not good to wear a Takuro Yoshida
It's not good to wear a Takuro Yoshida
I'll dress up as Takuro Yoshida
But you can tell by your nose
No
What do you mean by your nose?
I don't know
I'm angry
What?
It's not good
What's not good?
Even when I decide
I don't know Matsumoto
Why did you say it twice?
I'm emphasizing it
They are all
Matsumoto, you should lose
The atmosphere is like at home
Matsumoto knows it
Matsumoto doesn't know it
That's annoying
What should I do?
Why did you say it once?
It's really annoying
I don't know
I'm really weak
The song is different
I did the billiards with Machi
I'm really weak
I'm really really good
You can't show your strength in the actual performance
It's amazing
You're making excuses
It's not good
You can't show your strength in the actual performance
That's why
I heard that you were really weak
I can't show my strength in the actual performance
But I don't make excuses
I don't have any skills
You're going to do the billiards for the special
I'm going to do it tomorrow
I did it for the special too
I did it with Tanaka Misako
You did it because you wanted to kiss Tanaka Misako?
If it wasn't for that, I wouldn't have done it
I didn't kiss her
I don't know if you have bad breath
Really?
I'm not saying that it stinks
I've never talked at this distance
It happens sometimes
Right?
Who was it?
It was an actress who was said to be pretty
Did it stink?
It was really really bad
Who was it?
It was a yakuza
There was a monster living in my mouth
There was a yakuza
There was an office
I was surprised
When I was talking, a young lady came out
A young lady?
Wait a minute
This is
Happen
I was surprised
I'm glad I was human
If I was a dog, I'd be like
I have to promote the opening next week
My super car
What super car?
Camaro
It's matte black
It's like a super model
This is the only car in the world
I see
I decided to sell this
I'm not selling it
If there's anyone who wants this
Next week
The location hasn't been decided yet
It'll be on air
Please come
Bring something
If you don't decide
Something worth 100,000 yen
For example, someone bought this for 100,000 yen
That's fine
Or a photo of my room
100,000 yen
If you think it's worth 100,000 yen
If it's just standing
What?
Of course you have to get it with a polaroid
That's right
You can dress up
But you can't show it
Why?
It's my Camaro
Let's go downtown together
Wait a minute
I'm the judge
That's all
Anything is fine
It's 100,000 yen
Of course you can buy something
Something expensive
But it's fine
If you're over 18
If you have a license
If you don't have a license
You have to give it to someone
This is from me
It'll be on air on the 25th
It's a Christmas present
That's great
Let's take it home
It'll be fine
It's so warm
What is this warmth?
This
It's so warm
It's from me
What about you?
What?
What is it?
Camaro
That's great
It's a Christmas present
What is this?
What?
What is that?
I won't show it
What about you?
What will you show?
Why?
What do you want me to show?
The pistol you put in your bag
Do you really think that?
Do you really think that I put it in my bag?
It's possible
Is it possible?
It's fine
It's your Christmas present
You're amazing
I don't need a new car
I have a new car
I have money
That's not a car
That's my cousin's dad
My cousin's dad looks like this
It's shining
I'll put a magic on a witch
That's not a bad idea
I'll think about it next year
What is the most expensive thing in your house?
The most expensive thing?
It's my car
How much is it?
It's not that expensive
No
I won't tell you
I want to join
Sure
Bring the car I'm in
I'll lose my legs
It's cool
The car I'm in
I'll pull it
I'm not pulling it
I'll pull a dog and a cat
I won't pull it
I have to do it once in a while
I'll do it
Who are you cheering for?
A dog and a cat
If you kill it, it's over
I'm not killing it
Even if I pull it, it won't move
It's going to bite me
In the morning, a bird
When I get off the car, a deer is waiting
It's waiting around here
And it's like this
Okay, okay
In the UK, they have a violin
It's a human trait
Sometimes it goes like this
I have to show my stubborn father
Matsumoto is saying a lot of things
What did you say?
I said a lot
It's not like that
What did you say?
I said I don't have enough rice
You can't say that
I said I don't have enough rice next year
What is that?
Let's take a look
I don't have enough rice
I don't have enough water
I don't have enough glasses next year
This is interesting
I don't have enough glasses
There are a lot of glasses in the shop
They all disappeared
All the couples who are on the road
I'm looking for it because it fell
Why are you walking around there?
This program is sponsored by