The number of accidents that have occurred in the past 5 years has completely risen, and it is actually a fraction of 1 in 49 seconds.
They are having fun driving on the table, but they are always next to each other.
Hello?
A middle-aged man's car and a car in the intersection meet at the crossroad.
The traffic accident caused by the mobile phone while driving.
The car in the intersection was hit by a car in the intersection.
A few years ago, I was told not to use my mobile phone while driving.
I thought it was stupid to use my mobile phone while driving.
But it was my own idea.
An accident in the middle of the intersection.
The car in the intersection was hit by a car in the intersection.
I thought it was stupid to use my mobile phone while driving.
It was very cold that day.
The driver wanted to warm up his body, so he drove the car to the corn soup in the neighborhood.
But the distance between the neighborhood and the corn soup was a dead end.
The car was blown away by the impact of the accident.
Sometimes the car was blown away by the impact of the accident.
The car in the intersection was hit by a car in the intersection.
The driver was exhausted because of the work he had to do the day before.
As a result, his mouth looked red.
On that day, the driver was blind.
Before the accident, I made a mistake by looking at the green light and parsley.
I should have stopped the car and taken a nap.
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
But I couldn't do it.
He made a mistake by looking at the green light and parsley.
It was a sudden accident because he stepped on the brakes unexpectedly.
The car was blown away by the impact of the accident.
The driver was blind because of the sea milk.
The driver was back home, but he was already late.
The sea milk was very shiny.
The sea milk reflected in the light and jumped into my eyes.
I thought it was a delicious oyster.
I was taken away by the sea milk.
The sea milk didn't hit the oyster, but the car.
The hungry young driver.
His hunger reached its peak.
At that time.
It's a set of young steaks and young birds.
He was distracted by the waitress who jumped in.
It was time for the old steering wheel to avoid the collision with the shellfish.
It was a tragedy due to the youth of young steaks and young birds.
The weight of the steaks was weighed, but the weight of life was not weighed.
anger
The scientific story of the freakin' car, I looked up, and it was inounced as a truck with a cart in copy.
Yeah.
It's a overcome, but it's probably gonna to happen.
The driver
She kept an eye on the wine at the table.
It was a sad story about eating the whole bottle of wine.
The wine was sweet, but Chico ended up with a bitter taste.
At this time of the year when there are many events such as the New Year's party, sleep driving is the most common.
The driver was attacked by a water horse at the end of the year when he was tired of working over and over again.
It was a big accident that a moment of sleep became a life-and-death experience.
Only for a moment...
I don't usually sleep well.
I don't sleep well.
I don't sleep well at all.
When I get sleepy, I wake up with gum or candy.
But at that time, I was just tired.
I'm sorry.
Because of this accident, he got into a fight with another car.
And he crashed into a coffee cup at the end of the drug.
There are many other coffee cups, but there is no life in them.
In addition, this accident also happened.
This is the corner where sponge cake and glass line up.
One young man had an accident on this day as well.
Yes, I did speed up.
The speedometer needle was at a low speed.
But it was faster than I thought.
But it was really fast.
It was really fast.
It was faster than I thought.
I'm glad I was saved by the sponge cake.
I don't want to see anything.
Fortunately, the sponge cake didn't have a cushion.
The driver was saved.
He was distracted by the speedometer.
Thank you for waiting.
That was a perfect parking spot for the driver.
I only stopped for 5 minutes.
Why did you have to put curry on my car?
I just put curry on the rice.
I was hungry.
I didn't think the car would be a rice.
He had to put curry on the rice for only 5 minutes.
The yellow curry and the yellow body of the car attracted him.
He was surprised.
I was surprised.
I suddenly slipped.
After that, I put my car in the car.
I was surprised.
It was a big accident.
It was the biggest accident in my life.
The cold reality of the accident can be felt from the cold ice.
It was exactly the Mimocore disaster.
And finally, the waitress brought this dish.
It caused the biggest accident in the history of table accidents.
The sauce was poured on the hamburger on the table.
The driver's vision was completely taken away by the rising steam.
I don't know what's going on.
Suddenly the front of my eyes turned white.
After that, it was a big bang.
And the drivers who were driving around were also sacrificed.
The car was hit by a heavy accident.
It finally developed into a third world with a menu.
There is no last order for traffic accidents.
Roppongi
Matsumatsu-san, you always have Roppongi in your heart.
Yes, I do.
Please tell me the correct way to deal with a black man who is taller than 2 meters.
I said it clearly.
A black man of 2 meters can't win.
This is not a problem of losing.
But they are very confident that they have a big body.
If you have a big body, you will be weak.
Really?
How do you make it?
For example, a black man of 2 meters came from the other side.
The other side knows that they have a big body.
That's right.
How tall are you?
If you ask me.
When you go to buy clothes.
Don't say that.
They are aware of their 2 meters.
They only think about me.
On the contrary, a black man of 2 meters is very cautious.
That's right.
So they take advantage of the weakness of the other side.
How do you do that?
The other side is aware of their 2 meters.
The other side is aware of their 3 meters.
That's right.
How do you do that?
What?
The other side is aware of their 3 meters.
That's your feeling.
The other side is different.
This is Hama-chan.
I said something stupid.
Why is it stupid?
I understand your feeling.
But the other side is 1 meter 60 cm or 70 cm.
There is no dream that doesn't come true.
No, no.
Dreams are like that.
Absolutely.
Right?
For example, if you want to become a cream bread, you can.
That's absolutely right.
You can.
Why can't I become a cream bread?
I can't.
You can.
Why can't I become a cream bread?
What?
Absolutely.
I can't.
No, no.
No matter how many times I look at you, I can't.
You wanted to enter Yoshimoto and become popular, didn't you?
Absolutely.
I understand that.
Your dream came true.
That's stupid.
That and this are different.
What you want to sell and what you want to become are different.
You had a dream, didn't you?
Dreams are dreams.
Yes, yes.
It came true.
No, no.
It was good that it came true.
That's right.
Isn't it?
Then let's go to the next dream.
That's right.
So you had a dream that you wanted to succeed in the entertainment world.
It came true.
Your next goal is to become a cream bread.
Why?
Absolutely.
This is amazing.
It's going down.
It doesn't have to be that fluffy.
It doesn't have to be fluffy.
It doesn't have to be hard or fluffy.
It doesn't have to be delicious or sweet.
It doesn't have to be a cream bread.
It doesn't have to be as much cream as you think.
What should I do with the poison?
It doesn't have to be a cream bread.
If it doesn't work, it will work.
Tell me.
What should I do to become a cream bread?
Well, well.
Yes?
Yes, yes.
Then, let's go to Yoshimoto now.
Let's go to Yoshimoto and do our best.
Mr. Hamada, what would you say if I asked you what I should do to become a cream bread?
Do you understand that?
I don't understand.
You say good things in your own way.
But that kid says good things in his own way.
I don't understand.
I don't want you to force me to become a cream bread.
What are you talking about?
Cream bread is your dream.
No, no.
You're the one who says it.
I never said I wanted to become a cream bread.
That's your dream.
I'm not like that.
What?
It's your dream.
No, you said it.
I said it because you said it for the first time.
I didn't say it.
You said it.
I think it's strange.
I don't want to become a cream bread at all.
I said I wanted to become a bread maker, but you said you wanted to become a cream bread.
I wonder why.
But I don't want you to give up.
That's what I'm saying.
Do your best.
Can I become a cream bread?
No.
I think you can do it.
Cream bread?
But when I become a cream bread, I can't do it in a convenience store.
Don't you want to become a cream bread?
You don't say anything.
I don't want to take you out with me.
But when that happens, I don't know.
When that happens, I give up on my dream of becoming a two-meter.
I don't know if I want to become a jam bread.
Then I can join the cream bread and jam bread.
What about your jam bread?
I can't accept it.
I'm small and I don't know what to do.
When humans lose their eyesight, they wear glasses.
How do wild animals lose their eyesight?
It's basically the same as humans.
What do you mean?
I don't rely on animals.
That's right.
So even if I'm a tiger...
No, no, no.
I'm asking you how you're going to take care of yourself.
You're on my side, aren't you?
If you lose your eyesight, you're going to do this, aren't you?
No, no, no.
I'm going to grab it and go.
I don't know.
Let's do that.
When you lose your eyesight.
Humans put on glasses and make contact.
What's the difference?
The difference is that you have to see it up close.
I don't know if it's moving or not, so I'll do it.
I'll just look at it like this.
Hey, what are you doing?
Why do you have to go?
So there's no way to fix it.
There is a way to fix it.
You have to see it up close.
That means there's no way to fix it.
That's right.
In that sense, it's like wearing glasses.
You're doing it right.
I'm not wearing glasses.
I'm telling you to do it.
You're wearing glasses.
I'm not wearing glasses.
Have you seen it?
I've seen it.
Where?
I've seen it in pictures.
There's no picture here.
Have you ever seen it up close?
I've seen it up close.
I've seen a picture of a bust-up.
A bust-up?
I've seen a picture of this.
I'm not wearing glasses.
You're doing it right.
If you have a picture of someone who's doing this all of a sudden, it's no use.
Is that true?
It's a sports type.
There's a picture of a sports type.
You're wearing it all the way here.
Sports type.
No, no, no. There's rubber on the back.
Then you can see it.
There's a piece of paper on top of the rubber.
Are you stupid?
You're wearing glasses. Don't look down on me.
I'm sorry.
Matsumoto-san,
I heard you know how to make the most fashionable muffler this year.
Please tell me how to make it.
It's fashionable this year.
Really?
Please tell me.
Everyone wants to know how to make a muffler, right?
Do you know how to make a muffler?
I know.
I know, I know.
For example...
Try it on.
How do I do it?
Normally?
How do you want it now?
Is it okay?
If it's easy.
For the time being...
Something like this.
Or...
You have one.
I have one.
The one you just made is the standard, right?
This usually goes round and round.
That's right.
So...
It's a new breath.
It's a muffler, but it's funny to blow your breath.
This year's muffler is...
Like this.
I can't put it on since I left the house.
It was really bad just now.
You were really far away.
It was like an octopus gun that I washed in an instant.
No, no.
That's why you should wear it this year.
What do you mean you don't like it?
I'm sweating.
This is scary.
This is going to be popular this year.
That's why everyone should wear it this year.
I'm waiting for the bus from the station to the house.
My fingers are already in when I'm at the entrance.
Just take it off.
Because it's fashionable.
That's one of your differences.
No, no.
It's fashionable to have a lot of blood vessels.
So you don't get confused.
I don't get confused.