I can't do it because I'm a kid.
I'm happy.
Who's the star?
It's a signing match!
When you see this, you think,
what are they doing?
Who's the star?
It's a signing match.
The star appears?
The star appears.
Is there a star other than us?
Let's introduce the star.
Please come out.
This is a star.
This is quite a star.
I was a little excited a while ago.
This is quite a narcissist.
Nar-chan is in it.
If you have time, look in the mirror.
This is also a star.
This person is the producer.
I'm not the producer.
Harajuku
First of all, Saito san.
Stand up.
Why, stand up.
It's quite small.
Will it be able to hear?
I see.
It's very good that you can hear it.
Oh!
What does it mean?
It's so hard.
I have a lot of signs.
I thought it was not funny at all, but when I looked down, it was much more intense than I imagined.
I came to see this star.
Let's try to hit the Heipo.
Look at me!
This Heipo is popular.
This place is lonely.
There are too many people.
Where is this place?
This is Yotsuya 3-chome.
Is this written as Marusho?
Before Marusho, Heipo and Otomo...
It is written as Shinjuku Shinshu in Otomo.
I think this is a bit painful.
It is Harajuku Shinshu.
Yes, it is Harajuku Shinshu.
It is not Harajuku at all.
I thought it was Hinakamon.
I was told that this is a Heipo store.
What is Hatsurainichi?
Hatsurainichi is the first Heipo store in the city.
I think this is a foreigner.
I think this is a Hong Kong person.
I thought it was written as Saen.
What is this?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Heipo first.
This is Heipo.
If there is one person, the Shinshu of the military,
it continues, right?
Please do your best.
It continued.
When one person comes, everyone is embarrassed, even if they want it.
I see.
I don't want it.
Oh!
It's lined up at Otomo-kun's place!
Abe-kun here is a little...
What is this feeling?
This feeling.
Oh, it's gone!
Oh!
Wakai Onna has gone!
Wakai Onna has gone to Heipo's place!
What!
Why?
It's like a set-up, it's like a set-up, you know!
I'm used to it, and the conversation is also...
What's going on?
Please move Otomo a little.
He's a big friend to me, but...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
I'm lonely.
No, really, no...
It's so scary, you know.
He doesn't have any students.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
What's your name?
I'm Heipou.
Heipou?
What's your name?
I don't know.
Do you know this?
Are you a high school student?
I'm Heipou.
I'm sorry. Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
What's your name?
I'm Heipou.
Are you a high school student?
Yes.
What's your name?
I'm Odama.
Are you a high school student?
What's your name?
I'm Odama.
He is a high school student.
This old man is curious too.
I wonder if this old man will cut it.
What are you doing in a place like this?
You don't need it?
John.
John from Katakana.
Why Katakana?
What?
There is a young man.
A little.
Let's go.
What is this?
Do you know what an automobile is?
I thought I saw something.
I don't know.
How many did you cut?
Six or seven.
Eight.
About eight.
I want to know how to cut.
Eight for men.
Eight for women.
What is the sign?
How to do it.
I put my face in front and sign.
Heipo is not understood.
It's a sign.
I wrote it myself and said,
I'm sorry.
If you think about it in that way,
This is Otomo's victory.
Yes.
Heipo lost.
What should I do for Otomo?
Sign for Heipo.
This is Spongy. He is a human sensor.
First of all, you have to clean Hamada's car.
First of all, you have to wash your body.
Come on!
Get on!
If you come here, I'll pull you.
Come on!
It's a new car.
Please use a lot of water.
Come on!
Next time, let's go to your car.
That's right.
I'm happy.
Do you have Spongy?
I don't have it.
You have to clean it up.
You shouldn't be so angry.
A lot of dolphins are coming.
I'm getting drunk.
I'm an alien.
I'm wearing a tan.
Ladies and gentlemen.
It's really late today.
What time is it now?
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
It's 9 o'clock.
This is probably the slowest time since the musical started.
I'm really sorry.
This guy is yesterday.
You are yesterday.
That's right.
This guy was shooting in Aoyama yesterday.
Then the old man said,
Where are you shooting?
He came by bicycle.
There are many people like Kyoko Kishida and Ojinga.
I'm sorry.
Everyone apologized to me.
What are you doing?
What is this?
You are really short-tempered.
No, I'm not.
You are really in the way.
If you say that, we will apologize to you.
Everyone was in the way.
I'm not in the way.
I passed by lightly.
I said,
Come on.
You said,
What are you doing?
After that, Kyoko Kishida came to me and said,
Were you a bad guy?
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
I followed Kyoko Kishida.
Are you stupid?
If I liked you, I would have followed you.
You were sleeping.
You were sleeping next to Kyoko Kishida.
I was angry.
If Kyoko Kishida was angry,
It would be a big deal.
So Kyoko Kishida said,
Stop it.
You are a good person.
I don't want to see that kind of thing.
What?
I used to be with 30 Yakuza.
You are a bad guy.
Yes.
After that.
No.
It's beautiful here.
What?
What are you doing?
I don't want to see that kind of thing.
So let's stop it.
I'm angry because I'm a talent.
Is that so?
When I went to the convenience store the other day,
I said,
Don't you only go to EMPM?
I don't care if you say that.
That statement is a lie.
Why do I have to go to the convenience store?
Why do I have to go to EMPM?
I don't want to see that kind of thing.
You two are in line.
One is here.
If this is EMPM,
I will go to EMPM.
You're making a declaration.
Well.
It's a lot of things.
Don't make a big deal out of it.
If you hit him,
The newspaper will come out.
You hit him, right?
I don't know that.
That happened to me.
I got angry with a loud voice.
Let's follow it for the time being.
But if you keep saying that,
I'm going to hit you.
That's the attitude.
Don't say that.
When you got angry,
I was here.
I was talking to him.
Why are you talking to him?
Do you want to go to EMPM?
Why?
Why do you want to go to EMPM?
I'm sorry.
I'm going to EMPM again.
I'm going to EMPM.
You're stupid.
I called him for about two hours yesterday.
You're lying.
You were shooting on Takeshita Street yesterday, right?
That's right.
I was shooting.
It's a goods store.
I'm running a goods store.
In Harajuku.
Go there next time.
When I came to Harajuku yesterday,
Did you enter Noripee House?
I'm a fan.
I'm not a fan.
The top of my store was Noripee House.
I thought I'd take a look.
There's no one.
There were only three staff members.
It's because I was shooting downstairs.
Why are you doing such a horror movie?
Why are you so good today?
Why didn't you come on Sunday?
It's because I left my goods.
No, no, no.
I'm shooting downstairs.
I'm shooting downstairs, and there's a lot of people.
There's a staircase next to it.
If you go up there, it's Noripee House.
If you shoot like that,
What are you going to do next?
After that, we went up.
There's a lot of people on my floor.
The audience is flowing.
If you come out a little bit,
There's Noripee goods.
Why isn't there anyone?
I just made a mistake with the staff and the audience.
No, no, no.
I couldn't get it properly.
Noripee's trainer.
I'll buy it and sell it right away.
Why?
I can't get it at the store.
I'll buy it right away.
Don't say that.
Noripee is good.
What are you doing?
Noripee's...
Go!
You're here.
When I followed Takumatsu,
You said a lot of things.
You've changed.
I can't do anything, so I'll do it for you.
That's not good.
Is that so?
You're tough.
I followed that.
I didn't do anything.
Takumatsu.
Noripee didn't do anything either.
What are you talking about?
Don't say that.
Stop peeping.
You've been saying that all the time.
I'm in trouble when I'm with you at work.
What are you going to do then?
If you say Kanapi.
If you say that, I'll hit you.
That's right.
Oh, that's right.
I'm going to block it tonight.
I came to the show the other day.
And when I was with you,
You blocked it, didn't you?
I blocked it.
Kenya was like this.
This program is not a program with two episodes.
The big-necked Taisho and the good-for-nothing Taisho.
You're number one, aren't you?
You've got two episodes, haven't you?
Isn't it a program that Kenya shot two episodes?
That's what he said.
No, it's not.
Well, you're watching, aren't you?
That's what he said.
He's running away.
He's sleeping.
That's right.
Everyone's angry.
I'm not angry.
Kenya was smiling.
Kenya doesn't know what's going on.
I'm really sorry.
That's not what I meant.
What do you mean?
I want you to laugh.
I really wanted you to laugh.
Kenya is like this.
Oh, my God.
I don't want you to laugh.
What is it?
If you said that, I wouldn't say that.
I just said Kenya was smiling.
I have something to tell you.
Little by little, the showdown.
There's nothing to bet on right now, is there?
That's right.
If you stop betting and just get a penalty.
Why?
What are you doing?
Why can't I get a penalty?
Don't say that.
That's because you said too much bad things about people.
You're the one who decided that.
What do you think about time?
Kouhaku.
It's a story from before.
Kouhaku is fine, but it hasn't been announced who's going to come out yet.
The members.
What are you going to do?
If you lose, you'll be buried with someone or someone else.
What's so sad about that?
Kouhaku.
What happens after Kouhaku is over?
It's coming. It's coming. It's coming.
Why can't I come out?
That means the one who loses will come out, right?
Don't say that.
There's that thing about Tsumo.
Shindeshi Kensa.
I have to go there.
How tall are you?
It's already decided. I'm definitely going to come out.
No, that's why.
Don't say that.
I'm really in trouble.
How many centimeters do you have left? I don't have enough.
If you lose, you'll be buried with someone or someone else.
I'm that.
I don't really want to be a sumo wrestler.
Where is this in Nagano Prefecture? Hijiri-yama?
Yes.
I went to a training camp. It was very cold and I had a cold.
It's painful when your nose is clogged.
Actually, there's a way to fix that.
If you put a rod around your nose, your nose will go through.
That's absolutely true.
It stinks.
So it's around here, right?
If it's clogged here, you can sleep like this.
If it's clogged here, you can do this.
If it's clogged on the left, you can look this way.
No, if you do this, it will clog here.
If you sleep here, it will clog here again.
No, that's why.
If it's clogged here, look this way.
You can't do that until morning.
I can't sleep while I'm doing that.
You can't sleep at all.
It's true.
You'll get sick.
No, I won't get sick.
Only your nose is clogged.
Here?
It's clogged here.
That's what I'm saying.
It's yesterday's problem.
I don't care about this.
Well, sometimes I look in the mirror.
This guy is crazy.
He's crazy.
Hama-chan, please tell us how you felt when Akiko Wada took your lips.
I've seen it.
I'll leave it to Akiko.
She was doing push-ups on a live broadcast.
I was caught by that guy.
I was like, what?
It stinks.
This hand that came out of nowhere.
It's like it's going to explode.
The hand of that guy.
It's like he's killing Oyama.
It's like he's going to die.
That guy.
But if that guy does it seriously,
I can't resist it.
And the pants.
I'll hold it down with my legs.
I'll take it off.
Wait!
I can't resist it.
It's a little thin.
I took it off in one shot.
It's like a brother's dog.
It's dangerous.
I'm wearing a hat.