The next defendant, Heipo, please come forward.
That's not possible.
The defendant, Heipo.
He is a child-treatment team selector, but he has been sentenced to 2 years in prison for his misconduct.
Even now, it is clear that the thinness of the punishment is causing a lot of trouble to the people.
The victims' strong hopes have led to the third and even thinner punishment being decided.
I'm scared!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Prosecutor Hamada, please present your evidence.
Yes!
As in other trials, we have a VTR of the many evil deeds of the Heipou.
First, please look at this.
Yes, yes, yes!
It's the Heipou-sama's bird!
Yay! Heipou-san!
Let's take a picture together!
Yes, yes, that's fine!
Hey, Pou!
Hey, Pou has been on TV a lot lately.
The girls in the city are foolish, but recently she has been able to talk to celebrities and she is very popular.
She's so popular. There's nothing I can do.
Please listen to this news.
Hello, this is Maria. I want to meet with Hey, Pou. Please call me when you think about it.
What is this?
That's right, it's Yamada Maria-chan
In the previous Heipou trial, Heipou didn't know Yamada Maria at all, even though he had met her before
And because of that incident, he was able to talk to Yamada Maria on the phone
Isn't that amazing, Heipou?
This is the voice of a woman who is completely in love. Maria-chan seems to have fallen for me.
It's different from being on TV.
What are you saying? It has nothing to do with TV. This is the result of the attraction of my men. You don't understand the gai.
Heipo, who was so excited that he was about to lose his voice.
I've been invited to a date by Maria-chan.
There might be an electric shock soon.
You're a fool.
And a few days later, the servant was having a meeting.
Hey, Heipo. What happened to Maria-chan after that?
Of course, I met her. It was so much fun.
Hey Po, isn't it amazing?
I'm jealous.
It's really good, isn't it?
Leave it to me.
However, as a joke, Hey Po was invited to the stage of the appearance of Maria Yamada.
Please watch from the audience seat.
Maria-chan.
President, I would like to make an appointment for this incident.
Understood. Please enter the showroom.
This is from Producer Suga.
The VTR you just saw was a perfect example of reality.
I asked the people at the agency after that.
Apparently, he went to the dressing room after the show ended.
I see.
I said, I have to say hello to Maria.
When I said, good work, good work, Maria-chan said, good work, see you later.
She didn't say that to anyone else.
It was a very cool situation.
She said she left with a bouquet of flowers.
Is that a fact?
That is a fact.
But why did you lie in front of everyone, even though you had such a relationship?
Well, because Maria-chan said she wanted to see me and called me.
No, no, no.
I'd like to...
You're a student, right?
No, no, that's not it.
But you said you wanted to go on a date, right?
No, no, normally when you go on a date, you're in a position where you can't see the other two.
No, no, no.
You're acting as if you're alone.
I've always emphasized that I'd meet her alone.
That's completely a lie.
You've never met her alone, right?
Well...
After that...
You haven't!
I've been in a lot of loose calls with Maria-chan.
It's a bit of a no-go.
But, well, Tane-san is busy.
You're not being treated as an opponent, right?
The stage is also a subject. I have a lot of them.
Do you go into those loose calls?
I do sometimes.
Why do you say those loose calls in such a strong way?
There is a voice of a woman who wants to go on a date, right?
Ah, there is.
It was that kind of voice. This one, I definitely have to buy.
That kind of voice? Do you know it?
Of course I know it.
I know it.
No, this person is a very good person.
The story of the first girl
This is the story of the time when Heipo and Suga introduced the girls to their workmates
Hey, it's fun today
I wonder what kind of girl will come
And then the workmate appeared
Sorry, I can't come alone today
Why? If I do that, I'll be the only one to get burned!
He's confused about something unexpected, but he doesn't know what he's doing.
Suga-chan is also cool.
Garth! Why are you so flustered?
You're so flustered and cool!
I'm fine today, so you do your best!
I'll be quiet!
Thank you, Heipo!
Heipo is very sincere. The three of them are waiting for the girl.
It seems like she hasn't come yet. Then I'll drink a little and wait.
That's right. Then I'll have a Tio Pepe. Please give me a Tio Pepe.
What? What is a Tio Pepe?
What is it, Heipo? Don't you know what a Tio Pepe is?
A Tio Pepe is a dried cherry drink.
I didn't know at all.
Then, give me a Tio Pepe too.
After a few minutes.
Ah, this is Tio Pepe.
Hey, Heipo, you're not even a
Saku-Saku, are you okay?
Of course I'm okay!
What is this?
This is too hard for me!
I don't need this anymore!
Tio Pepe is...
Then, the two girls who were waiting for him appeared.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
The two of them were model-like beauties.
When Heipo saw them, he was like...
Oh, isn't that nice?
Let me introduce you. This is Mr. Suga.
Hello, I'm Suga.
I'm Heipo from the world.
Please come this way.
What a surprise! Heipo forgot his promise and started to make a girl all by himself.
And then...
Everyone, I have a very good sake. Would you like to try it?
Wow! I want to try it!
Excuse me, could I have a Tio Pepe?
Tio Pepe? What is Tio Pepe?
Tio Pepe is a dried jelly. It's very delicious.
Wow, Heipou-san is so smart!
He's so quick to get angry.
After that, Heipou was always in the middle of the drinking party, and he didn't leave the girl's side.
He was always so sluggish.
And after the drinking party, when Ichido left the bar...
What a bad face!
Mom, you know what's going on, right?
If you know, then hurry and go home!
Having said that, Heiko disappeared into the city at night.
That's so sassy!
What is he, anyway?
I'm always angry.
I see.
And then, he was a tall, pretty boy.
That's true.
And on the way home, he said,
Gassu, we're adults, right?
Yes, we are.
If you're adults, think about it properly!
Bye!
I was like, what the hell is this?
And then, the girl was living in Suginami or something in a taxi.
She was supposed to go drinking next, but she suddenly decided to go to that apartment in a taxi.
And then, she said, Excuse me, driver, Suginami, please.
And then, I don't know if she was lighting up or not.
So the girl said, Sorry, Sachi-san, my brother is coming from the country. I'm sorry for today.
He got off the car and took a taxi.
Excuse me.
He took a high-speed train and said,
Please take me to Oimachi.
Do you like big women?
Yes.
I like people who are about 170 cm tall.
Mr. Motoko Obayashi is a serious type.
Wow!
Really.
How many are there in the average?
I think there are about 160.
Then there are probably no 160.
There are definitely no 160.
I killed 150 people.
After that, you went home without anything, right?
Actually, I was waiting for a long time.
What?
I thought I would come back to see Mr. Heipo again, so I went out once and came back again.
This was a secret to Mr. Sugasa.
I see.
You can't do anything if you go back.
I didn't come out after all.
You didn't ping-pong?
I thought I wouldn't like it if a strange person came out.
I don't like weird people coming out, but you're weird.
This is a meeting of a program that trains new entertainers.
Saito-san, I'm thinking of having the new entertainers enter the comic contest.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, doesn't that sound interesting?
Then let's contact the entertainers right away.
Let's go!
Wait a minute! You guys are really boring people!
What are you going to do now?
We're going to secretly register you for a comic contest and announce it in the studio!
It's a prank! A prank!
That's right, Heppo-san! That's definitely going to work!
With this, we can see the artist's serious reaction and this time it's a prank!
But everyone, please don't get caught.
I'm sure of it!
With the idea of the paper, we decided to do a prank.
And on the day of the show...
Everyone, today is a prank, so be careful not to get caught!
It's okay! It's perfect!
The staff members who were preparing for the prank,
and the new entertainer who was the target of the prank,
were about to enter the studio.
At that time...
Uwaaa! It's late again!
Ah, Saito-san! Good morning!
Thank you for today!
Thank you!
Yes, yes, I'm asking you for a favor.
I'm expecting you guys.
Because you're going to be in the Kenyan Comedian Contest.
Eeeh!? Really!?
No way!
You said it...
Yes, yes, that's right. You were surprised, right?
It's the Kenyan Comedian Contest.
And, the prank that you will announce on the show...
Ah, I said it!
Heipo himself said the prank that he said before the show.
I'm sorry, but please don't tell anyone about this. Please don't tell anyone.
Heipo stopped everyone from saying that he said the prank.
It's not like he was not good at acting in the show.
Ah, don't say it!
The court will now decide the witness.
Understood. The witness, please enter.
This is the writer's personal report.
Is this the truth?
It's the truth.
I've expressed it a bit softly in the video, but...
I didn't realize that I had been pranking him.
I was talking about the Manzai Concours forever.
HOOOOOO!
I noticed it on my way.
I was pulling it a little.
I noticed that and I tried to break it.
OOOOOOOO!
I see.
I want to kill you.
This person is really stupid.
It's harsh.
You didn't notice this at all.
Well, since you're human, your lips slip.
I think it's okay to say it.
There's a place where you can't slip.
It's a place where you can't say it.
I think that's where you need to ask the comedians to understand and react.
It's not like that!
You destroyed a whole film!
If you say it more, you might have destroyed a whole group of comedians.
That's the most troublesome thing for comedians.
There are some people who should say it.
Huh?
No, no, no.
You're still talking back.
This is a bit annoying.
There's one more.
There was a series called the Limit.
The Limit of the Cold Chinese.
It was a secret show at the restaurant.
Before the show, we went to check on the restaurant.
How crowded the restaurant was.
When the director of the North Korean movie was going to the police, he appeared.
When the store manager came, he said,
Today, I look forward to working with you.
This is also a ruined pattern.
Oh, I see.
He said such a thing.
Why?
I should have said hello to you 50 years ago.
No, no, no.
I think it's fine to be angry, but I think you know that you have to be silent about the blue flower.
Why?
I said hello by mistake.
It was a mistake, right?
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't say that.
You're saying that you made a mistake.
We're sorry.
This is a story that a female staff member told me when she went to the company.
Hey, what do you do for a living?
I work at a boutique. What do you do for a living?
I'm a staff member for a children's show.
No way! A staff member for a children's show?
Oh, by the way, that Heipou came to our shop the other day, but he came to my head!
That's not true.
According to the girl, that day Heipou came to the shop by himself.
Heipou, Heipou, la la la la la la la.
Ah, here, here.
Welcome!
Ah, are you Mr. Heipo?
Yes, yes, that's right. I'm Heipo.
I'm so happy you came to our shop.
What are you looking for today?
Today, I came to look for a pair of shoes that would suit a gentleman like me.
Ah, then come over here.
Heipo immediately looks for the shoes that suit him.
And...
Ah, this is nice.
It suits me perfectly, doesn't it?
I think it suits you very well.
I see. Then, please give me the smallest size of this.
Understood. Please wait a moment.
A few minutes later.
He found his favorite shoes and put them on.
However...
Huh?
They're too big.
What did you do to them?
They're too big for this size.
Please bring me a smaller one.
I'm truly sorry.
That shoe is the smallest size in this store.
What is this?
This store doesn't suit a gentleman like me.
I won't come here again.
This Sanribo Dick.
When he realized that he didn't have the size, he left with a huge smile.
What? There's no way there are such small shoes!
Not only the staff, but also the general public were troubled by this.
Everyone, you can't go to a third-rate store like this!
Ebo-san, how big are your feet?
About 24 inches.
Then, there's no such thing.
No, no, no.
Even if you don't have it, you can just go home.
Why do you have it?
That's the most frustrating thing.
I like it, but I don't have it.
I have to think more forward.
That kind of...
Huh?
What?
I'm still asking.
I'm listening.
What are you doing, Taira-san?
The
Yamachan Quest that was broadcasted last year.
The Heipo on the air is...
Scary!
I can't break the screen at all.
I can't break it.
Heipo, shut up!
Shut up!
Actually, in this village, a very terrible incident has happened.
Before the recording, the director explains the secret hiding place in the haunted house.
Well, Heipou-san, please hide here and scare Hamada-san.
I see. You don't think I'm hiding here as a ghost, do you?
If that's the case, I'm sure you'll be surprised and you'll be able to film something you've never seen before.
Leave it to me!
As expected of the director of the show.
He quickly understands the intentions of the Onuma and enters the haunted house.
Now, please watch the shocking video that happened while he was on standby.
Please watch.
Please don't do that.
You can't stay here.
I'm scared.
Please come in.
No, no, no.
No, no, no. I'm scared.
Akari, you were okay.
I don't like you being so prepared.
Stay here.
I'm scared.
I'm going to drink it.
I don't know the magic.
I'm sorry.
I'm scared.
I'll do it here, but I'll do it in front.
Today?
I'm scared.
He's here.
I can't do this.
It's not in yet.
I wasn't scared.
I'm scared.
I can't do this.
Take it off.
I'm scared.
I'm going to do it again!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
What?
That's disgusting!
This is...
This is really shocking!
Why?
Why are you doing this?
It's scary, isn't it?
It's scary even in the room.
You're saying things like,
I can't do it today!
It has nothing to do with that.
O-Numa and Shion are so annoying!
Stop it! You're making me angry!
O-Numa, you hit your junior, right?
Of course.
That's right.
I wanted to hit my senior too.
That's right. In that situation.
What are you so scared of?
Because there are ghosts, right?
Eh?
Stop it!
Stop saying, eh?
But that project, or that corner,
You're the one who's supposed to scare the dark side of me.
Well, if it's someone else...
No, no, when you're the one who's talking, why don't you say that you're scared?
I thought I was okay at that time.
Right?
Why are you scared?
Please enter the stage.
The court is now in session.
Please announce the verdict.
The court has done nothing but reflect on its actions.
It has caused many people trouble.
It is a hard-to-tolerate fact.
Therefore, there is no room for explanation.
The verdict is the human breaker's punishment.
I'm sorry.
There is electricity over there.
In that room, the bedroom, right?
Yes, that's right.
Ah! Ah! No!
Someone help!
No!
Please forgive me.
Please, please.
Please.
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.