Matsumoto vs. Hamada Team. 50m revenge match.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
On the day of the match, the Hamada team is on the scene.
We're here.
I want to swim lightly and decide the order of the match.
I've never seen this before.
I want to win in that order.
That's true.
That's what everyone wants.
Let's do it.
It's okay.
He's really good at swimming.
That's strange.
You didn't swim much when you were in middle school.
I did.
And a little later, Matsumoto is on the scene.
This way, please.
Thank you.
I don't want to lose.
Are you hungry before the match?
Yes, I'm hungry.
I've prepared something for you.
That's amazing.
Let's eat.
Matsumoto.
I woke up early and made this.
I didn't make it.
For the sake of victory.
I'm sorry.
I woke up early and made this.
You can see it at this point.
It's not that easy.
It's not that bad.
It's finally time for the match.
It looks like a match.
That's right.
I had to drink hot water.
I can't drink hot water.
That's a lie.
I asked Fujiwara to pack my luggage.
That's a match.
I can only do it once.
I thought about it when we arrived.
I want to get revenge in the previous order.
I don't know how much I can swim.
I'm sorry, but I'd like to borrow this pool.
I'd like to borrow this pool.
I'd like to show you a little bit.
I'll take a picture of it.
I won't support you at all.
I'll show you a little bit.
I'm the only one who's happy.
Time is not in my picture.
Please shorten it as much as possible.
I always tell Suga.
You should have said anything.
You are an annoying person.
Can I get in touch?
I'm a little upset with this catch copy.
This is the Tobiu that I gave birth to.
This is a star of Shikoku.
This is not Shikoku.
Yamanaki was born in Nishinomiya, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Tanaka was born in Hiroyuki, isn't it?
Toyonaka was born in Wakahakegappa, isn't it?
To be honest, I'm a little dazed.
Even though I've been saying it for a long time.
I don't think it's a cheer.
I'm a little dazed.
I was born in Katsushoku, which Yoshimoto is proud of.
Toyonaka was born in Wakahakegappa, isn't it?
I don't like that hill.
Well, then show me a little.
All right.
Thank you very much.
Before the showdown.
First of all, practice, including swimming checks.
Zaki-san.
Hey.
Yes.
It's about 5 minutes with a cap.
You'd better get ready.
You'd better come out.
You'd better come out, En-chan.
It's a huge belly.
What's this belly?
It's terrible.
Zaki-san.
I'm not supposed to say that.
Get ready.
And then swim a little.
Look at that.
Yeah.
Yes.
Get ready.
Start.
How is it?
Let's go.
It's a little fast, isn't it?
Start and end.
Yes.
Let's go.
It's fast.
Fast.
It's so fast.
You were faster when you were about to die than when you were going that way.
I'm not going to the side.
Are you sure?
Hey, hey, hey.
If you hang your legs,
I'll win.
Eh? Who?
I will.
Eh?
It hurts a lot.
I feel sorry for you.
If you don't hang your legs,
you can move your body.
I'll do that.
But if you hang your legs,
do you have a draw?
No, I don't have a draw.
That means you lose.
Ah, I see.
Then, I'll hang one of your legs.
Let's do that.
I'll hang one of your legs.
I'm scared of hanging my legs.
Ah,
now,
all of you didn't hang your legs, did you?
I'll do it once.
I won't do it.
Do you want to go to the gym?
I don't want to do it at that distance.
But I can't do it.
This is
dangerous.
I knew it.
Now,
the team is practicing.
I'll call a special coach.
The lifesaver,
Inuma-sensei!
He's coming.
Ah,
it's cold.
It's cold.
Hey,
don't lie down.
Don't lie down.
Hey,
it's cold.
It's cold.
Pro lifesaver,
Inuma-sensei.
He is the first person
in the Japan Lifesaving Association
who has won 4 times in a row
in the Ironman race.
Inuma-sensei
will be the coach of the Hamada team.
I'll do my best.
I'll ask Inuma-sensei
to teach you.
Then,
let's practice.
Let's go.
This way.
No, no, no.
What about us?
I've been thinking about it since then.
Maybe I should be the second one.
What?
The second one?
I think I should be the first one
from the beginning.
I think I should be the second one.
Then,
I think I should be the last one.
Let's go.
Inuma-sensei.
Inuma-sensei, let's go.
Who is it?
Inuma-sensei.
I'm sorry.
I'm a very secretive person.
Who is the first one?
Yes.
The first one is Kenji.
Kenji.
First of all,
the best thing is to lose your balance.
When you kick the wall,
you usually look forward,
but if you look forward,
you will lose your balance.
I see.
It's the same as here.
Look down.
It's too cold.
It hurts.
What's that?
I thought I could do it.
That's...
Inuma-sensei.
I thought I could do it.
Ready...
Go!
Be careful.
I'm sorry.
It's too fast.
I lost my balance.
I saw their strategy.
They didn't want to go too far.
They couldn't do it at that distance.
I couldn't do it.
I couldn't do it at that distance.
I quit.
I'll change for sure.
For example,
it's a long kick.
It's a start.
What do you do with this momentum?
It's like this.
You can go to the other side.
You're great.
I'm sorry.
I can't go up.
I thought you were going to do something.
It's a touch.
It's very different from the last one.
It would be fun if I won.
It's fun.
They definitely think they're going to win.
48 hours.
Every time, every time.
Break time before the game.
Look at this guy. He's so skinny.
If you're in the ocean, you're a f***ing sea monster.
You're popular, aren't you?
Of course, I am.
Are you an idiot?
You said you were second, but I'm third.
I don't understand what you're saying.
One, two, three, four, five...
Wait a minute.
Six, seven...
Who are you?
I'm Jun Okuri.
What are you doing today?
I'm going to swim with everyone.
I'm bored.
With the boss and the four of us.
I'm not bored.
I'm waiting for you to go up there.
Let's do it.
Can I give you another one?
Ah, it's mango
Mango?
Mango or...
Lychee! Lychee!
Lychee!
But...
Huh?
What is that?
It's like poison
It's like poison?
But you know...
If you don't stay away from the person next to you...
Hey!
It's not good for the weather
I'm going to win if you say that
What are you talking about?
I'm going to win, right?
Huh?
He cried
The day Matsumoto-san cried
I cried
Let's review the rules
The opponent is a 10-metre tall guy
Matsumoto is 50-metre tall by himself
The Kamada team is 12.5-metre tall each
The key point is the touch of the Kamada team
How will the four of them cover the unaccelerated boss?
Just like the practice
The start and dash earlier was good
Thank you
Please do it in the actual game
Tanaka-kun
You did a good run
Just like that
Touch Endo
Endo
Don't sink
I won't do anything
Just come as it is
Let's do our best
Let's go
Thank you
I won't do anything
It's finally time for the battle
Matsumoto and the Kamada team's determination and pride
In the depths of their eyes, quietly
But with a hot head
They release the tension in their muscles
Will the Kamada team get revenge from their humiliation?
Is it a glorious goal to wait before their eyes?
Or is it a nightmare punishment game?
The answer is the water of God
Please wait
Yes
Let's go
On your marks
Get set
Let's go
Matsumoto and the Kamada team's determination and pride
It's still going
Wait a minute
Thank you
We did it
One more time
What the hell are you doing?
I dropped it
Don't talk
Don't look
Yes
This is strange
It's cold
That's strange
Do you want to go out?
If you get tired, go out
Wait a minute
Let's go
Thank you
We did it
We won
It's cold
We did it
We won!
Are you guys still comedians?
Comedians!
What are you going to do if you swim seriously?
Idiot!
I'm not an idiot!
Hey, you guys!
Idiot!
What are you doing?
Are you trying to get into the water?
Idiot!
Are you serious?
Left, right, left.
Left, left, left.
Idiot!
Did you win?
We finally won.
I don't like that kind of punishment game.
What kind of punishment game is it?
No matter who asks,
even if they say it was funny,
it doesn't matter.
What was funny?
If we did it,
we would have really died.
No, no, no.
But, you know,
I'm sorry.
what I'm looking forward to
is the actual game.
I'm going to play seriously from now on.
Thank you for watching.
If we have a chance,
we can play a punishment game.
This time,
we will play a punishment game
until the summer.
Of course.
We will make fun of some jokes
and make it fun.
I can't do it.