Hamada once again challenged the Matsumoto team to a 1-on-4 golf match.
Hamada was convinced that Matsumoto and Yamazaki would win the team play, but...
The beginner, Kokoriko Tanaka, got a miracle shot in a row!
As a result, Hamada lost to Matsumoya and Muzan.
Once again, he was punished for his fear.
And two months ago...
Finally, your punishment game has been decided.
There's a game called Niteru Eigyouchu.
I've played it.
You've played it, right?
It's about 100 times in 24 hours.
I think you should play it.
I've been saying Niteru Eigyouchu for a long time!
When I saw it for the first time, I was like, what is this guy doing?
Is he trying to show off?
This guy is desperate!
He's going to lose this year!
This is how the punishment game was decided!
Niteru Eigyouchu
Niteru Eigyouchu is a 3-second campaign run by Japanese TV.
This time, Hamada Masatoshi will be on Niteru Eigyouchu for 24 hours on April 19th.
And the other day, a press conference was held ahead of the 24-hour Hamada Masatoshi Eigyouchu.
Dear reporters, thank you very much for coming to the press conference for 24 hours of Hamada Masatoshi Eigyouchu.
Hamada Masatoshi and Matsumoto Hitoshi will be joining us.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
We will now hear from the chief producer of Niteru Eigyouchu, Kazuyuki Sakurada.
Thank you very much for coming to this incredible event.
As you can see on the sign behind me, the 24-hour Hamada Masatoshi Eigyouchu.
Up until now, I have not looked into this kind of project in every country in the world.
In particular, there were a lot of problems, including technology and other sections.
But we managed to put together a big project and make it happen.
So, I would like to ask Hamada Masatoshi to do his best to inspire the Japanese people.
Thank you very much.
First, I would like to hear from Matsumoto Hitoshi about the penalty game.
As you know, Hamada Masatoshi used to say that he could beat us in golf.
But he lost.
So, I thought about his penalty game.
As you all know, Hamada Masatoshi is a dirty person.
As a talent, I think he deserves a D-class.
What can a D-class man do?
He is a piece of trash.
He is a loser.
Shut up!
That's why I decided to give him a penalty game.
Thank you very much.
Now, I would like to hear from Hamada Masatoshi.
I'm going to beat you up.
How do you feel about the rules?
1, 2, 3, 4, 4 people hit the ball.
You said you could win, but you lost.
That means you lost.
I heard that you had a hard time with the technology.
Then you should quit.
We think so, too.
To be honest, he is a dirty person.
Shut up!
He is a D-class talent.
He is worse than before.
But he is wearing a T-shirt.
I think he is motivated to do something dirty.
Shut up!
Now, I would like to hear from the reporters.
Well...
It's been a while.
I don't think you should quit.
Do you really want to do it for 24 hours?
I would like to hear from Hamada Masatoshi.
That's not true.
This is just a game.
I'm sorry.
This is not a game.
Isn't this an extra?
This is not an extra.
This is an extra.
What are you talking about?
He is motivated to do something dirty.
This is a punishment game.
It's fun and easy.
You can do it.
I don't think it's easy.
It's 24 hours.
You have to do your best.
No one knows you.
I see.
Do you change the pattern every time?
I don't know what to do at what time.
I have it in my hand.
Please tell me.
It starts at 5.30 a.m. and ends at 10 a.m.
You have to do your best.
The last one is at 26.40 a.m. and the last one is at 32 a.m.
This is amazing.
You have to change your costume every time.
You don't have a character.
What is the highlight of the game?
I don't know.
Please tell me.
I make a lot of highlights.
I made a lot of highlights.
You can't show it in 3 seconds.
You also made highlights, right?
Yes, I did.
What kind of highlights?
I heard you said you would do your best.
I do my best.
Please tell me.
What about you, Sakurada?
I want you to think about it yourself.
I thought you could win golf with your skills.
Then I'll bet on you.
Why?
I don't know why I lost.
You lost twice.
I didn't win that many times.
I'll tell you a story.
I used the same shaft as Tiger Woods.
I prepared a shaft that would never be shaken.
I've never heard of it.
It's amazing.
Will Matsumoto watch the game on the same day?
I don't want to see it.
I don't think he'll watch it.
He knows what a D-class player does.
He's back.
He's back from F to D.
I don't know when it will be on the same day.
I don't think he'll watch it.
I don't care if he watches it.
It depends on the day.
I think Hama can do it.
Good luck, Hama.
That's all.
I heard you can do it for 24 hours without taking any water.
I'm more worried about my body.
Take some water.
I don't want to make a legend.
How old are you, Hamada?
I'm 40 years old.
It's hard to play 24 hours when you're 40.
I don't drink water.
He said he'd take one of his six bones.
He said he'd do his best with five bones.
He's blue.
I've heard a lot of things.
Hamada, why do you have five bones?
I have a question for Matsumoto.
Matsumoto's mother appeared in the previous game.
Will anyone else but Hamada participate in this game?
I don't know.
My mother won't be able to participate in this game.
When I played the game, my father baked a rice cake.
I didn't know what to bake.
My father was a little angry.
The next day
Let's start the steel shooting.
Thank you.
Hamada Masato's 24-hour business starts at 5 a.m. on Monday, the 19th.
Please look forward to Hamada's 32-hour business.