The first episode of the show is with Chikizu! New characters discovered!
Masumoto Hitoshi and Producer Hichihenge!
What is it? New characters discovered?
It's been a while since we've had a show with Hichihenge
It's been a while
Can you take a look?
We've been doing this all along
So far, Kogoriko Tanaka is the first
He won 40,000 yen
We have to get him out of this
I've been thinking about it
When it comes to that, there are only amateurs
I see
I mean, aren't you an amateur?
Well, I'm an amateur
I'm trying to find a new character
I almost gave up
Right?
I was shocked when I saw Sen-sen-shu and O-fuku-binta
That kind of character
What is it?
It's Ichimoku-san
It's nothing to do with an idol
It's a new character
What are you doing?
He's licking his nose
That's amazing
I'm not talking to anyone
He's licking his nose
This is it
The Yamato-soul that we almost forgot
When I saw him
Yamato-soul
That's what I thought
I heard that if you boil too much hijiki, it becomes like this
He said it's not human
Is that so?
Then you should make more in this program
This program is brought to you by the sponsor
What should I do?
It's been a while since I've been to Yamasaki
I've just moved
What?
I thought it wouldn't work
Why not?
I've just moved to Ikodate
It's okay
It's not a problem
That's right
I feel calm
Onuma Fujiwara's rebellion
We are not raccoons
I know that
I don't know if this is okay
Is that so?
Yes
It's okay
You can also fish in Tanaka's world
That's right
Even if you go alone
I'm not interested in fishing
That's right
Cyborg and Suwa Kobayashi
Cyborg
I don't like that
Cyborg's first challenge
Okay
Hey, is Takasu Koseisaka really interesting?
I'm a pot
Is that so?
Yes
It's a serious story
Yamasaki, put it in
It was dangerous
No, it's perfect
Next
What are you doing?
Introduce your wife
Introduce my wife?
Introduce my wife
I want to see your wife
I want to see
Hey
Ayappa
Thank you
If it goes on like this
It will be a dinner party at Yamasaki
That's right
I'm tired
It's okay if it's like bowling
I was doing it
I dropped it from above
Someone broke it
It will take a whole year
That's right
Why are you making such an unpleasant face?
Can you all be patient?
The trip was interesting
Trip?
Hot spring?
Isawa?
It's domestic
Everyone seems to have fun
What are we going to do next?
That's right
Monura
Irogappa
Yuri
Minami
Writer
I remember
Writer is dirty
But it's Monura
Have you ever brought your sister here?
Yes
She says wow
I'm surprised
Amazing
She says as expected
I met Ujiie-san yesterday
I was told about the wedding
I wonder if there will be a wedding
That's right
Who is this person?
Ujiie-san's girlfriend
She says gas
What should I do?
Who is it?
I was told it was a wedding
It's an old movie
We brought someone from somewhere
What about the pants?
It's the first time
It's the first time, so it won't imitate
It's stupid
I don't see it
I have to go in
Hurry up
I'll do it
This is it
37,000 yen
The ad-lib of the mother standing on the desk
That's an ad-lib
I said I wanted to do it
I had an ad-lib
I said I wanted to do that
I'm going to work with everyone from today
Are you friends?
I'm Kokoriko's junior
I'm good at jokes
I like to tell stories
I can't do that
Take her away
I'm sorry
Take her home
Did you notice?
There's no monitor in the hall
There isn't
Put it in the middle
What is it?
It's a commercial that only happens in Osaka
It only happens in Osaka?
It only happens in Osaka
Really?
You can only see it in Osaka
I understand
I'll show you
I'll tell you a story
It's hard
It's my first time too
Osaka's famous Okonomiyaki
You know it, right?
Write it down
Okonomiyaki
Mishin's Okonomiyaki
Toshi, I made a song about Okonomiyaki
Okonomiyaki for dinner
Mishin's Okonomiyaki
It's amazing
It's a scary family
Thank you
Toshi, go home
Is that so?
The egg is falling
Tissue
Hurry up
Hurry up, I have to go to school
You all talk too much
I don't understand what you're saying
It's a match bomb
I don't understand
I can't do this anymore
Thank you
You have to watch it
That's right
Yesterday
There was a stupid guy
It's been a long time
I was in the car with Kim
There was a guy who didn't let me in
I was worried about him
I wanted to see his face
The guy who didn't let me in tried to go to the left
He stopped in front of me
Then Kimura sat down
He opened the window and yelled
Shut up!
He is really bad
I didn't want to see him
I didn't want to see him but I wanted to do something
I wanted to do FUXX YOU
There is no one who wants to do that
I didn't want to see him but I wanted to do FUXX YOU
I didn't know how to do FUXX YOU
I didn't know what to do
I didn't know how to do it
I didn't know anything
I don't know what Kimura and I are doing
What is this?
I didn't understand
You wanted to do this
I wanted to do this
I couldn't do it because I was weak
I was very strong so I couldn't do it
I wanted to do this
I couldn't do it
I didn't want to see him
I didn't want to see him but I wanted to do FUXX YOU
It was easy
You were attacked
You said, it was last night
You said that
I was not attacked
Don't say that
You have to blur it
It was hard
You can't do that!
Is it a zoo?
It's not a zoo.
It stinks?
Don't you see goldfish or tropical fish?
That's strange.
There might be some goldfish sometimes.
What's that?
Isn't it a little fish?
What's so funny?
You have a family.
I'm thinking of buying an animal.
What do you want to buy?
A dog, of course.
You sound like a dog lover.
He's a man.
That's not true.
What do you really want to buy?
I want to improve my image.
What you really want to buy is a magazine.
I want a big magazine.
A mansion, right?
You can't buy it, can you?
That's right.
What?
What the f**k?
I want a vacuum cleaner.
What?
I don't have a dog.
I want a vacuum cleaner.
That's funny.
You look like a dog.
I see.
You're pushing a dog lover.
I don't know.
I really like dogs.
You want to get inside a dog.
That's strange.
If a cat is cute, you want to get inside a dog.
I know that.
You want to get inside a dog.
I have a question for Matsumoto-san.
Thank you.
Who is the 2nd place in the world?
What is Hamada-san's rank?
What the f**k?
I'll say it.
The 2nd place is...
Oda Mudo.
You're making fun of me.
No, no.
I have a lot of fans.
1st and 2nd place?
Yes.
That's the only answer I can give.
And Hamada-san.
I don't have a rank.
You don't have a rank.
You don't have a rank at all.
I don't have a rank.
You don't have a rank.
About 4 years ago...
I was in the 170th place.
But...
The 170th place is Tai.
It's the same person?
Yes.
I see.
Other than that, it was the same as Kano Jigoro.
Kano?
He's the old man who made judo.
How old is he?
It's not the way you think it is.
Why is he 1st place?
It has nothing to do with that.
I'm talking about the 1st place in the world.
I'm always out of rank because I say things like that.
He's 1st place.
Everyone thinks, what's the 1st place?
What's the 1st place in the world?
I think it's wrong to ask what's the 1st place in everything.
He's the 1st place in the world.
So if you look at me and think I'm the 1st place in the world, you're wrong.
Do you understand?
It's hard to be the 1st place in the world.
A lot of things.
Like greeting people.
You have to make a name tag.
It's hard.
I don't want to be the 1st place in everything.
But I've always been the 1st place in the world for 7 or 8 years.
Who decides?
The world.
Your story is all in the background.
He's the model of the popular manga, Sakiage Otokojuku's Heihachi Edajima.
Men are told that they should only cry 3 times in their lifetime.
When is that 3 times?
When men are born, they cry.
This is the first time.
This is when I was born.
Yoroshiku.
This is when I was 1 year old.
No one can control this.
That's right.
It's your performance.
It's your first performance.
This is when you cry.
Let's use this once.
This is the next time you cry.
There are only 2 more times.
It's the next day.
The next day?
That's too early.
Too soon.
It's the next day?
You have to say it again that you were born yesterday.
You said it yesterday, but it's Yoroshiku.
You have to say it again the next day.
It has to be 3 times, right?
It's the first time when you're born.
The first time when you're born.
The next time when you're born.
You cry because you cried when you were born.
I don't get it.
I don't get it either.
The last time.
What?
Stop it!
Don't pull out your nails!
Stop it, Takushi.
I'm going home.
Stop it.
I'll call you when I'm home.
Yes, please.
It's the next day.
What is it?
Why are you asking?
It's the first time when you're born.
You have to say it quickly.
What is it?
You have to say it.
You're a child.
When I'm home, put a smile on your face.
Put a smile on your face.
I'm satisfied with the answer.
Yamada-kun pretends to lift one sheet of the futon.
He's going to take it all.
I have a question for Matsumoto-san.
I don't know.
I don't know either.
I want to ask my father to write the answer.
What should I do?
What do you think?
It's easy.
Is it a direct answer?
Kami-san.
I want you to tell me directly.
Let's go to the restaurant.
This is the restaurant.
What do you want to eat?
Pork cutlet.
You can say it.
I want to eat pork cutlet.
Pork cutlet.
I can't do it.
Should I ask my father?
Are you going to ask your father?
Either way can be good.
You have to run away.
I have to ask my father.
You can't do that.
Turn around.
No, no.
Even if you do that, I won't let you go first.
It's hard.
Press it again.
Thank you very much.
I want to push it from here.
I'll play the ending again.
I'll push it from here.
How many times do you want to go?
Tell me from the beginning.
You'll go, right?
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.