Happy New Year
I'm Fujiwara from Yoshimoto Kogyo
You guys are on TV
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
This week's show is a special program for kids
Fujiwara chose the best VTR of the year
You did it
How was it?
Looking back on last year
There are a lot of things that left an impression on me
You can do anything
It's all about having fun
Well
From 10th to 7th
Let's take a look
Are you ready?
Mizuno
It started from here
It's fun
Let's see how it goes
I don't know
Let's start with Tanaka
Please
A B-class talent like you
And a C-class copywriter
I don't know what I can do
Everyone do your best
The talent competition started with Tanaka's strong greeting
The participants are riding the black bus
And the results
First, Okuda Tamiyo
Yes
Next is Hamada
If he passes Okuda, he will be the first winner
First winner
It's almost the same
3, 2, 1
Okuda Tamiyo
What are you doing?
You idiot
Why are you doing this?
Congratulations
We have been loving each other
We have been watching it
Let's be happy
Who is that?
Let's be together forever
Thank you for the speech
That's what the host said
I see
We watched it until the 7th place
It was the first original
It's getting more and more weird
You don't plan to do it again this year, right?
No
I don't want to do it again
I want to see it
It's going to be boring
It's not a brief
It's interesting
It's called Hishire Yume no Naka
It's cool
It's beautiful
Let's go
Drin
I'm sorry
It's good
End
It's funny
Something is going to be born
Yamazaki can't lose
That's right
I'll take it off
Take it off slowly
It's slow
Drin
Yamazaki and Endo, good luck
Next
9th
It's cold
I want you to do your best
I'm sorry
It's hard
The calendar of 1999 is made up of various punishment games
First of all, Matsumoto born in September
Start
I'll do my best
You have to do it well
I see
I'm the leader
Next, Hamada born in May
Gorilla
And the director Saito born in November
It wasn't fun when I was doing it
I don't know how to do it
1 million yen win
I want to get 1 million yen
1 million yen
What is it?
Did you hit something?
The UFO has fallen over there
It seems to be recording
Really?
Endo?
Hey
You are great
You are an alien
Take the alien back to the dressing room
Start the human experiment
Endo
What is it?
I'm glad
I'm going home
Bye
Can I say something?
Yes
Idiot
I found out that the famous director of the program is a fool
It even developed into a trial in the program
Endo
I was in Yoshinoya
It was when I was shooting in Yoshinoya
I remember this
After the shooting
The producer who got beef bowl from the store
Hey you guys
I got beef bowl
Share it with everyone
Yay
Onuma, who was watching the scene, caught Eddie
Hey
What did you get earlier?
It's Tadaken from Yoshinoya
Give it to me
Somehow
I took that Tadaken from Eddie
That night
Give it to me
We're eating out today, hurry up
Really?
Yay
It's been a long time since they've eaten out
The wife who takes care of them
The destination they arrived at
Yoshinoya
And of course the payment
Please use this Tadaken
How many tickets do you have?
I have all the tickets I got
All of them?
That's a lot
The woman also got it
What?
That's a lot
How many tickets did you get?
50,000 yen
What a scary man
There was a great reaction
There's no director like that
I've never been hit by Onuma
Yes
Please move
Tadaken from Yoshinoya
They're all dressed up
If they lose the game
They'll be left behind in the city
This is Senda, Mitsuo, Nana
Both sides are Nana
Here we go
Senda, Mitsuo, Nana
I don't know
It's different
It's one point
Senda, Mitsuo, Nana
I'm so mad
What's that?
I'm still thinking about it
If you fail
I'll be in trouble
One point for both
Here we go
From Sura
Mitsuo, Nana, Senda
Mitsuo, Nana
If you're strong, you'll get a lot of pressure
After all, the loser Matsumoto gets off the bus
And goes to buy crepes
So cool
I'm so embarrassed
You're going too far
We're going too far
The winner of the game is a luxury product
Even if you lose, you'll get a nice gift from Akko
It's a 30th anniversary of Wada Aki's life
It's a punishment game, right?
It's not a punishment game
Why are we doing a 30th anniversary of Wada Aki's punishment game?
First is the black beard battle
The loser gets a kiss mark on his neck
Ready, start
Akko, here you go
The loser gets a kiss mark on his neck
Don't use standard language
Come on
What is this 30th anniversary celebration?
Come to my house
I'll be done soon, so come
Be quiet
He's sitting down
It was amazing
He's really sitting down
Something's coming out
What are you doing?
Why are you going back?
I'm going home
If you draw the same picture as Yama-chan, you win
If you lose, you get a deep kiss with Akko
Here's the answer
The king
Let's start with Matsumoto
But it looks like the king
I'll decide after looking at Amano-san
The winner gets a deep kiss
Akko, here you go
The loser gets a deep kiss mark on his neck
It's a deep kiss
I want you
Stop
What are you doing?
I want you
That was amazing
I was serious
How many days did you spend in your room?
That's right
I heard it
I want to do cosplay again
It's frustrating
There are still two more
I want to see it in the toilet
That was interesting
I went to the toilet the worst one last year
I couldn't move
The winner is in here
He hasn't come out yet
Who is the winner?
Please watch the video
This is the punishment game
It's the same as the previous game
Hamada's first shot is a nice shot
But the rules are heavy
Matsumoto's team wins
Hey
Matsumoto's nice shot
Matsumoto's team wins
Hamada's punishment game
And the punishment game
Hamada, I want to see the Titanic
The Titanic?
The love scene was nice
What?
The love scene
Why?
Go to Hollywood with your mother and shoot the Titanic
Hamada's punishment game
Hamada takes his mother to Los Angeles
I want to go home
And this is the result
Close your eyes
I saw the video and I remembered again
I believe you
It's Daikon
I don't like this image
Open your eyes
I'm flying
I don't like this
I don't know how to look at this
I'm a monster
I'm Kazuo Umezu
I don't like this
I don't want to see this
I don't know how to look at this
Hamada kisses a lot
I kissed Tanaka
Tanaka's lips are soft
It's softer than any woman I've kissed
I'm serious
This is the first
I'm excited
I looked back
Let's do our best
Thank you
This program was brought to you by these sponsors