Next time, at the Gaki no Tsukai Ara!
Even if you sleep or wake up, it's Gaino-uchi Gainin Ibiki Announcement!
The winner is...
It's Kowa!
Yes!
Shut up!
I can't do this anymore!
This is terrible!
The 5 people who are at the peak of the Ibuki Gainin world.
Will there be any other Ibuki Gainin that will follow him?
In this program, we will be asking for more Ibuki Gainin, and will be doing a survey of 300 Gainin.
Then, 14 new voice actors appeared.
What kind of voice acting are they going to do?
They took a month to film their performance.
The tape they recorded was recorded in 500 copies.
I'm not going to do voice acting.
Then, 6 voice actors were selected and sent to the studio.
What kind of sound will they make?
It's amazing, isn't it?
For the first time, they appear in the movie.
But they are sleeping.
Let's go.
Let's see! The first entertainer is this person!
The entertainer with a good chance.
The entertainer who pulls the blood of the Eastern Japan.
Why do you have a nan?
I'm a little relieved.
You're not Indian, but it doesn't matter at all.
But Indians don't have anything to worry about.
Sorry, this is the limit.
What kind of sound does the castle make?
He immediately visits Chance's house.
Don't say Chance.
Ah, good morning.
Good morning.
Chance-kun.
I don't know if I can make a sound or not.
Good morning.
Good night.
After a day as usual, Chance goes to sleep.
There's no such thing?
Oh, really?
At least get a towel.
I think a bath towel is fine.
I think it's easier to sleep on the bedside table.
I think it's slanted.
I haven't slept yet.
It's so bad.
I'm not used to the TV.
When will the situation change?
It seems that he can't fall asleep
Excuse me, can you turn off the lights?
It's too bright
You can talk
He listens to the chance and turns off the lights
It's a chance!
Then, a change appears immediately.
Oh, it's coming!
This is a good sign.
This is amazing.
Amazing!
Oh my god!
What is this?
Who is this?
It's an old man!
Thank you for the chance!
Don't write it! Don't write it!
Don't write it!
You wrote a lot!
You have something at home!
That's right.
You have something!
I don't have anything at home.
And the sound of the chance is reaching its peak.
He's heavy today...
That was
not like a real change.
Liamo
What?
What is this?
Don't go!
The sound of the chance is like the animal's whining.
You are really good.
You are amazing, Chance.
The apartment was about to be kicked out.
It was too noisy.
The people in this apartment are noisy too.
The other ones are noisy too.
I was like this when I was in the dormitory.
The female student said,
I'm sick of it.
I was like this.
Can you be quiet for a moment?
Including the parents,
we had a meeting.
The medicine to suppress the stomachache was also taken.
You should have refused.
You were taken?
You should have cleaned your nose.
I'm sorry.
The next artist is Takada Corporation's Oya-ki.
On stage, he's always in good shape.
This man's Ibi-ki.
I did it!
It was so big!
Takada Corporation
The sound of Oyaki-kun
I think we are similar
How was it?
Oyaki-kun
It's really bad.
This is Akane-chan's.
This is a key.
I didn't do it.
It's definitely not.
Because he can't sleep, he turns off the lights and shoots.
What is that?
The pillow
The voice of the father is quiet, but the volume is not so loud
But after this, the sound of the father-in-law changed.
It hurts!
This breathing is long.
It hurts.
It's really long.
It's going to spit out.
I almost died.
I'm going to have a sore throat.
It's going to spit out.
Are you okay?
It's scary.
It looks so painful.
My stomach is about to explode.
I'm dying.
It's so painful.
I don't want to drink from the side.
The dog of the father-in-law is long and painful.
I see.
The sound is not that loud.
It's long.
That's the most different kind of smell.
That's right.
Do you know the difference?
I've been in a show before.
As far as I know,
I only know that my body stinks.
You're the worst.
When I have a bad breath, I can't stand the smell.
Once, I had a fart in the train on the way.
It was too smelly.
The smell of the thing you spit out is so strong that I don't know what to call it.
Since I'm a woman, I might call it the smell of the back of my ass.
But the smell of the back of your ass is because you're a woman.
Could it be that Jin?
How do you know, Jin!?
affiliated with JYP
complicated jokes
about Akapin
S character of faucet
acting cool
perch on the hidden под
Shaking water
Vorac funeral
Hey Hibiki-chan
partner
Ac endpoint
From now, H사가 Danoko will kill you
It's totally different from your image of V.
It's totally different.
The character is still not determined.
It's not determined yet.
What kind of smell is the red pepper?
It's totally different.
Hello.
It's a boy.
game
What a good night
When think in teary silent dream, artist moves
racist still drawn deep sleep
And then...
What's that?
Eh?
What is it?
Scary, scary, it's a little scary.
It's scary, scary, it's showing.
Ah, it's showing the
It's showing it completely.
This is bad.
I was saying..
I'm gonna complete the task..
etin..
What are you even saying?
What on earth are you talking about?
The end.
Zoma-hon.
The red pepper is a very difficult person to talk to.
I got it.
You said Zoma Hon!
You said it clearly!
You said you had a dream of Zoma Hon.
I think Zoma Hon is now the second generation of my father-in-law, Takeshi's fan.
He is the second generation of my father-in-law.
Oh, I've seen it.
In front of the Lord, if you get a good beating and get a little money, you'll be excited.
But in front of us, he sleeps in the back of the studio.
He's been so busy, so I think that's why he's sleeping.
What is this?
This is...
I usually sell cosmetics.
By your part-time job?
By my part-time job.
In Machimoto Keio.
This is a good one.
Ah, this is good.
It's a very good one.
Look, look, I'm fixing it.
Stop doing that.
The voice actor of Hirae no Hibiki, Hirae Shunsuke
The voice actor of Hirae no Hibiki, who can be easily fooled by the voice actor of Hirae no Hibiki
This is my boyfriend
This is a hidden camera
I don't know him
You know him well
I once had a job at a hotel
I happened to be in the same room with him.
I told the manager who changed the room for me,
He said, please stay with me.
At that time, the room was noisy.
I thought I should sleep on the bed of the unit bus.
Why do I care so much about my partner?
It's strange that the room is the same.
You are a little early.
I thought it was over.
What kind of smell will Dorian's Hirae draw?
I drew a girl's outfit.
It's a girl's outfit.
It's a raw look.
I don't want to show my armpit.
What's with those pants?
What's with that pattern?
You're a hot punk.
It's the money of a big family.
Here it comes.
The
This is a super turn.
It's amazing.
If you continue to shoot, a sign of fatness has appeared on the back.
What is that?
Does it stop?
It doesn't stop.
Wow!
Eh?
I don't breathe that much.
It's stopped.
Wow!
You're really doing it!
Eh?
Wow!
That was close!
About one minute.
Welcome back!
That was close!
What else is this symptom?
What's wrong?
Ah, it's a toothache.
What's wrong with you?
I'm dying!
Will the one who is alone be able to breathe without any breathing?
In his case, he's double.
He's double.
He's a little bit of a mess.
I don't like that.
But if you wake up, you'll have symptoms of pain in your jaw.
I wonder how much pain I'll have.
When I think back, I've been taken off my jaw once.
When I was in junior high, I used to say it in a big voice, but...
I was bullied.
I don't say it like this.
What are you coming up with?
There was a pattern that I didn't say.
There was a pattern.
Ibiki Gainin, Den Kacchan.
With a strong visual, I can see the Ibiki that the Gainin of Iyashikei can't.
3, 2, 1, go!
It's Dekka-chan!
Hello!
Well, Dekka-chan is here.
Dekka-chan, you were hospitalized recently.
There were a lot of things, right?
That's right.
Well, I don't have that much money, so I was hospitalized in a 6-person room.
The other five were all old men and they all snored.
I thought it was really noisy.
But somehow I fell asleep and woke up.
Then the manager said,
Dekka-chan, we're moving to a private room.
I was snoring and moved to a private room.
I asked why we were moving.
The moment I fell asleep, I heard there were five nurse calls.
Seriously?
It's all good!
What kind of sound will Dekka-chan make?
It's scary
It's Ronan's
I don't know.
I don't know about the last time I was a loner.
The start is slow.
It's a bit big.
Wow, this is...
Hey, don't hold down the nurse's call.
Did it stop?
What are you doing?
It's dirty.
Victory?
After this, something unexpected happens to Dekika-chan's body.
It's over. It's over.
Oh no.
What happened?
I don't know that!
Why are you doing that?
I think it's already done
The pain is gone, and the snorting sound of Zecca-chan is even deeper
Wow, it's a monster!
Uuuuugh!
This is...
If you sleep on the side, this is...
Uuuuugh!
I'll press the button.
Is Rekka-chan's voice really that loud?
Even if it's the other side of the sound, it can't be helped.
No, I can't hear you.
Kurowato, the Ibitio has come back.
Ibitio's Onigiri has arrived.
It hasn't gotten better since then, right?
That's right.
You said that Matsumoto-san and you went on a trip again.
So, Yamazaki-san and Matsumoto-san stayed in the same room, and I stayed in the private room.
Was that private room the Deluxe Suite Room?
See, it's like this.
It's interesting when you talk about it.
That's right.
His specialty is to talk about what happened.
I'm sorry.
Please watch the precious sound of the rice ball.
It's past 1 o'clock in the evening.
The rice ball is sleeping quietly.
Then, in 30 minutes from the end, a change appears.
The spray would be released.
The wheezing will be fordi of the sound, called the sound
of her nodding off.
It's like a ghost.
This is the feeling of being spoiled.
Are you a monster?
Monster, Monster.
What is this?
I'm sorry.
want to drop purchase
I just wanna see!
It is just basically like a training
This VTR is still better.
There are more times when it's normal.
Ahhhhhhh!
Really good.
Normally.
Ahhhhhhh!
It's a good thing.
The final winner is the rice ball.
Go, go!
Ryotome Jamboree, it's good.
Everyone come here!
The show of using children is currently on air on Japanese TV!
We have prepared various ways to make you come, and we are waiting for your visit!
What is this?