In the 11th episode of Gaki no Tsukai Arai, Chikitsuki! Genojin! Omae! Sou-chan-ka! Grand Prix!
Everyone here is lucky.
Let's go!
Today's guests, please come out!
Wait a minute, why did you come out looking so disgusted?
I just matched with Otake.
Really?
He really has such a cute face.
I don't want to be with a criminal.
What are you talking about, Genojin?
Let's introduce the guests.
First, Mr. Otake!
Next, Mr. Kanao!
Next, Mr. Matsumoto!
Hello!
Please come out.
You're dressed like this again.
What is this?
The last time I was dressed like this, it looked like I was from the industry.
This time, it looks like you're infiltrating Tama.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Let's go!
First of all, this way!
Your nipples are like the black of Othello!
You're sitting too low!
Please come out!
Your nipples are like the black of Othello!
That's not good.
This is completely black.
That's normal.
It's definitely black.
Your face isn't like that, but what's with your nipples?
Your nipples are like the black of Othello!
That's not good!
It's completely black!
What are you talking about?
That's not good!
No! You can't accept that!
Please come out, Mako.
Who's turn is it?
Next!
Ok, Tempest-san.
I think this person is underage, and has been beaten up a lot.
Oh, so the husband is underage?
He's being told that he's an adult.
And also, the person who has been beaten up even more.
Ok? Don't get angry.
I can't accept this.
Komaro-san.
Yes.
I can't accept this!
What is this?
One more time.
What do you mean you can't accept this?
In the quiz, you said you can't accept my answer.
What kind of person is this?
Aya-kun.
There are a lot of people who are underage.
That's why I'm writing this.
You should write about your acquaintances.
Oh, I see.
Like this?
Well, let's forget about that.
What do you mean?
Why did you write about Marusia?
Okamoto Natsuki-san.
Nijimai.
Konno Misago.
Kisamoto Matsuyama.
Kisamai?
Kisamoto.
Okamoto Natsuki.
Matsuda Seiko.
Nijimai.
He's going to bite me.
I wanted to write Okamoto Natsuki.
Natsuki's face is already like a mummy.
I don't know.
I don't know about that.
I'm scared.
The next question is straight.
Let's go.
This one.
You hate me, don't you?
I don't care if it's a boy or a girl.
I'm going to get scolded.
Give me a break.
I'm not the one who said it.
It's Machikazu.
That's right.
He's going to be in trouble!
Yes.
I never thought that the wishes I was going to sing today would be so heavy.
Should you write what you think is the right one?
Don't exposing it.
What?
I don't want to open what I have to show if I don't.
I'll refer you for now.
I'm not the one who said it.
Open up!
Ok, write it.
This one is terrible.
It's like McDonald's.
It looks delicious, right?
The people in town are the same.
You'll get in trouble.
Let's start with Mr. Oda.
This guy.
Yes.
We've been on the show together before.
When he's having fun...
Yes.
I'm not having fun.
This guy seems to be having a lot of fun.
It's getting more and more fun.
It's not just Ota.
Everyone's having fun.
That's what everyone thinks.
Yes, everyone's having fun.
Mr. Tenmei.
Yes.
I'm not mistaken at all.
It's Ota.
What?
Isn't this a woman?
No, no.
It doesn't matter.
It's a man.
Yes, Mr. Matsumoto.
I have a lot of them.
This is the one I'm aiming for.
If you don't hate it...
I don't have a job.
This guy.
When I was on the 24-hour TV show,
he came to me and said,
This is finally the major.
I can't stand it.
I don't want to be told that.
Now, let's see the results.
But what about the others?
Is there anything else?
Who else?
No, no.
Matsumoto is writing something.
This is the world's...
This guy is trying to make it two.
This is the best size.
Mr. Makoto Otake.
Makoto Otake.
Uru Saishi.
Kanda Uno.
Ryo Oshiba.
Kenji Muriaki.
Ryutaro Kamioka.
Ritsumi Pinko.
Tenmei Kano.
Kanda Uno.
Nae Yuki.
Ryo Oshiba.
Kenji Muriaki.
Kanda Uno.
Ryo Oshiba.
This is the world's best size.
This is the first time I read this.
The rest is Ryo Oshiba,
Makoto Otake,
Kenji Muriaki.
Wait a minute.
I'm in the 3rd place?
Kenji, I'm tired.
You guys won't let me eat.
We're a tired stomach.
Let's go.
It's because it's on that show that people hate it.
If it wasn't for this, it would be even worse.
Now, let's go. Shut up!
Ah, I have to do it!
Eh? Was it funny?
The whole world is making fun of it.
What are you talking about?
This is between you and Chan!
Now, please draw.
This is fine, right?
That's not good.
You're doing something good.
You're dead!
I'm not dead in his eyes.
That's not good.
No, no, no, no. I'm still alive in his eyes.
No, no, no, no.
You're making it sound so beautiful.
You're dead.
No, no, no.
This is between you and him!
This is too simple.
Now, Odaki-san.
Yes.
He said once that he was surprised when he died.
No, that's in the movie.
Tenmei-san.
Yes.
So, don't act like you can't read the audience's reaction.
Yamazato-san.
Okay.
See? The audience's reaction is bad, right? That's why I'm called Teresa Tenya.
Oya Masako.
Komori no Obachama.
Shiozawa Toki.
Kiyokawa Nijiko.
Mr. Okure.
Saito Seiu-kun.
Shiozawa Toki.
Awaya Noriko.
Sugai Kin-san.
Komori no Obachama.
Kiyokawa Nijiko.
Wakato Akira.
She went back to the sea.
Awaya Noriko.
Komori no Obachama.
Genji Pekin.
Oya Masako.
Awaya Noriko.
Komori no Obachama.
Shun, right?
What?
He's alive.
Your d**k is in the form of a wakamokori.
Please come in.
Mako-chan.
Tenme-san.
This is also this, right?
Tenme-san, you can call me d**k.
But this one is stronger than d**k.
One more time.
What d**k?
You can't say d**k.
I didn't know that at all.
Liar.
How many years have you been doing this?
That's normal.
I'm sorry.
Don't blur it out.
It's only you.
I don't like it.
You don't have to do that.
Why are you blurring it out?
I want you to blur it out.
I don't like it.
Here, take this.
Where is it from?
I want you to blur it out.
What are you doing?
There's no answer.
I want you to blur it out.
Well, it's started.
This is really a game.
You're just taking off your clothes.
But I went to the doctor.
And the doctors saw me.
Really?
They saw me.
Of course.
If it was me.
That was amazing.
Really?
That was really good.
It was like when the genius d**k, Hajime-chan was born.
I don't remember anything.
I'm just laughing at the atmosphere.
I don't know.
I really took off my contact lenses and bled.
Yesterday, I was doing a skit.
And I saw your face up close.
And I was surprised.
Your face was like this.
Like this, right?
What's with that face?
It's scary to do something like that.
It's scary.
One morning, I woke up and looked in the mirror.
And I was like, why am I eating candy in the morning?
Stop it.
It's because you're sleepy.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
That's how I am.
I have a lot of sick days.
I suddenly got sick on New Year's Day.
That's not sick.
There's a cause.
No, if you say that, I'll get sick again.
I'm sick, so I said, I'm going home.
And I got a macaroon.
Macaroon is a cut and a scratch.
Well, try it.
I gave it a try, and I got a macaroon.
And I got sick.
I'm sick of the president.
You're running fast.
I'm running fast with that.
I'm sick too.
I'm sick.
That's enough.
Why are you doing that?
I don't want to run fast.
And the doctor said,
I'm sick.
I was really scared.
I don't know if he's just keeping quiet.
I don't know if he's crying right now.
I don't know if he's telling the truth.
And then...
What?
Mr. Matsumoto of Arishihino.
What month and what day was this recorded?
I'm used to reading books.
The doctor said,
I don't know.
I'm scared.
Don't say that.
I'm going to watch the movie.
If you say that,
you'll come here next time.
Why?
You're here.
Why are you here?
You're in the same team as me.
And then...
When I went to the hospital,
I was so worried.
There were about five young nurses.
They were like,
I'm here.
They were waiting for me.
They were like,
I'm here.
They were waiting for me.
I think they decided to do a rock-paper-scissors.
The first place winner.
They said,
You're lucky.
I was like,
You're going to be a morogami.
They said,
You're going to shake your hand.
That's how it is.
I was like,
I'm going to be a morogami.
They were like,
I'm going to shake my hand.
Really?
They were shaking their hand like this?
They were shaking my hand.
That's so young.
What if something happened?
I'm so angry.
I'm not a morogami.
The result was,
They said,
You're not a morogami.
I know that.
Why are you just saying that?
You're not a morogami.
You know that.
What did you say?
I don't know.
From Hakata?
I came from Hakata.
Hakata's food store.
It's a business point!
Matsumoto-san, you're going to be 20 soon.
What will you do when you're 20?
This is...
Hey, wait!
What do you mean, what do you mean?
You're the same age as me and Sawako!
Ah, back then?
No, back then!
Why can't you do a lot of things?
I'm really looking forward to it.
Do you call it puberty?
Because you're 20?
You're still saying that.
But this is a strange thing.
I thought it would be a little more real, but it's not surprising.
Who's the normal commentator?
Matsumoto-san used to be in the O.L.
If there's bullying from your boss or senpai, please tell me.
I can't remember.
Hey, wait!
You're 19 now, right?
You can be over 18 or 16.
That's right!
Right after high school, I went out of the office.
What?
I went out and in.
Why?
It didn't continue.
I went out of the office.
I didn't like that.
Who did you get bullied by?
The Kaminari president.
You're a scary president!
He was very angry with me.
Because you're bad, right?
You were making mistakes, right?
Yes, about the bamboo skirt.
Did you say it like this?
It's in the O.L.
It's in the O.L., so it's not in the O.L.
I was bullied by my colleague.
Matsuura-san?
Who?
He's not my colleague.
Matsuura-san?
Yes, Matsuura-san.
He's not your colleague?
I cried under the desk with Matsuura-san.
Because you were angry?
No, not because I was angry.
I cried under the desk.
Under the desk...
That's why...
It's not a joke.
Matsumoto-san seems to be in a long-distance relationship.
Where does your girlfriend live?
She's from Rio.
Rio?
Brazil?
Brazil, Brazil.
What kind of person is she?
She's Indian.
Are you stupid?
So what?
Indians shouldn't go to Brazil.
There's nothing wrong with that.
Don't look down on my girlfriend.
You're too fast.
I went from India to Brazil.
They said the curry was spicy.
It's the taste of a foreign country.
It can't be spicy.
So I went.
You couldn't do it.
I couldn't do it.
It was too spicy.
I lived in Rio.
My girlfriend lives over there.
It's none of your business.
What are you talking about?
What was your first impression of Matsumoto-san?
I was attracted to Samba-san.
You were attracted to her?
You were just born.
Why were you attracted to Samba-san?
I felt sorry for her.
You were just born.
Why were you attracted to Samba-san?
I was attracted to Samba-san right after I was born.
You were attracted to Samba-san.
That's right.
So?
When I first saw Matsumoto-san, I thought,
she's like Niel-DK.
She's like Minami-Muki.
That's really funny.
I see.
That's what I thought at first.
I saw Madori right away.
Where did you see her?
I don't know if she's Niel-DK or not.
I saw her right away.
I thought she was Niel-DK.
Matsumoto-san, I have a question.
The mole under your eye is called a crybaby.
What is the mole above your eye?
The mole above my eye is called a crybaby.
That's too easy.
There's no mole above my eye.
What?
Did you think the mole was a crybaby?
You're stupid.
I didn't think it was a mole.
That's how it is, everyone.
Everyone is the same.
Do you know what a crybaby is?
No.
It's easy to make a crybaby.
Is that right?
It's called a talkbaby.
People who have mole there talk a lot.
Really?
Yes.
People who cry a lot get a crybaby.
People who laugh a lot are called upper there.
You have to talk about upper there, don't you?
Some people cry a lot...
Some people cry a lot.
Some people cry a lot, some laugh a lot, some get angry a lot...
There are a lot, right?
Some people cry a lot.
The person who cries a lot, is the boss.
And you cry more than that person?
It's not like that!
It's not what you think it is!
The person who cries a lot is the boss, right?
That's not what it is!
It's above the one who cries the most.
No!
It's completely different.
If it's a simple solution, then what does it mean?
You don't need to solve it.
But there's nothing in this.
So, even if it's above the one who cries the most,
it's not below the one who cries the most.
It's above the one who cries the most.
I don't get it.
What do you mean by above?
So, it's above the one who cries the most!
What are you talking about?
But, that's...
It's below! It's above!
Hey!
No, it's above.
It's above.
It's above the one who cries the most.
What are you talking about?
I don't get it.
You!
Die!
You die!
Be more proud of yourself!
You die at the top!
Be proud of yourself!
Be proud of yourself at the top!
Emergency!
A child's use, a long-awaited video creation.
The masterpiece of Mamoru-shu.
The perfect uncut version of that famous scene.
On sale to great acclaim.
The second volume will be released on July 21.
Please look forward to it!