This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
The usual dressing room for children.
A peaceful moment before the show.
But now, a man appears with a foreboding of a storm.
Let's go.
The director, Hidena Sakamoto.
Wherever he goes, he is always with his beloved bird.
His gentle personality and a calm smile always warmly embrace us.
Life itself is happiness.
But his hidden face is about to be revealed today.
What's up, Hama-chan?
You're so hot.
I wanted to go with you.
You wanted to go with me?
Yes, I did.
Where did you go, Machan?
I went to Chocochoco.
Where did you go?
I don't usually like it this much.
Where did you go to Chocochoco?
I went on a trip.
A trip?
I wonder if it's going to be good.
I'm looking forward to your lunch.
What's this?
What's going on?
This?
This egg is not here.
What's going on?
It's different.
Is it good?
Yes.
What's good?
What's good about this bento?
Is it good?
It's not good, is it?
It's not good?
It's not good.
Is it good?
It's well balanced.
It's like this.
It's not good.
Get out of the way.
I don't like this bento.
Ok, let's go.
Today, I'm going to show you guys something delicious.
What's this?
I'm going to make it for you.
In front of us, a man takes off his veil.
In addition to birds, he also controls fire.
He makes fire dishes.
This is what people call him.
What's this?
I'm going to make it for you.
I don't need it.
Why are you sleeping?
Oh, it's in.
Let's go to the bed.
What's this?
I don't know what it is.
It's scary.
Hey, hey, hey.
Open it.
Give me an egg.
An egg.
Is it me?
There's an egg in here.
Do you want me to take it out?
Yes.
It would be nice if you brought it.
Is one enough?
One is enough.
Yes.
Hold it.
My partner.
Why?
It's coming out.
Cut the egg.
Yes.
Do you have a knife?
I'll do it for you.
What size should I cut it into?
About two fourths.
Half.
Huh?
Two fourths.
Half and half?
You guys aren't doing anything.
I don't know.
You guys are just messing around.
It's good.
Sakamoto-san, this isn't right.
It doesn't fit in here.
You shouldn't have said that.
I've been wanting to do this for a long time.
I'm losing my energy.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
What is that?
It can't be helped.
It's everyone's service today.
Yamazaki, did you mix it?
Yes, yes, yes.
Did you mix it?
Yes.
What is that?
What's written on it?
It's something over there.
This is Itamon's wine.
What?
It's a strong wine.
Is that so?
This is it.
It's the vinegar of the grape.
It's vinegar.
Vinegar.
E.S.T.R.A.M.O.
Yes, the smell of meat is gone.
Yes, yes.
That's how you put the wine.
The smell of meat.
Boil it properly.
What are you talking about?
Oh, he's back.
He's back.
He's not coming back.
He's not coming back?
He's back, he's back.
Scary!
Ta-da!
Eat it.
It took a long time.
Eat it, eat it.
What kind of food is this?
This is...
Sakamoto D Omelette.
Sakamoto D Omelette is tasteless.
See you next week.
Thank you.
Let's have a good lunch.
This time, it's not going to be like this.
That was scary.
Ladies and gentlemen.
It's been a long time.
Right?
Well, well.
It's the first time this year.
Do you know why the monitor is showing?
Oh, really? Why is it showing?
It's not usual.
It's not scary.
The amazing thing is...
The people who are watching you on TV...
They say you're amazing.
Don't do that.
There are a lot of people like that these days.
Wait a minute.
I'm praising you.
I'm saying you're amazing.
Someone else is coming.
What do you mean?
You've been called a big brother before.
That's not true.
I'm just a kid.
What? What?
Last year, you spoke in a talk show.
Yes, yes, yes.
It was perfect.
I...
Oh, yes, yes.
What is it all of a sudden?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Well, I'll watch it.
I've answered a lot of other questions in this talk show.
Why are you suddenly feeling better?
No, no, no.
What is it?
Let's take a look.
That's right.
This way.
Let me tell you something.
Stop being angry.
What are you talking about?
Who would be happy with that?
If you were happy with that, you were still eating cup noodles.
In the 1950s.
The air is over.
After the air is over, we're going to talk about today's event.
Yes.
Part of the pedestrian heaven in Harajuku, Tokyo.
Due to the noise and traffic jam of the rock band.
From today, it will be disbanded.
A year ago.
You predicted a lack of glasses.
How did it turn out?
What else is going to happen this year?
The Earth.
It's a huge planet.
A very, very big planet.
I'm going to go up.
Around Australia on Earth.
This program was brought to you by the sponsor you are watching.
10 items of it, a rare item that can be seen as a meteorite.
This.
This is the Udo of the employee who was watching the air.
Amazing.
I didn't get told that he was amazing.
But he was watching this.
Amazing.
That's what he said.
That's right.
How many years have you been doing this program?
4 or 5 years?
7 years.
7 years?
You've been doing it for 7 years.
It's not just this.
I didn't get to say it, but there's a lot more.
What is there?
There's really a lot more.
Say that.
There are only two now.
What is it?
What did you say?
Tell me what you guessed.
That's why I said there's a lot more.
What is it, Kinpatsu-san?
There's 20 to 30.
This is bad.
No, no, no.
Just say one.
But it's really amazing.
Regarding the meteorite, this is a prophecy, right?
What's a prophecy?
It's a divine thing.
Regarding the meteorite.
Regarding the prophecy,
the flow of the world, or rather, what everyone is thinking,
all of it, how do I say this,
with all the antennas hanging around,
all of it, the flow of the world is being read.
I don't get it.
The flow of the world is being read.
I see.
I also knew that Murayama-san would quit.
Well, I heard it on the phone.
Wait.
It's light.
Well, that's how it is.
I'm looking forward to this year.
Because I already knew that you were going to be in Kouhaku last year.
Last year?
That's right.
Last year, I didn't say it yet.
I said it in March.
That's right.
Why did I say I was going to be in Kouhaku in January?
I already knew that.
My voice is getting smaller.
Why have you been looking at my nipples since this year?
You bully me.
Well, it's fine.
You...
What?
The story is a bit old-fashioned, but...
Yes.
When you looked at my face,
you had a really funny face.
Right?
Well, I said it, but it was a bit high.
It wasn't high?
When I was in Kouhaku, it wasn't high.
It was a bit high.
You...
My staff said that you were high.
Why wasn't I high?
Why weren't you high?
That's because I was high on stage.
No, no, no.
You weren't high.
No, it was like this.
My face was like this.
First of all, when everyone was going like this, you were going up like this.
You were going up like this.
At that time, I went down like this.
I found Hamada like this.
I didn't know Hamada yet.
When I was going like this,
you had a really happy face.
A real entertainer is a person whose teeth are life.
Right?
It was like Miki Sakugawa.
I said Saki-chan.
You didn't say it.
Well...
I'll start.
The one who eats sardines.
I know, I know.
After I was introduced to you.
The Kitajima Family.
It seems that they gather once a year as a family and have a banquet.
They eat sardines and drink alcohol.
What do they do after that?
Mr. Matsumoto of the Kitajima Family, please tell me.
I'm also a family member.
No, no, no.
I've been in the family for a long time.
Who is the one at the top?
Who is the one under Mr. Kitajima?
The eldest son is George.
Ah, George Yamamoto.
I understand.
What's next?
The one under George is...
Matsubara Nobue.
You know it, don't you?
That's right. That's exactly right.
I mean, you know it, don't you?
I'm a family member.
What are you?
I'm under Matsubara Nobue.
He's really loved by everyone.
He's a scoundrel.
I've always been under Matsubara Nobue.
You're lying.
I'm telling the truth.
You've always been under Matsubara Nobue.
That's right. I've always been under Matsubara Nobue.
It's a nice New Year's Eve, George.
Ah, you've fallen in love with George.
You were like this at that time.
I've always been like this.
Don't lie to me.
I've always been following him around.
What do you eat?
I eat Katsunoko.
Ah, George. It's a nice New Year's Eve, George.
I'm definitely not a scoundrel.
I'm also under the age of my father.
Under the age of your father?
From my father.
How old are you?
I'm like a family member.
What?
I don't understand.
Do you do karaoke?
I don't do karaoke.
Ah, I see. You don't do karaoke.
I have an annual event every year.
Ah, I see.
I write a lot of events.
From what time to what time.
Do you have a schedule?
Yes, I do.
I've already eaten.
I've already drank.
What time is that?
About noon?
That's about 6 o'clock in the evening.
What time do you do it?
About 7 in the morning.
That's enough!
Let's go home!
From 6 o'clock in the evening...
I start drawing flowers.
Wait a minute.
Drawing flowers?
Well then, let's do it, George.
Let's do it.
What do you have prepared?
I have thick brushes.
Huh?
You're not going to lose, George!
A draw card!
I've eaten.
I'm going crazy at this point.
Get out of the way!
What's with you?
They told me to get out of my way from the ramen.
I want to have a cup of rice this year.
When that's over.
When that's over, you'll be a threat again.
Two times?
Two times.
You guys are pretty funny.
I didn't do anything!
You're the funny one!
When I can't get along with my boss, I don't have the courage to fight or stop the time.
Please tell us in detail about the incident when Matsumoto-san quit after a big fight with a salaryman.
Yes, yes, yes.
Did you do it?
I worked as a salaryman for about four years.
I got promoted pretty fast.
What do you mean, promoted?
I got promoted fast.
You were promoted, right?
I was promoted.
Really?
Yes.
What did you do when you quit?
I was a manager.
What do you mean, a manager?
You've been a manager for four years?
I forgot.
I was a new manager.
Manager...
Manager's secretary?
Not secretary.
Manager Kokoroe?
Kokoroe! Kokoroe!
You called me Kokoroe!
What is that?
I was called Manager Kokoroe.
What is Manager Kokoroe?
What company was that?
Interior.
A company that makes lighting equipment.
What were you doing there?
What?
A company that makes lighting equipment.
Presentation.
What?
What's a presentation?
It's a presentation.
You went to a pretty good place. Why?
Well, this time, I had a lot of...
I had a business trip overseas.
I see.
So I had a fight.
With the Arabs.
With the Arabs?
I had a fight with the Arab manager.
The Arab manager kept pushing me.
I was really angry.
You didn't quit?
No.
If I do this again tomorrow, Yutaro will...
Well, at least for a day.
At least for a day.
I don't know if it was my imagination.
It's funny.
The story behind the necktie.
Tell us three things you've gained from having your necktie under your belt.
Of course there are three.
The first thing.
First of all, when you go to a butcher shop, even if you say 300g, they usually put in 400g.
Eh? Eh? Put it in?
Yes, put it in.
You say, is it okay?
It's funny.
It's the funniest.
You say, is it okay?
You say, please give me 300g of this part.
Yes, Mr. Inga.
You say, is it okay to put in 300g?
When you go home, they usually put in 400g.
Well, they also take 400g of money.
What is that?
Toku-chan!
Well, there's a lot of other things.
After that, there's that thing, right?
There's that thing where you can hug a woman as much as you want.
Why?
First of all, if you're seen by me...
If you're seen by me?!
What kind of guy are you trying to hug?
Are you going to the hospital?
If you're seen by me...
If I look at you...
If you look at me and say, I like you, I can definitely do it.
This is the power of the tie.
I wonder why that happens.
I don't know why.
I don't know why you put it in.
I didn't put it in today.
I didn't put it in today, so I don't have any strength.
If you put it in, most of them will be like this.
What?
In sports, your muscles are more activated than usual.
That's why.
You get the power you don't usually get.
What do you mean?
For example, I usually run at 50 meters in 6.5 seconds.
Usually.
Depending on whether you put on a tie or not, it's about 4 seconds.
Even now?
Yes.
If you put in a tie, your feet won't move, right?
My feet move fast.
If you put it in a tie.
What do you want me to do?
It's okay.
It's okay, but when you're running, you have to take it off.
All at once.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
It's going to be a mess.
Oh, no.