The next day
Dad, I've become a director!
What were you looking at?
Excuse me.
Dad, I've become a director!
Don't get in my way.
You'll get in trouble if you do that.
It's not good for the company.
Don't talk about my plans.
I don't have the talent.
Damn it.
Hang in there.
Ms. Tsuka.
Ms. Hamada and Mr. Matsumoto.
Five seconds to go.
Hey, there's a weird guy.
Hey, look at him.
What's up with him?
What are you doing?
Mr. Otomo.
That's not it.
I couldn't do anything to Otomo.
I just wanted to protect him.
He's my heart.
Look at me.
There's no scar.
This is manliness.
Otomo.
You're looking good, Otomo.
Mr. Matsumoto, a producer doesn't just make a show.
He makes people.
I don't know if that's true.
Die, you guys.
What are you guys?
Nothing.
Die, you guys.
You guys are all dead.
You're so stupid.
I want to go home at the end.
We're both downtown.
Sometimes there's a stupid guy.
Right in front of you.
Why are you guys all enemies?
Why are you guys so mean?
It's not like that.
When I look at you, I'm more manly.
I'm more handsome.
It's a matter of course.
What?
I'm saying I'm hungry.
There's a beef stew over here.
There's no one who's going to eat it.
Wait a minute.
You're a beef stew.
I'm a mozuku.
I'm hungry.
I've been eating for three days.
It's the same thing.
I'm sorry.
I don't know if that's what you said.
It's really weird.
I think you're a big fan.
If there's a fan from Fukuyama or Kimura Takuya, it's a big deal.
That's what I think.
When I think about downtown, I need a male fan and a female fan.
But I'm the one who attracts female fans.
You don't have any female fans.
You're not attractive.
Wait a minute.
What are the requirements of a man?
For example, there's a sense of cleanliness.
What is it?
It's slippery.
It's not shark skin.
If you have a wife and children, it's slippery.
It's not slippery.
A boy like me.
Are you stupid?
It's slippery.
It doesn't matter.
What is it?
I'm in a trance.
Let's take it easy.
I don't have much time today, but I'll be back soon.
You guys are just passing by.
We're going to come out, right?
To be honest, there are so many people in one place.
I don't know if it's rude, but it stinks.
I don't think it's right to say that.
You guys.
It's stimulating.
Don't say that.
It's a burden on our bodies.
It's going to sting.
I don't have much time today.
What is it?
Did you have a new sister?
You're so popular.
But it's amazing.
It's hard to shake it off.
I guess so.
Are you running away?
I'm running away.
When I walk down the street, I'm told to get married.
When you walk down the street?
When I stand up.
When I close my eyes, I feel like I'm going to faint.
He's running away.
It's amazing.
I feel like I'm going to get a shiver.
A shiver?
It's amazing.
When I open my stomach, I feel like I'm going to get a cookie.
What is it? Is it a snack?
It's money.
The other day, I was going to use this as an opportunity.
I have to get married.
I went to Belfare.
I didn't expect that.
How was it?
I thought it was going to be more amazing.
But it wasn't that exciting.
Really?
I was doing it naturally.
Like this.
I wasn't doing it like this.
But I was excited to some extent.
What are you talking about?
You were excited.
I was doing it naturally.
I don't really need that.
But the staff told me to do it naturally.
So I sat down.
I see.
I don't talk when I'm sitting down.
I really do.
I can't stop shivering.
You take someone who can't stop shivering home.
I can't help it.
I think I have to do something.
What do you mean you have to do something?
I have to do something.
I have to make a girlfriend.
Why are you laughing?
No, you're making me angry.
Your attitude is like, don't lie.
I don't lie.
That's Yamada-san's style.
It's because you're half-laughing.
I'm not half-laughing.
You're not half-laughing.
You're half-laughing.
No, no, no.
I'm serious.
You can say you're serious from the beginning.
Right?
I'm jealous of your life.
You're lying.
Your wonderful home.
I've never seen it.
Right?
I'm really happy to see you happy.
I want to have a home like that soon.
An ideal home.
Right?
That's right.
A big mansion.
You live in a big house.
No, no.
No, no, no.
That's right.
You say, hey.
Hey.
Who?
That's a bit too much.
I think I'll be longing for a home like that.
Really.
What do you think?
One or two things.
You have to ignore them.
Getting married.
Right?
Right.
I can't help it.
You can't do that.
I can't.
Even if you have a good personality.
If you look closely, you have a little bit of a mimi-kuso.
I don't want to marry a mimi-kuso.
I don't want such a
Why do you want a mimi-kuso?
I don't think there's such a place.
Is that so?
I'm looking for it in the newspaper.
Of course I'm looking for it.
What are you doing?
You guys are so annoying.
I haven't met anyone who does this kind of work.
That's true.
I want a woman who is about 40 years old.
That's a lie.
Why?
You should be younger than you are.
What are you doing?
Do you want to hear it?
Each person has a different sense of value.
Yes.
Please arrange the next three in the order that you shouldn't do it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Furin.
Medicine.
Baishun.
Now, Mr. Hamada.
That's medicine.
As expected, I don't say Furin.
I see.
That's medicine, isn't it?
Why is that bad?
It's a warning.
If you do that, you'll break your body.
In the sense that it will be useless.
Baishun doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter, but...
I agree with that.
If you don't want Baishun, then...
It doesn't matter, but...
But it's difficult to say how much Baishun you want.
My mother is Baishun.
She earns money from her father and eats rice.
And then she stabs him.
Sorry.
I'll ask you a question.
What is the worst thing you do?
Medicine.
And then?
Baishun.
Please stop.
You don't know anything.
What do you mean?
Is Furin okay?
I can't say it's okay.
Are you usually like that?
It's all bad, but I think Furin is the worst.
I don't think so.
Why didn't you get married until you were 31?
Because you couldn't get close to one person.
On the contrary, you said you would never cheat on your wedding day.
But you decided to get married after you had a belly.
That's not true.
It's hard to say that Furin is your partner.
Don't cry.
There is a shop near my house.
It's been a year since it was written that it was being used by Baishun.
What's going on in the store?
It's a bad joke.
It's just a joke.
It's a good joke.
Why are you so serious?
When I get home, I'll tell the three of them that Machan is amazing.
Is it different?
It's different.
Unlike in the old days, it's very effective now.
If it's a normal cockroach, it will die.
There is a king of cockroaches.
Is there such a person?
It's like a cockroach in a cockroach.
It's like a man in a man.
That's right.
How big is it?
It's three and a half meters.
It's not a cockroach.
I've been holding it for about a year.
Something's wrong with my head.
You've never seen it, have you?
What do you mean?
The king of cockroaches.
What is it?
That's why I'm telling you.
Where?
Of course, in the kitchen.
When I went to the kitchen, the king of cockroaches said,
What is it?
That's what the king of cockroaches said.
That's what he said.
He told me to get some soy sauce.
The king of cockroaches gave it to me.
Can you tell me the nickname of Mr. Matsumoto's Nanamagari Shochidai?
I want to tell you.
I want to believe you.
Of course.
That was probably in 1947 or 1948.
It started with the sun.
Right?
That's the world of dramas.
When did you and Nanamagari Shochidai meet?
This is...
You're so noisy.
Don't come to me all of a sudden.
You're talking like it's normal.
It was just a change of place.
A change of place?
Are you saying this is a drama?
I didn't buy anything like that!
This is Mr. Matsumoto!
That's fine, but...
It was just a change of place.
What did he say?
I don't want to say this.
Mecha-boin!
He's a man.
He was shaking a lot.
Was he fat?
I don't know if he was fat.
He said,
To Mr. Yama.
Mr. Yama, you're so light.
Mr. Yama said,
Huh?
You're...
Mecha-boin!
Is that so?
He said, Is that so?
Then the boss came back right away.
And he said,
You're going to be Mecha-boin from today.
The last one was terrible.
The way he died.
Did he die of fasting?
Of course he did.
Really?
What kind of way did he die?
He was a really bad guy.
He was beaten up a lot.
Mecha-boin!
By the five or six guys.
He was beaten up!
Ouch! Ouch!
I was the only one who got to the place of the transaction.
You infiltrated?
I infiltrated.
There was no time for everyone to wait.
The transaction was about to end.
He said, Wait!
Mecha-boin!
But he was like,
What the hell!
Aren't you a good father?
Stop it!
Ouch! Ouch!
And then...
Why did you die?
They...
They don't even know how to act.
From now on...
They're just playing dumb.
Let's go to the next scene.
Scene!
I made you the director...
Not to do such a stupid job.
Leave it to me.
It was too early for Otomo.
Right?
Cut!
I've never seen such a bad guy.
He was like, Oh!
Cut!
He was laughing.
Sura-chan!
Good job, Sura-chan.
Thank you.
It's still NG, isn't it?
NG!
I...
I made you the director...
Not to do such a stupid job.
Leave it to me.
It was too early for Otomo.
What are you doing?
I'm tired.
Can you give me a break?
I can't do this.
Sura-chan is doing it so well.
It's easy to stop him.
Thank you.
I made you the director...
Not to do such a stupid job.
Leave it to me.
Thank you, everyone.