Pikkashi Kankan is here to entertain you!
Now, it's time for Pikkashi Kankan.
I'm here to entertain you.
I'm the mascot of Gaki no Tsukai, Pricci Suzuki.
I'm an announcer.
Now, let's welcome the team to the stage.
It's the Hama-chan team and the Machan team.
Now, let's introduce ourselves.
Let's start with the Machan team.
I'm Okkun, also known as Matsumoto Hitoshi.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Takahashi Harumi, an amateur.
I'm Keiko Oe, from Saitama prefecture.
Nice to meet you.
Now, it's the Hama-chan team.
Good evening.
I'm Otomo, from Chofu prefecture.
Nice to meet you.
I'm the manager from Tokyo, Nitta.
The manager, Nitta-san, is also here.
I'll do my best!
Now, let's hear from the captains.
What?
I'm sorry.
It's late at night, so I can't help it.
I'd like to hear about your enthusiasm.
Let's start with the Machan captain.
I'm not going to lose to these dirty, rotten guys.
It's our fault, right?
You look a bit like Chibita.
Now, let's start with the first question.
It's late at night, at 1.40 p.m., sometimes it's 2.10 p.m.
Everyone, wake up and look at this.
What are you talking about?
This is a photo.
Please look at this.
This is the photo of today's guest.
This is the person in this photo.
Is that the person?
The little girl on the right?
That's me.
Now, who is the owner of this photo?
Let's hear from the Machan team.
Fuse Akira.
You're younger than me.
That's a bit different.
Oh Sadaharu-san.
It's similar.
How is it?
Kuruma Dankichi-san.
Ah...
Now, the Machan team.
Nitta Junichi.
Isn't that a bit too young?
Tachi Hiroshi.
Kuruka?
Sakagami Jiro.
It looks like you're a bit off track.
Now, the Machan team.
Morishinichi.
U-chan.
Watanabe Masayuki-san.
Now, the Machan team.
Are you laughing?
Well, I guess you could say that.
Don't think too much.
You have to say it properly.
You're annoying.
You're wearing that brown outfit.
I don't know your name very well, but it's you.
Now, Hamada-san.
Captain Morishinichi.
You're still saying Hamada?
Really?
Did you say Hakashin-go?
Morishinichi-san.
It's a bit different.
Atsumi Jiro-san.
You're saying Sannosen-yan.
Hazama Kanpei-san.
It's a bit of a shame that Boo came out.
Now, let's have the guest of the day come on stage.
Please.
Let's go!
It's Saito-san.
But, you know, you have a cute face when you're little.
Don't I look like him?
You do!
I didn't think you'd become so big that you'd get electrocuted.
The kids are watching, too.
How old were you when you took this picture?
About five years from now, right?
Your mouth is a bit different now, too.
You used to be so chubby back then.
Why are you so chubby now?
I used to be chubby.
I changed all my teeth.
I had braces, but they came out again.
They do!
You're funny!
Like this, you've overcome 30 difficulties.
You bastard!
Don't talk to me like that!
I'm free to do whatever I want!
Thank you very much.
I'm done with you!
I'm going to electrocute you!
Now, let's have Saito-san, the director of Kiseki who has overcome his difficulties and grown up to this point.
When Saito-san drinks, he always electrocutes the girl sitting next to him.
At that time, he said,
I saw you and I got electrocuted.
But what exactly is this electrocution?
Now, Machan Team!
I saw you and I got smaller.
You're doing it!
Now, Hama-chan Team!
We often go to karaoke together.
The girl sitting next to me asked me to marry her.
So I wanted to marry her.
You're a little too direct.
I wanted to do it.
Thank you very much.
I'm sure you'll understand.
I got electrocuted.
Don't say you got electrocuted.
With this face.
Then, since it's a live performance today, how do you always say it?
Even me, even Hamada-san.
I got electrocuted.
I didn't want to show it to the general public.
This guy.
At Hamada's wedding, when he said hello, he hit the microphone.
Fuji TV is so quiet.
That's not Nerotan.
He hit the microphone.
Speaking of Matsumoto-san's hobby,
It's watching adult videos.
This video title is...
Oki-san, isn't it good?
Chome-chome-chome-chome.
What is this chome-chome-chome-chome?
Yes, Hamada-san.
Oki-san, isn't it good?
You're wet, aren't you?
I see.
It's not about being wet or not being wet.
Just like that!
You know, in the quiz, you're pulling the audience.
You're completely pulling them.
Next.
Yes.
Oki-san, isn't it good? I'm wet, aren't I?
That's enough.
You're pulling the audience.
Oki-san.
You're mean.
If you say something like that, it's not mean.
There aren't many girls, so you shouldn't say something like that.
That's a good story.
Next.
Oki-san, isn't it good?
I'm f***ing crazy.
Hello, hello.
It's really...
You're doing well today.
I'm doing well today.
How do I say this?
It depends on the situation, so it's difficult.
That's right.
My face is facing this way, but...
It's like this.
That's right.
Women are like that.
They're like that.
I thought they were laughing until now, but suddenly they have energy.
But...
They're like that.
That's right.
Women are like that.
Men are like that when they're excited.
Women are like that until just now.
What the hell is this?
It's like the Kikurin of Bebop.
That's right.
Women are really difficult.
So I don't know anything about women and the weather in the mountains.
Men have the same personality throughout the year.
That's not true.
It's annoying.
There are days when I'm irritated, right?
I'm not. I'm not.
I'm a talent without a back.
But my head is a bit of a talent.
Don't say rude things.
I can't laugh or clap.
What?
It's bad when you're in a bad mood.
I'm not in a bad mood.
I'm in a bad mood because I don't care if I'm in a bad mood.
You...
Don't touch me.
It hurts. It hurts. It hurts a lot.
You're weak when you look at your juniors.
Your juniors?
You're strong.
You're like this.
You're good at using your lower body.
I've never used my lower body.
Where are you going?
Come closer.
Do you know how much your juniors hate you?
What are you talking about?
There's a junior called Higashino.
He's a good kid.
Who are you going to hook up with?
Who?
What?
When are you going to hook up with him?
You're going to the disco and going to the VIP room.
Bring the guy in the red clothes.
You're still doing it.
Don't listen to what he says and what I say.
It's me, right?
Look at me.
Look at my face.
You said it yourself.
I didn't say anything.
Let's forget about that.
What are you talking about?
What do you think of me?
That's right.
Higashino is 10 minutes late.
He's the same age as Kondo.
He's 10 minutes late.
Everyone is late, especially when they're young.
Why aren't you answering me?
Then he comes and says,
I'm sorry.
He catches a junior who says he's sorry.
This is a fairy tale.
You.
I did it for you.
And humans are...
I think you'll understand if you're a little soft-hearted.
You're a soft-hearted man.
You're a judoka.
You're a little...
If you think you're going to get hit, don't tighten your abs.
Humans are like that.
You get hit a little and you're like that.
But if you let your guard down, you'll get hit.
It's like you're working out.
The day I came with this guy,
I kicked him like this.
My muscles were loose, so I kicked him.
This time difference attack.
They both got hit in the face.
No, that's a dangerous story.
I did it for you.
I was late the day before.
I was late for two days in a row.
That's right.
Those two are the kids you care about.
If you get angry,
I can't go to play like I always do.
If you get angry at someone you care about.
That's why I've been late for two days in a row.
I don't want you to get hurt.
What the hell are you guys doing?
Bang!
Do you know Hanako Yamada?
Wait a minute.
That's not what I meant.
Tell me if that's what you did.
Hanako Yamada.
She had a wonderful dream.
She was on TV on Sunday.
When she came to the pool,
she couldn't calm down.
What do you think she did?
She wrapped herself in a blanket.
Hanako Yamada was like this.
I didn't like that either.
Wait a minute.
You had a blanket on your back, too.
I'm a human being.
So you were having fun at that time.
You didn't tell me you were on a strike.
I didn't.
I didn't do anything.
I had a reason to do it.
I took her to the back of the mountain in Rokko.
I told her not to do it naked.
I beat her up.
I pulled her leg.
I didn't like that.
Wait a minute.
You took her to Rokko, but you didn't beat her up.
I didn't beat her up.
I didn't.
Why did you take her to the back of the mountain in Rokko
and beat her up?
I beat her up.
I didn't do anything.
You were training her.
What?
She's a little weak.
She's a little stubborn.
That's why I beat her up.
What did you do?
I didn't do anything.
I took her to the back of the mountain in Rokko.
I didn't beat her up.
I didn't do anything.
Do you know Mina?
What?
What did you do?
Do you know Mina?
She's a little girl.
Do you know her?
I beat her up.
Wait.
That's not it.
You didn't move like that.
Who did that?
That's what I saw.
I don't know.
I was sitting like this.
I was talking like this.
I was like this.
I lost the game.
But...
I was wearing a jacket like this.
Right?
I don't know how many people there are.
I was wearing a jacket like this.
Right?
I don't know how many people there are.
You said 12 people.
Why did it take so long?
I almost said 2 people.
It's similar.
12 people and 2 people.
I almost said 2 people.
It's similar.
You're just an idiot.
What?
I don't care about that.
I don't know women.
You said something like that.
I can't think of anything.
It's like this.
What?
A poop?
Don't say stupid things.
You're a kid.
I wanted to say that.
I'm sorry.
It happens sometimes.
A young comedian's egg on TV.
It's not a big deal.
It's like this.
A poop?
It's amazing, right?
What?
You're a kid.
It's amazing, right?
What?
I don't understand.
It hurts when your little finger hits the pillar.
In the corner.
Like this.
10 times as much as that.
More?
Is that a thumb?
It's not a thumb.
What I'm saying is that it hurts.
It's a little finger, so it's not a thumb.
Let's ask Umekichi.
Women are women, right?
Do you know where your mother hides her napkin?
So what?
You know, so what?
You can't just take it.
Are you putting the key away?
Bring your notes.
You're blushing.
Are you cold?
If you're going to read,
put your fingers and your napkin in the corner.
Put your fingers and your napkin in the corner.
Do you want to introduce her?
I'll introduce her right away.
Komori Toshiko.
19 years old.
Chiba Prefecture.
That's enough.
You can show me later.
Tennis, skiing, golf.
My hobby is karaoke and diet.
I see.
My hobby is fortress and physical education.
Thank you very much.
It's time to read.
Let's read this.
My mother watches TV.
Oh, there's a bump.
Does it look like me?
I'm good at tapping.
Young comedian watching TV.
I'm a comedian.
Let's go to the next place.
The result of the golf tournament will be announced next week.
Please watch it.
After that, we'll play a penalty game.
When should we play a penalty game?
Let's do our best again.
Do not look away.
I'm trying to do it.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll let you know the result next week.
Hey, wait a minute.
I'm not asking you.
I'll let you know next week.
Next week, it's golf.
I'll let you know the result.
Oh, I see.
I'll ask for your assistance.
Please don't worry about it.
No, I can't do that.
He wants to quit golf and get an assassin.
I don't like it.
What?
I'll do my best until next week! Goodbye!