Next time on Gaki no Tsukai Arai, Tsuki Tsuki Henshin Bijouate Contest!
Today's opening act is amazing.
There's a person with a slightly frowning face.
It's a simple game to guess who that person is.
Let's introduce the answer right away.
The director of Takasu Clinic is Mr. Takasu Katsuya.
Nice to meet you.
I'm a professional, so please look at me carefully.
Next to me is Ms. Kiyoko Takagi.
Nice to meet you.
And last but not least, Mr. Hitoshi Matsumoto, a man of justice.
Hello.
Have you ever been called a man of justice?
No, I have a license for that.
You have two licenses?
I have a license.
Yes.
You're a professional, aren't you?
That's right.
With your teacher?
With a certain eye?
Teacher, that's a license.
Liar!
Let's go to the first question.
Here it comes!
How many of you have a license?
That's the first question.
Wait a minute.
You're not going to tell me where it is, are you?
You can just say your face.
Yes.
It's a tattoo.
I don't really understand, but when was it?
When did you get it?
That's right.
I got it this year.
This year?
That's right. It was about three months ago.
It's not a very meaningful question, is it?
Then just say it!
In a month, the tattoo will be gone.
I have a question.
Yes.
What made you the happiest when you got your license?
Well, I'm happy when people tell me I'm cute.
When I put on makeup.
When you put on makeup?
Why is your hair so messy?
It's because I did it.
It's because I saw myself.
Everyone, please come up to the stage.
Let's start with Mr. Takatsu.
Number two, number four.
Mr. Takagi.
Number one.
Mr. Miyaburiman.
Number four, your hair is so messy, right?
I think that's a fake tattoo.
That's not true.
Let's start.
The real tattooist is this person.
The correct answer is number two and number four.
Mr. Miyaburiman.
Amazing.
The tattooist does it to be beautiful.
So if you don't choose a beautiful person, there's no mistake.
But number four has more hair than number four.
That's why I know this.
This is the last question.
You successfully went on a diet.
It's already beautiful.
It's done to be beautiful.
So let's have that person answer.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Please ask everyone a question.
He's inside.
Can I ask how many months you lost weight?
That's a good question.
How many months did you lose weight?
About half a year.
Half a year?
How many kilograms?
How many kilograms did you lose weight?
I lost 30 kilograms in half a year.
How many kilograms did you lose before losing weight?
Before losing weight?
65 kilograms.
Before losing weight, 65 kilograms.
How many months?
How many kilograms?
17 kilograms in four months.
It's the most reasonable number.
The tattooist is...
It's the most painful number.
How many kilograms before losing weight?
110 kilograms.
110 kilograms?
How many kilograms did you lose before losing weight?
Before losing weight,
the tattooist didn't make a fuss if an animal or something approached him.
How many kilograms did you lose before losing weight?
30 kilograms.
30 kilograms?
Ask him what his nickname was when he was fat.
Is that so?
Fatty.
He's a fatty.
What was his nickname when he was fat?
Dadan.
Butcher.
Please draw your answer.
Please draw your answer, Mr. Takahashi.
Number two.
Mr. Takagi.
This is my hope.
I want this to happen.
You want this to happen, right?
I understand.
Number two.
Number three.
One by one, please come out from the box on the back.
First, number one.
Please come out.
Hey.
I'm powering you up.
Number two, please come out.
Please come out.
Number two.
Wow.
You're happy?
If you draw your answer, your father will come out, right?
I drew my answer.
Your father is a cat?
Yes.
He's a cat now.
But I'd rather draw my answer before I get fat.
Hey.
Don't say that.
This person is Masumoto's hope.
This is...
It's even thinner.
Please come out.
Number three, please come out.
It's open.
Wow.
Amazing.
Hey, hey, hey.
Number two.
What do you think of number one and number three?
I went to an aesthetic shop.
I recommend that.
You go to an aesthetic shop.
If you pay first, you can buy it with your guts.
I see.
So if you say you're going to pay little by little later, it won't last long.
By the way, if number three has that kind of money, he'll eat something sweet.
Hello.
How are you doing recently?
What do you mean?
I'm thinking.
There are many kinds of luck, right?
Yes.
Do you have any good luck?
Good luck...
I have...
Chigami luck.
Well...
This is Matsumoto's aesthetic luck.
Chigami luck is really bad.
You can't get it when you want it.
Well...
You go to the toilet, right?
You poop, right?
You poop at the public toilet, right?
I do.
Well, there are times when you don't have Chigami luck.
You don't check it when you go to the public toilet?
If you want to poop, you should open it first.
I open it.
I open it, right?
I have it.
That's good.
I don't have to worry about it anymore.
And when I'm done, I look at it carefully.
It's just a thick roll of paper.
It's just one sheet.
There are times when it's just one sheet.
It's entangled.
Do you call it Chigami luck in that sense?
It's bad. It's too bad.
There's a stock, right?
There is.
It's normal.
You can buy it.
You can buy it?
If I go in, I can't buy it.
I see.
Have you ever bought it?
I went in this year and bought it about five times.
Really, really.
If it's Chigami luck, I've been entangled myself.
I don't have any luck.
It's a toilet where everyone goes in and out.
So I've spent the rest of my life meaningfully.
What's wrong with that?
I raised it.
There's a guy like this.
This guy.
I put this guy in like this.
And then I put it in like this.
I see.
You're going in and out.
I put it in like this.
What's wrong with me?
I shouldn't be doing such a thing.
I can't help it.
But I've been in this year and bought it about three months ago.
I've bought it four or five times.
I'm so angry.
It's not so much outside.
It's sometimes at home.
I can buy it.
I can't help it.
It's annoying.
Why do you think I shouldn't do that?
I can buy it somehow.
I've bought a lot of work.
Some things are hard to do.
But I can do it.
Then...
It's like a telecom.
I can go up here.
I have to tear it by hand.
It's cheap.
It's not like that.
There's a wire.
There's no wire.
But it feels so good...
when two wires meet.
I can't use it.
What?
I can't cut it by myself.
It's a lie.
I've never done that before.
I can't cut it.
I can't stop at the point where the electric wire and the electric wire cross each other.
That's annoying.
That's because I'm taking care of that.
What's the point of this guy?
It's not that he's different, it's just that he doesn't want to get wet.
Ah, he doesn't want to get wet.
I can see it, but it's better to do it properly.
That's why I don't have that luck.
They're all sitting like a stone water அ
Even if he sits like this in the movie theater,
Even if it was empty before,
The air is very tight later
Even if it's just a little bit bisa
Pthat's the annoyance when he stands up
All the big guys sound like married womenI
Don't we?
There is, there is.
He's not that big, so I let him sit in the front.
But he's not that tall.
But his face is like Indica Mai.
What?
Indica Mai.
What's Indica Mai?
It's like a long rice.
I don't get it!
It's like Indica Mai.
It's long?
Yes.
It's good for pilaf.
I don't know about that.
I don't like it when people touch me.
Really?
Yes.
I don't like it when people touch me.
When I was a kid, I got hit by Warabimochi once.
What?
Warabimochi?
Warabimochi is...
Like this.
Warabimochi is like this.
Like this?
Yes.
I got hit by Warabimochi.
I don't get hit by anything else.
I got hit by gum or something.
I got hit by two or three things.
What?
I got hit by a super jet.
I got hit by a belt and a cape.
You got hit by a super jet?
Yes.
You couldn't get hit by it?
No.
You couldn't get it?
heard something.
Is that all?
Yes.
I heard you perched for a while then.
Stop it.
Really?
I heard it only for a week and then stopped.
Also, you know, there is something like this...
A yellow aberration hat with dirt on it and it is sour.
Like a ring.
After I threw it, that yellow hat,
When I threw it, it spread out and
It was such a big stick hat.
I twisted it and folded it.
It became a circle.
It was like a bag.
I put it in and lowered it from the neck.
I said, the sun is coming out.
It spread out.
I put on such a big hat.
Is that funny?
It's a real story.
I'm making it like you.
There are many things in the world.
We have to use them well.
It can't be helped.
The amount of money you've collected and the amount of money you've lost.
Which one is bigger?
Which one is better?
How many have you collected so far?
What?
When I went to school in junior high school.
That's right.
I had about 300,000 yen in my pocket.
It's like a bag you carry when you go to the cram school.
I'm a police officer.
It's like a businessman.
I see.
It's a black leather bag.
When you go to cram school, you have a long string attached to it.
You can hold it like this.
Yes, Mr. Kajibata.
A bag of money.
Bang!
That's right.
It was falling.
When I went to cram school.
What is it?
When I opened it.
When you went to cram school.
Yes.
It's fine.
When I opened it.
When you opened it.
It's a envelope.
It's an envelope.
What is it?
Why are you peeping?
Why don't you peep?
It's amazing.
I'm peeping from above.
It's fine.
There's cash and coins inside.
I brought the police.
I've never really seen anything on the street.
There must be something.
I've never seen a bag of money like this.
Beautiful people get bored in three days.
But ugly people get used to it in three days.
Is that really true?
Please tell me about that.
It's not that I get used to it.
It's more like I want to see it.
I really like the story of ugly people.
Dirty things and smelly things.
It stinks.
But I want you to smell it again.
That's true.
Right?
The ugly woman appears on TV.
I think she's ugly.
I change the channel.
I feel bad.
What did you say twice?
I change the channel.
I smoke again.
I want to see it again.
If it's still on TV...
It's still on TV.
I can't stop laughing.
That's it.
That's what I thought.
That's right.
I can't get used to it.
Did you look for someone after that?
Did you look for someone after Gorilla Man?
I was asked again today.
What is Gorilla Man?
That's a boo.
It was out.
You didn't look for someone after that?
I was asked again today.
Why do people who play sports do that?
It's a little tough.
The heavens give you two things.
I'm attracted to it.
I'm crying.
You're crying.
Sports players are the only ones in the world of manga.
That's right.
It's impossible for a lady to be a lady.
She's very good at tennis.
She's very rich.
She's a high school student, but she's allowed to do it.
She's a lot of money.
That's right.
I won't lose to Hiromi.
He's not going to be there.
If he was a real sports player, he would be very popular.
I want to look for more.
Please give me a postcard.
Continue to Gorilla Man.
The pen name is regrettable, but I'm in love with Hitoshi.
I'm looking for it.
I'd like to tell you something interesting today.
This is a postcard.
This is the title of Go Hiromi's album.
First of all, it's called Hiromi's room.
That's good.
And then, it's called Hiromic World.
It's funny up to here, but there's a stronger one.
It's called Pyramid Hiromid.
That's tough.
There's a disco called Jubilation in Osaka.
It's a disco for Hiromi.
So I made a disco like this.
What should I call Hiromi?
Jubilation.
Which one?
Hiromi.
Look at the menu of Jubilation.
There's a cocktail called Hiromi.
Hiromi will blend it and show it at the store.
No, it's Hiromi.
Hiromi?
Yes.
What do you call that cocktail?
Hiromi.
Who is Hiromi?
It's Hiromi.
When you fight, there's a person who makes a joint sound.
What is that for?
It's a dog sound.
It's only heard by dogs.
It's the same thing as that.
That's why it's called Poki Poki.
With this Poki Poki, it's called Exciting.
Huh?
Exciting is always...
Where are you looking at while talking?
Exciting is...
It's hard to talk.
Exciting is everywhere in the city.
What was the name of that cocktail?
It's Hiromi.
Exciting is feeding on the corner.
Listen to what I'm saying.
I'm telling you so that you can understand.
Come here.
What are you doing?
Poki Poki?
This Poki Poki...
It rides on the wind.
It reaches Exciting.
Exciting didn't know that.
It was feeding on the corner.
Right?
At that time, it heard Poki Poki from somewhere.
It went into Exciting's ear.
Ah!
It's calling me!
And then Exciting came running.
And that fight is Exciting.
I see.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Wait a minute.
In an exciting situation, there is something called Exciting.
That thing?
It's not that thing.
There is something like Exciting's life.
It's a fairy.
Ah...
Is that so?
Huh?
It's not a human.
It's a fairy.
I've seen that Exciting.
It's a man with a scar on his cheek.