Yamazaki Ichiban, Yamazaki Ichiban, Yamazaki Ichiban
This is good.
It's a good song.
No, it's not a good song.
Something's wrong.
Good morning.
What's wrong?
Did I say something wrong?
Something's wrong.
What is it?
I haven't come here yet.
You haven't come yet?
No.
I think there's something different about coming here.
What's different?
I think there's something better.
I think this program will be more exciting.
Do you think so?
Well, I'll say it.
Actually, I read it from Osaka.
I read it or I've been relying on it.
He's got a lot of skills, so I wonder what he's like.
A driver?
Yeah, I'll introduce him.
Is there anyone?
Come in.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Um, um...
The Ritten Investigation Team.
Mizuno Tooru, 37 years old.
Fujiwara Mitsuhiro, 35 years old.
Since the Showa era, they have been doing a lot of comedic things, but this time they have decided to move to Tokyo.
They will challenge a new battle against Kokoriko, by putting their lives on the line in the entertainment world.
I'll make you pay for this!
This program is brought to you by the sponsors you see here.
Let's decide whether to make him a little boy or not.
Oh, that's a good idea.
Let's decide.
After all, Riton has the power to do that.
That's right.
Well, that's the same for little boy.
What can't you do?
Riton can do anything.
He has a lot of ideas.
We can do anything.
Anything.
I'll tell you a little.
Let's go with that.
Let's go with goldfish.
It's an easy story.
You can make goldfish?
Yes, I can.
Really?
Of course.
I can do that much.
I can't do that.
I'll go.
I always eat rice balls and this.
You're the same as me.
It's okay.
I drank only water.
It's OK.
I drank it!
What are you doing?
You are doing this.
This is really amazing as a man.
Really?
Bad Oli.
If you have this, you can break it.
This...
Can you do it?
I don't know where my feet are.
You should kick here.
This is wrong?
Well, for now...
I don't know where my feet are.
You hit it right away.
I'll go.
You're so serious.
It broke!
Amazing!
Look! It broke here!
Did you see that? I was really surprised.
I'm so jealous.
Let's have a tension match.
It's so high.
Let's go.
Wow!
I can't do it!
End!
Funny!
Thank you.
Now, it's fun, but...
If Mizuno were here, he wouldn't be able to do that.
Really?
He's already gone.
Human nuclear power!
Human electronic power!
Ah, it's hot!
Water, water, it's cold.
It's not cold!
What's this?
There's a towel underneath.
Well, well, well, that was...
Well, there are things like that.
It's different.
Ah, it's hot!
I can't stand it anymore!
I'm done!
I get it, I get it, I get it.
Hey!
Let's do the same thing.
What can you do?
Bicycle, tires, live-stay.
I'm good at this.
Right?
It's not that hard.
It's quite bouncy.
That's the other way around.
It stops.
A
I'm gonna hit you!
Stop him!
Leave it to me!
I'm gonna hit you!
Stop him!
Alright!
One shot!
You're gonna do this!
If you're Japanese, then let's do a Japanese dance!
Japanese dance?
A battle to save the soil!
We can't do this, it's the last one!
Start!
Stop!
It's not funny at all.
I wonder what it is.
I thought of it as soon as it started.
I ate Hamada-san's noodles as soon as it started.
I should have stopped it a little earlier.
I thought about it a lot, but I think it's a good idea.
That's right.
Well...
Isn't it?
Well, but...
How is it?
Well, is it worse than before?
Before the Maesetsu?
Well, you've done a lot of shows in Osaka.
What kind of shows?
Tell me.
Like the academic sandwich.
That's right.
Hey, you're thinking about the show now.
And that.
And the planning office.
It's 4 o'clock on the 4th of the 3rd week.
And the after-setsu.
What is it?
I don't know if we'll be able to do it after the show.
We have to calm down the excited audience.
The audience will not be able to enter.
The elevator in the first floor?
After that, we have to do it for an hour and ten minutes after the show.
Can we do it?
You guys don't know about the Kage-tsu.
If you look at the front, there are people who are doing it.
Yoshimoto is funny.
I'm just a TV show.
Have you ever been on Kage-tsu?
Why can't you be on TV with such a saying?
So I don't care if I sell or make money.
I don't love you!
Don't laugh!
Do you understand?
We lost.
We were talking about losing, but we couldn't win.
You're right.
We lost.
Then, please give a speech today.
Thank you.
Today's speech...
Please give a speech for the kids.
Please.
It's your fault.
What the hell?
You have to admit defeat.
It's not like that.
It's like a ball.
It's easier to explain than to admit defeat.
It's not like that.
Please.
I can't play ball.
You guys are here to see.
I can't help it.
What are you doing?
What's going on with the audience?
What's going on?
Are you ready?
Yes, we are.
Let's go.
Please.
Can we go?
We are waiting for the audience.
The audience is waiting.
Please.
It's been a long time.
We talked about this when we were on the show.
We were on the show.
Pants and pants.
Hello!
You're quite popular!
I'm happy.
Please stand up quickly.
This is the stage for the kids.
I'm happy to be standing there.
Everyone's listening.
I'm getting angry.
There are three cameras. One camera, two cameras, one lady, one camera.
After this, the audience's tension dropped.
Good job.
I want to do the interview.
Please, Mr. Matsumoto.
Your back is round.
Can I come next Wednesday?
I'm going home.
Idiot!
Like this?
It's like a ball.
It's been a while.
The player is...
He's wearing his brother's uniform.
Who's his brother?
Ah, his brother.
His brother is really stupid.
He didn't disappear for a long time.
But it's gone!
It's gone!
That guy is an idiot!
It was really on.
It was still on.
It was on, right?
I ignored it like it was normal.
I ignored it too.
It's scary.
If you go out after that, what will people say?
He's still saying something cute because it's a home phone.
I've heard it a few times.
Hello? Hello? It's Akko.
I've heard it like that.
What is that?
It's like, the signal is bad.
It's like, what? What?
It's like, when you're with a girl,
you say hello, and it's a girl.
Hello? Hello?
I was like, this is bad, I'm going to call her.
That happens, right?
No.
I didn't know you did that.
Your cell phone is annoying.
Well, that's true.
Especially when you're talking about important things.
Yes, yes.
If you're having dinner with a girl,
that girl's cell phone won't work.
I don't know why, but the signal is weak.
Mine works.
I've been asked to lend my phone once.
When I was on the phone, she said,
I got a call.
I was so excited.
If you get a call, you can't refuse.
You can't refuse.
I was like,
Hello? Hello?
I hung up.
You were talking clearly.
The woman in front of me was like,
I'm a little...
I'm a little confused.
You're looking at me with a doubtful look.
It's not the day it started, but I have insomnia for a long time.
You say that again.
It's been a long time.
I should have waited for a lifetime.
That's fine.
People who have never had insomnia will not understand, but you think it's okay because you can sleep, right?
I'm sleepy but I can't sleep. Do you understand?
Can you sleep right away?
That depends on the day.
You're a fool. You can sleep right away.
I'm a smart worker.
I can think of many things even if I have a futon.
I can't sleep.
I don't know that.
When you're in a bad situation, at 12 o'clock...
...
I can't sleep until noon.
It's hell.
But that's because you're not feeling well.
I make a futon at 4 o'clock.
And it's like this at 4 o'clock.
And it's like this at 5 o'clock.
It's a little different.
And it's like this at 6 o'clock.
And then at 7 o'clock, he's like this again.
He's like, what the hell did I do earlier?
And then, at about 8 o'clock, he's like this again.
Please laugh a little.
You're crazy.
It's true.
But that's your rhythm, right?
But, when I'm next to you and watching you, I can't do anything.
That might change a little.
No way!
I don't like it either.
Why do you keep looking at me until I fall asleep?
But, you know,
I guess it's because you're alone.
If there's someone next to you, you might be able to sleep a little longer.
That's not relevant.
Well, this one.
This one and this one.
You're avoiding it.
This one and this one are this.
That's why...
I'll kill you!
It's sad to be alone.
Yuta, you're the only one in the world.
It's not like that.
It's not like that?
But I think it's better to be more popular.
I don't know that!
It's not that bad.
You're just a little bit.
What's this?
Go home!
Who's going to do this?
I have to do something to sleep.
Do you have a sleep-over?
If you do that, will you have it?
No, I can do it at home.
I can buy a sleep-over at the opening.
I can put a CCD in your room.
You will never sleep with that kind of thing.
If you don't sleep, I don't care if you cry or not.
I don't want to cry.
Who's going to check it?
It's embarrassing, my house.
You're so insensitive.
It's like a death camp.
I remember this room.
I want to show you the death camp.
I remember. I remember.
I don't care about this.
You're like that.
It seems that you have completed the game in a grand way.
I heard rumors!
What a big voice!
It seems that you are living in a great place.
It's not a great place.
Let's get into the camera.
I can't get in!
I want to see it a little.
I want to see it.
You know.
No, no, no.
You can't live in such a grand place.
Gonten is the
Why are you laughing?
Hey! You shouldn't show that!
That's not good for the show!
But it's amazing!
It's not amazing!
Who said that?
There's something like a observatory
What are you doing?
I'm just looking at something.
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at the stars.
You're not looking at anything.
I'm surprised.
What are you doing?
To make the boys and girls of the whole country better,
Matsuho-san said that he was busy on his day off with patrols.
Thank you.
If you were to be a father-in-law in the city, what would you do?
This is... well, I don't care, you have to think about it.
You are already a father, right?
But I don't have any other clothes.
You have clothes? You're wearing a double.
Double?
The school uniform was the same, Ichio.
You're double!
I'm double five times!
You're double five times!
I'm going to go!
I'm already at the age of 44.
That's because I'm old.
I'm not double.
You should think about it. You'll have a father later.
But I don't have a father.
What should I do?
You have a father.
Let's talk about something good today.
Let's talk about spilling.
No, spilling is not good.
Let's get to the point. Spilling is not good.
It's okay.
Yes.
There are people who watch you.
My father is walking around Shibuya and other places.
There are a lot of young people around him.
How many people are there?
Let's say 10 people.
There are a lot of young people around him.
At this time, there are 10 young men, so there is definitely one old man who smells like an old man.
I see.
That's right.
There are some who don't look like the same age.
There is definitely one.
Someone who doesn't look like the same age.
That's right.
First of all, I look for such a guy.
What are you guys?
While saying,
While looking for it,
Don't come!
While saying that,
The most old man who smells like an old man is...
Father!
What is the most unfortunate thing in this world?
This is a bit...
It's a bit...
What do you think?
What do you think of a fool being a fool?
In places that are said by the general public,
you say things like,
the one who is dead before the parents.
That's right.
Is that okay?
The record will be left.
The record will be left?
Listen carefully.
What is the most unfortunate thing in this world?
The most unfortunate thing in this world is...
It's time to think about what is the best parent-child relationship in the world.
Thank you very much.
OK.
I'm about to cry.
I don't like this.
You don't know that, do you?
If I say that I'm planning to do it, it's a standing operation.
Standing operation?
Standing operation.
What do you call it?
It's not an operation, is it?
What?
Really?
Please.
What?
What? What?
If it's true, then it's a thumbing operation.
Why? I was just trying to fool you.
With words like thumbing.
Everyone was like, wow! And I was doing this.
I'm sorry, can you say it again?
I'm sorry, I'll start from the beginning.
I'm sorry.
Masumasa-san, I'm sorry.
You don't seem to know anything at all.
It's just a continuation of the story.
What's wrong?
What is the most unfortunate thing in this world?
The most unfortunate thing in this world?
Yes.
I should say that?
Then, I'll do it.
The most...
the most...
unfortunate thing in this world is...
This is the time when I thought about what the best clothes in the world are.
What?
From me.
From me, the best clothes, the second best clothes, all the way.
Come on, Binten.
Thank you for watching!