After the Tokyo Olympics, Paralympic TV has started to gain more viewers, with a 60% success rate.
The number of viewers has increased to 48 million.
Many ghost shows have been created.
However, since the era of multi-channel, the number of viewers has increased to a large extent.
The fact that the number of viewers has decreased has become a problem for the Japanese government.
In 1994, we, Gaki no Tsukai, were not an exception.
We thoroughly researched high-viewing programs, and tonight, the opening of Gaki no Tsukai aims for the highest viewing rate in the TV market.
Good evening, everyone.
I'm Masatoshi Hamada of Dandan.
Today's opening of Dandan's Gaki no Tsukai is...
Let's seriously think about the viewing rate.
Our Gaki no Tsukai producer, Mr. Kenji Suga, is here to talk to us.
Let's hear what he has to say.
Mr. Suga.
What kind of program has gained the highest viewing rate?
I think everyone is underestimating me.
Right now, I'm not a man who can't get a high viewing rate.
I'm a man who can't get a high viewing rate.
You can't get a high viewing rate? I see.
There are three factors that I can get a high viewing rate.
People in the industry will be surprised.
First of all, ramen.
That's right.
Second, hot springs.
And finally, the animal that Mr. Mutsugoro represents.
If you have these three factors, you can get a high viewing rate.
I see.
Now, let's hear how the opening of Gaki no Tsukai will develop.
We have Mr. Hitoshi Matsumoto here with us.
Let's hear what he has to say, Mr. Matsumoto.
As I was saying, there are three factors.
There are also other factors.
I'll tell the viewers.
Today's opening is a choice of those factors.
Even if it's a big deal, let's say 60%.
We have baseball today.
Even if it's a big deal, let's say 15%.
I see.
I'll aim for 60%.
Please watch.
The ultimate ramen.
It's delicious.
Do you want some?
Why not?
Hot springs are the best.
Yukemuri Hot Spring.
It's getting a little hot.
Hot spring.
Is it good?
Yes.
It's delicious.
Animal food.
Yamasaki, give me some tissue.
Yes.
Dominos are delicious.
What are you doing?
Don't do that.
It's my first time going to a hot spring.
It's his first time going to a hot spring.
How is it?
Can I eat this?
It's delicious.
How is it?
Marathon Chinese food.
I ate it.
Please throw away the cigarette.
What?
This?
Yes.
Can I throw it away?
No, it's still on fire.
It's still on fire?
Yes.
Why?
Please throw it away.
No, it's still on fire.
Surprised human.
It's big.
Let's show them.
Mr. Maric's super magic.
It's a camera.
I love you.
Today is my first time.
I'm going to a hot spring.
It's small.
It's not nutritious at all.
Look at the back.
It's amazing.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
There are two stuffed animals over there.
It's a big stuffed animal.
I didn't know it was in the way.
When I came to see you before, it was like this.
You're lying.
I've known you since you were a kid.
I used to say, brother, brother.
I used to say, brother, please drop it.
I've seen it for a while.
It's a big thing.
I thought you'd get angry if I made a mistake.
I won't get angry.
How was it today?
I'm glad it was a little cool today.
It was hot in the spring.
It was hot.
It's hot.
My head is going to explode.
That's right.
They're just watching.
You often say bad things about people on the show.
I can't say that.
You can't say that.
You can't say that without a doubt.
That's probably a crime.
To some extent.
Who are you talking about?
When I went to the other world, it was a crime.
It's definitely going to happen.
Why?
Even if you throw something out of the window in a car, it's a crime.
I don't get caught doing that.
I don't.
But someone's watching from above.
It's as bad as killing someone.
Like firecrackers.
What?
Other than killing people or firecrackers, you're all okay.
I'm okay.
What a big guy you are.
But I think it's a little bit of a crime to throw something out of the window.
If it's piled up, if you go over there, it's definitely...
What are you talking about?
You'll be shown.
Like this.
What is this?
When you're born, you're born with about a thousand points.
If you say bad things about people, one point will decrease.
You have about five more points.
It's a dangerous situation.
If you go to the other world, there are about five scary old men.
Five?
It's really scary.
But you have five, right?
I don't know if it's scary or not.
It's a dead end.
It doesn't matter if it's a punch or a dead end.
So it's okay.
You're going to lose points, right?
But you have to earn points somewhere.
I want to ask you if you're doing something good.
You don't have to do something big like me.
What do you want to do?
I'd like to donate.
Wait a minute.
What about the money?
Money...
Something like that.
I don't know if it's something like that.
I do it once a year.
Money?
And something sweet.
It's a different era.
Donating something sweet.
I'm tired, so I'm going to eat.
Where are you going?
I don't know the whole story.
What are you talking about?
I think you should do something like that.
I don't have a machine like that.
I'm going to help my grandmother a little bit.
You're going to help your grandmother a little bit?
Just a little bit?
It's a matter of words.
I'm going to support my grandmother a little bit.
I think I should do something good at least once a day.
The other day, I was waiting for someone in a car in Shinjuku.
Why is it 2?
Is it not good?
I'm not saying it's not good.
I'm waiting.
That's right.
An Irish man came to me.
And he hit me.
I told him to give it to me.
I don't speak Japanese at all.
I have a heart.
What are you talking about?
You really don't know the words.
I have a heart.
What kind of heart do you have?
I have a memory in my arm.
What?
I don't have a memory in my arm.
What are you talking about?
I don't speak English at all.
It's a lie, but it's okay.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'll translate everything.
I'm in that car.
You don't need this, do you?
Do you understand?
I stopped the car at the front.
Suddenly, I couldn't move.
The battery seems to have run out.
Can't you do something about it?
OK.
It's good.
Why are you saying it's good when the other person is in trouble?
No, no, no.
If the other person is not good, my feelings are good.
You don't understand the other person.
Even if you say it's good.
Why are you nodding?
Say it's good.
It's good.
What are you talking about?
You don't have to do it the other way around.
Look at each other's battery.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Feelings?
Power, power, power.
I'm really grateful to the people of Iran for helping me.
Samurai.
I'll never say it.
You are a samurai.
I can't say it.
Don't do that.
Hey.
I'm really grateful to the people of Iran for helping me.
If you do something about it, I'll be grateful.
When I'm sleeping, there are people who hit me.
What?
When I wake up, there are beautiful women.
Please wake me up.
Beautiful wife.
Wife?
Where is your wife?
I don't know where my wife is.
Why don't you know your wife?
I don't know.
I wanted to say that if you do something good, there will be a reward.
I don't know if it's a reward or not.
I wanted to say that.
I see.
Don't do that.
I'll think about it when I meet her.
What?
I was in the pool when I was in junior high school.
That's a good story.
I was drowning in the pool and I almost died.
It's like a story of white and black.
What?
I saved you.
It's a story of color.
That's all I can say about saving people.
What did you save?
A swimming pool.
I was swimming in the pool and my pants were pulled.
When I said, what is it?
The kid said.
What are you looking at?
Why are you looking at me?
I'm looking at you.
I saved your life.
I got 30 points for that.
30 points?
I saved your life.
I saved you in the pool.
That's obvious.
Is there anyone who can't save you in the pool?
I was swimming in the pool and my pants were pulled.
Why am I swimming in the pool?
You're a beach baller.
You've been in a car and you've pulled small animals, haven't you?
I don't want to do it if I can, but I'll jump out of the car.
You've done it before, haven't you?
What are you doing?
It's dangerous to step on the brake.
What's that?
I don't know if it's a dog or a cat.
Don't touch it.
Let's go down normally.
Come closer.
If you don't know if it's a dog or a cat, you should be happy.
What are you talking about?
I can't help it.
Can't you go back?
I'm going to stop being your fan.
You're my partner, aren't you?
Why don't you laugh?
I can't laugh.
Why?
You're dirty.
I'm a good boy now.
I'm definitely going down.
You're lying.
I'm really going down.
Are you American?
I'm serious.
What are you looking at?
Don't lie.
I'm sorry.
Have you ever slept next to me until the morning?
I'm talking about whether there was or not.
That's hard.
That's not good.
That's 250 points.
You're the same.
I can't help it when I can't help it.
But if you run to the animal hospital, you'll have to get your energy back.
Have you ever been to the animal hospital?
Yeah.
Let me hear about it.
That was hard.
What did you do?
I went to St. Barnard's.
What time did you go?
About 2 o'clock in the morning.
You went to St. Barnard's alone at 2 o'clock in the morning?
No, I went for a walk.
Did you have a owner?
Yes.
I don't want to go to a place like that.
Why?
Don't you have a owner?
Yes.
Why did you jump out of the car?
I was running around.
I hit the car.
You hit the car.
Yes.
Why?
Are you okay?
Who are you talking to?
To the owner.
Are you okay?
The owner hugged me.
The owner hugged you?
Why did you say that?
Because the owner was lying down.
Did you hit someone?
You're laughing too much.
From now on, I will give this to the person who read the letter.
Suddenly, why did Devilman say, Devilwing, Devilwing?
He said it before he could do anything.
You should have told me.
I'm trying to do my best.
Why are you crying?
I don't know.
Are you aware of it?
I think it's a disadvantage to the enemy.
I dare to do it.
Why?
I'm stronger than you.
I don't know what he's going to do next.
I don't know.
I told you at first. I'm stronger than you.
No matter how many times I get hit by you, I won't lose.
I'm telling you from the bottom of my heart.
I think it's better not to say it.
I think so, too.
I'm not saying it.
You should make him think, what is he doing?
I don't know.
I don't know why.
Why?
Make him feel like he's watching something.
Like on TV?
Yes, like on TV.
I think it's Devilwing.
If you say Devilwing, I'm wondering what he's doing.
That's right.
I think it's okay to say something I don't understand.
But if you do this, it comes out like this.
Where does it come out from?
It comes out from here.
It comes out like this?
Yes.
What is this?
This is not cool.
But this is a little different.
What is this?
This is a pose.
This is Ultra Seven.
It comes out from here.
I don't need it.
This is strange.
How long will Ken-chan Ramen be on sale?
I don't know.
Can it be on sale forever?
No.
I don't know.
This is a commercial.
Can't you do it with a great budget?
Why?
There are a lot.
Lawson?
Lawson.
There are a lot of Lawsons, right?
What else?
Beer?
Beer.
This is strange.
I don't know.
This is an intellectual problem.
I was surprised.
I want to go home.
This is a commercial.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.