The opening is not interesting.
Next time, we will go to the supermarket again!
Once upon a time, on a Sunday, there was a supermarket.
Some stupid staff was doing it.
So we decided to do it again.
The rule is simple.
In two minutes, we will run around the supermarket.
We will put more and more cinnamon.
In the end, the person who puts the highest amount of cinnamon wins.
How many of the same things are not allowed?
Up to five.
You can put up to five things.
Wait a minute.
That's not funny.
There is a champion game.
In the champion game, there are four questions.
For example, if you think the answer is cheese, you go to the cheese store.
You go to the cheese store and look for it.
There is a question written on the back.
There are four questions, so you look for it and go around.
In the end, there is a million yen on the back.
Wait a minute.
That's not funny.
In the champion game, there are four questions.
Let's go to the champion game.
You are slow.
There are only two minutes left.
Let's run around and come back here.
Let's go.
Are you ready?
Is it okay to do such a thing?
Run around and come back here.
If you run out of battery, you can't run.
30 seconds have passed.
I can't run anymore.
Is it okay to do this?
Thank you very much.
One minute has passed.
Do you use that?
Are you going to the swimming pool?
Are you going to the pool?
30 seconds have passed.
I can't run anymore.
I was defeated.
8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
OK.
I didn't do anything.
Good luck.
OK.
I can't run anymore.
2 melons.
OK.
I was defeated.
The time has passed.
OK.
10 minutes have passed.
30 seconds have passed.
I'm sorry.
I can't run anymore.
I want to win.
I can't do it.
10 seconds left.
9, 8, 7, 6, 5 seconds left.
5 seconds left.
3, 2, 1.
I can't do it.
Yamazaki can't do it at all.
Yamazaki is a little angry.
Announcement of the results.
Both teams did their best.
The results are everything.
Let's announce it.
Koma-chan's team has a total of 68,544 yen.
Mach-chan's team has a total of 99,141 yen.
The champion team is Mach-chan's team.
I did it.
Now it's Mach-chan's team's turn.
It's the champion game.
Are you ready?
The final prize is 100,000 yen.
Can I borrow it?
It's 100,000 yen.
Really?
Yes.
I'll take it.
Here you are.
Here's the question.
Yes.
What are the 10 legs of an octopus living in the sea?
Ready.
Squid.
This way.
No, this way.
Squid.
Where?
This is it.
What is it?
Squid.
It's not a squid.
There it is.
It's white and thin.
30 seconds have passed.
There's no time left.
40 seconds have passed.
What is this?
This is difficult.
I can't do it anymore.
It's not a margarine.
Here it is.
5 seconds left.
4.
3.
2.
1.
Which one was it?
I can't do this.
Well done.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
Today is your last day of work.
You look cool.
Isn't it good?
My stomach is growing.
It's growing a little.
That's great.
My stomach is growing.
No, I'm not. I don't sleep that much.
Your eyes are dirty.
My eyes are dirty, but it doesn't mean that I sleep too much.
Why is that?
My eyes are dirty too.
Oh!
I'm wearing double.
You're wearing double?
I can't sleep.
You can't sleep that much.
Why?
Well...
Because we're f*****g close.
I'm really young.
You should have said sorry.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing? Are you rolling?
I'm rolling.
It's not like that. It's a kind of occupational disease.
What?
It's a kind of talent.
Do you know what talent is?
Well, kind of.
You're lying.
It's not as easy as you think.
For example, you think you're coming out without thinking, right?
You have to change your clothes after you go in.
You have to go on TV, so you have to wear a proper outfit.
And you're wearing makeup.
I want to draw my eyebrows.
It's ugly when it's shiny, so you have to press it with powder.
And you come out, right?
Your eyes are coming this way, right?
The light is shining.
It's ugly.
Why?
Well, it's just an example.
It's a kind of talent comedy.
It's you.
It's just an example.
I just happened to be in that kind of place.
You're going to come out again, right?
It's a kind of stress.
I don't know if I'm going to be Jiro.
That's right.
It's the most painful thing in the world.
But I don't know if I'm going to be Jiro.
I've been there.
It's a stomach ulcer.
It's hard poop, so it hurts.
No, no, no, no, no.
There's a stomach ulcer next to the eardrum.
What?
It's a stomach ulcer next to the eardrum.
It's coming out from the inside.
In my case, there's a stomach ulcer next to the eardrum.
I can only poop once, so I can't do that.
Well, that's what I was saying.
I was saying that, too.
It's a stomach ulcer.
No, I didn't take it.
I didn't take it.
That's why I put it on after taking a bath.
But it's a disaster.
After taking a bath,
Like this.
I hold a mirror in my hand.
I do this.
And then I put it on like this.
No, really.
I'm going to wake up from last year's love.
If you do something like this.
It's hard, but what's the hardest thing?
I'm having a headache right now.
I don't feel like talking.
Well, I'm going to get better, too.
It's not a headache, it's a stomach ulcer.
Well, it's a stomach ulcer.
There's a stomach ulcer.
Everyone says it's funny.
My stomach hurts so much.
My stomach hurts.
It hurts so much.
But doesn't it feel good?
How do you feel?
It hurts so much.
When I'm having a stomach ulcer,
It hurts so much that I feel good.
I'm sorry, I don't.
No, no, no.
You don't understand.
It hurts so much.
It doesn't feel good.
What are you talking about?
You're the only one who's talking.
I'll tell you in detail.
My stomach hurts so much.
It hurts so much.
It doesn't feel good.
That's why I'm telling you.
When I have a stomach ulcer,
I feel good for a moment.
So I can get over it.
Pain.
Same as that.
My stomach hurts.
My stomach hurts halfway.
But when it gets to the extreme,
It feels good.
It hurts so much.
It doesn't feel good.
We're still in the middle.
It hurts so much.
It feels good when I get over it.
I've been there for a while.
It's already tearing up.
Can you stand it?
Is it more painful than that?
I can stand it.
When I was a kid, I had a hard time.
It's hard, but it hurts so much.
It's getting better and better.
I don't think it feels good.
It hurts even if it's pinched.
But when I get over it,
It's getting softer and softer.
What?
Even if it's pinched?
Even if it's pinched, it hurts at first.
When I get over it,
It's getting softer and softer.
Really?
You're lying.
It's just a pinch.
That's fast.
You're lying.
That's not true.
It doesn't hurt that much.
Let's get out of here as soon as possible.
That's enough.
What do you think?
What are you talking about?
I don't know what to say.
I haven't seen yesterday's broadcast.
I've been saying a lot.
Yesterday's broadcast?
The arrow is over there.
That's before I got caught.
I heard you got caught.
I got caught.
It wasn't just an arrow.
What was it?
Three steps?
Why are you so strong?
There are two bullets in the gun, right?
It's soft, isn't it?
Why are you flying like this?
That's weird.
That's definitely weird.
That's why.
As I said earlier,
It was in a good way.
The bullet, too.
If it's a little off,
It's gone.
Someone shot it somewhere, didn't they?
I think so.
I've been saying that for a long time.
I've been saying it, so it's here.
Well, well, well.
It's me.
Who is it?
You have a nice voice.
It's me.
It's a big bottle of miso.
It's too sticky.
It's been a long time.
I'm tired.
I'm sorry.
Good luck with your work this year, too.
By the way, I was curious about it the other day.
After the trial,
There's a man who comes out of the courtroom with a paper that says he's a criminal.
Where did he go after he left the door?
I didn't go out.
I didn't leave the door.
I'm here to show it to the person waiting in front of me.
I'm sorry.
I'm here.
Have you ever seen the end?
The guy who went like this.
There is.
How is it?
It's wrapped.
I don't do that.
Have you ever seen it?
I haven't seen it.
I've seen it.
I saw it on the news.
It's wrapped in ink.
There's a production like that.
There's such a thing.
There is.
I didn't know that.
Is it dispatched?
It's dispatched.
I'm going to show it to everyone with a paper that says he's a criminal.
I'm going to go to the office anyway.
I'll say, thank you for your hard work.
No, no, no.
There's a lot of distance from there to the office.
There's a lot of distance.
I'll give it to someone who doesn't care at all.
I'll do it anyway.
I'll go home and get a drink.
Who are you looking at?
I'm the master.
Oh, my.
There's a master.
The story's getting bigger.
I'll say, thank you for your hard work.
That master.
That master has been doing it since the very beginning.
That's right.
It's called a trial master.
His name is already a trial master.
I'll say, thank you for your hard work.
In the dressing room.
Where are you going to the dressing room?
That's where they are.
It's your office, isn't it?
That's right.
There are a lot of older brothers and sisters.
The next turn is in front of the mirror.
What's that?
The next turn is the older sister.
The older sister is doing makeup.
The woman is also doing makeup.
The older sister is saying, how was the customer?
Hey, hey.
Please come next time.
That's it.
There's a place where I have to take it.
That's right.
And then the older sister came out.
That's what it's like.
It's like a day trial.
That's right.
Why do you use a bath or a pool for a long time?
When you soak in water for a long time, your hands, fingers, and soles of your feet become wrinkled.
I see.
When you use a bath for a long time, your feet become wrinkled.
You get used to it, don't you?
Yes, yes, yes.
Why is that?
Hmm.
Well, actually, I think everyone has had an experience.
For example, a float or something like that.
What?
A float or something like that.
Yes, yes, yes.
When you first use this, it's good, isn't it?
Yes.
And it's like, wha!
It's like this.
Where is the foam coming out?
No, it's not coming out.
Huh?
It's a big float, isn't it?
Who is it?
No, no, no, for example, it can be anyone.
It's a big float, isn't it?
So imagine a big float.
And then you put it in the bath, right?
When the mouth part is like this, it goes like this.
And the mouth part goes like this.
And then it goes like this.
Two or three days ago, I found a mole sticking out.
What is it doing in the mole?
Look at this.
Is it coming out?
The animals also come out by themselves.
What does that mean?
We have a world.
It's in the soil.
There is a town in the mole.
There are bullying issues in the mole society.
The mole that wants to die also comes out.
When humans die, they commit suicide by gas or by hanging themselves.
They jump off.
In the case of the mole, it is suicide to come out on the ground.
Is that so?
You don't die because you came out, do you?
If you come out, you die.
There is a picture like this.
What is that?
It's a picture.
No, it's a video.
What is it?
It's like coming out of a hole.
The mole is sticking out a little.
What does that mean?
When humans die, they stand on top of a building.
If you fall from here, you die.
That's the picture.
It's coming out, isn't it?
It only looks like we're showing our faces.
In the back, there are police officers with glasses.
Don't apologize!
I'm telling you not to apologize!
The name is a mole.
It's like this.
Don't come! If you come out, you'll come out!
If you come any closer, I'll come out!
Stop it! Stop it, mole!
It's like this!
I know.
There is such a world in the mole.
I see.
What is the last foreign language of Cecil's commercial?
It's a language that expresses love and trust.
Is that what you're saying?
That's right.
I see.
Thank you.
It's a language that expresses love and trust.
I see.
This girl calls me Kinoshita-kun Seisho Nagon.
She calls me Kinoshita-kun Seisho Nagon.
She doesn't say it. She can't speak Japanese.
What does she say?
She says that it expresses love and trust.
She says Cecil?
She says that in French, right?
What does she say in French?
I don't understand.
Don't make me laugh.
You have to understand that.
It doesn't make sense.
I was also interested in Cecil.
She says Cecil Hion Sosolomon Sasolomon.
Say it again.
She says Hion Sosolomon Sasolomon.
I see.
There's no doubt about that.
Does that make sense?
It doesn't make sense.
I don't understand what you're saying.
That's what she says in Japanese.
There's no Japanese or any other language.
It's French.
It's not French.
She says Cecil Hion Sosolomon Sasolomon.
So what language is that?
It's not a language.
She says Hion Sosolomon Sasolomon.
So what does that mean?
It doesn't make sense.
What language is that?
It's not a language.
You're Chimaki Joe.
I understand.
I understand what you're trying to say.
But I want people watching TV to listen to what you're trying to say.
I want them to think you're trying to do your best.
I understand what you're trying to say.
But I don't want people to think you're trying to say that you can speak Japanese.
That's right.