It's time for the 4th episode of CoordiNate!
This is the 4th episode of CoordiNate.
Our manager has been doing this since the 2nd episode.
Ryu-chan is the first guest of CoordiNate.
He is the guest of the 4th episode of CoordiNate.
Let's call him.
Here he comes!
Welcome!
I've been waiting for this moment!
I'm the master of CoordiNate!
Today, Ryu-chan will be the guest of CoordiNate.
When did you get this?
Ryu-chan, you are the master of CoordiNate.
Ryu-chan, it's me, right?
Yes, it's you.
Are you going to do something?
Yes, I am.
I've never heard of this.
I don't know what to do.
Ryu-chan should be here, right?
Yes, Ryu-chan is here.
Ryu-chan should be in the middle.
These two and these two will go shopping.
I see.
I'll buy something that suits Ryu-chan.
How many years have we known Ryu-chan?
We won this game, right?
Yes, we did.
That's what I mean.
I know everything.
We want to follow you to the downtown.
Hey, hey!
We won't be defeated.
We will do our best.
He is an anti-gay.
You are so persistent.
You guys!
Watch out! Watch out!
You should move away from this.
It hurts.
Be careful.
You are going to get hurt.
I'm going to get hurt.
Why are you so persistent?
It's dangerous.
Do you want to try it on?
Yes, I do.
I want to buy a bag for Sasa-chu.
I don't know if it's going to be popular.
You are buying it here?
You have a bad taste.
You are a three-year-old gay.
Which one do you like?
I like both.
I like the one in Kansai and Kanto.
I like the one in Kansai.
Hey!
I don't want to buy this kind of shoes.
I don't have such slippers.
You don't have such slippers?
You are the youngest.
I don't have such slippers.
Do you have such beautiful shoes?
I don't have such beautiful shoes.
You are a two-year-old gay.
Show me your face.
I don't have such beautiful shoes.
You are a two-year-old gay.
Show me your face.
I like this kind of shoes.
I have a bad taste.
I don't want to buy this kind of shoes.
You bought a tie and a pin, right?
I bought a tie and a pin, right?
That's right.
I don't think I can do this for the first time.
I have a bad taste.
I don't want to buy this kind of shoes.
First of all, the coordination of the two teams.
I'll ask you one thing.
The theme is good.
If you say the theme...
Don't say the theme.
This time, we're going to do it as a Kanto gay.
You guys all look like Nishiro.
So what's the theme?
It's light and clean.
First of all, the coordination of the two teams.
Ryu-chan, please come out.
If you do this, you'll be able to go to a party.
And this fashion...
If you stimulate it a little, you'll be able to make a voice.
Let's make a voice.
The scream of joy.
It hurts.
The point of this is the face.
In fashion, it's not this face.
I got it.
The coordination of the two teams is like this.
Let's move on to the coordination of Downtown.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
It's okay to be round.
It's raised to the top.
Our coordination is over.
What's the theme?
We started with the bag of Sasazuka Junior High School in the shopping district.
After all, bicycle commuting is the theme.
Especially if you go to the countryside, you can see it well.
A junior high school student who is doing bicycle commuting.
It's simple.
Let's see the coordination of Downtown.
Ryu-chan, please come out.
I can't touch it.
I'm wearing a jersey.
Helmet.
It's a helmet.
Even the shoes.
I realized something good.
It's too late to go home.
I have to go to the shower.
Do you often take a shower in various songs?
That's all.
I was going to drop it and go home.
But when I saw this, I didn't want to go home.
I didn't want to go home.
You should go home.
I don't know.
I'm going home.
I have to go to school in the morning.
What happened recently?
I went skiing.
You went.
You went with two people.
You sometimes play with two people.
That's strange.
That was cool.
Look at the school.
I can do sports.
It's strange.
It's a lie.
Everyone is having fun.
There was a lift.
I went for the first time in my life.
That's right.
I saw it for the first time.
It was like that.
There was a lift.
I went.
But it isn't for the end.
It won't be so fun for the end.
It makes me only thinly eyed only for the end.
I thought she was a good girl.
I thought she was going to fall from the top.
Sorry, I got caught.
When I saw her, I thought I could do it.
Really?
No, really.
When I saw her, I could tell she was like this.
But she was not feeling well.
Don't say that.
She was about to fall from the top.
The day before, she was very...
Don't lie to me.
You want to drink oolong tea, don't you?
I think she had a fight with a black guy.
Which guy?
I don't remember.
She was drunk and played table tennis.
I don't remember drinking alcohol.
I remember.
She had a fight with a black guy.
She had a fight with a black guy at the hotel.
What did she do after that?
She joined him with a trumpet.
You had a trumpet with a ski?
I don't remember what happened after that.
Is that so?
It would be nice if she went skiing.
Everyone is skiing. We are the first ones.
That's enough.
You like skiing, don't you?
You can't do sports, either.
Don't do it with you.
You can't do anything.
I can do anything.
What can you do?
What do you mean?
What have you done so far?
I've done most of it.
You can't do it.
As a comedian, I can't do it well on TV.
No, you are doing your best.
You can't do it.
When you guys were taking a bath,
I told you to sleep in your room.
You were sleeping, weren't you?
I was sleeping.
I checked if you were sleeping.
I left the hotel.
I was next to the ski resort.
Did you see it?
No, I didn't.
There is a liar in our school.
At first, he said he joined a troupe.
Everyone believed him.
But recently, he is with Isshiki Sae.
He was in a drama with Isshiki Sae.
He is dating Mori from SMAP.
He is a liar.
Why is he such a liar?
Who is Mori from SMAP?
I don't know.
I don't understand women.
They are liars.
I've been told a lot.
What?
I live in Yokohama.
I'm dating a junior high school student.
Is that a lie?
Why are you a junior high school student in Yokohama?
I've been to a junior high school in Yokohama.
What is that?
Are you angry?
I don't know what a junior high school student in Yokohama is.
I've read a lot of fan letters.
I'm angry.
From the opening of the fan letter.
Why did you do it?
I can't believe it anymore.
What?
I understand.
I can't believe it anymore.
What is that?
That's what happens when you read a fan letter.
I can't believe it anymore.
You can't be proud of anything because you had sex with me.
That's what she thinks.
Don't say that.
That was a little annoying.
If you're a second-rate actor, you'll be proud of it.
If you have sex with me, you won't be proud of anything.
That's what you think.
It doesn't matter who gets it.
If you are a third-rate actor, you won't be proud of anything because I have sex with anyone.
That's why you've been like this?
I haven't been like this at all.
I can't feel proud of myself.
It's a coincidence.
Is that so?
You're stupid.
I'm stupid.
What are the things that go round and round in red, white, and blue that are common in Tokoyas?
Like this.
Why do we have to have white, red, and blue?
We don't really know.
In fact, in order to draw the basic tree, it would be better to have yellow or green in it.
But it's white, red, and blue.
Well, that's true.
This is...
I'll tell you.
I'll cut it so that it goes round and round in white, red, and blue.
What are you talking about?
It has nothing to do with it.
I'll cut it so that it goes round and round in red, blue, and black.
Where's the black?
Isn't that strange?
Why is it strange?
It's this color from the beginning, so it's strange that it's black.
It's strange that it's black from the beginning.
I'll tell you. White, red, and blue can't be separated from each other.
What's wrong with that?
Tell me that first.
If you do that, I don't know.
If you do that, I don't know if it's this color.
You have to tell me that first.
An amateur is...
Who said that?
A person who doesn't have a license at all.
I can't open it.
Wait a minute.
I can't open it?
Where is that in?
I can't open it.
If you do that, I don't know.
An amateur is...
I can't open it.
Blue.
Blue vegetables.
What?
That's bad.
Is it over already?
I have a question about human faces.
It's natural that the faces of parents and children are similar.
But sometimes there are people whose faces are similar.
Why is that?
This is really true.
This is really...
It's not that they look alike because they've been together for a long time, is it?
If you say something like that, you and I...
Me and you...
How many years has it been?
Me and you have been together for a long time.
This and that.
How many years has it been?
It's been more than 20 years.
That's right.
Speaking of 20 years, it's already the Ginkgo ceremony.
What?
It's already the Ginkgo ceremony.
That's a bad title.
It's true.
What do you mean?
It's not similar.
It's not similar, is it?
In the end, this is the environment.
Is that so?
This is only good for the environment.
They live in the same house and eat the same food.
If that's the case, humans will gradually become similar.
Is that so?
That's right.
That's why everyone's family is similar.
When I bought it and lived with my family, we were similar.
But now that I live alone, I'm eating my own food.
I'm eating something different from my family.
My face has gradually changed.
Is that so?
Yes.
Even if you say that...
In the past, I had a different face.
What kind of face was it?
In the past, when I lived with my family, I had a different face.
That's not true.
When I built a one-room house, I had a different face.
Last year, I had a different face.
Now I have a different face.
I have a different face.
What are you talking about?
People like to imitate.
Why does everyone say,
Good evening, I'm Shinichi Mori when I imitate Shinichi Mori?
It's easy to understand, isn't it?
No, it's not.
What she's saying is,
What's that good evening?
It's easy.
It doesn't have to be good evening.
Good morning.
I'm Shinichi Mori.
But...
That's what she's saying.
Why?
Why is it good evening?
Isn't it easy to imitate?
If you say that, it's almost good evening, isn't it?
Isn't it?
Is it only when you're Shinichi Mori?
That's right.
Good evening, I'm Lupin.
That's impossible.
I've never heard Lupin say good evening.
I can never say it.
Why is it good evening only when you're Shinichi Mori?
Who started it?
Good evening, I'm Shinichi Mori.
That's right.
That's what everyone says.
I always think,
There's no special permission for comedy.
I want you to stop this.
You have to do it properly.
What do you say?
I can't use anything other than this person.
That's right.
That's why I'm talking about it.
I'm in a lot of magazines.
I'm in a lot of things I talked about.
Playboy, come here.
My story.
Is that so?
Haruta and I also want to put it out.
What are you talking about?
Don't take other people's story.
If you put it out, you'll get 5,000 yen.
You said that.
Even if you say something like that, you'll get 5,000 yen.
I'll tell you something.
I only take other people's story.
Are you going up the hill?
If I meet you in my dream.
What are you talking about?
That's Hiro's story.
I didn't take it.
I've been told a lot.
Please think about it.
For example, let's go into your house.
Let's say there was a pot.
This is a pretty expensive pot.
What would you say if you took it?
Hey, hey, hey.
You'll say, thief.
That's not what you're thinking.
Otherwise, it won't fall.
No, no, no.
Thief.
That's where you go into your house.
It's blooming in the garden.
I took the grass.
Do you call it a thief?
I'll tell you.
Do you say?
You say.
I'll tell you.
I've never really taken it.
Hey, hey, hey.
That's my cam.
Yamagaki.
Don't do that.
Hey, hey, hey.
That's a joint project.
No, it's not.
He's an idiot.
I've seen him do something before we did it.
I've seen the reaction of the people around me.
When I was doing it, he was looking at my face.
I was looking at it with this face.
But in my heart, I thought it was good.