I don't even remember saying clear, clear.
You're looking at me so much.
I'm looking at you so much.
I didn't say I was looking at you.
I really don't remember saying clear, clear.
But I remember it being like that.
When I said butt,
To be honest,
I want you to touch me.
That's why,
If that butt is popular,
Actually, at that time,
To everyone all over the country,
It's Miyasako's gag.
I wanted to say that this is funny with Miyasako.
Excuse me, is violence okay?
Violence is the law.
I'm sorry.
That was a few years ago.
Oh, Tanaka.
It's Yamazaki.
Oh, good morning.
Are you free this weekend?
Let's go to Hakone.
Hakone?
What are you going to do in Hakone?
It's a hot spring, of course.
Eat delicious food, play with women,
And go to the hot spring. It's so much fun.
Are you really having fun?
What's with that attitude?
I'm your senior, so I can't invite you.
You can just follow me.
I'm sorry. I'll go. I'll go.
Tanaka wasn't very motivated,
But he understood Yamazaki's forceful invitation.
And that day...
Good morning.
Yamazaki-san, what's wrong?
I fell asleep with the air conditioner on, so I'm not feeling well.
You'll be fine after you go to the hot spring.
You're right.
The two got on the train and headed to Hakone.
To be honest, I wasn't motivated at first,
But now that I'm going, I have to have fun.
Right, Yamazaki-san?
Huh?
Well, that's true.
For some reason, Yamazaki, who doesn't talk much,
And Tanaka, who seems to be having fun,
Got on the train and arrived at Hakone.
Hakone. Hakone.
Yamazaki-san, we're here.
I'm completely asleep.
And after getting off the train, Yamazaki couldn't sleep.
Is it the wind? I think I have a fever.
Tanaka, can you touch my forehead?
What? I don't have a fever at all.
You do, but you look like you have a fever.
This is bad.
Even if it's bad, I'm already awake.
Then, Yamazaki...
Let's go home.
Go home?
I didn't want to come, but I came all the way here.
It's no use saying that.
I have a cold.
Even if you say that, I don't have a fever at all.
Shut up. I'm not having fun anymore.
In this way, Tanaka and Yamazaki went back to Hakone.
Tanaka was suddenly suspended from his trip because he didn't want to go.
However, the wind of Yamazaki sleeping in the train on the way home
Was completely healed by the time he arrived in Tokyo.
I'm sorry.
Judge, can you give your testimony?
This is terrible.
But I think Yamazaki has a fever.
He doesn't have a fever?
This is it.
I came all the way here.
Yamazaki-san, let's go to the hot spring.
I told him a few times.
He got angry and said,
If you want to go that much, go by yourself.
I'm not here for rehab.
What's so fun about going to the hot spring alone?
He invited you, didn't he?
That's right.
He told me to stay by his side.
He said that he might still have a cold.
He said that he was worried about waking him up at night.
I stayed at home for a long time.
My face turned pale.
I thought it was really hard.
Let's measure his fever.
When I measured his fever, it was only 7.2 degrees.
It was only 7.2 degrees.
He wasted my day.
I don't know if it's normal.
It's not my fault.
It's your name.
It's not my fault. I'll do my best from now on.
It's like a name of a convenience store.
I have a very low fever.
Is that so?
34 degrees.
That's not true.
I may have a fever of 39 degrees.
But you invited me from the top.
If you're in a bad mood in the morning, call me and tell me to stop.
I was in a bad mood from the beginning.
I was in a bad mood after I got to the box.
What about that?
I was in a bad mood in Shinjuku.
I heard it with both ears.
I didn't say that.
I was in a bad mood after I got to the box.
I said that I had a cold.
Did you catch a cold as soon as you got to the box?
Yes.
You don't have to go home if you're in a bad mood.
I have a hard time when I catch a cold.
Everyone has a hard time.
You're the only one who has a hard time.
It's sad.
It's my fault.
I feel that you think a lot about me.
It's annoying.
You show that you don't want to answer.
You're lying.
I'll cry when you stop.
You look so sad.
You often talk about the stairs.
You often say,
The culprit is you.
Yamazaki says to his junior,
He looks surprised and says,
The culprit is you.
What's wrong with you?
It's amazing.
It's amazing that I was scared.
I was on a bus.
I went into a dark alley.
There was a tree in front of the garden.
The tree hit the window.
Only one person.
What's wrong with everyone?
It's terrible.
I was driving on a mountain road.
It's funny if I turn off all the lights.
There were three white people.
I was laughing.
What's wrong with you?
Stop it.
I can't stop laughing.
I said to my sister.
Stop it.
It's funny.
It was a few years ago.
Yamazaki was the peak as a talent.
Yamazaki has become popular recently.
I'm busy.
If I do all the hard work, I won't be able to do it.
Did you appear in the show?
Yes.
But I'm a regular.
I only appear once a week.
At that time, Yamazaki and K2 appeared in the show.
But it's okay.
Even if you're not a regular, you can appear in that show.
That's not true.
K2 is annoying.
Even if you're not a regular, you can appear in that show.
What are you laughing at?
K2's Horibe is a kid's writer.
I was listening to the whole story.
Yamazaki forgot about Horibe.
That's not true.
It's okay.
Yamazaki was so miserable that he laughed at Horibe.
Please show us.
Please explain the VTR.
At that time, he and I were working as a regular.
As a comedian, I wanted to appear in the show every week.
That's true.
But it was a kid's show.
We wanted to make the show more exciting.
I was a writer.
I went to the dressing room.
Yamazaki and Matsumoto talked about it.
It's a regular, isn't it?
That's right.
K2 is annoying.
I was surprised.
What are you talking about?
I'm not saying I hate K2.
I'm just saying I want to appear every week.
Is there anything else?
He used to drive a Mercedes-Benz.
He's the owner of a Mercedes-Benz.
He used to drive a domestic car.
When I changed the car,
I asked Matsumoto why he bought a Mercedes-Benz.
He said,
I can't drive a domestic car.
As a comedian, I can't drive a domestic car.
By the way, I'm driving a domestic car.
You're talking a lot.
I'm talking a lot.
This is the story of when Yamazaki went to Las Vegas for the first time on Japanese TV.
I went to Las Vegas with Mr. Shisamoto and Mr. Hakamada.
We played a game of casino roulette.
If I lost, I would have to play a penalty game.
I played without any preparation.
I lost the game.
The penalty game is a bungee jump of 50 meters.
Bungee jumping is a very delicious penalty game for comedians.
Yamazaki made a face that he didn't like.
In his heart,
This is delicious.
I'm sorry for the two of you.
I, Yamazaki Hosei, will eat this program.
By the way,
I'm sorry for the two of you.
No problem. Thank you.
Yamazaki Hosei is not good at acting.
This is the end of the broadcast.
I have worked with various comedians so far.
I have never seen such a person who makes me disappointed.
I was looking forward to him.
He is the worst.
This is the opening of Yamazaki Hosei.
Sorry for the troubling you.
Don't do that!
I'll take it.
No, no.
No, I'll take it.
Sorry.
No, no, no!
No, I'm sorry.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to.
No, I'm sorry.
I'll take it.
Hello.
Welcome.
I'll take it.
Why did you jump out?
And in the test of courage...
The sound is too loud.
What do you think?
This face.
Is this a real dog?
Ah!
I was surprised.
It disappeared.
It really disappeared.
And in the legendary Yamazaki vs. Jimmy dog fight...
There is a way to use this.
How do you use this?
Do you use this?
And in the test of courage...
Sit down!
This is dirty.
It's dirty.
Ah!
Oh!
What?
Ah!
Oh!
What?
And in the test of courage...
In order to take a picture of the ghost in a haunted spot...
There is a way to do it.
It's a ghost!
Ah!
Scary!
Who is this?
Ah!
As expected, Yamazaki Hoosei is the ultimate horror entertainer.
This is the end of the scary horror.
What is it that you want to show Yamazaki Hoosei?
You know, there is a big gaga in Gaito, right?
There was a big gaga in Den-Chun.
There was a big gaga in Yamazaki-san, right?
Ah, that's right.
And then, about 5 seconds later,
I heard another scream like this,
and when I looked at Yamazaki-san's face,
I saw that gaga in Yamazaki-san's face.
Why is this happening?
Well, it must be because the scale is small.
There are various things.
I've seen a lot of Keiba newspapers before,
and I've bought them.
But that's because the scale is big.
That's interesting!
That was on the other hand, in Japan.
It was yesterday's newspaper.
Yesterday's newspaper.
The horse's name is different.
Huh?
This is not it.
This is curious, isn't it?
Huh? The horse's name is different.
That's what I did.
I was expecting it to be yesterday's newspaper,
but I got it right.
Perfectly.
Even if you look at it again, it's nothing.
We've received a testimony from someone
who is very close to Yamazaki-san.
Let's take a look at it.
Who is it?
Yamazaki Keiba
Yamazaki-kun's scale is small.
In the past,
Yamazaki-kun had a job in the Ultra Quiz.
It seems that he was aiming for a step-up
in the Ultra Quiz at once.
It seems that he put a lot of effort into recording,
but to be honest, it didn't come out well at all.
At that time, he was young,
and he was participating in the 99,
and he was taken away by Okamura.
Normally, there are comedians there.
Oh, shit.
Okay, next time.
Next time, I'll take back what I did the other day
and stand out as much as I can.
I'll take a laugh.
I think he's a normal comedian,
but in his case,
his scale is very small.
So it means that the program is bad.
He doesn't bring out his own charm at all.
In other words, Takeshi-san is bad.
He doesn't know.
He's come this far.
The next time he was asked to appear,
he refused.
When he appeared in Karasoyagi,
he didn't do well at all.
If he was a normal comedian,
he would say,
Okay, next time.
But it's also bad for the program.
He doesn't play with me.
In fact, Sanma-san is bad.
When I was drunk,
I asked him if he said it or not.
He's really a small guy.
Really, Yamazaki-san...
Well, Yamazaki.
Yamazaki-san.
He's really small.
You're really small.
He's my senior.
He's been my senior for two years.
Well, his career.
I want him to be happy that his junior got a job.
That's right.
He's been my senior for a long time.
When his junior gets a job, he's really happy.
That's right.
That guy.
Yeah.
When he gets a job,
he doesn't call me anymore.
He doesn't play with me anymore.
What does that mean?
And this fall, when he lost two jobs,
he came to see me.
That's a good thing.
I'm going to beat him up.
You're really a small guy.
I'm really small.
He's really small.
He's been beaten up.
Please,
punish him.
Please.
That's all the evidence we have.
Yamazaki-kun, if you have anything to say, please say it.
I don't know if I can say it's an incident,
but I admit that there was a lot of things.
But,
he's cute, isn't he?
Did you just hear the voice of the public?
It came out from the bottom of my stomach.
Then, if you have anything to say, please say it.
Please punish him.
He's cute, isn't he?
He's like this.
There's no way he's a judge.
What about me?
I'm a defendant.
Now,
what should I do?
Please erase it.
Ah,
then,
the Chief Justice,
Matsumoto Shintoshi,
will announce the verdict.
The fact that the defendant, Yamazaki Hosei,
has been causing trouble to many people
because of his small scale
is an irreplaceable fact.
He has far exceeded our expectations.
Therefore,
regardless of whether or not the defense is ready,
the verdict will be
a one-man piano concert at midnight.
Is that true?
Please play the piano at a night school
where no one is around.
All night long.
Why do you have such a back?
Well, basically,
I'm a defendant,
and I'm not a lawyer.
Thank you.