The next day
Good morning.
What's wrong?
Please help me.
What?
What are you looking at?
What's wrong?
You know I'm here.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, for now, I'm going to...
I'm going to watch a video.
I think you know what I mean.
That's all you have to say?
I'm a three-piece.
I almost died.
forests
I still got it.
Huh?
It's obviously my name, isn't it?
My name is obviously.
That sp Kanal?
Yes.
It's still not it at all, is it?
It's obvious that my name is Uteru, and so is my face.
It's like Uteru, isn't it?
But you can tell by the way I talk and the way I move.
And it's my intuition, but I think that was 7 or 8 years ago.
Why are you saying that now?
Well, I don't know if it was 7 or 8 years ago, but that's fine, isn't it?
I think it was 7 or 8 years ago.
I'll go back in time.
You still have a long way to go.
I'm sure you all have a long way to go, so you probably don't remember anything.
To be honest, I don't remember anything from that conversation.
I hope you'll do something about it.
But it's a bit strange that you said,
Don't draw Itao.
It's strange, and it makes me feel sad.
But I felt like I didn't like it when I saw it on air.
You didn't say anything?
I thought I'd put up with it, but I'm still angry.
You're angry today?
But it's okay if it's just a footnote.
Mr. Sugata.
Yes?
Is it okay?
I guess so.
It's better to talk.
To be honest, when this door opened, I thought it was money.
That's all I have.
Is this okay today?
I don't know.
It's okay.
It's okay?
Yes.
Excuse me.
Before the talk.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's fast.
You're in a hurry.
I was looking at the clock over there.
I was worried.
Where are you going with the money?
Where are you going?
Let's put it on.
Really?
I'll put it on.
I'm nervous.
What kind of feeling do you usually have?
I'm interested.
This program is provided by the sponsor you see.
I don't think it's related to this place.
It's good.
I found it.
Did you find it?
Where is it?
I found it.
It's dangerous.
It's Yutty.
It's slow.
That's right.
Where are you going?
Let's get off.
It's strange.
This is amazing.
It's hard to get.
It's delicious.
That's a big print.
Yutty's face is big.
It's peeking into someone's house.
Let's go in.
That's a person's house.
It's a person's house.
It's a dog.
What are you doing?
Takayama.
The dog is running away.
Look at this.
Thank you very much.
I caught it.
It's about 10,000 to 20,000 yen.
I think it was looking for a house with a dog.
That's right.
That's why it's purring.
It's a scam.
It's terrible.
The shutter is closed, but the dog doesn't run away.
I caught it.
Mr. Hamada.
The dog is running away.
It's here.
Thank you very much.
Please be careful.
Yes.
It's amazing.
That's right.
It's 20,000 yen just for this.
It's amazing.
Before that, I brought my hair to Suwa.
That's right.
I was worried of the dog running away.
It's a cash dispenser.
I think it's a drug.
It's a drug.
I'm worried, too.
I saw who was doing what.
Really?
Do you know that?
Someone is coming.
Yes.
It does not matter what people say.
I see.
Huh?
Is that a plastic bottle?
It's full of trash.
It's a plastic bottle.
Yeah, it is.
I see.
You can't buy plastic bottles with money.
You can't.
Unless it's a big one.
It's full of trash.
Where is it?
It's in the park.
There it is.
Is it in?
It's in.
It's a child.
It's a child?
Yeah.
It's a child.
There it is.
It's full of trash.
Huh?
It's a shrimp.
It's full of trash.
Huh?
Thank you very much.
You're my father.
I know you're doing this at home.
Of course.
Let me see.
You're very nice.
It's moving a lot.
What should we do?
Let's go home.
Let's give the child.
Good luck.
It says half price for the shrimp.
No.
It's not a shrimp.
This is annoying!
You are cute.
Where are you going to sell this?
такое
I don't know if it was profitable when it was cheap
It's harder to sell than it is to sell
It's in
What is this?
What is a kid's shop?
End of version import
It says it's certified
It says it's selling competitive materials
But it's different from Kejiran
It says it's cold
I don't think I've ever seen a woman like this
Where are you going?
Are you going home by bicycle?
What kind of shop is this?
Don't show it
I haven't seen it yet
I'm going to catch up
I can't do that
He ran away
It's been raining a lot
I thought I lost it
Isn't that Mr. Ito?
The white car
You
Isn't that the white car?
But it's not a bicycle
It's Mr. Ito
It's not a bicycle
I know that situation
I haven't seen it
Shall we go?
I got hit
Look at this
License
It's a young comedian's license
Really?
Isn't that BAKANA?
BAKANA
Did you shoot BAKANA?
He said he spilled the stew
It's a stew again
It's the same as the first time
I was hit a lot
I was hit
Look at this
It's the same situation
Did it fall?
It fell
Be careful
He said be careful
It's fast
They are following Mr. Ito
Finally, the secret of Mr. Ito will be revealed
Mr. Ito
I found it
Did you find it?
Are you playing hide-and-seek?
I'm sure I saw it
Where is it?
It's here
It's a bench
It's broken
It's easy to understand
There are many
What is it?
I don't know
That's Mr. Ito's chair
It's a chair
He threw the umbrella
Where is it?
I don't know
It's a fan
I see
What is it?
They are collecting money
Is it an organ?
Yes
I see
Is it an organization?
They are friends
What kind of organization is it?
It's Mr. Ito
He is collecting money
It looks like Mr. Ito
It's not enough
What is it?
It's broken
I saw it
It's a fan
It's not enough
Let's do it
It's broken
I saw it
Where did you see it?
It hurts
I got hit on my neck
Why did you run away?
Are you OK?
I got hit on my neck
Why did you run away?
It doesn't move
Why are you standing on the edge?
It's like a game character
If you don't touch the controller, it won't move
Mr. Ito
Don't fall in love with me
Hamada's ear
The wind is blowing
Thank you
I was listening to Kokoriko for a while
It was like a dry laughing
It wasn't like that
I was laughing because of my aura
Your aura is different
It's coming out like a person
Can you see it?
It's coming out like this
It's not good if it falls
It's like a man who slides with his aura
It's like a liquid
I understand
I won't talk anymore
The weather is bad
It's raining
It's not good
In Japan, it rains with this hand
I can't go to the garden except for the rainy season
I don't know why it's raining in the fall
I'll try to change the name
I won't talk anymore
I have something to say
Everyone is looking at me with a kind face
It's like Matsumoto is talking too much
I can't feel the atmosphere
I want Hamada to talk too
It's not talking too much
What is Matsumoto talking about?
Is it that?
I was curious about that
There's nothing
Are you really going to win?
I'm not interested in baseball
What did I say when baseball started this year?
I'm a huge fan from today
Did you say a huge fan?
I said I was a huge fan from this year
Did you say that?
I said that
That's right
I'm feeling down right now
I'm very excited
How was today's game?
Today's game was good
I didn't think it was that good
It was good
Do you know where you played today?
I played with the other 11 baseball teams
That's what baseball is about
It doesn't matter where you play today
It doesn't matter
I don't know if I won or not
You're playing with a team other than yours
Then who are you playing with?
Are you playing individually?
You're playing thinking everyone else is your enemy
That's right but
Where is today's enemy?
What is today's enemy?
What is today's side dish?
I don't know
Listen to me
Why are you listening to me?
I heard that you lost your mind 3 times when you were a kid
Can you tell us what happened?
To be honest, it was when I was in the first grade of elementary school
Why are you so young?
Then why did you lose your mind?
When I saw you
Why? You were a first grader
I was really surprised
Why?
Why were you surprised when you saw me?
What kind of season was that?
I heard that you were in elementary school
I think I've said this before but I was in Pantano
Pantano is in G-Pantano
It's in Bellevue
Bellevue wasn't half bad
You might think it's a lie but it's wider than U.S.T.
Bellevue isn't like that
I was in Clipper
Wait, wasn't that a vertical roll?
It was a vertical roll
Do I have long hair like this?
I was in a vertical roll so I can't lie
You had something like an instrument
Isn't that the same thing as a snufkin?
Snufkin is a guitar, right?
No, you had something like an instrument
What's an instrument?
Something like a marimba
That's not it
You had something like a harp
I was surprised and I got scared
Oh really?
My friend said, wait, wait
He said, wait, wait and I woke up
He came closer
When he came closer, it was the second time
That was the second time
When I woke up, I laughed
It was the third time
It was the third time in a row
But I was surprised too
When I saw you, I thought you were walking on the sidewalk
You're a small kid
You're so dark
You're walking on the sidewalk like this
I don't walk on the sidewalk more than one time
At least more than two times
This is a question for Matsumoto-san
I saw a lot
When bugs die, why do they look up?
I can't say that, but I remember
When you go to a funeral
You say, look up
I know
You don't stop?
Why?
You're definitely scared
I'm not scared
You know I'm going to a funeral
That's true, but
What should I say?
You don't have to say anything
But you say, look up, look up
You get tired of it
To be honest
Really?
But it's not like it's a joke
The other day at Yoshie-shi
You said look up
Tsurubayama-san came
He said, Hamada, come here
I said, look at this face
That's the cause
It's fine
It's fine, but
You shouldn't look at a normal person
That's why
You shouldn't laugh
That's what Tsurubayama-san did
He said, look, it's a katakana
And he said, look up
Right?
He's obviously blindfolded
That's true
You're scared of him
You don't know
So even if I die
I don't know if my family will be there
My family might say, look up
But you shouldn't look
Why?
It's a win-win
Please
What do you mean please?
It's fine, everyone will laugh
That's fine, right?
That's fine
I said this before, but Shohei-san
Even if I die, I want you to put on yellow glasses
If I say, look up, what kind of glasses are those?
That's fine
I'm popular because
If I say, look up, look up
I want to look like this
I want to laugh like this
I understand
I want to wear glasses like this