Let's win with 100 points difference in the first episode of Ragi no Tsukaya!
Mr. Madoh, it's a good weather.
It's a good weather.
I'm playing the game after watching this title.
What do you mean?
Recently, there are many restrictions.
Everyone is stressed out.
I'm going to blow up here and win.
We can win 100-0.
Mr. Hamada.
We are the student team.
We played baseball here.
Yes.
But we can't win 100 points.
Even 20 points is not a big deal.
Yes.
We have to play home base more than 100 times.
We have to play more than 10 times per person.
But it's not baseball.
It's softball.
It's like throwing it from the bottom
Bang bang!
The average score we got was about 48
About 48
In the end, after we got all the scores,
we said that the weather was the only good thing
It's a battle
It's really boring
It's hard
Let's win the game with 100 points difference
This time, they will beat the opponent until they get 100 points difference
It's a pleasant game
The important opponent is
You are calling only the ones who can't move
There are many who can't move
This way, this way.
Even more, even more.
Even more?
Yes.
Now, let's have the opponents appear.
Please.
Thank you for waiting.
100 Tensha Borogatsu Softball.
The players of the opposing team have entered.
Number 72, Takashi Sasano.
Takashi Sasano.
Wow.
Really?
What are you talking about?
You don't have any baseball experience, do you?
It's the same as Nariho.
But it's a light baseball.
I can't do this kind of reckless planning.
You're saying it's a bad idea.
I'm not going to take it out.
I'm a fan of thinking about other things.
Even if it's a variety show.
But it's not just Sasahara-san, right?
Even if Sasahara-san was the only one who was in the game, what would the other players think?
That's the problem
Let's go to the next player
Number 45, Fifi
It doesn't suit the uniform!
It's very uncomfortable
Have you ever played softball?
Baseball?
Egypt doesn't play that at all.
They don't play baseball.
But I think I can do it.
Really?
You have to get the ball.
Africa has a high physical ability.
The wind is strong.
The wind of the desert!
Let's go to the next game!
Stepangu, No.11, DJ Kou
What?
Hey hey hey hey hey hey!
The king of the New York City
What about Kou?
Hey hey hey hey hey hey!
I'll make you laugh!
Kou, you have power, right?
I have power, I'm fine
Kou, you don't do anything, right? You don't play baseball or other sports, right?
No, I don't play baseball, but I played rugby
Really?
But it's different.
It's different.
Next player, please.
Number 72, Mr. Maric.
Mr. Maric.
Maric is here.
He's here.
The uniform is already dirty.
What happened?
He's here.
The uniform is already dirty.
What happened?
You are not an experienced player, right?
I touched softball for the first time in 60 years
I see
This is good, I understand
Please
Next player, please
Number 66, Mizusawa Aki
Mizusawa Aki
Really?
He is fine
Please don't get hurt
Please listen to the injury
Are you doing any exercise?
I'm a hip hopper, so I can do this.
I can do this.
I understand.
Please take care of me.
Next player, please.
No.53, Taka Toriki.
How did you do that?
It looks so heavy
It's heavy
How much do you weigh?
120kg
I can't run
You are a batter
Have you played softball?
No, since I was in elementary school
I don't know about the ball
You have to use your body
Seba-kun, 73kg, Okamoto Nobuto
Okamoto Nobuto
It's a very simple line.
It's simple.
How did you learn that?
The shop is closed now.
I'm just doing what I do.
You don't have to do that.
Excuse me, but how about your experience with the softball?
I played it a little 40 years ago.
Everyone is like that.
No.60, Daniel Karr.
Daniel Karr.
This is definitely not.
Definitely not.
Ah, the skater.
The skater.
Daniel-san.
What's wrong?
I did it a lot when I was a kid.
Your body is so big.
You can do a good batting.
It looks like you can hit.
I feel like I'm a ticket collector.
The last one is this person.
Number 54, Sakamoto-chan.
He was sleeping until the end.
I'm Sakamoto-chan. Nice to meet you.
Can you do it?
I've gained 88kg.
I'm a yellow-eyed man
I'm a
Can you do it?
I've done it in the school days
It's been 45 years
You can get 100 points with this
I think I can do it
Really?
I can do it
If you roll it, it will stop
No, no, no
What kind of...
Three-way
Are you serious?
Of course
Are you hungry?
You have a great sense of direction
The game starts 3 hours ago
The first day of the trip
Good morning
The guest team 9, including Sasano, arrived at the resort early to warm up
We'll do our best
It's cold
I'm sorry to wake you up this early
I don't know what's going to happen
It's fun to do 100 push-ups
It's not easy
No matter how hard it is
Even though it's sunny, it's still a cold season
So they warm up carefully
This is hard
Isn't it amazing?
After warming up with jogging, they stretch
5,6,7,8
Stretch the back of the thighs
How was it? Did you relax?
No, but I did stretch
It's dangerous if you don't stretch
It's about 10 seconds.
As the tension in his muscles gradually loosens with the dash,
Let's go for the handstand.
he practices knocking to get used to the softball.
However, he is a beginner.
The former idol Mizusawa Aki.
I got it!
Fifi from Egypt
Daniel Kaur who is good at Yamagata dialect
He is good at tunneling
20 years ago, he was the top student in the university entrance exam.
He caught it with his knee.
Are you able to do it, Okamoto-san?
No, I'm not able to do it at all.
You're able to move the most, right?
Yes.
Just now, I was so tired that my legs were shaking.
I'm so tired
Of course, the team is warming up before the match
It was warm
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
Make some noise!
Let's do it again
I was surprised
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
Stretch your back.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
Let's do 200.
Stretch your front.
Keep your back straight.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
The director is shaking.
His legs are so slanted.
Ready, go!
Don't throw it like that
That was dangerous
You're a long-distance runner
Why are you running like that?
The ball is huge
Your butt hurts
I want to hit you like this
Are you ready?
The ball is big
Don't say that
It's been a while since I've seen this kind of ball
I'm ready
I'll say it like this
This is serious
This is scary
After warming up
The order meeting to win the casting
First, from Da Jun
The first shot was a bit too much for me.
Running home run.
I'll go home.
It's a waste, but I'll go home.
That's right.
What about Tanaka?
Do you want to go?
I played baseball.
Then you'll play here.
Yes.
I'm going to be the 4th.
You're not going to be the 4th.
I'm going to be the home run.
Yama-chan, are you going to be the 3rd?
No, Hamada-san.
Let's go with the cleanup.
Hamada-san, Matsuyama.
Okada.
Are you going to be the Inamoto?
Or Fujiwara?
Either is fine.
You guys are experienced.
I was a soccer player.
Who are you?
Yoshinobu-san and Komu-san.
I don't need that.
Yoshinobu-san is over there.
Yoshinobu-san will be the last one.
I'll be killed instantly.
Let's go.
Do you want to be a pitcher?
No, I'm not good at playing with my shoulders.
I'm not good at playing with my shoulders.
This one was bad too.
Short.
It's important to get the first one.
You have to get it.
Can you do it?
Tanaka can do it.
You can do it.
Yes, I can.
What about the second one?
There are many catchers.
Fujiwara...
Can you do it?
I think it's better to be a little bigger.
I don't have any experience, but I'll do it.
Are you okay?
Are you sure you are OK with this?
It's not funny at all at home.
Then I can't do it.
If it's funny, I can't do it either.
You need a third.
I'll do it then.
I'll go.
What about the second?
You go.
The pitcher will start.
Then Yama will start.
Then Masumoto will go.
It's your turn.
You can't do it.
There is a possibility that they won't come back to us
That's right
They will take 100 points
They will attack the first floor
The first floor is 100 points
Yes, yes, yes
They don't need to protect
Sasano-san is doing his best
White board
It's like a school without a classroom during the war
From Sadaima, the team that uses the children against the Fingpio All Stars is starting the game.
We will introduce the defense of the Fingpio All Stars.
Pitcher, Takashi Sato.
Catcher, Riki Sakato.
The first is Kenji Sakamoto.
The second is Takatori.
The third is Nobuto Okamoto.
The fourth is Nobuto Okamoto.
The fifth is Mr. Marimitsu.
The sixth is Daniel Carle.
The seventh is Daniel Carle.
Shoto DJ Kou
Left TeeTee
Center Sakamoto-chan
Right Mizusawa Aki
The bag's Audrey Schultz is Shirley S dites
Number 3
Ah!
100 points!
There is no need to shape it
Not yet!
This person still square!
This person will fly, the bag
Don't throw!
It's a little bit too much.
Mr. Kasano is full of motivation.
The timing is a little bit off.
It's a ball. It's not a ball.
It's not a ball at all.
Let's just shoot it.
It's a ball.
If you do it sideways, you can't shoot.
Here we go.
Nice!
7-0
Fighting!
But you...
It's like this
I thought you were more slow
100 points!
2 points!
Please!
1st and 2nd
7-0
You're doing great!
Go, go, go!
Goal, goal, goal!
That was close.
Good, good.
That was good.
Go, go, go!
I'll pull it.
That was dangerous!
Dangerous!
3 points, 3 points, 3 points
Okay, goal!
2 points
If you pick up the ball, you'll think...
Throw it!
It's the worst
You can't do that!
You can't shoot like that!
Out!
Shota!
This is bad!
He's being pushed back!
I'm out!
Shouzo!
Everyone is pretty good
He's really angry
Ah, he got it!
He got it!
This is bad!
The 10 outs is bad!
It's different from what I thought
Please, please
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10
Old man, you're tired, you're tired
It's okay
Okay, okay
99 more
Only 1 point is left from the 2nd round out. leaving with 99 points
From this孫 hooker league...
ので Bllively
Come on, come on...
Come back, gain it
WIl Sacy
Come back
Ok ok
orden
Take that
包装
Hiyahh
I was beaten!
I thought I could do a sliding but I was beaten by the team
You were beaten!
I'm sorry
It's rare for a smart girl to be beaten like this
Reiwa-san is rare
The attack of the Gaku team from the first round
The attack is...
Minamoto is in the 2 base and is in the lead
The next is Komu, he is in the center and gets hit continuously
I'm tired
Ko-san, what happened?
When I heard the step, I heard a thud.
You're still in the game?
Will the type change?
Let's change the type.
Okamoto-san!
Short!
He comes a lot.
Short has too many hits.
So DJ Kou is in first.
Okamoto Nobuto is in short and the game resumes.
2 outs!
He's laughing
He's laughing at this moment
Why is he laughing?
From here, Yoshinobu
End
Pass!
That's it!!
Masumoto and Datta explores the bottom of last month's zinc amount
91 points
2 outs in a 1st round
91 points in the remaining rounds
So, what kind of games will the field смith F
Come on judges Now,督
Get him!
Ahhh, shot!
ienza throw
It's an까sa play
memorial
Kou san didn't caught E concepts
There was, He just missed
Viceps This Play Sorry aboutickets
Mom can't metal-tetunnet
It's safe.
It's not stolen.
Ko-chan, do you need this?
Headphones.
No, I don't need them.
J.C.! The final episode of the game of the 100-point song, BOROGACHI!
DotaBata Play!
I'm so sick of this!
It's so bitter!
The power of the bread, the power of the bread
The past broadcast is being broadcast exclusively on Hulu.