Good evening.
When I first came out, I didn't think it was a good idea for a guest to be so excited.
I see.
Right?
When you come out and you're not in a good mood, it's better to invite a good guest.
But today, it's just a guest who's not in a good mood.
Today, Hana-san, you seem to be in a good mood.
Why?
That's why I hear a lot of laughter.
That's not true.
Maybe your wife is sick or something.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
I go to the toilet every now and then.
You go to the toilet every day.
I go to the public toilet.
I see it every now and then.
I'm the only one who doesn't like it.
What?
Thank you for always using it beautifully.
Isn't that scary?
What do you mean?
It's scary, isn't it?
You know that, don't you?
That's right.
That means...
That means you should use it cleanly, right?
That's right.
But don't you think I should stop saying things like that?
Why?
It's scary.
It's better to say, let's use it cleanly when it's dirty.
Right?
You know that, don't you?
That's why you say things like that.
But I don't know if I should spill it.
I don't know if I should spill it.
But when I suddenly say it, you say, I won't spill it.
That's why you say that.
I won't spill it.
It's like your urine is coming out.
It's you.
Who thought of that?
But if you don't do that, you won't know where your urine is.
There are a lot of people who say, is this where your urine is?
But I think that's scary.
I don't know if I should say it, but it's scary.
It's like when a student is about to start studying for an exam,
you're being teased.
What?
You know that, don't you?
Get out of here.
I don't think that's good.
But I think that way of writing it has decreased a lot.
It has decreased, right?
I think so.
But there was something else.
When I put up a sign saying, thank you for your cooperation,
it really decreased the amount of time.
Is that so?
In reality, it hasn't decreased that much.
I haven't been arrested.
What do you mean by that?
Did you buy Boudin today?
I don't care.
You're going to be a nuisance.
Don't you want to go home?
It's not the time to be doing this.
Hurry up and write down your memory.
Why are you so surprised?
I was really surprised.
You're going to be like this forever.
There are a lot of people like that.
It's hard to talk.
So even though you haven't been arrested,
it has decreased by saying that.
I think you should stop thinking like that.
Why?
It feels like a bad time has come.
It has come.
Speaking of a bad time...
What?
You said something like that.
The other day...
It's totally fine,
but Okama was arrested.
Okama was hit by a car.
Of course.
He was like,
I'm finally coming out.
You're a fool.
I'm glad it was a big car,
but it wasn't a big hit.
It was a small hit.
I thought it was a big hit.
I got out of the car.
I'm not in my teens.
The person who was hit was an old man.
He was a little older than my dad.
He was over 70.
It's totally fine,
but he didn't apologize at all.
I see.
It's fine.
There's no one older than my dad
who's like this.
I was like,
Are you okay?
He was like,
Did you get hit?
I said,
I got hit,
but it's a little cracked.
The tail wasn't cracked.
I said,
I see.
Why?
I said,
Listen carefully.
My ears are weird.
I thought he was apologizing.
No matter how many times I open it,
I can't hear anything.
If it's my car,
it's fine.
I'm fine with it.
But it's a big car,
so I can't say it's okay.
I said something like that.
I see.
I said,
Is that so?
What?
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
Why don't you apologize?
I had a job.
I was on my way to Kiyotashi.
There was a recording.
I think my face is sticking out.
Don't say things you don't need to say.
I said,
Is there anything in that neighborhood?
There is.
It's over there.
I said,
Is there anything in that neighborhood?
No, it's not.
It's a different place.
I said,
Is that so?
My house was right there.
It was right there.
I see.
I said,
This is my house.
I got a license.
I said,
I can't give you that.
Is that so?
But I haven't apologized yet.
I haven't apologized yet.
I said,
I'll go home and get a copy.
I see.
That's fine.
I said,
Are you serious?
That's fine.
I was laughing.
I stopped my car.
I was waiting.
He was going faster than I thought.
I said,
I don't understand.
He was going faster than I thought.
I said,
I'm sorry.
I got a copy.
I was thinking it was weird when he ran away,
But when I got the copy, I said,
I'm sorry.
Why?
I wanted to go to the end of the world without saying sorry.
I said sorry at the end.
I thought,
That's right.
It's hard.
But even if you say that,
There was a mess.
After that?
If there was a mess,
When I gave the car to the trucker,
He hit me like this.
But I'm old, so if I can't do much,
I won't do anything for him.
If there was a mess,
After that, there was a mess.
It's definitely a lie.
It's true.
I don't know if he meant to apologize.
I see.
I don't know if he meant to say hello,
But sometimes he doesn't.
What?
He always says,
Good morning.
But you ignore him.
Hey!
You ignore him like this.
Hey, am I an idiot?
What?
What is this?
You decided not to say hello when you were born,
So maybe that's why.
Hey,
You're going to do that again, right?
That's right.
The showdown.
You haven't decided what to do yet, right?
Yes.
I'm not a regular,
But I have a little kid.
You have a little kid?
He's a trash comedian.
He has a can, a bottle, and plastic.
I'll call him.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
It's a big deal,
But it's not a big deal that the audience is excited.
It was a big deal.
We're here to watch the showdown.
What did we do last time?
Bowling.
Bowling?
Yes.
This kind of bowling.
I didn't know it was that old.
It was a year ago.
It was a long time ago.
What are we going to do next?
I don't think so,
But why don't we have Yamanagi do it by himself?
That's a good idea.
That's not the power of a downtown kid.
I want to do it by myself.
It's been 98 years.
The two of us,
Matsumoto, Kogoriko, and Hoka.
I don't care about the others.
Kogoriko, Hoka.
You're always in it.
That's what all the news reporters do.
Lose, lose, lose.
Three wins, three losses.
Tanaka, you're going to have a baby.
I want to have a family, but I'm lonely.
Don't say you're lonely.
I'm having a lot of fun.
I don't care about the team.
I don't care about what we're going to do.
At school,
I asked him if he was interested in a flying box.
Yama?
He said he could fly a kite.
You mean this height?
I can fly a kite.
You mean you can fly this height?
Yes, I can fly a kite.
So you want to fly a kite now?
That's right.
I'll try to fly a kite at school.
I'll try to fly it on stage.
Let's fly it.
What do you want me to do with the kite?
You can do it with your hands.
Do I have to do it like this?
Or do I have to do it like this?
You can do it with your hands.
Are you sure?
You don't have to jump and fly like this.
You can do it with your hands.
Like this?
That's right.
It's okay.
I'm sorry, but I'm going to ask you something.
You don't have to laugh.
This time.
I said I wanted you to laugh.
If you can do it, it'll be fun.
It'll be fun.
Don't be scared.
I'll do it like this.
Go over there a little more.
Which way?
That way.
There's only one way.
There's a lot of ways.
Which way?
Can I take it off?
It was easier earlier.
It's better to make your body lighter.
It doesn't change much.
Do you want me to take it off here?
Take it off.
Take it off?
All of it?
Can you do it?
You don't have a microphone?
If you have a microphone, it's okay.
It's okay?
I don't want to talk about such important comments.
Catch it.
Put it on your neck.
What are you doing?
Why are you putting it on your neck?
Wait a minute.
Why did you take it off before that?
I want to do it like this.
Like this.
It's changed a lot from the beginning.
It's changed a lot.
Mayonnaise.
It's better to go this way.
Be careful.
It's dangerous over here.
You should look over there.
It's okay.
It's impossible.
You're just trying to show yourself.
You're like a downtown servant.
You first said that.
It's okay.
It could be that
I'm going to jump and go all the way over there.
I'm going to go there and really burn myself.
Where? Where do you want to go?
When you get to the sign...
The burger place.
This burger.
It's a monster.
That's right.
I'm just going to watch.
I'm scared to go down because I don't have any legs.
About 90% of the customers are getting tired of it.
I feel like this one is more of an obstacle than this one.
It's okay.
This one?
Yes.
When you jump.
I see.
I think that one is harder to open.
What are you doing?
Kitty-chan!
I'm going to start now.
Just one thing.
What?
I'm sorry.
You're so scary.
I knew it after I saw the underwear.
When did you...
I'm really going to start now.
I'm surprised.
What kind of lie is that?
I wanted to say something like that.
You're all so good at making up things.
I'm sorry.
You didn't open it.
What do you want to do?
Please write it down in the manuscript.
First of all...
What did you want to do?
Let's end it here.
Who's going to solve it?
I still have a lot to decide.
That's right.
Basically, I'll do it like this.
When the audience comes out and asks what the fight is,
I'll take off your underwear.
Why?
The order is...
Do you want to do it?
If we go in order, it's the order in which Mr. Hamagawa loses.
It's like this.
It's three by three.
If it goes by flow.
Then, if I go normally, I'm the only one.
That's right.
That's all right.
I don't feel like losing.
But when I said it last time,
Koko Riko and the other people said they wanted to go there.
I went there with this person's intention.
Koko Riko and the other people said that?
That's right.
It's hard to say, isn't it?
Actually, don't you want to join my team?
Hmm...
No, no, no.
That's a strange development.
Why?
This time, how about we split into S and M?
S and M.
If that's the case...
It's completely like this.
Me too.
This is a half-hearted thing.
No, I'm also M.
I'm also M.
Naya-san, you're saying M-like.
I'm also M-like.
No, I'm also M-like.
Then...
I'm also M.
Ah, Tanato is S.
Tanato is S.
I'm S, unexpectedly.
It's S, isn't it?
S and M.
Are we going to lose?
What kind of game is this?
Tanaka's S is interesting.
I won't stop.
Even if I look at it, I can't go up any further.
Can I see it once?
Oh, sure.
Even if you can, I'll do it.
Okay.
With Guppa...
Yes.
Ah, isn't there something like this?
Isn't there something like this?
No, this is...
No, no, this is important.
It's important.
This is important.
Why?
Eh?
Matsumoto-san and Hamada-san, please break up.
Ah, Dada-san.
That's right.
Don't say such things.
No, no, it's okay.
It's okay.
Then Hamada and I will break up.
Yes.
Then Guppa and I will break up.
Ah, is that okay?
Yes, yes, yes.
Then we'll do it.
Yes, let's do it.
Why are you breaking up with me?
Eh?
Then Guppa and I will break up.
Ah, no, it's not like that.
Then Matsumoto-san, you can decide individually.
Then, I don't know what you're talking about.
You don't know?
You don't know anything?
Then, let's all imitate the rabbit.
Why are you imitating me?
It's different.
Then Hamada and I will break up.
Then you guys don't know, right?
You don't see it.
Ah, you don't see it.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
You don't see it.
Yes.
That's the meaning of it.
That's fine.
Yes.
Then Gu or Pa?
One, two...
Pa.
Gu.
It's that kind of thing.
That's the possibility?
It's that kind of thing, right?
The three of you are going to decide on Gu or Pa?
You're going to convey it, right?
You don't know the explanation, right?
I'll tell you what.
I don't know.
Dann, everyone, let's imitate a chicken.
Gu, you should give me one.
Well, then, we'll try that again.
You'll give it again?
Here you go.
Are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready.
Ready, set, go!
Ah, then it's me!
Isn't that fine?
But before that, I'd like to come over here.
A leader like this...
The teamwork is...
I don't know what you're talking about.
No, it's not like that.
Our feelings are...
No, why don't you understand?
You understand, don't you?
Of course I understand!
Koudan is Koudan.
You don't need anyone else?
Eh?
No, that's right.
If the two of you really want this guy, then we'll go, right?
It's a deal.
If you say something like that, it'll be like Dondoko Yamaguchi.
Why did this member become a regular?
Because of what happened now.
Because of what happened now, right?
Let's decide again, right?
Yes.
What should we do?
Let's decide what to do first.
For now, we'll do what we have to do.
Yes, please.
This is hard. I really don't like this.
It's a penalty.
I really don't like the inn type.
If you say that, I really don't like the Onigoko family.
I really don't like the Onigoko family.
But there's a rumor that you'll do it for 48 hours.
I really don't like it.
I can't do it anymore.
How many years has it been?
I'm already old.
I'm old, so I'll just go.
I'm still young, right?
I'm already sick of being a new member, so my butt is still so big.
It's Ado-chan's butt.
It's not like that.
Hey!
This summer, the confrontation again.
This program was provided by the following sponsors.