This is the first episode of Chikichiki Beach Ballein Okinawa!
So you're wearing your newest swimsuit.
I've always wanted to see this.
It's not sold anywhere.
It's not sold anywhere anymore.
This is a swimsuit from 3 years later.
Oh really?
It's pre-recorded, right?
It's pre-recorded.
It's like this.
This is the bottom.
But I think this is a little big.
That's right.
This is necessary.
What's the back like?
The back is like this.
I'll do my best today.
It's a beach ballein in Okinawa.
There are two beach balleins.
I'm not a skater, but I'll do it with everyone.
First of all, Team Zero.
It's always a prelude to our program.
I've been doing it for about a year.
Team Zero has been here since the first time.
It's the first time I've been on the show.
Even if it's only men.
That's right.
It's Okinawa.
There are two gyaru.
Here you go.
These two are going to be separated.
Let's do it together.
All right.
I can't see it in the sand.
Everyone's in the sand.
I'm just kidding.
Is that okay, referee?
Isn't that four times?
It's a double dribble.
Did you hear that?
Is that okay?
It's a double dribble.
It's safe.
I'm sorry.
You just had a great chance.
I'll show you.
I'm scared.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you.
I can see the next one well.
That's amazing.
It's been a week since I came to Okinawa.
I'm not that tanned.
Do you like Okinawa?
Basically.
To be honest.
I don't hate it.
But where do you like the most in Japan?
Osaka.
Osaka is the best.
Where I am.
You're not where you are.
It's where I was born.
To be honest.
I'm sad.
Why?
I thought you'd be a Osaka person until you die.
I'm a Osaka person.
I'm talking like a Osaka person.
I'm talking.
My wife is a woman from Tokyo.
I'm not talking about Osaka.
I'm talking about how I was betrayed by you.
You've been living in Tokyo all this time.
But the child you're going to have.
What the hell are you talking about?
I'm looking forward to this.
I'm looking forward to it.
Have you thought of a name?
Not at all.
Next year.
I haven't thought of a name yet.
Ryukyu.
You guys.
Don't call Okinawa Chinan.
Since I came.
Don't call Chinan.
Ryukyu-chan is cute.
It's not cute.
Why?
Ryukyu-chan is cute.
Everyone calls you Kyu-chan Kyu-chan.
What do you like?
What?
I.
Well, Japan is big.
I think my second hometown is Okinawa.
You can say it wherever you go.
If I get married.
I'd like to go to Okinawa.
You said it when you were in Hokkaido.
Hokkaido?
Why are you angry?
They have a bad temper.
Don't think about it.
I don't care if you don't think about it.
After all, Okinawa is Okinawa.
Why Okinawa?
After all, women from other countries are very hot.
I've heard of it somewhere.
You're still wearing it.
No, it's true.
Have you been to the moon?
I've been to the moon.
With a woman from the south.
I don't know.
I've heard of it somewhere.
Well, a woman from the south.
I've been to the Philippines.
You're going too far.
Don't go too far.
But what about Okinawan women?
Okinawa is a country.
Well, it's a country.
Is it developing?
What?
The life.
What about it?
I don't know if I'll stay in a hotel tonight or go out.
Is it developing?
You don't have to ask me that.
What about it?
What do you mean?
There are various things depending on the land.
Depending on the land?
Depending on the land.
Osaka is a pretty big city.
The women are pretty...
They're pretty lively.
That's the meaning.
I know that.
And, um...
I heard that the women in Nagoya are pretty light.
That's your specialty.
What?
I've been to Nagoya.
I've been to a fashion massage.
You haven't been.
What's here?
Fashion massage.
What?
Which one?
There's one.
There's one?
I don't know.
I've been there.
There's a Maihara Sako Gai.
What's that?
Maihara Sako Gai.
What's Maihara?
What about it?
Maihara Sako Gai?
I've never heard of it before.
What's Maihara Sako Gai?
It's like an ancient...
A ruin or something.
This is Maihara Sako Gai.
It's like an air balloon.
What's Maihara Sako Gai?
I've heard of it.
I've heard of it before, so I've come this far.
We...
That's right.
That's strange.
There's something like that in Okinawa.
In Okinawa?
Yes.
What is it really like?
It's sexual, right?
How long have you been a virgin?
If I were a 15-year-old, I wouldn't say that.
In Osaka, I was in the first year of high school.
Really?
I was in the first or second year of high school.
Is it fast?
It's slow.
You're good.
By the way, how old are you?
I think you're even slower.
I see.
I wanted to know that.
Why?
What's the point of knowing that and thinking about today's action?
I want to know.
Where are you going?
Where are you going today?
Maihara Sako Gai.
Sako Gai.
I don't want to say that, but I want to go to a disco.
Really?
I want to go with Nori.
You can't go?
You came here and...
What?
You came here and dressed like a gentleman.
Don't point your finger.
No, I...
I went to play with you while you were sleeping.
What kind of play?
You were healthy.
You...
Don't point your finger.
That's not it.
You're asking me.
That's right.
You're thinking about something sexy today.
I won't let you say that you're not thinking.
You said there was nothing.
You're the one who made it out of nothing.
There must be something you're thinking about.
I'm not thinking.
Everyone is wondering what to do today.
Really?
Then don't wear underwear until you get back to Okinawa.
I'll take a bath.
That's a weird bath.
What is that?
What?
What are you doing?
I'm thinking about something.
I'm thinking about what to do after this.
There's nothing?
There's nothing.
I've been asking you about it.
Leave that aside.
Why should I leave it aside?
I want to ask you that.
Are you going or not?
I'm not going.
You're in a hurry.
You have 15 minutes.
I'm not going.
You're not going.
How many years have I taken you?
How many years have I gone?
Are you going or not?
I'm not going.
You're not going either.
Don't lie to me.
I don't want to meet you there.
I can't meet you because I can't go.
I think you want to go because you're so determined.
Do you want to go?
I don't want to go at all.
You're not going, are you?
What?
I'm not going.
I'm not going either.
What are you doing?
What kind of person are you?
Hello.
What's your name?
I'm Sueyoshi.
Sueyoshi.
Your voice is low.
I'm Sueyoshi.
How old are you?
I'm 23.
What were you?
I was an instructor of jet skiing.
Don't you have a title?
I don't have a title.
The queen appeared in the first round.
You're just an older sister.
I'm just an older sister.
You're an instructor of jet skiing.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Good luck.
That's great.
I'll do my best.
A long time ago, Matsumoto was working part-time at a bar.
One of the two stayed there with his mother until late at night.
When he finished his work and was about to go home, his mother approached him and was about to be attacked.
Who did that?
Please tell me.
Did you get attacked?
He was working part-time at a snack bar.
His mother was like...
In a good way, she was like Pigmon.
What do you mean by good way?
You're crazy.
You're like Pigmon.
Pigmon...
Jamila?
She was a good person.
She was a good person, but she was scary.
Her makeup was flashy.
We were always together.
If we couldn't go home by the end of the day,
the two of us would stay at my mother's place.
But he was on vacation.
Yes.
He was on vacation.
I was the only one who could go home.
We were late for the end of the day.
The two of us would stay at my mother's place,
but my mother was like,
You can go home by yourself.
Come on, come on.
She was getting more and more scary.
She was like, I won't do anything.
So we stayed there.
At around 3 o'clock in the morning,
I opened my eyes.
She was like,
You're so scary.
Stop it.
She was like Hongo Takeshi before he was remodeled.
You're so scary.
The child I gave birth to at that time was this one.
I think there are people who are chasing you wherever you go.
What do you think about them?
Please give me some advice for what to do next.
I think I know why you're a stroller.
Your next job.
That's amazing.
We know things that we don't know.
You're worse than a detective.
That's true.
Your shoes are like Marco's shoes.
That's amazing.
There are a lot of good and bad things.
The good thing is the car.
I went to the scene to get a car.
I couldn't stop it.
I opened the space and stood up.
I was like this.
I was like the old man at the parking lot.
That's true.
And when I was in pain, they fixed it for me.
How did they fix it for you?
I don't know.
I don't think there's anyone in Okinawa who wants to chase you.
If you give advice to someone who's chasing you, don't chase them too far.
Don't overtake them.
You're good.
If they notice you, tell them you went first.
There are people who go first when they notice me.
There are people like that.
You don't know if there's a lot of cars around you.
If you go like this, you'll get hit.
You'll get hit.
But still...
I'll do my best!
And there are times when you're in bad shape because you're a girl.
That's true.
There are times when you get hit once a month.
If you're healthy every day.
But you don't show it.
You don't show it when you're in bad shape.
So when I'm in the car, I'll be like,
Grandma!
I'll take a break.
I'm happy about that.
I'm unhappy about that.
Next.
Good evening.
I have a question.
Machan is in a certain show.
This must be about Yutomo.
He's very quiet.
He walks very quietly.
And he's dressed up.
He's wearing a black bra.
What do you think you are?
Applause!
When you're on TV and talking to Hama-chan, you look very cheerful and happy.
But who is the real Machan?
Do you hate your fans?
Or do you have some deep worries?
I think it's a very stupid question, but please tell us.
I'll tell you.
This was the same when I came in today.
It was scary?
Yes, it was.
He said it was scary.
What's scary?
His face.
His face?
It doesn't matter.
It's always because he's hot.
You came here by car today, right?
Yes.
What did you look like when you got off the car?
I had a smile on my face.
I see.
Even the fans said,
Matsumoto-san, please take this.
I'm scared.
It was scary.
I'm sure you are.
The other day, I said,
Ah, this is Machan.
And he said,
Ah.
He didn't say,
He said,
Thank you.
Ah has a lot in it.
He didn't say,
Ah.
Ah has a lot in it.
Ah has a lot of gratitude.
And,
He's a sweet guy.
Even if he was born,
You wouldn't know it.
Ah says,
Thank you,
And he's a sweet guy.
You wouldn't know it.
You're laughing.
You should have a smile on your face.
When I got off the car today,
I said,
I'm scared.
And when the door opened,
I said,
I'm scared.
You're kidding, right?
You're kidding.
I think I said,
I'm scared,
because I felt bad.
I was laughing.
But everyone thinks so.
What should I do?
You should think of something fun while walking.
If I think of something fun for me,
I'll do it.
That's the face you're thinking of.
I don't need a face.
So I'll just do a little bit.
Action?
That's right.
A face is normal.
Even this.
Look at it once.
You won't know if it's good or bad.
What?
So,
Yes.
We're back at the store.
Today,
We did a beach ballet.
We did.
We did jet skiing.
And,
What else?
Marine jet.
We did that.
Yes.
We rode a lot.
But,
My latest swimsuit was amazing.
It was amazing.
That was perfect.
It was a little dangerous.
I tried not to imitate the kids watching TV.
But,
You didn't sell that, did you?
No, I didn't.
Really?
You wore that and went to the beach.
Yes.
In my memory,
I and Gunji Kawamata were on TV.
Kawamata's was a little older.
No, no, no.
It was a big one.
Yes.
I want to go to other places on this show.
I want to.
Yes.
Well,
I'll be back in Tokyo next week.
I'll be back in Tokyo.
I want to do it.
Yes.
I'll be your assistant.
All of them are the same.
I'll be waiting for you.
So,
The Okinawa version of the Karaen.
This is the end of this week.
See you next week.
Good bye.