Reihou, Fujino Fumoto. This is the holy land of bus fishing, Kawaguchiko.
Two people from downtown started to learn fishing two years ago.
They were captivated by the charm of bus fishing, and Matsumoto was able to win the golden trophy that the fishermen longed for for two consecutive years.
And this year, the fishermen of the entertainment world gathered to aim at the emperor.
The third Gaki no Tsugai Alliance, Chikijiki Entertainment Fishing Championship!
Wow!
First of all, the participants!
Good morning!
Now, it has started.
The first participant is Mr. Matsutoshi Hamada.
Nice to meet you.
This is the third time.
Yes, this is the third time.
My partner has already won the first and second times.
That's right.
I will do my best to win this time.
Please do your best.
I will take all of them.
Then, I would like to invite various people.
Gaki no Tsugai Fishing Championship!
The first challenger is Mr. Itoi Shigesato, who likes dad jokes.
Mr. Itoi.
Yes.
How are you doing recently?
I'm doing well.
Are you doing well?
Yes.
Then, please do your best.
Is it the end?
Let's continue.
The second challenger is Mr. Tamio Okuda, who lives in the bus in Inseide, the capital of Paris.
Thank you.
Please come here.
Yes.
Hello.
Do you like to take the bus?
Yes, I like it.
Is that so?
Yes.
Then, please do your best.
Thank you.
The third challenger is Mr. Yosuke Eguchi, who is busy with drama.
Hello.
How are you doing?
Hi.
I like it.
I'm going to take the bus today.
What time will you arrive at the bus stop?
This time?
Yes.
What time will you arrive at the bus stop?
When the sun goes down.
I understand.
Thank you.
Please welcome the very first challenger.
He is from downtown Tokyo, in Anagasaki.
Mr. Hideaki Tomuraga.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Mr. Chokunaga, how do you feel about bus fishing?
I'm looking forward to it.
I understand. Thank you very much.
This is the last one.
Defending champion.
Born for bus fishing.
Mr. Matsumoto Hitoshi.
Don't laugh at me.
I don't want to be introduced.
I'm angry.
Everyone, this is the trophy given to the champion.
I've won it twice.
Mr. Matsumoto.
This is the third time.
I was born again.
It's heavy.
By the way, it costs 600,000 yen.
Really?
The champion can take it home.
I've won it three times.
If you take it home, put it on the TV.
Is it decided?
It's decided.
You'll know when the guests come.
From now on, I'll give you a dantang lure.
Are you ready?
I'll give each boat one set.
This time, as a special rule,
If you fish a bus with one of the lures in 30 minutes,
10,000 yen will be added for each one.
If you catch it in the meantime,
10,000 yen for each one.
Which one do you want?
I'll put one set on each boat.
Let's get started.
You guys fish.
It's not going to be a show.
You guys, too.
Shut up.
Come on.
I can't win.
I'm moved.
I'll do it.
I'll do my best.
Last time, it was Willy.
This time, it's this year.
This time, I want to go one step at a time.
Well...
I'll win.
I said it again.
Well, I'll do my best not to lose to Masumoto Hamada.
Who will get the golden trophy?
The hot battle for the position of the man begins now.
First, the Itoi-Matsumoto duo starts fishing at a point away from the other boats.
As soon as he threw the fishing line, it hit the Itoi's rod.
OK, OK, OK.
This is a net.
All of a sudden.
All right.
I got it.
This is big, isn't it?
This is big.
All right.
On the other hand, the Hamada-Tokunaga duo and the Okuda-Eguchi duo started fishing at the same point.
I got it.
Wait a minute.
It's small, isn't it?
I got it.
Hey, don't get carried away.
It's small.
Even though the prey is small, Hamada is a little impatient because he was caught first.
I haven't caught a big one yet.
Itoi-san.
Itoi-san?
What kind of fish?
A big one.
Really?
Yes.
What kind of fish is it?
I got it.
It's easier to catch than before.
It's big.
Wow, it's big.
Itoi got another hit in a row.
It's big.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I'm counting on you, The Ending Champion.
What?
I don't feel like I'm going to catch it.
I'm going to be frustrated if I catch it first.
It's the other way around.
That's right.
It was a good start, but after that, it was a combination of Okuda and Eguchi, which Sao didn't say was lucky.
This time, I want to avoid only the small ones.
I want to avoid only the small ones.
But if I catch all of them, I'll definitely lose.
I'm hungry.
It's like a movie theater from a long time ago.
It's amazing.
I'm hungry.
It's good.
I'm not good at fishing.
Hey!
The Hamada-Tokunaga combination is still not a hit.
It's just that time passes quietly.
Brother, can you catch a big one?
No, I can't.
You can't?
I'm sorry.
I don't think you can do that.
I thought so, but suddenly there was a sign of a hit on Tokunaga's rod.
It's big, it's big.
Eh, it's coming?
Toki, you should have hit it earlier.
Sorry.
Asaki.
It's big, it's big.
You should go slowly.
Drop it, drop it.
You!
After this...
Cut it, cut it!
Alright!
Cut it, cut it! Cut it in the middle!
Cut it in half, cut it in half.
It's hard.
7...
3, 4...
No, no, if you do it now, you'll be in the first place.
I think the one earlier, Tamiyo and Eguchi...
Now, it's safe.
Don't talk so much.
It's hard.
If you let Hama-chan catch it first, you'll lose with your mouth.
On the other hand, Eguchi and Okuda's duo quietly went fishing.
You must be hungry, right?
Oh, excuse me.
I brought you a lot.
Thank you.
I want to give it to you, but to be honest...
I have a younger brother under the same roof.
What do you think?
For the last episode?
For the last episode.
Is that okay?
Seriously.
I'll tell you.
Oh, please.
Yes.
Then, I'll give it to you.
What about mine?
It can be a short song.
I don't need it.
Tokunaga-san said he caught one.
Wow.
Only two of them caught it.
I know how scary they are, so I won't say anything.
I see.
That's amazing, too.
I'll give it to you because I'm hungry.
Really?
Yes.
I'll give it to you.
Tokunaga-san said he caught one.
It's a broken radio.
I'll give it to you.
At that moment, Eguchi's rod was broken.
Is this big?
Net, net.
This is a good one.
It's big.
Cut it.
Let it go.
Yes.
Seriously.
It's good.
Eguchi, good job.
Itoi and Matsumoto move to the spot where everyone is.
I caught it.
You caught it?
Yes.
Everyone, we'll start the Dantann Rower.
Please change to Dantann Rower.
You have 30 minutes.
It's long.
Don't say it's long.
I don't have time to do this.
I'm the one who caught it.
Matsumoto Hamadaru is famous for the lake.
He moves to the surface in a beautiful way.
I'm sure Black Bass can't help eating it.
Let's throw it down.
It doesn't have to be powdery.
It's heavy.
I caught it.
Where should I throw it?
I can't catch it.
Seriously.
I have a motorbike.
I can't catch it.
Look, it's floating.
Look.
I can't catch it.
It's floating.
It won't sink.
30 minutes is hard.
It's hard.
What do you think? 15 minutes?
Let's make it half.
It won't sink.
If I catch one in 15 minutes, let's make it 20,000 yen.
How can I catch it if it doesn't sink?
It's cool if you can catch it.
It's cool.
This is pretty hard.
This is...
It's cut.
Which one did you cut?
Hama chan lure.
I caught it.
Did you catch it?
The lures are...
It's amazing.
It's floating.
It's cool.
We're friends.
Did you go down there?
It's over.
I'm glad.
Hurry up.
It's enough to replace it.
I don't like it so much.
Everyone, there's only one hour left.
Are you ready?
The result of the down-to-end lure is zero.
There's only one hour left.
At that time, it finally hit Matsumoto's rod.
Isn't it ten?
That's right.
All right.
It's yellow.
This is the Hamada-Tokunaga duo.
It hit Tokunaga again.
It's coming.
It's small.
He said it was small.
It's yellow.
It's blue.
That's right.
If you catch it like that...
Don't laugh, Hamada.
I caught it, Matsumoto.
Really?
I caught one.
Only Hamada.
There's no A.
It won't end.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
On the other hand, the Okuda-Konbi duo is silent.
I'll do my best.
Stop it.
When the Yamazaki boat approaches to put the cut in the Itoi-Matsumoto Konbi...
It's coming.
It's big.
It's in the water.
All right.
That's great.
It's big, isn't it?
It's big.
As expected of champion Matsumoto.
He suddenly became the winning candidate.
On the other hand, Hamada still hasn't caught anything.
Is Matsumoto's big?
It's pretty big.
Really?
I caught another one.
The second one?
I won't let you win.
Hamada decided to compete at the same point as Matsumoto to aim for the big one.
You're in the way.
You're a bad guy.
I was aiming for the big one.
You're in the way.
Is it out of place?
Why are you running so hard?
Take this.
What is this?
What should I do if I'm a bad guy?
Hamada was desperate to go fishing even though he had such anxiety in his head.
It's about time for the sun to set and there's not much time left.
Eguchi and Okuda changed their points and Okuda caught something.
This is the biggest one.
It's the biggest one so far.
I got something.
There's a lot.
And Eguchi also caught something.
It's the biggest one today.
I want to catch something.
He's so motivated.
Meanwhile, Matsumoto caught something again.
I wonder what it is.
It's a good one.
Isn't it?
I wonder if it's a good match with the one before.
Hamada hasn't caught anything yet but he's changing his points again.
Oh no.
It's a big one.
There's not much time left.
All the boats are gathering at one point.
It seems to be going well.
This is bad.
What do you think?
He's catching a lot.
Everyone.
This is the last 5 minutes.
There's only 5 minutes left.
Everyone is trying to catch something.
Will Matsumoto catch three in a row?
Or will Hamada catch something?
We still don't know who will win.
Who will be the winner of the 3rd round?
The result is out.
Everyone worked hard for the 3rd round.
Everyone caught something.
Let's start with Eguchi.
How many did he catch?
He caught a lot.
It's a big one.
It's 32.
32.
Tami.
Bring the biggest one.
It's a small one.
It's a big one.
It's a good one.
It's 32.
It's Togura's turn.
It's a big one.
It's 35.
It's 36.
He was satisfied.
It's a big one.
It's 37.
Matsumoto.
Why me?
It's your turn.
It's okay.
Why?
It's my turn.
It's a big one, so I have to catch it at the end.
I see.
I don't want to be disappointed.
It's a good one.
It's a dead one.
I can't catch it.
It's 36.
What's going on?
It's not over yet.
I don't know.
It's a big one.
It's amazing.
Is it a joke?
What's this?
Why is it a macadamia?
It's the worst.
What are you doing?
Some of you have caught it before.
Before?
Really?
Before was before.
So it's 37cm.
Ito is the winner.
I'm happy.
Matsumoto is the winner.
He caught three in a row.
I'm disappointed.
Please win.
I'm happy.
I'm so happy.
And the number one T-shirt.
The second place is Hikobito.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Really?
I don't have a lot of T-shirts, so I'll go with Matsumoto's T-shirt.
Are you trying to improve your image?
Wait a minute.
I have a lot of T-shirts like this.
I'm kind.
It's 36cm.
It's a little tight.
As you can see today's results.
Everyone, thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work.
Everyone, Ito's T-shirt is number one.
This is a gift for the viewers.
Everyone wants it.
I don't think there's anyone.
If you want it, I'll give it to you myself.
This is too much.
This is my dad's joke.
As the first comment today,
I'm going up one step at a time.
I was able to get up from the last place to the fifth place.
I'm happy.
Today.
The fish I let go was big.
It was the first time I had one like that.
Or I took it off.
I'm going to time again every time.
It was my first variety show.
I had fun.
I'd like you to use it again.
If there's another chance, thank you.
Today.
I've been down about five times since morning.
I've been thinking about where and how to fish.
I've been doing it until noon.
I'm really happy to win.
After all, if you work hard, you'll get rewarded.
I'll do my best, too.