Let's do it!
Thank you very much.
If you ask me to do it, I'll do it right away.
That's fine, but there's no All-Star among 18 people.
What do you mean?
All-Star, right?
Well, there were 18 people, so I had 9 people selected, and now I'm going to bet on the draft.
After that, I'll do a baseball game, and the losing team will be punished.
I don't need a par-man number two.
Actually, I don't have one either.
And I want to avoid Otomo.
Are you betting on the par-man number two?
What do you mean by betting?
Do you have a par-man number two in this baseball game?
No, I don't.
Then I don't have one either.
I don't have a par-man number two in this baseball game.
No, you don't.
Well, let's see how the players are doing before the draft.
Number 3, the one selling 90kg, is Sakanishi.
This is Toshiaki Sakanishi.
He's pretty sharp.
Really?
Well, that's what everyone thinks.
Oh, really?
He's not as good as he looks.
Is he a horse?
I see.
He's eating to be able to eat.
Please eat.
This is Producer Suga.
This guy is...
Is he really strong?
No, of course not.
I knew it.
He's from Tokyo.
Oh, he's a little...
He's like Kunaki Kajo.
Wow, he's really something.
His sister is Kimiko Ikegami.
Really?
Yes.
Yes, really.
This is Saito, the chief director.
Oh, Saito looks like he's selling something.
He's doing his best.
What are you saying?
What?
I don't think I need this.
You don't need it?
Well, it can't be helped.
It's a good deal.
10 out of 10.
This guy is pretty good.
I just want it.
It's okay.
I have a feeling.
This guy has been coming to Yoshihiriyano since 3 o'clock.
Oh, really?
Isn't he your friend?
Oh, that's right.
There's no one I want.
Your friend?
My friend.
You hit him with your palm?
You hit him with your palm, didn't you?
That's so lame.
What is this?
You're amazing.
You're so weird.
You're so grotesque after you hit him.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Now, let's have a draft meeting.
Now, let's have Mr. Wakabayashi, the director of Nihon TV, introduce himself.
Mr. Wakabayashi, please.
Thank you, Mr. Wakabayashi.
Please.
Thank you.
Now, I will announce the names of the players.
First, Team Matsumoto.
First place.
Noriyasu Hiromitsu.
22 years old.
Team Zero.
Team Tamada.
First place.
Noriyasu Hiromitsu.
22 years old.
Team Zero.
Now that the names are overlapped, we will have a lottery.
The person who draws the red ball will win.
The person who draws the blue ball will win.
As a result of the lottery, the first place goes to Noriyasu Hiromitsu.
22 years old.
Team Zero.
Team Matsumoto.
Second place.
Kawano Tooru.
46 years old.
Tokyo Agency.
What are you doing with such an old man?
Team Tamada.
Second place.
Nitta Atsuo.
25 years old.
Manager.
Fifth place.
Team Matsumoto.
Sakamoto Hidenao.
32 years old.
Manager.
I'm pretty strong, aren't I?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm not just batting, I'm also good at defense.
Please suffer after death.
I'll fire you.
I'm sorry.
That means there are only two people left.
Yamazaki Chiebunsharo.
Ohtomo Edi.
Pama No.2.
And the writer, Adachi Motoichi.
This is hard.
I don't care.
I'm more worried than when I went to Thailand.
Rock-paper-scissors.
What?
I don't care if there are two Pamas.
What are you talking about?
I don't care.
Matsumoto Hidenao.
32 years old.
Manager.
I'm not just batting, I'm also good at defense.
Please suffer after death.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Good evening.
Today's audience seems to be in good spirits.
In good spirits?
How should I put it?
I feel close to them.
I don't feel like I've met them for the first time.
Next time, we're going to play a new punishment game.
We're going to play a new punishment game.
There are a lot of things that we have to decide on.
What Hamada is going to do...
Why?
We're not playing a game, we're not deciding on the winner.
This time, it's baseball.
We're going to play baseball.
We'll be divided into the Matsumoto and the Hamada teams.
Downs and Towns.
We'll have to put in 9 or 8 staff members.
The team that loses gets punished.
We've decided on that.
We've decided on the members too.
We've decided.
We've decided today.
Yes, yes, yes.
So, the punishment game is going to be with 9 losers.
You've done it one by one, right?
You or I.
Yes, yes, yes.
This time, the whole team is responsible.
What are we going to do with 9 people?
Everyone's talking about a lot of things.
What?
As a plan.
Another scary thing.
First, the plan is that all 9 people lose their eyebrows.
You have to walk around Kabukicho at night like this.
This is pretty scary, isn't it?
The camera is also hidden.
You have to walk around with your head rolled up.
That's a little dangerous, isn't it?
This is the first thing.
The other thing is that all 9 people have to take off their shoulders.
So, their arms go like this.
Then, they go into the cage and become a orangutan.
All 9 people have to pull out their teeth.
One at a time.
Then, they put them into a box and take them off one by one.
Then, they have to put them on.
There are also some in the back teeth.
You have to put them on in the front.
This is a masterpiece.
The rating is 29%.
This guy.
You can't get 29%?
What's so sad about it?
You lost, so you have to pull out your teeth.
Even if you pull them out, you can put them on.
It's someone else's teeth!
You don't know if it's your own teeth or not.
I don't like that!
You don't like other people's teeth?
I don't like this one and that one.
That's the problem.
You have to put them all in the front.
It's someone else's teeth, so that's the problem.
You don't like the fact that you have to pull them out.
Why?
Why do you have to pull out healthy teeth?
Even if they rot.
If you say that, why do you have to put them on?
It's a punishment game.
You're complaining from the bottom of your heart.
You don't have to say that.
You don't have to hurt your body.
What?
What is that?
You have to pull out your nipples.
You can't complain about that.
Why do you have to pull out your nipples when you're playing baseball?
You can't cut your nipples when you're playing baseball.
You can't cut them.
There's nothing you can do about it.
Have you ever had a problem with your nipples?
Is there something wrong with your nipples?
Tell me.
Have you ever helped someone with your nipples?
There's nothing wrong with that.
You don't need that kind of nipples.
I don't need that kind of nipples either.
It's strange if you don't have them.
It's strange.
There's nothing wrong with showing your nipples.
If you have your nipples open and smooth, it's strange.
What do you mean?
You should have them more than you don't have them.
More than I don't have them?
You...
It's strange that you don't have them.
Really?
That's right.
It's a bit embarrassing that you don't have them.
So, cut your nipples.
Why should I cut them?
Listen to me.
It's okay.
Don't cut them.
Listen to me.
Why?
I'll cut them.
I can't throw them away.
Even if you throw them away, don't cut them.
I can't cut them and throw them away.
Don't cut them.
If I don't have them, it's a bit embarrassing.
So, I'll put them here.
If that's the case, it's not strange at all.
It's strange.
It's strange that you don't have them.
You don't have them after you cut them.
I have them.
So, cut your nipples.
Cut your nipples.
I'll cut them.
That's right.
So, what should I do?
I have to do it with nine people.
You'll make them do something, right?
I was thinking about it.
I'll make a drama.
How about this?
A drama with a punishment game?
I'll make a drama.
The nine people who win are the main characters.
I was thinking about it.
I can't make a deadly drama.
It's about 15 minutes long.
The person who wins is the victim.
So, the loser will be killed.
I won't be killed.
What will you do?
I can't punish them in the drama.
What kind of punishment will you give?
Well, there is one person.
There is also a punishment game.
Really?
It's in the drama, so it's okay.
It's in English.
Even if it's a punishment game.
Pararan.
Just say it normally.
You have to say it in Japanese.
Pararan.
That's enough.
Did you just say Pararan?
Don't say Pararan.
I've seen a lot of dramas.
The drama of an amateur is quite interesting.
That's it.
It's a story about giving a punishment in the drama.
I think it's pretty good.
I think the setting is interesting.
But it's about the punishment in the drama.
What kind of punishment will you give?
Can I give you a fire?
I don't like it.
You are a punishment.
You can't give me a little pain.
Then you will be punished, too.
Then I'll give you a light.
I'll give you a light.
I don't think so.
I don't think I wanted to give me a little pain.
But you wanted to do it?
It's fine.
You don't want to do it?
But you want to do something.
You'll give me a fire.
I'll give you a long-lip.
What kind of boy is today?
Hello.
Oh, hello, hello.
You have a strange name.
Mr. Rasaru Ishii.
My name is Magnum Fox.
How old are you?
I'm 35.
I'm 35, a month old.
I see.
But in this program, I'm supposed to be like a leotard.
I'll prepare it for you.
That's what I'm supposed to do.
Oh, I see.
It's decided.
Wait a minute.
I'm surprised.
It's decided.
I'm going crazy right now.
What the hell is he doing?
It's really...
It's my underwear attack.
Did you put it out yourself?
Yes, I asked for it on TV.
Yes, yes, yes.
I asked the entertainer to put out a postcard.
I saw it.
I'm so happy.
It's better than just a postcard.
I'll put out a letter of recommendation.
It's written in the photo.
It's written seriously.
I want to be on TV for a while.
I'm so happy.
Look at this.
What is it?
If you pass, the penalty is a failure.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to be played.
Yes.
At this angle.
I didn't come here because I want to promote my play.
Well, but this is...
This is the bottom of happiness.
That's right.
It's at Hakuhinkan.
Yes.
It starts on February 20th.
The three red lights will be seen for the first time in a long time.
Yes.
Recently, Komiya-kun has been fishing all the time.
Fishing?
Yes.
He's really into it.
Please do your best.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your direction.
I'll remember it.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
I thought a girl would come.
I was surprised.
I expected it.
What's wrong with this?
Is it your own play?
No, I'm doing it on the internet.
Oh, I see.
Thank you very much.
It's my own play.
I really didn't know.
I really didn't hear it.
Today, the girl who brought a letter said she was going to perform.
Oh, really?
I was surprised.
It's true.
It was a strange old man.
I was surprised.
This person's pen name is Shitoko Matsumoto.
Yes.
I'm a fan of Mach-chan.
I'm a high school girl.
Please listen to the story of my friend Emuko's mother.
One day, Emuko was watching the rerun of School Wars.
My mother came and said,
Oh, School Wars.
Is Anderson dead?
If you say that, it's an isopia.
It's an isopia.
By the way, Natsumi Ogawa misunderstood Noriko Ogawa and said,
Hama-chan was a lolicon.
My mother said that.
My mother.
Please say something to my mother.
Oh, really?
It's a big joke.
It's a big joke, but it's true that Hamada is a lolicon.
What?
It's you.
You're a lolicon.
You like white socks.
Hey, hey, hey.
Which one of you believes me?
It's me.
Yahoo!
Oh, yeah.
I'm a lolicon.
Hama-chan is a lolicon.
Thank you.
Hama-chan and Mach-chan, happy New Year.
Well, well.
By the way, this is a long time ago story, but please listen to this story until the end.
It's okay.
By the way, this is a long time ago story, but my friend's sister...
What is this?
It's Okinawa, right?
Hama-chan came to a bar in Okinawa.
And at the karaoke of the bar, a woman who was born in Osaka or a song from the South Pole.
She didn't care about the song she requested.
This is my song.
Suddenly, Hama-chan ran to the karaoke and started singing with two microphones so that no one could sing.
Really?
Even if you're a celebrity, you don't have to sing other people's songs.
Are you so confident in your singing voice?
Well, I'm afraid of Hama-chan, so I don't think ordinary people can say anything.
Please keep up the good work.
By the way, Hama-chan loves Ultra Super Dynamic very much.
Oh, really?
I love it very much.
That's right.
I'll tell you why I read this letter.
In this letter, there is also Machan's Manojima.
I can't forgive this kind of letter.
It's like a conversation that says something about me.
What do you think, Mr. Matsumoto?
This kind of letter is rare, isn't it?
What?
I can't see myself in this letter.
You don't have to say that.
You don't have to make a fuss.
I'm not good at writing letters.
And I'm not good at cutting letters.
I don't know how to use it.
It's a little different, isn't it?
This kind of letter makes me angry.
It's okay.
At least write something at the end.
I will never accept this kind of letter again.
You should write it.
Machan, Hama-chan, Happy New Year.
Mr. Kyoichi appeared on the show.
That's right.
I was surprised.
I was surprised, too.
I was surprised to see him on the show.
I laughed because he was hiding somewhere at 6 o'clock.
I couldn't find him.
I would be grateful if the TV viewers could see him like this.
You want to appear on the show, don't you?
That's right.
Why don't you send me a letter?
When you appear on the show, you should wear a swimsuit.
Women should wear a swimsuit.
That's right.
If you're a man, you should wear a turtleneck.
What about Peter?
I don't think so.
If you give me 50, I'll give you what you like.
I understand.
And I can't think of a punishment game.
It's almost done.
What's in it?
This is written by Takasu and Ichito Omodo.
It's an interesting mini-drama.
I'll give you a punishment game.
On February 1st, a movie called Nihonkai will be released on Showa Teppu.
20 people will get a ticket to watch the movie.
Two people?
That's right.
I can't watch a movie with two people.
But you have to do it one by one.
Yesterday, I saw a movie in Shinjuku.
It's called Hamazama.
Really?
I don't know.
I bought it.
The 20th person can get tickets and the 30th person can get a ticket.
I'll give you your ticket.
I'd like you to show me Peter's best.
The costume is free.
I saw it.
Thank you very much.