After this, I'm not going to play Gaki no Tsukai anymore.
I'm not going to play Gaki no Tsukai for the first time!
100 Yen Crane Battle Royale!
I'm not going to catch a cold today.
Today, I'm going to play a game.
When you go to the game center, you can get 100 or 200 Yen.
You can pull up a stuffed toy and bring it to your place.
I'm going to play that game as a human being.
I'm going to introduce you to a great person.
She's the queen of SM Entertainment, Yukari Jo!
How long have you been doing this?
It's been six years.
Just by looking at her face, you can tell she's an M.
I can tell.
By the way, I'm from downtown. I have a partner, Matsumoto Hitoshi.
Who is he?
He's an M.
He's an M?
Downtown Matsumoto is an M?
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
He's sticking out his shoulder.
Matsumoto is sticking out his shoulder?
I see.
Today, I'm going to play Crane.
Crane!
I'm going to play Crane as a human being.
Please welcome these two!
Hello!
Nice to meet you!
What the hell are you doing?
Please keep playing Crane.
I'm sorry.
What?
Yamazaki and Noriyasu.
Today, they are...
They are going to play Crane.
But!
There are many obstacles waiting for them.
Please clear them while playing Crane.
Okay.
Let's get started!
I'm from Ukarujo.
Who are you?
What?
I'm from Ukarujo. I'm here to play Crane.
Are you going to play Crane?
No, I can't.
Please.
Come on.
Don't make me do my best!
Don't be afraid of me!
Ouch!
I don't know how to play Crane.
I'll do my best.
Hey!
Raise your hand!
Help me!
Hey!
What?
Do your best!
If you don't go to the surface, I can't catch you.
I'm here to play Crane.
Crane.
I'm scared of you.
Hey!
What are you waiting for?
It's Crane Army!
Crane!
I'm being shot!
Crane Army is too many!
I'm also frightened now.
Turn on the sound of the water.
Drop the water.
Don't take the doll.
No.
Watch out.
Don't take the doll.
No.
Yonaguni.
Good job.
Good.
Why?
Watch out.
Don't take the doll.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Good, good, good.
By the way.
You do your best.
What?
You shouldn't take a break.
Why?
It's hard.
I want to take a break today.
You have to get up early today.
You.
You don't say that every week.
I can't get up today.
I can't.
I've been alone for two days.
Why?
I don't want to go home.
What?
I don't mean anything bad.
I'll take you home.
No.
After work,
I went home at night.
It was so cold in the room.
It's supposed to be warm.
It's a bi-home.
It's so hot.
It's so weird.
It's always warm.
I don't want to go home.
But we're always alone.
We're always alone.
No one is there.
It's true.
You'll be 29 tomorrow.
You're alone.
I can't be 29 tomorrow.
I can't.
I'm not going to sleep on this show anymore.
I have a problem.
Then I get a fan letter.
I'll do anything.
You guys.
What do you call it?
Why do you accept it like that?
It'll be tomorrow morning.
You can't throw away chocolate.
It's too terrible.
That's true.
I'm a skater.
I stepped on it.
But, you know...
You know what?
Mota, I'm really happy!
I'm really happy!
I can't help it, but I'm really thankful.
You're thankful?
Mota, what are you going to do?
That thankfulness...
Why?
Why are you thankful?
You have to say it!
If you're thankful, say it!
See?
You're so cute!
What do you mean cute?
You just started!
No!
What do you mean cute?
Your hair is so fluffy!
What do you mean?
You're so cute!
Is it a cat?
You want to hug it, right?
I understand that.
It's hard for a cat,
but you want to hug it.
You're so cute!
That's what you're saying, right?
The gift I got from my fans,
I'm so happy!
I'm so happy that I want to slap it on my tongue!
What's this?
I'm so happy!
If you do it like that,
it's normal to get slapped on the tongue.
That's my best thing.
If you do it like that,
I'll be so happy!
If you express it like that...
If I see your performance...
Shut up!
I'll be so happy.
If I say something bad...
Hey!
You really believe in me, right?
You keep saying that.
There are still people who believe in me.
I'll warn you.
You do this sometimes!
I've never shown
my feminine side on TV.
Really?
Your gestures are all like that.
What's wrong with that?
That's what's wrong with you!
I have a lot of female hormones.
Why?
What's wrong with that?
I don't have any female hormones.
I have no female hormones.
I've had no female hormones for a long time.
I have no female hormones for a long time.
It's hard!
Wait!
I always
do a lot of
high-level jokes.
When I do that,
it's like cold rice.
I've given
wonderful dinner
and meat juice to everyone before.
It's hard!
That was also hard!
I'm sure you're eating a great steak.
My high-level jokes.
At times like this,
I'll make everyone eat
something like cold rice.
That's what you're doing now?
That's my joke.
It's called dinner full course.
You're talking about a piano.
That's what I'm talking about.
No, you're the one who
says whether you have or don't have female hormones.
Yes, I have a lot of female hormones.
I'm a little
H-rated.
You're saying that because you're fat?
No, no, no.
I'm a little H-rated.
What do you mean by H-rated?
I've said it many times.
That's what you do!
Then, as a comedian,
what kind of reaction would you have
if your father touched you?
Stop it!
I don't even know if you're a comedian.
Then, why would your father touch you?
Why would you do that?
You're just singing.
What's wrong with that?
That's right.
I'm waiting for a man in front of my apartment.
I'm waiting for a car, so I know if he's there or not.
Oh, I see.
Oh, I'm on TV right now.
I'm on TV right now.
Oh, really?
Yes.
The sky is so beautiful.
When we used to do it,
the driver would go like this.
It's not like that.
The keyhole is so deep.
The inside is so clean.
I'm a professional.
I don't think so.
If you don't wash your car often,
you'll get mud on your car.
You'll get mud on your car.
A few years ago,
when I was on my way to work,
next to the door,
there was a sign saying,
poop.
Gyo-san,
there was a word,
but it was poop.
I thought it was poop.
No, it wasn't you.
It's hard.
I woke up early today.
Oh, today?
Yes.
You were here at 2 o'clock today.
I was.
You can wake up at 2 o'clock.
Yes, I can.
Were you sleeping?
No, I wasn't.
Why?
What?
I was baking cookies.
Hurry up and read it.
That's not how you read it.
The other day,
I was wearing a new pair of shoes
and went out.
I said,
I'm fat,
but can you two laugh at me?
That's the end.
I can't stand fat people.
I always want to eat something.
Really.
Yesterday,
I was on my way to school.
I was really fat.
I wasn't in the car,
but I was really fat.
I was eating something
that looked like a candy
with pink sugar on it.
I don't know if you're trying
to hide the fact that you're fat.
I was hiding it.
I was like,
Fatty, fatty.
That fat guy is funny.
He hides his sweat.
You see,
fat people breathe with their mouths.
What?
They're supposed to be made
so that they can breathe.
That's why they have holes.
What do you mean,
they breathe with their mouths?
It's time to say it.
You have to open your mouth as much as you can.
What?
It's an emergency.
It's SOS.
I guess
I eat twice as much.
What do you mean?
I forget.
I ate a while ago.
What?
I didn't eat.
I ate a lot,
but when I moved a little,
I was like,
I'm hungry.
I don't eat.
Fat people like juice.
I like it.
I'm always full.
You're still eating.
Yes.
When I sit down,
I drink fruit milk.
Fruit milk.
When you used to do it with Bambi.
I drink only fruit milk.
Yes, yes.
Right?
You have a club mom,
but you don't have a club dad?
You have a club dad,
but you don't have a club mom?
A club dad?
I have a club dad,
but I don't have a club mom.
I see.
You're going to be a club dad.
Why?
I'm not going to be a club dad.
I didn't drink a lot.
I thought I'd drink more.
I don't know if it's because
I don't read well.
It's an emotional union.
You're always doing it.
If you do that,
I don't need a club mom.
See?
If you were reading now,
you'd be like this.
You can do it.
I can do it.
I can still use it.
I don't need a club mom.
I want to hear it.
If you say it like that.
I see.
I don't need a club mom.
You're really good.
I want to hear it.
You're the best.
Shut up!
That's funny.
Let's talk about you.
You're 71 years old.
Recently,
you can tell the difference.
But you still can't tell the difference
between Machan and Hama-chan.
Please tell me which one is which.
What should I do?
What should you do?
This is...
You know,
the fat one and the thin one.
The big one and the small one.
We don't have that many.
If I had to choose,
the spicy one
or the juicy one.
You're really good.
I don't know which one is spicy
and which one is juicy.
I still can't tell the difference
between Machan and Hama-chan.
Machan and Hama-chan.
I can hear it.
Machan is watching a show.
He's doing a drama.
Machan likes the kingdom of the wild.
He doesn't like the kingdom of the wild.
He always watches it with Harada.
They don't really get along.
You know,
in the kingdom of the wild,
there's a lion chasing a deer.
He's really excited.
He's like,
Run! Run! Run!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Machan is like that.
When he sees a lion or a deer,
he's like,
Lion!
But I don't know
which one is downtown,
Machan or Hama-chan.
What?
I'm sorry.
I didn't get it.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What?
What did you want to say?
You watch the kingdom of the wild,
don't you?
I do.
But you don't really watch
the programs we're on.
So, the old ladies
who watch the kingdom of the wild
clearly know which one is the lion or the deer.
But Machan and Hama-chan
don't really know.
So,
you're walking down the street,
and the deer is walking this way.
So,
it's the deer!
I can't say it's Hama-chan.
I'm pointing at the deer.
That's the old lady.
Come here, Mii-kun!
Who's Mii-kun?
He's my grandson.
You should ask him that.
I can't do anything.
So,
Mii-kun's older sister is here.
I don't know if she's here.
This is my first time seeing Mii-kun.
I don't know about Yocchan.
This is my older sister.
Yocchan's older sister.
Yocchan, come here!
The young Yocchan
is like,
Hama-chan!
But you're Hama-chan!
But this is a deer!
The old lady is here.
The old lady is a deer.
I see.
There's a difference between what you see and what you don't.
It's a long story.
If you could become gods
what kind of things would you make?
You'd combine something with something.
Combine?
A lion and an elephant.
A lion and an elephant?
You'd combine a lion and an elephant
and make a lion and an elephant.
This is an elephant.
The whole thing.
The nose would stretch out
and the hair would go like this.
That's all there is to a lion.
I don't get it.
Well...
You don't get it?
I'm sure there are many animals
that haven't been discovered yet.
Are you talking about soil?
I'm sure there are.
There was something else.
I wonder if there really is.
A hippo?
There is a hippo.
There is a hippo?
That's a long story.
I've never seen a hippo.
That's all.
I get it.
I'm serious.
If you go somewhere
and see a hippo
you'll know.
You'll say,
I saw it in the bathroom.
I really saw it.
I didn't see it.
I was seen.
You were seen
in the bathroom.
I see.
You saw it.
You didn't see it at first.
You saw it
like this.
It was deep
and wide.
It was like this.
It dug a hole
in the side.
There is a hole
There is another hole
in the side.
Like a mole?
Yes.
I dug a hole
and it came out.
From the hole?
From the hole.
I dug a hole
and it came out.
Why?
What is this?
Thank you for watching.