It's the same as usual, the dressing room in downtown.
What's that weird atmosphere?
What?
It's not weird at all.
Is that so?
It's normal.
It's a good atmosphere as usual.
It's calm.
It's better to go around.
That's right.
I have a talk with Mr. Omao.
Where's Yamazaki?
I haven't seen him yet.
I haven't seen him either.
I haven't seen Yamazaki either.
That's right.
Excuse me.
Mr. Yamazaki is locked up in the bathroom.
He can't come out.
What do you mean?
Is he locked up?
I think he's locked up by himself.
He can't come out.
It's his will, isn't it?
I think so.
I can't come out at all.
Excuse me.
I want you to come out.
Yes, please.
Excuse me.
Please come out with me.
Why do you keep saying that?
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
It can't be helped.
Yamazaki goes to the bathroom.
Yamazaki.
Mr. Omao.
Where are you?
What are you doing?
Do you know why I'm in this place?
He can't say it.
What are you doing?
There's a lot of pain.
It's a real show.
It's better to come out.
Please come out.
Are you coming out?
No, I'm going home.
Wait a minute.
There's a lot of pain.
He can't say it.
These days.
I don't want to be in the opening.
I see.
What do you mean?
It's natural.
It's not natural.
I've been doing it since the second time.
That's all.
I've been on TV since I was 24.
This TV?
I've been doing my best in the first round.
Do you know how hard it is to do your best in the first round?
You know that best.
Don't say that.
I don't say that.
Wait a minute.
Do you love me?
Even if you say you love me.
I have nothing to say to you.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
Uncle.
No.
I'm Tadaka.
I like you.
The show is about to start.
I'm in trouble.
Please come out.
What kind of welcome is this?
I'm in trouble.
Please come out.
I'm sorry, Tadaka.
You're always a support to my heart.
Mr. Yamaguchi.
I'm a fool.
I'm Endo.
Endo is a fool.
I hate Endo the most.
It's a shame that you're out.
He stepped on to the Marshal.
Mr. Yamaguchi.
Please come out.
Take your time and get out of here.
It's hard to get out of here.
You have your own house ready, right?
Of course.
I won't be embarrassed if you come out.
I know that.
I won't complain then.
I can't do it. If it's funny, I'll do it.
Of course I'll do it.
Of course.
Let's do it.
Okay.
What are you doing?
You're a coward.
I'm a coward.
Do you understand?
Do your best.
You've been talking to me like that.
Thank you for your support.
Thank you very much.
I don't think the winner is happy with this.
I think so, too.
I pulled it.
I really pulled it.
I can't say it's not funny.
I understand.
I don't understand.
What are you doing?
You think I'm going to slip, right?
Who moved?
I'm sorry.
You think I'm going to slip, right?
You're a kid.
Let's go.
I'm here to call you.
Are you filming me?
You're still doing it?
I was pretty confident.
I didn't think they'd do it.
I didn't think it'd take that long.
I wonder if Tanaka will be able to do it.
Don't worry about it.
Wait a minute.
If Tanaka is able to do it...
Are you going to hit your shoulder?
Let's go.
What is it?
Isn't this amazing?
Really?
It's really, really funny.
I don't think you should be so proud of yourself.
No, I shouldn't be.
What?
What is that?
Don't you think it's weird?
I don't think it's weird.
That's right.
It's amazing.
Are you really confident?
I'm really confident.
Okay, let's go.
Let's stop.
I can't show such an interesting thing on TV.
It's a loss for us, too.
This result is the second half of the program.
There are a lot of young people right now.
Yes, yes.
I'm going to get rid of them all at once.
I found something that I could get rid of at once.
Are you really confident?
I'm really confident.
Yamasaki is like that, and so is Aikata.
You're the only one who's like that, right?
That's right.
I feel like I'm tightening myself more and more.
Then I'll do it like that.
Really?
That's amazing.
Then let's see.
Let's see.
Then let's go.
I went to a different place.
I think I drew the back of the back of the back of the back of the back of the back of the back.
I think it's like this.
That's right.
Oh, I'll do it again.
I'll shoot it.
Well, I'll apologize.
I'm sorry.
We'll do our best from the beginning.
We were a little too sweet.
I've been raised to be a great guy.
Let's just do it together.
Yeah.
Go back to the beginning.
But.
Tanaka is sweating a lot right now.