Question! What is the first place of the Cup RR?
Mecha-tsu-tsu Genki!
Tonight is the remote Ogiri corner!
In the last week's show, the nine members were aiming to clear the course.
What is the fourth member?
Yosuki!
Sakai Masaaki!
The first place is...
Kai!
He successfully cleared the stage!
Tanaka Hiko!
What is the fourth place's final score?
It's a piece of crap.
What?
Stop it!
What's with this regular season?
The regular members are still in the lead.
They have cleared the stage for 9 consecutive years!
Will they be able to achieve their goal tonight?
The rules have been revised
Each person will announce the answer to the question
Matsumoto will decide if it's interesting or not
With 9 people clearing the game, everyone will be able to get 10,000 yen each
Please make it easy.
It's easy.
It's easy to cut.
It was really easy.
Please make it easier.
Please lower it.
What is this?
Let's go to the next topic.
What is the special skill used by American ninja?
Please write it down.
It's difficult.
I think so too.
It's difficult among the topics so far.
I thought that was better than I expected.
I think I underestimated the performance of this.
I have to go to a higher level.
But Matsumoto-san, after this topic came out, everyone's movements stopped.
That's because the pieces that have really increased the rotation rate seem to have stopped.
Oh, that's the phenomenon.
It's completely stopped.
I want the top to be in the back of the head.
What is the special move used by the American Ninja?
German suplex shuriken.
It's good as a top.
Let's go to the prize.
The ultimate skill used by American Ninja is?
Ninja Art, Pistol
That's good
You can do it
Ok, Okada
The ultimate skill used by American Ninja is?
Chihuahua's Neck Punch
He got it
Amazing
Otake, go!
Yes!
The special move used by the American Ninja is...
Go!
Cherry Pie Attack!
Yoshio, go! Yoshio, go!
The special move used by the American Ninja is...
Missile!
It's the same move! It's the same move!
Alright, Tsunai, go! Tsunai, go!
The special move used by the American Ninja is...
Machi-Bi-Su!
Push it, push it!
Go, go, go!
Machi-Bi-Su!
What the hell is this?
It was close!
The order might be wrong.
If we ask the regular people, maybe...
Do you want to ask?
Let's do it!
What is the special skill of the American Ninja?
Drop kick!
Yama-chan, what is the special move of the American Ninja?
American Popcorn!
What? Really?
Who said the special move of the American Ninja?
leaveação Massachusetts
Oh!
Everyone got it!
wait!
You got it wrong!
Wait, Let me answer!
It was oboroi!
The real answer is wanting to see!
Let you watch rebound!
We must be funny!
We are funny.
He is American.
Let us watch it!
Don't just listen to him!
It's not funny.
Ma-kii bisa posit?
Sorry.
Ma-kii ambos.
Ma-kii discard?
This is not funny!
What are you doing?
Can you do it with 10 people?
Let's work together
Let's do our best
What are you doing?
I will rest Tanaka and Yamazaki
Wait a minute
You want to rest?
I don't want to rest in the remote
Even Tanaka is remote
You don't want to rest
Sorry, I don't have a night off.
Sorry, but I'll go with sweet and sour.
Okay!
Let's do it all!
Sweet and sour is a problem.
Question!
What is the name of the strawberry sweeter than the sweet king?
Please answer!
Sweet from the first question.
This is good.
Sweet and sour.
Even elementary school students are happy to think about it.
I can do it in kindergarten.
You can do it in kindergarten?
I'm confident that I can continue.
But I think it's dangerous if I don't clean up my regular.
It's okay.
It's just strict.
It's a regular.
Look at that.
Seriously, it's stopped.
It's frozen.
I'm surprised.
Wow, I'm surprised.
Who wants to go first?
I'll go first.
I'll go.
Shouji, what is the best sweet strawberry flavor?
Sweet soy sauce.
Wrong!
It's not sweet.
Next question.
It's sweet.
It's hard.
Isn't it really tough?
Next topic...
Wait, wait, wait
Let's go with this
Okay, here's the topic
What do Indians do when they catch a cold?
Please write your answers
The difference in culture
I see
How to make it funny
I see, I see
How to make it taste good
Who should go next?
They can decide
I see
I'll go first
Really?
It's a very bad one, so I'll give you a score.
You can't say it's a bad one.
Okada, let's start.
What do you do when an Indian gets a cold?
I press the red button on his forehead.
Good!
That's how it is.
Okada, who did you choose?
Someone who looks like he can do it.
Then, please choose Shoji.
Shoji.
Let's go. What do you do when an Indian gets a cold?
Go into a curry room.
Yes!
This moment is exciting.
Choose one, Shonji.
A snot.
Damn it.
Let's go. What do you do when an Indian gets a cold?
I'll put a turban around your throat.
Correct!
It's coming!
Who will you choose?
Let's go!
Then, please choose Sakoshi!
Sakoshi!
Let's go with Sakoshi!
What do Indians do when they catch a cold?
They put curry in the urinal and pour it in.
I'm sure of it.
What are you saying?
Okay!
I did it!
This is a good connection.
Okay.
Then, Yoshio-chan.
Let's go with Yoshio-chan.
What do Indians do when they catch a cold?
They drink a glass of Gamla Masala.
It's coming!
That was close.
It's coming! It's coming!
I did it!
Who is Yoshio?
Otake
What do Indians do when they catch a cold?
Put a naan on your forehead
End
Otake
You got a naan
It's fine, there's still 3 people left
Let's do it! What do you do when an Indian gets sick?
Yes, I dig up the soil
That's great!
Which one will you choose?
Please choose Hoze!
O Sitcom
When IndianNotes feelcom Customizing
What is O quit with mask
?
You can..You can..You can
Truly you can
Relied
Ooh..This good
You canなた δια c히
Sero
Definitely you can
This is interesting!
If he succeeds, he will get the prize money!
Finally, Tanaka is winning!
Let's continue, Tanaka Naoki!
What do Indians do when they catch a cold?
The cleanliness of the river of Ganjitsuga
How is it?
The garbage of the river of Ganjitsuga
I called the neighbors
How many people?
I'm really waiting
How many?
It's really infinite. The number of people is infinite.
The prize money is already...
It's tough.
Sorry.
I didn't want to wait.
It's the number of people, right?
But the current mission was good.
We can still go. Let's go.
We can go.
It was good.
This is it.
Let's go.
What is thank you in Gorillago?
What?
Thank you for your hard work
Please go home
This is a very good question
Actually, this is the best question
Ah, is that so?
I think it's okay to break the Pooh button now
Thank you
Chance, chance
I think you can go with just a ping pong
Pooh button
But G.S.
Please contact the office
Please turn off the Pooh button
Thank you very much
Is there anyone who thinks it's better for me to say it?
Then I'll go
What is arigato in Gorillago?
Bon Bokura
This is a reggae song
It's a song by a hip hopper
It's a hip hop song
It's like a greeting
Gyaaa!
Wait, wait, wait!
That's harsh!
That's harsh, isn't it?
What do you think, Mr. Hamada?
Not at all.
Not at all, right?
You can't do this.
Give me another chance.
Okay, then.
I can't ask you the same question again, so I'll stop with the gorilla.
Okay, I'll change the question.
He's thinking of the topic right there.
Then I'll go with the chicken.
What is Arigato in Niwatori?
Isn't it easier?
I see
Niwatori's Ohayou is Kokekokko
You just have to change it to Arigato
Who wants to go first?
Shall I go?
I'll go
What kind of heart do you have?
I'm sticky
Let's go
What is the thanks to in the name of a chicken?
Ehh!
Correct!
Yoshio-san! Yoshio-san!
Let's go! What is the thanks to in the name of a chicken?
Tosa-kato
Tosaka-to
Correct!
You don't know the answer, right?
It's Tosaka-to, right?
Let's go, Yoshio! Who will you choose?
Zakoshio
Let's go with Zakoshio
A stable Zakoshio
What is Arigato in Niwatori-go?
I'm sure you can do it
Weeeeee!
So, who will you choose?
Eh, Tsuda-kun
What is the answer to the word, Thank you in Iwatori?
Ko ke ke
That's good! That's good!
Everyone is a bit scared in this situation
Shota!
Okay!
Shouji, what is the word that you say thank you in a chicken language?
You're really good
That's good, Shouji!
You're really good at that
Who is it?
Then...
Otake!
Let's go with Otake!
Let's go!
What is the word for thank you in Miyatori dialect?
Oh!
Chochu-nee!
You can do it!
What is this?
You're being kind!
I can do this, right?
You can do it!
The remaining 3 people are regular people.
Who will you choose, Saotake?
Endo-san!
Let's go!
What is the meaning of thank you in Miyatori dialect?
ORIGOTTO!
I can't do it!
ORIGOTTO! ORIGOTTO!
Will you show your kindness?
Please shout it again!
ORIGOTTO!
Eh?
Please! Please!
Please!
How is it?
Good!
It's good!
It's dangerous!
Where is dangerous?
Who will Shouzo point at?
Then...
Hose!
Let's go, Yama-chan!
What is the meaning of Arigato in Miyatori dialect?
Please
Arigato
He spoke
He did it
Good
That was good, wasn't it?
It was good
Good
Next, if he succeeds, he will be the director of the prize
Attacker...
Let's press it!
Attackers from far away...
That's Yokoz!
Thank you! What's that?
Attackers from far away...
Three white clouds...
Attackers...
I can see it!
He's back!
He came yesterday, but he's back today?
Yay!
The gold medal!
That was close!
We finally got it!
I think we all got it.
Right?
I didn't think of Endo like that.
I didn't think of you like that.
Next question.
What is the 13th picture?
Please write it down.
I think it's very difficult.
But it's difficult to guess.
Everyone, this is the last question for the time being.
The last one?
Shouzo, do you know the 12 poems?
I'm asking if you know them.
That's true.
Shouzo, please say the 12 poems.
Ne, Ushi, Tora, U, Tatsu, Mi, Bi, Bi.
Bi?
What's Bi?
Alphabet?
It's funny that you answered that.
It's a new one.
But this time, the goal is to get a BZ chance.
It's the last one.
Let's go.
Okada, are you ready?
I'm already stuck.
What is the 13th picture?
What is it?
One more time!
Wait a minute
Oh, I think I know
You know it, right?
I think I know
Who will you point at?
Please point at Suwa-san
Suwa
What is the 13th picture?
Benz
Good, good, good
I like it
Suwa-san
Suwa, who will you point at?
No, he's not trapped by animals.
I see.
Kojima-kun!
Uwa!
He said, Uwa!
What is the 13th picture?
Okapi.
There are many kinds of animals.
Otake.
Otake!
What is the 13th picture?
Riki Choshu.
It's good, the Pokemon is not wearing at all
It's coming in pieces, it's good
Shoji-san
Let's go
What is the 13th picture?
The Chief
It's good
It's good, it's not wearing at all
Then, Zagoshi-san
Zagoshi, what is the 13th picture?
Mic exercise
That's good
It's about time. Zagoshi, who will you show?
Mr. Hosei
Ok, I understand
What is the 13th picture?
What is it?
An employee?
That's good
He's very hardworking
But he's working hard
I see
He's working hard
But he's not working
Okay, okay
Good
You've won the prize
You'll take 20,000 yen
Let's take it home.
Endo-san!
Endo-kun, what is the third picture?
Yes!
It's here!
G.T.!
If you succeed, you will get the prize.
Endo-kun, what is the third picture?
Yes!
Shikoku.
Shikoku. Three cities other than Tokushima.
Kagawa, Ehime, Kochi.
I'm starting to understand.
Shikoku. Three cities other than Tokushima.
Endo, that's not true.
You're not going to tell me the truth?
No, Endo.
When you do this, you should not be so particular about the regular.
You should not be so particular about it.
House Dance is on the air!
The past broadcast is broadcast exclusively on Hulu.
Kyuryu Kensaku!