The ultimate entertainment, Hollywood!
A dream stage that everyone admires.
The super famous Hollywood directors came to the set to audition for the leading role.
The last time, Endo was deceived.
This time, the target is the two-shot Kofori, Chihara brothers Seiji, and the three 130R Hong Kong martial arts comedians.
What will be the outcome of the prank?
Excuse me.
Hello.
Thank you for coming today.
Thank you.
Actually, today, I think you've already heard it, but the super famous Hollywood director is coming to find the leading role in the next film.
I want you to take the audition today, so it's up to you to come today.
Thank you.
It's about time, so I'll take you to the audition venue.
Thank you for waiting.
We will now begin the audition.
First, I would like to introduce the director and cast of the film.
Please.
Now, I will announce the title of the film that will be auditioned today.
The title is here.
The Bodyguard.
This film is a long-running film with a production cost of 250 billion yen.
Today is the audition to choose the leading role, the bodyguard.
I asked Yoshimoto Kogyo, the largest entertainment agency in Japan, and the three most manly people came.
Now, I will introduce the cast of the film, The Bodyguard.
First, the director of the film, James Creamy Caramel.
Hello.
Next, the world-renowned singer, with her amazing seven-octave voice, has sold more than 20 million CDs.
In this film, she will show off her ultimate nice body.
The heroine, Miss Whitney Buzdon.
Hi.
Next, the genius child actor, E.I. with a big break in Home Alone.
The evil boss, the genius IT boy, Fucha Osmond.
Next, the silent battlefield with the performance of Ibushi Gin.
There are many masterpieces such as Death on the Hill.
At the Hollywood Film Festival, he has won the Best Actress Award for 12 consecutive years.
The heroine, Mr. Bob with the role of the sushi shop owner, Mr. Itacho.
Welcome.
Next, the mysterious cat woman, Thomas MacLegger.
It seems that the plane was delayed by about two minutes, so I will introduce it as soon as it arrives.
Now, Mr. James, please give us the audition.
OK.
First of all, the basics of acting.
The greatest weapon of a man.
I would like you to sneeze at Hanako Yori.
Please stand by.
Sorry.
You are welcome, sorry.
Now, if you are ready.
First of all, from the first person.
The director will give the cue, so please.
OK.
OK, OK.
Next.
Next person, please.
OK, next.
OK, OK.
Brother?
Are you brothers?
No, no.
I thought you were brothers because you were very similar.
No, not at all.
Yes.
Well, everyone, I really look forward to seeing you as a man with a hard coat.
Now, I would like to move on to the next acting task.
Bodyguard is.
You can't keep your eyes off the client all the time.
And you have to eat quickly.
So, please eat the xiaolongbao you are about to serve quickly.
Stand by, please.
Wow.
Yes.
One by one.
First person, please.
Anyway, speed up.
Come on.
Please eat faster, please eat faster.
Then it's no use at all.
It's too late.
Please eat faster.
It's ridiculous.
If you are going to be late, please leave.
Thank you for waiting.
Mr. Thomas MacLagher, who played the role of Catwoman, who was late here, has arrived.
Please.
Hello.
Do you like tempura?
It's a big one.
Do you eat natto?
Yes.
Thank you.
Then I would like you to show a little more acting.
The enemy of bodyguards is not limited to humans only.
Sometimes they are attacked by wild animals.
So now I'm going to give you the pants.
Think of it as a poisonous snake.
The snake is about to be swallowed by the snake.
Please act it out.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Cut.
Wonderful.
It was a very Claude-like performance.
Excellent.
Next, I would like to see your sense of rhythm and dance.
Please show a sexy dance to the enemy of the refrigerator.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Cut.
Please dance more sexy.
More sexy.
Please show your sense of rhythm.
Cut.
That's enough.
OK.
Fighting.
It was wonderful.
Well done.
It was very wonderful.
I was impressed.
Brother?
No.
Twins?
Are you twins?
No.
Thank you.
Next, the story is about bodyguards and heroines falling in love.
I would like you to kiss the three of them.
The first one, please kiss your husband.
Action.
Cut.
It was wonderful.
It was the story about falling in love.
The second one, please kiss your boyfriend.
Stand by, please.
Action.
OK.
Cut.
That's enough.
Beautiful.
It was wonderful.
Excellent.
It was very wonderful.
The last one, please kiss your boyfriend.
Action.
Cut.
That's enough.
Very nice.
It was wonderful.
It was the love scene.
There may not be anyone who suits the love scene as much as you do.
That's what he said.
It was wonderful.
OK.
Next, please show us the action scene.
I will talk about you.
Please record it.
The genius IT boy will understand everything by recording.
Please take a break.
OK.
Cut.
That's enough.
Thank you very much.
Next, please show us the action scene.
Action.
OK.
That's enough.
At this point, the three judges are lined up.
They are lined up perfectly.
85 points.
You did it.
It was wonderful.
OK.
Then.
The last audition.
OK.
I would like to have the last audition.
There is a scene where the bodyguard is attacked in the climax scene.
Yes.
I would like you to play that scene.
Then, please change your clothes.
Yes.
Please get ready.
OK.
Then, the main character is the sushi restaurant owner.
In fact, he is a hitman who is after the heroine.
Mr. Bob, please shoot the pistol.
Yes.
Please stand by.
Excellent.
Wonderful.
Really wonderful.
Thank you very much.
OK.
It was a very wonderful audition.
Yes.
Then, I would like you to enter the screening.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for waiting.
I will announce the results of the audition.
Mr. James, thank you.
OK.
I will announce it.
The bodyguard audition.
The bodyguard is...
Mr. Kato.
Yes.
Let me explain.
He was the man I had been interested in since I entered this room.
Yes.
He said that his sweet mask was perfect for the image of the movie.
But he didn't do anything.
But I want to see his Matsuken Samba.
Yes.
He is doing Matsuken Samba right now.
Matsuken Samba.
Mr. Kato's Matsuken Samba.
I would like to watch it.
Yes.
Things You Don't Ever Want to Do
I drove all the way to Shijuku.
It wasn't such a big intersection, but I wanted to turn right, but if it was a small intersection, Yajirushi wouldn't come out, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
It would come out like this, right?
So that means there's no need to ignore the traffic lights.
That's right! You can't go there! You can't go there for the rest of your life!
But if you're in the middle of the intersection, you can go to Sugiyama-san.
I was thinking, I cannot go there since so many cars are going there, so I can't do that.
There were about 5 cars behind me.
And then it went like this.
And I said, the car in front, stop.
And then it stopped.
It's not like there are traffic lights or something like that here.
But you can clearly see that it's different, right?
Well, it's different, but here it's like Kansai's nori.
What kind of nori is that?
Even in Kansai, it's red.
What about the traffic lights?
I thought it was a bit strange.
I usually tell them to stop, so they stop.
Then a police officer comes and says,
No, if you go like that, you'll become a traffic light.
I see.
Huh?
This one has a lot of hope.
It's a traffic light!
I told you it's a traffic light.
I didn't say that!
You're becoming a traffic light.
Is this a movie?
It's like a movie that just came out.
Huh?
Just be careful.
That's right.
I didn't let him touch my face.
Oh, I'm going to get a heart attack.
Well, that's that.
That's what the police officer said.
It's a bit confusing these days.
Can you let me check your car?
That's what happened.
But wait a minute.
You probably don't know me.
If you're a talent, you don't usually look at cars like that.
But this is it.
So that's how it ends.
That's what I think.
I'm not saying I don't like it here.
It's possible that you'll look at the car and be careful.
There's nothing to worry about being investigated.
I opened the trunk.
I was waiting.
There was another great man.
He came up to me and said,
Machan!
What are you doing, Machan?
That's no good.
I opened the trunk.
Hey, hey.
That's enough.
Didn't you notice?
I was waiting.
That's enough.
You don't have to look at it.
I opened the trunk.
Machan, I'm sorry.
Let me just cut the tip.
No way!
I'd love to see Machan's eyes.
Hey, hey.
I've been waiting for you.
That's enough.
You don't have to look at the car and be careful.
I opened the trunk.
I was waiting.
That's enough.
I'd love to see Machan's eyes.
Hey, hey.
The third DVD is about to be released.
The third DVD, which has been released for four months in a row,
is a one-night trip to a hot spring resort that you must not laugh at.
The Matsumoto team's night of terror will be revived.