What the hell is this?
It's the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Arahen!
It's a shocking special!
Tsukitsuki! This is the world's magic!
Today, we have a special guest from China.
Let's introduce him right away.
Sensei, please!
Nice to meet you.
Yes, I'm fine.
You're fine?
Your nose is dripping.
Yes, the studio was hot.
After eating hot food, my nose comes out.
I think that's how it is.
I see.
I've never seen your magic before.
Oh, really?
I want to see it.
The one on the grass wall.
What?
Is it called the grass wall?
It's called the grass wall Akira.
From China?
Yes.
Aren't you alone today?
I brought my student today.
What is this?
It has something to do with magic, doesn't it?
What do you call it?
It's a part of your clothes.
A part?
Yes, a part.
Then, let's get started.
For example, like this.
Yes.
Wonderful!
Are you angry?
No.
Wonderful!
What?
No, are you angry?
Next.
Next, this girl.
Yes.
What do you call it?
She's doing a human pump.
Yes.
That's what she's doing.
What do you call this person?
What do you call her?
It's Fujiyama.
Fujiyama is a goldfish.
What?
I'll challenge him.
Is this a good idea?
No, no.
It's Fujiyama.
It's okay, it's okay.
You're taking off your clothes, aren't you?
Yes.
You look like a goldfish.
Let's see the inside of your mouth.
Look.
It's not there, is it?
It's not there.
Ah!
Oh!
Right?
Okay, next.
Okay, next is me.
What?
It's me again.
Oh!
Stop looking at me.
Next.
Yes.
My favorite disciple.
This person?
Hirose.
This person is Hirose.
Yes.
I'll put Hirose inside.
Oh, I see.
Next.
It's a little difficult.
Yes.
You're going to cover it up, right?
What are you doing?
It's okay.
I'll raise it a little.
Ah!
It hurts.
It went in.
Now.
This is the main thing.
Yes.
I'll go.
Oh!
So it doesn't hurt at all!
Okay.
Wait!
Wait a minute!
What's wrong with you!
It hurts so much!
No, no, no.
It hurts!
You're saying it hurts!
No, no, no.
It doesn't hurt at all.
I just feel like it hurts.
Hirose says it doesn't hurt.
That's great!
Now let's put it back.
Yes.
It's okay.
Anybody can do that.
Really?
Didn't know I could do it inside.
Even though you have to be at least someone like me.
Really?
If so, will you join?
Well, I don't think I can do it myself.
What do you mean?
Please
It's fine, I'm the host
No, no, it's fine
Eh?
It's fine
No, no, seriously
No, it's not fine at all
I don't understand anything
No, no, it's fine
No
No, what are you talking about?
No, no, no
Let's go
Eh?
What are you going to do?
See, I got it
I finally got the hang of it
What are you doing?
It's fine, right?
I'm going
What are you going to do?
No, no, I'm going to move it
Are you okay?
Yes
Go
Put your hand in
Eh?
The funny thing is that you can go a little more
Yes, yes, yes, yes
It hurts
Yes
The funny thing is that you can go a little more
Ladies and gentlemen
Thank you
Now
Let's move on to the next one
It's already over
I don't like this hall
It's like a bomb explosion
I told you
What kind of hall is this?
Kanda Pance Hall
Kanda Pance
What are you doing?
What is Kanda Pance?
What does it mean?
I don't understand
How do you decide the name?
I don't know
I understand
If you think of something dirty in an apartment, it's like a play hub
There's something like a Maison
It's attached
It's hard
Even though it's a wooden building
Yes, yes, yes
What is it?
Grand Topia or something like that
I don't know
Well
It was in the opening of this program
The dirty part of Yamasaki
What is that?
Put four sheets of wood together
Yes, yes, yes
That's it
Yes, yes
What is that?
When you open the door, the car is running
Yes, yes, yes
It will be completed in half a day
What is it?
It's attached
Soreng
It's completely different
It's not like that
Soreng
It's strange
How to name it
It's because of the title of the program
It's a lot of trouble
Yes, yes, yes
What should I do for the next new program?
I have to think of a lot of titles
Let's make a good country, Downtown
What is that?
Everyone will say
Soreng
Nakamatsu is a fool
Yes, yes, yes
Yes
The boy's oath
Someone decided this on their own, right?
It's like we said it well
In the story
I said it as it is
Someone must have thought of a way
The boy's oath
I don't really like the title of Osaka-ben
Really?
The intonation is
I say the boy's oath
Did you see the boy's oath yesterday?
That's what they say
That's why it's better to be different
What do you think of Osaka-ben?
Is that so?
We used to have a tour
We had a tour
Really
You guys are crazy
Ah
I laughed
I'm really good at singing
It's true
We appear as a silhouette
In the intonation
Yes, yes
We break it and come out
Ah, I can't do it
I don't believe it
It's true
I don't know
You know it, right?
You went there, right?
Yes, yes
At that time, the tour
Downtown 78
The title of the tour
It was a big hit
Yes, yes
The subtitle was
I won't apologize
It fell down
Boo
Yes
From now on
Downtown tour 89
I won't apologize
It's cool
So we need to think about the title
I won't say that I'm going home
But it's shocking
It's shocking
How is it?
Recently
Well
I'm tired
What?
Oh
Confirmed value
But it's like that
From next year
Even if you work harder
It's the same
Why?
I'll take all the tax
Oh
Oh yes
Recently
There is a common person
Common people
Comedians
They think it's cheap
Is this a good or bad story?
Oh yes
They think it's cheap
Really
So next year
Maybe
I don't think I can earn a million
Oh
Yes
See, I'm tired
That means you have more than a million
I have
Right?
Oh
So if you think about it
Comedians are looking down on you
It's cheap
Then
I wonder if I can do a kick-off
Well, that's right
I don't think I can do this
I don't think I can earn 300 million
If you can earn that much
I'll give you more
If I can earn 300 million
What?
I'll do it with a tank top
I don't know what it is
What?
I don't know
No
Why do you earn so much money with a tank top?
So
Sweating
Oh
I sweat that much
I put a towel on my shoulder
I'll do it while I'm sweating
I'll do that much
Yes
That's it
You'll understand if you do that
It doesn't cost much
Yes
That's right
It doesn't cost more than that
People think it's really cheap
Oh
Yes
I'm the top baseball player
But there are comedians who have more money than I do
Yes
There are
Really
That's right
You guys look down on comedians
You guys think about it
What's that?
A pig's wakataka or something
I've seen that before
What's that?
It's a pig
I can throw it
What?
What's so bad?
I'm not like my brother
Wakataka Fever
What's that?
Come on
I don't know
Right?
Well
My team's Yamazaki says
Wakataka is expensive
You can do whatever you want
There's no woman who won't do it
There is
If you ask him
He says he can do 100 out of 100
He can do it
Yes
There are people who like fat people
And people who don't like me
He's a guy who's married to a girl
He's crazy
But the worst thing I've seen in my wife's team is
F***
This is
The Gorilla Man
That's really
Hey
Seriously
I was surprised
The wide show
I was surprised when I saw the Gorilla Man
I was surprised
You're laughing
It's my wedding ring
The Gorilla Man
He's sweating
It's dirty
It's terrible
Who's the Gorilla Man?
Hey
It's terrible
TV is for celebrities
Well
You can't say bad things
I can't
He's always like that
He's a skater
F***
It's terrible
It's too red here
He's desperate
Well
The accelerator
Yes
The triple accelerator
The triple
What?
He gave up the triple accelerator
He gave up
Because he's bad
If he wants to fail, he can
Yes
He's desperate
He's like this
He's not burning
He's desperate
I don't know what he's thinking
He's doing something with a long mouth and an umbrella
He's doing something
It's red here
Who's the bad guy?
The other day, there was a beautiful girl
She was so ugly
She was like, you can't say beautiful things
She was doing something like this
And
Next to the screen, there was a beautiful girl
Yes
But
I still can't talk to Gorilla Man
You can't
Gorilla Man is a gorilla
He was doing badminton
What did he look like?
Next
This is sudden, but please listen
After watching this program
I think it was when I was sleeping
I was talking in my sleep
And in a loud voice
What?
I was saying
When I heard this from my sleep
It was about me
But I laughed
Do you talk in your sleep?
No, I don't
But I talk in my sleep
He talks in his sleep
He really talks in his sleep
I don't know what he's talking about
He talks in his sleep
What?
I don't talk in my sleep
But I've heard it before
When I was sleeping with you
Really?
Really
I used to talk in my sleep a lot
I don't know now
I don't go to a love hotel with you as much as I used to
I don't know
But you should get rid of badminton
I heard that I couldn't sleep until the morning
You couldn't sleep until the morning
I thought I could sleep
If you get rid of badminton in the morning
He won't wake you up
He'll wake you up
Wake up
If you eat a lot and go to sleep, you'll become a cow
If you eat while sleeping, what will you become?
That's a difficult question
Let's think about it together
Let's go
One, two, three, four
He says he'll become a cow
I wonder why
When I was a kid
I didn't think I'd become a cow
I was really scared when I was a kid
I heard that if you blow a whistle, a snake will come out
I heard that if you pull a string, your fingers will bend
Really?
I thought I'd become a cow
This is hard
It's not a good thing
I thought I'd become a cow
I was scared of that
This is my question
What will you become?
I have another question
I'll ask this in parallel
How does a shellfish feel when it spits out sand?
These two questions
A shellfish doesn't do anything bad
It's just that it's in the water
For example, in winter the shellfish gets freed
Remember when it got thrown into the
Karate style linear K ela
That's it
A fisherman comes to the range
And they hit it
It's the triple kick
Then someone else comes
Then he throws it into the mountain
He does that
It goes into the shellfish
Then he throws it into the landing
With these kinds of shells
I feel like I'm going to puke.
Are you okay? Can you fight?
I'll do my best. I'll do my best.
That's difficult.
What happens if you eat while you're sleeping?
What happens if I eat while I'm sleeping?
After you eat...
There's a song about eating while you're sleeping.
What happens if I eat while I'm sleeping?
You can't do that if you rest.
Hey, don't be so stubborn and sing!
What happens if I eat while I'm sleeping?
That's right. You eat while you're sleeping.
What does that mean?
What happens?
You'll be full at night.
Then, what happens if I eat while I'm sleeping?
That's tough.
What happens?
You can eat while you're sleeping.
You can't?
You'll be fat.
You'll be fat, but you'll be a pig.
And after you eat, you'll be a cow.
You're getting close.
The problem is...
What happens if I eat while I'm sleeping?
You're getting close.
I'm getting close?
You're getting close?
You eat while you're sleeping, right?
Yes.
You're not a sleepwalking old man.
That's right.
What?
Let's go home.
Let's put this away for now.
Let's put this away.
Why are female comedians so ugly?
Female comedians are ugly and smelly.
I don't understand that.
I don't know that story.
Whose story is it?
It's called Double Sakuranbo.
Do you know it?
It's really smelly.
I was really tired from work.
I had to go to the dressing room.
The dressing room was full of water.
And my nose...
It was really smelly.
I woke up and it was really smelly.
What?
I looked around.
I saw Double Sakuranbo's high heels.
I got closer and my nose...
I didn't know that.
Do you know that my feet don't stink at all?
I don't know that.
Your feet don't stink.
They don't stink!
Let's put this away for now.
It stinks!
Let's put this away.
Let's put this away!
It stinks!