Good evening. Today, I would like to ask if my way of speaking really has the spirit of an actor.
As you all know, I'm in trouble right now.
Today, as you all know, I'm shooting a drama called Leave it to Ryoma at IKUTA studio.
Who the hell are you?
Get out of here!
Let me go!
Even if I go in the middle, will he be able to deal with this Ryoma?
I used to play the piano in Hong Kong.
What's wrong? There was a sound just now.
What's wrong?
It's not a return, but I'd like to give it a try.
Let's go. I'm shooting right now.
I'm going in here.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Instead of playing the piano, let's play the guitar.
Ryoma, what time do you start shooting?
I start shooting at 8 in the morning.
I'm trying my best.
Don't say that.
You start shooting at 8 in the morning?
That's right.
I can't believe it.
This situation reminds me of a dead body.
Like a pigeon.
It reminds me of that.
Don't say that.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Ryoma, wait a minute.
I just remembered something.
You're not the only one who remembers.
Don't do that.
I know a lot of names.
Wait a minute.
I don't think you're going to say anything when you turn around.
I'm sorry.
This is better.
This part and this part.
Why are you alone in the dark?
Look at me.
What is it?
You're back to being a fool again.
He left.
Are you okay?
There's a vacation.
He won't be on the scene.
It's okay if he doesn't.
Call everyone to come out.
I don't know if I can put it in, but I'll ask them to come out.
Please play up to that.
I don't know what he's going to do after that.
I'll call you as soon as I hear it.
I see.
You can play up to that.
It's so quiet.
Please throw the stand by turn.
Thank you for waiting.
Okay, let's start the show.
10 seconds before the show.
8, 7, 4.
5 seconds before the show.
4, 3, 2.
It's unbelievable that the Kamikiri has become a human.
You're persistent.
But he tried to kill Katsu-sensei.
Hey, Ansei.
You...
Hey!
Why are you working alone?
Huh?
Hey.
Katsu-sensei's father came back again.
Katsu-sensei.
Just a little more.
This is bad.
I can't get along with Kisou-san.
There's something...
There's something wrong.
The tea has come in.
Thank you.
Here's your tea.
No.
What are you doing?
The tea has come in.
Excuse me.
What's going on?
When did you get here?
What was that scene?
Hey.
What are you doing?
The tea has come in.
I was thinking about that scene.
It's not a good idea to drink tea in the middle of the night.
I wanted to see how Hamada-kun can be a good actor.
I see.
Did you just do that?
I did.
I didn't know anything about the other cast members.
I didn't know that.
Everyone was surprised.
I think they're worse than Kouha-kun.
In that sense.
I didn't know there was an old lady who brought tea.
Are you okay?
This is my first appearance in a drama.
Thank you very much.
I want to show the gala properly.
Kouha-kun gave me 50,000 yen.
That's good.
I don't have that much money.
Ladies and Gentlemen.
What?
Congratulations on your first appearance in a drama.
No, no.
Congratulations.
I suddenly went to Hamada's drama to play.
You're wearing a kimono and dressing up as a woman.
I was wondering what kind of face I would make.
You were just in a daze.
Normally, when you do that, you know the other actors.
You said, let's just keep Hamada quiet.
You didn't know that at all, did you?
I didn't know that at all.
You didn't know the waiting room, did you?
What is that waiting room?
Everyone doesn't know that.
So I was really nervous.
I didn't know that I was coming to the show.
You didn't know that you were coming to the show.
Well, I didn't know that I was coming to the show.
I was told that there was a lot of interruption.
There was a lot of interruption.
I was told that there was a lot of water.
I was surprised.
He was recording you walking and something.
Yes, yes.
He said he was going to put you in the drama.
I don't know where it'll come from, but...
Well, I've done a lot of little roles like that, even until now.
Everyone just doesn't know.
What little roles?
Well, my debut was when I was about 5 years old.
Small roles?
I debuted from small roles.
What have you been in?
Well, I've been in a lot of things.
Everyone's like, what? You've been in that?
I've been in a lot of things.
What is it?
Well, the most famous one is still in Man Man.
Man Man?
It's like a movie or a drama.
I saw your post earlier, and it was already exposed.
What?
The one from Nittere's Friday Road Show.
It's like, fa-la-la-la-la-la-la.
It's at the bridge like this.
I don't get it.
I get it.
Well, I get it.
But the drama is out, so please send me a gala.
I'm counting on you.
It's really tough.
I'll be doing this for the last time.
What is it?
On New Year's Eve, I'll be taking a break.
For your sake.
Who told you to come?
I did it for your sake.
It took a lot of time.
The make-up, the costumes, everything.
I was surprised when I saw the gala.
It's 50,000 yen.
What? What do you mean by that?
It's not a lot?
You're stupid.
I've sung that much, and it's 100,000 yen.
What? 100,000 yen?
That's right.
Really?
It's New Year's Eve.
It has nothing to do with the date.
If it's New Year's Eve, I can get a part-time job.
You can get paid.
That's right.
It's not 50,000 yen.
But if you're in this situation,
do you know the look on your face when you go out and get 50,000 yen?
When you go out, you open your bag and do this.
You need a lot of stamina.
I've been running since two months ago.
What's your bag?
It's this.
I did it.
To be honest, I didn't think I'd get paid.
Because we're friends.
I don't know what friendship is.
You're the one who's talking.
I didn't think I'd get paid.
That's why I forgot.
When I saw you, you said you'd pay 50,000 yen.
If that's the case, I don't need it.
You're not that big a deal.
What?
You said you'd pay 100,000 yen.
I went to support you.
I don't know why it's cheap.
Support is more expensive.
That's right.
No matter what you do, it's weird that I'm paying 50,000 yen and you're paying 100,000 yen.
Don't say anything.
I'll give you 25,000 yen.
Wait.
Are you going to be number one this year?
It doesn't matter.
I went to support you.
It's weird that I'm cheaper.
I'll give you 25,000 yen.
You're not that big a deal.
I forgot.
I don't need that little money.
That's right.
It's what you want.
You don't want to be paid 50,000 yen.
It's better to be told it's free.
You should have told me that you don't need money.
What?
Why are you worried?
I'm a big fan of acting.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to your acting.
Are you really going to act?
Yes.
Really?
What will you do?
I'll be in the first and second place.
Why can't you be in the first and second place?
I'm in the first and second place.
It's like a Japanese show.
You want it?
I don't want it.
I work with money.
That's right.
That's a big difference between you and me.
What do you mean?
I want to see everyone's smiles.
You...
Are you stupid?
I want to see everyone's smiles.
You want to see money and smile.
It's not the same smile.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Don't mention it.
I wonder if there's anything else.
There's nothing else.
Really?
I forgot.
There's nothing else I can do.
You forgot, didn't you?
Yes.
Don't you think this is popular?
That's an unexpected answer.
This is popular.
Why?
I think it's very popular among young people.
Everyone does physical education.
I'm from Shibuya.
What?
Who are you?
I'm from Shibuya.
I see.
What?
I'm from Shibuya.
I'm still young.
Mr. Matsumoto is a night technician.
Yes.
What kind of night technician is Ms. Matsumoto?
What do you mean by that?
Didn't you see that?
What is that?
Famicom communication.
What?
Famicom communication?
Famicom?
It's not a computer. It's a Famicom.
It's a Famicom no matter what you do.
You're a fool.
I'm sorry.
You don't know about Famicom communication?
No, I don't.
It's not a Famicom. It's a Famicom from a while ago.
Don't talk nonsense.
There's a microphone on the two-player of a Famicom from a while ago.
You're talking about my child.
Don't talk about Famicom communication.
You're a fool.
Himawari Musume.
Yes.
The new captain.
The new captain, Himawari Musume.
How old is he?
He's 48.
He's going to be 49?
He'll be 49.
The new captain?
I see.
Well, it's a female character.
What?
No, no.
You're kidding.
I didn't ask if he was a female.
What?
You're asking a big question mark.
It's a woman's status.
A woman's status.
I'm curious.
Yes, yes, yes.
You understand?
Yes.
Then, please tell me.
Okay, let's do it.
What?
Why?
What's wrong with me?
Well, what am I?
What am I? You're not my partner.
Ah, a tsukkomi.
I'm trying to do it now.
Tsukkomi.
What am I?
Tsukkomi?
No, no.
No, no, no.
I'm starting to work now.
So, a man.
Ah, a man.
I'm a woman.
What should I do?
I'm a man, right?
I'm a man.
In such a cold way.
I can't hold you.
You want to hold me?
Hold me like you're holding me.
Yes, yes.
I can't hold you to your heart.
I understand.
What should I do?
I'm a man, right?
Yes, you're a man.
From here?
Yes, from here.
It's like a game of UWF.
Let's enter like this.
Wait a minute.
I'm doing it like this, but I'm going to sleep here.
I'm going to enter like this.
This is dangerous.
I'm going to show you the power of love.
Get out of my way.
Come here.
From the 13th of next month, you're going to be a witch, Matsumoto-san.
Please teach me the magic spell that turns all the women in the world into nudes.
In the past, there was a manga called Nagaigo.
No, no.
For the time being, you're going to be a witch from the 13th of next month, right?
Yes.
I'm going to be 14.
Yes, I'm going to be 14.
We're going to be 14.
Why are you saying that?
We're going to be traveling on a broom.
From the 13th of next month.
What is it?
Please teach me the spell.
What do you think it is?
You're going to be a witch tomorrow, right?
Yes, I'm going to be a witch tomorrow.
It's almost time.
I can feel it in my body right now.
You can feel it?
What do you mean?
I feel like I'm going to be a witch.
It's the same picture.
But you just forgave me.
I'm starting to feel like I'm going to be a witch.
How does your body feel right now?
It's hard to explain it with words.
You can't explain it in detail.
It's hard.
I'm worried about the steam coming out of the rice.
It's going to be like this.
Are you pregnant?
It's like that.
What is it?
All the women in the world are nude.
I understand.
First of all, it's embarrassing for a girl to wear clothes.
Why am I wearing clothes?
I see.
First of all, I'm going to be naked.
I'm going to tell a woman that I'm really naked.
It has nothing to do with the spell.
Wait a minute.
Open the blind.
What are you doing?
The woman is surprised.
That's right.
At this stage, I'm not wearing clothes in my world yet.
You may be naked.
I may be naked.
At that time, I look back.
Why are you wearing clothes?
You...
That's enough.
That's what a woman thinks.
Until now, I thought I was stupid.
I see.
That's right.
I think I'm crazy.
Why are you wearing clothes?
What are you doing?
If you say that...
I'll do this.
First of all...
I'm sorry.
I'm scared.