I want to know more about Ikko.
Quiz, about Ikko no 500.
No one said anything about wanting to know more about him.
Question 1.
That was fast!
Ikko's last name is?
I don't know!
That's close!
The answer is...
Ah, that's right.
Kouda?
Now, the correct answer is...
Toyota, Kazuyuki.
Toyota?
It's really red.
Really.
My eyes hurt when I see you with red eyes.
It's like a snow mountain.
By the way, everyone.
For this time, the 500 points of Ikko,
the person with the least correct answers will be left alone with Ikko.
The worst one is...
You have to do your best.
It was different before.
Question 2.
How old is Ikko?
How old is that?
It's definitely Ikko-san.
This much?
I'm not sure.
I think it's about this much.
Answer open.
I think it's about the same age as Downtown-san.
It's a little older than Downtown-san.
I think it's about 45
I think it's below
Now, the correct answer is...
It's coming, right?
It's just about the same
What is Ikko's favorite color?
I don't know
It's annoying.
I don't know.
Open the microphone.
This is...
It's just me.
The correct answer is...
The pink rose is completely red.
It's here.
It's missing.
I'm going to say something, but I'm still not used to it.
It's not a word.
It was a combination of the original.
Ikko, when was the first time you fell in love?
When I woke up.
It's not a question like this.
I think it was when I woke up.
5 points.
The answer is 5 points.
It's not a question like this.
It's probably early.
Yes
Now, the correct answer is
First love?
Yes!
Hamada-san is here
He's really good
Why is he so different?
He's better than Ikko
What are you talking about?
Ikko's first love
You?
I think I know that
Please show your answer.
The answer is...
Everyone chose a man.
I chose Kazuyoshi.
Tamori.
Now, the correct answer is...
Izumi Seijirou.
Don't say it with your first name!
What is the first thing a man checks?
It's about time you hit me
I know, I'm worried too
He opens the answer
I'm worried too, I'm at work
I'm worried too
Now, the correct answer is
Body check?
Yes
The part you like?
The back
When I get questions like that, I get a lot of questions back
I want to answer them
Body?
It's not that
What country do you think Japan is?
It's a country.
I see.
If you go overseas...
You'll know when you go overseas.
I think it's a place that's not just beautiful.
That's right.
So, the correct answer is...
Hmm...
Marjib.
The answer is...
You don't understand.
I don't understand.
This is the big L.
I don't understand this cycle.
The big L is coming out.
What do you think your self as a woman is?
As a woman?
You mean I am?
I think this is about right.
Oh, I think it's correct.
I still have a half chance.
It's the best.
I want to see more and more.
Oh, the end is high.
Yes.
Then, the correct answer is...
It's your turn.
It's this one.
You didn't make a mistake.
It's high.
It's 120 points.
You know it's not that high, right?
You were just saying that, right?
I see.
You have a lot to say.
I do.
What would you want to be if you were reborn?
Something like this.
5 minutes to the buzzer.
Oh, really?
Well, well.
So, finally, in my life, I feel like I was reborn.
I hated myself for being so complex.
I was told I was like a woman.
But I'm glad I was a good boy.
Let's hit him.
What is this?
It's like a sex scene.
That's right.
But when it comes to men, it's a low-class.
How many times do you forgive a kiss on a date?
Kiss?
I don't know that.
I don't know.
I don't care.
I really don't care.
This is pretty hard.
It looks like that.
What should I do?
It's like a f***ing f***ing.
Well, I'll go.
You're going to kiss, right?
Yes.
I'll go.
The first kiss.
In this case, isn't that what kissing is?
Does it mean just kissing?
That's just kissing at first.
The correct answer is...
Oh!
Amazing
It's really...
What do you mean by the eyes are the most important?
I don't know
Who do you think is the most useless out of the 5?
Here it comes
This is difficult
Previously, the same question was asked about the quiz Hamada 500
The 3 of them answered Tanaka
What is this?
And Hamada's answer is...
Tanaka's answer is...
I...
fries
car
you know my hairstyle is...
Tanaka-san
I don't have that hair
I guess it
say it
I'm Sayaka
ah, realmente
Akami-sama...
Stop it, stop it!
It's just Akami.
Middle...
No, no, no!
I think I got it right.
I thought it was the end.
I was fishing and then I got it right.
I found a underwear thief on the balcony.
How does the girl scream?
I'm sorry. I forgot.
I still remember.
I have to say this.
It's a betrayal.
Now, the correct answer.
Of course, don't mess with me.
What?
What is it?
What is the first item?
I think this is a serious question.
That's right.
Is it different?
It's like this.
Kan-chan?
Like this
It's different than that
Is it different?
If it's different, it's still this
I think it's in the story mode
It's in the story mode
It's in the story mode?
I'll make it a little more sharp
I don't know what kind of face I'm making when I hear it
That's the most interesting
Now, the announcement of the correct answer
He has become a family member.
When I woke up, I saw him and my mother and sisters having the same eyes.
I don't have anything to say but I have feelings for my family.
You got it.
You got it right.
The pattern was perfect.
This is fun.
It comes out sometimes.
It's a good one.
What is Ikko's favorite weather?
I'll go with this one.
It's the best.
Ikko doesn't twist his neck here.
He doesn't twist his neck here.
Really?
I don't twist my neck either.
I'm a Mordivian.
The weather is good.
Please announce the correct answer.
Definitely sunny
It's a lie
It's a lie, Amano-san
It's sunny
From the start, after 3 hours, he's in trouble with his unrecognizable personality
It's a good thing
It's the flow of the ocean
It's the red ocean
It's the Atlantic
It's a good face
What is the most worrying thing in the world?
Hmm... the most worrying thing in the world...
Is this a pattern that we should talk about?
There is a possibility.
That time...
I will definitely talk about this.
Now, the correct answer is...
It's the education problem.
There are many elementary and middle school students who are bullied by their teachers.
But teachers and parents are changing their minds.
When children see this, they lose their place to go.
They can't believe it.
So I think parents and teachers have to work together.
And also, how to save the students who have come this far.
I think life is about the students who have come this far.
I always take care of them.
That's why it's about balance.
To achieve that balance, we need to educate them.
And all the things like talking.
It's all.
This is the first CD that Ikko bought.
This is the generation.
CD?
This is not a CD.
Answer open.
Bakugan Ranran.
This is a great answer.
Now, the correct answer.
Is this okay?
That's right.
Why?
That's not it.
It's not that.
Why did you write that?
That's right.
And I'm free to meet you again.
I'll take it.
What is the switch that Ikko often presses?
This one?
I think it's the switch that he presses the most.
It's the last one.
Right?
Is it because there's no one who can play the guitar?
It's the second one.
Secomu?
Because it's a woman, it's really scary.
It's strange to say, after all.
After all, it's Secomu.
It's a TV channel.
Everyone is like that.
It's completely different.
Which is more beautiful, bare-faced or naked?
This is difficult.
The body is...
You don't like it, right?
If it's a girl, I don't like it.
The correct answer is...
The more beautiful, bare-faced or naked?
I think it's naked.
What?
What is that?
There was only Yamazaki, Hadaka
Wow, it's big
I want to take a picture of this
Hadaka
It's completely left
It's left
If Ikko is a man, how old would you like him to be?
How old?
How old is the mother?
I see.
I like the current me.
Yes, you do.
That's right.
The answer is...
Well...
Now, she is 45 years old
As a woman, she is trying to be a great woman
Her arms are getting thinner
Her face is getting...
She is getting closer to her ideal
She is 45 years old
I'm going to interview him.
I'm not going to say such a thing.
Where was Ikko last Christmas?
I've been asked this question before.
But I think you were busy, so you had to do something.
I don't know.
Mic open.
Well then.
I don't remember.
If it was two years ago, I was in Sabuto.
No, it's not.
Last year, last year.
That was there.
That's what happened.
Sometimes he would come out and say,
I refuse.
Even though he can do it, even though she can do it,
He's an old man.
He doesn't remember Christmas.
The 500th question.
Alright.
The next question is,
How many times can you say,
From the beginning,
At 7 o'clock,
We finally reached the final question.
Based on what we've learned so far,
The answer is...
It's definitely the line.
This is the easiest one.
This is definitely the answer.
It's meaningless if you don't see it.
It's a dead end.
I don't like it.
Now, the answer is...
Well, it's not about money.
I'll do it if you take the best pictures of me that have never been taken in Japan.
It's not a price.
You said you'd do it.
It's the best.
If it's going to be like this, the best situation...
I'll do it.
It won't hurt.
It's shaking.
I was right.
Now, all 500 questions have been answered.
Now, I will announce the winner of the quiz.
The winner is...
Tanaka!
He's been called out.
Do you work here?
This is my first time.
What?
I've been here before.
I've never seen you before.
This is my first time.
I thought you'd be nice to me.
I can't do 500 times.
I thought you were a true man.
You were like that when you were in the old days.
I'll try to be a little stronger.
I'm sorry.
Ouch!
My hip is so painful!
I got a cramp.
It's okay, Tanaka.
It was dangerous, right?
This is a serious cramp.
vict management