The first time, we were at the Gaki no Tsutaya.
We were doing a prank on Yamazaki.
Nakamura died!
Good evening.
Today, we're going to trick Yamazaki for the first time in a while.
Well, I'm used to being tricked.
I'm very careful.
That's right.
That's what we thought.
The staff, Nakamura.
Let's pretend he's dead.
He's already dead.
Actually, I thought he was dead when we finished the七変言.
First, let's call the main character.
He's already dead.
This is scary.
The reason why we asked Nakamura to be here today is because...
This is the most boring part.
Even if he's dead?
Yes.
This is Nakamura Yoshinobu.
He's the most mischievous guy in the history of the Gaki no Tsutaya.
Actually, this prank has already been done since last week.
Nakamura approached Yamazaki.
He promised to give Yamazaki 100,000 yen next week.
Yamazaki was impressed by the last conversation with him scheduled for next week.
Actually, this is a big hit.
Yes.
Let's pretend Nakamura is dead.
Then, he will appear.
Got it.
Nakamura, who was supposed to die in a car accident, appears in the back seat of the car.
Will Yamazaki be able to withstand the fear?
I've been practicing for a long time.
Really?
I'm Hagi.
Good morning.
It seems he's going deep inside.
Is it 12 o'clock today?
Your face is so stretched out.
You actually go for a walk?
Are you a foodie?
Oh, I see.
It's like a weird prank, isn't it?
I got it!
How many times do I have to tell you?
You guys!
It's so hot!
I don't want to talk to you.
What?
Really?
What about you, Samo?
I told you that I can talk to you.
But I don't know how to do it.
Really?
What about you, Doji?
I don't know how to do it.
Maybe tomorrow or the day after.
Maybe we can talk about it.
How about you, Okamoto?
I don't know how to do it.
Good evening.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
Is it that bad?
I think so.
Thank you so much.
You know, people say that he goes through a really tough time.
Okamoto, thank you so much.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Good morning.
He's coming.
Why are you going to the bathroom?
Look behind you.
It's the same thing.
What?
Are you still talking about it?
Yes.
I see.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
Are you okay?
Look inside the car.
Look behind you.
He's coming.
Are you okay?
Wait a minute.
I promised you.
What's wrong?
I don't know what's going on.
Did you have 100,000 yen?
You were worried about that, weren't you?
I've been saying that for a long time.
What's going on with 100,000 yen?
I don't know what's going on.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Yamaguchi, do you have a job after this?
I don't have a job.
That's a lie.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
You're a woman. You can't go out alone.
Come to the dressing room.
I got it.
You're so mean.
Don't take money from me.
It's cold, isn't it?
There's a place to stand.
I don't know what's going on, but you're over there.
I'm over here.
It's decided, isn't it?
It doesn't matter what kind of show it is.
There's a commercial going on right now.
AM, PM.
I'm being blown away by fear.
I'm being blown away from this side.
It's annoying, isn't it?
A jet plane is blown away by such a big fan.
That's the only time I'm over there.
Wait a minute.
I'm not the only one who says I don't buy it.
That's strange, isn't it?
It's a very detailed place.
Wait a minute.
When I'm doing it alone, I'm over here and you're over here.
That's right.
In your case, there's a man over here.
In your case, there's a woman over here.
There's a woman over here.
There are two at the end.
Why do you only say that at that time?
You're wasting your history.
Why am I over here?
I'm doing this.
Hamada is over here, so it's okay.
It's okay.
I'm not in trouble.
I'm not in trouble because I was blown away by the wind.
That's not the case.
Why is it only today?
Why is it only me on this day?
I'm a little depressed after I got home.
Why?
I don't know.
It's the same in magazines, isn't it?
I'm the only one who takes pictures with a bad mouth in downtown.
Why?
Why am I always the opposite wind?
Why is it the same today?
Do you remember?
It's the same with pictures of two people.
I don't do TV these days, but I'll do it on the cover.
When you take a picture of a single talent, you should take the best picture.
When it comes to two people, you prioritize the good image of one person.
Obviously.
Wait a minute.
That's not the case.
You think too much about it.
It's obvious that you're the one who chooses.
It's Hama-chan's book.
I chose it with the feeling of Hama-chan and lemon.
That's enough.
You're a bad person.
Even if you're alone, there are some weird pictures.
Yes, there are.
This is a picture of the last episode of FOCUS.
Why did you take a picture of Tenno-kawa?
Why did you take a picture of Yamafu?
What is it?
I'm not angry.
How is everyone?
How are you doing?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry to say something like an old man, but this year is early.
It's early.
I'm sorry to say something like an old man.
What is it?
I'm about 40 years old.
Don't say that.
That's right.
I'm not 40 years old.
It's okay if a man is 40 years old.
The age of a man and a woman is completely different.
A man's 40 years old is about a woman's 25 years old.
I'm sorry.
Don't say that.
If it's at least 10 years old, a woman's 25 years old is an old woman.
There are various ideas.
25 years old is an old woman.
A woman's 25 years old is an old woman.
A woman's 25 years old is an old woman, and a man's 40 years old is an old man.
This is exactly the same.
You guys are stupid.
That's you.
Don't say that.
I'll say it because I'm in my place.
If a man is 40 years old, can you fall in love?
Yes.
A woman's 25 years old is the time limit.
Wait a minute.
A woman's 25 years old is your time limit.
There's a difference between men and women.
What's your time limit?
Your...
When is the man's time limit?
Why are you so stubborn?
What's wrong with you?
You're sweating all by yourself.
When is the woman's time limit?
About 35 years old.
You're so mean.
What's wrong with you?
You have a big target.
You have a lot of coins.
Did you find out?
I'm so angry.
Why am I the bad guy?
You're 35 years old because you're not old.
You're 25 years old because you're not old.
I saw the woman there.
It's okay. You can't be honest.
How old are you?
22 years old.
24 years old.
It's over next year.
It's okay.
You're cool.
When you eat a cup of ice cream, please teach me how to lick the lid.
Of course.
Please teach me.
It's okay.
What should I start with?
Start with the moon.
I thought you were going to teach me how to eat grapes.
Please teach me how to lick the lid of a cup of ice cream.
It's okay.
Even if you teach me how to eat grapes?
Please lick the lid.
Like this.
I opened it.
And?
It's a miso-like thing.
You're like a mountain.
It's amazing.
It's not cool.
Please teach me how to lick the lid without spilling it.
How to lick the lid without spilling it.
When you open the lid and lick the lid like this, it's not cool.
That's right.
I see.
So you have to open the lid and lick the lid from here.
That's weird.
Are you so desperate?
You have to go like this.
That's more comfortable.
Why?
You have to open the lid and lick the lid.
You can't do it at once.
Why are you holding the lid?
What kind of situation is this?
You have to put it on the desk.
I know that.
You have to lick the lid.
I don't know what you're eating.
You have to put it on the desk.
Why?
Where are you eating?
You have to put it on the desk.
I don't understand your background.
The office!
The company?
The company.
You have to call the company.
You know, right?
You have to put it on the desk.
You have to lick the lid from here.
It's so annoying.
You don't have to do that.
I want you to steal a lot from me.
What do you want me to steal?
Your coolness.
You can teach me. I'll imitate you.
What do you want me to do?
Your coolness.
Have you ever thought about how to walk?
When a kid starts to walk,
ladies and gentlemen,
de de de de de de.
When a kid starts to walk,
it's not cool at all.
I'm thinking,
it's not cool today either.
You should have said that earlier.
Why didn't you say it now?
Why didn't you say it normally?
Play the music for me.
What is it?
You...
How many times have you done this?
What is it?
Are you kidding me? Get lost!
That's the difference.
I'll do that next time.
I don't want to come out like this next time.
But the hall is different every time,
so it's hard to come out from the other side.
Why is it different between right and left?
What is it?
You're not supposed to do that.
You don't have time to think.
Give me some more time.
I can't wait.
I'd like to ask Mr. Matsumoto,
who can make anyone laugh.
Please make the 5-second CM caster laugh
right after the kid's broadcast.
Who was that?
The one who comes out right after this.
I don't know who it was.
Mr. Ida?
Ida?
Ida Yumi.
If that person is watching this broadcast,
and it's going to be broadcast as it is,
you can make him laugh.
You can't make someone who's not watching laugh.
That's true.
So if that person says that he's watching this kid,
and he says,
I'm watching this kid,
and it starts,
I see.
Then you can do something next time.
You can say,
this guy's tank lorry did this and that.
If that person says,
I'm watching this kid,
you can make him laugh right after the next episode.
But I don't think you can say that.
Even if you're watching.
There are things you have to say.
Like what happened to the tank lorry.
If you don't say that,
you can send a sign while commenting.
The tank lorry exploded.
That might be harder than saying it.
That's fine.
The tank lorry exploded.
If you read the news,
you lose your persuasion.
If you say it at the end,
you say,
No, it's the same.
It's the same.
Then it's the tank lorry.
No, it's not.
You don't have persuasion.
If I can say that it's the same,
I'll start filming next week.
I'll ask you to stand in line.
When I'm calling you,
I'll stand in line.
When it starts,
I'll stand diagonally.
That's different.
That's not persuasive.
Why is that?
You have to look at the camera seriously.
Of course it's persuasive.
What about Mr. Kin?
Mr. Kin is also persuasive like this.
I want you to suck my nose.
The tank lorry.
That's not good.
If you don't suck my nose,
I don't know what to do.
Then I'll stand diagonally.
I don't know if it's like this.
I think you know that.
I'll do it a little wider.
If it's like this,
I'll look at you.
I'll never say that.
I'm sorry.
I'll start laughing next week.
I want you to suck my nose a little.
This program was provided by the sponsor.
I can do this anywhere, right?
That's right.
I can do this anywhere.
I'll use it when I go camping.
Mr. Toyoda.
Really?
I can do this anywhere.
That's great.
Thank you.
This is Mr. Matsumoto.
This car is Toyota.
I bought it at Toyota.
Thank you.
This is a Windham.
That's a good car.
It's a different sense of security.
I want you to suck my nose, too.
You're the only one who can do this.
I came here a week ago.
That's great.
I can do this anywhere.