Next time on Gaki no Tsukaya, Chiki-chiki!
Even if you buy it, it's hell! Even if you donate it, it's hell!
Totsugi! Kojo-bashi Grand Prix!
So, Mr. Matsumoto.
Yes, yes, yes.
Today, you changed your thinking a bit.
Well, every time, this Kojo-bashi Club was announced.
About 20 minutes later, that stage was already over.
I think it was about 20 minutes.
That fast?
We will never challenge such a thing again.
Is it a complete withdrawal?
Yes, it's a complete withdrawal.
Last time, the Gaki members played against the Kusukurizurizu, led by Yuichi Kimura, as Kojo-baffalos.
The Kojo-bashi Club was attacked by the Kusukurizurizu.
Both teams had a great match, without a single step.
In the midst of a fierce battle, the Gaki team also won.
And this time, with a new way of thinking, we will send you a scary Kojo-bashi project.
It's us. What is it this time?
I want to see other talents' Kojo-bashas.
I see.
I want to see that pitiful appearance.
A fool's face.
I want to see a refreshing face.
I see.
It's a bit of a surprise today, but we have invited various guests.
This time, we will have a Kojo-bashi match, as we did before.
By inviting guests?
That's the plan.
The other team will have a match against us.
The main purpose of this time is to have a Kojo-bashi match with our staff.
Kojo-bashas.
We haven't prepared well.
That's right.
Suddenly, Kojo-bashas will attack us.
Kojo-bashi-man.
This is it.
This is going to be tough.
This time, the rule is that if you can endure the Kojo-bashi for 2 minutes, you will get 100,000 yen.
100,000 yen.
That's tough.
But if you want to give up, we will ask you a question.
It's a question that you definitely don't want to answer.
If you can answer it, we will release you.
I see.
But if you don't want to answer it, you have to endure it.
May I?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Today's orchestra is very strong.
It's like a band.
That's right.
Everyone, the target this time is...
Who is it?
It's this person.
Oh.
It's a member of Kojo-bashas.
It looks interesting.
It's very interesting.
But I like Shu-san in this program.
It's quite...
There's someone like Shu-san.
The one who pushes?
That's right.
How many times do I have to tell you that there's someone like Shu-san?
This program is brought to you by the five sponsors.
The target this time is the young Uenzu Eiji.
And Girls.
And the veteran group Shu Tomitaku.
The four stars of Nishikino Akira.
First of all, this member is going to compete with us.
I see.
I'm nervous.
Nishikino-san is scary.
I wonder what's going to happen.
He's always standing close to me.
The four countries are waiting for the show without knowing anything.
Good morning.
Please take a picture of us at the venue.
Yes.
Please take a picture of us.
After this, they will realize it with their own eyes.
The ultimate Kocobashi hell that suddenly attacks.
Kocobashi target.
First of all, Uenzu Eiji.
How far will Earth's idol face collapse?
Thank you.
Uenzu-san will enter.
Please check the set.
Thank you.
This time, I have a question for Uen.
What is the most memorable food of a celebrity?
This is...
As a celebrity...
This is a good question.
This is Yuta and Otora.
That's right.
This is a good question.
Uen-san, please show us your teeth.
Masuda-san is a momoe-chan.
This is a good question.
Please answer it.
I'm sure each of us has...
Yes, I'm sure each of us has...
But I thought momoe-chan's teeth were normal, right?
They were not normal.
You can tell.
I'll give you an idea, so just answer and give up.
The winner will get a total of 200,000 yen.
That's the content.
What is the content?
It's okay.
It's okay?
Yes, thank you.
It's almost time.
Almost time.
Let's continue.
One more, one more
If you can do it in 2 minutes, you'll get 100,000 yen
100,000 yen, 100,000 yen
You can't do it?
I'll ask you a question
If you answer it, I'll release you
I'll release you
I have a question
Who is the celebrity you calleше thirty in a row?
I'll release you if you answer
if you answer, release me
Who is the celebrity you calleше thirty in a row?
Asshole
Who is that?
Who is?
Who is the celebrity you calleше thirty in a row?
I hate it
I'll release you
Barz
Who is that?
Who is it?
I want to be an idol.
I have a runny nose.
The end.
It's over.
I see.
That's amazing.
You said you wanted to be an idol.
You said it.
That's amazing.
But it was long.
How long did it take?
It was 400,000 yen in 40 seconds.
Hasegawa Kyoko-san.
You said it.
Well, that's true.
I haven't heard a proper comment yet.
I was surprised.
This is the end.
Thank you for your hard work.
The end.
Please go home.
I think there are still some leftovers at home.
Give up time.
1 minute and 13 seconds.
The idol WENZU's side dish was Hasegawa Kyoko.
WENZU, did you calm down?
Yes.
What is it?
Really.
I thought it was over.
I couldn't take it anymore.
It's been a long time.
I suddenly remembered my childhood.
Who will be the next target.
The next target is a girl group with a cute character.
UGLY GIRLS
Tanaka and Yamane.
Are these two cute even if they are criticized?
UGLY GIRLS
We're coming in.
The first one.
It'll be big.
This is a big one.
It's a bit scary.
The one who is more unpleasant is 88 years old.
This is something...
Stand in the middle, and then, like a
The two of them are,
Tanaka's most sensitive sexual intercourse.
If he's not allowed to do it, he's a man.
This is a real man.
This is hard, isn't it?
I've never thought about it like this before.
If you wanted to forgive me, that's impossible.
I would like you to stand up and get the prize.
Thank you.
He's wearing the same T-shirt as me.
He's going to fight?
Tanaka's turn.
Oh no!
Tanaka!
Can he do it?
He has 20 seconds left!
20 seconds!
Tanaka!
Question...
What is the first thing you think of?
The first thing...
I can't!
Where are you?
I'm having a hard time here!
You're in the video!
What are you doing?
I'm over here!
Where are you?
I'm having a hard time here!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Where?
Inside my butt.
Time's up.
What is this?
Inside my butt.
Inside your butt?
I've never heard of this.
I don't know the name of this.
Yamane start!
Please, please.
Can you do it?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
This is really hard.
I wonder if I can do it.
I think I can do it.
This guy is amazing.
This is really hard.
Yamane, if you can't do it, please answer this question.
Can a male entertainer forgive his body?
I'm not going to let you go.
This is really hard.
I'm really not going to let you go.
I'm not going to let you go.
I'm going to say this.
Who?
Fujii, I need you to fix this.
What is this?
What the hell is that?
Fujii, fix it.
What the hell is it?
It's over when you get there.
Huh?
It's over.
I don't want to do it!
Give up time is 1 minute and 3 seconds.
An Girls' Tanaka's body was like a wall of ass.
And Yamanen gave up in 1 minute and 1 second.
The male entertainer who can forgive his body is Naohito Fujiki.
Look, Yuta is still young.
Yes, he is.
He is still a junior.
That's right.
He is still fresh when he is young.
He is quite an old man.
He has a bad feeling.
I don't know what to say.
I have never seen him like this.
I feel like I'm going to have a heart attack.
The third target is the owner chef of Kanto Meisai.
Shu Tobinoku.
Nice to meet you.
Please come in.
Mr. Shu will come in.
Nice to meet you.
This is bad.
He is wearing a hat.
I will give you a tip while looking at the place.
This is a wall.
Yes.
Mr. Shu.
What are you doing?
Are you all right?
What is Shu's favorite color of underwear?
That's right.
This is the same underwear.
When you stand up, the yellow-haired people will come and tickle you.
Please be patient as much as you can.
Is there a scene?
I will give you a tip while looking at the place.
This is a wall.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Please come in.
Start.
Mr. Shu.
What?
Are you all right?
Seems like you are very well estàngly.
What?
And you?
Exactly, because of two minutes?
Yes, thank you.
Take it easy.
What?
Why?
Are you all right?
Who cares?
Thank you.
Thank you for being patient.
What's that?
You're really aman.
I was nervous.
ONO!!
C'mon everyone!
The intermission is long!
Please wait a minute.
You have one minute left.
Please don't, don't ahead yet.
I got you, another 2 minutes.
It's okay do you want another 2 minutes??
Five-minutes...
You've got to be kidding me!
Kojogashima is really hard
That's it?
You can do it
What is this?
Ah, my hat
My hat
What is this?
His beard is coming out
My hat
My hat is coming out
I don't know
You can do it
You are really strong
15 seconds left
15 seconds
You did it!
It's coming from here
Thank you for the puzzle
That's right
You can say it
What should I do?
It's done
Amazing
What is this?
It's not broken at all, Shiro-san
It feels good
It feels good?
Really?
Really
It's amazing
I thought it would be impossible
It's my first time
Shiro-san
It's amazing
Hello, Hana-chan
It's in
Let's go with Sasaki-san's yakiniku
What?
What is that?
I can't tell
The fourth target is the star of 35 years of entertainment life
The star of the stars, Nishikino Akira
Thank you
He appeared in his own judo machine
He is a star with a lot of energy
Nishikino-san, please come in
Thank you
A judo machine
What?
So
You plan to fight
But
Although it was mentioned earlier
But he isn't agile
That's right
You made up your mind
I really made up my mind
He made up his mind
Well
One of the three Nishikinos
Dear everyone
Want to make a snack
Do you have 3 Nishikino or not?
Do you have it?
I want to see it, but I don't want to hear it.
He's doing the things that are coming out recently.
He's throwing it away.
He's throwing it away at this age.
The guitar is already naked.
What are you talking about?
It's completely naked.
This is amazing.
That's what I said.
Start.
Good morning.
It's 100,000 yen in two minutes.
It's OK.
Say the name of the restaurant.
It's ***.
***.
What?
It's not a ***.
We're giving you a massage.
If you want to give up, here's a question.
Who's the celebrity who had a side dish before?
I'm asking, sir.
A celebrity.
It's a side dish.
Does it feel good?
Hey, come on!
Why? Why?
Why?
Amazing!
It's a complete wind poison!
This picture is abnormal.
What is it?
The end!
Amazing!
It's a complete wind poison!
It feels good!
What is it?
I'm not good at taking pictures.
I see.
What is it?
What are you doing?
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
You're going to be released.
Who is it?
It's Mako Ishida!
What?
Is that how you did it?
You were doing it for 3 minutes!
Right?
Is that how you did it?
It's only 10 minutes, right?
Give up time is 23 seconds.
The middle school boy, Okazu Hamada, was Mako Ishida.
What is this?
Amazing!
It's not about age.
It's about how you do it.
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
Give up!
Say the name of your beloved woman!
My beloved woman!
Say it properly!
Who is it?
I love you!
This is my second time on this show.
I'm confessing my love to my wife.
Give up time is 27 seconds.
Endo's beloved woman is Chiaki.
I'm jealous.
That's all from Kochobashi!
Thank you!
The recording ended safely.
Actually, Kochobashi was aiming for the last man to be the target of the day.
What is it? What is it?
What is it?
I was surprised.
What?
What is it?
Can I forgive you?
What?
Who is it?
Can I forgive you?
What?
Who is it?
Yuji Oda!
That's right!
You're always thinking about it, right?
What are you thinking about?
I was surprised.
I'm really scared.
Give up time is 33 seconds.
The man that Matsumoto can forgive is Yuji Oda.
Senpai, I'll do my best.
Senpai! Senpai!
Yuji Oda can do it.
The sixth video of the children's user DVD.
The miracle release.
A serious battle between a man and a woman.
Complete collection of songs.
It will be released on July 27th.