Next time, we'll be at the Gaki no Tsukaya!
Let's watch Denpa Shounen too!
Tiki-tiki Toshimatsuri Soccer Tournament!
Toshimatsuri Soccer Tournament!
That's right.
It says here that the blood is running, but...
I don't know what you're talking about.
Let's do our best today.
You have to use your physical strength from time to time.
You have to move your body.
The uniform is a little small.
Everyone's wearing a little tights today.
If you open it up a little, it'll look like this.
That's what it looks like.
This is Ganba Matsumoto team.
Ganba Matsumoto team goes to these members.
This is the team I chose.
He used to play soccer.
Soccer?
Yes.
How long have you been playing soccer?
I've been playing soccer for about two years.
It's been two years.
It's a lie that it's been two years.
Here we are.
Hamada Perdy!
This is soccer.
Who played soccer?
It's like a crab.
I'm going to do the first round.
This is the judge.
Here you go.
It's a lie!
By the way, when did you first play soccer?
When I was in elementary school and high school.
I played soccer for about five years.
I'm going to play soccer for about five years.
This is Takakun!
Ganba Matsumoto!
This is a rock-paper-scissors game.
There are a lot of people.
Get out of the way!
This is a rock-paper-scissors game.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
OK.
I can do it.
I can't do it.
No. Don't go.
Come on.
Hey hey hey, I hit it!
It was visible, I hit it!
I'm not defending here.
When you turned to us, I wasattacking them as well!
', Spar!
Was it you?
Yes.
That guy overthere! I mean Udemyan!
That fool broke open!
You jinxed us!
You should blame him!
You passed the judge!
Why can't you blame the cheafer?
You should go to the police!
It's a real person.
Don't kick it.
I'll replace the guitar.
I'll be back.
The original song was completed before.
It's really
It's really light.
Cl noticeable
B G
The original song was completed after.
Let's do it!
Throw it forward!
Throw it! Throw it! Throw it!
I can't do it!
Why didn't you throw it forward?
Throw it! Throw it!
Throw it!
what do you think about last Aikido and it was ok?
Oh! it passed the record!
I can't give up now.
You can't give up?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Well, it's over for this year.
This is the last time this year.
It's the last time.
Of course, I'm not going to give up.
It's an unbelievable tandem.
When you wake up in the morning, you'll be like,
Ha!
My soul is burning.
It's already like this.
It's really a plasma.
It's amazing.
When you wake up in the morning, you'll definitely be like,
That tissue, nose,
They're already...
The source of evil.
It's already...
I'm going to do it with my hands like this.
It's already like this.
If you do this, the room looks wide.
It's already a plasma.
It's become an amazing thing.
It's terrible.
You know, your nose is clogged.
I'm not feeling well when I sleep.
My nose is clogged.
That's why Hitoshi's breathing is like this.
I'm going to do it with my breath.
I'm going to do it with my mouth.
You have to use the monkey engine.
I'm not using a normal normal engine at all.
It's a second engine.
I'm going to do it with my mouth.
I can't use my nose at all.
When you wake up in the morning, you'll be like,
Ha!
My soul is burning.
It's already...
Hitoshi, you're crazy.
Hitoshi's pillow is clogged.
It's not clogged.
It's clogged.
It's terrible.
I've been on the bullet train for a week.
I can't get on the bullet train.
There's a lot of bad gas.
There was a funny guy on the bullet train.
He's been on the bullet train for a long time.
He fell right in front of my seat.
I can't help but talk.
I'm very excited.
And there's no one to talk to.
I'm going to be on the train.
Thank you for your time today.
Yes, yes.
This is it.
I can't help it.
But I'm going to laugh.
It's funny.
These days, fake coupons are coming out.
It's hard for me.
I'm screaming.
If you're that drunk, you'll feel good.
I don't have that experience.
I can't drink that much.
There was a party the other day.
I was drunk.
I don't know what to say.
It's funny no matter what you say.
What's that?
Yes, yes.
I can't help it.
It's funny.
When I was in junior high school,
I was watching TV all the time.
It was a wallet.
The word wallet is funny.
I was laughing until the morning.
But it's a wallet.
There's that.
I don't know why.
I was hit by a temple.
It's dangerous.
I was hit hard.
I felt good.
I was waiting for a step.
Don't cry.
I didn't want to say it.
But I was so excited.
I couldn't help it.
Don't say that to me.
I'm a victim.
I'm the one who made me feel bad.
Don't say that.
I can't help it.
That's why I'm a victim.
I'm talking to you.
Don't you understand?
I think it's a strange move.
I'm listening.
I can't help it.
What should I do next year?
What?
It's a job.
I want to know how you're going to do it.
What are you going to do in April?
I'm going to quit in April.
That's what I'm saying.
I've never seen a show like that.
What's going on?
That's not it.
I'm going to think about it.
I think like that.
I'm thinking about it.
Are you going to make it?
I see.
If you think you've done as much as you can,
I refuse to come anymore.
Let's go.
That would be nice.
That's what I'm saying.
What about around here?
That's why you shouldn't squeeze it.
I don't think it's necessary.
I'm going to shape it up.
We're a little drunk right now.
We're drunk.
First of all, let's start with West Pride.
What's in West Pride?
West Pride?
We don't do that kind of show.
We're not doing it.
We don't have downtown.
We don't have a bar.
It's a little different.
We have a show like that.
It's kind of like this.
It's on both shoulders.
It's like this.
But it's kind of like this.
It's kind of like this.
I see.
What's this?
I'm a little...
Here.
I just went with the flow.
I went with the flow.
I thought everything was fine.
It's like this.
I'm not going to save it.
I see.
There are various things.
But you can squeeze in a little more work.
I go out too much on New Year's Day.
I don't have time to go out on New Year's Day. It's almost morning.
And two days later...
Ah, two days later...
Downtown...
Downtown's Happy New...
Nyan Bakan!
Are you deaf?
Downtown's Happy New Nyan Bakan!
It's two days in January.
It's from 9 o'clock in the evening.
It's two hours.
And next to me...
The TV host said,
Did you watch Kaseifu?
I was doing a two-hour drama.
And next to me, the TV host said...
What was it?
The special edition of NARUHODO.
This is Nyan Bakan, after all.
It's the special edition of NARUHODO.
If I'm home, I'll watch Kaseifu.
Are you kidding me?
No, no, no.
That's a little...
No, it's just...
My Nyan Bakan has an eye.
Oh, really?
Hey!
Everyone watching the TV!
What?
Don't you want to see Machi's brother?
If you watch Nyan Bakan, you can see the two-shot of the Matsumoto brothers!
If you don't say it, I'll never understand Nyan Bakan.
No, it's not like that.
Why not?
There are about 180 of them.
This is the 182nd, right?
Right?
And you know, the two of you...
My brother came, and my brother's wife came.
And the two children came.
Two years old and one...
Three years old.
I'm here, so I'll talk to you when I'm done today.
When I got home earlier.
Two years old, you... You're not old yet, are you?
What?
I recently did a flying box in a physical education class.
Yeah.
I was angry.
Why?
Why do you have to fly something like that?
What's the use of it in the future?
It's not necessary.
That's not it.
If I say it's not necessary, that's not it.
I don't know. I don't know.
It's my role.
Why?
There are things in general life that are good to do a lot of flying boxes.
I'm just going to live my life and run like that.
There's nothing to do like this.
I'll check it out.
There's no such thing.
Wait.
No, no, no, no.
I'm going to jump over here.
Exactly.
What are you talking about?
You did it for the first time today.
I only did it once so far.
That's exactly what it is.
It's exactly what it is.
I've been talking about it all this time.
Do it about once.
I thought I was going to say something like this.
No, no, no, no.
That's what I'm saying.
I can't use it.
You often say, do you need a mathematical equation or a number equation?
I think it's necessary.
What do you mean?
That's what I'm trying to say.
What I often say is...
You do the counting, right?
You're doing something you shouldn't do, right?
I think I'm doing more and more counting.
So, then...
Doing the counting is...
It's exciting.
There's a sense of tension.
I'm going to steal someone's eye.
For example, what is it?
The price of the price.
I don't know this.
I'm going to steal it when I don't know.
And then I'll take a look at that person.
I'll never forget what I saw.
That's why it's called counting.
So, this counting...
It might be bad, but...
I'm going to remember this.
I tried to memorize it.
It's hard to remember, but...
I can't remember, but...
I stole the teacher's eye.
I don't forget what I saw.
That's why I'm going to steal the price of the price.
I'll steal it when I'm in middle school.
But that's a bad thing for me.
But there's one problem.
I can't remember the price of the price.
I don't think this is going to work.
What you're saying is...
I don't think it's going to work.
Counting...
If you can remember it by counting.
I don't think that's a bad thing.
Oh, I see.
That's right.
When you're in middle school or high school,
Don't you want to come to school?
You're the only one who gave me a score.
You don't have to show me anything.
Don't take it.
I hit you once during the exam.
No, no, no.
I was thinking like this.
I don't want to see it.
I don't want to see it, but...
If you do it like this,
The guy next to you...
I hid it.
I hit you during the exam.
I'm a fool.
Why don't you guys understand?
I hit you during the exam.
I hit you.
I'm a fool.
I don't want to see it.
I have a question for you.
There's a great catchphrase called the Lion of the Hundred Beasts.
Other animals don't have a great catchphrase.
How do you do it?
I'll tell you.
Oh, that's right.
Isn't the lion the only one who does that?
That's right.
This is discrimination.
Discrimination.
I don't think the lion is called the Lion of the Hundred Beasts.
I'm angry about that.
Do you think so?
I think so.
It's in the attitude.
If you make that face,
It's going to be that attitude.
If you do that, you're going to get nothing.
Don't worry.
I'll put the lion's head on it.
It's big, isn't it?
That's right.
Just like that.
Then you're the Lion of the Hundred Beasts.
I don't know where the lion is.
I'm the lion of the hundred beasts.
The nose is long.
It's hard to tell.
No, it's the same thing. It's big, it's long.
It's like I'm the story of this guy.
Right?
It's the lion in the story.
Yeah.
It's big, right?
That's right.
That's why I say it's long.
That's how I say it.
Neck.
It's long.
It's like a giraffe.
There's only a neck.
That's not true.
The tail is long.
The legs are long, too.
There's only a long neck.
Why do you have to say that?
That's not true.
If you say it's big, there's only an elephant.
It's big.
It's an elephant.
It's a catchphrase.
Yeah.
It's an elephant.
That's what I'm saying.
The elephant is over.
You can't just look at it and say it.
That's why you can't just look at it and say it.
There's only one way to do it.
I see.
For example,
a bongoose.
What's a bongoose?
Hey!
Huh?
What's a bongoose?
Oh, the one that looks like a snake?
The one that looks like a snake?