Watch this!
This is the first time we have a kid's show!
Chiki Chiki GENERATION!
Are you really that good?
There are a lot of GENERATION members in the entertainment world.
You're hiding it, but you're actually that good, right?
We want people to see that.
Like Okama?
Yes, Okama.
Okama this time...
I should have said Okama.
Do you know a lot of them?
Well...
Don't say it.
First, we have Mr. Kenji Nagira!
Hello!
I'm sure you know a lot of GENERATION members.
There are a lot of GENERATION members who have secrets they can't tell, right?
Yes.
I'll do my best.
Next, we have Mr. Tenmei Kano!
Hello.
Tenmei, you know a lot of things, right?
A little bit.
This time, we have Mr. Matsumoto!
Hello!
Well, I'm good at seeing things through.
I'm sure you know a lot of things.
Today, we want people to see things through.
The first question is...
This!
The actress who seems to be very good at it.
You're pretty good at it, aren't you?
You have a lot of skills, don't you?
That's what the actress said.
You're fast, Tenmei.
I'm interviewing 40 men.
These are high school students, college students, and salaried men.
Mr. Nagira, what's your answer?
Wait a minute.
What are you doing in the middle of the show?
This is Mr. Nagira's answer.
Did something happen?
It's okay.
This is...
It's a simple question, isn't it?
Mr. Nagira, what's your answer?
I don't have a lot of skills.
You have a lot of skills, don't you?
Tenmei's answer!
I've come to a ridiculous place.
Do you think Mr. Oikubo is good at it?
I'm sure he's good at it.
Actually, I really wanted to do it.
Do you want to do it, too?
I don't have a lot of skills.
Do you have a lot of skills?
I'm...
I'm a leader.
That's amazing.
I'm a switch-hitter.
Now that we've got the correct answer, let's go to the VTR.
Let's go!
Natsuki Okamoto.
Kanako Higuchi.
Rumiko Koyanagi.
Yuko Asano.
Shion Iwashita.
Shima Iwashita.
Yoko Minamino.
Rumiko Koyanagi.
Taya Sugimoto.
Minako Tanaka.
Keiko Saito.
Shima Iwashita.
Taya Sugimoto.
Natsuki Okamoto.
Rumiko Koyanagi.
Yukio Toake.
The leader of the
VTR.
Komotaro Zamurai?
What do you mean by Komotaro Zamurai?
I don't think Komotaro Zamurai is the VTR.
I know that!
Here, read it.
A moment of blankness.
What?
I shouldn't have said that.
Does it look like that?
That's what I read.
There's no way it's that strong.
Masamune-kun!
Masayuki.
Masara-ken!
I see.
Isn't that person in the back?
What could it be?
I think it's getting a little dark.
Let's just say it's the VTR.
Here we go!
Matcha?
Matcha.
Tamori?
Ryu Oshiba-san.
Ryu Oshiba?
Toshi-chan.
Hana-chan.
Matcha.
Hama-chan.
Motofu Yuki?
Tamori-san.
Ryu Oshiba?
Ryu Oshiba.
Tamori-san.
Ah, it's Tamori-san.
The VTR winner is Tamori-san!
Everyone, out!
Tamori-san is in first place.
Everyone feels that way because he's in the show.
That's why he's in third place.
Masamune-kun is in third place.
Why is that?
Kato Chia-san.
Toshi-chan.
I don't think he's in third place.
That's why he's in third place.
He's been in third place for a long time.
He has a long history.
That's why he's in third place.
Let's go.
The last question!
The last question is this!
A celebrity who looks like he's pooping!
You poop a lot when you poop!
What do you think?
Please write it down!
What kind of sound does the world make?
Mine is correct.
Let's hear it!
What kind of sound does the world make?
I know what it is!
A female actress, Mori Mitsuko-san,
doesn't look like she's pooping.
It's because she's been in the show for a long time.
Tenmei-san.
It's common sense.
Morio-san.
He looks like he's going to poop a lot.
I can tell.
Masamune-kun.
Wink?
Which one is it?
Which one of them looks like he's going to poop a lot?
Machiro-san, stop putting them together.
The answer is this!
Nagira Kenichi.
Niko Takeshi.
Wada Akiko-san.
Hamano-san.
Nishikawa Norio.
Hama-chan.
Danpu Matsumoto.
Akiko.
Tamori.
Matcha.
Danpu Matsumoto-san.
Tsurutaro.
Takada Junji.
Nishikawa Norio.
Matcha.
Matsumoto-san.
Nishikawa Norio.
Unexpectedly, it's Matcha.
Hamada-san.
It's Matcha.
He's going to poop a lot!
It's Matsumoto-san!
By the way, first place is Matsumoto-kun,
second place is Nishikawa Norio-san.
And fifth place is...
Tokoro-san, Nagira-san, me,
and Mori Kumiko-san.
Mori Kumiko-san.
No way!
And Yoshida-san is on the left and I'm on the right.
Today, I'm talking to the two boys from Kumigaki.
It's me!
When is this broadcast?
It's on the 30th.
Ah!
So, the 24-hour television is over.
You know,
the 24-hour television,
the voice of love saves the earth.
If the 24-hour television is over,
then later...
You can't say that in the town.
I was going to say it normally.
I was surprised because you said it in such a place.
This is after it's over.
What?
So, after the 24-hour television is over,
the voice of love saves the earth.
Yes, that's right.
It's amazing.
What?
You said it as you planned.
My eyes are open.
Why?
Are you crying?
I don't understand.
I'm crying.
You said it before that.
Why are you crying now?
But I want to do it a week ago.
I'm already crying.
Liar!
I don't want to cry.
I don't understand.
You know,
especially you,
you always look like
you are in a bad mood.
But you, Hamada,
you cry easily.
You cry easily.
You are a fool.
You too.
He is a fool.
Wait a minute.
He is a fool when he talks.
It's a title.
He is a fool.
It's a big story.
When we had a concert,
when we had a concert for the first time,
we just sang a song.
That's all.
It wasn't a disbanding concert.
It was just a normal concert.
Let me tell you.
When the ending song was over,
you cried like this.
No, no, no.
That was
when I saw you
when I was about to sing the last song.
You were like this.
When I saw your face,
I was like this.
You were crying like this.
You.
You have to say it properly.
When I cried,
I was like this.
You were like this.
You were crying like this.
But when you cried,
and I cried,
for a while,
I felt like I was relieved.
This guy.
When this guy came,
he was crying like this.
When I said,
thank you for your hard work,
he was pooping right away.
At that time,
I wondered what a disbanding concert was like.
I thought so.
I admit that.
But I don't know if you're going to destroy it in 24 hours.
Like the old Triathlon.
We're the only ones laughing.
We did a program with Shinsuke, right?
We did.
There's a triathlon, right?
There's a triathlon in Miyakojima.
There was.
From our program,
one of our young members
recruited a middle-aged man with a car.
That's the guy who appeared in Triathlon.
The two guys in the car
trained for a long time.
The training was broadcast for half an hour.
The training scene was broadcast,
and it was followed by the documentary.
That's right.
Right?
It's the same as Mr. Ike.
Mr. Ike.
Mr. Ike said,
do your best.
Mr. Ike swam all the time.
Swam and switched to a bicycle.
This time it's a marathon.
Full marathon.
32.195 km.
We swam all the time.
And Mr. Ike...
What?
He came in.
To the last goal.
It was the finale of half an hour.
I'm sorry.
If it had been a few hours later,
it would have been out.
That's right.
And Mr. Ike.
Mr. Ike.
Mr. Ike came.
Mr. Ike came running from the other side.
This is the goal.
It's taping.
If you cut the tape,
it's already a goal.
There are a lot of other people crying.
Mr. Ike.
Everyone is cheering.
Hamada is also together.
Mr. Ike, this way, this way.
Mr. Ike, do your best.
I cut the tape on my back.
What did you do for half an hour?
Then I went back to the hotel and pooped.
I'm scared.
But maybe 24 hours.
What about that?
If everyone takes it to me.
What?
I'll get it too.
Well, that's okay.
I wonder if I'll get it.
I don't have a fax machine.
I've had it before.
I took a phone call.
Agnes was talking on the phone.
Agnes, where are you?
I've been in Japan for more than 20 years.
I'm still in Katakuta.
Agnes is a cowardly name.
Why?
I want to call her out, but I can't.
Agnes.
I think it's a little cowardly.
What did you say?
Do we have a place to receive it?
I think so.
I'm waiting at Bodokan.
That's right.
I shake hands with her.
Thank you.
I'll be honest with you.
There are a lot of handshakes.
It's creepy.
That's right.
I don't want to hold her hand.
It's scary.
She's sticky.
We're the only ones who wear gloves.
People who wear gloves will know.
It's creepy.
That's why I have gloves.
People who wear gloves will know.
This is the end of the sleeves.
It looks like a long sleeve.
At least I have a dress.
Why?
Why do you have to change your clothes according to your gloves?
I'm going to drink a little wine.
I'm wearing a dress.
I'm wearing a T-shirt with a size of 74.
It's strange to wear gloves like this.
If we have a show like this, I want to make it.
I've been thinking about that.
There is a program that only people who have seen the show can understand.
After all, I don't think it's good to joke around like that,
in the midst of a charity program like this.
You said something like,
I can't work 24 hours a day,
so I can't do it.
I don't feel like that on a charity program like this.
You're really going to kill me, aren't you?
Even if you kill me, even if you kill me,
I won't do it.
Because on a charity program like this,
you're going to kill me, aren't you?
You're wrong.
The manager above me came to me first.
He said,
I can't do this much.
How old are you?
Oh, I see.
But I'm not that old.
Really?
But this time, I'm going to do it properly.
That's right.
In the middle of this, I'm going to eat gum and become Kase Taishu.
I'm a little upset about that commercial.
No, no.
If you think about it, you're already back.
I'm already back.
That's right.
That's not me.
When I was back,
I didn't think about anything.
I was doing what I was told to do.
I saw the airing.
What?
Do you know when I'm back?
I'm desperate to eat more.
That's a good idea.
It's really a martial art.
That's...
That's really rude.
That's not a little...
It's a little bad, isn't it?
Well, that's...
I want to become Kase Taishu.
If I can, I want to see it for about a day.
Really?
Yes.
If you become Kase Taishu,
You often say you're a man, don't you?
They do whatever they want.
Is that true?
If you go with that kind of look,
I think it's going to be like that.
First of all, there's a breakaway.
Isn't it refreshing?
Your face is...
Isn't it fresh?
Breakaway?
After all, it's a breakaway.
Why is it like this?
It must have stopped at this point.
It's a terrible story.
After all, we don't know.
180?
There's about 180.
There's more.
But it's just a story here.
It's not just a story here.
It's a serious story.
A man who is over 180.
Something's wrong.
I'm sorry.
Really.
That's how you say it.
If you think hard about something,
It won't grow that much.
If you think normally, you don't think about anything.
That's a beautiful thing.
The light is back.
I have a question for you.
When you're breathing, sometimes from your nose.
What the hell is this?
That's true.
Normally.
There are times when I'm breathing normally.
And then I think I'm breathing right now.
There are times when I'm breathing.
I've done it many times.
Thank you.
I wonder why.
This is probably...
When you add it to a million power.
Who?
You.
Why didn't you add it to a million power?
For what?
When the energy.
When it reaches a million power.
Who are you?
Energy is a million power.
What do you mean?
My arms are moving.
I can't move here.
I'll ask you.
When it reaches a million power.
I'm a normal human being.
You're normal human beings, too.
When the energy reaches a million power.
When it reaches a million power.
There's a signal.
A signal?
You're charging now.
I haven't been charged for a long time.
That's because you've been working too hard.
I haven't received any signal recently.
That's because you're taking out the energy.
Sometimes.
That's right.
Because I'm taking out the energy.
I see.
It's the same as a electrical device.
When you charge it, the red light turns green in a few hours.
It's the same as that green light.
It's a warning.
You're telling me that my arms are a million power.
It's full right now.
But when I'm tired from the cold.
I sometimes say,
Sometimes.
It's not like you're making the same sound.
That's energy.
I've been charged.
Listen to what happened in Osaka a little while ago.
When I took a taxi in Osaka, they gave me tissue paper.
I thought Osaka was a terrible city.
And the next day, I took a different taxi.
And then they gave me ume jintan.
Why do they give you so many things in Osaka taxi?
That's right.
What about Osaka?
Osaka taxi service.
The driver's attitude is the same.
The service is alive.
The service is amazing.
It's alive.
As you can see, they gave me tissue paper, ume jintan, green jintan.
That's right.
And...
But they gave me a lot of things.
That area is really alive.
Tokyo is tough.
But who said that?
Takahashi-san or someone else said that.
That's right.
In the past, the service was a problem.
In the middle of the night,
I felt really sick.
I couldn't breathe.
I was so sick that I thought I was going to die.
And it was too much to call an ambulance.
It was embarrassing to call an ambulance in the middle of the night.
So I called a taxi.
I got in the taxi.
I was so sick that I thought I was going to die.
At that time, the taxi driver said,
Takahashi-san, please.