Next, the Suki-Kiraito Pioneeent!
You're a heavyweight, aren't you?
Don't you feel like you're going to make an enemy?
You?
No, in many ways.
It says Suki-Kiraito, and it's up to number 7.
And there are seven for you.
Seven, right?
From A to G. And there are seven for me too.
We'll put them on randomly.
We'll stick them on like this.
And among them, there's the famous talent.
So it's not our will.
It's not our will?
If you stick them on randomly, you'll end up hating them.
And now, the winner.
What's the winner?
I don't know what the winner is.
Let's give him a round of applause.
What?
I really wanted to do it myself.
Seriously, seriously.
What?
It's stuck.
Let's see how much you hate them.
Okay.
Here I go.
Why do you hate them?
Because they're gross.
It's all the way up to here.
When I put my hand out like this,
it reminds me of Chinese food.
Suki.
You like sweet things.
How do you like Suki?
Do you think I'll do it?
A little bit.
Are you stupid?
Why do I hate them?
You're the one who hates them.
When I said it on TV,
I thought it was a bit harsh.
You're a good person.
I'm really a good person.
Really?
I'm just a person who says what I think clearly.
I've never heard Oe Senri sing before.
He said,
Oe, this sound is off.
It's like this.
It's a mess.
In the meantime, Oe was really depressed.
What do you like?
It's a mess.
Where?
I've never even talked to you.
You're bullying animals.
You don't even like them.
It's amazing that you can say that.
What?
I often say that there are no bad people in people who like animals.
It's just a story that I really like.
I hate you.
What do you call it?
It's selfish.
You're more selfish than selfish.
I'm talking about him.
It's selfish.
What do you call it?
It's a mess.
As a human being,
He's already 29 years old.
What do you call it?
Do you call it a distinction?
Do you call it morality?
Do you call it common sense?
It's empty.
Then it's my turn.
Takeda Tetsuya is the image of Mr. Kinpachi.
I still have that image.
Mr. Kinpachi and Takeda Tetsuya have a big gap.
What is that?
The real gap is big.
That's not a bad word.
I'm going to change my hairstyle.
Do you hate your hair?
It's not human.
I'm going to change my hairstyle.
You have a wide width.
Your hair is flowing nicely.
This part.
It's refreshing.
It's a grayish style.
It's fashionable to wear red.
I see.
Let's go.
What do you hate about this?
You're bullying the cast.
I don't know.
I don't know if it's okay to write a weekly magazine.
But when I look at it from the outside, I think,
What kind of person is this person?
I think so.
You don't like magazines, do you?
I don't like magazines.
I hate it in that sense.
Let's go to the person you hate.
I really hate this.
What are you saying?
I've hated it since the era of high socks.
I don't think it's the era of high socks.
That's a lie.
It's okay to die in the sun on the hill.
The lyrics don't matter.
It doesn't matter.
This person has been in the industry for more than 20 years.
Don't take my hate.
I don't know what you're talking about.
How long have you been in the industry?
I don't know if you're a doctor or something.
That's exactly right.
What I like most about him is his hairstyle.
What do you call it?
It's like a movie theater.
Do you think so?
But his Japanese is good.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Agnes, I'm sorry.
Why are you so honest?
I'm just kidding.
Why are you so desperate?
I just wanted you to laugh.
I'm sorry.
What should we talk about?
I bought an interesting story.
Did you win?
Whose story is interesting?
Daisuke Hanako's story.
Daibou really loves Hanako.
He really loves her.
There are two new boys.
They're called Pinocchio.
I've heard of them.
I don't know much about them.
There's a boy named Chambara Torio.
He has other students.
Pinocchio is one of them.
Daisuke Hanako and Pinocchio are brothers.
Their relationship is very bad.
But they're beautiful.
Pinocchio and Daisuke Hanako went out to drink.
Daibou went home.
Only Hanako went out to drink with Pinocchio.
Pinocchio and Hanako broke up at 12 o'clock.
Hanako likes alcohol.
Pinocchio went home.
Hanako didn't come back.
Why?
I don't know.
If I'm not funny, I'll be bad.
Daibou knows about Pinocchio.
Of course, he's Pinocchio.
The next day, Daibou is like a super saiyan.
He's like a super saiyan.
Next day, Pinocchio came to the school.
He said, good morning.
The other guys knew that Daibou was gone, so they said,
Run away Pinocchio!
It's like a character.
Why did you run away?
That's right.
I don't know.
If that's the case, then Daibou will do this,
and Pinocchio will do that.
Yes, yes, yes.
I think that's Hana-chan's trick.
She's mistaken.
Yes.
Then Hana-chan will grab his shoulder,
and do this!
What did you do to my Hana-chan?
And then,
she hit him like this.
Pinocchio's partner,
was about to leave,
and he was waiting at the stage.
Pinocchio's partner?
What happened?
He hit him.
He went up to the stage,
and when he looked up,
he was Super Saiyan.
Where did Pinocchio go?
Hey!
He was like a brother to him.
Daiseki!
What did you do to my partner?
He grabbed him like this.
Then Daiseki,
this guy,
scratched my Hana-chan.
He scratched her because she was sexy.
Then Pinocchio's partner,
will do that!
That's what they say.
I don't know where Hana-chan went after all.
I don't know either.
Daigo really loves Hana-chan.
He loves her.
It's a difficult place.
Ah,
you've become a jet ski guy again.
That's right.
You've never been across the sea, have you?
You haven't even been to the sea recently.
What are you doing?
Ah, I forgot about that movie.
Forget it!
Ah, but he's good at surfing.
Surfing.
I took him to the hospital a long time ago.
He can also dive.
Scuba?
What?
That was a light answer.
Scuba.
I've been around the world a lot,
and I've dived a lot.
Which sea was the best?
Where did you dive?
I think it was...
the west coast.
The west coast?
Nairu River.
Wait a minute.
You took me to Nairu River.
Nairu River.
Do you think it's Nairu River?
I don't think so.
You took me to Nairu River.
I think so.
That's no good.
You're kidding.
Which was the best?
You know,
I've dived a lot in the sea.
The most beautiful thing was...
the Japan Sea.
The Japan Sea was the most beautiful.
I've been to New York.
I've been to Egypt.
Egypt?
You've been to Egypt?
I'm sorry, I was too early.
We're not talking about scuba diving.
I thought we were talking about scuba diving.
Show me how to do it.
The way to dive?
Show me the way to dive.
There's an oxygen bomb there.
In the middle of the ship.
The oxygen bomb is around there.
What?
You can't use it?
I'll use it.
You can't use it.
It's scuba diving.
It's not scuba diving.
You can use the oxygen bomb like this.
Like this.
Like this?
Yes.
And then?
And then you can dive.
What?
You can dive like this?
There are people who say that.
I've never seen it.
Interesting.
Show me some signs.
When you dive.
What do you mean by a sign that it's dangerous?
For example, a shark is coming.
I can see it from here.
I have to tell it.
A shark?
That means a shark is coming from the other side.
Yes.
I have to tell it.
What do you do?
I look at it like this.
I can't tell its face.
Now everyone says it's easy to tell.
It's hard to tell.
You were too nervous.
Too nervous.
I'm smiling.
I think it's a shark.
You think so?
I can't tell its face.
I have to tell it.
There's a sign.
I can't tell its face.
It's a little far away.
I have to tell it.
Where is the shark?
What?
Here.
The shark is coming.
It's swimming.
I have to tell it.
Who is it?
It's that guy.
He said no.
Come here.
Your face is red.
Why did you say no?
My partner.
Do you have a partner?
Are you aiming for an entertainer?
I have a lot of friends.
We know that you've decided.
I'm wearing a jacket with a hood.
A jacket with a hood?
We don't usually wear this.
The friends from earlier because we went together linked to force.
So, I've been forced to do it.
Why have you been forced to do it?
How did you manage it?
You're getting more and more rich.
You were also forced to do it, so I Words go out.
It can't be helped.
And then I thought you were golden.
They're already juniors.
That was Tsukumi Ota.
When a dog stumbles, it clings to human legs and shakes its hips.
What kind of psychological state is that?
What is the best way to calm it down?
Like this.
It's amazing.
If you leave it like that, it will stick here.
It comes out like this.
Ah, it comes out like this, white thing.
If you take that and put it somewhere, it will be something.
I think it will be fun if more things are done like that.
Like this, it sticks like this, and if you put this on the morning face, it will be morning face.
It would be funny if it was like that.
It would be funny.
But if they were the same animals, they wouldn't be able to do anything well.
What do you mean by anything?
They wouldn't be able to mate an elephant and a dog.
There would be a lot of animals.
But if they mate with a big animal, they would be able to take over the body.
That's not true.
If a male dog mates with a female elephant, it would be born from a female elephant.
But if a female elephant mates with a male dog, it would be born from a female elephant.
If a female dog mates with a male elephant, it would be born from a female elephant.
That's not true.
Why?
It would be born from a male elephant.
But if a female dog mates with a male elephant, it would be born from a female dog.
What do you mean by anything?
I'm saying the same thing.
It would be born from a male dog.
But if a female dog mates with a male dog, it would be born from a female dog.
What?
It would be born from a female cat.
What are you talking about?
If a female dog mates with a male elephant, it would be born from a female dog.
It would be born from a female dog.
That's right.
That's enough.
I'm done.
There are people who wear hoodies, but I've never seen people wearing hoodies.
When do you wear hoodies?
Wait a minute. The reason why I'm telling you this is because I don't recognize it.
What?
The hoodies you wear.
Why?
That's absolutely unnecessary.
I wear it when it's cold.
I'm asking if you can survive the cold when you wear it.
It's warm. I'm wearing it all. It's warm.
It covers the visible part.
That's right.
It's warmer than not wearing it.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about a female dog.
What?
What are you talking about?
Do you know what a female dog looks like?
Tell me about the female dog you drew on your head.
Tell me.
What are you talking about?
What's the size of a female dog?
What?
It's about this big.
That's a female dog.
There's a difference between a male dog and a female dog.
I drew a female dog.
What about ears?
What?
It's about this big.
It's about the size of a female dog.
This is a human figure.
What are you talking about?
It's about the size of a female dog.
What's wrong with the nose?
The nose is wet.
This is a dog.