Today, we are going to visit the house of Team Zero, Noriyasu Yamazaki, who is the host of our program.
I heard that he moved to the house of Team Zero.
It's been two weeks.
But I don't live in a place where I don't think I'm Japanese.
Today, we are going to move to the house of Team Zero.
That's right. We can't do anything, but we thought hard about the present for Team Zero.
So today, I'm going to tell you about the present.
I'm calling you today.
Teacher, how is it?
Nice to meet you.
My junior moved today.
He lives in a terrible place.
I see.
If you don't have a present, let's do it.
Let's do it.
This program is brought to you by the sponsor you are watching.
Hello.
I heard that you moved.
I brought a present.
A cake.
Thank you.
Let's do it.
Let's eat.
Yamazaki, don't stop.
I heard that you moved today.
I brought a present.
A cake.
Thank you.
Let's do it.
Let's eat.
Yamazaki, don't stop.
I heard that you moved today.
I'm interested in the direction of the house where I moved.
That's right.
In the real world, there are many famous people.
I want you to tell me the direction of the house and if there is anything in the house.
Really?
Teacher, please come in.
Teacher.
What is this room?
This is the room where I moved.
This is a terrible room.
What?
This is terrible.
Is it terrible?
What?
Are you crying?
I'm surprised.
I'm serious.
If this happens, I won't be able to leave the theater.
Are you serious?
This is not good.
What?
Everyone is following me.
This is terrible.
Everyone is silent.
I don't like this.
But, arrested people are like that.
Listen to me, properly.
Teacher, don't you trust me?
I don't trust you.
But, in reality,
someone is dick-headed.
You are crazy.
What?
Don't be mad.
Sit down.
Yes.
I will be righteous.
You are right.
We wanted to have fun.
Do you want to quit?
It's not just fun.
Shit.
I really did.
I don't have time for that.
I'm a genius!
Thank you very much.
Good luck.
We'll do the rest.
That was good.
It's all thanks to you.
We're all making money.
It's true.
Thank you.
Let's go to Ise.
This will make peace.
It's the morning of peace.
I won!
Yamazaki.
Congratulations.
This is crazy.
Yamazaki.
You're the one who's going to write.
That's where you're supposed to be.
Let's leave.
Bye.
You'll be a prisoner the next season.
Let's meet again in an hour.
Make it clean.
Goodbye.
I'll be back with you.
I'll be back next week.
I'll be back three weeks in a row.
Don't be silly.
Let's go.
It was a lot of fun at the opening today.
What do you call that?
We've been doing it on this board.
We haven't been on location that often.
It was a lot of fun.
But there was one more thing.
I wanted to do something like,
I love you at the door.
That's what I wanted to do.
That's what you wanted to do.
That's what I couldn't do.
I want you to see this.
But the staff here are really bad.
I'm really bad at it.
When the fireworks went off,
I was really satisfied.
What is this mayonnaise?
Mayonnaise. Mayonnaise.
What am I supposed to do?
I'm going to throw it all out.
That's a little weird.
After that, it would be nice to have some vegetables.
I want to cut it so it's easy to eat.
I think it's okay to throw this in.
But sometimes,
What do you call that?
I can't teach you how scary your seniors are.
But I did a lot.
What?
Today.
Well, I did it today.
I think I did a lot.
You can't be strict with your seniors.
Really?
Oh, I was so angry the other day.
I went to my manager.
What do you call that?
That's too much.
He's an idiot.
That's not funny.
Well, the other day,
We had a party.
I like the staff of Yume.
I went to karaoke.
After I went to Meiji-kun.
When I went to karaoke,
I drank a lot of alcohol.
I'm a pretty strong person.
But that day was amazing.
It was amazing.
I said, yeah!
With that face and that outfit.
I sang Rebecca's Friends.
When Moonwalk came out,
I thought Nitta was coming.
But when I noticed, Nitta wasn't there.
I was wondering where he was.
I left him alone.
The manager, Tamura-kun.
Nitta was down there.
I couldn't go.
You really wanted to go.
Really?
I had to go see him.
Matsumoto-san, don't go.
Why?
He said, why?
I'll go.
Don't go. Please.
Why?
I understand.
If you say that much,
It's okay to go.
Don't get angry.
Why would I get angry?
I don't get angry.
This is breaking.
I don't get angry because I know you're drunk.
I don't get angry.
I'm serious.
Don't get angry.
I know.
I got out of the car.
I was shocked.
You were shocked.
What is it? What is it?
That looks good too.
Look at my Kamaro's bonnet.
It has Nitta's shoulder.
Do you want to see it later?
I was so angry.
Nitta opened her eyes.
I was wondering if she would apologize.
She said, I slept well.
You slept again.
You slept again with someone else's bonnet.
It feels good.
She is quiet in front of me.
But when I'm with her, she is quite reckless.
When we are with her, she suddenly talks.
She talks a lot.
That's good.
I'm afraid of the power of alcohol.
What do you do with white vinegar?
After eating it?
If there is something like that.
I eat it a lot.
You can eat it with a toothpick.
I don't eat that.
It's disgusting to put back something that came out of your mouth.
At that time, I put it in my mouth.
But if it comes out of my mouth, I eat it.
If it comes out of my toothpick, I eat it.
I eat it as a small dinner.
You eat it as a small dinner.
I'm really hungry.
Really?
I slept a while ago.
I was sleepy.
Let's sing a lullaby.
You are good at singing.
I'm going to hit you.
Don't hit me.
That was a lullaby.
Don't sleep.
I thought so.
There is no one who sleeps during the show.
You are like a cat.
Really?
Let me touch you.
Meow.
Why are you like a cat?
That's strange.
You are like a pigeon.
Let me touch you.
Why?
Why can't I sing a lullaby?
The other day, I went to Tokyo Station.
There was a strange person.
He had a crash on his head.
When I came to him,
I asked him to be my disciple.
Please be my disciple.
Please.
I've been rejected by many people.
Don't do that.
I want to be a good disciple.
This time of the year is a lot.
I see.
I can't get a job or a new school.
What should I do?
I know that you are watching us.
You are longing for a star.
I understand.
You are taking a picture.
I'm not taking a picture.
No one is here.
Why are you being so cautious?
I'm not taking a picture.
Please write a letter.
Hama-chan.
You wanted an English lesson, so here I am.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
What did you say?
Well.
You talked about our sponsor.
Yes.
I didn't say anything.
You didn't say anything?
Yes.
This is Jiyo-san.
She speaks English.
Yes.
She's doing this on purpose.
If you say you won't do anything, I'll bring her here.
Please greet me in English.
Please say something.
In English.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
I speak fast, so I understand.
What are you talking about?
No, no, no.
Speak slowly.
I understand, but I speak fast.
Please say something in English to me.
You can speak Japanese?
Yes.
Your eye makeup is a bit tight.
What are you talking about?
Can I ask you something?
I know most of it.
Where are you from?
Oh.
What?
I don't know.
Give it back.
What?
I don't know.
I just know.
You're stupid.
Give it back.
One more time.
Yes.
Where are you from?
Where are you?
Who told you to repeat?
Speak slowly.
Where did you come from?
I didn't ask you where you came from.
I just wanted to know where the star lives.
You're a victim.
Speak slowly.
I don't understand, but I understand what you said.
Nice to meet you.
Yes.
If you're a white student like this, this is what it means.
What?
Like this.
Yes.
If you don't hold it hard, it'll be like this.
I see.
Nice to meet you.
This is from Ibaraki.
This is from Hama-chan.
Hello, Hama-chan.
I enjoy watching your show every week.
Hama-chan is left-handed, right?
Did you know that the life of a left-handed person is 9 years shorter than that of a right-handed person?
When I was watching TV at night, I was told that the life of a left-handed person is shorter.
I wanted to let you know right away, so I wrote it down.
But it's not too late.
If you want to live long, let's be right-handed right now.
I heard this, too.
Really?
It's 9 years early.
You're going to die?
Yes.
A left-handed person is smarter.
Really?
They use their left brain, so they're smarter.
They use their right brain, so they're smarter.
Don't make fun of me.
Are you right-handed?
You're more stupid than me.
They use their right brain, so they're smarter.
Really?
If you follow this pattern, I'll die sooner.
That's true.
You're a left-handed person.
You live 9 years longer than me.
Really?
That's a lot.
That's how it is calculated.
That means you have more sadness than I do.
What are you talking about?
What if I die 9 years later?
9 years is not a big deal.
What if I die when I'm 37?
It's not a big deal.
I won't have a wife or children when I die.
There's nothing to do.
That's it.
But if you die in a few days, you'll think about it, won't you?
In a few days?
If it's 3 days, it's not a big deal.
If it's 3 days, I can do what I want to do.
Really?
I can do that.
First of all, I eat a lot of delicious food on the first day.
You eat a lot of delicious food.
You're poor, so you don't know.
You're poor, too.
I'm really poor.
But I have more money than you.
I have a lot of money.
I have more money.
I had a microwave.
I didn't have a microwave.
I had a steam iron.
I had a pressure cooker.
I had a microwave.
I don't have a microwave.
I'm sorry. I lied.
What?
I told you, but when I get home, I put cold barley tea in the refrigerator.
It doesn't matter.
Everyone does that in the summer.
You didn't have a microwave, did you?
I had a microwave.
Did you take coffee milk and milk properly?
I bought it and took coffee milk and milk.
Really?
Did you take Yakult?
Yakult is for children.
Why?
I don't know.
Did you take vanilla essence?
You didn't take it, did you?
I didn't take anything, but I took vanilla essence.
Why do you have it?
I had a snowy uniform.
Always?
Always.
Why did you go to the bathhouse?
You don't even have a bath.
You didn't take a bath before you got married.
You didn't go to the floor of my house like you did.
You didn't run like a mouse when you ate.
I was hungry, so I didn't have any food to eat.
Thank you.
Don't cry.
You gave me a donut when I had a day off.
I was so upset when you said you would give me a donut.
Good evening, Mr. Hamada.
I saw you on TV at Nisei Academy.
You went to a great school.
You were the vice principal.
Can you tell me about that time?
It's a normal school now.
It's not like that anymore.
You have long hair and you dress normally.
It's completely different from what we used to do.
You've been going to the dormitory for a long time, so you don't know anything about the world.
It's really interesting to see you when you come back from time to time.
I was surprised.
I went to school for the first time in six months.
I went home and played.
I was watching a singing show with you.
I was surprised to see you.
Why is your face so dark?
He's like that.
I was wondering what he was doing.
I was surprised to see you with a fresh face.
Hey!
You have three colors!
I often hear the word explosion in the news program.
I was surprised to see you explode.
It happens once in a lifetime, doesn't it?
Explosion!
I don't care about that.
You have too many colors.
It's the same as King's.
King's?
Who are you?
Hello.
This is the neon tube I used in the previous set of this program.
This is all I have.
You didn't come to get this, did you?
It was a condition that I would definitely come to get it.
I'll give you a prize today.
I definitely want an electric sign.
It's not an electric sign, is it?
It's a neon sign.
I guess so.
What is this?
You called me without saying anything.
That's right.
I got it.
You called me.
I see.
This is Higashi Nobuhiko-kun in Chiba Prefecture.
Or Yasugi Kiyoshi-kun.
You're nervous now, aren't you?
That's right.
That's how you did it.
Suzuki Miki-chan, 17 years old, from Matsudoshi.
Let's give it to her.
Shall we?
Yes.
Suzuki Miki-chan, this is for you.
Please come to get the neon tube.
Congratulations.
We're going to do a game of dodgeball with 500 people versus 500 people.
The losing team will have to play a penalty game.
We're looking for a penalty game.
What does that mean?
A penalty game with 500 people.
If you have an idea, please send it to us.
And so on.
I'm not going to use you as a kid.
Only next year.
Please.
That's right.
Thank you.