Last week, during a fake comedy show, Hamada was attacked by an unidentified person.
The two-shot footballer, Minoeva, and his five friends were killed.
It's my fault!
Who are you?
Hamada's
The two-shot footballer, Minoeva, and his five friends were killed.
The recording was stopped, and everyone was left in the corner.
But...
I think I won.
Really?
The double-edged sword Kobori is attacking himself, saying he might have kicked Hamada.
He shows no sign of depression.
And Kobori is alone, in fear, he goes to Hamada's dressing room.
If you lick it, it's bitter.
If you lick it, it's scary.
Stop it.
Are you angry?
I'm not angry.
If you're not angry, why are you hitting me like that?
Next, the footballer, Iwao, also goes to Hamada's dressing room.
If you lick it, it's a half.
It's a lie.
Hamada went to the three people who were left in the dressing room.
I'm not a thief!
You're a thief!
If you lick me, I'll be red.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
The prank was a huge success.
But this is not the end.
Everyone, we have finished the first part.
Now everyone will be the main character.
Now, the two karate guys will come.
And this time, Masamasa will be the main character.
Everyone, please act properly.
I'll help you.
This scary prank will be done by Matsumoto.
The Young Lady Prank, Karateka!
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Karate guy appears without knowing anything.
And now he meets with other young people who are watching the show.
He joins the show with the license of Yamasaki and Kokoriko.
After this, he shows the show full of impact in the dressing room.
Dave Spector is also ready.
OK.
Finally, the real show of the fake comparison.
Now, we will start the special tag match of the 2005 comedy competition.
abercrack the underdog Kurt Niffs
Ha Ha Ha Poise!!
next we have the coming golden boy called Young Generation's
Hahahaha
センセー cursed
The judge of this game is the lip gorilla of the referee world, Banten Hamada!
Yeah!
How about you, Iwami?
Now, my turn!
Here we go!
I can't lose!
Yo yo yo yo yo!
Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
I'm the champion!
I'm going to eat you!
Let's start the game.
Now, both teams will be given a bouquet.
Here you go.
Fight with pride, teacher!
Stop it!
You can't do anything here!
Who is it?
Don't make a scene here!
You...
Sorry, sorry.
Hey, Suwako.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I don't understand.
Please go to the dressing room.
I'll talk to you later.
It's so hot in here.
Let's go back to the dressing room.
Thank you.
The first two people were in a weird mood because of the heat.
They were like, oh, we've done this.
It was a bit hot.
This isn't a prank, it's probably a prank.
I think so.
Meanwhile, the young people are going back to the dressing room.
Karateka, who suddenly froze up, is already completely naked.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy that I brought my flowers.
It's like a solo concert.
At first, it wasn't funny.
But it started and it became even more funny.
I think it was a beautiful feeling.
From the beginning.
I don't think it's a good idea to say that you didn't go to the first meeting.
I think it's like a place where you don't know who you are.
Can I go in?
I'm not going to be able to go in.
No, no, no.
I'm sorry, but...
Wow, this is tough.
Only the two of them are running.
They're sitting down.
These guys are totally out of it.
You guys are not standing here.
I wonder if this is really cut.
I'm sorry.
You should have done it properly.
This is effective.
I thought it was a unicorn.
What are you doing?
I'm interested in the flowers.
This one is like a flower.
All of us are like this.
That's right.
I'm leaning on Kouji-san's back.
Kouji-san is leaning on me.
It's better to go.
Yamasaki and Kokoriko head to the youth room.
And they are going to chase after the target, Karate-ka.
What did you want to do at the door-to-home?
I went first and then everyone else went and I was told to go to the mic.
EI?
It was a performance.
Then Hama-san said,
I went to the Hanataka Sotei.
I didn't say anything.
Who kicked me with a stick?
Wow, this is strong.
I can't hear the sound of a person.
Someone pushed me and my knee was in.
Knee?
My knee was pushed.
Pushed?
Yes, pushed.
I don't know who it is.
Maybe.
Hamada went to the hospital and he said,
I shouldn't have licked it.
I don't know what to say.
I heard it earlier.
I think it's a bit too much.
He said that it was a tiger.
This is the last chance to surprise Matsumoto.
Meanwhile, Hamada heads to Wakadestache's room.
What will be the fate of Karateka?
What's going on?
What do you mean, I don't know.
I'm talking.
I'm angry, but I don't know what's going on.
I think it's a molly.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
Did you do something?
It's probably a self-introduction of the tiger.
I think it's called,
What?
Ah yes, oh yes, I'm Irie.
I'm Irie.
The one who introduced the Japanese language was the tiger.
Ah, is that so?
It's called Irie.
It's a word for Irie.
Ah, is that so?
The tiger was quite cute.
I don't know if I lick it.
The tiger is cute.
How did you put the tiger's face?
I was wearing a mask.
It was me.
Oh, you guys?
Yes.
You guys are different.
Yes, it was me.
Which one of you hit him?
I hit him.
Oh, it was you.
Someone was holding him.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Who was holding him?
I don't know.
Is there anyone in here?
You?
I didn't push it.
I was just looking at it thinking it would be better if I didn't push it.
Someone pushed it, right?
Yes.
Who pushed it?
You?
What's wrong?
I just saw it.
I don't know.
I was saying it earlier.
Yes.
Chan.
What's wrong with me?
It's okay.
It means you hit me.
Yes.
Come here.
So, this is the situation.
It's not a problem.
Come here.
I went with you.
Please shake hands.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
See you.
Will this go into the recording?
No more spinblade
Conf Intense
reveals his true self
If I lick it, I'm wifi
I'm scared of the
long hair
I'm scared of the long hair
Yabu-chan
Eh?
Abe-san...
Abe-chan, don't say that.
It's a prank.
A prank.
Everyone but you knew?
Everyone knew?
Even Genju-san?
Yes.
That's right.
Wow!
I'm really scared. I thought we were going to break up.
Let's go to the other room.
There's no difference.
Meanwhile, the other party's Irie is nervous and speechless.
The next day, Matsumoto was...
I'm going to kill you!
You!
Don't lick me!
I'm done with the first one.
I'm scared.
What's wrong?
Don't be angry.
I was so scared!
What should I do?
It's here!
I was like, what is this?
I didn't know anything and I was so excited!
Who was it again?
Aoi!
I'm sorry.
Next time on Gajiro Tsukai Arai, Chikishiki's summer holiday Yamachan presents, Go! Shiodome Jambari!
This time, there is a word to describe this Shiodome.
Ready, set, go!
Utaka!
Uchaka is a word that is used in Shiodome.
Makiwara-san is making a song called Uchaka.
Maki?
Maki.
Oh, Maki.
Can you play it for us?
Uchaka.
Yes.
Amazing.
Uchaka.
Really?
Yes.
You didn't do the dance.
It's impossible.
It's sudden, right?
I should have done it in advance.
I was a bit irritated by the staff.
Yamazaki, you're embarrassing me!
I'm sorry.
Go! Shiodome Jamboree Unchaka is held in Tokyo Shiodome until August 31st.
Starting with the special booth of the popular TV show, special events are held.
And the first member to visit is...
What do you call this?
It's cute.
I'm not happy.
Happy Zubi.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I don't remember anything.
And I have the contents of Happy Zubi.
Last year, I was in the end.
I was in the end.
I was in the end last year, so I'll be in the end this year again.
I'll do it.
It's fine.
Is it funny?
I want to see the senior's mountain climbing.
Do you enter from here?
Yes, I enter from here.
Be more excited than usual!
Yes.
Do you know the rhythm of Samba?
Do it seriously.
Do it, Shinkoku!
Here I go!
1, 2, 3!
Shinkoku, Shinkoku!
Ah, it's so cold.
It's bad for the end but you couldn't look directly.
I'm going to hate you, Chan.
Ichiro walks around the venue and goes to the next booth.
What's this?
This is Fuji-Q Highland's
There's nothing!
This is scary!
There's nothing left!
Nothing!
Got it!
Senbos!
No!
You're too fast!
I'll be in the background!
No!
You'll be in the background!
I'm not a ghost.
Are you okay, Eiko?
You're a ghost.
I'm not a ghost.
Here he is.
No, no, no.
He's not here.
Let's get out of here.
I want you to sit here.
No, no, no.
Eiko, Eiko.
Please let me go.
Let me out!
What?
Ahhhhhhhhhh!
Here! Here!
Excuse me.
This is the director.
General director.
That's a big deal.
Here we are!
The hot spring inn?
Yes, the hot spring inn with the Uwagawa hot spring.
We've set up a booth here.
Let's go!
Look!
Wow!
It's nostalgic!
We've been on that before.
Did you bring that with you?
Hello everyone!
Hello!
From here, tour guide will guide you.
The first person to greet you is...
Hello everyone, welcome.
This is Hamada in downtown, and Tanaka in Kokoriko.
And there's one more person, a guy called Yamana, who's made a joke out of him.
That legendary hot spring.
I don't think a country bumpkin like you can go on without laughing till the end.
You're terrible.
I'll do my best.
Of course, the end of the year special was a laughable one.
If you laugh, you'll be given a penalty and if you don't, you'll be forced to leave.
What's that?
This is a bit of a concern, right?
Yes.
Well, please.
This is...
I just laughed.
Because the camera is going to go bang!
What's that?
I'm sorry, Mr. Homma.
Yes.
It's real.
It's real, isn't it?
Does it mean that you can meet it sometimes?
It means that you can meet it sometimes.
I see.
It means that it can be used that much.
This is the bath.
Please take a seat over there.
Mr. Edo, please.
Mr. Tanaka, please sit here.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Huh? You laughed.
What do you mean by that?
It's not a joke.
The school trip is over.
And the next day...
Everyone, come here.
Gakitsuka 5 is...
These 5 are Gakitsuka 5 members.
If you buy this DVD, you can get a Promoide of Gakitsuka 5.
Hamada-san, you can have one.
Thank you.
Only one of Nakamura's boots is in the Heipo.
I don't care if this one is wrong or right.
This is rare.
I think,
Nittel Jamboree,
I think it would be better to leave a trash can where the boots came out.
Gakitsuka Boots is on sale during this period.
It's a good time to enjoy the show.
We're waiting for your visit!
DVDs are on sale!
Episode 5, A Trip to the Hot Spring House You Must Not Laugh at!
Episode 6, Yamasaki vs. Mori!
Episode 7 will be released soon!
Please look forward to it!
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors