Let's play the original game of Gaining High 1
The second half
The second half of the game
The Gaining High 1 challenge is a game that the Gaining High 1 members usually play in the theater or in the dressing room
I'm going to sing
Amazing
I'm not!
The second half of the game is even more exciting!
The first half...ah, I'm sorry.
I think I'm going to fall.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's a very strong game.
I understand.
Please welcome, Zun Zero Gain!
Who is it?
Hello!
Thank you for coming!
Who is it?
I think I've met him once at NGK.
I don't know him that well.
Oh, really?
Nice to meet you.
You're not a big fan of Otaku, right?
We've only met once.
We don't know each other.
Nice to meet you.
I hope you recover soon.
You've never met Otaku, right?
I have.
Mel-sons! What is the original game they thought of that is good at making jokes?
Originally, we thought of Wada Manju.
Wada Manju?
Manju, yes.
Yes, Wada Manju.
Wada Manju thought of it.
It's a game that's really popular among young comedians.
Please explain it.
The game we thought of is this.
3 words, no talking!
Yes, just like that
We'll have you talk using words other than 3 words
If you can't get into the rhythm, you're out
There are many words other than 3 words
Using the rhythm and talking using other than 3 words
Of course, even if you say words that are negative, you'll lose
A match?
Yes, 1 on 1.
Everyone will be watching but...
Who will be playing against you?
Dokumanju.
Ah, I see.
It's Wada Manju.
Wada Manju.
It's Dokumanju.
Then, who will be playing against you?
Matsumoto-san, excuse me.
Wada Manju and...
Wada Manju is strong, right?
Wada Manju is a game of
I've never met anyone like him before, so I want to play against someone I won't see again.
Why do you say that?
Why?
Let's do it again.
Let's decide the winner by rock-paper-scissors.
I'm scared.
The face of the manju is the face of the manju.
That's right.
You're so kind.
If you write the absolute result, you'll be in trouble.
I won't.
I'm not in trouble.
It's the basics.
It's going to collapse soon.
No, not that.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Matsumoto-san goes first.
Let's start with the first letter.
I'll go first.
Here I go.
Ka!
Kangaroo!
Ruby!
Oh, no.
Sorry.
This guy is a piece of shit!
This guy!
You're still not done yet?
I don't want to see this!
You've got to take this!
Take this!
Hey, Mr. Hamada!
This guy is dangerous!
He's going to take this!
Take it!
I've been thinking about this guy since last night.
I thought I would take it tomorrow.
You're still not done yet?
Wada Manju.
Which one should I start with?
I'm already tired of you.
Then let's start with Wada Manju.
Wada Manju will go first.
Here I go!
What's with that...
...that way of talking?
I didn't say anything.
What's with that?
You hate me, right?
I like you.
You really hate me?
I don't hate you.
Really?
How much do you like me?
I've been watching your shows.
What?
I really like you.
It's a generation.
You're a bit too old for this.
What's wrong?
I didn't plan this.
I just wanted to play a game.
Ah, sorry, sorry.
That's not it.
Sorry, sorry.
I'm sorry.
That's not it.
I didn't ask.
I didn't ask if I could kick.
Sorry, sorry.
So, from Hamada-san.
Thank you.
Okay.
Ki.
Kisu.
Sumi
Ni
Nitsukansu
What?
You said it before
Nitsukansu
Su
Suri
Rinpasein...ah, Unkatsu
What the hell?
I troubled you.
Not me.
We would never do that!
Let's do it!
We did it!
Matsumoto, you should do it!
Stop it!
We have no choice but to win
Let's start from Matsumoto
Let's start
Ma
Matsumoto
Tonakai
Ika
Ok, next.
Kejirami.
Mirin.
You should do it properly.
This is a difficult one.
You should drink three letters.
You are motivated.
You are motivated to fight.
I just want you to enjoy it.
It's a battle field.
Go home!
What are you going to do?
Thank you very much!
That was quick!
Now, the next artist, please come in!
Hello, nice to meet you.
Thank you for coming
Next is the question question
What is the original game that they suggest?
Thinking of the original game is a hobby
Today's game is this
One letter game
Please take care of us.
It's a game that everyone plays.
If I say, Ki,
For example, I say, No,
Ki, No,
Then Hose says, U,
Matsumoto says, Wa,
Everyone says one letter at a time and makes a sentence.
I see.
Ki, then Ki,
Ki, Tsu, Ne,
What word comes from Ki?
I wonder if it will continue.
How long will it last?
It will continue forever.
I see.
It's not over in the middle.
It will continue.
If you don't understand the meaning, it's over.
I see.
The connection of the sentences is strange.
There is a tempo, right?
Yes, it's a good tempo.
After it's over, I'll count 3 seconds.
So even if you can't say it, you're out.
That's what it means.
I hope I can say it.
One by one, they will say a word and make a sentence.
If the sentence is broken, you're out.
Let's get started.
I'll go first.
Yes.
Ah!
Tomorrow,
Please,
Take care of me.
Even if you say so.
Kodomo a...
Ashi...
Ta...mo...
Pa...ta...ma...ni...wa...o...te...
Wait, you're not doing it right!
It's not good, it's not good.
It's not good.
I don't remember the last part, so I thought it was okay.
I don't remember.
Show me what you just did.
Everyone was good, right?
I think it was my fault.
It's still...
Let's watch it again.
I look forward to tomorrow.
Please say it
Te mo?
Ne?
Ne ko?
Ah, so it's ne and ko?
I see
So it's ne and kin
I thought it was ne and kin and it started with ko so I thought it was a child
But I kind of got it
Okay, I got it
It's that tempo right?
Please do it at that tempo.
Let's go.
I'm starting.
What?
TACHI?
I want to do it properly.
Ruru.
Tachi-uru?
Tachi-uru is a hand.
A hand?
Tachi-uru is no longer good.
It's too difficult.
What is Tachi-uru?
You can say anything.
Tachi.
I want to eat the Tachiu.
I thought so too.
And Endo was rolling around.
I thought so.
Really.
Everyone thought about Tachiu.
I thought so.
I was really surprised.
You were really surprised.
Now, the second comedian, please.
This is Aikawa Takizawa.
Thank you!
It's been a while
Thank you
I was doing well
Me too
Thank you
I always watch your show on TV
Me too
I brought a game
This is the game I brought
Look this way, A-chan Rock-paper-scissors
Rock, paper, scissors!
What? What is A-chan?
You are so stupid!
If you do that, you will be like that.
Look this way, A-chan, rock, paper, scissors.
Not that way.
I will explain the rules first.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Win or lose, A-chan pose.
If you lose in rock, paper, scissors,
If you do the same pose as the winner, you lose.
First, A-chan pose.
There is a joke.
Please take a look.
Aikichi Yazawa who guides the way.
Is it a hospital?
It's a hospital in Kokomatsu, isn't it?
There is a traffic light.
The traffic light is turning right all the time.
I see.
Get on.
Ha ha.
This is one pose.
There are three poses in total.
This is a little difficult.
This is the first pose.
First, make your face like a girl.
Second, turn your fingers.
Third, this.
This is the pose.
Can you do it with me?
This?
This one?
No, this one.
Stretch your back a little.
And this face.
Oh, yes.
Then, these three.
Okay.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Let's start with the first one.
The first one is a rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Look over there.
Hey, wait.
No, no, no.
Do it later.
You have to do it later.
At the same time.
Together.
Matsumoto, are you ready?
Can I do it too?
You do all of it, huh?
I want to do it with a guy who's sweating oil like this.
Please don't hate me.
Do it with a positive attitude.
I'm a first-timer, so please do it.
Really.
Then the first one should say,
Look this way.
Look this way, A-chan.
Yes.
That's right.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Aiko-desho.
Look this way, A-chan
Oh, that's good
At first, it's a rock-paper-scissors
Look this way, A-chan
Ah, I just got it
You won
I won
That was funny
It was funny, right?
Thank you, thank you
Now, Matsumoto-san, everyone.
Yes.
This is the last one.
Well, this is the reason why we started this project.
We have a new member.
Oh, yes.
Please welcome!
Good morning, good morning. I'm Roxy.
Roxy, you're here.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Can I say something?
I don't know the game you played last time.
Oh, you didn't play it.
You did the full cut, right?
What did you do?
To be honest, I can't explain it.
Really?
I don't know what you did.
Did you measure it?
I got to choose the item I liked,
and I had to pick the item,
and I played something like Shurikugensta.
You did?
I played a game where you had to guess the amount of water in the cup.
We played a game called, Can you continue to cry?
I don't remember that.
Really?
Today?
Today, we have this.
Ta-da!
It's a choice game.
Like last time, we didn't choose.
And it's a choice game.
Last time?
What?
I don't understand the explanation.
Last time, we didn't do it.
We did it.
We have a special version of that game
It's a choice game
The name is interesting though
It's a choice game in Katakana
I understand
It's a choice game
Please give us 3 minutes
Please start at the same time
The choice game you will play is this
The choice game we will play
Please look
We have prepared a lot of trees this time.
The way you hold the tree is completely different.
We have prepared all kinds of trees this time.
Not all kinds of trees.
I think there are more.
Please choose three trees you like from these.
It's crazy.
Please choose.
I want you to choose three.
Please choose your favorite trees.
What is this? This is strange.
It's a miracle.
So, these three.
Three.
You can choose three.
Three is fine?
Then, Mr.Mizu, please sit down.
Please.
Choose this?
Then, the game we will play is this.
Wood and soil.
Oh, sorry. I made a mistake.
This is the game we will play this time.
Wood and soil.
I don't know what I did wrong.
No.
It's important.
I made a mistake.
Really?
Yes.
It's a soil game with wood.
A soil game with wood?
It's a game where you make soil with the wood you got.
What?
Then, you have 3 minutes.
Wait a minute.
What?
There's no explanation.
What does it mean to make soil?
Please make soil with three pieces of wood.
Oh, I see.
Correct! That's what I'm talking about!
You can't say it out loud!
What the hell is that?
Please make a soil with wood!
It's a soil made of wood!
You can't say it out loud!
Let's say it out loud!
I'll make a soil!
The person who makes a soil with a cleaner wood wins!
But I already chose it, so I don't know.
And you guys will be able to see the amazing, unique, and artistic, and delicate...
Wait, wait, wait!
It's a bit too fast!
3 minutes!
Please start at the same time!
I don't get it!
Let's start!
Hidekochi, start!
He's doing this?
Please do your best!
The choice is important.
This is really decided by choice.
If there is a stand-up style,
Tanaka-san, you did it with such a choice.
This is a little...
It's a little...
The second one below.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
It's over.
First of all, let's start with Tanaka-san.
I'm sorry.
Here you are.
What?
Too bad!
You said you couldn't get a nail.
Really?
You were so nervous.
It was a bad choice.
Next time, please give us a good choice.
Thank you.
What's next?
Matsumoto-san.
This is the first one.
Please.
Wonderful.
The number.
It was simple and easy.
It was the fastest.
It was the best choice.
The balance is a little thick.
The hole in the hole is also good.
If you have a dojo, you can swim and do it.
I think it's good, so please wait for the results.
Thank you.
Please be good soil.
Hosei and Endo successfully made the soil with wood.
The last one is Hamada.
Finally, Hamada, please.
I'm sorry, this one doesn't go up.
I have to put it in here.
The second one below.
It was like this.
I have to put it in here.
So, why did you choose such a thick one?
It's like this.
It's a more
This is a good one.
This is not good.
This is a bad one.
Shio Para 2018
The bus that is familiar in the series of the child's user, you shouldn't laugh, is also going through a salt stop this year.
Can you stand the laughter of the victims?
We are waiting for you.
I'm sorry!
Let's announce the results.
Everyone, please look at the soil.
Please raise your hands.
This time, it's out.
Soil, soil, no, soil, no.
This time, we got three soils.
That's all.
It was Okura. Thank you very much.
Who got the land?
Who won?
I got 3 lands
Who got it?
I did
I got 6 lands
You got 2 lands?
If possible, I wanted 5 lands
I see
I'm sorry
I don't know if Yagaki-san said it in Kanji
But that was already decided from the beginning, right?
I wanted you to imagine it.
That's right.
I got a message from Mr. Kosei.
I imagined it, but that's all I have.
I wanted to see you guys worried about what to do.
Oh, really?
I'm sorry.
I'm the bad guy?
Well...
Head.
Head?
That's...
You're a Russian love.
No, that's not it.
If you get fired...
I'm not fired.
But I don't know what will happen this time.
Again?
I think it will be fun.
Before that, everyone was excited.
Look this way and choose between Yazawa and me.
I'm 16 years old forever.
AHAHAHA