In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Arai, Tsukitsuki Tsuttsun Hachihenge!
First, I'd like to explain something.
Yes, yes, yes.
What is Tsuttsun?
Well, isn't Tsuttsun amazing right now?
Eh?
Right now, it's...
Is he the main character of this program?
No, no, no, don't say that.
I've done a lot of things, you know.
But in the end, isn't everyone outnumbered?
So I want to create new characters here again.
I think you've still failed.
It's supposed to be interesting in my head.
You know, I heard that today's going to be really bad.
Also, everyone has been Hachihenge for the past 7 episodes.
You know, everyone has been Hachihenge for the past 7 episodes.
Only this guy is Hachihenge.
This may be what some people think...
But it's not.
It's scary!
Anzenpai!
I want to do more than one.
That's not what I meant.
I don't want you to misunderstand.
For now, today's star is Tsuttsun.
This is Tsuttsun.
Tsuttsun is the nickname of Tsuttsun.
He loves Noh Miyano onee-chan and Stewardess.
He was given the nickname of Pinocchio by Tsuttsun.
He is the director of Gakunoki Type.
Is this guy going to be the opening act?
Yes.
You don't need this today, do you?
I don't think I need the money today.
I had to do my make-up here.
But I went to the make-up room.
I saw it.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to be the host of the show.
That's the concept.
What kind of staff are you going to have?
I'm going to be the host of the free talk show.
This is not good.
I've done it once before.
I don't like this.
Is there a TV program you're going to appear on?
I'm going to appear on TV.
What kind of TV program are you going to appear on?
I'm going to appear on a TV show.
I don't know.
I'm going to be the host of the show.
I'm going to appear on a TV show.
Please select Mr. Usamoto Matsumoto!
I don't know.
You don't look good with senior actors.
If you do it like this, the picture won't turn, right?
How is it?
No!
You're not good at this!
What are you talking about?
I wonder if it's like this...
There's no more K-1, right?
Yeah...
It's like this...
Hmm...
Yamazaki, right?
I don't know.
You're not lying, are you?
What should I do?
I want to challenge myself with various things.
Yes.
It's Vero.
Huh?
What's wrong with Vero?
Vero, are you hurt?
Let's go!
Vero, come here!
Vero, are you hurt?
Excuse me.
Yes.
What should we do with Yama-chan?
Well...
On my program,
I invited a big guest.
He used to be on a comedy show.
I watched his old V-app.
Now he's on the same show.
Stay!
Hey...
What's wrong?
Excuse me...
Good morning.
I'm sorry.
Taima-chan, let's go to the bar next time.
Let's go.
Yes.
When? When?
I don't know.
When you have time.
What's the appointment?
Who is it?
It's Sugasa-san.
Is it Sugasa-san?
I haven't been able to watch him for years.
I don't know.
I want to move.
Please decide the room.
If it's a good room, I'll live there.
Really.
How much is the rent?
17-80,000 yen.
Where do you want to live?
I want to live in Hatsudai or Yoyogi-ue.
Yoyogi-ue is expensive.
It's expensive.
I'll go.
I see.
This is the last one.
What's wrong?
There's nothing in it.
It's just the right amount.
I thought it was a free pass.
Me?
Ladies and gentlemen.
No, no, no.
It's been a while.
What?
I'm glad you're awake.
I just like Gakuya.
I've been crying.
I was still crying.
I'm really tired.
Well, you just woke up.
Very good.
You just woke up.
That's the usual.
You weren't far away.
That's right.
Jimmy bye Jimmy
He kind of collapsed recently.
I was a little flustered.
You were a little flustered?
That was a good move.
It was a good move.
Somehow...
Yeah?
It was a promotion program for the Ministry of Education.
No, no, no.
Well, well, well.
It was good, it was good.
What a waste.
I don't think he's a human being.
I don't think there's anyone who can beat him.
In that field.
Of course, of course.
There's no one who can beat him.
Even before, the queen of SM.
Yeah.
She was beaten up like this.
She was called the queen.
It hurts, it hurts.
Please stop, my lady.
You're not a lady, are you?
I'm sorry, my lady.
There's a difference between a lady and a queen.
It's completely different.
You're the only one who's different.
No one...
No one thinks that way.
I think it's really bad.
There's something like that, right?
In everyday life.
There is, but it's not something you can say now.
I'm not going to say it because it's embarrassing, but...
You know, when you go to a department store.
If you're on the escalator,
There's a broadcast called,
The escalator is on a cyborg.
I'm sure there's a cyborg on it.
I don't think it's that funny.
It's coming out, so I can't help it.
There's a cyborg on it.
A cyborg, a small cyborg.
Why is it a parent and a child?
It's a department store, so it's a parent and a child.
I don't know.
Well, Jimmy can't win.
Jimmy can't win.
He's going to go.
Yeah.
Where did you say you worked?
Wine factory.
Oh, wine factory.
I don't know why it's a wine factory.
Yeah.
It's a waste.
There are a lot of people who don't quit.
Who?
Who doesn't quit?
It's me.
You're so mean.
Don't put a bug in there.
No, no.
I don't know if you're going to make it bigger.
I'm saying this because I want you to put a bug in your own eye.
What?
You want me to put a bug in my eye.
I want you to put a bug in my eye.
I said I wanted you to put a bug in my eye.
Let's take it off.
What?
Why don't you take it off?
The naked-on-naked fight.
We don't have a fight, so I'm saying I want you to put a bug in my eye.
That's why.
Jimmy.
Jimmy?
Jimmy is telling you to go where it's a waste.
Run.
Go where it's a waste.
There are a lot of other people who can't quit.
Who are you talking about?
That's not a big problem right now.
No, no, I just got caught.
I really want to hear it.
It's just an example.
An example? It's just an example, right?
It's fine. It's totally fine.
It's just an example.
Ah, that's Mel Gibson.
So what I want to say is,
Even though Jimmy is funny,
That funny Jimmy can't quit.
He can't quit.
It's a waste.
There are a lot of people who are not as funny as Jimmy.
You!
Who is that? Who is that?
I'm saying what you're saying right now.
Who are you?
I don't know who you are.
I'm asking who you are.
Who are you?
There are a lot of people like that.
What is it?
I've been in the defense lately.
If I become number one in the Cho-Japan show,
That's not it!
You're the one who's in the defense.
Really?
If I become number one,
I'll be in the defense.
I used to say that.
There are a lot of shows that I hate.
What kind of show is this?
Ah, damn it!
The show I hate the most is...
I'm sorry to say this, but...
It's not funny at all.
That's strange.
Everyone laughs at you for saying that.
I think it's funny, but...
Do you know that difficult joke?
I wonder if you know it.
I know it, but...
That's enough.
You said it, so I want to hear it.
Jimmy, it's a waste.
There are a lot of things like Jimmy's next.
I don't know if it came out.
But in the end, you can't beat Jimmy.
That's amazing.
It's different.
Today is another good day.
This is good.
This is a good picture.
Mr. Matsumoto skydived without a parachute.
How did you feel at that time?
I thought I was going to die.
I didn't do it.
Are you following me 24 hours a day?
That's what I was told.
You don't know what you're doing on your day off.
I don't know that.
You can't say that I haven't skydived without a parachute.
I'm sorry.
Shut up!
Be careful when you talk.
I'm sorry.
Why can't you say that you haven't done it?
I don't know that.
You haven't done it.
You're fast.
Pull me a little more.
I'm sorry.
I was scared.
Were you scared?
You were scared to death.
That's right.
Why did you skydive without a parachute?
First of all, I wanted a hungry spirit.
I don't think it's right to fly with a parachute.
For example, you're skydiving now.
You're skydiving now, right?
You can't do that without a parachute.
You have to do it without a parachute.
That's not a parachute.
I don't like it.
I don't like to rely on things.
But you can't enjoy it without things.
Then you should quit.
No, no.
You should quit.
You shouldn't rely on things like that.
Didn't you stop me?
I was stopped.
But I didn't listen to you.
Who?
Don't you know?
I don't have permission.
I don't want to do it without a parachute.
It's a suicide.
I put it on and went up.
Did you put it on?
I took it off when I was about to get off.
I don't need it.
I see.
I told you to go up.
I thought you had a problem.
I was scared because I didn't have a parachute.
My legs hurt a little.
You are a snob.
A snob.
That's a snob.
You are a snob.
What do you call a child born between a half and a half?
It's a quarter.
A half and a pure child are a quarter, right?
Is that right?
A half is...
For example, a half is a child born between Japanese and Americans.
There's one half in the 5, right?
And there's another half here, right?
What happens if this half and the other half get married and have children?
That's what it is.
This is my child.
All of them are my children!
Hey! Hey!
What is it?
What? Isn't that what it is?
Half and...
No, no, no.
The Japanese.
For example, the Japanese get married and have children.
Oh, is that so?
So what are the half and the other half?
Ah, there's something.
There was something.
There's something, right?
Right?
Hey, I'm closing my eyes, but you ignored me.
There was something.
No, there's about 4 of them.
Yes.
But from that point on, aren't you going to be a 3rd or a 4th grader?
You're not moving at all.
I'm sorry.
I have a question for Sexy Voice's Wazumoto-san.
Sexy Voice?
Yes.
A woman's voice is sexy, but what kind of voice is sexy for a man?
Well, when we're having sex, we're both sexy.
It's a clash between sexy and sexy.
Ah, so when it's that kind of voice, it's already sexy?
It's sexy.
Ah, is that so?
It's all sexy.
So when it's that kind of voice, it's already sexy?
Yes, it's already sexy.
Sexy.
Huh?
It's sexy.
What's that?
It's normal.
A man is sexy, and a woman is sexy.
A woman's voice is sexy, that's for sure.
Yes.
Ah...
Uh, but, well, even for me...
I have my reasons.
Yes.
So, after all...
Ah...
But you come over here!
I haven't thought about the emotion at all.
This is too sexy.
Wait a minute.
No, no, please do it one more time.
Ah...
No...
Why do you say you don't like it?
You're the one who's doing it.
You're doing it while saying, I don't want to.
He's saying he doesn't want to too.
Awasan is saying he doesn't want to too.
I don't want to.
It's fine if you don't want to.
This is sudden, but I'm really weak at facing the other way.
I have a question for the king of facing the other way in the entertainment world, Macchan.
How can I definitely win?
I've never lost at facing the other way.
Really.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Look over there.
What are you doing?
Rock, paper, scissors.
Look over there.
Hey!
You're not going to move?
If I do that, I'll lose.
That's not it. Tell me a way to win properly.
It's a way to not lose.
I'm asking if I can win.
Oh, really? I understand.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Look over there.
Who's going to stop me?
I'm asking if I can teach you how to win.
There's a way to face the other way.
Do you understand?
There are three ways to win.
If you lose suddenly, you lose.
If you face the other way, you lose.
Right or left.
Humans tend to have a heart condition.
So it's more likely to face the other way.
But I don't know if I'm facing the other way.
So the best way is to win.
Rock, paper, scissors.
You'll be in this state.
When you make a U-turn.
First of all, I'll take the lead.
And then look over there.
No, look over here!
The heart is more important.
This program was provided by the following sponsors.