High Tension! The Best!
Good evening!
It has started again this week!
That's right!
High Tension! The Best!
By the way, this corner is not very popular among the general public.
However, Mr. Uchimura of Uchannanjan is very popular.
Is that so?
If there is one more person...
Yes?
High Tension! The Best!
The 10th place this week is...
Moro Strike!
KoKoriko!
Naoki Tanaka!
No.47!
Welcome to the show!
Thank you!
You are the 10th place for your first appearance.
Yes!
This time, the 10th place song was canceled.
That song was canceled.
Mr. Tanaka, your mother is calling you today.
Is that so?
Please talk to her.
Hello?
Nao-chan?
Isn't it real?
Don't use honorifics to your mother.
Mom?
Yes?
It's Nao-chan.
Hello?
Your son is the 10th place.
Is that so?
Yes.
Thank you.
No problem.
Why don't you say something?
I was surprised.
What?
I thought it was real.
Hello?
Please do your best for your mother.
Mom?
Yes?
Don't do that.
Hello?
How are you?
Please watch it.
Thank you.
Mr. Tanaka, please stand by.
He's a little shaken.
There are some difficult things to do.
Let's go.
This week's 10th place, Mr. Tanaka will do a mono strike.
Mr. Tanaka.
Thank you very much.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Let's continue.
The 9th place is 76 points.
Kojikan Monogatari.
Gokuraku Tonbo.
Yamamoto Keiichi.
The 8th place is 121 points.
Aipatchi Juin Musume.
Gokuraku Tonbo.
Kato Koji.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Ladies and gentlemen.
The 9th and 8th place Gokuraku Tonbo have a day off due to work.
Is that so?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Please come next time.
Please come.
Let's continue.
The 7th place this week is 163 points.
Miyasako Hiroiki.
Hello, Mr. Kojikan.
Hello.
This time...
It's the 7th place.
It's only Miyasako, isn't it?
What about you, Mr. Hotoyama?
I'm out of the ranking.
I'm making a new song right now.
I see.
You have to do your best.
I'll do my best today.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
Why are you angry?
You're very strict.
Yes.
What is it?
Are you dissatisfied with the 7th place?
Yes.
I don't know.
I'm confident in this song.
What?
The 7th place...
I don't know what to say.
Do you have a pattern of going up next time?
I'm not sure about the 7th place this time.
I see.
I don't know what to say.
Standby.
The 7th place.
Yes.
Thank you.
Let's go.
The 7th place this week.
The 7th place is Miyasako Hiroyuki's new song.
My stomach hurts.
Something came out.
I'm going to give birth.
Hello.
Thank you very much.
It was a wonderful performance.
It was good.
It's true that the 7th place is not good.
I see.
Thank you.
Let's continue.
The 6th place this week is...
185 points.
It's a surprise.
Takasu Hamane.
This is his first appearance.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
Unfortunately, it's because of work.
Is that so?
I can't come to the studio, but I'm shooting a VTR.
Yes.
Let's take a look.
Let's go.
It's Tokyo Station again.
What is it?
I'm surprised.
You're still doing it.
I'm happy.
I stepped on the ground.
It's cold.
It's too cold.
Thank you very much.
However, the 6th place is...
The 5th place this week is...
254 points.
Aihohoi.
This is Mr. Endo Shodo.
This is the 4th place.
Mr. Endo, who was the 1st place last time, is the 5th place.
What do you think?
It's strange that a person like me takes the 1st place.
If you think about it, it's about 5th place.
It's a great comment that you have some room.
Are you okay?
You're naked.
Mr. Endo, since you've been naked, you've never hugged a woman.
It's been about two months.
I haven't talked to a woman in person.
Let's go to the 5th place.
Let's go.
The 5th place this week is...
Mr. Endo Shodo.
Aihohoi.
Do you know Puerto Rico?
Are you going to Puerto Rico?
Where is Puerto Rico?
What am I?
Aihohoi.
Thank you very much.
I think you still have a lot of energy left.
I can't help it if I fall in love.
The 4th place this week is...
301 points.
T.S. I Love Me.
Animal Teedan.
Osaru.
Please.
Kattobase Kakefu.
It was Kakefu.
I see.
There's a lot of dirty stuff.
It's just Osaru.
I'll do my best.
Please stand by.
Thank you very much.
I'll do it barefoot.
Let's go.
The 4th place this week is...
Animal Teedan.
Osaru.
T.S. I Love Me.
Glasses.
Yasushi-kun.
Tie yourself.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was really great.
It's great to be at the top.
Let's take a break.
What?
Before announcing the 3rd place.
Isn't that enough?
What are you doing?
Let's go to the 3rd place.
Let's take a break.
This week's spotlight.
This week's spotlight is...
The 9th place from the prefecture.
The 23rd place this week is...
Yamasaki Hosei.
Yes.
It's a spotlight.
The previous song was really bad.
It didn't work at all.
This time, it's the song of love.
The song of love.
The song of the planet.
How long do you think you can go up?
Yamasaki-san.
It's not Hong Kong.
It's because it's us.
Please understand.
It's a big hit.
You're lying.
Everyone says it's a big hit.
It's a big hit.
Please stand by.
Let's go.
This week's 23rd place is...
Yamasaki Hosei.
The song of the planet.
Kya!
It's so refreshing!
Okay, thank you very much.
It's so refreshing that it makes you want to cry.
Okay, let's go!
I think he knows best.
Let's go for the last one this week!
350 points!
Men and women are different!
Fujii Takashi!
Hello, Fujii-san.
Hello, hello.
Fujii-san, this is your new song, right?
That's right.
It's your third song.
Yes, it's a new song, but somehow it's so mysterious.
It's a new song, so it's fine.
I see.
This week, we've received a letter from a friend of Shingeki-san.
Oh, it's fine.
If you don't want to do the warm-up, go to Osaka's famous Pachi-pachi-panchiya.
You're George-san, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
God, Fujii-kun is in the top 10.
Is he okay? Please protect him.
Thank you for your growth.
It's Master Kuwabara, right?
Yes, yes.
Kuwabara Kazo-sama.
From now on, you don't have to worry about me.
I see.
The three of you.
Huh?
I understand.
Thank you very much.
Are you feeling sick?
I'm fine.
Let's move on to the third place. Fujii Takashi-san.
A man and a woman are different.
Shut up.
That was easy.
I see.
This is from Osaka for that.
That's right.
The second place of this week is...
449 points.
Human's eyesight.
I won't let you say goodbye.
I, Ritton Chosadan, will take the water.
Okay.
I won't let you say goodbye.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
Yes.
Ritton-san.
I won't let you come to the studio.
Is that so?
It's been a while since the ranking went up.
That's right.
It was the same last time.
Yes.
But this time, I have a phone call for you.
Hello?
Is this Mizuno-san?
This is my partner Fujiwara.
Is this Fujiwara-san?
Yes.
Where are you now?
I'm at work right now.
I'm in Hamamatsu.
Hamamatsu?
Yes.
I've been busy lately.
Where is Mizuno-san?
Can you hear me?
I'm already excited.
Yes.
I've been excited all day.
Is this Mizuno-san's voice?
That's right.
Ah.
Yes.
This is wonderful.
Okay, then.
Please give me the human power.
Human power!
Boo!
Ah!
I want to play baseball.
But I can't use my hands here and there.
Boo!
Give me some water.
Let me go.
Let go of me.
Don't hold on to me.
Give me Curry's glasses.
Curry's glasses.
Ah...
Well, it's a little long, isn't it?
Yes.
Well, well, well.
I don't know why, but this is already our second place.
Second place?
It's going up.
That means, who is the winner?
That's right.
It can't be. Let's go.
The winner of this week is...
The winner of this week is 524 points.
Yosh, Hurricane Jelassie.
Kokoriko, Endo Shouzou.
Top 10 and 2nd place.
2nd place.
And the new song is 1st place.
This song was released before Aiho.
What is Aiho?
Aiho.
The song that was released before Aiho.
Thanks to Aiho, it became popular.
On the contrary, Aiho made it popular.
That's right.
Right?
It's wonderful.
If you wear something like this, won't it stand out too much?
What's the point of not having a woman?
That's what I want to say.
I want to go to the gala with you.
Thank you.
Let's get ready.
Go from the back.
Let's go.
The winner of this week is...
Yosh, Hurricane Jelassie.
From now on...
I will...
Do it.
I want to eat corn.
I want to eat it.
I want to eat umeboshi.
Whale.
Hurricane.
I want to eat...
Corn.
I want to eat.
Thank you.
There is a long line!
Let's take a group picture!
version
I must go to the restroom
In the harbor, my hand sways
And that guy, a taxi driver
asi
vert
How are you doing?
How are you doing recently?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Well, taxi drivers are getting better and better.
What do you mean by getting better?
How have you been doing since then?
What do you mean?
After you went on air, have you been like, Ma-chan, can you write a song for me?
No, but...
Wait a minute!
I don't understand.
I understand.
You were talking about that last week, right?
That's right. I talked about it a lot.
Well...
When you don't look at my eyes properly, it means nothing is coming.
Actually, I thought about it.
I thought it would be nice to hire an artist to sing a taxi driver song.
The other day, I didn't ask who you wanted me to sing it for.
That's right.
So, instead of me writing a new song and making a song,
that taxi driver is a masterpiece.
It's a masterpiece that goes against the sun.
So...
Isn't that a kind of cheating?
I've never cheated.
What kind of cheating are you talking about since last week?
It's like the old days.
It's like a blue 300.
I've got the nuances.
I've got the exes.
But that's not cheating.
If you say that, it's cheating that I'm wearing a jean and that I thought of wearing a jean.
Well, well...
I'm scared of your face.
The other day, I went to the countdown TV.
At that time, both you and I...
I found out that the staff were really scared.
That's not true.
When we were shooting the song, we went into the studio.
There was a set of songs.
I've got a set change.
I've got a chair waiting for me.
Did you see that?
What is it?
There are five pipe chairs.
That's good.
Five?
That's for that member.
There are two soft sofas next to the pipe chair.
I don't know.
Really?
The soft sofa is completely different from the pipe chair.
There are two soft sofas that can fit about 30 pipe chairs.
I don't know.
What do you mean?
The other members sit on the pipe chair.
You and I thought I would go crazy if there were seven pipe chairs.
I asked them to sit on two of them.
Of course.
You're not the only one.
Why?
It's safe.
There are five pipe chairs and two soft sofas.
This is a downtown thing no matter how you think about it.
That's a downtown thing no matter how you think about it.
I don't dare to write it down, but you get it, right?
Fujiwara is amazing.
Well, well, well, well.
That's great.
I was working in the neighborhood of my apartment for about a week.
It was a little noisy and hard to sleep.
But that has nothing to do with Fujiwara.
It's a normal conversation.
Fujiwara, it was noisy today, too.
You don't have to say, is that so?
It's a normal conversation.
I'm sorry.
It's really annoying.
Really?
I'm sorry.
Is there construction going on on your back?
Once, when Mr. Sanma did something with seven men and women, it was amazing.
When Kagetsu came, everyone was amazing.
It was dangerous.
It was so loud that I couldn't sleep in the dressing room.
You do it, too.
I don't remember that.
Really?
I couldn't help it because I didn't like it.
I thought I would say hello to him if I met him once.
I met him in the dressing room.
I thought he didn't like it.
He said, good morning.
He said, say hello to me.
I said, good morning.
I'll give you a present.
He said, yes.
I don't accept that kind of greeting.
I said, come here.
It's scary.
Good morning.
Thank you for watching.