It's itchy!
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Arahen, Chikichiki!
Gaki no Tsukai staff comedy show!
Today is Gaki no Tsukai staff comedy show!
It's just like the title!
No one will understand, right?
But we will do our best!
First is the first person!
Please!
Gaki no Tsukai staff comedy show!
What are you doing?
Come here!
Where are you going?
What's your name?
I'm from Saitama prefecture. I'm the producer, Suga.
What? Was that Hikaru Genki?
What are you doing?
Gaki no Tsukai staff comedy show!
I want to be a flower.
You come to me secretly.
You pick me up and hold me in your hands.
I also want to be a red grape.
I want to be sweet from your mouth.
What are you talking about?
It has nothing to do with you!
It has nothing to do with a bird!
Next is this person!
Where are you from?
I'm from Kyoto. I'm Yamasaki.
From Kyoto?
Yamasaki-san, did you come from Kyoto?
Yes!
Why are you saying it again?
Yamasaki-san, I'm looking forward to working with you.
I will defeat the bear!
Kuno, come on!
Ah! It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
Yamasaki-san, what was that?
I just removed my shoulder.
Yamasaki-san!
Escalator!
Thank you very much.
Yamasaki-san!
It was good!
Thank you very much!
Next is Umeda-san.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
I don't know who you are!
I will imitate the site director.
The site director?
Hey!
Next is this person!
I'm from Nara. I'm Tsutsumimoto.
I'm in Hamada-san's dressing room.
You're in my dressing room?
I'm sleepy.
Good morning.
You have a big chest.
What are you talking about?
Hey!
You're in my dressing room!
Momi! Momi! Momi!
It's quite safe. Do it once.
What are you talking about?
Next is this person!
You're in my dressing room!
Go home!
Next is this person!
Good morning.
I'm from Shiga. I'm Noriasu.
From Shiga?
I like spicy food.
Is that so?
Even if you lick this, you can smile a lot.
I see.
Please lick it.
I don't want to lick it.
I don't understand.
Thank you very much.
Wait!
Next is this person!
I'm Ayatori.
I see.
Hoki.
Thank you very much.
Next is this person!
I'm going to tear off the manga.
I might not be able to tear it off.
What are you talking about?
Sueki-san, the camera is filming you.
One, two...
Sueki-san, that's good.
Next is this person!
Good morning.
I'm from Shiga.
I'm Adachi.
Today, I'm going to try a super magic trick.
Is that so?
Can you tie me up?
Yes.
You can tie me up like this.
Are you really okay, Adachi-san?
Is this okay?
Adachi-san, please.
Here I go!
Adachi-san!
Sueki-san!
What are you doing?
Go home!
Next person, please!
What's your name?
I'm from Amagasaki. I'm Takasu.
I'm from Nara. I'm Okamoto.
What are you going to do today?
Acrobat.
Acrobat?
You've been doing this for a long time?
About 10 years.
Then, both of you, please.
You've been doing this for a long time?
About 10 years.
This is the last person.
Today, at the opening...
Everyone enjoyed it very much.
You didn't have the energy to do it?
I didn't have the energy to do it.
I think...
You're still here?
You can predict the future, right?
This is one of your talents.
You should have told me when we first met.
I've been thinking about a lot of things.
You didn't reply.
You didn't tell me anything.
I've been thinking about what I'm going to do next year and the year after that.
Somehow.
I can't see it right now.
That means...
I want to see it.
I don't know if I'll be able to break it next year.
I heard you're dead.
Do you think I'm dead?
I did it.
I really can't see it.
I'm dead.
I'm being killed.
I think you're crazy.
Who?
The guy with long hair.
Bring me a knife.
Mr. Katsuki!
You really...
Don't say things like that!
If you say things like that, I really think the guy with long hair is me.
And then there's going to be something funny again.
I'm going to make it funny again.
You're going to color it.
Last time, I was able to make it funny and funny.
But this time, I'm going to make it funny and funny.
No one can do that.
Please be careful.
My fans are really crazy.
I wonder why.
I'm a little scared.
I see.
There are people who use me.
Are you stupid?
I'm not stupid. I think that's what they think.
If you think that way, you shouldn't say such a thing.
You shouldn't say such a thing.
The guy who thinks he's a professor is sick because of the professor.
I thought it was over last week, but I still want to say it.
If what you're saying is right, that's what it is.
Why is she saying that?
She thinks she's a professor, but she's sick.
She's saying that.
I see.
Right?
You don't have to open your mouth.
You're just crazy.
I am.
But there are a lot of people like that around me.
I wonder why.
I'm really worried about this, too.
If it's a little off, it's about what you say and do.
We have something in common.
If it's my feeling, she'll understand.
That's true.
I saw something like a fairy the other day.
You're saying that, too.
When you go home, there's a fairy next to the pot.
That's what you say.
When I saw it, I thought, wow, she's here.
And finally, if it's a match, she'll believe it.
She'll believe it.
That's it.
That's definitely it.
I've seen a lot of fairies, too.
That's the problem.
Why?
There's no way I've seen it.
No, no, no, I've seen it.
I've seen it, but what I'm seeing and what she's seeing is probably different.
It's a different kind of thing.
If you say that, she'll think again.
Why?
What kind of fairy are you?
I've seen a lot of them, so what kind of fairy are you?
If you say one thing, she'll say, I've seen a lot of them.
When I opened the fridge, she was there.
That's what I'm saying.
Hey, hey, I'm home.
I didn't open it.
She was there.
What kind of fairy are you?
If you say that on TV, she'll say, it's about me.
Why?
If it's about that, I want you to come.
I want to see it.
I've been saying there are fairies in many places.
That's why I don't like it if you just say what you saw in the fridge.
What kind of fairy are you?
What kind of clothes are you wearing?
I'm a fairy who doesn't wear clothes.
You're naked.
I'm naked.
The one I saw the other day.
What about your tongue?
My tongue is like a horse.
That's not a fairy.
You're holding it like this.
It's a fairy.
It's like a horse.
That's why I was sleeping.
Hey, wait.
Hurry up and say something like that.
Didn't you open the fridge when you got home?
Were you sleeping?
I was sleeping.
Didn't you wake up?
You were sleeping at night.
I was sleeping at home at night.
I want to make that sound.
That's right.
Why?
What is this sound?
I saw a lot of things.
There's no mistake in the fridge.
I can hear it from the inside.
I opened the fridge.
Then I heard a sound like this.
Wait a minute, everyone.
It's okay.
I heard a sound like this.
I was running.
Maybe it's because it's a fridge.
I heard a sound like this.
It's because it's cold.
You can leave it alone.
I opened the fridge.
It's a fairy.
It has a kind face.
I opened the fridge.
Why?
What are you looking at?
Which one?
I was surprised.
You won't open it again, will you?
Of course I'll open it again.
Did you open it?
Did you see a scary thing?
I opened it.
You opened it.
Why do humans wave their hands when they walk?
Are they waving?
They're not conscious.
What happens when humans walk?
It's not that strange, is it?
But it's hard to walk.
There's a reason.
There must be a reason.
What kind of reason?
Are you thinking about it now?
No, I'm not thinking about it.
Just say it.
Why do humans wave their hands?
Of course.
Don't say that!
You're a human.
No, no.
Don't say something you don't like.
If you say that, I don't like it.
You should understand.
I don't understand what you're saying.
Why do you wave your hands?
Because I'm waving my hand naturally.
What do you mean by walking?
What do you mean?
I'm waving my hands at you.
You should say that too.
No, no.
I don't understand.
Say it.
I don't understand, so I'm saying it again.
What do you mean?
What do you mean by walking?
Wave your hands.
No, no.
I don't understand.
Wave your hands.
I'm asking you. What do you mean?
I'm asking you. What do you mean by walking?
I'm asking you.
That's just what you wanted to say.
I'm asking you. What do you mean by you don't understand?
I understand.
When Japan didn't have the government...
When Toyotomi Hideyoshi was still Kinoshita Tokichiro...
That's what I'm thinking.
That's what you're thinking.
At that time, we were still walking like this.
It's strange. It's hard to walk.
That's what everyone said.
What do you think?
Come on, everyone. Let's talk.
Aren't you going to walk? Come on, everyone.
Everyone was walking like this.
I understand that.
At that time, only one person said,
Hey, what?
Why are you so fast?
You guys are fast.
Yuta?
Yuta.
Really?
Why am I so fast?
Why is everyone so fast?
This is the recording of the children's machine.
Is that so?
This is a set.
What are you doing?
Where did you come from?
I came from Hyogo Prefecture.
Hyogo Prefecture?
What is your name?
My name is Matsumoto.
Matsumoto?
I run a bar called Sanpatsu Yahoo Izakaya.
What?
What are you going to do today?
I'm going to do a one-person skit.
One person skit? That's great.
I have something to tell you.
No, no, no.
Please take a look at it.
Matsumoto, please.
Today is my first date with him.
But will he really come?
I'm worried.
This is the meeting place with him.
It's in front of Shinjuku Arutama.
He's late.
When will he come?
Will he come?
I found his white Camaro.
Dear.
He's coming, he's coming.
This is his apartment.