In commemoration of the 400th anniversary of Hishiku, we will be giving you a special gift!
It's the 400th anniversary?
Yes, it's the 400th anniversary.
Is that so?
You're all so talented, why did you come here?
I don't know.
What?
Did you read it?
No, I didn't read it.
Huh? Yamasaki?
I didn't read it at all.
Why?
No, no, no.
It's okay, it's okay.
Even if it's an incident.
That's because I'm the one who gave it to you.
Do you know that?
My dad is a comedian.
It's the 400th anniversary.
We started the first episode on October 3, 1989.
Is that so?
Yamaguchi-san, how many episodes have you done?
I've been doing it since the second episode.
We've been making it together.
Did you participate in Koho-riko?
Yes, since a year ago.
This is the 56th episode.
Let's eat it clean.
Did you participate from here?
Yes, I participated from here.
Since that year, the kid has been powering down.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
For the time being, this has become a series several times.
Let's take a look at this.
Can you take a picture of this?
It's strange that you can take a picture so quickly.
I was listening.
A special project for the new year.
A challenge to catch up with Shinten.
Who will be the problem?
Will this sword be a toy?
It's not a toy.
Matsumoto Shirojo, who is ready for the new year, appears.
If I was told about it before, I wouldn't be able to do it.
I succeeded in Masamune, but they didn't understand it.
That's what it is.
Let's do it.
This is Catherine.
Is this Catherine?
It's to unify the mind.
It takes two or three minutes.
Of course.
Are you going to do it?
Let's do it.
Matsumoto Shirojo, who is ready for the new year, appears.
It's strange.
Are you okay with your bangs?
How is it?
It's quite nerve-racking.
I can't see it.
It's fine.
Let's do it.
I hit it.
Come on.
The third.
The second one was dangerous.
This one is also crazy.
It's nostalgic.
It's also young.
Yes.
Thin.
Next.
Yes.
I see.
Right?
I wonder if it's okay to look at this.
A child's summer vacation comparison.
Manager Okamoto is angry again.
A man who has defeated his own existence with a life-threatening challenge.
Do you know?
Manager Okamoto.
I'm from Okinawa.
With this one word, he was forced to bring a child to Okinawa.
What is Okamoto challenging?
Don't do that.
Why?
Because cats don't like it.
How many times have you been to Okinawa?
Hey, stop smoking.
Are you stupid?
Are you really stupid?
You haven't been here yet.
I've been to Okinawa many times.
Cats are scared.
That one?
Yes.
Which one?
That one.
What are you doing?
Okamoto, dive into the water.
Like a blowfish.
A blowfish in the water.
Manager Okamoto challenges a blowfish in the water.
Okamoto.
What's wrong with you?
I'm thirsty.
Are you ready?
Yes.
I'm ready.
What are you doing?
I'm just removing the skin!
Take it off!
It's spicy!
If you come here and take the tip of the bamboo, we'll go down.
I'll push you!
Let's go!
This way!
The direction is wrong!
Let's go!
Okamoto-san!
This is reality.
This picture is ideal.
That's right. It's like a dream.
It's perfect.
Number 250.
Number 250?
If you come here and take the tip of the bamboo, we'll go down.
Thank you very much.
What are the viewers doing?
The viewers are angry.
Hurry up and take the tip of the bamboo!
In the entertainment world, there are two strong men who divide the power of the society.
They don't know the amount of blood they shed.
The head-to-head conflict has deepened the level of confusion.
Stop it! Stop it!
They don't know what to fear when they're cut off.
The entertainment world is fast to cut off.
Yamazaki Hosei.
Burning the fire of hatred.
Yotami.
Aimaniel.
You haven't been on TV lately, have you?
I don't know.
You know what?
I'm looking for a job.
Even if you're on TV, it's better to be on TV.
Don't you know what it's like to be on the other side of the screen?
I don't know what it's like to be on the other side of the screen.
You can't do that.
You're the only one who can do that.
Don't say such a thing.
Let it burn. Let it burn.
So hot!
It's so hot!
It's like a prison!
It's frozen!
It's so hot!
I'm going to wash it with a firework shower!
It's so sticky!
What are you doing?
I'm a human!
It's so hot!
It was long, wasn't it?
You look like you're wearing see-through clothes!
How are you feeling now, Yamazaki-san?
I'm so tired.
We still have a long way to go.
How are you doing these days?
I've been doing my best.
Is there anything you'd like to see?
Goho Matsumoto's drawing class.
I was surprised to see Hamada-san's drawings.
That was the debut of Sho Yuki.
I laughed a lot, but it was clearly a stupid laugh.
Goho Matsumoto's drawing class!
We're going to draw on the same theme.
I really like Disneyland, so I'll draw Mickey Mouse.
Mickey Mouse!
I'll draw myself.
Do you want to see Garg's drawing?
I see.
This is where the drawing was.
I think so.
It's a very intense competition.
I drew Mickey Mouse.
It's so funny.
The children are running away.
It may not look like it, but it's like this.
What?
It's scary, isn't it?
I have four ears.
Let's move on to the next one.
Here.
What is this?
The viewers will understand this.
It's strange.
This is bad.
This is the worst.
I think I can draw well.
Why don't we draw our own characters?
We'll draw our own characters.
I'll take a look at it.
What kind of expression is that?
You're a monster!
What is this? What is this? What is this?
He's laughing.
It's his face.
What? Wait a minute!
This is it! Your mouth!
I want you to laugh a little.
Yes, yes.
There's a lot of wood.
After this, the favorite work of Downtown will appear.
I want to see that.
A theme park.
I've done a lot of openings.
I like it a lot.
But the ratings are not good at all.
I don't know what's left.
I like it a lot.
Welcome.
Which one would you like?
Coffee cup.
Yes, please give me a coffee cup.
Coffee cup start.
Start.
It's over.
It's an ocean coaster!
It's an ocean coaster.
Start.
It has an ocean coaster on it.
It's a good song.
We're going to have a parade.
I got it.
Next customer, welcome.
You're just in time.
What time is it?
We're going to have a technical parade.
Please come out for a moment.
The lights are beautiful.
Okay, we're done.
Let's go to the observatory for your father.
We're going to the observatory.
Please take care of your father.
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
Please get on the bus.
There's a bus.
Please enjoy your trip.
Please get on the bus.
It's a long way.
It was fun.
Do you have anything you want to see?
Let's see what Jimmy has.
Jimmy's manager is talking about his business.
He's watching if he can do it alone.
What's the result?
I'll do it directly.
You can take it.
I'm happy.
He can't get on the bus.
It's a long way.
Let's go to the hospital.
Where is TBS?
Turn left and go straight.
It's better to go.
Let's go.
Jimmy has a job.
I'll give you half of this.
Thank you very much.
Hello.
What should I do?
He's running away.
I got it.
It's strange, but I'm here.
Jimmy is here.
Thank you very much.
I'll give you half of this.
Can you touch me?
I'm naked.
Why are you naked?
I don't know.
I'm scared.
I'll go home.
Thank you very much.
My character did the taiyaki.
He's frowning.
Oh, thank you very much.
That's all?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
I think I'll get a reward if I give it to her.
Excuse me, miss.
I'm really going home now.
Um, from my manager...
The gyaru is...
That...
Sakurai-san...
She said she'd give it to me.
Oh, the gyaru that was so popular...
I was thinking about it.
What?
What are you doing?
Isn't that a cam?
Kiss, kiss.
What are you doing?
I'm going to take a bath.
After this, Hamada will be angry at that big artist.
Hamada has been very angry before.
Hamada-san?
Yes.
He was so angry that he went to the barbershop.
Did you see the barbershop yesterday?
I think I saw it.
There was nothing there.
Did they laugh?
Have they ever laughed at what they said?
I don't think they've ever laughed.
That's right!
You shouldn't have said that.
Your hair was long, and you didn't have ears.
I was told that a long time ago.
That you didn't have ears.
You're a comedian.
I don't think it's funny.
That's enough.
Hamada Masatoshi.
I'm going to take a bath.
I went to your barbershop, so it's okay.
We didn't do anything.
Rather, listen to the song.
What song?
I'm going to take a bath.
Okay?
But...
Machine?
It's machi, right?
He's manly.
Azuki-chan is really good at singing
You guys are really good
He's controlling something
This is Ikansho
He's singing
It's Azuki-san, right?
Let's go on a ride together
It's a long ride
Didn't you tell him?
I told him
I'm saying this because I don't like bad guys
I'm saying this on behalf of everyone
I'm saying this for you
I didn't know
I don't know
What happened?
This is my life
It seems like he understood
I said everything I wanted to say
I know
He was angry
Really?
He said I'm not that fat
That's how it is
There's no problem
There were many things
There's no limit
Let's do this again
Let's do this 420 times