The game is called, If you make a person laugh, you win.
And this time, it's a casting competition.
Everyone will be asked,
Why is this person on our show?
Everyone will be cast.
One or two people each.
Those people will be asked to laugh.
Let's do it.
If you laugh, you lose.
The person with the worst grades will get a bad prize.
This show is brought to you by this sponsor.
Let's decide on the order of the parents.
Is there anyone who is confident?
Can I go first?
Of course, if you're confident, you can cast.
That's right.
What do you think?
I'll go first.
Tanaka will go first.
Young man.
Everyone except Tanaka,
will get 10,000 points.
Please cast.
I'll go first.
Let's go.
First, Tanaka will cast.
I'll go first.
Oh, my love, my darling.
I've hungered for your touch.
It's coming out.
It's fun to look for it.
No, no, no.
When it came out, I was in the front.
There's that, too.
It's fun.
But did you see it?
Did you see it?
It's Ibuki Goroh.
To be honest, I've never seen it before.
You were surprised, weren't you?
Tanaka, Endo and Yamasaki didn't laugh.
I was surprised.
Yamasaki 2,500, Endo 2,000.
Suddenly, Okita's casting.
Tanaka, plus 1,000 points.
Who's going next?
Let me go.
I want to get this back as soon as possible.
I see.
So you're the boss.
Go ahead.
Endo 2,000.
I'll go 2,500.
2,000.
Who's going to win?
Are you going home?
Let's go.
Matsumoto is the boss.
Yamasaki 4,000, Start!
Endo 2,500, Endo 2,000.
It was hard to judge.
Tanaka didn't make a mistake either.
I was patient.
Yamasaki didn't make a mistake either.
Really?
Yamasaki has a normal face.
He's got a normal face.
Endo 2,500, Endo 2,000.
How was it?
It's safe.
Matsumoto got 0 points.
I'll go.
I'll go 3,000.
Zaki.
I'll go 2,000.
I can't go 2,000.
I'll go 1,500.
1,500?
Let's go.
I don't have any money left.
I have to win.
2,000?
2,000.
Let's go.
Yamasaki 4,000, Start!
What?
Who is it?
It's a coward.
It's funny.
I thought it was a grandma.
It's a grandma.
Thank you.
This is huge.
This is really dirty.
You're really dirty.
Can't you go to the second round?
Everyone is recruited for a quick casting.
Yamazaki gets 8,000 points.
Next.
Endo, tell me honestly.
Are you confident?
Well, well.
2,500.
I'll go with 2,500.
That's a little.
It's a little.
I understand.
I want to go to the last round.
Endo is the son of his parents.
Light.
Endo.
Okay.
It wasn't good.
Are you okay?
Everyone didn't laugh.
Everyone is safe.
Endo's parents are minus 7,000 points.
Please cast.
I'll go with 2,000.
I'll go with 2,500.
It's a job meeting.
I saw it yesterday.
I saw it yesterday and saw it today.
I saw it, but I'm being watched.
I'm strong.
Wait a minute.
That's what you said.
I knew who was going to win.
I can't do it.
Endo Matsumoto is in the pot.
I'll go.
Second stage.
I'll go with 3,500.
I have to go.
Tanaka's laugh is the only one.
I had to take it.
I have to take it.
I'll go with 3,500.
$3,500.
$3,000.
$3,000 for Endo.
$2,500.
Okay, let's go.
Second Stage, I Am My Father's Glittering Flower.
Ready!
That's how you do it.
I watch it every week.
You don't know?
What?
Matsumoto-san, you don't know?
What are you talking about?
Hamada got 1,500 points from our staff.
In the process, Hamada got 1st place on both stages.
Matsumoto built the stage.
Okay, let's go.
There's not much time left.
Okay.
The car is here.
If you win, you'll be in the top 10.
Let's go.
I Am My Father's Glittering Flower.
Start!
Oh, my love, my darling, I've hungered for your touch alone.
This is fun.
Thank you.
That was close.
$4,000.
If it wasn't for that grade.
That's right.
Oh, my love, my darling, I've hungered for your touch alone.
Okay, I'm in.
You're in, right?
Yes.
Okay.
All of them?
Matsumoto-san is the last one.
I'm the last one.
How many points do you have, Tanaka?
I'm in the top 10.
What?
Really?
Yes.
I'm still in the top 10.
Really?
You're that good?
Yes.
Yamada-san is in the top 10.
That's amazing.
I'm in the top 10.
Yes.
Yamada-san is in the top 10.
Let's go.
I Am My Father's Glittering Flower.
Start!
Oh, my love, my darling, I've hungered for your touch alone.
Okay.
That was close.
I knew you couldn't do it.
But then you hit the ball going like this.
Really?
Anyway, anyone would laugh.
You fell for it.
I did.
I'm in the top 10.
Okay.
The forever-final idol, Tsuyoshi, will get plus 6500 points.
To be honest, if I lose the game, I can't pay the money.
How much do you have left?
Zero.
I thought you had zero.
If you lose, it's over.
Even if you cry and laugh, this is the last one.
How much is it, Mr. Tanaka?
5,500 yen.
Mr. Endo?
5,000 yen.
Mr. Yamazaki, that's...
8,000 yen.
I think he'll be number one.
Mr. Hamada?
6,000 yen.
If you win all of these, you'll be number one, right?
That's for sure.
That's right, right?
Yes.
That's good.
It's just as I thought.
Now, let's go. This is the last one.
Now, Nieramekko, start!
Nieramekko
That's dirty!
Now, the results are out.
The winner is 25,500 yen, Mr. Matsumoto!
Thank you!
This is the last one.
Thank you very much.
It's a bit like the debut of Ima-dan.
Ima-dan
Don't fall for me!
Hamada's
Hamada's ears are
Ima-dan
It's blowing in the wind!
That's funny.
At a time like this, do your best.
That's right.
Do your best and go home.
I went to Russia.
Before that?
Yes.
I went there to have fun.
Russia is amazing.
I'm surprised.
Where?
It's surprisingly cheap.
I went to the strip.
Why?
Why did you go to Russia and go to the strip?
Russia is a strip.
It's a Hiroshiki strip.
I know Hiroshiki, but I don't know the strip.
I went to the strip.
When the Russians came out, they said,
Chichi-be-ron.
I said,
Be-ron-ron-be-ron.
I'm sorry.
I don't know the strip.
I'm sitting.
You're sitting.
When the chips come, they say,
Chichi-be-ron.
Be-ron-ron-be-ron.
Chichi-be-ron-be-ron.
I said,
I went with the staff.
Kurama-san, you're wearing glasses, right?
Kurama-san took off his glasses.
He said,
Be-ron-be-ron-be-ron.
What do you do?
You return it?
I returned it.
I took a spoon of coffee.
I said,
Ero-e-ro-e-ro-ro.
I put it in the cup.
It's a cup.
I'm working really hard.
And the chips.
When the money was given,
He gave me 10 rubles.
How much is that in Japanese yen?
I drank 10 rubles.
I said,
Arigatou.
I was very happy.
I returned it.
10 rubles is in yen.
It's 40 yen.
40 yen is a huge amount of money.
Which woman would give 40 yen?
Even my woman wouldn't do it.
She wouldn't do it.
Hey, Akagi.
What is this?
Can I read it?
Yes, please.
I am the director of Gaki no Tsukai.
My name is Akihiro Onuma.
Since the last time I was on a TV show,
My life has changed a lot.
When I walk in the city,
People point their fingers at me.
When I go on a trip to Hakone,
People surround me.
When I go to my sister-in-law's house,
I quit my part-time job.
But recently,
I have received incredible information.
There was a man who was more stingy than me.
His name is Matsumoto.
Why?
Wait a minute.
Why do you keep looking at me?
I am extremely stingy.
I cause a lot of trouble to people around me.
At this time,
Shouldn't we pursue the truth thoroughly in court?
Next week,
I will apply for the trial of Matsumoto Hitoshi.
Wait a minute.
Why are you looking at me?
Why are you getting a little closer?
I am extremely stingy.
I am not stingy at all.
I am telling you.
There is a video clip.
There is a man who is showing off.
Let's watch it.
Today? Now?
Yes.
I went to the pool once.
Pool?
With the usual members.
Who is the usual member?
Matsumoto.
You are so stingy.
The pool at the hotel costs 5,000 yen on weekdays.
It was a public hotel.
I went there on a Sunday.
The price of the pool is 2,000 yen.
I was angry with the price of the pool.
I decided to go to another pool.
I went to the pool next to the golf course.
The price of the pool was 4,500 yen.
It was very cheap.
I added 500 yen.
It looked like a restaurant inside.
I asked if I could eat two.
What should I do?
500 yen?
I asked for a four-person meal ticket.
I asked if I could eat two meals.
The price of curry was 1,000 yen.
The price of ice coffee was 600 yen.
I asked for curry and ice coffee.
I asked if I could eat it for 500 yen.
I was glad.
It was the first time.
I knew it was 1,000 yen.
You are stingy.
Are you stingy?
I went to a 5,000 yen pool.
The price of the pool is 2,000 yen on weekdays.
See you later.
If the price of the pool is 2,000 yen, give me 2,000 yen.
That's stingy.
I don't want you to give me.
Give me 40 yen.
I just did it.
Next week, we will talk about the trial of the judge.
The original video of the game, the legend of the 20th century.
Part 1.
It will be released on October 21.
100 people will be selected from 5 people.
We will give you a picture book of the best selection.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.
You can find the body of a concrete nail that is seen as the president of an unknown place.