Natsumoto Shintoshi is seriously going to the White-Hatou-Rin again.
In the afternoon of V-KIMA, the staff is once again summoned by the producer.
You did it with the White-Hatou-Rin pants, didn't you?
At first, I was told that the sword wasn't a toy.
You did it because you were frustrated, didn't you?
Then, it looked like you were wearing a helmet.
It was on January 2nd, wasn't it?
Was it the second time you did it?
It was the second time.
It was hard, wasn't it?
I looked at it again.
I think the balance of the body is a little bad.
I see.
But...
That's right.
It's dangerous.
It's over.
That's right.
However, in terms of the program, what do you think, Mr. Suga?
I think it's a little frustrating.
So...
One more time.
You said you didn't have a helmet.
You said you were serious about the sword.
It's better to do it.
It's dangerous, isn't it?
It's dangerous.
It doesn't matter if you can't see it.
Let's do it when it's over.
Let's do it.
However...
The rating was good for the end of the New Year.
It's called part 3.
You're still saying that.
Stop it.
Who are you talking to?
I'm talking to you.
Mr. Matsumoto, who has finally appeared, is back.
I want to talk to you.
I'm still talking to you.
It's still dark.
What do you mean?
The second time, you said you looked like you were wearing a helmet.
That's not possible.
That's the end of the story.
I'm wondering if it's okay to end it there.
I'm just wondering what the numbers are like.
Well, it's a matter of numbers.
I've been making progress like this.
But today...
Are you going to do it?
I don't know.
I'll prepare it for you.
This is a good thing.
It's dangerous.
Stop it.
8 horsepower.
I think that's about it.
After all...
The viewers see me as a cartoonist.
I don't think that's right.
Why?
Before that, it's like it starts and ends.
What?
You know that, right?
But I can't show you the two of them breathing.
You don't have to show me.
I can't show you the down-to-earth breathing.
What are you laughing at?
Well...
Let's get our minds together.
Will you do that for me?
Next time, do it right away.
As soon as I come in, I'll shake off my sword.
Okay.
Let's do it.
The time has come to make it come true.
The time has come.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Let's talk for another 30 minutes and go home.
Today's opening was quite interesting.
Today's opening was interesting.
You said the opening was interesting.
I have something I have to say.
What is it?
Matsumoto-kun's punishment game.
The second day of February.
Wednesday.
From this air, it's the day after tomorrow.
It's Sunday, so it's the day after tomorrow.
From 4.57 a.m. on Wednesday.
For three minutes until 5 a.m.
I'll do a live broadcast.
What was it before?
I...
Am I a fool?
I was doing it.
At that time, I got three minutes.
It's going to be a show.
Matsumoto-kun and...
Okan's Akiko...
For three minutes, I'll do a manzai.
Okan's Akiko will do a front-run.
It's really...
No, it's not that.
I'll give you 100 manzai.
Let's say okay.
Why do you have to do it at 4.50 a.m.?
I don't understand.
For three minutes, I have to do it.
I'll do a live broadcast.
I'll do a manzai.
Manzai.
I'll do it, but...
I'll do it with two answers.
Akiko will do it, too.
That's good.
I asked the staff once.
I don't know what he said.
I asked him once.
He said yes.
Before that, I was supposed to do a Goranger show.
From Hitoshi Ranger.
From Okan Ranger.
From Oton Ranger.
From Oni Ranger.
I was supposed to do it with all five of them.
But there are many problems with Goranger.
The problem with the copyright.
But I asked my dad to do it first.
And he said he wanted to do it with all five of us.
He said yes.
Your family is amazing.
What are you talking about?
That's what happened.
It was convenient.
That's right.
My dad said he didn't have to do it.
But my staff was paying attention.
My dad was so excited.
He said he didn't have to do it.
He was so excited.
But your dad will come, right?
My dad will come.
He will come to Onen.
He will come to Oikko.
The power is different.
Who?
My family.
I don't want him to refuse.
If you can watch it, please watch it.
If you can't watch it, you can watch it at the opening next week.
You can watch it at the opening next week.
You can watch it.
It's okay.
What I hate the most is...
With my mom...
We did it before.
When we were doing a comedy show.
We did it in the dressing room.
I told my mom not to do it.
I told her not to do it.
What do you think?
I told my staff not to show it on camera.
I told them to do it.
Otherwise, you can't watch the real Akiko.
I will make Akiko.
I told them to do it.
But you need to show it.
Yes, you need to show it.
You need to show the real Akiko.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please call me.
I will think about it.
You don't need to think about it.
He said it.
I will think about it.
You don't need to think about it.
Please call me.
I'm proud of you.
You don't have any shame.
That's your way.
Everyone has their own way.
I don't need to thank you.
No one has done it for me.
I don't want to see it, but if it comes out, I don't want to see it.
My grandma.
I don't want to say it's normal.
But I'm nervous.
I understand that.
I'm nervous.
I'm going to show it more and more.
Really.
Wait a minute.
What kind of role do you play in the comic book?
I have a small face.
Akiko is a mother of a rock.
I sing.
I think so.
Akiko has this.
I don't want to do it!
Miss Hawaii
I have a vague image of her
But that's how it is
What do you think of her outfit?
I think it's a moomoo
So it's Miss Hawaii
I see
It's really lucky
Normally you can't do it with her
Why?
You can't do it with just the three of you
If I lose this time it's because
Your grandma and my grandma
Will do a comic band with just the four of us
Your grandma is a drummer
If she does this
She'll come out in front of you
It's just that
I don't want to do it with your grandma in downtown
I'll definitely do it
This week
What is it?
Television?
It's not television
It's television
You're on TV but
It's more fun if you do it with your grandma
Why would I do it with my grandma?
My grandma and my two shots
It's not that fun
But your two shots are really fun
Is that so?
It's exactly the same
I'll definitely do it
For now
Wednesday
Tomorrow morning
At 4.57
I'll do it
I'm looking forward to it
I have to say this
But it's cold this year
It's cold
Why is it cold this year?
Why is it cold?
It suddenly got cold
It's already night
You're always playing the guitar
What is it?
I'm asking you
Why is it cold?
I'm the one who's thinking
I don't want to talk about that
But it's really cold this year
Aren't you wearing a patch today?
I'm wearing a patch
I've been wearing a patch since last November
That's early
Why are you like that?
You're still in your 30s
Don't be silly
Sometimes in rock songs, you pronounce it like ta
Ta
There are people who say ta
Why do you say ta?
For example, Kenji Fukuyama
Masaharu
Kenji is...
Masa?
How do you read this?
I don't remember the name of the story
I really don't remember
The kicker
The kicker is terrible
What was it?
Be My Baby
You're still in your 30s
What was it?
I don't understand what you're saying
Be My Baby
That's how you sing it
What song was it?
What was the chorus part?
Be My Baby
No
That's not it
That's not what I want to hear
You bastard
How did you become Be My Baby?
It's a dream
You can't sing it
I want to sing it
It's a dream
Doesn't anyone know?
I know
I won't tell you
You're everything
Be My Baby
Right?
You're young
Be My Baby
That's not it
What's wrong with you?
Be My Baby
That's why
If you're on a singing show
You can't sing the lyrics
You can
But you can't sing the whole thing
You're singing that?
My mom is always angry
When she watches TV
I don't know what she's saying
You're telling her to sing?
I think
Grandmas
Should be able to sing
While doing the dishes
In the kitchen
But the grandma
She's like
Be My Baby
That's not it
Oh yeah
The other day
We were going to a drama
There were a lot of people from Tokyo
Around
We were eating lunch
Osaka's okonomiyaki is really good
That's what they say
When you go to a live show
They eat it
Oh really?
It must be good
I don't think the okonomiyaki in Tokyo is good
That's what they say
Okonomiyaki
I ate it a lot
What is okonomiyaki?
That's it
Okonomiyaki
There's rice
Miso soup
Pickles
This room
This reaction
I was really surprised
You guys are wrong
Okonomiyaki and rice is really good
Really
Okonomi
It changes
You can eat as much rice as you want with one okonomiyaki
I can eat
This is not a joke
When I say this
The next person will say
Then I'll eat takoyaki with rice
That's what they say
But
Think about it
Don't underestimate me
Does takoyaki go well with rice?
That's right
But okonomiyaki goes well with rice
Don't you guys know the difference?
I don't know
I was alone
I feel sorry for you
I was crying
That's why I said
You can eat as much rice as you want
That's strange
Don't cut it
Miso soup
Pickles
You can eat as much as you want
Rice
It's really delicious
I don't know
It's a luxury to eat only okonomiyaki
That's right
In a sense, it's like eating curry roux
You can only eat curry roux
That's not allowed
That's how it is in Osaka
Then
If your grandmother forgets to cook rice
You can kill your whole family
You can kill
Omoto
3, 2, 1
Nomon
Omoto
Calm down
I don't know