Chiki Chiki Golf Battle! The punishment game is you!
What are you looking at?
Can you show me your face in front of the camera?
I don't know!
I was told that I can't take off my jacket.
I can't take it off.
Why are you still like this?
It doesn't matter if I'm wearing a jacket.
But it's hard to move.
It doesn't matter at all.
I don't care about my shoes.
I don't care about anything.
Even your shoes?
Yes!
I don't care about my shoes.
You don't care about your teeth?
Yes, yes, yes.
I see.
Let's do it.
What is this?
This is Shomei's army.
I know that!
What?
Can you borrow this?
What is the meaning of this?
Do you know what kind of plus side it has?
If you wear this, you won't be able to go to the gym.
Wow!
Either way, you can't do it.
Why?
Are you really left-handed?
Yes, I am.
Do you shoot with your left hand?
No, I shoot with my right hand.
Then, which way do you shoot with your glove?
I shoot with my right hand.
Either way, you can't do it.
I will shoot first.
Yes.
It is difficult to hit the pole like this.
This club is big.
Hey!
Like this.
It is good, isn't it?
Yes.
How do you hold it?
Hey!
It is important.
This is good.
Hey!
You are holding it.
It is empty.
Look at the ball.
It is good to hit it like this, isn't it?
It depends on how you feel.
Yes.
The ball is here.
It is good to hit it like this, isn't it?
It depends on how you feel.
You are not good at acting.
I am bad at acting.
It depends on how you feel.
Hey!
Don't go home.
It is good.
It is good to hit it like this, isn't it?
It depends on how you feel.
I see.
Hey!
It depends on how you feel.
I see.
You are thinking about it.
It is good.
It is hard.
I think so.
Yes.
It is good.
It depends on how you feel.
I see.
The teacher is coming today.
Yes.
Nice to meet you.
Excuse me, please teach the teacher what he just did.
You are used to it, aren't you?
I can do it if I get used to it.
Look.
Put your hand on the ball.
I will do it.
I got it.
Don't think about it.
Hello.
Are you not interested in the game?
What?
Look!
It is not working.
I know.
You are not interested in Islands.
No, I am not.
Are you not?
Look at me!
Look sideways!
What is this?
What?
You're so cool!
Why aren't you wearing your pants properly?
What?
Your pants
You're not an old man, you can hear me, right?
Well, it's fine
I'm getting angry
Today, we have to think about the punishment game
We haven't decided yet if we're going to play golf
We're going to play golf
Golf, right?
You were pretty good at golf
It was my first time, but I'm pretty good
No, you're not
No, no, but I'm really...
There's no sports that I can't do
I've mastered everything
With this slender body?
That's right
This quickness
First, when I was swimming
This was amazing
I thought it was bad
Wait a minute
You thought it was bad when you were swimming?
What was that like?
I was getting better and better
What do you mean?
What do you mean you were getting better and better?
It was really fast
The speed was fast
Fast?
If I kept swimming like this
I felt like I was going to get splashed with water
I thought this was bad
If you get splashed with water, you can go to the movies
But as a comedian, I'd feel bad
But I can still go to the movies
If you get splashed with water
But when I do this
If I get splashed with water
No one would say I'm cute
Since you've mastered a lot
You should be able to play golf
For now
I'll practice a bit more
Let's think about the punishment
Let's stop being scared
What do you want to do?
If there's nothing scary
What?
Let's do something embarrassing
I've done something embarrassing
I'll sell my female hormones
And make breasts
Even if you sell your female hormones
Your breasts won't come out
They'll come out
They won't
They will
It's silicone
Then I'll put in silicone
What are you?
You're doing something embarrassing
You're competing
You're losing
You're next to your father
You're cutting with a knife
You're putting silicone inside
What's so embarrassing about that?
Let's do it, it's fun
It's fine
You're talking like this
If you do it like this
It's fine
It's fun
You're stupid
Put it on your nose
What are you doing with your nose?
I won't put silicone inside my nose
You won't
What will you do if you put silicone inside your nose?
Even if you don't understand
If you put it in here
It won't come out
It's plastic
It's like a French nose
You can't do that
You lost a punishment game
You put silicone inside your nose
You're laughing
When you stop laughing, it's over
You have to talk normally after that
In your heart
It's fine
It's over
You can't do that
If you go to a place like that
You'll be surrounded by a wire
And you'll be riding a bike
That's possible
What about that?
That's possible?
It's possible
Right?
Look, everyone is saying it
Do it
Who are you saying it to?
Are you saying it to this person?
Wait a minute
Why am I the one saying it?
Hama-chan won't lose
Hama-chan won't lose?
It's fine
It's like a gacha pin
Don't say things like that
You have to bring all your family
It's fine
If you lose, will you bring your mother, father, and brother?
I'll bring all of them
Bring all four of them and do a family skit
I'll bring all of them and do a family skit
I'll bring all of them
You guys
You'll die of starvation
The day you see your family
It's fine if it's you
You have four family members
I have five
It's not about the number of people
If you lose, instead of doing a family skit
Do a Go-Ranger
With your face painted
I only have four people
It's fine
I'm here with you, so do a Go-Ranger
For now, take the lead
Go-Ranger
This is delicious
There's a story
In Hikoku
The dog fight in Tosa
You have to break it
Well, well, well
The old men are fighting
It won't end with a well
Well, well, well
Don't they do that in Japan?
The dog fight
That one
This one, right?
Yes, yes, yes
That's good
That one, right?
Let's go to Spain on this show
Spain
We went to Okinawa
Let's go to Spain next
That's right
If you can do it, that's good
Let's increase the number of pro-wrestlers
What are you doing?
Say it
Family?
Do a family skit
You said it
My dad is weird
I can't catch a running mouse
Give me your letter
For the time being
Don't introduce me
How long have you been talking?
What time is it?
It's already 7.40
7.40?
Hello
She's coming
Let's go
Yes
Let's give the letter to the person we want to introduce
Let's introduce
Let's start with the general
What do you like? Spaghetti?
And downtown
Thank you
Please leave it here
Let's introduce the letter
First, this person
From Ibaraki
Yuko Naito, 17 years old
Kama-chan used to live in a car
Is this true?
If it's true, please tell us more about your life
I didn't live in a car
You used to drive a Mk2
Yes
If you didn't go home
If you didn't go home at all
You were always in the car
I didn't go home
I just packed my luggage
I was asked if I lived in a car
It was amazing
The luggage
Autumn, winter, summer, spring
All of them
What's with the Masatoshi collection?
That's not true
It's because there were a lot of clothes
I didn't put summer, spring, autumn, winter
I was surprised
That's true
It was packed
Yes
Everyone was looking for you
They were looking for Golgo 13
Right?
That's what it is
Please read it
My pen name is Nagano Ken
I hate Mach-chan
There are a lot of people like that
My friend Yuuki is a big fan of Masatoshi
He always says he likes Ike-ike
So he became Ike-ike
He shaved his hair
He bought a bodycon suit
He started to wear flashy makeup
Yuuki said he couldn't change it
Now he's completely Ike-ike
He used to be a quiet and cute kid
Give me back my old Yuuki!
He's watching Gakitsukai
Please say something to Yuuki
Go back to normal
He only listens to what you say
He doesn't listen to me
I value Yuuki
Now Yuuki is Ike-ike
He doesn't have many friends
There's no one who says I'm a good kid
Please, Mach-chan
Go back to your old Yuuki
There's no need to go back
I want everyone in the world to be like that
So
If he becomes Ike-ike
And asks you what you think
It's okay
I don't know if I can meet him
I feel sorry for him
That's true
But even today's guests
They're all wearing too much
They're hiding their skin too much
It's the fashion of this time
This season
This isn't okay
More, more
Show more
It's cold outside
That's not okay
It's better to dress like a primitive person
Where in the world do you think you're going?
A woman wearing pants is the worst
It's all skirts
Skirts that you can see
That's good
Right?
Everyone, don't think too much
Even if you dig out your own blood
I don't think much
Don't lie
I'll try to dig out my own blood
You'll do it?
I don't care
I don't think it's bad
Really?
You can let me out
Freely?
You can let me out freely
I don't think I'm a weirdo
I don't feel anything
Everyone, more
What do you feel?
What?
You don't feel anything even if you dig out your own blood
What do you feel?
In the situation where I dug out my own blood
You don't have to dig out your own blood
Well, in that case
You don't feel anything even if you dig out your own blood
What do you feel other than your own blood?
If you dig out your own blood and put something in it
What are you surprised at?
No, no
You're hiding too much
Hiding too much is normal
You're hiding like a real person
That's not good
Go to another country
There are countries where they don't hide their breasts
They only hide their bottom
If they hide their bottom, I think it's fine
Yes, yes
You're lying
That's right
Men only do this with bamboo
Bamboo?
I'm doing bamboo, but you're sticking out your balls
What?
Do you know what clothes were originally for?
To prevent bacteria from entering
I'm not ashamed of being able to see bamboo
I'm just doing it so I don't get hurt
I'm going into the forest
So I don't get hurt
So why are you sticking out your balls?
I'm not hurt
That's not good
What's not good?
If you get hit, it hurts
What do you do if you get cut?
There's a stone in the river
I don't know why it's round
It's round because it's flowing
It's round because you're sticking out your balls
It's not round because everyone's sticking out their balls
It's round because of the wind
It's round because you're sticking out your balls
You're making fun of me
It's true
You don't know anything
Even your nose is round
It's round because it's sticking out
What?
What did you say?
It's round because my nose is sticking out
My ears are sticking out though
What?
Ears
You're sticking out your ears
No, we are just sticking out our ears
We're sticking out our noses
But our ears are still sticking out
We're sticking out our ears
Your ears are sticking out and your nose is sticking out too!
I'm digging out your chin!
Your chin is round!
But the part you're digging out...
Isn't it round?
It's long!
If this was round...
I would think so too...
But it's really long!
It's going to be round from now on!
Your fingers are going to be round!
The Doraemon is going to be round!
That's a cat from the future!
It's going to be round!
That's how it's going to be from now on!
I can't accept this...
I can't accept this ear!
It's not round!
Your ears aren't sticking out!
It's sticking out!
This is the ear!
I'm digging out your chin!
It's not round!
It's going to be round!
This is the ear!
It's not sticking out!
You're persistent!
That's enough!
So...
We're done for today!
That's all for today!
Next week...
Let's think about it!
That's all for today!
See you next week!
Bye!
Next week...
How are you going to buy it?
So...
This is the final decision.
Let's do that.
Until now, Yuta has lined up all of them.
My father too?
Your father too?
Your father and the one with the long nose.
He lined up all of them.
He chose them all.
He did this and that.
The one with the long nose is impossible.
Anyway, all of them.
The assistants too.
They are still recruiting.
Please look forward to it.
That's all for now.
I'm not going to be a kid anymore.
See you next week.
Please look forward to it.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.