The next day
Father!
Why?
In the first episode of Daki no Tsukai,
Machan got hurt!
Right?
Every time.
Machan had a hard time before, but this time he got hit in the face during a TV shoot and his face got swollen.
He couldn't show his face in front of everyone.
So I'm going to show you a chiki-chiki video.
First of all, let me show you the opening of the chiki-chiki race.
Until then, I went to the venue and walked around the nearby road.
This is the first chiki-chiki race with a title.
This is the opening of the chiki-chiki race.
Today, I'm working on the machine.
Mr. Matsumoto, please show me.
How are you doing?
Are you sweating?
Chiki-chiki is a gentleman's sport in the United States.
Mr. Matsumoto, please show me.
What are you doing?
I can't reach it.
It's really hard.
Who is this person?
I'm sorry.
Mr. Matsumoto, please show me.
We can't speak English.
I want to speak, but I can't.
I'm your Geos.
A lesson to speak.
Geos of conversation.
Oh, no.
It wasn't in. Bright.
I'll put it in now. Bright.
Light and bright for coffee.
It's light and light.
Isn't it?
A good international phone.
In addition, we have a good discount service.
For example, Merit 10
It's a 9.5% discount.
An international phone.
Attractive 10-color color pochette
Today color group pochette
From the colorful Honda Primo
Did you get hit again?
The 13th time.
It's been a long time.
The authentic taste of the north.
Well, that's right.
Cool figure.
I've seen a manly figure.
Now, let's continue.
Let's buy a lot of Chiki Chiki.
We went to various stores separately.
I'm going to buy something for less than 100,000 yen.
I did it.
When?
90 years.
I don't remember.
Is it okay?
Take this 10,000 yen.
Buy 10kg of things.
10,000 yen.
I wonder if there's a 10kg woman.
That's not what it means.
How many kilograms is this?
It's a house.
What are you talking about?
It's funny.
But...
It's a house.
How many kilograms is your father?
First of all, please give me one.
What did you buy?
Hey.
What is this?
Do you have a receipt?
I don't have it.
I don't know.
Why?
I don't get receipts on Japanese TV.
I bought it myself.
I really like it.
Stop it.
That's a bullet.
What is it?
Cat sand.
It's a stuffed animal.
I don't need it.
Stop it.
It won't move.
The reason why I was late.
This guy suddenly jumped out.
It's like a Japanese bridge.
It's hard to catch a Japanese bridge.
I can't catch a Japanese bridge.
It's true.
Let's measure it.
How much is it?
It feels good.
It's 7.5.
It's 9.5.
It's a snack.
It's a dryer.
I don't need it.
Will it move?
I don't know.
Put it on.
Hey.
Don't step on it.
It's 10 kilograms.
10 kilograms.
Hey.
It's not moving.
What?
It's 6 kilograms.
Let's go.
Okay.
Hey.
It's over.
It's gone.
It's 10 kilograms.
It's true.
I'm glad there were only two.
It's a face of a joke.
Hey.
I won.
It says 5 kilograms.
Next.
I don't like my body.
What is this?
You don't like your body?
Look at it.
It's blue.
I don't like my body.
It will run around the shopping street.
You run away.
Hey.
You are very fast.
You run away.
I know you don't like it.
I'll chase you.
Go.
Hey.
What are you doing?
This is very cool.
Where are you now?
I'm here.
Hey.
You are a fool.
I don't like my body.
It's going down.
Where is the guy in a strange costume?
Hey.
Hurry up.
You are very fast.
You run away.
I don't like my body.
Wait.
Where are you now?
I don't like my body.
Hey.
Where are you now?
I don't like my body.
My sons are very bad.
I'll go.
Hey.
I think I prepared dinner.
What are you going to eat tonight?
I'm going to eat a hamburger.
Don't be shy.
Hey.
What did you eat tonight?
I'm going to eat a hamburger.
Don't be shy.
What are you going to eat tonight?
I think I prepared dinner.
I'm going to eat a hamburger.
I think you can make me a snack.
What is that?
Snack?
My recent snack is this.
I put a page on it.
Do you know why I put it here?
I hate boring stories.
Don't be silly.
Don't you think so?
Next work.
Let's shoot a movie.
What is it, Oto-san?
What?
What is it? What is your favorite word?
Well, I love the Giant Army, so...
Like Nakashima-senshi said, the Giant Army will never die.
Right?
Did you just say that?
What do you mean, right?
Yoshio!
What is it, Oto-sama?
What is it? Yoshio, what is your favorite word?
Well, I'm a genius, so when a genius forgets, it comes back.
Like this, it's not a big deal, though.
Thank you very much.
It's good that it was quick.
Waruo!
What is it?
Waruo.
What is it, Tabitabi?
Tabitabi?
What is it? What is your favorite word?
Huh?
What is your favorite word?
It's not that.
Well, it's not that, but it's a favorite word.
Kamishihougatame.
That's a good one.
It's a favorite word.
It's a four-letter word.
A four-letter word?
Like, gaden, gaden-insui.
It's a four-letter word like that.
Daisuke Hanako.
Now, the next one.
What is it?
What is your favorite word?
Now, the next one is,
Grandfather and Grandmother Hide-and-seek.
Mr. Tokujirou Namikoshi and his aunt Komori
are the guests of Grandfather and Grandmother.
They've come all the way here,
and they've hidden themselves in a horrible place.
It's like this show, though.
They don't really treat the guests well.
Okay, Hanako.
I've set everything up for you guys.
Okay.
First of all, you don't know this.
Really?
Even though I've been a veteran detective for 50 years,
I've never been able to follow this path.
Really?
Yes.
Now, let's go.
If you get it, you'll get it right away.
I don't think he's found yet.
There are people like this at the station sometimes.
Grandfather and Grandmother Hide-and-seek.
He doesn't want to do it.
This guy.
I get it.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to do it?
Well, he likes it, so leave it alone.
But I couldn't stop him from going this way.
This is really funny.
It's Konori's grandmother.
Grandmother.
What?
I wonder what he does when he wakes up in the morning.
It can't be a male toilet, can it?
What are you doing?
Grandmother, it's like you've got a pattern.
Grandmother.
Grandmother is a celebrity.
Grandmother, it's like you've got a pattern.
Here we are.
It's called Chiki Chiki Nozohime.
This is a song that you two like.
It's 10 songs each.
Nozohime did it.
It's funny.
Masumoto-kun is very enthusiastic about GALANTE.
Let's take a look.
First of all, Mr. Yoshida.
And the performer is Mr. Ryodo Yokomori.
I'm sorry, but I'm crazy about you.
GALANTE, GALANTE.
It's funny.
I'm crazy about you.
You left without saying a word.
I'm laughing at the past.
I wish I could hate you.
I like you after all.
Yoshida.
I was confident.
I put in too much emotion.
What's wrong with you?
You didn't become your own.
The impersonation went ahead.
I see.
That's good.
Who is it? Who is it? Who is it?
The shadow of the night beyond the sky.
The gacha man with white wings.
I'll sing until the end.
You're a man, aren't you?
You have to live strong.
Don't worry about me.
I'm praying.
Yoshida.
I can't do it by myself.
It's the first time I've heard it.
I don't want to be masturbated.
Did you know we were recording?
Really?
I think this is new to everyone.
We're going to visit the Yamazaki family.
It was hard at the time.
Hello.
I heard you moved.
I brought you a cake as a souvenir.
Thank you.
Let's eat.
I'm worried about the direction of the house you moved to.
That's right.
In the real world, I'm calling the most famous person.
Please come in.
Teacher.
This is the room I moved to.
This is terrible.
What?
You can't do this.
Everyone's on it.
I told you not to do it.
This is bad.
You can't do this.
Everyone can't do this?
I told you not to do it.
There's an attachment to your body.
Don't do it.
Listen to me.
Thank you very much.
Good luck.
Let's go to the doctor's office.
Thank you very much.
Please come again.
We'll go home together.
I'll come again next week.
I'll be back in three weeks.
How was it?
As I said last time,
I think there are many people who saw it after the time changed.
If you haven't seen it before,
I'm sure you've seen it.
Masumoto will appear with a beautiful face.
Thank you very much for tonight.
Goodbye until this time tomorrow.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.