This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
What to do. What to do. The natural destruction caused by the civilized society.
Let me introduce the cast.
First of all, the first person to deal with the environmental pollution of the earth.
Professor of the former Cambridge University, Mr. Hitoshi Matsumoto, who presided over the World Natural Protection Campaign.
Mr. Hosei Yamazaki, chairman of the World Dirt Deposit Committee, who said that he was interested in the dirt of the earth by his own dirt.
Mr. Shouzo Endo, a member of the Seto Inland Sea Fisheries Association, who woke up from Shikoku to say that he would like to make an appeal to the ocean in recent years.
Mr. Naoki Tanaka, the director of the Blue Sky and Sun
Mr. Kenji Suga, the director of the Nangoku branch of the National Nature Company.
Mr. Kozo Komurasaki, a member of the Japan Agriculture Association, who strongly opposes forest deforestation and continues to support Japan's agriculture.
Mr. Yoshinobu Nakamura, a heat island narcissist who continues to fight with the country on the issue of global warming.
Mr. Akihiro Ohnuma, chairman of the Tateyama Tanuki Association, who has been observing the ecology of wild animals in Japan for 15 years.
And Mr. Souichiro Hamada, the host of the discussion program.
Good evening, everyone. Today's theme is the natural disaster that will affect the civilized society, and there are three years left in the 20th century.
Today, I would like to discuss what we should do in the face of the global warming, and what is important for us human beings.
I will listen to your opinions little by little. Mr. Tanaka, what do you think?
Well, I think we have to pay more attention to the current environment in Japan.
What do you mean?
For example, the construction of golf courses.
We are building more and more golf courses, even though we have plenty of them.
I think the current Japanese government's leisure facilities are strange.
What do you think, Mr. Sugata?
I don't think that's right.
Mr. Tanaka?
Golf is something that should be done.
It's not that. The person who does it is the most important person.
The person who doesn't do it is the least important person.
It's not that we should do it.
Well, if you ask me...
It's strange to say something like this on a day like this.
Well, let's say...
Even if you put it on a signboard...
It's made out of wood.
Isn't that strange?
No, it's not.
That's right.
By cutting down the forest, it will eventually be destroyed.
Because humans need oxygen to breathe.
I think it's very problematic to cut down the forest that produces oxygen.
What do you think, Mr. Aonuma?
When it comes to making a golf course...
Wild raccoons and foxes...
No, no.
You're saying that because you're bad at golf.
No, it's not like that.
Well, let's listen to him.
You're saying that you're bad at golf.
Why do you keep making golf courses?
No, it's not like that.
It's not just humans who live in this world.
If you think about that and cut down the forest...
Wait a minute.
Komura, what do you think?
I'm listening to your opinions from here.
I'd like to ask you how much you understand the importance of nature.
No, no.
What's important is important, but...
It's a matter of temperature, isn't it?
In the end, the destruction of nature is...
That's right.
Nature is important to humans.
It gives us peace of mind.
Does everyone understand that?
Mr. Aonuma, what do you think?
That's definitely true.
Nature is important to animals, isn't it?
That's right.
Mr. Nakamura, what do you think?
The warming is going on now.
What we have to think about now is how to stop the warming.
Mr. Matsumoto, why are you laughing?
I'm not laughing.
What do you think?
I'm not in a position to say anything about the destruction of nature.
What do you mean?
When you come here, you come here by car.
Whether you take the train or take the bus, you come here.
At that point, I think we're destroying nature.
Mr. Aonuma, what do you think?
Wild animals are said to be decreasing every 13 minutes.
If that's the case, we have to think about the destruction of humanity.
Thousands of years ago, there was only one animal per year.
Wait a minute.
Mr. Tanaka, what do you think?
After all, there are times when the life of an animal can be stolen by human waste.
I don't have a shirt.
I want to say something.
What do you think about the destruction of nature?
There are people who play golf.
You don't have a shirt.
I think it has nothing to do with the environment.
Mr. Endo, what do you think?
I play golf, but I think there is a problem with the sea and the fish in the sea.
Mr. Tanaka, what do you think?
It's a problem that pollutes the sea.
Everyone's opinion is wrong.
I think we should learn more about the sea.
Mr. Masao, what do you think?
I'm sorry.
It can't be helped.
What about Mr. Yamasaki?
I think it has nothing to do with golf.
It is the first step of nature.
It can't be helped.
It has nothing to do with the environment.
What about the body?
I think it has nothing to do with the environment.
It has nothing to do with the environment.
Mr. Yamasaki, you don't understand the meaning.
Mr. Komura, what do you think?
I don't understand your opinion.
Why do you say that?
Are you a woman or a man?
I'm a man.
That's okay.
Golf is okay.
The sea is okay.
What else?
The sky.
The sky?
The environment is bad.
What do you think?
Mr. Masao, what do you think?
I'm sorry.
It can't be helped.
What about the sky?
The sky is gray.
What are you talking about?
It's just the weather.
It's a cloudy sky.
It's because the sky is strong.
Well...
It seems that our stories are different.
I don't know what to do.
Can someone summarize it for me?
Can anyone do it?
I think the individual should think more.
I think you should think more about Japan.
I often go abroad.
When I go abroad, I see a lot of stars.
I can't see it in Tokyo.
For example?
India.
India?
I don't understand the story.
I can't see it.
What do you think about wild animals?
There are a lot of wild animals.
There are a lot of wild animals called natural monuments.
I think this is strange.
There are a lot of wild animals.
I think it's strange that it becomes a natural monument.
I think the individual should think more.
What do you think, Mr. Suga?
I can't let Mr. Onuma come to the competition.
You are particular about it.
I don't want him to come.
I'm talking about environmental destruction.
Mr. Onuma comes to the golf course every time.
It's not a shot.
It's not a play.
A few hectares of forest has been destroyed.
A raccoon is in the forest.
You're talking about a raccoon.
I'm a party to protect the raccoon.
That's what happens.
What's going to happen?
You're talking about a raccoon.
It's the end of the ecosystem.
I have to stop it here.
There were three raccoons in Tateyama last year.
Who?
Think about it on a global scale.
What do you think, Mr. Matsumoto?
To be honest, I think there's a problem.
I see.
No, that's not true.
I think it's a disorganized meeting.
I think everyone is aware of it.
It's not just from tomorrow.
We have to do it now.
What's going on with electric cars?
I see.
The exhaust gas will be gone.
Electric cars won't help the environment.
I want to tell the company about it.
We need solar power to make electricity.
We need to protect the sky from the sun.
What do you mean?
We need solar power to make electricity.
We need the power of the sun.
Damn it.
What's this?
As I said before, we need solar power.
We need to think about it.
I think it's impossible to fix the earth.
I see.
I can't open it.
I can't figure it out.
What do you think?
From today, tomorrow, and the day after tomorrow,
we can do one thing at a time.
What do you mean by yesterday?
I'm sorry.
You don't know what you're doing.
Yes.
Let's think about it.
That's a good idea.
I don't know.
I think it's better not to get in the car from tomorrow.
You don't get in the car, do you?
As I said before, it's not from tomorrow.
I'm already a champion.
So, from today.
I see.
When I leave this place, I'll walk home.
What do you think, Endo?
This country is a developed country.
I think we need to make it a law.
I think we can do one simple thing.
If the garbage is falling, everyone picks up the garbage.
That's the only way to improve the environment.
That's not what I mean.
Don't drop the garbage.
I see.
That's a good idea.
What do you think, Nakano?
I'm a natural person.
I don't throw away the garbage.
I see.
I think it's better to start with small things.
What do you think, Matsumoto?
I'm going to tell you from tomorrow.
It's not from tomorrow.
It's now.
Now?
I don't know why you don't think about it.
Well, well, well.
I can't talk to you while I'm saying that.
You mean we should do our best, right?
Yes.
Am I wrong?
Well, that's your opinion.
Let's do our best.
It's important.
What do you think, Yasugawa?
Well, I think we should stop throwing away garbage and make it a law.
I see.
We shouldn't cut down the grass.
What do you think, Tanaka?
I was disappointed to come here today.
I was disappointed in your lack of consciousness.
Consciousness?
This is a good place.
I've realized what I usually say.
I've finally realized what I usually say.
I can't talk to you anymore.
I won't come here again.
Don't say that.
I see.
What about you, Yasugawa?
I want you to stop throwing away garbage.
I think we should exchange opinions and do our best.
I see.
Am I wrong?
I've heard a lot of opinions from you.
But I can't do it.
I can't do it.
That's all for today.
Let's meet again next time.
OK?
Let's discuss it again.
Thank you for coming today.
Thank you.
To Be Continued...
Well...
It's over, isn't it?
It's over.
Well...
I'm sure you have your excuses.
Yes.
You want to make an excuse, don't you?
What are you talking about?
I don't want to make an excuse.
There was a long nose.
Was it long?
I thought it was a mistake.
I see.
I was surprised.
I guess you didn't have the skill to follow us.
I guess so.
That's true.
How did it go?
What did you guys say?
Well...
I guess it was a long nose.
It's a long nose if you laugh every day.
It's funny even if I see it now.
What is it?
Is it a god's word?
It's funny.
Well...
It's over today.
Yes, it's over.
Well...
You said you wouldn't get in the car.
I said it.
You said it.
I did.
I think it's better not to get in the car from tomorrow.
You won't get in, right?
That's right.
I'm sure of it.
Well...
I've prepared something for you.
That thing from Hawaii.
If you're going to say something like that...
You can just walk home.
You said it yourself.
I was looking forward to it when you said it.
I was scared.
Shall we go home?
Let's go home.
Is he coming?
Where do you live?
Odaiba.
In Odaiba?
If it wasn't a car, what train would it be?
It would be the Yurikamon line.
It's a picture.
What? I don't get it.
I don't get it at all.
It's a natural theory.
It's like Odaiba.
Odaiba.
Can I take a picture of you?
Can I take a picture of you now?
This is interesting.
I like the way you're going to say it.
That's right.
It's the first time I've seen you say that you're not jealous.
I've seen that.
Don't say that.
Don't say that you're not jealous.
We're living together.
The first time I saw you, you looked like a fool.
You looked like this.
I see.
When you get on the train, you can draw a figure.
Like a girl's loose socks.
You can go to the bathroom.
You can go to Ginza line.
You look like a girl's loose socks.
I'm a little scared.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm Osaki.
You still look like a girl's loose socks.
You're still a girl's loose socks.
Thank you for your hard work.
Love Hurts
A small incident
hurt my love.
You jumped out of the room.
Under the winter sky.
Like the falling snow.
I should have loved you.
Our love is.
Next is Takeshiba.