It's time for the children's game, Mokura-Tataki Game!
We're here at the cold sky.
Yes, it's cold.
What is this cold sky?
Mokura-Tataki.
Yes, I'm going to skip it.
We're going to play a classic game called Mokura-Tataki.
I see.
We're going to capture the hearts of children.
From adults to children.
I see.
Let's go to the children's game.
Go!
Mokura!
Go into the middle.
First, slide.
He slipped once.
What is Mokura?
It's my name.
You're Mokura.
And you?
I'm Kong.
He slipped twice.
From now on, each person will be adjusted.
We have a clock here for 30 seconds.
If you succeed three times out of ten, you win.
What do you mean by three times?
If you don't get hit four times, you win.
If you don't get hit three times, you win.
It's a wonderful game.
Here it comes.
This is a gift.
What?
Who is it?
Why don't you do it?
This beat.
Are you serious?
Is this a beat?
No, it's not.
This is a gift.
Are you serious?
Look at this.
There's something wrong with golf.
All right.
Stop it.
Let's do it.
All right.
I'll tell you something good.
Both of you...
You should be on the show.
I'll tell you something good.
Both of you should be on the show.
All right.
I'll do my best.
You should be on the show.
Let's do it.
All right.
Ready.
Start.
One time.
Two times.
Three times.
You lose.
I got hit three times.
No.
This is strange.
Here it comes.
Ready.
Go.
What?
The end.
You have no talent.
Do you want to make another chance?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I'll do my best.
I'm sure you can beat me.
Can you hit me here?
I can't move.
Suya-san.
You'll get hurt.
This is a nuisance.
Let's take this.
What are you doing?
This is a nuisance.
I can see well.
What are you doing?
I'll give you a bottle.
Spit it out.
The air is coming out.
I'm busy.
This is a nuisance.
I'll give you a bottle.
I'm tired.
What do you think?
Is this okay?
Did you win?
I'll kill you someday.
Wait a minute.
Is this a school trip bus?
Do you want to sit in a bus?
There are many.
It's creepy.
Do you want to sit in a bus?
This is a band.
There was something to celebrate today, right?
I passed the exam today.
You're going to get in the car again, aren't you?
To be honest, I was relieved when you got in the car.
Why?
You stole gasoline again.
You're going to commit a crime.
If I tell you the truth, I don't want you to get in the car.
Are you stupid?
You're going to get in the car again, aren't you?
I've never had an accident when I was in front of you.
You're lying.
Are you serious?
You were spinning in the high speed.
No, I'm not.
Are you stupid?
You're going to get in the car again, aren't you?
What did you do once?
What's the thing that can break the tire?
The standing wave phenomenon.
I got in the car.
I was spinning in the high speed.
Suddenly, I heard the sound of a helicopter.
I thought it was strange.
The back of the car was shaking.
I thought it was me.
The tire on the right side of the car was broken.
The rest of the tire was broken.
Then I heard the sound of a helicopter.
It was a penguin toy.
There was such a thing, but there was no accident.
Did you hook your grandmother?
Have you ever cut your grandfather's Achilles tendon?
Is your grandfather like this?
Everyone is angry.
But your grandfather has a crack in his ear.
Your grandfather suddenly stopped.
I couldn't stop it.
My grandfather suddenly stopped.
Because your Achilles tendon was broken.
Because I don't have the strength to hold on.
It's strange.
You took a lot of time.
My grandfather said that.
My grandfather was 70 years old.
I have the same age as my grandfather.
My grandfather challenged me for the third time.
I was surprised.
Did you challenge me again?
I tried again the next day, but I couldn't do it.
If I fail today, I'll quit.
My grandfather was a little blue.
I didn't say that.
I've been driving for 70 hours.
I was watching him drive.
I said, of course you are.
When I came out, my grandfather looked like this.
I passed.
I'm glad I passed.
I don't like it when I'm checked.
I've been watching him drive for a long time.
My grandmother is the worst.
Why are you stretching your neck?
I'm fine.
I'm stretching my neck.
My grandmother is the worst.
Animals jump out.
There is a short-legged dog with brown hair.
It's like a big dog.
When I drove it, it jumped out.
I thought it was a fried chicken.
I thought so.
I thought it was strange.
I hit the car.
I thought I would kill it.
It jumped out.
It's like me.
It's true.
It's hard to drive a car.
When I got in the car, I had a stomachache.
You mean you want to throw up?
Yes.
It's hard.
It's a one-way street.
It's very crowded.
I have a stomachache.
It's like knocking on the entrance.
Please get out of the car.
It came out of the keyhole.
If there was a door.
It came out smoothly.
It's hard.
I want you to think about it.
It's like this.
I understand.
It's like this with this hand.
It moves little by little.
But I can't step on the accelerator.
It's like this.
It's really like this.
The person next to you will be surprised.
It's like this next to you.
It's really like this.
But the front tire is like this.
The front tire is like this.
It moves like this.
It's really like this.
What is this?
There is a sauce on it.
It's hard.
This is human.
Mix it.
Take the sauce off.
It's hard.
I have a question for you two.
What is in the head of Tetsuko Kuroyanagi?
What do you mean?
It doesn't look like hair.
There must be something in it.
What is in it?
I don't know.
I don't know either.
What is in it?
It's like that.
It's like a treasure.
What is a treasure?
It's sweet.
You are a fool.
It's like a bag of sweets.
It's sweet.
It's like that.
I went to drink with my friend and I lost my memory.
This is the first time.
Have you ever drunk so much that you can't remember?
No.
I drink so much that I can't remember.
I remember when I was flirting with a girl at the club.
Wait.
You took me to the past.
What?
You brought me here.
I didn't bring you here.
What are you talking about?
You called me and came here.
I called you.
I'm coming.
Then I'll bring you a girl.
Why are you saying that?
I didn't say that.
You are a fool.
Wait.
Someone help me.
Please.
Hey.
You brought me here.
I didn't bring you here.
I just followed you.
That's not true.
I brought you here.
One of the four of us was drunk.
I didn't drink.
I thought you didn't have a memory.
I didn't drink so much.
I was singing all the time.
So you remember.
I remember.
What do you mean?
I don't remember what kind of strawberry talk we had.
I didn't talk to her enough to have a strawberry talk.
What are you talking about?
Stop it.
Don't stretch your neck.
Really?
I'll tell you.
I went home.
I didn't do anything.
I don't want to talk about that.
I had a new year party the other day.
The vice president came.
The vice president of Japan TV.
His name is Matsumoto.
Matsumoto, good job today.
And Horiguchi.
What?
That old man is strange.
He keeps saying Hama-chan.
And Horiguchi.
Horiguchi even though he is Hama-chan.
Horiguchi Hamaoka.
It was the same today.
I went to Japan TV today.
The president gave me a letter of appreciation.
There were two letters at first.
Hamada Masa.
It's called Masatoshi.
Matsumoto Hitoshi.
I read it.
I read the letter of appreciation.
Matsumoto's letter of appreciation.
Matsumoto Jinshi.
You read it at first.
You read it at the third time.
Jinshi.
It's similar, isn't it?
I'm really sorry, but that old man is stupid.
Shock.
Enemy.
Telephone.
Paco.
Paco?
How many times do I want to hit my head?
It's strange, isn't it?
There are a lot of strange things.
Recently, Matsumoto and Hama-chan often say it's tight.
I found something tight at home.
I found something tight.
Please give me your opinion.
An umbrella made of an empty tobacco box.
It's tight.
The old man in the taxi.
It's hanging.
It's tight.
A cardboard box with Natsumo's father written on it.
I'll forgive you for that.
It can't be helped.
It's written like that.
My father always wears my underwear.
It's my year's underwear.
It's your family's underwear.
It's my family's underwear.
My father always wears my underwear.
It's written on the white brief.
Father.
It's tight.
I didn't have a bath at that time.
I can't go to the bath with my father.
But sometimes I go to the bathroom.
It's written on my father's underwear.
It's cool.
It's manly.
It's okay.
That's all.
Let's go home.
I'll put this away for the time being.
It's a marionette.
What is a marionette?
You did it the day before yesterday.
What is this?
I want to see it.
Try it.
There are two fists here.
Are you kidding me?
Don't move here.
Are you angry at this time?
I'm angry at this time.
Don't move.
Tell me how to move.
Like this.
Can I bend this?
How is it?
Like this.
Wait a minute.
It's true.
There are two fists.
Don't laugh.
Yes.
It's true.
I heard that the pig won.
Takahana?
What are you doing?
It's spring.
You are a strange person.
Why is everyone making such a fuss?
It was amazing.
What is it?
There was an old man.
It was amazing.
It would be nice if my father was so great.
Really?
I don't know Kazushige at all.
Who is Kazushige?
You are a professional.
What is it?
You are Kazushige Nagashima.
Yes, I am Kazushige Nagashima.
Everyone likes Nisei.
Who likes Nisei?
Babel Nisei.
If you want to go to the sky, the president will come.
I think this is amazing.