Good morning.
It's 6 o'clock in the morning.
What time is it?
It's 6 o'clock, 11 o'clock.
Today is the 11th of May.
It's Hamai-kun's birthday.
I haven't had a bath yet, so I'm in a good mood.
I'd like to have a birthday party with just the two of us.
Downtown's two-person birthday party.
What's wrong?
It's a mess.
Happy birthday to you.
Now it's time for the two-person birthday party.
It's time for the two-person birthday party.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday dear Hamachan.
Happy birthday.
What are you doing?
You're 24 years old.
I'm glad.
Happy birthday to you.
You're 34 years old, but you have a long way to go.
Eat, eat.
I thought you'd be a little lonely on your birthday.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday to you.
Cheers.
Happy birthday dear Hamachan.
Do you like yakisoba?
I'll make it for you.
What are you doing?
Should I put in a lot of sauce?
I'll put in more sauce than usual.
I have a lot of things to do.
I have a present for you.
Open this.
Do you want to see this?
It's a little funny, isn't it?
Eat this.
It's embarrassing.
How is it?
Go home.
Do you want to play a game?
No.
Why?
It's funny.
How long are you going to do this?
Let's do it again next time.
Clean up the mess.
See you tomorrow.
It's delicious.
What are you doing?
It's a good timing to wake up.
If you don't stop the yakisoba, I'll keep saying it.
Stop it.
Stop the yakisoba.
It's annoying.
I can hear happy birthday from far away.
It's so far away.
What is it?
I'm singing here.
I don't know who this is.
It's a good timing to wake up.
I was surprised.
What are you doing?
I'm angry.
Are you angry?
Why are you angry?
Because the staff are still working.
But our senior is still sleeping.
I don't know what to do.
Let's do it.
I'm in the upper room.
I'm sleeping.
I'm sad.
I'm planning to wake up.
Let's do it one more time.
It's scary.
Good morning.
What's wrong?
Everyone is working.
It's hot.
What's wrong?
What do you want to do?
Nothing.
It's hot.
I don't know anything.
My thighs are hot.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Where are you going?
It's hot.
But there was someone else sleeping.
Everyone is working from the morning.
Who is it?
Kenji.
He is a professional.
I think I'm going to drop it.
I'm going to put my butt on it.
I'm sorry.
Be quiet.
It's hot.
What's the smell?
Good luck.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
You guys slept too much.
Everyone is working from the morning.
Let's finish.
Why are you guys sleeping?
Let's stop.
It's not fashionable.