Hello!
S Один crush
Introducing my
pert longing
not full into the stomach
banyak
I'll be back soon.
You've been off for 9 days, right?
Yes, that's right.
You look so tired.
Because I haven't worked?
Because you haven't worked, it's strange to be here.
You should hold it in.
Why?
It's shiny.
That's not true.
The monitor doesn't look like that.
The TV screen is shiny.
I don't care about the TV screen.
The TV is the main thing.
You're lying!
No, no, even on TV, your face is shining!
It's okay, it's like this, it's like this.
It's not because everyone is laughing, it's because you're shining!
Well, well, well, I guess I'll have to go and release it.
Release?
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
We just took a break, didn't we?
Oh, really?
We went to Okinawa last time, and then in the second half we went to Hachijojima.
Why are you always talking about the island?
No, no, it's just funny.
You've never heard of Hachijoji, right?
There's nothing there.
There's no convenience store.
But that's in Tokyo.
And there are people?
There are people, well, a little bit.
From that little bit...
Come here for a moment.
Come to my room for a moment.
That's why I don't have a theme like that.
I'm just playing with my thoughts.
I'm sorry.
You changed your mind.
I changed my mind.
Okinawa and...
Okinawa!
You bastard!
I have only family.
I have family but...
No, no, no.
You have family.
No, not Okinawa.
I'm not.
There are a lot of people who travel.
Well, I've seen a few of them.
You're doing it!
Stop it.
You're making me even more excited.
You're doing it!
I don't want to talk about that!
I want to talk about what happened in Okinawa.
I don't care about the women.
No, that's not it.
Basically, that's what I want to hear.
What happened?
I was a bit surprised.
I was driving in Okinawa at night.
I was on the road.
There was no street lights.
I was jumping around.
I was jumping around in the distance.
I was driving by.
There are cats fighting.
Hmm.
But in Japan, in Tokyo and Osaka, you can see it, right?
And they go like,
Fuuu! Fuuu!
When it comes to Okinawa,
I think it's probably the blood of the Iriomote.
Cats aren't ordinary cats.
This tree is rough.
And these two are...
Koemasa-san and...
You know?
These two are Koemasa-san and...
Kanse-tsutori-yaimutan.
They're doing it.
What is this?
This is scary.
Sometimes, we...
We're lit up with lights.
I sometimes see them while I'm in the room.
That's amazing!
So everyone says,
the cat is cute, it's cute.
That's a lie.
Well, I've never seen that kind of place.
After all, in front of humans,
they go like this,
like this, like this.
But,
in places where people don't see,
the cat fight in such a dark place
was really scary!
You've been watching it all the time?
I've been watching it all the time.
And then he stood up and bit my ear.
He bit my ear and it was like this.
And then my ear was ripped off.
It was scary.
And the one who got ripped off was like this.
And the one who bit my ear was like this.
What? Is it over?
It was a scary thing.
I saw something scary.
That was amazing.
It was amazing.
At first I thought he was a masked wrestler.
Which one?
Both.
Oh, both.
I see.
I wanted to show that.
Well, if you see it, you'll see it.
It was amazing.
At the end, it was like a fight between masked wrestlers.
I had my hands in the mask.
But...
I was out of the center of my eyes.
No, you weren't.
I could see my nose from there.
I wasn't wearing a mask.
I wasn't out of the center of my eyes.
There were a lot of things.
I was scared.
I see.
That idiot Yamashita.
I like him.
I say it a lot.
I'm taking him with me.
Do you know anyone who has a bad nose?
Like chikuno or bien.
Ah, I know.
Those people, when their blood pressure goes up, they do something amazing.
Their faces hurt.
When they go to Okinawa, they go into the landing position and go like this.
Their blood pressure goes up.
I see.
He was next to me, but I was thinking, ah, I'm going to get stuck.
So I did it from the side.
I did it like that.
I thought, maybe they broke up in Tokyo.
With someone?
With your lover?
Why now?
It's fine.
I was doing this all the time.
What is this guy?
I was like that.
What I did was, my face was completely pale.
My face was painful.
What are you doing? It's hot in Okinawa, enjoy it.
I said, I'm going to Edo.
I was following him, but when I was preparing for the interview,
I couldn't get better.
I couldn't get better. My face hurts.
I don't understand the meaning of the word, my face hurts.
What is it? My face hurts.
My stomach hurts.
He had surgery a long time ago, but he had a lot of poop.
You dirty bastard!
Your nose is smelly!
Well, it's a disease.
I don't understand the meaning of that.
Your nose is smelly as it is.
And then...
And then, I borrowed a car.
I got on the car.
What the hell?
I was going like this.
I was feeling better.
I was feeling better, but then I hit Yamashita's head in the middle of the car.
And I started to have a bad feeling again.
I started to feel pain again.
I said, I'm going to the hospital.
I said, let's go eat somewhere.
I started to have a bad feeling again.
I said, let's eat something.
I said, I'll have udon.
I got better.
I took a sip of udon.
And the pressure of the air changes like this.
It's like this.
And it's like this.
Don't take me with you.
I'm so old.
I was like,
I'm sorry.
I have bad hearing.
But it's not that bad.
What do you mean by bad hearing?
You know, when I did that, I said I couldn't hear.
Oh, number 9?
I couldn't hear, so my ears were...
...crashed, right?
The pressure on my ears made my ears go crazy, so my head went like this.
I don't want to say that my face hurts.
But if your face hurts, it's scary.
I'm scared of my face.
No matter how I think about it, it's strange.
What do you mean by your face hurts?
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
Even if you say that, nothing hurts.
Isn't your bone hot?
It's okay.
Really?
You're so cold.
Actually...
I always say this in my letters...
But there's someone who wants to talk to me.
I'll call him.
No, it's not that important.
Please come in.
Hello
Yamazaki Hosei-kun has a little something to say
This is amazing
If you appear again, I can fix it
No, no, it's okay, it's okay.
I've been a child servant since the second time.
Since the second time, you've been a child servant.
Yes, yes.
It's been 12 years.
Well, good job.
Ah, good job.
Good job!
That's impossible!
Well, I think so, but...
I'm getting married!
This is the first time I've seen this.
This is the first time.
This is a real story.
It's a serious story.
Who? Who?
Aya.
I don't know who that is.
Who? Who?
Aya.
Aya? Who?
So, it's not like you're a comedian.
That's not what I meant.
I'm just a normal person.
A normal person?
Yes.
A photo?
Oh, wow.
The other person?
Who? Who?
I said it wasn't anyone!
Ayayaya!
What are you talking about?
I've met him many times.
Oh, really?
Yes.
We've known each other for a long time.
Yes, that's right.
3 years.
3 years, yes.
It was long.
Yes, yes, yes.
It was a long time.
She was a little girl with small eyes.
Well, that's it.
Yes, yes, yes.
This is...
It's amazing.
Congratulations.
I have a lot of questions about marriage.
Please answer them.
I will ask you some questions.
Yes.
Yes, thank you.
First of all,
You can be a wife.
What is your wife's first impression?
Well, I don't really have to say that.
I think she doesn't like the relationship.
She's your senior.
She wants to know that.
She's used to it.
She might have asked you.
What?
What is your first impression?
That's important.
First impression.
I thought she was cute!
Where did you meet her?
In Roppongi
In Roppongi?
I went to eat with Matsumoto-san
I went to eat with Matsumoto-san 3 years ago
Matsumoto-san and I went to the car
And then when I went
You went to eat with Matsumoto-san?
Matsumoto-san went home right?
Matsumoto-san went to the restaurant
I said, and then I pointed at her face, and she said, ah, it's Machan.
Eh, really?
That's right.
I've never heard of that before.
And then I went down and said, what's wrong?
Eh?
What's wrong?
What did you say to who?
No, to that Aya.
Where is Aya?
Aya is outside.
Eh?
Aya is a fool?
A fool!
I can't believe it!
Why were you outside?
Were you just walking outside?
I was just walking outside.
Just walking?
Just walking.
With who?
With Aya and Aya's friends.
I was just walking.
And then the car came.
Mr. Matsumoto's car came.
And he said,
Ah, it's Machan!
After that, I went to the car.
And I said,
Ah, it's Machan!
And I looked up.
And he said,
Ah, it's Yama-chan!
Then, you get off the plane and ask,
What's wrong?
Ah, so that's where you connect to the plane.
That's a really long story.
You get it, right?
I don't know what to do.
Then you shake hands with the person.
And then, well,
The person on the phone tells you.
You're fast.
And then, that's the first step.
Get used to it.
So you're saying you're going out with her?
Yes, we're going out.
I see.
So, what kind of play did you two have when you first dated her?
We went to Ebisu and we were with Hoto-chan.
With Hoto-chan?
Yes.
Me, Hoto-chan, Aya, and Aya's friends.
Ah, so you were just friends with no future.
So you were like, what are you going to do about it?
No, no, no.
There's still more.
There's still more?
You still have a girlfriend?
I don't think everyone is interested in that.
I can understand that.
It's like, I don't care anymore.
Tell us your favorite part of your girlfriend, Aya.
I'm called a futan.
You're being called gross.
Why is it called futan in Hosei Yamagaki?
You know, that's because...
What is it?
I used to live in Ikoda.
When she came, she was climbing the stairs like this.
I'm sorry.
Honestly, I've never seen such a gross press conference.
Press conference?
No one is coming.
I think everyone is coming.
I thought you were really angry.
There was no staff.
It was the first time I announced it.
I was saying, Fuccha, Fuccha.
Fuccha, Fuccha, Fuccha, Fuccha.
I was saying that.
Before I knew it, she called me Fuccha.
She answered the question.
That's right.
She is a cute girl who can say such things.
I see.
Pure.
Yes.
Wait a minute.
I don't have the energy to ask.
You do!
I don't know! I can't read the atmosphere!
You're asking so much here!
I can read the atmosphere!
It's okay.
It's okay?
Then, let's stop asking these questions.
It's okay, right?
Which one do you want, Daki-san?
There's a lot.
Which one do you want to answer?
Ah, the wedding ring.
Did you give it to her?
I haven't given it to her yet.
Oh, really?
I haven't even given her a seat yet.
Are you okay with this?
No, I mean, I'm not interested in you two anymore.
What?
Wait a minute.
If you open the door, I'll go.
Did you propose to her?
No, I didn't.
What?
You're just saying it.
Why?
I'm surprised.
You should have proposed to her.
No, no, wait a minute.
Yes?
Really?
Is she really your girlfriend?
Stop it.
Are you making fun of me?
I'm doing the same thing as you.
You saw it, right?
You said, you didn't see it.
I'm telling the truth.
But shouldn't you propose?
I proposed to her and we dated for about a week.
That's fast!
You said you wanted to get married, but you didn't!
I asked her about the timing of the marriage, and she said it was all about timing.
So after a week, I proposed to her, but she said no.
She rejected you.
She said no once.
You thought about it well.
I thought you could get married in a week.
You didn't say no, did you?
I said no.
I'm sure of it.
But, I don't think you don't want to.
We haven't been together for long, so I can't think of anything.
Is that how you see it?
No, I don't want to.
Excuse me?
It's been two years.
It's been two years and three years.
Three years.
Yes.
So you don't want to propose again?
No, I don't propose.
I really don't propose.
You should have proposed.
But I can't do it anymore.
It's embarrassing.
You should ask Hamada about that.
How to propose.
Oh, Senpai!
Senpai's proposal...
What is it?
Do you propose with that face?
I think it's fine if you propose properly.
But honestly, you've been proposing for 3 years, right?
I don't propose to her.
I don't have anything.
So you have a purpose?
I understand.
You are talking here.
I think it's strange.
I didn't hear it.
Are you doing it on your own?
I'm going to talk about this when I get home.
I said on TV.
I'm going home now.
I don't know if I'll come back.
Don't be surprised.
I see.
It's strange.
So...
I don't understand.
It's strange.
I see.
Okay, I got it.
Right?
There are many things I want to congratulate you.
What do you mean?
I did it.
If you don't say that, you can't propose or get a girlfriend.
I'm surprised. Yamazaki is your father.
No, I'm his father.
What are you going to do?
Seriously?
You're a friend!
I don't like this!
So, since the second time, the one who appeared before, Yama-chan, has become like this.
So, from our program's producer.
And then...
From...Chief Séb squeeze...
Meaning?
S-Sordon knit
See?
It's just...
destroyed and
wrong
There's a lot of flowers
My
Russia
I can tell from your appearance, but you are a single-minded person.
You are one rank higher than me.
I can tell that you are giving me a hard time.
What should I do? Should I open it?
Open it.
Yes.
I'll open it.
I'm scared.
Which way should I look?
Which way?
No, no, look up.
I'm scared.
Ready, go!
Hup!
That was too scary.
Eiko-san!
I'm scared!
It's okay.
It's like, boom, boom, boom.
In order.
Boom, boom, boom.
Here we go.
correct
whoooooo
shall we get started!
Cheers!
Heipo is amazing. He just gave him a shampoo.
Let's drink to the world's Heipo's temperature.
Congratulations, Yama-chan.
From now on, I'm not alone.
With my wife and...
...with my children...
Together, I'll live a wonderful life as an entertainer.
I'll live a life of perfection.
What?
I'll live a wonderful life as an entertainer.
I pray that you will be convinced.
Well, it's fine. Let's all be convinced together later.
I prayed for that.
Let's toast to Yama-chan's good fortune!
Thank you!