This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
I now pronounce the verdict.
Please enter the courtroom.
Now, the defendant, please enter.
The defendant, Tatsuo Uemiyo, has been convicted.
Now, the judge, Tatsuo Uemiyo, will begin his trial.
The defendant will defend against the defendant, so please enter the courtroom.
Uemiyo, I'm going to expose you today!
Don't think you can get away with this!
Judge!
Yes?
Regarding this trial, I'm going to give you some evidence.
I'm going to call a teacher.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Teacher!
Uemiyo Tatsuya
That guy is from Zura!
Teacher!
Yes?
Teacher Raskun!
Yes, yes.
I understand.
I've looked into a lot of things.
Yes.
I've seen a lot of evidence.
First, I'd like you to look at the evidence photo.
Please show it to me.
Yes, please show it to me.
If you look at this, you can see that Uemiyo Tatsuya's iron-cutter is loose.
I see.
As expected of Uemiyo Tatsuya.
If you don't say a word, does that mean you're angry?
Well, well, teacher.
This isn't it.
Oh, it's not it?
You're the one who made me angry, you bastard!
I got this Uemiyo Tatsuya's favorite brush from the dressing room.
I see.
This is it.
That's a lot of hair.
I took one of these and enlarged it scientifically.
This is the photo.
Oh!
100% nylon!
We were surprised.
First, let's look at this.
This is it.
I wonder when this photo was taken.
Uemiyo, when was this photo taken?
No matter how many years ago, it hasn't changed at all, has it?
Well, well, well, that's what you say.
What's the difference?
I'd like you to focus on this area.
The area between the cheeks and ears.
I moved the camera further.
You moved the camera further.
Yes, yes.
This is what it looks like.
Well, well, well, that's fine.
We don't know yet.
When I moved the camera further, I found something amazing.
I see.
Bang!
A string!
What?
It's a string, isn't it?
It's tied up like this!
It doesn't have a string attached to it today.
Well, it's for TV.
I see.
And I also got a picture of your usual relaxed appearance.
I'm going to laugh at this.
Yes.
This is before the show!
Do I have to wear that?
You're wearing it now!
Next.
Yes.
It's a picture of the TV.
His face isn't smiling.
What?
He's wearing it!
It's a string!
I hit him once before the show.
When he was hit by a wire, he made a sound like this.
I see.
It's because of the string that the iron plate on the back is broken.
Bring me the wire.
I don't need it anymore!
I'm going to hit the professor's head.
I see.
There's another proof video.
Can I watch it?
Yes.
This is the doll in front of the Umeda station.
This is the 10th floor.
Yes, it's the 22nd floor.
Is this the doll island?
Yes, it is.
Next.
Shut up!
This is the doll that looks exactly like Tatsu Umeda.
That's right.
It means that the doll is the same as Tatsu Umeda.
I see.
This is what it looks like when it's hidden.
Can you bring me the proof video?
Yes.
This is it.
If you pass by Harajuku, please take a picture of it.
This is what it looks like.
Mr. Daibashi!
The doll is running wild.
Congratulations.
This is what it looks like.
If he's hiding,
he might think that his friends and acquaintances know about it.
I see.
He's very close to him.
I'm talking to this person.
I see.
I don't want to say this because it might affect my friendship.
But I have to tell you the truth.
This is Katsura.
The basis of the name Katsura is that
when he was young, he had a razor.
When I saw it in the dressing room, I wondered what it was.
I thought it was a razor with a razor.
But it wasn't.
He used both of them.
He doesn't seem to like Haga Kenji.
The reason why he doesn't like him is because
Haga Kenji's hair is fluffier than human hair.
That's the only reason why Katsura likes him.
Well, that's one reason.
His friend is also a razor.
Are you saying it clearly?
His friend is saying it.
There's a secret room in Umemiya.
A reporter is there.
He's peeking into the dressing room.
I don't know what's going to come out.
Let's go.
This is in front of Umemiya Tatsuo's dressing room.
Umemiya was here earlier.
I'd like to come in while he's away.
Hair.
What? Hair?
Oh, okay.
I'm sorry.
You're eating your lunch.
It's because it's Shura.
Oh, I see.
Look at this.
There's more hair on the desk than you need.
There's something else.
The one in the back.
Yes.
What's that?
It's like a jewelry case.
This one?
Yes.
Can I open it without permission?
It's okay.
He's here.
It's weird to have a jewelry case for work.
Please take a good look at it.
It's not that heavy.
It's not heavy?
Yes.
I'll open it.
It's Zura!
We have a variety show.
Now, finally.
We need to do this.
We've developed a special chart-based diagnosis system.
Let's do that.
Let's go.
This is the first one.
His wife is a foreigner.
Which one?
Yes.
Here it is.
Do you think your daughter Anna is cute?
Yes!
That's a yes!
In the past, she appeared in the movie, The Uncanny Battle.
Which one?
Yes!
That's a yes!
That's it!
Thank you very much!
Now, the defendant, please come to the center.
Judge, please make a decision based on what you just saw.
Now, I will give you the verdict on the defendant, Tatsuya Uemia.
The verdict is...
Death sentence!
What?
What do you mean, death sentence?
Death sentence!
About three days ago, we had a 24-hour talk.
Yes, we did.
We just did it.
And then you came out here and told me to talk.
What are you talking about?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Wow, you're an IB.
You're talking about the past again.
But you know, I was surprised.
About what?
We had a 24-hour talk, and I was so tired.
Yes.
I almost died.
That's true.
I thought I was going to die.
It must have been hard.
I went home and slept like a pig.
The next day, you said you were bowling in the afternoon.
Are you an idiot?
I went to Hakone for a different show.
Yes, yes, you did.
To shoot the ending.
I joined the show in the evening.
You joined the show in the evening, didn't you?
That's the limit.
Maybe I should have taken a break.
Before that, everyone was in a bowling tournament.
So I thought I shouldn't go.
I played about three games.
What? Are you a singer?
Where are you?
I don't know because I haven't been in the show for 24 hours.
But now I feel fresh.
I feel like I'm in downtown.
Two hours, three hours, four hours, five hours.
I'm an old man.
I didn't see it before, but I was doing my best.
I was tired.
That's right.
You're looking at me from the beginning.
In the middle of the night, you gave out curry at dinner time, didn't you?
When it was about that time, I was tired of looking at it.
I was tired of looking at it.
I said, line up.
I gave out curry.
There was this person in front of me.
I looked at the curry.
You're usually like this.
I can't get used to it.
I thought I'd look at it a little bit when I went to the curry shop.
I look at it from the back.
I've been with you for a long time.
I don't see your face.
Because it's creepy.
We're both.
I've been looking at your face for 24 hours.
I feel bad.
It's true.
Wait.
I've been tired for 24 hours.
I'm going to sleep in the car.
Your face comes out.
It's creepy.
That face came out, too.
I fell down like this.
It's creepy.
What's wrong with you?
There's a lot of people today.
I'm glad you came.
Why are you sitting in the back?
I don't know.
You came and didn't say,
Kato Shimura.
Who's Kato?
Who's Shimura?
You didn't say, Shimura, back, back.
I'm not angry.
Shimura, back, back.
What are you doing now?
I don't know if you're a director or something.
I don't think so.
Let's go home.
It's creepy.
Did you sleep?
I came home on Sunday.
I slept for five or six hours.
I played bowling.
I played golf the next day.
Why?
I can't stand it.
Wait a minute.
What do you mean you can't stand it?
I want to live.
Do you want to live?
I don't usually sleep.
I want to live.
I want to see a lot of things.
I want to see.
I want to eat a lot of things.
I want to ask.
I want to lick.
There are a lot of things I want to lick.
I can only lick one.
I want to lick it.
Are you a chef?
You can't sleep for more than eight hours.
You'll get a headache.
Isn't that true?
Not at all.
After I finished, I slept in the car for three hours.
I went home and went to bed at 12 o'clock.
I slept until six o'clock.
I slept for nine hours.
I woke up for about an hour and ate.
I went to bed at seven o'clock.
When I woke up, it was five o'clock.
Do you get a headache?
Not at all.
I've never slept for 23 hours.
If you sleep so much, you'll wake up in the middle of the night.
I didn't wake up once.
No.
I can't remember.
But you woke up in the middle of the night and ate.
That's true love.
I didn't wake up for 23 hours.
If I didn't wake up, I would have slept too much.
What do you mean?
I only sleep alone.
Is that so?
Yes.
I feel bad when I sleep with you.
Why?
Because I sleep with my eyes open.
I was told that I would wake up the love of 100 years.
With your eyes open?
I sleep like this.
I'm sure I'll be a thief.
I'll wake you up.
I'll be a great security guard.
I feel like I'm wearing a buckle.
I'm serious.
I slept for 23 hours.
Is that so?
I'm sorry.
I didn't wake up.
You slept again, didn't you?
I slept for a long time.
I slept with my left hand.
I don't remember.
I slept.
You should exercise.
You slept with your left hand.
But you're fine.
I guess you don't live long.
Is that so?
Yes.
You can't sleep like that.
You can't catch up with anyone.
Who?
That's why you haven't recovered.
You're still tired.
Don't turn your ankle.
This?
No, no, no.
Why is there a board on the kamaboko?
You can tell by the way it's made.
The board on the kamaboko is recent.
It's been four or five years.
That's not true.
It's true.
It didn't have a board before that.
That's not true.
You used to work with a kamaboko board, didn't you?
No, no, no.
That's not true.
I used to work with a kamaboko board.
That's four or five years ago.
I'll tell you why.
Five or six years ago,
flooring was popular.
It started back then.
Who are you talking to?
The kamaboko will come looking for a room, won't it?
What's that?
A kamaboko without a board?
That's right.
What's that?
I don't know.
Even if you put out a tatami, it won't work.
I don't need a Japanese room anymore.
He doesn't either.
There's a theory.
A theory?
I think the kamaboko is a processed product.
What do you mean?
A kamaboko is a living thing.
A kamaboko swims like this.
It's a sea creature.
When you take a kamaboko, you dig a board like this.
You stand up like this.
You dig a board like this.
When you take a kamaboko, you dig a board like this.
When should I take off my arm pillow when I'm sleeping with my girlfriend?
When the color changes.
You take off your arm pillow before that?
If I take it off...
You look like a man. You have a gentle side.
You put up with it until you get a tingling sensation.
If I take it off...
Your image has changed.
Really?
What if the color changes?
There's no one who would do that.
There are people who don't like arm pillows.
Is that so?
They don't like arm pillows.
What is it?
There's a face around here.
It's like this.
What are you doing?
Don't tell me you have a wine glass.
I have one.
You have a wine glass and an arm pillow.
How do you drink it?
When it comes to me, it's amazing.
What is?
I'll wait in the new room.
You take it off and go in.
You're like an old man.
You go out once.
And then bang!
What is it?
No, no.
Where do you do it?
In the room?
No, at home.
And then bang!
I'm already home.
And then you take off the arm pillow.
What kind of clothes are you wearing?
Are these boots?
Boots.
And then...
What is it?
Boots.
Boots like this?
How do you do it?
You take it off and put it down.
And then this.
Wait!
Both are long!
And then you take off the one here.
That's it.
What is it?
Don't put it out vertically!
And then bang!
I'm already naked.
You're not wearing anything.
And then...
You take it off.
What are you doing?
Wait!
Don't touch it!
What is this?
You're too bright!
What is that?
B!
One at a time.
And then...
Go home!
Thank you for watching!