In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai, we have Yoshimoto-Kamayaki Combi vs. Shinkuro-Senshika!
Today we have Yoshimoto-Kamayaki Combi.
You're the Combi, aren't you?
That's right.
What do you mean by Combi?
You're going to combine them?
Yes, I'm going to combine them with Combi.
The Combi that will participate in this tournament is our regular team.
Now, the back row.
Who are you?
We've been together for the longest time.
Lately, I rarely get involved with people who are older than me.
You're older than me, aren't you?
I'm older than you, though.
I'm the leader of the team!
Now, the back row.
Who are you?
I'm Shoji Shinagawa.
Nice to meet you.
I wonder if it'll be okay.
What about over there?
It's finally here. Please take care of it.
It's the first time, isn't it?
It's been two years, hasn't it?
License!
We've never done anything like this before.
This is the Combi's life.
We'll see how well it goes.
If it's like that, it doesn't matter.
It'll definitely go well.
We'll do our best.
As expected, there was nothing.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Everyone, this is for practice.
That's right.
Why is it for practice?
It's for girls.
This is for girls?
That's right.
That's strange.
It's for girls.
It's our first time doing a synchro.
Of course, we need a teacher.
Please come out.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
The first member of the boys' synchro club, Fuwa Hisashi.
He was in charge of the choreography for the movie, Water Boys.
He'll be our coach today.
This teacher.
Teacher?
He's a teacher.
Stop it.
You can get angry.
Teacher, please teach us from the beginning.
The first female member will demonstrate.
Please take a look.
Please.
Wow.
She's not standing up at all.
She doesn't usually use her legs.
That's right.
Wow.
This is the first time I've seen this.
This is amazing.
Wow.
Amazing.
Can you do that?
Please teach us properly.
The first is the practice of floating in the water.
Use your hands to make your body float.
First, the Ritton Investigation Corps.
Why are you moving your legs?
You can't move your legs.
Huh?
What's wrong with you?
I've never seen you float.
Next, the Kokoriko challenge.
You're good.
Your eyes are different.
It's still too hard to talk.
Next, the Yamasaki-Komurasaki combination.
Are you okay?
Yes.
What's wrong with you?
What?
You are...
Your name is...
Yama-chan, you're amazing.
You're amazing.
Can you raise your legs a bit more?
That's right, raise them a bit more.
What is this?
It was a bit dark.
This is good.
This is amazing.
Next is the practice of smiling.
First, the teacher's demonstration.
That's disgusting.
Isn't that something to burp?
Now, each duo challenges their smile.
First up is Shouji Shinagawa.
What are you doing?
You're dirty.
And you jumped here.
Don't smile.
Don't cry.
Don't make me cry.
Next up is Riko Kokori.
What are you doing?
Why are you like this?
Don't put your chin out.
I was going to show my front teeth, but I was like this.
Next up is Downtown.
I'm ready.
What are you doing?
I'm scared.
Please open your eyes.
Why did you open your eyes when I came out?
I was going to make you laugh, but I didn't.
What kind of face is that?
Please open your eyes. I'm really going to make you laugh.
I was going to make you laugh.
Your eyes are white.
Your teeth are terrible.
I was going to make you laugh, but I didn't.
The last one is a big move.
It's a lift where one person stands on top of the other person's shoulders and poses.
However, this lift is quite difficult for beginners.
It's difficult, and every combination fails.
Yamasaki and Komorosaki's combination is...
I can't lift my body.
I'm going to die.
Downtown finally challenges the lift.
What kind of combination will it be?
Why are you letting go of me?
Hey, you idiot.
My hand is also a hand.
This is also a hand.
It's a balance.
You can do it.
Amazing.
You did it.
This is amazing.
It's like Rolls Royce...
The synchronization practice is over.
From now on, each combination will be divided and practiced for the competition.
Which combination will show us a great synchronization?
The lesson is over.
It's time for the competition.
I'm a little nervous.
I'll explain the rules.
There are three judges over there.
They each have 10 points.
A total of 30 points. This is the highest score.
I don't know why they each have 10 points.
Do you know that?
I don't think they have 10 points.
From now on, we will begin the competition.
Entry number 1.
Kokoriko's 10 years of love.
Amazing.
Beautiful.
It's beautiful.
The background is completely different.
You're laughing.
You're good.
Are you okay?
Tanaka is always slow.
It's beautiful.
It's better than I thought.
The current score is 24 points.
What do you think?
I think it was perfect.
I think it was beautiful.
Entry number 2.
Shouji Shinagawa's Love Celebration 2002.
What is that title?
It's like this.
You guys are the same.
Shouji has a very good body.
Shinagawa has one leg.
Shinagawa is not laughing.
It's not easy.
You're smart.
It's a big move.
It's amazing.
It's coming out.
It's Titanic.
It's a beep
It's dirty
Don't be fooled
It's not a trick
He's being fooled
It's a trick
It's just a scratch
I wonder how the judges will judge
The current score is...
25 points
He got it right away
I don't have any gold left
Entry number 3
All men are beautiful
What's the title?
These two are close to 50 points
Really?
It's too early
The shape is bad
It's dangerous
It's difficult
I don't know what to do
It's like a joke
It's difficult
I'm just answering
I can't look
I'm embarrassed
It's over
As long as you look at him
The current score is...
15 points
He got it right away
It's too early
Have you Arg Можно?
Yes
It's too early
I can't look
It's a big deal
He's done
Wow!
This is a great song to listen to.
This is the tempo!
Wow!
This is great!
There's plenty of room for improvement.
Wow!
Yeah!
This is great!
Wow!
The score is...
26 points.
Wow!
This is great!
Thank you!
What do you think, Riton?
What?
I'm so angry right now!
Number 5
Yamazaki Hosei & Komurasaki Kozo
Thank you.
That's a great dance.
Konno's smile is dirty!
Look at that smile!
Wow, I'm so angry!
Here he comes!
He's fast!
He's pretty good!
Next up is...
I don't know which one is the best?
What is this?
I'm not sure.
I don't know.
What is this?
The last one is...
Oh, oh, oh...
Kawasaki has never done this before!
What is it?
Oh, oh, oh, this is it!
The last one!
The current score is...
27 points!
Really?
This is a bit strange.
It's the top!
Wow!
Thank you very much.
What is it?
Everyone, please give us your answer.
Huh?
Hey, Matsuura Aya!
Well then, finally...
That's right, finally!
To be honest, I was looking at it, but...
Well, well, well...
You guys are pathetic.
Really?
I can't tell at all.
What is it?
It's not integrated with water.
Why don't you talk to the water more?
Talk?
Is that okay?
But it's the oldest combination, right?
That's right.
It's been 20 years, right?
Of course, of course.
Then please watch our way of life!
Okay!
Entry No. 6
In Downtown
The two of them are at the lake.
What's a lake?
Ah, here it comes.
Here it comes.
The smile of the person behind you is different.
That smile is different.
It's not a smile.
Your father is a great man.
Here it comes.
Ah, here it comes.
You're breathing well.
Yes.
As expected.
What?
Get in the water!
Well, get in.
Get in.
Here it comes.
Hey!
Is the song over?
Ah, get in.
Get in.
What?
In the water?
The appeal is the best.
You can't clap like this.
What is this?
You're not talking to the water at all.
It's just a hat.
The current score is...
30 points.
Hey!
I'm getting angry.
What is this?
I got 30 points.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Full marks.
That's not it.
Yoshimoto Synchro Championship.
The winner is...
Downtown.
Now, we will present the gold medal...
to Mr. Yoshimoto Synchro.
This is strange.
Thank you.
This program was provided by the following sponsors.