Ladies and gentlemen.
I'm sleepy.
I thought I was going to sleep, but after 2-3 hours, my body is tired but my head is still awake.
My grandma is still in my head.
That's right.
My body is still awake but my head is still talking to my grandma.
I can't let go of my grandma's fantasy.
But you have to talk on time.
Are you a teacher?
Or are you just making up stories?
That's not true.
We had a meeting about an hour before the show.
There aren't many grandmas who can do that much in an hour before the show.
I'm not praising my grandma.
But I was so excited that I had a cold.
It's finally done.
I haven't seen it yet.
I just got an electric shock.
It's Hitoshi.
Hitoshi and Oka.
My mother is here.
She's here again.
My eyes are burning.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Why are you getting in my way?
I'm listening to your song.
Don't say that.
It's time to imitate.
It's hard for you to imitate.
It's easy.
Really?
I can't do anything.
Junko Sakurada.
I'm Junko.
You're all Junko.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
What are you thinking?
I can do it, mom.
Number 18.
Really?
What song are you going to sing?
It's Tokyo, mom.
I'll sing it for you.
I'll introduce it.
Let's sing it together.
Long time no see.
What do you mean long time no see?
You've been singing for a long time.
What are you talking about?
I'm excited.
You're more excited than usual.
It's dangerous to attract people.
You're a kidnapper.
I don't know.
I'm a kidnapper.
Take someone important to you.
Take someone important to me?
Yes.
Take someone important to you and kill them.
Kill them?
It's a bad attitude.
Hello?
What's that?
It's a prank.
What are you talking about?
Hello?
Do you have a son?
I have a 6th grader.
What's wrong with that?
It's embarrassing.
It's not funny.
Hello?
I have a 2nd grader.
Take someone important to you.
Take someone important to me?
A 2nd grader?
What are you going to do?
It's a prank.
Take someone important to you and kill them.
I'm tired and excited.
He's waiting for you.
He's looking at your face.
I'm getting old.
You're still walking.
I've been doing this for 3 years.
Thank you.
Is my partner here?
Your partner?
He's on his way here.
Thank you.
Good morning.
Hello.
I can't help it.
It's amazing.
I've been doing this for 3 years.
I can't help it.
I don't like it.
Here you are.
Thank you.
If you don't remember that,
I'll ask the god to give you a picture.
I can't show you.
I don't want to wear it.
I don't want to do it.
I don't want to do it either.
Look, look.
I can't do it.
It's a little hard.
I'm going home.
When I called you,
You said,
I'm going to open a temple.
I'm going to burn it.
I should have said that.
And...
I don't know if you can really imitate it.
I don't think so.
I will do it.
Long time no see.
Please hold my hand.
I wonder if it's okay.
If it's the real thing, I'll fly around.
It's a place where people pull.
I'm scared.
I can't help it because I'm told to pull my hand over there.
What if I pull my hand?
What if I run away?
What a good hole.
I see.
What if I say?
That would be the worst.
I'm scared.
I don't want to.
Why don't you do it?
I'm annoyed now, but I'll write it down when I watch the movie later.
I don't want to.
I'm scared.
Hello.
It's me.
What?
Did you sleep?
Listen to my mother's cry.
Grandma.
30 seconds left.
25 seconds left.
I'm nervous.
5 seconds left.
4, 3, 2, 1.
3, 2, 1.
Time's up.
It's Hitoshi.
It's Okan.
Hitoshi and Okan together.
Okan.
My mother died.
She died today.
What are you doing?
You're disturbing my mother.
It's been a while.
Hitoshi.
What is this?
Do you want to play?
What?
Bring me the prize.
Bring it?
What are you going to do with it?
Thank you very much.
It's been a long time.
Really?
It's nothing.
Let's do our best next year.
Next year, let's go with a doctor's story.
What are you talking about?
Thank you very much.
It's over.
I'll call you again.
Bye-bye.
It was scary.
Hitoshi, you're doing well.
I always watch you on TV.
It's been a while.
Take care of yourself and keep up the good work.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for having fun.
Take care of yourself and keep up the good work.
Hitoshi, let's meet again soon.
Let's do a comic book with your mother.
Let's do our best.
That's all.
Thank you very much.
That woman is too excited.
She's not excited at all.
But I know you're excited.
One of them is pretty good, but the other one is crazy.
Gyo-san's fans came.
I was taking a picture from the window.
Please don't turn on the flash.
The fans outside...
I'm holding back.
Who is it?
It's Joichi.
I don't know.
There was an old lady with glasses on.
I don't know her.
Wait a minute.
I don't know her, but she's in the Matsumoto family.
Did you bring her?
Hitoshi, long time no see.
I'm saying, oh, my God.
Who is it?
I'm saying, hello.
I didn't ask you until the end.
I asked, she's my dad's brother's wife's sister.
That's a little hard.
I don't know her.
I'm saying, please show me the mother.
That's hard.
No matter what you say.
Who's that?
Who's the old lady with glasses on?
I've never seen her.
I don't know.
She's my brother's sister-in-law.
She was looking over here.
She was worried.
She was afraid.
She thought I was gone.
She was looking over here.
You can't have a family.
Ah!
Congratulations!
Congratulations to the second child.
You're doing quite well.
I thought you were only doing it outside, not at home.
Only doing it outside?
Say something!
You're doing quite well at home.
Why?
I'm doing it to make tea.
I'm not doing it to save money.
Amazing.
The Hamada family is slowly being made.
Of course.
The Hamada family is young.
The Hamada family is much older than our family.
I was surprised.
When I saw the news, I was surprised.
Were you reading the news?
No, I wasn't.
On Sunday...
You're just a student.
Who's saying, well...
On Sunday...
I wasn't saying, well...
You were going to work on Sunday, right?
I was already quite late.
But I don't know.
The kids are all over the place.
You're really...
You're really no good.
I think...
I think this is the only story.
No seeds?
I think it's probably no seeds.
Around the 21st,
I had a fever of about 44 degrees.
Really?
I can't believe it.
I had a fever of about 44 degrees.
My fingers were melting.
You're lying.
It's true, it's true.
It hurts when it burns.
At that time,
when I had a fever of over 40 degrees,
I was like,
will I have no seeds,
or will I be a fool?
I was like,
I'm having fun!
No, no, that's not it.
I was like that even before I had a fever.
If it was that bad.
They said I was a slave.
But I wasn't a fool.
There was a lot of computer graphics.
That was a fool.
If nothing happened,
I think it's probably true.
But I don't think I can be a child.
I'm not a character who can be a child.
I'm scared.
If I go somewhere in a wheelchair.
If you do something like this.
I'm scared.
But I hate you.
I hate you.
At that time,
I was like,
they're not cute.
I think everyone should live more honestly.
This girl is cute.
Men are cute,
but women are cute.
Most of them are lies.
Even though they hate it.
Women can't be cute without children.
They're determined.
That's you.
No, no,
in my heart,
even though I don't like it,
I love children.
That's what women say.
They think I'm a terrible woman.
To be honest, I wish I could live a simple life.
When I go out to eat and talk about poop,
they say,
I don't feel like eating.
That's ridiculous.
That's definitely a lie.
Well, that's a lie.
I don't eat while pooping here.
I can't eat it.
I poop around the glass and drink wine.
Why doesn't it hurt when you pinch your elbow?
That's right.
It hurts when you pinch it.
No, it doesn't hurt at all.
No, it doesn't hurt at all like this.
But it hurts like this, doesn't it?
No, it doesn't hurt at all.
Hang in there.
No, it doesn't hurt at all like this.
It hurts when you pinch it.
Why doesn't it hurt when you pinch your elbow?
No, it doesn't hurt at all like this.
There's a jujube in it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Isn't there something like that?
No, no.
No, it doesn't hurt at all like this.
Right?
That's right.
That's what I usually want to see.
I have a cell phone.
Well, most people have a pocket bell these days.
For example, whose cell phone is that?
Oh, it's mine, right?
Oh, your cell phone is ringing.
But that's a mistake.
I have a cell phone, but it's not my cell phone.
The cell phone is borrowed.
It's a rental.
I have it, so it's my cell phone, but it's not my cell phone.
The elbow is like that, too.
Whose is it?
The elbow on my body.
If you look for it, you'll be too sad.
I'm looking for my parents.
I know how you feel about looking for the owner of your elbow.
That's what you say.
But if you go there, it might be a problem for the other party.
There's a family there.
Do you know?
You're bleeding.
This one hurts!
There's no way it'll come out
What did you sleep on?