Chiki-chiki! Shiku! Machan! The plan has fallen down!
So, the plan has fallen down.
I'm sorry.
Let's go!
Right?
Sorry.
Before this time,
I used to play downtown in the middle of the night.
In the middle of that,
there were a lot of clashes.
I was like this.
No, I was like this.
There were a lot of things like that.
In the middle of that,
for example,
in the first round,
the Kouhaku-Utakashi match.
Who will win?
It's not a bet.
The one who loses in this,
in the first round,
the VTR that you're about to see,
is Zoom-in Asa.
I'm going to appear live in this.
I'm just going to appear a little behind.
It's a refreshing morning.
It's the best.
Zoom-in Asa
Hello.
Yes.
I'm going now.
Stay on TV.
Yes.
Watch my way of life.
Zoom-in Asa
I'm still on the phone with Hamada.
Yes.
I'm really on the phone.
Hello.
Yes.
I'm going now.
I'm going to appear live in this.
Stay on TV.
I'm still on the phone with Hamada.
I'm really on the phone.
Good morning.
It's Wednesday, January 17th.
First of all, Asa Ichiban is going to Shizuoka.
Zoom-in Asa
By the way,
we started at 5 o'clock this morning.
There are 146 tickets.
And 154 people were injured.
It seems that a strange person has been coming from the morning.
It is said that you will be able to fly to Heijo by wrapping a freezing material around the runway.
It seems that Hamada will also go well.
I think I can fly today.
However, if you go into the shade, it will slip, so I would like everyone to be careful.
Then, towards your smile this morning,
Zoom-in
Next, I played baseball.
Matsumoto said that I was good at baseball.
Then, the team called Down's Town was divided.
Let's play a game.
The person who lost this time is Kanchu Suie.
As you can see, I'm dressed up.
I was given only what I won.
It was so warm.
However, such brave men came in this cold.
Look over there.
They are still stupid.
Look at that rough wave.
From now on, you are heading towards that rough wave.
Do you understand?
Yes.
It doesn't matter if it's cold.
I lost.
Yes.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
My body hurts.
I have a cold.
Hanazaki.
Yes.
Hey.
Bring that ball.
Let's go.
Bring it.
What are you doing?
I can't.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to cry.
Next time,
The other day, I went to Karaoke thinking I'd forgotten.
I can't sing at all.
I'm not a turtle.
I'm a water turtle.
I can't sing at all.
I'm not a turtle.
It's about 10 meters high, so it's going to be 4,000 meters.
It's still 1 in 4.
It's the worst.
It's 3,500 meters now.
It's 3,500 meters.
It's almost there.
Here we go.
The other day, I went to Karaoke thinking I'd forgotten.
I can't sing at all.
I'm not a turtle.
I'm a water turtle.
I can't sing at all.
I'm not a turtle.
I'm going down.
Hamada-san!
Do you understand?
I'm waving my hand.
I can hear his voice!
He's saying something.
I'm going down.
Hey!
I'm waving my hand.
I'm going down.
Congratulations!
I'm going to take it off.
I can't express it in words.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
Please come again.
I'm moved.
Thank you very much.
Next is a project.
It's called the 1000 people project.
Let's play dodgeball with 1000 people.
I wonder if I can do it.
That's how it started.
For the time being,
It was 500 people vs 500 people.
We played dodgeball with 1000 people.
The losing team will be punished.
That's what I'm saying.
That day,
I lost again.
I rode a roller coaster.
When I got on the roller coaster,
Everyone was wearing a bald head.
I'm going to ride a roller coaster.
The bald head is funny.
It's stupid.
Please take a look.
It's a ball.
Are you ready?
Why are you playing dodgeball with your fans?
You have to be punished.
It looks dangerous.
I hate it.
40 meters.
The lips are cute.
It's very high.
Don't move.
This is the scariest song.
It's very scary.
I was talking to him.
He said,
If I play dodgeball,
I can return the ball with my bare hands.
He said,
I did it.
If I can't return the ball,
I'll be punished.
I was punished.
It hurts.
Why did you do that?
Don't move.
We don't know what it is.
It's like a video game.
It hurts.
It's noisy.
My hands are cold.
It hurts.
I'm not cool.
That's all.
We'll do our best to promote our program.
Thank you.
Let's go over there.
Our work is done.
What time is it?
It's 1 o'clock in the evening.
There are no kids in downtown.
Do you want to see it?
It's 1 o'clock in the evening.
There are no kids in downtown.
Do you want to see it?
Let's do our best.
It's 1 o'clock in the evening.
There are no kids in downtown.
Do you want to see it?
It's 1 o'clock in the evening.
There are no kids in downtown.
Do you want to see it?
It's 1 o'clock in the evening.
It smells really bad.
It's OK.
I'm doing it now.
Who does this when they do makeup?
Let me introduce my wonderful partner.
She is...
Ms. Ikue Kakiwara.
She is eating the bento.
She is a big girl.
Nice to meet you.
Welcome.
Do you want to see it?
I'm doing one more thing.
I'm going to a hair salon.
I'm going to see the hair salon.
I think she will come next week.
I didn't have confidence.
I'm going to see the hair salon.