What kind of second half will the serious battle with the pride of winning and losing be like?
Let's go as far as we can go!
From now on, everyone will be given a variety of settings, so let's see how long it will take to complete those settings.
If it's cold, if you can't take it anymore, please press this button.
If you can't take it anymore, please press this button.
The person with the shortest seconds will be me, Shibakunasu.
Shibaku?
What does Shibaku mean?
It means Shibaku.
Shimi?
Yes, yes.
That's a long story.
First of all, Yamazaki-san.
Your topic is...
An impersonation of Tawara Toshihiko.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
This is really...
This is really tough.
Let's go as far as we can go!
Ready...
Sorry.
I'm too old.
I'm sorry.
What is this?
Are you okay?
Is this going to be long?
Yama-chan, 14 seconds.
14 seconds.
It's going to be even longer.
14 seconds?
This game...
This game is dangerous.
Next is Endo.
Endo's topic is...
Guitar solo.
Wow!
Yamazaki-san, you look like a *** girl.
Yama-chan, Yama-chan, Yama-chan.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Endo-san, quickly bring the guitar.
This is not a guitar.
This is tough.
Let's go, Endo-san.
Let's go as far as we can go!
Ready!
You did your best.
It's been a minute or two since I started.
Let's go.
Next is Miyasako.
Miyasako's topic is...
Octopus dance.
This octopus dance is going to be long.
It's long.
Let's go.
Miyasako, you can do it!
Let's go!
Ready!
This is the worst.
You're doing well.
22 seconds.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Don't cry.
This is too hard.
Let's go.
Next is Tanaka.
Tanaka's topic is...
Impersonation of Bruce Lee.
It's been a while since I've done this.
Let's go, Tanaka.
Let's go as far as we can go!
Ready!
It's over!
There are two left.
Hoto-chan.
Hoto-chan's topic is...
Big explosion.
What did you say?
Big explosion?
Me?
It's cold.
This is too bad.
Let's go, Hoto-chan.
Let's go as far as we can go!
Ready!
Hoto-chan!
I get it.
This is too hard.
It's because it's a big explosion.
It's because you're dead.
Hoto-chan, 4 seconds.
Let's go as far as we can go.
The last one is Matsumoto-san.
Matsumoto-san's topic is...
Impersonation of a chicken.
This is embarrassing.
This is the hardest one.
Don't cry so much!
I was just training myself to cry.
Damn it!
This is the hardest one.
Let's go!
It's cold!
Look at me!
Let's go!
Ready!
Hoto-chan!
4 seconds!
This is really hard.
Hoto-chan, 4 seconds.
What?
4 seconds.
It's Hoto-chan!
Thank goodness!
It's dangerous!
It's cold!
Let's go!
Everyone, do you remember this?
We did this before, right?
There are 6 lines.
Put your name plate on it.
If you open it, you'll know who will get punished.
There are 5 lines in order.
There are 15 lines.
Take it to the other person so you don't get punished.
But there is one line that you can't put on the other person.
If you can't put it on the other person, you'll get punished.
Why did you get punished?
Let's announce the first punishment game!
The first punishment game is this!
Stone wash!
There is one person who gets punished.
The remaining 5 people will stand in a line.
Stone wash in order.
I'll definitely win!
Everyone, put your name plate under the line.
Who will get punished?
This is the end of the first round.
Please put your name plate under the line.
There are times when you can't put your name plate under the line.
Don't put your name plate under the line.
There are 15 lines.
I want to run away, so I'll give it to Matsumoto-san.
Please throw it away.
Matsumoto-san ran away.
I'll give it back to Matsumoto-san.
Please give it to both of you.
This is not good.
I'll give it to Matsumoto-san.
Please give it back to Matsumoto-san.
This punishment game is stone wash.
There are times when you can't put your name plate under the line.
I'll give it to Matsumoto-san.
I'll give it back to Matsumoto-san.
Matsumoto-san, come here.
I really want to do this.
This punishment game is stone wash.
Please give it back to Matsumoto-san.
I'll give it back to Matsumoto-san.
This punishment game is wet tissue.
Please give it back to Matsumoto-san.
I'll give it back to Matsumoto-san.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.