What is this?
This is crazy!
What is it?
Wait a minute!
Why are you giving me a license?
What do you want?
Did you get a license?
Yes, I did.
Really?
License is a small amount, right?
No!
Then why are you giving me a license here?
There are many reasons.
Give it to me!
Why are you suddenly talking about money?
I will give it to you!
The timing is still the same!
There was a lot of money before the show started.
Really?
If I give it to you,
How many will you give me?
I won't give it to you with one hand.
Really?
Did you hear that?
I'm looking forward to it.
This is the first episode this year.
That's right.
This program is sponsored by the following sponsors.
To be honest,
I don't like the first episode of the show.
Really?
I'm still not excited.
I'm not excited.
But the audience is excited.
The audience is excited.
Yes, they are.
It doesn't matter.
It depends on the show.
That's right.
Where have you been?
I've been to Australia.
I've never said a word about that country.
Australia?
You go to places that are easy to understand every year.
I go to places that are easy to understand.
I've been to Guam this year.
You are a fool.
Yes, I am.
It doesn't matter.
It's not over if it's over.
I went to the elevator.
We were in the room for 22 times.
On the way, the door opened.
A stupid family came in.
An old man and an old woman.
The old woman was about the same age as me.
She was so ugly.
That's okay.
Like that other children's.
That's good.
You are like, who is this?
It's okay.
You embrace like this.
There was only you in the group we were in.
And you ask how many times on the skit with this group.
That'sbeeping.
It's.
17 times.
It's bad.
I thought, I'm missing the words.
Right?
Well, yeah.
And then, I thought, there must be something when I get off.
So I opened the door and went in.
And my grandma said, there's nothing here.
She was like, I'm not going to say anything.
I'm not going to say anything.
I couldn't get out of the house.
I was like, I'm not going to say anything.
It's just a word.
That's what I think.
If you say something like that directly, it might become a fight.
He's the one at fault, but he doesn't want to fight.
So at that time, I said, I'm sorry.
I don't have anything to do with him, but isn't it strange to look at him?
It's probably better to be a third party.
That's right.
Right?
If you don't do that, he's really embarrassed.
If you ask him what he's doing, he'll say, please don't do it. I'll do it if I have to.
It's definitely better to do it.
It's okay, but it's not good.
Well, he's the one at fault.
That's right.
It's definitely like that.
It's better to have a psychological part.
He's like, shut up.
He's like a fool.
He's like, huh?
Because he's a fool, he does team-w
He's a fool.
Is this guy going to do it?
It's like I'm not protecting anything.
There's no way I can just listen to you.
I'm feeling sort of like I used to live downtown.
Come here.
It's a subtle hair color.
Pen name number 8, Light-san.
Yes.
I have a question for you, the kind-hearted Matsumoto-san.
Ah, sure.
Matsumoto-san, it seems that you were expelled from the high school baseball league because you made a terrible mistake in your high school years.
What kind of mistake was that?
Well, I made a lot of mistakes.
Please tell me. What kind of mistake?
Eh?
What kind of mistake did you make?
The first time I made a mistake was when I threw the ball like this.
The moment I threw the ball and went to catch the ball, the seam of the ball came off.
Why did you do that?
Because it came off.
The opponent was like, wow, it came off!
Ah, I see.
This was very popular.
I don't know if it was popular, but...
Before you threw the ball, you had to pull the thread.
That's primitive.
If you just pull the thread, anyone can do it.
Ah, I see.
But it's a bit like a baseball.
Well, that's not a big deal.
I was just a bit angry.
Ah, you were just a bit angry?
Like Burning by the string.
like Burning by the string.
Yeah, I was like Burning by the string.
Any number of Roughly Characters is not enough.
So he told me, any number of Roughly Characters is not enough!
Well, it's fine.
Obviously you haven't worked on the loose ones.
How?
For example, about disappearable woodwork.
Those are only candles in manga magazines.
Yeah, right?
But they aren't like that.
Isn't it something that can be used realistically?
Could you tell us more about that?
Well, I wanted to remove the woodwork.
Look whoever it's from...
It's...
from the ball's perspective!
What was that?
You show it with who's perspective?
The ball you wanted to disappear from!
Well, I guess with the ball's...
It's from that perspective right?
Yea, it's a concept...
If you're aizione, it's also the ball you wanted to make disappear, right?
It's the ball that I wanted to make disappear...
The ball I wanted to disappear was also a CSS...
And there will be an end to it all.
That ball I wanted to disappear was broken.
What do you mean?
The batter is the one who wanted to hit.
This one threw the ball that wanted to disappear, but the other one threw the bat that wanted to hit.
And then it got hit.
Well, the batter is the one who wanted to hit.
That time was amazing.
Pen name 90's girl.
I have a question for the comedian who sings the lyrics.
Sure.
A long time ago, the song called Hair and Y-Shirt and Me was a huge hit.
Yes, yes, yes.
What did you want to say about that song?
Well, have you heard it before?
Well, yes, but I don't remember it clearly.
Ah, that's right.
Well, that's right.
But it was a huge hit.
Well, yes.
What did you want to say?
Well, that...
Hair and Y-Shirt and Me.
Well, to put it simply...
That heart is me.
To put it simply...
I said it really simply.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Matsumoto said that you went to your son's class.
Is that true?
I did.
You didn't!
You didn't go!
I did.
I think it was when I was in 4th grade.
That's a long time ago.
Yes, I did.
Oh, really?
Yes.
I don't know if I should say this on TV or not.
Why?
I was surprised.
What do you mean?
I watched it from the first hour to the fourth hour.
That's a long time ago!
Normally, there are at least two of them.
When I was about to go home, the other students wouldn't let go of my hand.
Ah, I see.
Because you came.
Yes, because I came.
Originally, there was a place for children.
I wonder how many times I patted my head.
I patted my head about 2,000 times.
Why?
I was surprised.
Yes.
Other than the third hour, my nose kept drooping.
A 4th grader's nose won't droop.
That was a huge amount.
There was a groove around here.
It was like a habit.
It was drooping so many times.
For some reason, it was split into two at Chikubi's place.
That was amazing.
The teacher didn't say anything.
Sometimes, I drank water.
Why did you do that?
My throat was dry.
Because my nose kept drooping so much.
With your blue eyes.
Lastly, Matsumoto-san.
The pen name is Sarukko-san.
What is it?
I always enjoy watching your videos.
I have a suggestion for you.
The year has changed.
Why don't you make a new debayashi and watch it?
Well, I've always...
You've made all your debayashi, haven't you?
Yes, I have.
I think it's about time for me to change.
Really?
When I was watching the previous debayashi, you were satisfied with it, weren't you?
Yes, yes.
The previous debayashi, too.
Oh, when it came out.
That's right.
Are you sure you want to change it?
I've been using it a lot.
You don't look like you've seen most of the shows.
I've seen it.
You don't look like you've been involved in most of the shows.
If I could, I'd like to do it again next year.
That's fine.
I'll ask Mr. Matsumoto to make a new one.
No, no, no.
Then, shall we record it?
That's fast.
What kind of debayashi are you thinking of this time?
Well, I'd like to go with a Latin style.
You want to go with a Latin style?
Well, everyone is mixed up in a Latin style.
That's right.
Right?
It's not a subtle hair color.
It's a little purple.
Is it okay?
Is it okay to make it look fancy?
Well, it's a debayashi.
What was the previous one?
The one with Garigari-kun.
Oh, that's just a fake.
When I made it, I said it over and over again.
That's the worst.
You said Garigari-kun at the end.
I just happened to wear it.
You just happened to wear it.
It's not a question of which one is the previous one.
Then, please.
Hitoshi is the Asian papillon.
You're wearing it again.
What do you mean by again?
What's Hitoshi is the Asian papillon?
Then, I'll ask.
Isn't Hitoshi the Asian papillon?
If it's not, then I'll apologize.
Hitoshi is the Asian papillon until the video.
Then, I'll cry.
I'll cry.
No, no, no.
The music now is perfect.
It's not perfect.
I don't say it's perfect.
What is it?
I feel it.
Like this.
I don't know how many people are here today.
When you came out, I think you'll be like,
When you saw me, you'll be like,
Oh, it's a papillon.
Where do you participate?
It's okay.
I can't participate in the papillon.
You can do whatever you want.
That's right.
Hitoshi is the Asian papillon.
Hitoshi is not the Asian papillon.
You're wrong, too.
I'll live for a while.
May I?
Don't write your ass in front of people.
Oh, oh.
Hitoshi is the Asian papillon.
Wait a minute.
You know what?
It's embarrassing to be laughed at,
Hitoshi is so embarrassing.
A large-scale show.
Like, how far can we go?
I just did it.
Let's go as far as we can go.
It's like that.
It's okay, it's okay.
Really?
Oh, then you should participate.
What would you like to do?
Well, then.
Please be the papillon.
Your voice is in.
Then, you can be the voice.
It's okay to choose the voice.
That's not it!
You've been singing like this the whole time!
That's right, that's right.
It's not like this, it's really like this.
It has nothing to do with debayashi!
Please take care of that.
I'm really embarrassed.
You're embarrassed, but I'm embarrassed too!
Well, well, well.
That's really, really...
It's good, isn't it?
My face is a little dead.
It's better to have it alive.
It hurts.
That's why I'm going to say,
Itoshi wa Asia no Papillon.
Yes.
Then I'll say something.
Then you should come in while dancing.
Come in?
Well,
Come in solo.
Wow!
Come in.
Well, that's fine.
Itoshi wa Asia no Papillon.
Masatoshi wa Asia no Papillon.
You can come in.
No, I'm not a Papillon.
It's like,
I'm not listening!
It's like that.
What kind of debayashi are you?
Everyone doesn't understand!
It's cold!
That's fine.
Can you follow me?
But that's the moon in the dance.
It's not just you.
Papillon is like that.
If you follow me, I'll...
Hamada wa Asia no Papillon.
Then I'll come back right away.
That's why I'm dancing.
Are you okay?
Me?
Yes.
Itoshi wa Asia no...
That's right.
Itoshi wa Asia no Papillon.
Then?
Hamada wa Asia no Papillon.
Then you should come in.
Ah, Hamada mo is better.
Yes.
Hamada mo, yes.
It's okay?
Yes.
Even if you haven't danced for a long time,
I know you haven't been on stage.
I know that from the first time we met.
Ah, this person is not very happy.
That's...
Well, let's give it a try.
Let's see if you can really dance.
It doesn't matter if you dance.
It's just this part, right?
What kind of way of thinking is that?
Why are you saying that?
It's not like that.
After all, if you listen to the song,
you'll know that you're dancing.
That's something that comes from your consciousness.
Ah, you're dancing.
I want you to feel that you're dancing.
Itoshi wa Asia no Papillon.
Come on!
Ah, yes.
Ah, it's already started, right?
Come on, dance!
Come on, dance properly!
Is that okay?
You really don't have any talent for dancing.
Why are you doing that?
Itoshi wa Asia no Papillon.
What?
You're just doing it randomly.
The previous one had a base,
and it was solid, right?
Ah, yes, yes.
The tempo was good.
That's right.
You changed that, so you did it well.
Ah, yes, yes.
You only have that one phrase.
That's not true.
What are you saying?
Itoshi wa Asia no Papillon.
Hamada mo Asia no Papillon.
It's already finished.
But,
But, I still love my mom.
Ah, yes.
Then what's the answer?
Why can't I think of the answer first?
Ah, I said something that's not consistent.
That's strange.
I'm doing it with cheap gyalas.
It's not gyalas.
Is that so?
Then, let's do the song.
Then, Masatoshi, Hamada,
then, Masatoshi, Hamada, please do Asia no Papillon.
Then, I'll do it.
But, I still love my mom.
Then you can write one.
I'm fine writing with you.
Then, we're going to change it, if you like.
Then, we're going to change it.
Just write it.
Just for now, just remember one.
What the hell is that?
Ah, I got it!
Can I do it in a heavy metal style?
Can you do it?
I can do it.
You can do it?
Then let me hear it.
I left one of the previous ones.
What are you going to do?
No, no, it's fine.
I haven't completed the heavy metal style at all.
Let me complete it.
How did you complete it?
If you say ah, I'll say ah too.
Really?
Ah!
I can't put my tongue out.
It's quite embarrassing, isn't it?
As expected, the Asian papillon is fine.
The Asian papillon, Udemoto.
No, the Asian papillon is fine.
I've never been to Asia.
Can I have an Asian papillon for one year?
Please.
Then why don't you come in?
Yes, right away.
Ah, it's been a while since we talked like this.
Right?
It's been a while?
No, this is the center mic.
Ah, is that so?
Well, it's fine.
Perhaps, that is...
It's fine.
I'm going!
Yes, then please.
In the end, please.
Please say it without laughing.
Ah, that's right.
Everyone, I'm sorry, but please.
Please say it in seconds.
I'm going.
5 seconds.
4, 3, 2, 1.
Cue!
One year, the Asian papillon!
Ah, it's still the same.
What are you doing?
The sense of rhythm is zero.
Come in quickly.
3, 2, 1, cue!
One year, the Asian papillon!
Ah, it's still the same.
You have to do this.
If you had this, you would have done it.
Let's do it properly.
You have to do it properly.
One year, the Asian papillon!
You should have said that to me first.
I said it was one year, and you said it was one year, so it's not wrong.
Come on, let's do it properly.
Hitoshi is an Asian papillon.
Hamada is an Asian papillon.
But I still love my mama.
OK!
OK? Thank you.
Let's listen to it.
Right away?
Right away.
Let's listen.
Hitoshi is an Asian papillon.
Hamada is an Asian papillon.
But I still love my mama.
Why is this like a training room?
I don't know.
Why is this recording?
It's OK.
You're going to fall from the bottom of the van.
Adam?
I'm going to fall from the top of the van.
That's funny.
Why is this recording?
I'm going to fall.
This program was provided by the following sponsors.