It's been a long time, hasn't it?
That's right.
It's my first time.
And it's Harajuku.
It's a young man's match.
Is it okay for an old man to walk?
Don't play with me.
I'm at work.
I'm going to walk around today.
I'm going to walk around, but it's not fun to just walk around.
Today, I'm going to walk around with Mr. Warakawa.
I go to various stores.
There is a fitting room.
Everyone goes in there.
I walk around the curtains.
I dress up and make the employees laugh.
It's individual play.
I understand.
If it's not funny, I'll kill you.
I'll kill you.
Please be careful with that.
It's amazing.
What is this?
I don't know.
Is this a girl's store?
It's very modern.
It's amazing.
Can you show me your face?
From here?
Yes.
Show me your face.
It's you.
Even ordinary customers can't do this.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
I don't know.
Don't you wear a hat like this?
Stop it.
Stop it?
It's okay.
You might look good in a hat like this.
It's like this.
I don't think so.
Please look inside.
Please put this on.
That's good.
This is good, too.
It looks good on you.
Wait a minute.
It's cute.
You don't look good at all.
It's hard to talk to you.
Don't say that.
This is the room.
This is a man's room.
Hello.
Thank you for coming.
Please buy something.
That's right.
END
Please buy something.
I like this.
That's right.
Hama-san.
Please come.
This way?
It looks short.
I'm sorry.
Ice coffee, please.
Is that so?
Do you have ice coffee?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Is it okay?
The clerk is calling you.
I have to ask the clerk to take a look.
Can you go?
Yes.
Why are you calling me?
Please look at the clerk.
I don't like it.
Why did you open it before?
I thought you wouldn't say that.
But you opened it before.
That's right.
It's a little different.
It's completely different from the image.
I thought you were going to wear it.
That's right.
That's why the first look is important.
It's not the kind of clothes that END wears.
Thank you very much.
It's cool.
It's not what Yuta said earlier.
I don't know how important the first look is.
That's right.
That's what I want to say.
It's different from the image.
That's right.
I want to say one more thing.
You shouldn't slip.
That's right.
What do you think of these two?
Do you want to try it on?
It's a little adult.
It's cool.
Let's try it on.
It's nice.
It's neatly organized.
That's right.
Let's ask someone to try it on.
Yamaguchi-san.
I think you should try on a jersey.
You don't have a jersey, do you?
I don't know if it's a jersey.
Let's try on a normal jersey.
Is this Lonsdale?
Yes.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Hurry up.
What is this?
It's Lonsdale.
It's easy to cut.
Really?
What do you think?
Let's try it on.
What are you doing?
You shouldn't do that.
Stop it.
What are you trying to wear?
Come out.
It's a jersey.
It's easy to cut.
Really?
It's a good size.
I think you can do it.
You're talking nonsense.
I think you're a man who's been living your life.
I think so.
I think you're older than us.
Old man?
I don't know.
It's not a big deal.
The weather is nice.
It's not like this anymore.
If there's a crepe, I'll eat it.
Let's eat.
I'll do my best.
There's ice cream.
You said crepe.
There's crepe in Harajuku.
Do you want to buy one?
Why do you buy one?
Let's buy one.
I'll buy vanilla mocha.
I can't use it.
This is a vanilla mocha.
105 yen.
This is for you.
Thank you.
I want to lose to 100 yen.
I'll give it to you.
Thank you.
It looks delicious.
It's delicious.
Thank you.
I'll give it to you.
Don't fight.
There are many.
It's a brown one.
It's an open cafe.
Don't fight.
I'm embarrassed.
I'll give you another one.
You are a foodie.
I'm glad.
You should eat it yourself.
He is angry.
I'm angry.
He's laughing
To be honest, I don't know how to react
It's good
I'll drink it here
It's embarrassing
This is for kids
I'll use it
It's okay
Yamasaki, drink beer
I can't do it
You can't do it
Drink beer
Drink Tanaka Wokka
Tanaka Wokka
Are you going to make him drunk?
Are you okay?
I'm going to do it now
Why are you looking at this old man?
It's amazing
Let's toast
Cheers
Thank you
I haven't finished my work yet
Yamaguchi, you are good
What are you doing?
It's a one-on-one
It's Wokka's double
When I was young, I played one-on-one with Matsumoto
We played one-on-one
At that time, it was crazy
It was crazy
It was one-on-one
Wokka Wokka
You don't drink alcohol, do you?
I can drink
You can drink
When you're in trouble
I'm going
Are you okay?
Who's next?
After all
What do you call it?
Giga Arai
End
Everyone is like that
Next time
My master
Really?
This is
This is the origin of the laughter of the general public
I think my master will say that
Really?
To be honest
I'm counting on you
I have a sense of crisis
Don't have a sense of crisis
How many years?
12 years
It's impossible
18 years
18 years?
Is this the 20th anniversary in two years?
That's right
Can you change the image of that Ibushi Gin?
I want to see that
Please
Let's go with this feeling
Let's go
18 years
It's the end
Of course
Shut up
Let's see
18 years
You can see it
Let's go
Let's hurry
You can see it
If you look at us
I and Matsumoto
This is not good
That's right
You have decided what to do before you enter
You can decide after you enter
Really?
I realized it from the 17th year
Last year
I realized it last year
I didn't realize it
I didn't realize it at all
It's not over yet
It's not like this
No
It's not like that
It's good for summer
It's not good
You are talking a lot
He is my master
I can do anything
But I don't choose the best
Sometimes I go home
That's the worst
I'm fine today
This
This is a big space
Hello
You can see it from the wind
I don't wear suits
I'll change my jacket
Can I change my suit?
I
I'm a professional
I have to listen to the staff
Why are you wearing it?
I'm going to buy it
I'm sorry
I'll have my jacket later
I have to listen to the staff
He has money
I can't buy my jacket
Alright
Is this all summer?
This is all summer
Isn't it hot around this time?
Oh, I have a jacket
Isn't it hot in here?
It might be a little hot.
It's almost the same as I thought.
White is the key.
This is the end of 2018.
Wait a minute.
Are you a prosecutor?
Are you hungry?
You look like you're going to die.
I did it.
You did it.
There's a lot of white.
That's right.
But I don't know if it's scary.
Did you see something?
I saw it today.
That's right.
Is that what happens when you wear it?
I think I went to a town like that.
I don't think I look good in a suit.
Maybe it's better not to wear it.
Thank you very much.
What is it?
I don't know.
As you can see.
Wonderful.
As expected.
It's our 18th year.
That's right.
It's different from the first year.
It's the weight of history.
Who's going to do it next?
I'll do it.
We chose the store.
That's right.
I'll leave it to you.
It's open here.
That's right.
Look at this.
There's a lot of laughter.
Is it here?
The laughter of people walking is falling.
That's right.
But the top and bottom are the same store.
The laughter rises from the bottom to the top.
That's right.
Let's go.
It's here.
I'll show you the 7th year.
That's right.
I'll do my best.
There are a lot of T-shirts that you like.
That's right.
You're so fast.
You're not tanned.
That's right.
Are you okay?
I don't know if it's expensive.
Excuse me.
Can I come in?
Can I come in anywhere?
That's right.
There are a lot of cars here.
Are you going to dress up?
I'm going to go to the theater.
Theater?
You don't understand the word for theater, do you?
I don't know the word for theater.
I'm talking to an actor.
I came here.
I'll show you the store.
Are you happy?
I'm happy.
Did you find anything?
No.
I found it.
Did you find anything?
What is this?
No.
Did you find anything?
The end.
Please close the store.
I'm sorry.
I'm still young.
The silhouette has disappeared.
I'm sorry.
Good luck.
It was still early.
It was early.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
It's difficult.
As you can see,
It's been seven years.
As you said,
It's been 18 years.
Please show me.
I'm addicted to comedy.
Please call me OACHU.
I'm always laughing.
I want to laugh.
I'm ready.
It's red.
Look.
It's normal.
It's OACHU.
What if you get out of the store?
What?
Is this the store?
Look at the name of the store.
Hachika 2N 1
Hachika?
This is the name of the store.
I do not know.
Come here.
It's the 18th year.
Hello.
Please show me.
It's a store name.
It's a no-sleeve.
White pants and no-sleeve is good, isn't it?
Yes, no-sleeve is the trend now.
It's quite an image.
I'd like to change my mind.
I'd like to go to a place where my interests have changed.
I'd like to try this on.
Try it on.
May I?
It's quite an image.
Is it okay to wear this?
What if I'm wearing it?
That's too much.
May I?
Yes.
Excuse me.
Today is the 18th anniversary.
It's a miracle.
I think I'll be able to see a little bit of his comedy.
I'm going to drop everything I'm holding on to.
I have to hold it all down with a smile.
How old are you in the audience?
I'm in my 20s.
You're pretty young.
The old man is coming in.
He's the guide.
Can I come in?
Please stand up.
I'm ready.
Can I come in?
Please stand up.
I'm ready.
Can I come in?
Please stand up.
What's wrong with you guys?
It was a powerful technique.
To be honest.
I thought it was a terrible technique.
Today is the 18th year.
Is that a sword?
That's not a sword.
I don't think it's a sword.
Take a little more bamboo.
Do you really want to come in?
I really want to come in.
I'm sorry.
What?
Your pants are frozen.
To be honest, it was a powerful technique.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter?
Please give me a receipt.
I give you a receipt.
I found it.
Please give me a receipt.
I'm shopping.
Don't get in my way.
It's private.
It's not private.
It doesn't matter.
And it doesn't look good on you.
It doesn't look good on you.
This is a store for junior high school students.
35-year-olds don't look good in it.
Don't get in my way.
Get out of here.
I don't feel good in it.
It doesn't look good on you.
It's private.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.