This is the 5th episode of Gaki no Tsukai, Tsukishige! Tsukikirai Dottieru!
Hello, hello.
It's been a while.
This is the 5th episode.
That's right.
It's been a while.
It's really been a while.
I don't like it.
Let's just say that this isn't our intention.
I'll put it on without permission.
That's right.
We'll talk in a way that you don't know where to start.
I'm really sorry for the entertainers who got it.
That's right.
I'll talk about how to do it.
I'm afraid it'll take forever.
Are you apologizing or not?
Then shall we do it?
Isn't it obvious?
Oh, is that so?
That's right.
There's a lot of heavy stuff in here today.
This program is brought to you by the sponsors you see.
Okay.
Let's go.
Here we go.
Thank you very much.
Stop it.
I've been watching you all this time.
Hey, hey.
That's enough.
Even if it's done, it's still a scene.
Wait, wait.
Let's try your hate.
Do you hate me?
I hate you.
This is a good thing.
It seems to be the most hated woman in the world right now.
I don't know why you hate me so much.
Well, I hate you.
What do you hate about me?
The way you talk.
You look like you have a bad breath.
I don't think it's a good idea to say that just for the sake of image.
No, no, no.
You're watching TV.
It's just an image, isn't it?
I hate you.
Hey, if you really have a bad breath, say it.
When I went to the bathroom, it smelled like poop.
It doesn't matter if you say that.
Matsunosuke Shio was angry.
It stinks.
It seems that the image of the drama was quite bad in this case.
There was a drama that I was doing with Ken Ogata.
The role at that time was so unaccepted by women.
I feel sorry for that.
Please follow me.
I hate you.
It doesn't matter where you are.
I want you to do your best.
I'm sending you an e-mail.
Rather than saying that you hate me, I want you to say,
I hate you.
I want you to do your best.
I think it would be nice if I could see it in the Keirai line.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Next to this.
Do you like this?
It's cool, isn't it?
What do you mean?
The eyebrows are drawn more than necessary.
He is a young actor now.
Is that so?
I think everyone is watching him now.
Do you want to be like him?
I want to be like him when I'm young.
I see.
It's cool.
What are you doing to my favorite child?
Stop it.
It's disgusting.
It's about this.
It's a song.
This person is good.
What is good about him?
He doesn't do much activity.
He is doing it.
He earns more than I do.
But I think he is short-tempered.
But why is he short-tempered?
When he appears on TV, do you watch him?
I saw him.
That's not good.
It's not a variety show.
I saw him.
I don't want to be next to him.
I saw him in the quiz.
Do you watch him when he appears on TV?
But I like him.
What are you talking about?
People who support him are different.
Is that so?
Tell me what you hate about him.
You hate him a lot.
No, I don't hate him.
What are you talking about?
I don't like him.
What?
I can't forgive him.
When I was young, I didn't like him.
You don't like him at all.
When he appears in front of you, you don't like him.
That's right.
I don't like him.
I like him as a man.
I got it.
Hurry up.
I don't like him.
I don't know how you feel.
I hate him.
In the middle.
Rikiya-san.
He looks like a kind person.
I'm just kidding.
I can beat him.
He is my country typhoon.
What kind of technique is that?
I can't beat him.
Country typhoon?
You look weak.
You look weak just by saying country.
I can't beat him.
Is that so?
Tell me what you like about him.
Okay.
Do you like him?
No, I don't like him.
I don't like him at all.
I haven't seen him before.
Do you like him that much?
If you say so.
It's been a long time since he came back to Golden Brown.
He came back.
That's right.
In that sense.
I found him.
That's right.
Let's go next.
Okay.
Next.
Do you like him?
Is that so?
I like the way he looks.
Even though he is a porn star.
If I could see him a little bit.
I like his attitude.
I love his attitude.
I want to kill him.
I love him so much that I want to kill him.
That's right.
I really want you to do your best.
Who is that?
MCAT.
His real name is Ichiro Yanagida.
Is that so?
His real name is Okamoto Takeshi.
Okamoto-kun.
He always wears a spear-like hat.
He has a very low back.
When I see him.
He has an attitude like this.
Like this.
Boom.
That's what he says.
I don't know him very well.
You still like him.
That's right.
I like him.
Who is this?
Do you like him so much?
Can I sit over there?
But I like him.
What is this?
You put out a record, didn't you?
That's right.
I don't want to see him.
But I'm late at night.
I watch TV until the end.
I don't like smelly things.
I hate it.
That's right.
I turn off the TV.
But I don't like it.
I can't help it.
Jesus.
You remember it too much.
I don't like it.
On the contrary, I want to tease him.
But this kind of woman is a narrow-minded woman.
You put out a record, didn't you?
I make a record.
You make a record.
Amen.
I'm very happy.
Jesus.
Thank you.
Last week, a woman came to my house.
She said,
I'm here.
If you don't say that, I have a follow-up report.
I don't know what time it was.
It was past 12 o'clock.
I heard a sound.
It's the same.
I said,
Yes.
I saw it on the monitor.
I saw it on AVEC.
That's a rare pattern.
This is Hama's house.
What?
I was surprised.
I started to kiss her.
Her eyes were in front of the monitor.
I hugged her and hugged her.
I kissed her.
What should I do?
It's amazing.
It's sweet.
Don't do that.
You come to my house.
That's right.
I'm scared.
What's the follow-up report?
It's been a week since then.
Is it the same person?
The same person came again.
I didn't keep my promise.
What is the purpose?
Please give me a hug.
I understand.
Let's shake hands.
But...
Don't do that.
I'll give you a hug.
I can't do that.
I can't fall in love with a woman I like.
Don't say that.
I'm not interested in women.
I can't do that.
Don't say that.
You're the only one I like.
She told you that.
I'm angry.
She was angry at me.
That's right.
Stop it.
Don't do that.
You stay away from me.
Please don't do that.
I'm angry.
Stop it!
You're the one who's saying that it's ugly.
The ugly thing I'm saying is, even though it's ugly...
You're the one who's saying it's ugly.
Even though it's not good,
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm saying that it's the ugly thing that you haven't noticed.
It's strange that you admit it, but the ugly thing in the world,
many ugly things, you don't think they're ugly, right?
For example, even though he has a face of about 50 points,
even though he's handsome,
there's no one who can understand that he has 50 points, right?
For example, if you're a man,
if you only talk about the face, it's really about 30 points, right?
Even if you say that you have 30 points,
you think you have 50 points, right?
That's not good!
When I look at you like that, I get angry and run away.
How many points are you running away from?
How many points do you think you have?
80 points.
So, you have a sin of 50 points.
Even though you have 30 points, 80 means 50.
Yes, yes, yes.
Can't you just increase it?
Yes, yes.
This anger is my anger of 50 points,
and it's my country typhoon.
Can't you forget it?
Can't you forget your own skill?
It's really a typhoon, isn't it?
Yes, yes, yes.
Can't you just increase the typhoon?
Everyone thinks you have 30 points.
I've heard that you have 30 points.
Hey, wait a minute.
What kind of conversation is it that I have 30 points?
What kind of talk is that?
When I got on the plane, I said that I was a captain.
I'm an announcer.
I'm going through a bad place right now.
Anyway, you have 30 points.
I have 30 points.
I don't care.
I don't care if I get angry.
How many points do you think you have?
I don't care if you give me points.
I don't play with looks.
I don't care about that.
How many points do you think you have?
I don't want to be honest.
Of course.
How far can you go?
Only your face?
Or this really...
Red body?
It's not red.
So what's my 30 points?
A total score of 30 points?
Only your face.
Then give me the whole thing.
Put the whole thing in?
If you put the whole thing in, it's 30 points.
What?
It's not increasing.
It's increasing.
It's a plus point.
Why is it increasing?
Look over there.
Turn around.
30 points.
I don't know what you're doing.
It's okay.
It's okay if you're the same age as Matsumoto.
How many points do you have?
I'll be honest.
85 points.
85?
It's okay.
I don't care.
It's just that you have a handicap.
It's a handicap.
It started with a bunker when I was born.
Wait a minute.
This is really rude.
How many points do you have?
I don't think it's as hard as everyone says.
It's about 40.
Wait a minute.
No, no, no.
Thank you for your help.
Wait.
I have 30 points, but why do you all have 40 points?
Why is your score so low?
First of all, you rely on medicine.
This is the most important thing.
Wait.
What kind of technology is that?
I didn't do anything.
Say something.
Everyone is too determined with their characters.
Don't you think so?
For example?
For example, Shimura Ken.
His face is quite masculine.
Is it masculine?
Just by looking at his face.
It's not masculine.
If you look up, you'll think it's hard.
But Mr. Ikagaya is...
I'm not angry.
He's also a bunker.
I'm angry.
I've never seen a person who is said to be the second best actor.
It's called Tsutsui something.
It's not ugly, is it?
How many points does he have?
Tsutsui?
Tsutsui has about 50 points.
Tsutsui has 50 points.
You're looking for something lower than yourself.
I don't think I'm the worst.
Who is lower than me?
Who is lower than you?
There's a lot of them.
I don't know if I'm lower than you, but I know someone like you.
Who?
Oguchi.
It's Oguchi.
I did it.
Is Oguchi lower than 30?
I don't know.
Who is said to be the most muscular man?
It's me.
It's me in your evaluation.
Really?
How many points do you have?
My own?
70 points.
65 points.
I won't give it to you.
If it's 65 points, it's 27 points.
That's mean.
It's not mean.
It's sad.
Why?
Is it sad if it's 65 points?
How many points do you have?
I'll give you half.
If it's at least 40 points, I'll give it to you.
I'll tell you the truth.
You.
30 points.
I want to tell you the truth.
I'm sorry.
Don't say sorry.
I'm really sorry this time.
This is serious.
How many points do you have for me?
About 50 points.
Really?
Are you happy with 50 points?
Hey.
Wait.
You have a low score of 50 points.
And the audience is surprised by your score of 50 points.
Really?
I'll give you half for 65 points.
How many points do you have for 30 points?
No one has a problem with this guy's score of 50 points, right?
This is serious.
Sing more.
I don't want to talk with you anymore.
If you don't do it here, I can't help you.
You have to sing more.
I'll ask you every time.
How many points do you have?
Okay.
Okay, come to the academy later.
I can't believe you have 89 points.
I was looking for a guy who has the same score as me.
But it's Jean Claude Van Damme.
There are many kinds of people.
How many points do you have?
Is your scouter correct?
What about Clipper?
Who is Clipper?
Ah, Higashi.
I bought it.
Did you compare it with Clipper?
Matsumoto used to be called the god of pantomime.
Please show it.
He was called the god of pantomime.
He was called the silent artist.
Well, that's the way it is.
He was called like that.
Today, I'll show you the wall.
That's...
That's a complete amateur.
If you ask me to show you the wall, an amateur will do it right away.
I can't do that.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I'll ask you something.
Do you always touch the real wall when you see it?
You don't touch it, do you?
I don't care. Please do it.
That's the appearance.
That's your point of view.
This is the real wall.
No, that's not true.
I think that's an advanced technique.
Ah, I see.
But, in general,
like this.
Please show me this.
If you want to do it, you have to take it off.
Please wear it.
What?
Ah, that's the way it is.
You have to make your body soft.
That's the way it is.
It's not bent so much.
How about this?
What?
The wall.
Please show me the wall.
I can't do it without a song.
What kind of song do you want?
Who told you to dance?
The wall.
I'm thirsty.
The wall that comes close.
The wall that comes close?
It's a normal wall.
What are you doing?
It's simple.
You have to make your body soft.
That's the way it is.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I was surprised.