Check the bond between the parents and children of the Edo family
Hohohoi, the Nobel Prize is presented!
How about you? Have you ever received a Nobel Prize?
There's no way I have
I think you will
There's no way I will
That's right
Today, the children of the Edo family
There are two of them, right?
They're still small
My father said he could win the Nobel Prize.
He said he could get it.
Why did he say that?
Because Hohohoi saved the world.
He said he could get the Nobel Prize.
Today is the award ceremony for the Nobel Prize.
Yes, yes, yes.
You're so
But it's amazing for the children.
They can get a lot of prizes for winning the Nobel Prize.
That's amazing.
Are you okay?
You can't stop me?
What do you mean?
I mean, you can't stop me from making a Tokyo Tower.
Do you have money?
No, it's a Nobel Prize.
Nobel Prize?
It's a Nobel Prize.
You're saying too much.
You're going to raise 100 sports cars.
But if you say that, the kids will be surprised.
Kokoriko Endo created a hit joke with a kid's use.
Hohohoi
This time, the two sons of the Edo family were invited to the ceremony as the Nobel Prize was awarded.
I don't know what the Nobel Prize is.
Anyway, everyone is really amazing about me.
You know, the hohohoi hohohoi thing.
That's what everyone in the world, especially children, are happy about.
And I'm going to give you an award for that.
What?
Here?
The Edo family has prepared many luxury items as the prize of the Nobel Prize.
Among them are the dinosaur figurines that Shonan Sora-kun wants,
and the rideable radio control car that Jinan Uta-kun adores.
However, in order to obtain these luxury awards,
They must achieve this in the awards ceremony.
There are certain conditions.
In the end, the children will do the hohohoi.
If the children don't get excited,
the Nobel Prize might disappear.
If the children hear this,
they might laugh for their father and for the hohohoi.
And they want that.
They want that.
Usually, there is no reason to laugh at the Hohoi.
I don't think so.
So, there are many people who are prepared.
In that sense, it is about how much the children laugh at the Hohoi.
What is it?
The ceremony is about to begin.
To make Sora and Uta believe that this is a real Nobel Prize,
the award ceremony has prepared several hidden cameras and extra foreigners.
The four of them will monitor the performance of the Eendouken in a different room.
Endo Prefecture, time travel, we have arrived at the award ceremony.
We have arrived.
Wow, look at this.
This is the reception.
Wow, congratulations, thank you.
Congratulations on the award.
Thank you.
Wow, this is a red carpet.
Hello, what's your name?
Suwa-kun
Suwa-kun, what's your name?
Usa-kun
How old are you?
5 years old
3 years old
You're a big brother!
First, let's celebrate with champagne
Let's eat.
Can you clap for me?
No, no, no.
Endo, you are starting to believe this, aren't you?
What kind of a fool are you?
I don't know.
After the reception, Endo goes to the control room.
This is the changing room.
It looks like a hotel.
Let's sit down.
It's no use to make a room for the Nobel Prize winner.
It's nothing.
Really?
You just put the sofa there.
Sorry.
You are reproducing it.
What's wrong?
Like juice?
Suddenly?
Do you drink juice?
No, I don't.
You look nervous.
I'm nervous.
Do you want to win the Nobel Prize?
Yes.
Are you listening?
What are you doing?
What?
You can't win the Nobel Prize from such a person.
Do you want to buy a flower?
Yes, I do.
You thought it was bad, didn't you?
Your wife is laughing and blowing the candle.
Well, you have to laugh.
What will you do if your father's Nobel Prize is gone?
I don't want it.
No, I will destroy the water.
What?
I will throw away the water.
Who?
Dad did.
Dad did? Why?
Because he was married.
This is how you talk to your children, right?
It's not funny at all.
This is how you talk to your children.
Before the Nobel Prize ceremony, the main venue is visible.
Thank you.
Everyone is clapping.
Watching toys makes me excited.
That's right.
You can watch toys here.
It makes you excited.
This is the venue for the Onberi Show.
It's empty, isn't it?
He's already stopped.
His eyes are fixed.
That's right.
His eyes are fixed even when he's completely stopped.
What is this?
I got a toy!
Wait, don't touch it yet!
Don't touch it yet!
Look! Look!
Look!
You usually eat it smoothly!
You eat it smoothly, right?
Is this your sword?
Look! Look!
You can eat it really well!
Look!
It's really amazing.
That ball is amazing.
Hey, you can eat a lot of this.
What is a tsuru tsuru?
Hey, leave it there.
When he returned to the engine room,
he was busy with the Nobel Prize in the world's Vip and other commemorative photos.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
And Tanaka, his partner.
It's been a while.
Congratulations.
No, no, I'm sorry.
You've been saying that you wanted to win the Nobel Prize since you were a kid.
I want to win it.
If you can win it, then go ahead and ask.
Isn't it amazing?
Dad, you won the Nobel Prize!
Right?
Congratulations!
Thank you.
You became a partner of the Nobel Prize.
Well, that's true.
Yes.
See you later.
Bye bye.
Please.
How was it?
Did it hurt?
Yes, it didn't really echo.
I felt it.
It didn't echo that much.
It didn't really hit me.
It hurts weirdly.
Let's go, Jotaro.
I'm sure the two of them will be happy.
We should go too.
I guess so.
I'm sure they'll be happy.
Are they crying?
Yes.
I wonder what the children will think of the downtown.
Oh, that's right.
Congratulations!
I'm really surprised!
Hello!
This is Hama-chan.
Yes, Hama-chan.
Thank you very much.
Do you know what prize you will get?
What prize?
A ball.
What?
It's hot.
What are you talking about?
I'm glad you laughed.
I'm sorry to say this, but...
I have a friend who asked me to buy you a sign.
Oh, no problem.
All three of us.
Can you make it round?
No problem.
Oh, it's good.
It's a Nobel Prize.
Here you are.
Thank you.
I'll come again.
Thank you!
You've seen it, right?
Matcha and Hamachan.
They're on TV, right?
Dad is amazing!
Thank you.
Dad is amazing.
Good job.
I got it.
You got it.
It's not important.
I don't know what's left.
I'm sending a message to the secretary.
The Hohohoi Nobel Prize for the Happening.
From now on, I will be giving the Nobel Prize to the En-do Shouzo, Hohohoi.
Now, Mr. Hohohoi, who has received the Nobel Prize, will enter the stage.
It's a song.
It's been played all over the world.
Thank you.
First, I would like to give a trophy and a medal to the Chairman of the Nobel Prize Committee, Mr. Nobel.
burner.
Lady Kyun hospital,
Mr. Einsatz,
You have been doing hohohoi for 23 years.
I hereby declare that I have made a solemn pledge to the world peace.
Thank you very much.
Oh, the kids are paying attention.
Now, please take a photo of the memorial.
This is embarrassing.
It says Nobel Prize.
And today, we have received a congratulatory comment from this person.
No way.
A congratulatory comment?
Hi, Shozo.
Today, I'm sending a congratulatory message to my old friend, Shozo, from the White House.
That's too much.
I'm sorry I couldn't attend the award ceremony directly.
I just took office and I couldn't leave.
Hohohoi is the symbol of world peace.
On behalf of the American people, I offer you our sincere congratulations.
Shouzo, congratulations on winning the Nobel Prize.
Hohohoi.
And today, these people have also come to the venue to congratulate you.
Please come up to the stage.
Thank you!
Congratulations!
It was really good.
Thank you.
I'm proud of you.
I'm your senior, but I'm proud of your junior for winning such a wonderful award.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I'm really happy that the word Hohohoi has become a common word in the world.
Please keep up the good work. I'm really proud of you.
Congratulations.
I think the way of thinking will change after the award.
The way of thinking.
I think it's not the way of thinking that has been done before.
I would like to see it.
Thank you very much.
From here, we will answer the questions from foreign media reporters from all over the world.
Thank you for the Nobel Prize.
Thank you.
What is Hohohoi to you?
Well, it's a joke that came out of nowhere.
It's something that came out when I was really cornered.
Actually, it was about 25 years ago.
I'm not interested.
I didn't even think I'd win the Nobel Prize in this way.
As Hamada-san said, I think it's the opposite of what I said earlier.
I'm really in my 50s, so I'm focusing on the children of this world.
If you could laugh at my hohoi, I think it would be a good ending.
It's not like that. I'm 3 years old, so I'm worried.
If you have any unexpected difficulties in hohohoi, please tell me.
There was a good side to the story because of Hohohoi, but there was also a night when he crushed me.
What are you talking about?
A night when he crushed me.
After this, Mr. Endo will be able to show the Hohohoi that he won at the Nobel Prize.
This model will be broadcasted on the same channel in over 120 countries around the world.
Mr. Endo, please prepare the Hohohoi.
Mr. Sawa, it's about time.
Yes, I wonder what kind of reaction the children will show.
Do you want to see the reaction?
Yes, I want them to smile for their father.
The people at the venue are moved.
Nobody is laughing.
I'm curious to see what they think when they feel that way.
Thank you for waiting, everyone.
Mr. Hou Houi.
The end of the novel by the novelist Shouzo.
Isn't this the bakery?
Oh, it's this way.
Oh, this way.
Oh, I see.
Oh, they're laughing.
What do you think of the tattoos?
The two of them are laughing.
Do you know the rhythm of the Sampa?
To make the world peaceful!
They're laughing.
They're laughing!
It's fun.
This is a good family song.
Yes.
It's a natural family song.
That was the end of the show.
Everyone, once again, a big round of applause.
Overall, I don't think they've received it very well.
They haven't received it.
They're going to be sent home like this.
They're the ones who won the Nobel Prize.
They're the ones who won the free open-air bath.
They've safely finished their hard work and have a peaceful endo-ke.
Next Day
The atmosphere changes immediately.
Even children can understand.
He's really angry.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
His father is being scolded by a foreigner.
He was angry.
Why?
You know how I did the Nobel Prize?
Yes.
I did it like this.
Did you laugh?
I laughed.
I laughed a little.
A little?
You shouldn't laugh a little.
If you don't laugh, the dinosaur toy, the car, the food, the refrigerator, the coffee, everything will be gone.
OK? Can I have it?
No.
You don't want it, do you?
I'll try again.
Try laughing.
I'll do it.
Don't make me do it.
Don't make me do it completely.
Make a voice.
It's not that funny.
It's good.
It's a big laugh.
To show the proper Hohohoi for the Nobel Prize, the Edo family returned to the venue once again.
The big laughter from the first time was heard in the venue.
The song came out like this.
Dad couldn't see it, but I had to concentrate on the method.
Everyone was watching.
It was a little different.
The number of the number has changed.
I'm scared.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Can you listen to me?
I'll do it one more time.
I'll give you one more chance.
I want to see you again.
I was taken away.
I'm really tired.
I'll practice it once.
One, two, three, go!
You're making me do it all over again!
I'm going to do it with the table!
You're not laughing, are you?
You're not looking?
You're just screaming.
It's really close, right?
Now, the last chance. The strong bond between the parents of the children of the endo.
Watch it carefully.
I'll spread my arms.
Here it comes!
I haven't done anything yet.
What are you doing?
You haven't done anything yet.
I'm not going to die.
Everyone, please give a round of applause for Mr. Hontoro Kazaki.
Thank you!
Thank you for your hard work!
It was great! It was great!
Today, the members gave gifts to Sora and Uta who worked hard for their father.
Thank you!
It was great!
It was great today!
Bye!
Susышkaraiー Hik via Fajiru