Happy Birthday to you!
You...
You've been doing this for 2 years now!
Ah, I'm sorry!
Happy Birthday to you!
Hey, last year you were even better!
I'm not like this anymore!
You're making me blush!
That means I'm more interesting than last year!
You're more interesting than last year!
Next time, on the Gaki no Chikai Alliance,
Chikichiki Shinto Mechakusureba
Himamata Sushi Daisakusen!
Mr. Asakusa, what is this all about?
Today, we're here at the Asakusa Torinji.
Yes, we're here.
What is this all about?
We've decided to do a dodgeball match soon.
Yes, we will.
Yes.
We've decided to do a dodgeball match soon.
We're counting on you.
Well, it's impossible to gain strength from now on.
So, we'll start from the spirit.
I see.
That's why we've come here today.
Yes.
We've come here for dinner.
Let's have fun together.
Please come in.
In the middle.
Don't open your eyes.
You see how on TV,
you're sitting like this,
and the ball is going from behind, right?
That's right.
So, today, we'll have dinner.
Ah, really?
Yes, please.
Stand up like this.
This guy is...
The producer's fault is that he's so cheeky.
Is that so?
Well, I hope you win this time.
I'll do my best.
He's so cheeky.
Let me stab him.
He seems to be serious only at this time.
That's it.
Now the show will get excited, right?
Yes.
I'll do my best at the supermarket.
Do you do that kind of show?
Yes, I do.
And I'm from America.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
The next day
You're smart.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Then, let's sing together.
Lower your head.
I'll watch this show.
I'll watch it when I go home.
Please do it again.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Is there anyone who wants to do it again?
What's this?
I'll do it again.
I don't think you want to do it again.
That's right.
Please do it again.
That's it.
That's too much.
Thank you very much.
What's next?
Next is...
I don't know what kind of disaster will happen.
That's right.
Be quiet.
Don't move.
I'm giving you a tissue.
Let's take it.
He's a spider.
It hurts.
Please do it against the edge of your teeth.
I'll do it from the bottom of my heart.
Mr. Hamada.
That's it.
I wonder if their spirits have gotten stronger.
I don't know about that.
I think all of them are bad.
I want to punish the worst of them.
The one that stood out the most was...
Otomo-kun.
I saw him earlier.
Don't open your eyes.
Otomo, what are you looking at?
I think Suga is the one who's hot right now.
I opened my eyes.
Otomo opened his eyes.
I saw him.
Oh no.
I opened my eyes even though I told you not to look.
I think it's Nitta.
I see.
Why do you have so much hair?
Why can't you get a haircut?
In the end,
it's Nitta.
I see.
Let's give a round of applause to Nitta-kun.
Here we go.
It's hot.
He's crying.
Ladies and gentlemen.
I'm so excited.
I don't know what to do.
It's been a long time.
I'll do my best today.
What are you going to do?
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
You were talking about something random.
You talk about something random.
I'll talk about it.
It's hot these days.
Why?
Is it hot?
Wait a minute.
I didn't say why.
What's wrong with you when you say so?
It's hot!
Everyone, I think.
In people,
The
And then he goes like this, right?
The old man is a bit of a fool.
That's how it is.
The role has been decided, right?
The role, right?
Right?
That's why you can't just let it go like that.
You want to get caught.
The personality of a guy who goes like that is a bit strange.
It's bad.
It's definitely like that.
It's not like that at all.
Why?
It's not like that at all, right?
That's why, how do I say it?
I often say things like that in the manga,
but when I'm watching TV,
you know,
when I'm watching TV,
or when I'm at the venue today,
I say things like that instead.
I say things that you can't help but say,
and you're like,
I've said things that you can't help but say.
I've said things that make everyone laugh.
I say things that you can't help but say,
and you're like,
people who are listening,
they'll think,
you're such an idiot!
And then you'll say,
That's how it is.
It's a change.
And then you'll be like,
yeah, yeah,
I don't think he's an idiot.
Right?
Yeah, yeah.
The details.
But, but,
even if you're like that,
when you're at home,
for example,
when you're watching TV,
you don't say things like that?
If it's strange.
You don't say things like,
you're a liar!
I have that too.
You do.
I do.
I think everyone has that.
When it comes to saying things like that,
me or anyone else has it.
Everyone has it.
From where and where is it saying things like that?
Eh?
For example,
when you're angry,
when you say,
you're such an idiot,
that's a saying.
When you're angry,
that's a joke.
In that sense,
it's a joke,
but,
when you say,
you're such an idiot,
that's a saying.
If you're going to say something like that,
it's,
you're such an idiot,
that's a joke.
You don't say things like that.
This is,
you know,
it's in the anime too,
saying things like that.
When I research it.
When did you research it?
Well,
for example,
what and what?
In the anime,
for example,
what and what?
That's why,
I wrote it on the radio before,
but,
in Asuta no Joe,
saying things like that,
it's a joke,
that's a saying.
Eh?
What about Joe?
Which one?
Joe,
in Asuta no Joe,
saying things like that,
it's a joke,
that's a joke.
Who said that?
Tange, Danpei,
said that.
I see.
It's already decided.
Why is that?
What do you mean?
That's completely a joke too!
What's so good about it?
You know,
when someone says something,
and you say,
hehe,
and you laugh,
that's a joke.
I see.
You can't reply.
You can't talk.
That's right.
When you can't talk,
you just say,
hehehe.
That's right.
That's also a complete joke.
That's true.
In the anime,
there's also a joke
and a punchline.
Kyutaro the ghost.
The joke is
Kyutaro,
right?
Who's the punchline?
You know,
the punchline is Pico.
My sister's.
Oh,
really?
But,
the joke is Kyu-chan,
and the Pico is the punchline,
but the natural joke,
the one that's like
Jimmy Onishi,
is Ojiro.
Ah.
He doesn't talk.
He only says,
bakeratta.
Even if he gets punched,
he says,
bakeratta.
He's like Jo and Ishii.
He's like Jo.
No matter what he says,
he can't talk.
That's right.
That's also in animals.
What does that mean?
You know,
there's a saying,
the strong eat the weak.
The strong eat the weak.
The strong eat the strong.
The weak eat the weak.
The strong eat the weak.
That's in the animal world.
So the lion is the joke?
What?
You don't listen to other people.
The strong eat the weak.
So the lion is the joke?
Yes, the lion is the joke.
The lion is the joke in everything.
He's so mean.
Then there's no joke that's as good as the lion.
Why?
There's no joke that's as good as the lion.
Really?
Yes.
So in the animal world,
the only joke is the lion?
What's with the lion's head?
In the animal world,
there are jokes and jokes.
But in the animal world,
the lion is the joke.
That's how strong the lion is.
Yohkann,
you're in a star group called Town Town.
Right?
I'm not in a group.
You're in charge of jokes.
How's your head?
What?
Can you fight?
It's not in my legs yet.
In the Town Town,
you're in charge of jokes.
But you're never in charge of jokes.
You have times when you get in charge of jokes.
You go up against the wall like this,
saying,
strong, strong, strong, strong.
That's why in the animal world...
You,
You know...
What?
When you talk about people...
What is this?
There are times when your nose is red!
Don't you have that?
When your nose is red.
I don't have it.
There are times when your nose is red!
That's you.
It's definitely nose cancer.
That's enough.
There are no more pictures.
There are a lot of things like this.
I got it.
If you talk a little more...
There will be a lot of comedy boxes.
No, I don't know what's going to happen.
I don't want to go any further.
As expected.
I'm going to make a lot of things.
There are empty boxes.
There are.
Please write.
What is that?
There are a lot of customers today.
Thank you.
Here.
It's a lie.
Let me introduce you.
This is Keigo Horiguchi.
He is 23 years old.
Is that so?
I thought he was younger.
He is from Shinagawa district, Tokyo.
His hobby is to go to...
...Yurakugai.
Yes, Yurakugai.
He likes to go to Yurakugai in Gotanda to look for matcha.
It's just one shot!
This is for those who are listening.
Why are you so nervous?
Everyone...
What?
I didn't do anything wrong.
You should have told me.
I did it proudly.
You didn't.
I said what I wanted to say.
Everyone...
Hey, hey, hey!
Why are you shaking?
I didn't do anything wrong.
It's okay.
Thank you very much.
There is a rumor in my class.
Hama-chan is Charlie Hama's son.
Matcha grew up in the jungle of Africa.
Are you Charlie Hama's son?
What?
Charlie Hama.
This is hard.
There are many.
It's true that I grew up in the jungle.
Let's do it.
Bring it on.
How many doors do you have?
Not many.
It's true that I grew up in the jungle.
Who raised you?
What?
Flamingo.
Are you okay with that?
Flamingo raised me.
Why were you in Africa when you were little?
Good question.
Can you do it?
Yes.
One day, I went to Africa to play.
It's true.
Even now, there is a place called flamingo.
When you shake your head, it's flamingo.
What?
Flamingo...
You're slow.
That's not good.
Don't step on it.
The staff of Flamingo are scary.
Is that so?
When we were in Africa, they were smiling and laughing.
The staff of Flamingo were playing tag.
They thought we were just like bugs.
But if we waited for them to see us, they would call us stupid.
If we screamed, they would say, shut up, you idiot.
The only thing we're not afraid of is Team Zero's lines.
Why are you clapping?
You should stop making fun of the audience.
You say that, too.
I don't make fun of them.
Don't talk.
You say that, too.
I don't say that.
You do.
Have you ever heard of it?
Yes, I've heard of it.
You're a fool.
Hey!
That's not good.
Next is Ikki.
One more.
One more?
I'm tired.
Good evening.
I can't say good evening.
You can't usually say that.
It's an old saying.
Machan, Hama, good evening.
Say it.
Good evening.
Machan, Hama, good evening.
The set behind you has changed.
That's right.
I've been wondering about it.
While Machan and Hama are talking,
when the set on the right side is shown,
you can see something like a person's face.
That's written on the set.
I don't like that way of reading.
It says, I'm laughing a little.
It's here. It's in this picture.
It's true. It's in this picture.
If it's in a figure, it's in this picture.
Isn't it this?
It's in this picture.
It's a little funny.
It's around here.
Can't you see it from far away?
Can you see it from far away?
It's you!
No, no.
It's true.
Why are you laughing?
What should I do? It's difficult to laugh a little.
It's a little funny.
Is that so?
It's nothing.
It's nothing?
Yes.
Let's go home.
There's nothing else.
It's true.
What are you doing?
We're standing on the stage like this,
and we're talking like this.
I don't know if it's easy to talk,
but we don't talk for that long.
So I'm nervous.
Standing on the stage and being watched by everyone,
I'm very nervous.
You have some room.
This part is delicious.
I just put it in my pocket.
There's a cigarette.
That's it!
Let's go because I'm nervous.
That's all.
I want to talk more.
I'll talk.
I'll do this.
I'm going home.
I can't go home again.
That's true.
But...
That's it.
I've been smoking a lot lately.
About manga 1.
If manga 1 becomes like this,
I'll be in trouble.
The old lady.
Right?
The worried old lady.
If this happens, what should I do?
The old lady.
It's called Yoshinba.
What?
Didn't you think of this?
I'm not so confident.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Hello.
What are you doing?
I'm talking.
If you don't talk, it's annoying.
That's right.
It's strange.
It's the ending.
Yes.
I'm an assistant.
Why don't you ask the staff to find a girlfriend?
Who's your girlfriend?
Yanaoka.
That's it.
Your girlfriend.
Takasu?
What do you think of Takasu?
Takasu.
You're calling me Michan.
Michan.
What?
Takasu is Michan.
That's good.
It's like the program has changed.
And then there's the power man number two.
I met him on TV.
That's good.
That's it.
Goodbye.
Good job.
Please give me a hug.
What's wrong with you?
Please lend me your T-shirt.
That's funny.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.