Good evening.
What are you thinking about?
Debayashi seems to be in a rush to do something.
I told you from the start!
I told you to change it over and over again!
I've been thinking about it for the past three weeks.
That's too late.
It's hard to come up with something.
Let's really stop.
Let's do an impersonation of Keisuke Kuwata.
Wait a minute.
What?
Actually, everyone does an impersonation of Keisuke Kuwata, right?
I've seen a lot of Keisuke Kuwata, but I think I'm the most complete.
Keisuke Kuwata?
When it comes to me, I can impersonate Keisuke Kuwata in 10 different ways.
You don't have to do 10 different things.
Show me the best one.
I can't show you the best one.
There are about 4 Keisuke Kuwata impersonations in the world.
You don't have to show me that.
Show me 10.
What is it?
Tsunami.
What was Tsunami like?
I don't know.
You can do an impersonation.
What was Tsunami like?
10 different things.
Don't be shy.
You can't just step on poop.
You can only step on poop today.
Stop it.
What was Tsunami like?
There's something like this.
I'm lost in the wind.
The next one is easier to impersonate.
Have you ever done that song?
I have.
Do it.
I just remembered.
What's the next one?
Why are there so many?
Did that song sell so well?
I don't know.
Stop it.
What was it?
I don't know.
I'm lost in the wind.
Your T-shirt is dirty.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
I'm lost in the wind.
That's right.
I'm weak.
I'm lost in the wind.
I don't know.
I heard that.
I'm frustrated.
I don't know that much.
You don't know everything?
I don't know everything.
Later.
Why don't you know anything?
What?
I was curious.
I'm lost in the wind.
I'm weak.
That's the next problem.
I don't know that.
I'm frustrated.
What is it?
I'm lost in the wind.
I'm weak.
That's it.
But you don't laugh.
I thought it would be like this.
Was I that big?
You were big.
Later.
Wait.
It's finally coming out.
Can you do it with this?
Let's do it with 3.
Please.
With 3.
Actually it's more than what it looks like.
That's it.
No, no, no.
Even if you do it 10 steps.
No matter how many steps you do.
It's not that big.
3 is like this.
It's 3.
It's 3 out of 10.
You're always throwing it the wrong way.
But now everyone should have seen the belly button.
Don't do 10. Do 6.
6 is a lot.
Do you want me to raise it?
No.
Come closer.
It hurts.
No, no, no.
6 means there are only 7, 8 and 9 left.
Until 10.
There are only 3 left.
You're trying really hard.
It's still like this.
I'm trying really hard.
Then do 7.
You haven't changed.
I haven't.
7.
That was 7.
8.
8, 8.
Now it's finally 9 out of 10.
Right?
9.
You have a lot of power.
I have a lot of power.
I was looking at it from a distance.
Then it's 9.
Now everyone is like,
Oh, it's true.
It's true.
It's not true.
That's what you think, right?
Yes, I understand.
You're going to do 10.
Yes.
I'm sorry, but it's finally time to judge.
Yes, 10.
Listen with all your heart.
I'll listen with all my heart.
Listen as if you've become Keisuke Kuwata.
Who?
The listener too.
The listener?
And all 10 of you will sing together.
If everyone sings, I can't hear it.
Is it similar or not?
Let me check.
It's hard for me to get that kind of reaction with 9.
That's because everyone thinks it's similar.
If you listen to 10 and think,
Everyone stand up and clap.
You ran away just now, didn't you?
You didn't run away, did you?
I don't know.
Why are you acting like a gorilla?
Say that.
I don't mean to be like a gorilla.
I can't say that.
I'm sorry.
I thought you were like a gorilla.
Don't mind me.
I'm sorry.
I just heard it a little.
You look like a gorilla.
Why don't you talk?
I'm not motivated.
I couldn't get motivated at all.
I just heard it like that.
I made a mistake too.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Don't say that.
If you say that, I really don't know why I'm wearing a y-shirt.
I'm wearing a y-shirt because I don't want to look like a gorilla.
That's right.
Because if I don't wear a y-shirt, I'll look like a gorilla.
I don't want to be just a gorilla.
I'm not saying I'm a gorilla, I'm saying I'm a gorilla.
I don't know how long ago I heard you saying you're a gorilla.
I couldn't make a mistake.
I'm a gorilla.
Did you hear that?
You're not saying you're a gorilla, are you?
I'm not a gorilla.
No, I'm a gorilla.
Stop it!
You're a gorilla!
If that's what you're saying, then I'm a gorilla.
I'm a gorilla.
That's good.
It's good, right?
I'm sorry, but you can do whatever you want.
It's just my nasal voice.
I see.
It's not as loud as usual.
What?
Nothing.
I'm sorry, but you can do whatever you want.
I'm not a gorilla.
My voice is coming out.
I'm sorry.
It's not like that.
My voice isn't coming out?
You said you're not a gorilla.
I just admitted that I'm a gorilla.
Then what am I?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm a gorilla.
It's coming out!
I'm sorry, but you can do whatever you want.
Is Keisuke Kuwata the gorilla version?
If Keisuke Kuwata is the gorilla version...
I think that's enough.
You've done a lot, haven't you?
I've done a lot?
What is this?
What is this conversation?
It's my stress release.
I've done a lot, haven't I?
If I can do it, I'll do it at home.
If I can do it, I'll do it at work.
It's like everyone's gathered because of my selfishness.
I've done a lot, haven't I?
Why? You came out and didn't say anything, but you said you'd do it.
I said it.
I want to make everyone proud.
It's cold this year, even though I've been told many times.
Even though I've been told many times.
What is a gorilla?
It's not even a gorilla.
Who's aiming for a gorilla?
What are you talking about?
It's the same as trying to be a human being.
Who's trying to be on the gorilla side?
It's the opposite.
I don't understand what you're saying.
That's enough.
I have something I have to decide today.
That's right.
Hey, come here.
Thank you.
As I said before, we're going to have a rematch.
Wait a minute. Why is everyone...
That's the key.
It's the Hamada side.
Why are you getting more and more confused?
In the previous penalty game, the four of us are really stuck.
What?
Yes?
I spoke properly.
We're stuck in the previous penalty game.
Oh, you're stuck.
I'm stressed out.
What are you doing?
As I said the other day, it's a swimming competition.
The staff is simulating it.
I'm thinking about this version.
Let's watch the video.
Are you sure?
Yes.
He's still a swimmer.
Wow.
He's good at swimming.
That's cool.
He's like a kamasaka.
The first swimmer is Hirao, 50 meters.
The Hamada team swam 12.5 meters.
Matsumoto swam 50 meters.
I just did this.
This is a touch.
If you swim 12.5 meters, you'll be the next swimmer.
12.5 meters?
Yes.
There are four of you.
I can't speed up.
That's right.
If you stop once...
It's completely different.
This is a touch, right?
This is bad.
This is impossible.
But you're still swimming.
Yes.
You're getting slower.
Who is this?
I don't know.
I lost.
Matsumoto won.
The next swimmer is Kurool, 50 meters.
The Hamada team swam 12.5 meters.
This is a touch.
Get ready.
I'm not good at swimming.
I can't swim.
This is impossible.
You're getting faster.
The Hamada team won the race.
The last swimmer is Kurool, 50 meters.
This time, they will use the swimming cap as a baton.
This is a baton.
This is impossible.
The swimming cap lost a lot of time, and Matsumoto won the race.
Why did I get this?
This is a strange story.
I see.
I noticed something that no one noticed.
What is it?
First of all, if it's not a 50-meter pool, it's no good.
If it's a pool, it's no good.
The opponent will turn, so it's a big loss.
So the three of them will swim in the middle of the pool.
And the one who can kick will win.
And the hat is too heavy.
But the baton is good.
What?
No, no, no.
I don't think so.
The baton is good.
The baton is impossible.
Let me say it again.
The baton is good.
The baton is impossible.
But Matsumoto won the race, didn't he?
Yes, yes, yes.
No, no, no.
Why?
I don't have any proof.
I touched the baton, and he said,
No, no, no.
But Matsumoto won the race, and he said,
I don't have any proof.
I touched the baton, and he said,
I found out where you were going.
All of you are Japanese.
Japanese?
So how do we play?
I'm going to…
We're going to compete, right?
To compete.
The free or free, right?
No, no, we're going to compete.
Yes, right.
So it's a kind of
We're going to compete.
Dark roll.
And the free one is dark roll.
Yes, and that's the best,
Nice.
It's dark roll.
But what if I say I can't do dark roll?
But what if I say I can't crawl?
What?
You can't crawl?
Not that I can't, but I've never really thought about crawling.
We haven't thought about it either.
When I watch TV, I'm focused on the TV.
We're the same.
When we're eating, we're focused on the food.
No, that's not it.
He's the one who suggested the swimming competition.
That's right.
Hmm...
Well, even if you say that...
The one who suggested the swimming competition was Gorilla.
You didn't say Gorilla.
That's right.
Well, that's fine.
I only know one thing.
What?
I can't jump into the water.
You can jump from below.
Stand up.
You can't jump into the water?
I can't jump into the water.
But I can't do that either.
You can't jump into the water?
Then you can jump from below.
You can jump from below.
But that's not good.
That's right.
The pool is 50 meters.
50?
It's not 25 meters.
If it's not 50 meters, it's hard to understand.
What about the memo?
The memo is fine.
Miso.
You don't have to write it.
You don't use it, right?
What do you use?
I don't use it.
Gorilla.
I want to write Gorilla.
Please write it.
I don't use it.
What do you use?
I don't forget.
I don't forget today's return.
I see.
It's okay.
It's not related to the competition.
So
If you look at the part,
I divided it into four parts.
50 meters.
Why didn't you say that?
What is this bitter feeling?
Everyone will swim evenly.
12.5 meters.
Can I decide the order?
No, you can't.
Why?
Bitter.
I want to do it in the previous order.
It's a revenge.
That's right.
I want to hit Mr. Matsumoto at the start.
Let's do it.
You lost last time, right?
I lost.
I'll do my best.
Tanaka.
Endo and my baton.
I lost last time.
I lost.
Let's go with this.
There is no point in winning with this.
When is the game?
Next week.
It's coming.
It's a punishment game.
It's a punishment.
It's a punishment that I will never forget.
But
After the game,
I think about whether there is a punishment or not.
There is a punishment.
Why did you get a punishment?
It's coming.
Stop it.
Why are we running?
It just happened.
It's not just a coincidence.
It's a taboo.
What are you talking about?
It was like that at the time.
No, no.
I'll do my best.
I'll be like, which one did I win?
Next week.
Without batons?
Without batons.
I'm begging you.
I can't do that.
Drink the water.
If you drink it...
Where?
Okay.
Next week.
Revenge.
The first match of the 21st century.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.