Ladies and gentlemen.
Good evening.
I went to Sendai.
In the New Year.
When I went to Sendai, it snowed a lot that night.
Kim, Itao and the three of us.
We didn't think it was that cold, so the three of us wore slippers.
We didn't buy cigarettes.
When we arrived, it was normal in Sendai.
Everyone was walking around in slippers.
It snowed a lot at night.
When I went to eat and went out of the hotel, it snowed a lot.
The three of us.
We couldn't walk like this.
The three of us had to walk vertically from top to bottom.
Up and down.
We had to walk up and down.
We couldn't move.
We had to stand a little.
It would be nice if we could walk like this.
No, no, no.
You don't want to buy shoes on a trip, do you?
Even in the summer.
I thought I forgot to say Beach Zori.
No, it's Beach Zori.
Wait a minute.
Wait, wait.
It's Beach Zori.
I don't know.
I don't want to go to the beach with you.
I'm going to take you home.
It's the same thing.
It was hard.
We were in most hotels.
I watched TV on New Year's Eve.
Was it fun?
Everyone is funny now.
Everyone is funny.
But the funniest person is...
The funniest person is...
Kubota Toshinobu.
What commercial?
That's amazing.
I can't take off one or two lines.
I think I took off red and yellow.
It's just white.
Half and half.
Are you singing?
I'm surprised.
Let's go.
5, 4, 3.
Half and half.
He can't do it.
If he did it, it would be cold.
It's cold.
I think the staff around him would say,
I think so.
He doesn't think it's cold.
If he's cold, it's getting colder and colder.
It's getting cold.
You have to get in.
I think I was in the dressing room for about 30 minutes.
I tried not to move my head.
If I moved my head, I would fall.
I was told,
Half and half.
Don't be mean.
When I first saw it, I thought it was cold.
I thought it was stupid.
No, no, no.
He's doing a good job.
I'm going to tell you a little bit.
The most annoying thing in the commercial is,
I think it's Suzuki Ganran.
Ishiya.
It's not that bad up to here.
Ishiya, half and half.
It's okay here, too.
It's sold out.
It's here.
It's useless.
There's a nut for the locker.
The one that tightens it like this.
The screw is like this.
If you do this,
That's what you want to do.
I've never written it down.
I'm so pissed off.
I haven't even played with you.
I can't help but look at you when you're so pissed off.
Well, I don't think so.
I'm so pissed off.
You know, there are a lot of talented people...
Umm...
What?
When I'm told that I live here, I'm so pissed off.
Why?
Of course I am!
Why haven't you moved to Osaka yet?
Who told you that?
I'm so pissed off.
You know, I'm so pissed off.
I'm not pissed off!
Well, I don't think you're a Tokyo talent.
You're so twisted!
I'm so pissed off.
You know, it's like asking if I'm still in the theater.
This is the end of the story.
What?
You have been able to make a lot of predictions, like the lack of glasses, the rise of the meteor, and the suspension of the volcano.
That's right.
The year 1997 has started, but let's hear your predictions for this year.
It's getting older every year.
But the genre is...
I think it's better for everyone to listen and be interested.
Yes, yes, yes.
About the entertainment world.
By the way, I was talking about the entertainment world and it was exciting.
There are a lot of entertainers, right?
Everyone wants to be a couple.
Who is left?
I see.
I'm probably Maeda Bivalia.
I don't know what Maeda Bivalia is doing.
Everyone is holding hands and sitting down.
It can't be helped. I'll sit down and connect with you.
I'll go to the party.
Who will go to the party?
I'm sure I'll be the same as Maeda Bivalia.
It's strange to be Maeda Bivalia.
Everyone else is Baer, right?
There are a lot of people who say that.
They say it's interesting.
They come to see us.
Surprisingly, Kai-san is the only one who doesn't know what to do.
Kai Yoshihiro is the only one who doesn't know what to do.
The other day, Komoro-san made a song and we all sang it together.
Kai-san was in it, right?
Kai-san was in it.
Kai-san is in it, right?
He's in it.
Kai-san will never break his back.
He's running around.
He's running around a lot.
I was the last one to go to the toilet.
I was the last one to go to the toilet after everyone's song.
Please let me hear it.
The one that everyone is connected to.
It's okay.
Someone was singing my part.
I was listening to it.
Huh?
Is this Kai-san?
That's right.
Yeah!
I think it's similar.
I've seen a lot of shows like this.
Kai-san!
No!
Kai-san is an interesting person.
I think Kai-san will never break his back.
I think he'll die.
But I can't help it.
In the end, he's like Yuki-san's older sister.
What are you doing?
That's what he said.
I'm an entertainer.
Everyone can be surprised.
Can I say this?
Did you know about Seiko-chan the other day?
I knew.
That's why I said it last year.
You didn't say it!
What are you talking about?
Who's getting a divorce?
Huh?
Divorce?
What?
What's the point of getting a divorce in the entertainment world?
Divorce is...
It's unpleasant, isn't it?
It's the first time I've seen it.
Hey, don't speed up!
I have a question for Matsumoto-san.
Matsumoto-san used to be on the ranger stage.
Please tell us Matsumoto-san's performance on that stage.
You're the one who got off the helicopter.
I got off the helicopter and shot like this.
Where did you do that?
Over there.
You know, right?
Where did you do that?
What?
Afghan.
Afghan?
What the hell are you talking about?
Why are you talking about Afghanistan?
I was told to sing and dance in Afghan.
You even sang.
At night.
At karaoke.
Please tell us Matsumoto-san's performance.
There were a lot of things.
I was often asked to help people.
I have 8 licenses.
Please tell us.
If I don't have 8 licenses, I won't be able to join the special forces.
First of all, I have a normal license.
That's right.
If I have a normal license, I can ride a motorcycle.
You can ride a motorcycle.
I have two.
You don't have to be on the ranger stage.
Why?
If you ask me to bring you something, I'll take a motorcycle.
You don't have to be on the ranger stage at a time like this, do you?
I don't mind.
I also have a boiler.
What?
A boiler.
I see.
I'm a boiler man.
A boiler.
That's it.
You still have more.
I have 8 licenses.
I still have more.
What is it?
Next to the boiler.
Welding.
This is the brand of the tank.
That's your job, isn't it?
I have to bring it to someone and do it.
You don't have to tell me how to do it.
This is like this.
There are times when this is broken.
I don't think you know.
I don't know.
Welding.
I also have a kind license.
I'll try to save you once.
You don't have a kind license.
This was the most difficult for me.
Really.
Because there was a technique.
Kind license.
What do you do?
I gave a balloon to a child.
I saw the instructor all the way.
Please tell me how to do it.
That's not the point.
There's not a lot of fighting going on.
Oh, I see.
More than that, for example, the oil leak in the tanker caused a lot of trouble.
I went to help Anna.
I see.
There were a lot of activities like that.
The most memorable thing for me was the night in Yamaguchi.
What was the situation like?
What?
I was floating on a helicopter.
Floating?
Yes, I was floating.
Oh, I see.
You were floating on a helicopter.
You were flying, weren't you?
Yes, I was.
I see.
I was flying.
Bambi was in the valley.
What?
On the valley floor.
Which way?
On the valley floor or on the valley floor?
On the valley floor?
Yes, there was a rabbit on the valley floor.
Bambi was there?
Yes, Bambi was there.
Bambi was there.
Bambi was flying like this.
He wasn't born yet, was he?
Oh, I see.
I said, Bambi!
I said, I found Bambi!
I said, Matsumoto, do it for me!
That's what I said.
You were the only one there.
So I steered the car automatically.
We steered the car automatically,
so we Sharped the helicopter.
Otherwise I had
I don't know. I don't know how to do it.
When I go like this, I can touch the head.
I want to grab it, but I can only touch the head like this.
That's the limit.
I shake it like this.
I forgot.
No, no, no.
I go like this.
I shake it like this.
No, no, no.