The day before the accident
If it's 10, it's not good
I think it's about 20
It's not good
This is about one
Two
Let's go one more
If you die of the accident
You will retire
If it's like this
If it got trapped
Like these
Then it can't survive
This is the reason
Is it?
It's OK.
If it's too much, it'll be fine.
I'll do it like this.
Will it come off?
No, it's OK.
Can you do it with one piece of rice?
Is the amount of gunpowder the same as the one you boiled yesterday?
It's OK.
Not the exact amount.
Just do it as you said.
It's OK if you get hurt a little.
But if you don't be careful, it's dangerous.
I'm counting on you.
It's better if you say it quickly.
Let's go.
Open it.
Let's meet again.
It's OK.
Let's close the lid.
There's no water.
Pull it.
Are you OK?
It's OK.
You have to close it.
I'll close it again.
You have to close it, too.
What are you doing?
It's OK.
Are you OK?
You can do it, right?
It's OK.
Let's go.
Are you OK?
Yes.
Are you ready?
Are you OK?
Yes.
Let's go.
Are you OK?
Yes.
Are you ready?
Start.
That was...
I felt bad.
I'm in trouble.
Don't do that.
Look at me.
It's about you.
I'll look at you.
Don't do that.
Hey!
There was a lot of gunpowder.
I'll go.
Are you OK?
Is this the place?
That sound is not funny.
It's not here.
Where is it?
There it is.
Are you OK?
Hey!
It was a success.
I'm glad.
I'm moved.
You can stop now.
What are you looking at?
Do you have any ideas?
What are you going to do?
It's simple.
I'm going to do it once a day.
I don't think that's going to come out of your mouth.
You have to say thank you and good morning.
You!
You've never said thank you properly.
Don't stab my neck.
You say it.
Do you have a college entrance exam this year?
What are you talking about?
Are you serious?
Do you want to pass?
I'll pass.
I can't.
People who watch TV think I'm crazy.
I think so too.
I'm a normal person.
I have to teach them that I'm a normal person.
I'll do it when I have to.
It's different from normal to school.
If you have common sense...
What do you mean by common sense?
If you have common sense, you can show your face.
If you don't have common sense, you can't say thank you properly.
I never say that.
You never say that.
You always say that when you enter the scene.
What?
You always say that.
I never say that.
Hey, get the staff together.
With the glasses on.
I don't need glasses.
I don't say that when I greet.
I'll do it with this tone.
You don't say that.
You don't say that?
I always say that.
When people are talking in the dressing room, you'll come in and say,
I don't know.
Seriously.
I always say that.
You don't say that.
Why don't you try it when you come home in the morning?
Good morning.
Shut up!
What are you doing?
What is this?
Have you ever properly greeted me like this?
You are the one who doesn't greet.
Don't say such stupid things.
You can't say thank you at all.
I said thank you!
Thank you.
What are you saying?
What are you doing?
I'm not in the mood.
I said thank you.
You can't say that.
I said it, you idiot.
You!
You said you would bring me a cup of tea.
You are making a face like it's nothing.
It's true.
You can't do it.
Let me say it.
Thank you.
You can't say that.
You can't say such stupid things.
I said it.
I said thank you to him.
I always say thank you.
You are making a face.
I always say thank you to him.
You can't say that.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
It's true.
You should have said it.
You go to many places and work.
From now on, both of you should be polite.
Let's do that.
I will do as usual.
You don't say hello to me.
Why should I say hello to you?
I don't know.
I don't say anything.
You don't say hello to me.
I do.
Good morning, Hama-chan.
Say it.
Hey, get the staff together.
I don't know anything about you.
I can't hear you saying good morning, Hama-chan.
I'm a little shy.
But I can't say it.
You should say it out loud.
I don't understand.
I can't communicate with you.
Even if you do it behind my back.
Please.
I won't say it.
If you don't say it, I'll fine you.
OK.
How much do you want?
10,000 yen.
What?
OK.
10,000 yen for one time.
Really?
Really.
Are you serious?
Yes.
I'll earn a lot of money.
But you can't take that money.
What?
Where are you going with that money?
I won't give it to you.
I'll save it for when I do something on this show.
My money will support this show?
You'll be surprised if I say I'll support it.
That's not true.
I said it on this show.
What?
If I do it properly, I won't be angry.
Why are you saying that?
What are you talking about?
If I do it properly, I won't be angry.
What?
You should do the same.
Don't hit my head.
If you hit my head, I'll give you 500,000 yen.
I'm really worried about you.
When I went to the zoo with my dad,
when I went to Awaji Island with my family,
when I took my mom to the park,
I can't remember any of them.
What are you talking about?
Say it quickly.
What did I say at the beginning?
I remember something, but I don't remember it anymore.
I can't remember anything.
You're crazy.
So please stop it.
You can't do it.
I'm just saying it.
You're right.
It's okay.
You know what?
Kids cry.
What?
Are you talking about that?
No, no, no.
I'm talking about you.
I haven't hit you yet.
Really? Why?
Did you start talking?
It's funny that you said it hurts when I hit you.
I don't think so.
It's a little sad that my child speaks standard Japanese.
That's right.
Children speak Osaka dialect.
Right?
If I say that my child doesn't know,
it's not very cute, right?
If I say I don't know,
he'll hug me like this.
Child.
It's not that bad.
I don't know.
Well, standard Japanese is a little hard.
It's hard, right?
That's why I think you're a little lonely.
Your Osaka dialect is especially dirty, right?
It's sticky.
I still speak Osaka dialect that is close to standard Japanese.
Are you stupid?
That's not true. I often get angry, right?
Yes.
That's why when I speak in a normal way,
it's normal.
It's the same.
Your dialect and my dialect.
No, it's totally different.
It's not different.
It's totally different.
It's the same.
It's not different.
I'm telling you it's different.
This is the strange thing.
It's different as a receiver.
Who says that?
Everyone says that.
I don't say that. It's the same.
It's totally the same.
Try to get angry.
Idiot!
I'll tear you apart!
I won't say that.
I'll say, hey!
Hey!
It's different!
You say, hey!
I'll tear you apart!
I just wanted to say that.
I'm serious.
Why?
I don't want my family to be like that.
But I don't want it to be between Osaka dialect and Hyojin dialect.
It happens sometimes.
It happens.
People say sa recently.
I'm not aware of that.
I didn't like this sa when I came to Tokyo.
These guys say sa, sa, sa, sa.
Hey, I'm sa.
I'm tired.
When you're tired, you don't say sa.
When you're tired, you say, I'm tired.
I don't hear that often.
That's why I say sa recently.
I don't really feel that sa.
Why?
I don't really hear that sa, sa, sa, sa.
That's why I say sa.
Your reaction just now...
I was going to go next, but I stopped for a second.
I've never heard you say sa, sa, sa, sa.
I'm the one who's letting you go.
I'm surprised.
I should go.
You shouldn't change.
You're talking in Hyojin dialect because you feel bad.
I can use it.
Why?
I can't say it at all.
I can use it.
I'm from Tokyo.
You're from Thailand.
What?
Hyojin dialect.
Oh, really?
This is good.
No.
What?
This is a good suit.
Yeah.
Your hair is natural.
It's cool.
Yeah.
What do you think?
Speak!
I can't speak.
No, but what?
What?
So what?
I think all living things are useful in their own way.
For example, a cicada eats dirt and cleanses it.
A sparrow eats a cockroach.
But what I don't understand is a beetle.
Why would a beetle wear such a hard shell?
This is it.
A beetle.
But I think that a beetle is born to suppress a beetle.
What do you mean by suppress?
If a beetle doesn't break, it becomes a beetle's world.
That's fine.
It doesn't break, it becomes a world.
You!
Is it okay for you to become a beetle's world?
It doesn't matter.
A beetle is making me sick.
When I went to the dressing room, it was written that you are a beetle.
I'm alone.
If there are a few regular people in the program, a beetle will definitely be in it.
If the beetle is late, the beetle is waiting.
I don't know what to do.
I don't have time.
I'm sorry.
The beetle is waiting.
If the beetle is late, the beetle will come.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
If you have something to complain about, say it.
It's hard.
It's you.
Shinjuku is a world of beetles.
There is also a beetle yakuza.
If that's the case, I don't wear sleeves.
I don't wear sleeves.
If it's a beetle, I don't wear sleeves.
Do you know that?
Of course.
It's hard.
It's a bear's hand.
Of course.
It's hard.
If it's a beetle, it's a big deal.
I don't wear sleeves.
If that's the case, I don't wear sleeves.
That's why the beetle is holding me down.
Thanks to the beetle, we...
You noticed it.
Did you talk?
I see.
I have a question for you.
Why do heroes like the Kiranger have their nipples?
The Kiranger.
Leave it to the Kiranger.
I love curry rice.
The Kiranger is joking.
It's really funny.
Why?
It has a face of a locomotive.
No matter how you look at it, it's just a leotard.
It comes out.
The Kiranger has a big heart.
It's a one-shot.
I really laughed.
It can't be defeated.
The Red Ranger can't be defeated.
It has a really strong mask.
The Red Ranger goes like this.
The Red Ranger trains a lot.
I want to win somehow.
Until I meet it.
Commander Edgar.
The old man who has a lot of Gorangers.
He tells the old man to drop a rock.
And then he goes like this.
He trains a lot.
He's good.
He tries again.
He loses again.
There's no time.
It's almost over.
It's not over.
What will happen?
Commander Edgar says,
This is the only thing I have.
He opens it horizontally.
The Goranger.
He opens it quickly.
And he gives it a memory.
It doubles the power.
It has a memory from 1 to 5.
Until now, it was 2.
Now it's 5.
And then?
What happened to the rock?
The old man dropped it on purpose.
I was surprised.
It's a Kamen Rider Musasabi.
It has wings.
It's Musasabi.
It flies like this.
And it says,
Kamen Rider, let's meet again.
It has a crown.