Well, today, I was watching a comic book.
Oh, you're going to give up.
Why?
Because I didn't go yesterday.
Did you catch a cold?
Yes, I caught a cold.
Why didn't you stay in your seat?
I couldn't talk because I was in my seat.
I see.
Don't do that.
So, this program started on October 3, 2006.
Is that including the New Year's Day?
That's right.
What you're going to see today is the children's phone call room on November 28, 2006.
You've been doing it all the time, haven't you?
Yes.
But there's no more content.
This is the last episode of the comic book.
That's right.
Most of our content is gone.
It's gone.
On the way here, you said,
What should I do?
On the way here, I came here without thinking.
I came here and explained to Hamada how to do it.
We did it together in the dressing room.
We did it together once or twice.
But it was a mess.
You're really a genius.
What is it?
You can do it right away in the comic book.
You're the greatest comedian of this century.
There's no doubt about it.
Shut up.
This is the last story.
I've done it anywhere.
I've done it for the first time.
I've only done it once.
I'll never do it again.
People who watch TV will say,
Why don't you do it when you've done it so many times?
Why did you do it so many times?
Why don't you do it?
I'm lying.
I'm not lying.
I'm grateful for your good reputation.
I don't usually appear on TV these days.
It's not a very interesting TV.
It's on the movie now.
I'm more interested in the radio.
I talk to children on the radio during the day.
I talk to children.
I can't hear it.
I can't understand anything my family told me.
I talked with my parents.
They can't hear it.
It's hard to understand.
Let me call my friend.
Hello.
Yes.
meter
I'm looking for you on the phone.
That's what I hear sometimes.
Yes.
Hello.
Last Sunday morning,
Hello?
It's late!
You are too late to talk to the child.
Hello?
You are too early to talk to the child.
Don't come to that place.
Hello?
This is Mr. Hamada, the child telephone counselor.
What's your name?
I'm Matsumoto.
Oh, you're Matsumoto. What's your name?
Sato.
Oh, you're Sato.
What's your name?
I'm Matsumoto.
Oh, you're Matsumoto?
Matsumoto?
What's your name?
Sato.
Sato?
Yes.
Matsumoto?
Where's Sato?
Yes.
What's your name?
Sato Matsumoto.
Your name is Sato?
Yes.
This is strange.
You have to think of me.
I'm sorry.
Why didn't you say Sato?
Hello?
What's wrong?
I have something to ask you.
That's why you called me.
You know...
I'm not interested in Buddhism.
What?
Why are you interested in children?
I don't care if you're not interested in Buddhism or not.
I want to ask you something childish.
What?
I'm not interested in Buddhism.
Why are you worried about me?
I want to know more about you.
Something childish.
Hello?
Lately,
I've been thinking about what to eat.
I want to eat squid.
What should I eat?
Ask your mother.
Don't call me all the time.
If you call me,
I'll hit you.
If you want to say something,
say it.
I'm sorry.
You should ask your mother.
I want to ask something childish.
Why is a giraffe's neck so long?
That's a good question.
It's my first time.
Say it again.
Why is a giraffe's neck so long?
This is...
It's not a neck.
Don't call me a giraffe.
I don't want to call you a giraffe.
A giraffe's neck is
very
relaxing.
That's why
I can't wait for a snack at 3 o'clock
and I have to wait for a long time.
Really?
Yes.
Who is a turtle?
Who is a bear?
I'm not anybody.
I am a bear.
It's not you.
A turtle is tomorrow.
What?
A snake is beautiful.
A bear is...
A gorilla is...
What's wrong with you?
That's how it is with children, isn't it?
How can it be like that?
Zote!
Isn't that stupid?
If you say such a complicated thing, I'll be in trouble.
I'm a child this time.
You're a brother.
Hello?
I'd like to ask you something.
What do you want to ask?
Harry!
How can you answer when you come out?
Brother!
No one calls you at such a place.
Brother?
Say it.
Hello?
I'd like to ask you something.
You're a child, aren't you?
That's how it is with children.
I'd like to ask you something.
How can you answer when you come out?
Come out properly.
I feel sorry for you.
How can you answer when you come out?
Hello?
I'd like to ask you something.
What is it?
I'll say it again.
This is the children's phone call room.
I'm Matsumoto's sister.
I'm Matsumoto's brother.
I'd like to ask you something.
What is it?
I'm sorry. I'm in a catch-on.
Why?
I'm not waiting for a child in the call room.
I'm sorry.
Hello?
I'd like to ask you something.
How can you give birth to a baby?
How do you give birth to a baby?
How do you say how?
What do you mean by the dog is like a child?
Think about the way you say it!
You are raising a child and you say,
Hey, the dog is like a child.
You'd better say it without looking back.
You are asking something childish.
Childish?
Childish.
Hello? What's the matter?
Hello, brother.
Well...
I have something to ask you.
Why do dogs bark?
That's a great question, isn't it?
Is it a great question?
Mr.Uni is very tired.
I see.
Why do dogs bark?
This is a very difficult question.
Is that so?
So, Mr.Uni, I'll check it out.
Don't hang up the phone. Wait.
I'm sorry.
I'll be out soon.
Don't hang up the phone.
Hello, do you understand?
Hurry up.
This is a very difficult question.
Can you wait a little longer?
I'm sorry.
I'll be out soon.
Can you wait a little longer?
Don't hang up the phone.
Well, I've seen the manga.
I'm doing it.
It's great, isn't it?
I'm doing the manga.
I don't recommend you to watch my manga.
Is that so?
Because I think you'll lose your confidence.
What are you talking about?
I can't show you the finished work.
Don't lose your confidence.
We're from a different world.
Really.
This is the last manga.
Next, the storyboard.
I've been doing this for a long time.
Rolling Thunder Man.
This is the first time we've ever tried a storyboard.
We've been doing it as a talking storyboard.
Let's do a storyboard.
This is the first storyboard.
I like it a lot.
Rolling Thunder Man.
I like it a lot, but I can't do it every time.
I can't do it.
I can't do it every time.
Did you do it on the spot?
I've done it a few times on the spot.
But I couldn't do it on the spot.
On top of that, I couldn't do it on the spot.
I feel lonely being alone.
Thank you.
Mister.
Who are you?
I'm Rolling Thunder Man from M36.
Rolling Thunder Man?
Yes.
I didn't know that.
I don't know if it's impossible on Earth.
Impossible?
What are you doing here?
I'm a Peggy Seijin.
Peggy Seijin?
Yes.
There's information that the evil Peggy Seijin is attacking Earth.
If we leave it like this, the people on Earth will get hit by Peggy Seijin or something.
Something?
That's why I came to protect this beautiful Earth.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Peggy Seijin is coming.
I don't know if Peggy Seijin is looking at you.
I can't do anything.
I'm still a kid.
That's right.
Be careful.
Thank you.
See you.
You're a strange man.
This is from Isojima.
It's so hard that it won't open.
Uncle.
Yes.
What is it?
It won't open.
What?
The Isojima lid.
It's Peggy Seijin's doing.
Really?
What a terrible thing.
I'm okay.
Thank you, uncle.
What a terrible thing.
It's not a matter of life and death.
What?
I'm tired from M36000.
I don't know that.
Be careful.
Thank you, uncle.
Yes.
Uncle.
What?
I'm scared of Peggy Seijin.
Be quiet.
Rolling Thunder Man Mimi.
It's not a matter of life and death.
Peggy Seijin is talking bad about you.
I didn't do anything.
It's not a matter of life and death.
I can hear that you're thinking about evil.
Really?
If you don't do anything, Peggy Seijin will pull your hair.
Do something, uncle.
I'm scared.
Where are you, Peggy Seijin?
Peggy Seijin.
Rolling Thunder Man.
It's not a matter of life and death.
I can hear that you're thinking about evil.
Peggy Seijin is talking bad about you.
What are you talking about?
What are you talking about, uncle?
If you don't do anything,
Rolling Thunder Man...
Are you thinking about it?
Yes.
What?
I have a good idea.
What is it?
Even if Peggy Seijin attacks us,
I'll defeat him with Rolling Thunder Man.
You can defeat him normally.
Then, will you live with me?
I live alone.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Please live with me, uncle.
Please.
Please live with me.
Yes.
Then, three years passed.
I'm home.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Why are you taking off your pants?
What?
What are you doing?
Don't do that when you're alone.
I'm not doing anything.
Something stinks.
What?
Clean up the room.
I feel sick recently.
You...
Aren't you on the side of justice?
What?
It's just the beginning.
Please live with me.
At the beginning...
What are you doing?
Why are you taking off your pants?
What?
Clean up the room.
I don't want to do that.
It's your job.
Don't touch me.
I've changed.
I was kind at the beginning.
Why were you kind?
You're angry because you didn't clean up the room.
You're not doing anything at home.
Do your job.
Stop it.
I hate you.
What?
Go home.
Where are you going?
What?
When will you stop calling me Peggy Seijin?
I told you three years ago.
Rolling Thunder Man.
It's about time.
When will you stop calling me Peggy Seijin?
It's been three years.
You lied to me.
That's not true.
You don't care about Peggy Seijin.
It's been three years.
What are you talking about?
I'm full of clothes.
Do your job.
What is this?
What is this shirt?
Why are you dressed up?
Rolling Thunder Man.
What is this?
Can you beat me?
I can't stand it anymore.
If there is only rice, this may be Rolling Thunder Man.
That's all for today.
It's been 30 minutes since we started.
People often ask me to do it.
It's fun.
How about doing it for an hour?
People often ask me to do it.
You have to do it for 30 minutes.
It's an hour-long program.
How about doing it for an hour?
I don't know.
It's rare to do this at this time.
Thank you very much.
We usually do a stock program.
We don't have it on this program.
I want to put out a stock program.
I'm not expecting anything.
It's a part of your health.
We have to do it for the content.
But we did the opening special.
We did the opening special.
We did the punishment game special.
It's nothing when it's done.
We should make it.
That pattern.
That's right.
And that one time is mine.
Hey, are you doing this on purpose?
You're the one who left it at the end, right?
Yes, yes, yes. This is my one time, so don't take it.
That's right, but if you don't use it soon, I might use it.
The reason why this is happening is that, the day before yesterday, we were shooting CX for two days.
We were quite tired of CX.
That's right.
This is gradually changing.
Is it CX?
I wonder if it's a conversation between CX and Nittere.
What kind of conversation is that?
Yes, that's right.
I wonder if it's a conversation between CX and Nittere.
That's right.