Tonight's Gaki no Tsukai will be played with the original game of Gainin Kouan!
The second half!
The original game that I thought of will be chosen!
Gaki no Tsukai
Let's go! Gainin-san, please!
Hello!
My name is Newton Ito!
Newton Ito?
Akita-chan!
It will definitely sell!
Thank you very much!
I don't know how to say it.
Newton Ito Kouan Game Tour with high tension gag!
I've been doing it for 25 years.
I've been doing it a lot.
I've done too many games, but I've done it all.
I thought it would be nice to combine two simple games.
It's weird if you say it's a gold medal.
But it's weird if you say it's a gold medal.
I've been doing it for a long time, so I'm getting used to it.
I want you to be more excited.
I see.
So, rather than a new game, I combined two existing ones.
That's exactly right.
Here's the game I brought today.
Hit it, wear it, look over there.
It's a board game.
You know both, right?
I tried to mix it.
First of all, hit it, wear it, look over there, and rock-paper-scissors.
If you win by rock-paper-scissors, look over there and do it.
If you look in the same direction as the basket, you get one point.
Up to this point, it's almost the same as the usual rules.
Look over there and do it in four directions.
It's a 75% chance that you can avoid it.
Then you can get a hammer chance by avoiding it.
If you hit it before you guard it, you'll get one point.
If you guard it, it's no count.
If you get three points, you'll be the winner.
If you ask me, I don't know.
It's supposed to be simple.
You have to try it.
I've fought a lot of young people before, but I've never lost.
Really?
I've won all of them.
It would be amazing if someone won today.
So I thought I'd get rid of five people.
That's good.
Five people will challenge MUTON Ito, who has never lost before.
Who will go first?
MUTON will decide.
First of all, Mr. Endo.
I'm really good at hitting and guarding.
That's why I want to beat Mr. Endo as soon as possible.
I see.
I'm ready.
One, two.
Hit and guard. Look over there.
Look over there.
One, two.
Hit and guard. Look over there.
Look over there.
What's that?
Endo?
What's going on?
What's wrong with you?
Don't run away from Mr. Takeshi.
Don't deceive me.
But isn't this one point?
It's still one point.
I got this point.
One, two.
Hit and guard. Look over there.
Look over there.
One, two.
Hit and guard. Look over there.
Look over there.
I see. I get it.
One, two.
Hit and guard. Look over there.
Look over there.
I lost.
Now it's two against one.
One, two.
Hit and guard. Look over there.
Look over there.
One, two.
Hit and guard. Look over there.
What?
That was great.
Why are you standing still?
Why?
I thought I was going to lose.
I felt it in slow motion.
It's hard.
I was stuck.
I'll explain it.
I'll do it in fighter mode.
Get ready.
I'm ready.
One, two.
Hit and guard. Look over there.
Look over there.
I got it.
This may be difficult.
I see.
Who's next?
Mr. Hosei.
Please.
Look over there.
I thought I was going to lose.
I had to defend right away.
That's right.
It changes from defense to attack.
It's interesting.
One, two.
Hit and guard. Look over there.
Look over there.
I'm sorry.
That's a lie.
You were already in the way.
I can't do this.
This is downtown.
I was already in the way.
You were already in the way.
I was just in the way.
I was surprised.
One, two.
Hit and guard. Look over there.
Look over there.
Look over here.
I lost.
What is this guy?
Leave me alone.
The drawer is empty.
Hit and guard. Look over there.
You are a weak person.
Please cover me.
At least take off your helmet.
I definitely will.
Please cover me.
Next is the challenge of TANAKA.
Look over there.
He lost.
MUTO and ITO of the three consecutive wins.
I will not lose.
If I win here, I won't have to do Hamada anymore.
Let's decide.
It's okay when you lose.
Please decide.
Thank you.
Hit and guard. Look over there.
I lost.
Didn't you say hit and guard?
That's right.
You don't have to say it.
I just didn't say it to you.
You don't get points.
I don't get points.
It's a waste.
Hit and guard. Look over there.
I lost.
1 to 1
Hit and guard. Look over there.
I lost.
It's over.
I've been playing rock-paper-scissors for a long time.
The last challenger of the Gaki team is Tomo.
Please take a picture of me.
This is like a beautiful picture.
A beautiful picture.
One, two, three.
Look over there.
I lost to the simple one.
First of all, I want to give you a break.
I thought it was the easiest one.
One, two, three.
Look over there.
The reaction is a little different.
The opponent is scared.
In a different sense.
Please do your best.
Save it.
Save it as much as you can.
It went in beautifully.
You are strong.
I don't think I can win.
2-1?
I will only support the MET.
Someone will support the MET.
In downtown.
Matsumoto will support the MET.
I will support the MET.
I support the MET in MUTON.
You can put it here.
If Matsumoto takes it.
If Matsumoto takes it, it's over.
I support the MET in this position.
That's right.
This is a little.
This is the first time.
I don't know what will happen.
One, two, three.
Look over there.
What is this?
You lost.
Thank you.
The next entertainer, please.
Hello.
You are a man and a woman.
I'm Tan-chan.
I'm BIN-TAN-PAN.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you.
How many years has it been?
It's been half a year since the combination was formed.
It's about that much.
If you look at my work history,
This is Tan-chan, the 8th year.
I'm 15 years old.
We're 7 years apart.
It's strange.
BIN-TAN-PAN's game tour.
Every month,
I always play an original game.
I'm doing a live show.
I'm going to play this original game.
I'm doing it to get out.
I brought the one that was the fastest today.
Here it is.
Let's match the words.
The rules are simple.
First of all, I will put out one kanji of the topic.
You can put it in front of the kanji, in the back, in the front and in the back.
Please add one kanji and make two-letter words.
When you're done, put it out.
If you match the kanji in the same way, it's a success.
I expect everyone to write something.
That's right.
If you have a chance, try it.
I'll do it.
Thank you very much.
Do you do it with just five people?
I'll give you a topic.
Plus Tan-chan.
I don't know what Tan-chan is thinking.
If it was Tan-chan, it would be easy.
Let's match the words.
The first kanji is here.
It's I.
You can put I in the back or in the front.
Please make two-letter words.
Let's match it with everyone.
It would be great if this was the first time.
I think it's a good match.
Really?
Are you ready?
Let's open it together.
Please open your answers together.
Netsuai, aijou, renai, aijou, renai, aijin.
Aijin.
It's definitely strange.
I can't write it.
I can't write it at all.
Why did Amada come out on purpose?
That's not it.
It's strange.
I can write it.
It's amazing.
It's difficult.
The next topic is here.
Hito.
It's Hito.
Of course.
You can write what you think.
That's right.
I don't know.
What should I do?
I think everyone will write this.
I can't trust Tanaka.
It's simple.
Let's match it.
Wait a minute.
Let's open it one by one.
HOSEI.
Please open it.
Jinko.
Did you match it?
What is Jinko?
Our reactions are different.
It's completely different.
I didn't expect it to be so different.
What is it?
Please open it together.
amazing.
It's a human being.
But it's the same.
It's the same.
It's a human being.
Next, let's look at Tanaka.
Please look at Tanaka.
Carrot.
It's a carrot.
Do you have a vegetable here?
Carrot.
Is it okay, Matsumoto?
I'm sad.
This is definitely the answer.
What is it?
I thought everyone would be right.
It wasn't.
I'm sorry.
How many years have you been doing this?
This is a service problem.
This depends on Hamada.
That's right.
It's the same.
Hamada, please.
amazing.
This is amazing.
I almost cried.
If you're about to cry, write it down.
Next actor, please.
It's okay.
Nice to meet you.
It's a greeting of a guy who eats with his parents' money.
What is it?
I want you to do your best.
What is the next game?
This is the game we brought.
This is a word game.
I want everyone to play this.
Please explain the rules.
This game is.
There are 50 cards with Hiragana letters in front of you.
This is a game where you make words related to the subject.
If it's an animal's name,
look for it.
For example, let's make a chicken.
If you make a lot of characters,
that's enough.
It's better to make two more than a cat.
It's fine if not two characters.
But it takes some time to find it.
I'm gonna put in half,
but I want you to put it in.
Oh, you don't have a horizontal bar.
This is okay.
Pick the
That's how long it took you.
The person with the highest number of letters wins.
I will announce the topic.
Don't wear glasses.
You can wear it.
What are the characteristics of glasses?
You are a talent who stands out with glasses.
I can't see.
I'm sorry.
The first topic is this.
What to put in a pot.
Let's start typing.
It will be over when one person is completed.
Everyone, please do your best.
HOSE is fast.
HOSE, what is it?
Kombu.
You got 3 points.
I don't know anymore.
There is a topic.
Please return all of this.
HOSE got 3 points.
3 points.
Thank you very much.
Kombu.
Do you want me to complete it with kombu?
You don't look at me at all.
I can't see it at all.
The next topic is this.
What animal do you want to buy?
Let's start typing.
There are various animals.
Everyone, please do your best.
HOSE is fast.
What is the answer?
Cat.
You got 2 points.
Wait a minute.
Let me play.
I lost because it was a cat.
The next topic is this.
Sports.
Let's start typing.
This is difficult.
There are various animals.
Everyone, please do your best.
Please do your best.
My muscles are in the way.
Let's start typing.
I can't see it at all.
Hamada is fast.
What is the answer?
Ice hockey.
Please show me.
There is a small 2.
No.
I'm looking for it in ice hockey.
Matsumoto.
Soccer.
He is showing his umbrella.
OK.
Hamada is OK.
Thank you very much.
Soccer.
There is a stick.
Ice hockey.
You got 7 points.
That's great.
This is soccer.
This is not soccer.
This is a stick and an umbrella.
I can't see it at all.
Let's move on to the next topic.
Please write a phrase you like.
There are various phrases.
Hamada often says.
Is it taken?
No.
There are 4 phrases per letter.
Why?
Please write a phrase you like.
Are you ready?
Nakanishi.
What is it?
Wait.
He got 3 points.
Is that so?
Wait.
I'm ready.
What is it?
That's right.
That's a bad word.
I agree with that.
That's right.
Nasu Nakanishi.
Please write a phrase you like.
Hamada has 7 points.
Who will win?
This is the next topic.
Please write a phrase you like.
You know the charm point.
Please think about it.
Matsumoto wrote a phrase you like.
Please answer.
Please write a phrase you like.
I didn't write a phrase I like.
I really wrote a phrase I like.
What is it?
Hatomune.
That's right.
That's a charm point.
Did you write it on your profile?
I'm happy.
He got 4 points.
I can see the other side.
There is a difference of 3 points from the top.
The next topic is this.
Please write a phrase you like.
I wrote a phrase I like.
His answer is a simple one.
Please answer, NAKANISHI.
I wrote a phrase I like.
I got 5 points.
What are you trying to make, Tanaka-san?
I'm going to make a big bike.
That's a long word.
You're challenging me.
Matsuno-san?
I'm going to make a pigeon.
He was riding a pigeon.
A pigeon with a pigeon's chest.
I'm going to make a pigeon bus.
A pigeon bus is cool.
I've never thought it was cool.
It's reversed.
By the way, this is the last one.
Here's the last topic.
Combination name.
Let's start.
This is hard.
I think it's going to take a long time.
If you have this, you can reverse it.
Combination name.
It's reversed.
How is it?
Hamada-san has a lot of cards.
I want luck.
Give it to me.
Did you get it?
I got it.
Hamada-san.
Not yet.
I got it.
Hamada-san, please answer.
I want St. Louis.
If you show me the card.
It's cool and long.
OK?
I want St. Louis.
That means 8 points.
I want it.
That's great.
Hamada-san won with a total of 15 points.
Thank you very much.
What is this?
I was going to make Yasushi Kiyoshi.
This is Hei, but it's okay.
It's not Hei.
It's Helen.
You deceived me.
I'm sorry.
The previous broadcast was broadcast exclusively on Hulu.
Please search for Hulu.