Happy birthday to you. Happy birthday to you.
Why?
Look at this.
This is what I came up with.
It's a Tsukkomi machine.
If you wear this, anyone can be Tsukkomi.
So, I don't really...
Who are you?
I'm Hamamoto.
Hamamoto Kenkichi.
I'm Hamamoto Kenkichi.
I don't need you anymore.
Normally, you can't be Tsukkomi.
But if you wear this...
If you wear this, you can be Tsukkomi.
Turn it on!
Where did you put it?
Hey, you have to put it in the back.
I didn't know.
Like this.
In the back?
You have to put it in the back.
I've done this before.
I want someone who looks more like an amateur to do it.
I see.
You can say that.
Your glasses are shaking.
But if you wear this...
It doesn't matter.
Turn it on!
I'm scared.
Why?
Why Senbei?
Let's edit this.
I hate sweet things.
It's sweet!
It doesn't matter.
You can do it.
Turn it upside down.
It's funny.
It's all the same.
Over there.
Let's do it.
Why?
You have to put it in the back.
It doesn't matter.
Sorry.
I made it weak.
I just realized.
You can wear this.
No, no, no.
It's B2.
B2.
It doesn't matter.
Turn it to B1.
You can do it.
I'll raise it to maximum.
I'll raise it.
I've raised it a lot.
It doesn't matter.
My body is weak.
It's weak.
What are you doing?
How about that yellow guy?
You can do it.
Don't make me do this.
There's a place where I left a question.
Why don't you do it?
It doesn't change much.
Let's change places.
Don't do that.
I'll do it.
It might be different.
What is it?
I'll do it.
I don't want to do it.
It's embarrassing.
I'll do it.
Let's go.
He's smoking
It's getting dangerous
The last one
It's like Matsubokkuri
He'll do it
Switch on
The girl
The girl next to you
Switch on
Who should I switch on?
Look
The girl next to you
Switch on
Matsubokkuri is dangerous
Matsubokkuri
Let's go home
Let's watch the best scenes
I went to the audience
And I touched everyone
You won't do it?
This is for fan club
I see
Then let's watch the best scenes
Huh?
It's for the sake of the children!
Hello
You know, on a day like today, I feel a bit of pressure
Why?
If I don't get excited with my talk more than usual, the opening will be ruined
Daniel-kun!
What?
The power of energy is amazing
When I saw this at home, I was like, huh?
When I saw the opening the other day, I was like, was he laughing this much?
I'm laughing as much as I can!
After the show, everyone, please stay here for a bit
Only the laughter
I won't do it after all
It wasn't funny, but it was funny
There are a lot of shows like that, right?
Yes, yes, yes
I can't even go on set, why am I laughing like this?
There are a lot of shows like that
I won't say it to anyone, but it's not good
It's not good
It's still good today
Tell me how to do it
This is the color of the mustard, right?
This is the color of the mustard, and this is the color of the mustard
This is the black line, and this is the black line
It's not that black!
If you say it's black, it's a bit...
If you say it's black, it's like this
It's like this
These days, there are a lot of strange things coming to the house
I think so
This time, the enemy was really bad
Ah, yes
In the middle of the night, it comes like this
Ah
Right?
The monitor shows it
It's a ugly woman with glasses on
Ah, yes
Um...
She says her name
Well, that's a form of courtesy
No, that's a way of saying if I know it or not
Ah, it's me?
Yes, yes
I don't know about you, and it's a nuisance if you come at this time
When she comes, it's ping pong, ping pong, ping pong
I don't know about that
She keeps pressing it
It's been about 10 minutes, ping pong, ping pong, ping pong
After pressing it for about 10 minutes, she suddenly can't press it
Ah, she gave up and went home
I thought so
Ma-chan
It's my mother's voice
She's screaming in the basement
I can't do this
I can hear it from the people in the office
She's doing something bad
I can't do this
I called the police
It's ping pong, ping pong again
I can't think about it here
I can't let the police come
I can't let them come
It's Shizuoka
I have a favor to ask you
Don't laugh
My car broke down
I have to go back to Shizuoka by myself
I don't have any money
So please put me inside
And lend me some money
I don't know if you know about me
But I don't know about you
So I can't lend you money
While I was running, I saw my face on the monitor
I was talking
The police came to the monitor
What are you doing?
Come here
Ah
Yes
No
I wanted to see that monitor
After a while
About 10 minutes
I'm still talking
I'm sorry
They won't come anymore
That's the problem
I was really driving
My car broke down
I can't let them come
Will they come if I tell them not to come?
It's your message
If I tell them not to come
They won't come
If I tell them to come
They will come
It's natural
It happens
Right?
Again
I'm really tired
I should have come
But
There are many professional wrestlers
They are always after
Giant and Baba
But
If I beat Baba
I beat Baba
You should be proud
You shouldn't look down on Baba
You will be proud
If you beat Baba
Even high school students
If you have a strong body
You can beat him
You shouldn't look down on Baba
What do you know about Baba?
Do you know how big he is?
Of course I know
I've seen him many times
He is bigger than you think
I've seen him
You are a fool
What are you talking about?
You don't know what a wrestler is
That's not true
Wrestlers are different from when you see them in the studio
When you fight in the ring
Wrestlers are bigger
For example
I'm doing this
If
If you fight
Your body will change
Really?
How will you change?
If you fight
Why?
Will a bird speak?
A small missile
will come
Your legs will be catapulted
It's easy to move
I can move like this
Don't look down on catapult
People who laugh at catapult
will laugh at catapult
It doesn't matter
If you laugh at catapult, it's harder to move
You are scared of catapult
You are a fool
What are you doing?
Really
Do you want to go to the toilet?
Yes
Take it out
Why do old people
come closer when they talk?
I don't have a big voice
In that sense
I don't have the power to talk
That's why
Matsumoto
Don't forget that
I don't remember
You don't know
how old people feel
I don't know
When you think about
what old people are
They want to go to the toilet
They talk to young people as much as possible
They try to go to the toilet
They come again
I thought so
What kind of scream
is the happy scream?
What?
You are an old man
You have a big mouth
There is no scream
There is
What are you talking about?
You are angry
I am doing it because there is
I am saying it
Happy scream isn't like that
What do you mean?
If there is a storm
It is not a happy scream
I am telling you
For example, you are walking on the street
You see a million yen
You pick up a million yen
What do you do?
A million yen
At that time
There is a happy scream
No
You are not aware of it
You are saying it
There is no scream
There is no
What do you mean?
What is a happy scream?
What are you talking about?
What are you thinking?
A million yen
There is a million yen
There is a happy scream
I found it
I know
Let me see
You are thinking
Tell me
That's why you are thinking?
Yes
I am thinking
I am sorry
That's why you are thinking
You are walking on the street
A million yen
There is a million yen
What?
What is that?
What is the happy scream?
Right now, it's like...
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
It would be strange if it was a happy scream of Kakumon Hirodaki
Yes, yes, yes
Don't be a snob
Ah, you prepared it
Yes, yes, yes
I was wondering what kind of happy scream it would be
Ah, I forgot
If you say it a little more, it will be a big deal
I don't understand such a thing
I'm teaching you now
Ah, I got it
I don't understand such a thing
Natori
The lion of the beast is the strongest animal in the jungle
On the contrary, what is the weakest animal?
It's a quiet...
What is it?
What kind of cry is it?
Huh?
For example, the lion of the beast is a very strong animal
Yes, yes, yes
It is
It seems to be very strong
That's right
No matter how you think about it, you can't win
It's scared by its voice
It's very weak
It's really weak
The cry of animals
Even dogs are scared
Yes, yes, yes
So it's a smaller animal
Huh?
It's a little bit...
It's wet
Where is it?
It's a little bit...
It's an animal
It's in the food container
Even if it hits the bottle on the roof, it's going to die
It's like this
Huh?
No
It's completely different
How is it?
Can you hear it?
Yes
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts
What happened?
There's nothing like this
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts
I feel sick
It's like this
Isn't it talking?
What is it doing?
It's crying
Even if an enemy comes, it gets sick
It gets sick
It's like Japanese
It's not Japanese
It's a cry
Cook do do
Like this
I see
I heard a rumor that Mr. Matsumoto and Mr. Hama are dating
I have a question for Mr. Hama
What part of Mr. Matsumoto do you love?
What?
I'm starting to get caught
What are you talking about?
The real thing is...
I don't care
Should I tell you what happened back then?
What?
I was surprised
My clothes were all wet
After that you took a shower
It was so hot
I cried for three days
That's gross
You should talk to me when you're hungry
What?
What are you jealous of?
You're jealous of me
You want a lot of things from me
I can't give it to you
I won't take it
I'll give you anything
I have a lot of things I don't need
Let's start with me
When I woke up and saw your face
I was really depressed
Why?
I felt like my head was going to explode
Let's talk about you
When you woke up and saw my face
I ranked you up
You can't say that
You didn't notice when you woke up
I didn't see your face when I woke up
I went to the bathroom
I thought I'd brush my teeth
This is me?
Why are you showing your face?
When I saw you in the mirror
I took a picture of you
Who?
You
Me?
You took a picture of me
Did I?
When I was walking down the street
You took a picture of me
Wait a minute
What is this?
Did you come out of the store on purpose?
Yes
I'm the owner of the bar
Wait a minute