I'm in Ginza today.
Oh, really?
You're walking, aren't you?
What?
This is Ginza's club street.
Club street.
In Osaka, it's called Kitashinchi.
I see.
Kitashinchi's club street and Tokyo's Ginza's club...
Show me Ginza's club.
All of a sudden?
Take this!
Thank you very much.
Are you having a fight with a kid?
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
I shouldn't have done that.
As time goes by,
there are a lot of beautiful places.
It's still a little early.
Are you the owner of the club?
Who?
I'm the middle-aged lady.
I see.
You're a bully.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
Are you showing me?
Yes.
I found you.
You're the real thing.
Yaki-udon has a lot of power.
I'm going to get rid of your hair.
Where are you now?
What's the name of the shop?
4th floor.
How old are you?
19 years old.
What were you doing before you got a job?
What?
Were you a high school student before you got a job?
Were you a teacher?
I don't know.
Don't tell me.
Today, I'm going to show you
Ginza Shogun.
I'm going to show you Ginza Shogun.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you very much.
I was so excited every time I saw you.
Really?
Yes.
You're a good audience.
Yes, you're a good audience.
It's raining.
I'm sorry.
Hang in there.
Actually, I don't have a good body.
You're a weirdo.
That's right.
I usually take a break.
I can't take a break.
I'm going to work hard.
How many times have you been here today?
Sixth time.
We're still going on.
It's amazing.
No more.
Really.
It's a little hard to do.
It's hard to do because it's a night of martial arts.
There's a lot of stuff going on.
When something weird happens,
It's hard to say.
It's really a martial art.
There was a riot incident a while ago.
I'll show you this one.
You can still see it in Osaka.
They're running around in the car.
They're noisy.
I'm sure they're here, too.
They're driving a car.
There's some people driving in a box.
If you look inside,
with a plastic bag.
You know what I mean, right?
I'd rather smoke in a plastic bag.
They're driving and changing plastic bags.
They're all smoking.
No.
They're not in the car.
It's a plastic bag.
They're protesting.
No.
You're driving a car and you're sleeping!
There's probably one guy in the emergency room who's got that much money.
Why don't you just buy a car instead of driving it?
What's wrong with that?
If you feel sick when you're in the emergency room, you should just buy a car.
But if you have money, you can't do anything good, right?
Yeah, they're just walking around, you know?
They're just bad for you, right?
Yeah, they're bad for me.
And there's that guy who's got a house in the house that his parents gave him.
That guy's got a house?
And he doesn't have a head, so he puts his own woman in there.
If you break up, what are you going to do?
Yoshiko's life.
Yoshiko's life?
Keiko's life.
Keiko's life?
The guy who's a little funny.
A cicada's a week's life.
It's got nothing to do with that!
Yoshiko's life.
Keiko's life.
A cicada's a week's life.
I know that even if you don't say it.
It's funny, isn't it?
You're so dumb, you know?
You know, the guy who's walking around, what do you call him here?
The guy who's called Yankee in Osaka, right?
Yankee, right?
The guy who's got his hair out like this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's got a woman in there.
You know?
He's walking around like this.
He's got nothing to do with that!
He's walking around and he's got a cicada in there.
That's true.
They're walking around and they're got a cicada in there.
Why do they do that?
They're very careful.
They know when to go the wrong way.
If they go the wrong way, they'll go to the wrong direction.
You're so dumb!
They can't go home on a rainy day.
You can't go home on a rainy day, can you?
You're the cicada that's walking around.
I've seen you sitting down.
What's that?
The convenience store?
I've never seen you sitting down in front of the convenience store for 24 hours.
Are you a beast?
I've never seen you like this.
You can't sit down.
You're walking around.
You're a fool!
You can't sit down like that.
Even if I tell you how to walk.
If you walk like that, you'll get tired when you get home.
It's 8 o'clock in the morning.
It doesn't matter what time it is.
You've done it before, haven't you?
You're so stupid when you're in high school.
You're a bad person.
And you're wearing your mom's underwear.
Oh, no!
I'll give you 200 million yen for that.
You're the worst!
You were the most suspicious one in the last case.
You took a little child with you.
You called me later and said you'd take my money.
That's the worst.
Hello.
I'll take your money.
What's wrong with him?
You're so straightforward.
Think about what you said at first.
You don't have the right to take money at all.
Hello.
Don't you have a 2nd grader son?
I do.
I have a 6th grader son.
I don't care!
I don't care how old you are!
I don't want to hear it!
Just say it!
How old am I?
It's none of your business!
Your son is in my care.
What?
He's in my care.
Don't be surprised.
I don't want to hear it!
I don't care how old you are!
Hello?
Yes?
Bring me some money.
Money?
I have a 2nd grader son.
I don't care how old you are!
Hello?
Yes?
I'm in Czechoslovakia.
That's not what I meant.
That's too far!
Are you coming to Czechoslovakia?
Get out of my way!
Hello?
Yes?
Do you know about the 2nd grader son?
Yes, I do.
He lives in Czechoslovakia.
Is that so?
Bring him here.
Okay.
I'll tell you the price.
5 million yen.
5 million yen?
It's expensive.
5 million yen, right?
Are you crazy?
I don't know much about business.
5 million yen, right?
That's fine.
Why?
If you tell me the price, I'll bring it to you.
It doesn't matter if it's expensive or not.
If it's not, I'll do something about it.
What?
You're crazy.
Tell me the price.
You're a poor man, too.
You're the closest yakuza to everyone.
Bring me the money.
I'll be nice, so bring me the money.
Hello?
Yes?
Don't talk too much.
Bring me 5 million yen.
5 million yen, right?
5 million yen.
Okay.
I have to fool the people around me.
Bring it to me as you said.
Okay.
Listen carefully.
Put 5 million yen in the green bag.
Write on the white paper that it's a yellow bag.
If you put it in a red bag, I'll put it in a black bag.
Do you understand?
Write something.
Why don't you write something?
You can write it in a blue bag.
What?
Bring it to me in a blue bag.
Why do you do as you say?
Okay.
Don't be late.
If you're late, I'll go ahead.
Where are you going?
You're always late.
You're like a second-hand box.
That's right.
I'm here.
Hello.
Yes.
Please come.
I'll go.
I'm sorry.
What?
Hello.
Don't be surprised to hear it.
What?
My mother told me not to call for a long time.
It's noisy.
Hey, camera man.
And she goes to the front.
Okay.
It's absolute.
She has a long leg.
Okay, thank you very much.
I'm glad you're here.
Please come again.
You're not doing well.
I'm about to fall.
Sorry.
I'm not sure if you'll be angry because it's Japanese TV.
The Giants won the championship.
That's great.
Why do you want to win the championship so much?
It's our song.
I think it's happy to be able to be so desperate.
I think it's happy.
I think it's very interesting.
It's like trying to cheer for the team that you like.
You like that player, so you cheer for that team because they're good.
So, all of them are...
All of them?
I'm tired of them!
I'm just going to say it.
There are 6 teams in Perique.
6 teams in Perique.
The probability is that we'll win once every 6 years, right?
What's that?
That's the strength of every team, right?
You're saying that too, but you had a midday hat on when you were in elementary school, right?
I had a hat on because I liked that hat.
I didn't wear it.
Why did you have a midday hat?
I don't really like the 9 players.
What are you talking about?
If you get beaten up by a pitcher, you'll say,
I said to her, well, it can't be helped, it's only three days in a year, so it's fine if you take three days off.
I'll introduce you to the assistant today.
The assistant?
I haven't decided yet.
She's still a staff member.
Thank you very much for today.
I said this for the sixth time today, but I'm wondering if we're going to do any more jokes.
There's a lot of things.
What should we do?
It's fine.
You don't want to sleep?
I want to do something different.
But I think everyone wants to see a comedy.
I think it's fine.
Can I call Nami's name?
Nami-chan is 16 years old.
I'm suddenly nervous.
I want to do it with Masatoshi-sama.
Is that so?
My body is hot.
It's so intense that my body and mind are broken.
I really want to do a comedy.
I'm a little depressed, but I want to see Hamada-san live.
I want to see Hamada-san in person.
There are a lot of Hamada-kun fans.
I'm not a Hamada-kun fan.
I'll give you that word as it is.
Hamada-kun is a very decent person.
Don't be silly.
I'm serious.
How can you say such a thing?
Your fans can't keep their eyes on you.
I was driving a car in Osaka.
When I stopped in Shingo-machi, I was surprised.
At that time, you were wearing a color.
I found a car in the world.
I stopped in Shingo-machi.
I was surprised.
Hamada-kun's fans are strange.
Hamada-kun was annoying, so I killed him.
Where are you now?
I'm going to bury you now.
Hamada-kun is in the trunk.
Your fans are strange.
I have a grandmother who is in her 30s.
She is always angry.
I'm sorry.
I got a letter from her daughter.
She said, I'm sorry.
It's strange.
I'm sorry.
I stopped in Shingo-machi.
I was scared.
I'm a fan of Downtown.
I have a lot of fans.
When we were in Nijome Theater,
It was like a shutter of Tetsugoshi.
It was a sliding method.
I was going to go out.
I got a letter from Tetsugoshi.
I'm a fan of Tetsugoshi.
I know that.
Please calm down.
Wow!
It's crazy.
He,
Wow!
…
I think it's great that you're back to being a fan.
Yeah, but I don't get it.
You're the only one who said such a thing.
I'm sure you'll say that you're a fan because you don't know anything about Hamada.
But if you know all the bad things about you, you'll never be a fan.
You'll blame it all on me.
Bad things?
I don't have any bad things.
No, really.
What?
Nothing.
I really don't have any bad things.
What do you mean you don't have any bad things? You're the one who started it all.
You're the one who started it all.
Normally, when you're at work, you're surrounded by your friends.
Whether it's early in the morning or late at night.
Good morning!
No matter how tired you are.
What are you?
I'm Kurasa Hamada.
How many years have you been a player in this world?
What are you waiting for?
What kind of person are you?
I'm Japanese.
That's because you have low blood pressure in the morning.
Normally you say that, but when you're with the staff, you become that smelly fart.
If you put up with it, you'll get a stomachache.
Your fart isn't a normal fart.
You have to think about it with everyone.
It's a really smelly fart.
If it's a girl, she'll cry.
It's really smelly.
She'll laugh at you because she's never farted.
It'll stick to your skin.
Don't fart.
Don't fart if you have a bad mouth.
I don't have a bad mouth.
You can hear that Osaka people have a bad mouth.
If Osaka people hear this, they'll get angry.
That's true.
What kind of bad mouth?
Is it a bad mouth?
If you have a bad mouth, you'll have wrinkles on your face.
That's scary.
Everyone will get angry.
My face is in the middle.
If I do this, everyone will get angry.
Everyone will get angry.
Don't say it's a bad mouth.
That's strange.
Lastly, I did it.
Osaka dialect.
Dengana.
What does dengana mean in Tokyo dialect?
What is dengana?
It's desu-gana.
That's good.
It's not gana.
It's desu-gana.
It's difficult.
It's not something.
It's dengana.
It's not a postcard.
It's a postcard dengana.
It's not.
It's not dengana.
It's mangana.
I'm a mangana who can fly from here to there.
That doesn't happen in everyday conversation.
I can fly from here to there.
That's why I'm a mangana who can make a phone call.
I'm a mangana who can make a phone call.
That's wrong.
You should have a phone call and a mangana.
That's right.
Young people are hard to talk to.
You're a mangana with a postcard.
That's wrong.
That's definitely wrong.
It's already started.
It's over.
You said you'd do it again next week.
That's right.
What?
I don't remember because I'm an idiot.
Do you do the same thing?
What?
That's not right.
I'll do it again next week.
I don't know how much I'll be able to edit today.
You talked a lot.
I talked for about 25 minutes after the story ended.
Why do I have to talk so much when I have a sore throat?
I heard another man say, stop it.
I couldn't stop it.
Today, we have a guest.
He's from Settai.
He came to see us.
Like this.
I'm looking for a celebrity.
I'll make a special guest.
But you.
If you sit in front of me, it'll be hard to do it.
You can't sit in front of me.
He's a big guy.
I'm still looking for an assistant.
I'll add a picture to the poster.
I'm here.
I'm sitting on the mountain.
This is the last time.
But.
It's not strange to say it's the end.
It's not strange.
This way of using it can be done either way.
It's not strange to say it's the end.