So today, it's not just us, it's also a lecture
The teacher is here too
Hentou Teikaku-san!
You're talking!
I think it's time to start the lecture
Wait a minute!
What is it?
The teacher is going to do it next time!
Even if you start talking, I won't understand
I don't understand
What do you mean you don't understand?
The point is...
Hentou is here
Ah, you're going here too?
Please stand here
What is this?
This is the teacher, Hentou
Ah, that's amazing
Then, from here...
But I'm strict
Actually, do you know that I have an English school?
That's right
What floor is this?
This way?
It's in Shibuya
Who is that teacher?
Hentou International Academy
It's on the 6th floor of the building in the back
Who is that teacher?
Hello
You!
Hama-chan, you're good!
Give her a round of applause!
Thank you
Then...
Hello, right?
Wait a minute, I'm a little confused
Why?
This is a very polite greeting
From now on, I'm going to make a cry of an animal from America
I want you to guess what animal it is
Is that okay?
Baa!
This is different
This is more like an impersonation than an English word
This is definitely not a sheep
Is this a hook?
It's a hook
What is it?
It's a reindeer!
Reindeer?
Do reindeer cry?
No
Now?
Just now I said Baa
Baa
Can you say Baa?
I said Baa!
You didn't say it
Kento!
Baa will come out, so listen
Baa, Baa, black sheep, have you any wool?
Black ship
Say it!
You just said black sheep
You just said it!
Is that okay?
You're saying animal
A ship is a ship
Black ship
That's right
That's a black ship
I said black sheep
Isn't it sheep?
Sheep
What?
That's correct!
It's sheep
Teacher
Teacher, we have a question for you
Hey!
Are you kidding me?
Come on!
That's why I'm putting this here
Okay, okay
What should we do?
We will use our bodies
to do body action
Kento, look here
We will do this
Do we do this in English?
We have to do it with our bodies
We can't make a voice, right?
We can
Excuse me
Today is an English lesson
Just say the words you know
in English
In English
Okay, come on, come on
This is it
Laura
That's Japanese!
It's Laura!
I said it
So
There's no other choice
It seems like you don't know
Excuse me
I need a little bit more help
So could you do it one more time please?
Please one more time
That's right
Say it again
Okay
I don't know what you're saying
I don't know
I don't look like this guy today
Right?
I don't know
Okay
I think I know
Is this Mr. Saejo Hideki?
Correct
Should we do it in English?
Leave it to me
Right?
This kind of
Let's say
Let's say it's a short sentence
Okay?
Okay
Don't use Japanese
Okay, come on
Fuck!
I'm really sorry
I apologize in place of the main character
The entertainer
What?
You're late for the time
You should have given everyone a bottle of juice
Ladies and gentlemen
Thank you
Hello everyone
What?
What is it?
It's good
Oh my
What's wrong?
The juice is working
Recently the staff
Wanted to do it
Idiot
What is it?
Please take it
20,000 yen
Why is it 20,000 yen?
It's 200
200?
You said 150
One by one
What kind of juice is that?
It contains 50% of the juice
50%?
Hey
Hey Nitta
Nitta, Nitta
Yes, yes
Yes
This is my bag
It's good
What?
I don't know how much you have
Change your clothes
What is it?
You don't even want to do it
This is my bag
I don't know
Give it to me
I can open it
I know
Why do I always put my wallet here?
I don't know
Give it to me
I'll open it for you
Give me 20,000 yen
Wait
Give me your license
20,000 yen
Don't read my license
Don't step on it
You
It's like we're having a date
How much is it?
It says 20,000 yen
10 dollars
Hey
This is my wallet's protective paper
What is that?
I always put this in
I can't lose money
Is that so?
After doing this
That's good
20,000 yen
You're so stingy
By the way, how much money do you have in your wallet today?
I'll show you
Stop it
You have a lot
Why do you have so much money?
It's not like that
What is it?
Are you planning to do that again?
I don't know
Hey
Why do you have so much money?
It's not like that
Why are you so stingy today?
Today?
When did today start?
I don't know
20,000 yen
You can't do that in front of the TV
It's not like that
I have a lot of money
Give me 20,000 yen
It's not like that
Fresh gag
Don't be so stingy
My wallet
What is it?
Give it to me
You're making fun of me
I'm just kidding
20,000 yen
Thank you
Why are you saying thank you?
Are you going to give it to them?
Taste it
I'm not drinking it
I'm not thirsty
Open it
This is
Thank you
What are you talking about?
There is this thing called Pocon
There is no Pocon
It would be great if we could do it together
It would be great
I don't want to say it if we do it together
I don't know
Hey
Taste it
You did it
You fulfilled your promise
That's right
We can proceed with the program
Everyone is drinking and listening to me
It's like I'm inviting them to a dinner show
Is it that good?
What?
It's 100 yen
I don't know what to do
It's your fault
What?
Let's do it when I get older
Do it
When I get older
What do you mean when you get older?
It's when you are older than me
It's not like that
There is a time
That's right
Like today, it's 3.30
It's 31 minutes
That's right
It's 3.30
When I become a high-ranking talent
Well, recently
I don't think I'm popular
Hey
People tell me
I can do whatever I want
I really can't do it
They just come out and shout
They just shout
They don't shout even if I ask them to
Even if you ask them to?
Even if I ask them to, they don't shout
Have you ever tried it?
I haven't, but I know how to do it
How do you know?
Even if they shout
What?
Even if I ask them to, they don't shout
That's not what I meant
It's because I've seen it on TV
You can say that because you have experience
I don't have experience
You said that's not what you meant
It's different from this
You can't misunderstand that
The reason I shout is because I'm a high-ranking talent
If someone else comes out
For example?
For example, if there are 100 fans in downtown
And I walk around
Everyone will come
But who would it be now?
Who?
Who's popular now?
An actor?
Who do you like?
Toshi-chan?
Toshi-chan
That's what this kid said
That's cold
This kid likes Toshi-chan
Why are you here?
Right?
Toshi-chan came
I followed him
100 fans gathered
They came
They said, Toshi-chan
Toshi-chan was worried
Toshi-chan came
90 people came
That's a lot
Don't say 90 people
All of them
There are a lot of people
I have something to say
There are 5 people left
95 people went over there
The remaining 5 people
There are 4 people who are your fans
It's me
Wait
You can say whatever you want
What are you talking about?
That one person
He dropped his glasses
I don't know what's going on
Wait
That person
Yokoyama Yasushi
You're more popular after you got married
Are you stupid?
That's not true
You're more popular
You should work hard in Tokyo
I don't think so
You're more popular
Are you planning something?
I'm not
You're making fun of me
I'm serious
You're cute when you talk like this
Are you kidding me?
I'm serious
You're cute when you talk like this
I don't think I can get close to you
How did you become popular?
I saw you on TV
I became popular because of you
I didn't do anything
I went to the disco and everyone was dancing
I'm the Yakuza after the war
What?
You did it that way
I want you to come to me
I've always been a dandy Omomochi
Why don't you say it yourself?
You're always shy
Really?
What should I do?
What?
When people say bad things about me on TV
I get mad
I get mad on TV but I'm normal
I'm normal when I talk
That's why I'm a dandy
I'm not a dandy
I thought you were scary
But you're not
When I went to the golf course
I was being pulled by the caddy
You were scared
I was scared
Everyone was asking me what number I was
I said 7
I said, yes, and he went like this
It's completely different from TV
I thought he would say it more
And then he went like this
He's kinder than I thought
I said, yes, and he ran off
What number is the next one?
5, and he went like this
At first, he was already trembling
He was like, Kazan-kai!
And he had a bow
And then he went like this
Why?!
I'm like Non-non
There's that thing
It's like this
It's like that
Sorry
Didn't you say Non-non?
It's Non-no
It's not Non-non
If you say Non-non, it's Moomin's this
Let's do the writing
Writing
Yes
Yes, yes
Let's ask the audience tonight
Who's your favorite talent?
Who's my favorite talent?
Tama-san
What do you like about me?
Don't be shy
I'm a fan of Downtown
I'm saying that I'm a fan of Downtown
Why are you like that?
You guys
If I were told that, I'd say,
Why Matsumoto?
I wouldn't say that
Where should I write?
All of them
Who's the one without a box?
Thank you
All of them
Face
Face?
You're like
You're like a codfish's lip
Codfish's lip?
Isn't it good?
There are people like that
I love you as a fan
Please use me
You have good proportions
Please be careful not to be invited
Thank you
Sorry
Let's move on to the writing
This person
I've thought of a big bet for Matsumoto and Tama-chan
What?
A bet
There will be an all-star game soon
In that game, who will win?
It will be held during the summer vacation
It will be held in a month or two
What do you think?
It's good for a bet
Everyone will know
But what will you do if you lose?
It happened in the past
I appeared on Zoom in Asahi
I appeared on Galala
And I appeared on the radio show of Studio Alta
But I know a lot about all-stars
I know that Parry is stronger
If I win, I will compete in Parry
What kind of bet is that?
If you were going to compete in Parry, we wouldn't have talked about this
But why?
It's not that Parry
Don't you want to lose?
I don't
You were upset when you appeared on Zoom
I was upset because I woke up sleepy
So let's think about it
Let's think about the punishment
That's right
Let's go home
That's enough
What time is it now?
8.35
I don't know
Even if you give me juice
I will drink it
But no one is drinking it
It's a waste
It's a waste?
Then don't drink it!
What are you going to do if you can't drink it?
And the ending
You can't come here until 9
I can't make juice
I don't know how to make juice
What's the base?
I will think about it
Without orange juice, you don't know the base
It's like a cocktail
I will think about the taste
I don't know how to make juice
What is this?
Tanaka Seiji was playing with a toy can
That's not good
You can't drink it
What if you die?
I won't die
I have something
I will think about it
Thank you
See you next time
At a place like this
Thank you for the juice
It cost 20,000 yen
It's obvious
It can't be helped
It cost 20,000 yen
It's 5,000 yen
No one is drinking it
It's okay
You can take it home
Do you think so?
I think so
It's not a punishment game
What is it?
Money
Why money?
You didn't wait for it?
I didn't wait
Let's do it
And
You wrote a letter
It's not a punishment game
You wrote a letter about All-Star
Did you read it?
I think it's good
Japanese people know about it
Let's do it next time
Next time
I don't know who will be on it
Let's ask the staff to put it on the board
Let's do it
Next week
Let's think about the punishment game
That's all
We only need the staff
See you next time
Please subscribe to our channel