I've noticed something new.
For example, you go to a cafe, right?
You come here, right?
You order something, anything is fine.
When you're about to go home, right?
When you're about to go home, you call for something.
If you call for something and say,
I have a cigarette,
it will definitely spin.
It will definitely spin.
No matter how many times you do it,
it will definitely spin.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai Yaranen, Chiki Chiki Maashite Maashite Ichiban!
The teacher, Mr. Matsumoto...
You're desperate, aren't you?
You need to relax more.
The teacher, Mr. Matsumoto...
Why are you laughing?
Mr. Matsumoto said it, right?
He said it.
During the talk,
he went to the coffee shop and said,
I'm sorry.
If you say that, it will definitely spin.
Whether it's true or not,
I want to enjoy it as if I'm playing a game.
That's what he said.
We have two coffee shops ready,
but we're only telling the owners about this.
The staff won't know at all.
Then, Mr. Don Tan, Mr. Kokori,
please disperse.
I can't say it at all.
Then Hamada and I will do this.
Yes, disperse.
Oh, like this?
Yes.
Who will do it?
Ready, go!
Matsumoto Endo Team,
Hamada Tanaka Team.
I don't like Endo.
Why?
Mr. Matsumoto, let's spin it.
Then, Mr. Hamada Team will do it.
That's fine.
What is the shop like?
It looks like this.
This is the data.
This is a home-like atmosphere
that the owner of the shop doesn't like.
Here it is.
A shop that doesn't allow compromise.
It's here.
Why?
It's the opposite.
Which way should we go?
Let's go this way.
But if you think about the motto of this shop,
it's a home-like atmosphere that the owner doesn't like.
Then, let's compromise.
I think this one is better.
Endo is better.
Hey, wait a minute.
I think this one is better.
I don't think it will spin.
I don't think so.
It's here.
Then, Hamada Team.
You're not sitting down, are you?
I'm sitting down.
Start.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
It doesn't spin.
Is it okay to order only drinks?
Yes, it's okay.
Why is it okay?
Is it okay?
Then, I'll think about it.
I'm sorry.
It doesn't spin at all.
I'm surprised.
I'll order drinks.
It's not good to sit down.
It's not good.
Orange juice.
Yes.
It doesn't spin.
It says it doesn't spin.
Really?
It spins the other way.
It doesn't spin.
That's why.
When it goes like this, it spins to the left.
It spins.
Don't shake your hand like that.
That's right.
If you get 100,000 yen like that, you can earn as much money as you want.
You just have to look back.
It doesn't spin.
I wonder if it's just a lie.
I'm sorry.
It hasn't spun yet.
It spins to the left.
It doesn't spin.
It doesn't spin to the left.
Don't say it out loud.
Oh, you got a penalty.
Excuse me.
This is the timing.
It's spinning now.
Did it spin?
Yes, it finally spun once.
Excuse me.
It's spinning now.
Wait a minute.
Excuse me.
It's too late.
Just say it out loud.
Okay.
It's spinning now.
It's really hard.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
You'll understand when you see mine.
I'll spin with my toes.
You're kidding.
Let's eat and go home.
He gave up.
It's perfect.
Let's eat and go home.
What do you mean go home?
I can't even go to the bathroom.
What are you talking about?
You can't do that.
That's harsh.
I'm not playing anymore.
Let's enjoy the game.
Yagami.
Yes.
We have to play next.
We have to eat.
I'm not hungry.
What are you thinking?
I'm working.
Let's enjoy the game.
I'm going.
I'm hungry.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Okay.
You're fast.
I'm sorry.
I told you to go home.
What?
It hurts.
Why can't I hear you?
I told you to go home.
Everyone was eating.
Please go home after you eat.
I'm sorry.
Yagami is a kind person.
He gave me a low score.
Wait a minute.
How many points do you have?
What?
You were playing a game.
I was playing a game.
For example,
I'm going to come here.
I'm going to order.
Excuse me.
What would you like to order?
I'd like an iced coffee.
Okay.
Excuse me.
I'd like this.
I'd like an iced coffee.
Don't start again.
You can go home.
Father.
Don't be shy.
It's a lie.
The game has started.
It's started.
Yes.
What would you like to order?
She's a young woman.
That's right.
Excuse me.
It's normal.
It's normal, right?
It's really normal.
You waited, right?
I didn't wait.
You were having so much fun.
Excuse me.
Did you do something?
Scary.
It's really scary.
Ice coffee.
I'll bring the menu.
No, I'll have the ice coffee.
Excuse me.
Please bring the menu.
It's normal.
Excuse me.
We're not done yet, Mr. Matsumoto.
Wait a minute.
We're not done yet?
That's right.
It can't be.
We're not done yet.
Count properly.
I'm counting.
We've been doing this for eight times.
We didn't say anything.
Excuse me.
What is this?
Where is the toilet?
But...
I didn't think it would spin so much.
We're not done yet?
Excuse me.
What is this?
The timing of the heat.
That's not the right timing.
That's the timing of the heat.
I'll bring the menu.
That was terrible.
I was watching it all the time.
It's the same thing now.
Can you do me a favor?
I'd like a jam.
Oh, jam.
That's right.
It's over there.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry.
Again!
It's over there.
It's over there!
What did I just do?
It's over there.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, it's over there.
It's over there.
I'm sorry.
That was great.
You said it 4 times.
I've done that many times.
It was elegant.
Let's do it again.
Is it okay?
Excuse me.
Is that...
Again!
Amazing.
Excuse me.
Again.
Is it okay?
30 seconds left.
Excuse me.
It's a dash.
The camera is already on.
The original.
Excuse me.
Look at that.
I can't get it.
8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1
Please turn around
Yes
Sorry
Turn around
Yes
I knew it
You're so excited
The result is
Yes
Team Hamada turned 3 times
Team Ninkyu turned 3 times
Yes
Team Endo and Matsumoto turned 3 times
Wait
Listen
Isn't it strange?
We've been waiting for the last one
I've been waiting for the last one
Kageyama
That's all
What is this?
This is a game
It's a game
It's a fun game
I don't need it anymore
Why did you turn the wheel?
I want to take you to Hamada
Hamada, Tanaka, Shinji
It's strange
What's going on?
Let's turn the wheel
Let's see who turns the wheel
The person who turns the wheel is Rei
You're the one who turns the wheel
The woman who turns the wheel is Rei
Ladies and gentlemen
It's been a while
Is it?
Wait a minute
What's so strange about you guys?
You guys don't look like a funny duo
Did you go on a holiday?
I did
Did you really go to Ise?
Yes, I went to Ise
I went to Ise and Parque Espana
I didn't go anymore
That's amazing
It's amazing
It's like this
Fujiyama
Fujiyama is not a fire
Do you want to ride it?
Who?
You
Do you want to ride it by yourself?
I can't hear you
I can't ride it
Is it a punishment game?
Are you going to play a punishment game?
What punishment game?
I can't ride it
Why are you playing a punishment game?
I said I can't ride it
I can't ride it
That's amazing
Why are you so scary?
It's you
No, it's not like that. In terms of character, I'm not scared of those things
It's just that Machan is cool
It's Machan
Stop it
You don't need to be cool
It's just that he's cute
You're the type of person who goes all out in terms of character
Why are you scared of those things?
You should go more
Why?
You should ride it
If you're going to go to a place like that
I want you to ride it
Ise didn't really want to ride it
Why?
It was really funny
Kimura from the station was really funny
When I went to Ise, he was saying something
Iwate, Ikea, something like that
He was saying that
He was eating udon at the drive-in
After that, he went back to the hotel and said cup ramen
I don't know what he was doing
You guys don't know
I ate something like a green fox
I ate a green fox
But that year and that year
The taste of the green fox was a bit different
Is that true?
I know that
You should go eat something
You went all out
That's true
But if I go with everyone
I'll have to pay for everything
You're such a troublemaker
That's not something I can do
What do you mean?
Why do you have to pay for everything?
There are times like that
That's true
When you go out to eat with a woman
You wonder why a man has to pay for everything
Women think it's normal
I see
I don't think that's right
Women don't do that
Women only pay when they have money
When they have money, they pay for everything
It's a sex pay
For me, even if a woman is walking
Who are you paying for?
I'm paying for men
The last time I saw a woman with her shoulders out
And her pants were like this
Her pants were like this
I didn't see her pants
That's why I want to sue her
That's fine
It's the second half
It's fine if you show it
You shouldn't be the only one paying
Hagi
Yes
After the rain has stopped
It's very annoying to walk around with a long umbrella
Don't you have an easy and cool way to hold it?
You know
In the end
Umm
Please tell me
I'm putting this together
A cool way to hold it
In the end
Please tell me
When you think of an umbrella
This isn't an umbrella
This is an umbrella
Is that okay?
Yesterday was the first time I held an umbrella
An umbrella is an umbrella
Strictly speaking
At this stage
It's in front of an umbrella
You can say that the umbrella is 20 years old
It's 20 years old
An umbrella is
This is called an umbrella
If it rains
You can do this
If it stops
Basically
An umbrella should be like this
This is the coolest way to hold it
Don't tell me you're going to turn around from there
When someone calls you
This is the coolest way to hold it
What's cool?
Why?
I think this is the coolest way to hold it
No?
Actually
If you hold an umbrella in the rain
When it's over
Can you keep walking?
Can I do this?
You can walk
There are people who get in my way
They come from this side
I hit them
Why are you surprised?
I didn't think I would hit them
I hit them
It'd be nice if you stretched it
It's nice if I stretched it
You can stretch it
It would be nice if you stretched it
It's nice if you stretch it
I've been hitting them for the past 15 years
Did you have a fight?
You should have stretched it!
You should have closed it!
When you park your bicycle in the middle of the road,
there are times when you find trash in the basket.
Yes, there are.
It's annoying to throw it away.
It's annoying.
But you can also throw it away.
What do you do to make it look the best?
It can make you look beautiful.
There are many ways to do it.
The first way is to ignore it.
Ignore it?
When I'm riding my bicycle,
there's trash in front of it.
You can also pretend to be on the bike
and hide in the middle of the road.
No one is watching.
You can go home riding your bicycle
and say,
Yo-san, I did this today.
Or this.
No!
There are many ways to do it.
But I brought it home.
But that's impossible.
You can't do anything about it.
That's true.
What should I do with the trash?
Are you ready?
You treated your bicycle as a trash can.
That's right.
That's a terrible thing to say.
That's true.
It's my bicycle.
There's a lot of trash in it.
That's right.
I'm telling the truth.
What should I do?
Yay.
It's yay.
Did you grow up?
I don't care about that.
Why?
What are you going to do with the trash?
The trash in the basket...
Don't say that.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
What are you going to do with the trash in the basket?
What are you going to do?
What?
What are you going to do with the trash in the basket?
Don't talk in Osaka dialect.
What should I do with the trash in the basket?
I don't know.
Let's do it.
It's a shame.
Hey, Matsumoto.
I knew it.
Who said that?
You made me think.
Please.
What should I do with the trash?
It's trash.
Who said that?
Who?
You made me think.
There is no trash in my bicycle.
That's right.
I wonder if I can finish it.
Something amazing happened in my house.
My grandmother often takes a nap.
I don't know if she is a fool.
But she breaks the calendar.
It's New Year's Day in my house.
I'm happy and I'm silly.
Goodbye.
I was wondering why I had my hair in the basket.
I'm in trouble.
What am I supposed to do with that?
It's strange. I'm waiting for the magazine to be published.
Downtown's key user Arahen.
Well, he's a key user, but he denied it in the second half.
Ah, key user Arahen.
I want you to take a look at it.
Give me the monitor.
Stop it.
Ah, there's a monitor.
Turn off the light.
What?
It's downtown.
No way.
What are you talking about?
It's downtown.
Really?
Did I read downtown?
No way.
Let's take a look at it.