In the end, there haven't been many guests recently.
It's a bit of a shame to have a big guest, but we have to think about it.
I don't know if there's a guest like this in Gaki.
For example, Hiroko Yakushima.
I saw him a little bit.
I called him.
Why are you laughing?
This program is brought to you by the sponsor you see.
If you come, Hiroko Yakushima will do this.
I'm here.
Good morning.
I'd like you to come out when you're done.
Is that okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm in trouble.
Ladies and gentlemen.
What's going on?
I made something.
I made one and another.
It's a combination.
It's getting bigger.
You made your own.
I think it's that.
I don't like to talk about private stuff.
I thought I'd quit.
I'm older than him.
I thought I shouldn't do it.
I broke up with him the other day.
That's a big deal.
I thought I'd quit.
He was crying.
I think he was having a hard time.
I said I'd quit.
I told the lady.
The lady packed my suitcase.
Thank you very much.
I said I'd never fall in love again.
You.
I said I'd leave the laundry.
I left.
Laugh a little more.
Where's the fun?
I quit.
How many days have you been quitting?
Two days.
I quit.
I didn't go in.
I didn't quit.
It's amazing if you quit for two days.
How many times have you fallen in love in a week?
Three times a day.
Of course.
I can't stop.
Who is it?
I quit.
It's been two days.
For example, it's like a rehearsal.
If you practice too much, you can't do well in the actual performance.
What do you mean?
If you spend too much time on practice, you won't get excited in the actual performance.
Do you understand?
What's the difference between the actual performance and practice?
It's different, but I want to be more sensitive.
That's because you practice too much every day.
If you practice every day, you can't do well in the actual performance.
What are you like?
Well, I'm the same as you.
Laugh a little more.
When I was in junior high school, I didn't think I was doing that much.
I didn't think I was doing that much.
I thought adults couldn't do it.
Now I'm 34 years old.
I can't do it at all.
I'm surprised.
You're very good at it.
When I was in elementary school, my father was still doing it.
That's right.
I thought I'd quit.
I see.
You haven't been to the video shop these two days.
Yes, that's right.
Which one?
Which one did you go to and which one didn't?
Well...
I did it yesterday.
You did it?
Why are you lying?
I think it's cool.
Is it cool?
I'm getting angry.
Why are you lying to me?
I'm laughing.
I don't want to talk about this, but I'll tell you one thing.
I've never done it without any punishment.
I see.
I want to do it once.
I've never tried it.
I want to do it without any punishment once.
I see.
I don't think I should quit.
Why?
I have children.
It's not like I'm doing it in front of you.
If I do it in front of you, the kids will be surprised too.
Mom!
Dad!
Hurry up!
It can't be helped if this story gets too big.
Let's start with the first one.
You say good things.
Cyborg!
It's Cyborg Koichi!
This is Cyborg Koichi!
It seems like you've seen him before.
Oh, is that so?
If you talk like that, I'll go to the exam.
You like the name Cyborg Koichi, don't you?
Yes.
Who gave you that name?
The president of the gym.
When he comes back next time,
I'll give him a name like Soreike.
Like Hatshin.
It might be better to give him a name like that.
Hatshin.
It's like a cyborg.
That's right.
It's like he's been
I think that too.
It's better to give him a name with a lot of codes.
Something like short.
That's right. And the president should be more like a doctor.
I'll prepare it for you.
When you take a shower and come back to the gym,
what do you think is the coolest thing to do?
I don't think it's cool.
What do you do?
For example,
you say, I'm going to take a shower.
And you go.
I think it's a bath towel.
I'm not sure if it's my waist.
Your waist?
It's like this.
I'm not sure if it's my waist.
How long do you wait?
But it's like this in bed.
It's like the gate of youth.
You're pretty good.
That's not good.
Then the woman...
Why are you standing up like that?
I'm talking to you.
It's hard for the woman to get in.
That's not good.
What do you want to do?
Well, there are three.
I'm sorry, but...
I'm sorry, but I can't tell you the coolest thing.
Why?
Because I've been working on it for a long time.
Isn't that right?
That's not good.
I've been working on it for a long time.
I was thinking about it when I was in the first year of high school.
That's old.
Are you still working on it?
I'm sorry.
Then I'll tell you the second one.
Okay, then the second one.
When a woman comes out, she's holding her pants up against the wall.
She's reading a book.
She's reading a book when she comes out.
Isn't that cool?
I don't know if I can finish reading it.
That's not true.
When she comes out, she's reading a book.
When she says, Oh, you're here.
This is where it gets cool.
She takes out a bath towel.
And she puts it in her mouth.
You'll know what's next.
The continuation.
The continuation of the next one.
You'll know what's next.
The best one.
I want to hear the best one.
I'll tell you later.
What do you mean later?
After a little while.
I'll tell you the second one.
Don't think about it.
It exists in reality.
You just have to untie the ribbon.
You don't have to wait to untie the ribbon.
There's something like that.
Animals often tell humans about danger.
When rabbits make a noise, earthquakes occur.
When birds make a noise, fires occur.
Please tell us about the behavior of animals that tell us about other disasters.
Well, I don't know what's good.
Anything is fine.
Is there a dog that's as loose as that?
There's a dog, too.
Is that so?
What would a dog do?
There's a dog, too.
Cats wash their faces.
What?
There's a dog.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about a dog.
Is there a dog?
There is a dog.
What?
I told you there was a dog.
Please tell us about the behavior of animals that tell us about other disasters.
To put it simply, I can't think of anything.
You can't think of anything.
I can't even panic.
You can't even panic.
I want to lie down.
But if I say something like this, people will think I'm running away.
People will think you're running away.
I hate it when people turn their backs on me.
I don't like that.
I don't like running away.
I don't run away.
I want to end it with this.
You want to end it with this?
This time, I'll make you run away.
I'll make you run away with your back to me.
When a woman comes back to a new chair after taking a shower, what is the coolest thing to do?
You're really good at killing your partner.
You're a free hunter.
You know what?
Yes?
I really feel it.
I really feel the feelings of each and every one of the guests.
You're still trying to run away, aren't you?
I see.
That's what you think, right?
Are you stupid?
That's not true.
Why?
Mama, Aniki, Mama.
I'm going to end it.
Right?
That's right.
You're crazy.
I'm thinking about it.
I'm thinking about it right now.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I've been lying for a long time, too.
Hey, you're a jerk.
If Akko refused this, let's think about it.
I can't plan anymore.
Yes.
I'm going to the mountain.
Yeah.
Yes.
Was it like that in the morning?
I want you to come to the party
This program was brought to you by the sponsor of this program