Thank you very much.
The reason why I asked you to come here today is...
Next week, we're going to have a special episode of our show.
It's going to be a 7th episode.
Oh, a 7th episode?
Yes.
I'd like you to do it.
Oh, really?
The 7th episode of the special episode of Gaki no Tsukai that started with Matsumoto Hitoshi.
Up until now, 13 famous people have come back with their own sense of humor.
There are 7 dramas in it.
And this time, a man with white teeth is going to appear.
For the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai, will it be Kichi or Kyoto?
Yamashita Shigenori 7th episode!
It's been a year and a half.
That's right.
Yamashita Shigenori 7th episode.
At this point...
The channel is going towards CX.
That's right.
This is not good. The atmosphere is not good.
Really?
Normally, when you go to a 7-yen shop, people ask you to give them 1000 yen bills.
But no one says anything.
Everyone is full of bills.
I'm just a little bit.
Just a little bit?
Yes.
The challenger is Yamashita Shigenori!
Thank you.
It's Yamashita Shigenori.
Yamashita Shigenori 32 years old.
Born in 1991 in Yoshimoto, a Jyarizumu family.
With his sharp wit, he won the Grand Prize for Comedian and Newcomer Award.
He won them all and moved to Tokyo.
He has been on more shows recently, and in 1998, while he was still in the 80s,
Yamashita's selfishness suddenly disbanded
Even if he starts again as a pin comedian, he has a difficult life as a comedian
The more I work hard, the more I get hurt
I think everyone will really get hurt during the show
I think it's a little too slippery
No.1 so far
It's a polyvenom
That?
That's right
He got 44,000 yen
I think it's Tanaka, Miyasako
I don't like it!
He's a broadcaster, Takasu
Where do you want to go?
At least I want to beat Miyasako
Really?
Don't hold it
It's scary
I don't know
I know what kind of guy Hamada likes
You know?
I don't know!
I don't like guys like you!
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
What should we do?
Oh
Right?
Yeah
That's right
It's been a while, do you want to see someone?
Suga-chan is writing a big book about Harley
Oh
You can get parts for each
Since it's a Harley?
Yes
How much did it cost?
1.5 million yen
That's scary!
That's 1.5 million yen on a motorcycle
That's a lot
That's what it means
But this is interesting
Tanaka's beard is in the water
I want to quit water if I can
Why?
I'm going to get caught in the water
I'm telling you to quit water
No one will think that I'm wearing this
What do you think?
There's something
I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm late
I didn't get the memo
I see
I got it
I see I see
I'm sorry
What are you going to do?
I don't need that box
There are still 6 of them
Really?
Yes
Thank you for the meal
It was a little cold
I wonder if it was okay
I broke the glass
Brother
I heard you moved
Can I play with you?
Sure
Can I?
Yes
Can I play with you?
Sure
Can I go home?
Thank you
He ran away
What's in there?
I don't know
It's a guitar
Yes
I want to see
I see
I'm sorry
I'm sorry but I'm not good at this
I just laughed a little
Can I laugh?
What?
Yamasaki
I laughed
I laughed a little
Why did you laugh?
The door knob was very slippery
I know
That was funny
I want to move but the old man is great
I can move freely
That was funny
Yamasaki
What number did you say?
Yes
It's 1000 yen
I tried to say it for a long time
It's too much
It's hard
To be honest, I can't hold it
I have to take it off
I'm scared to take it off by myself
I'll help Kame
Ouch
How do I take it off?
I took it off
I'm glad
Is it okay for a comedian to explain first?
That's right
Why are you doing this?
I was surprised
Yamashita Shigenori-dono
You did a good job with the pain
I was impressed
Congratulations
Thank you
That's all
I didn't need that
I'm a fool
Why do you keep laughing at that little joke?
That's all
I can't do it
What are you doing?
I love you
Put it all in
He's funny
What did you say?
I said I love you
I love you
It's so funny
Even if it's the second time
It has nothing to do with Yamashita
If you look at it like that
I put it in
I thought you were a fool
So it's 11,000 yen
11,000 yen
You're in 9th place
9th place?
By the way, Sugachan is an amateur
I love you
Good evening
Do you know that?
I heard it the other day
I thought I see
I'm going to stop saying that I'm a runaway
What do you mean?
A runaway is cool
Naming
So I'm going to be a runaway
There are people who admire
There is no need to give a cool name
Don't call it a runaway
It's called a runaway
No matter how much you say it
I don't think it's a runaway
I don't think so
For example, the other day in the news
If you say that a runaway is something
It sounds cool
The news said that a runaway was running away
If you say that
It sounds cool
Yesterday I said that was a runaway
Sorry, I'm going to quit tomorrow
That's not true
That's a nuisance
That's right
They say that they don't cause any trouble
But when they are tired and sleeping
Can't you say it's a nuisance?
You have to say it
You know it's a nuisance
Then you should quit
Everyone thinks so
When I say something good
The audience's reaction is like this
Everyone thinks so
Even if you don't say it's a nuisance
I said that
So you have to change it from the news
That's right
I don't know how to treat the news
But sometimes people go to snowy mountains
Someone was in trouble the other day
He's gone
He's gone, right?
What?
To the snowy mountains
He's going?
He's going
That's true
Really?
He just went
He said it's cold
He was treated like a challenger
He was treated like a good person
The next day
There was an old man who climbed up the snowy mountain
He was arrested
Why?
It's the same as a challenger
It's just different
Everyone was clapping
He couldn't get the ball
Isn't that strange?
It's the law that you can't just climb up the mountain
Why can't I just climb up the mountain?
It's not your thing
I can't just climb up something that's not mine?
I can't just climb up on the spot?
What do you mean?
You can't just climb up on the spot?
You can't just say that?
I can't do anything
That's the law
You can't do that
There were a lot of strange old men who climbed up the mountain
Like the spider man
They were fighting
That old man climbed up the mountain
He was arrested
He was really tired
He wasn't even a spider man
He was really weak
I thought it was amazing
No one wanted to climb up the mountain
That's strange
It's the law that you can't just climb up the mountain
Why can't I just climb up the mountain?
It's the same with Everest
It's the law that you can't just climb up the mountain
Everyone was clapping
Even in Everest, if you climb up the mountain, you can't just climb up
Where are the people who climb up the mountain?
They're always in Everest
That's the law
Don't say that
Who said that?
That's the law
I'm doing Project X
I'm doing a documentary on NHK
I can cry when I see an old man who climbed up the mountain
It depends on how you treat them
I wonder if I can cry when I see an old man who climbs up the mountain
You can cry
Your upper body is naked
It has nothing to do with being naked
That's why I'm doing a documentary
You were crying
That was the moment when I was like this
What?
The feeling between you and me
This is a question for Matsumoto-san, who is a volunteer in the Japanese soccer team
What does Torsier Japan recommend as a flat 3?
What is a volanchy?
What?
You don't even know that?
Can you teach me?
Volanchy
Simply put, it's like joy
Volanchy, volanchy
Volanchy is about the position of the defense
That's right
That's where it comes from
It's about joy
Okay, then
Where do you call a person a volanchy?
There's a circle in the middle of soccer
It's around that
That's usually the position of a volanchy
If you can play well there, it's a volanchy
What does a flat 3 mean?
It's too late to explain
But I don't know
You can just translate it into English
What does a flat mean?
A flat is a volanchy
What does a volanchy mean?
It means to be forgiven 3 times
What does that mean?
It was 45 minutes, right?
It means you can forgive 3 times
You can forgive 3 times?
You can take off your shoes and go around
No, no, no
That's not allowed
It means you can forgive 3 times
But that's not allowed
That's not allowed
It's been said
So let's not do that
That's right
Flat 3?
Aren't you doing it right now?
I'm doing it
In Italy, it's flat 3 every day
Flat 3 for women who drink
I see
That's why
Let's not stick to one ball
It's called cataclysm
Cataclysm?
So you add 2 more balls
And you think which one is the real one
You put it in and it's out
It appears in ancient myth many times
And it's a question to Matsumoto who changes the color of the temple
I don't know
What kind of smell does kentaurus have?
What kind of question is that?
I don't know
When you see it, you think it's an animal, right?
That's right
It's a mixture of humans and animals
So what kind of smell is that?
I was in the elevator with kentaurus once
It was a very small elevator
I went to the 8th floor with kentaurus
I went to the 9th floor
I was with kentaurus for a long time
So I could smell it
I see
What kind of smell is that?
The most easy to understand smell is
The smell of the air conditioner I turned on for the first time this year
It doesn't smell that bad
But it's still breathing
It breathes kentaurus
Up and down
Do you know kentaurus?
Half, half
Is that so?
Kentaurus is an animal that breathes
Did you just say half?
Why did you say half?
No, no
When kentaurus breathes, it breathes animals
Half, half
But this is different between animals and humans
It breathes animals
When I'm in the car, the car here and the car here
I feel irritated
So if you ask me if it smells or not
The bottom one smells
It smells like poop
That's what I mean
The bottom one doesn't only smell like poop
I made a mistake
What have I been saying?
I've been saying things like this
I've been talking nicely
I was wondering if there was a face here
There isn't a face
It's just a difference in memory
To be honest, this animal here
It smells like poop
It smells like poop?
But this one is different
It smells like Tactics
It goes bang, bang
It's so nostalgic
Tactics
It's Tactics