Tonight's guest is...
I'm going to put a hand cell in the power supply
Sanchiro Komiya's 24 hour long interview, the end
The past that has been bullied since he was young
The person who bullied you may be watching this on TV, please say something to the camera
I'm already higher than him.
I'm the one who's lost.
The high school era that started with club activities.
Everyone uses the brand.
It's become a school discussion.
For example, elementary school students.
They're wearing school clothes at school.
Since they were in third grade,
a boy passed by.
When he took off his jacket, he laughed.
At the end, he chased after him with a trunk switch.
He said, kya kya kya, and went home.
Two days later, he went to school with his mother.
He said, this brother of mine, what's going on with you?
Everyone knew about that rumor.
If you sleep on the bed, you'll become M.
What do you think?
Scary, scary, scary!
Scary, scary, scary, scary!
Tonight, we will reveal the true face of Komiya!
It's 8.18pm.
There, for dinner, we will go to a restaurant in Komiya.
What's the name of the restaurant you're going to?
It's Mara.
Mara.
Mara?
Is it a restaurant you go to often?
Yes.
It's a joint restaurant in Yamagata.
A joint restaurant in Yamagata?
I go there about 3 times a week.
About a week?
Yes.
What is that?
It's a drug for the heart.
It won't heal.
Drink some chocolate.
Do you use social media?
No.
Why not?
Because I'm afraid of comments.
So you don't search for your ego?
I don't know.
I go searching.
But sometimes, I do.
I get depressed.
What kind of words do you hate?
When I was on TV, my wife screamed.
So I put a claim in the song.
And...
I was in high school.
I don't know if it was a girl or not.
Yesterday, at school,
I was told that I looked like Sanshiro Komiya.
And that's how I ended up here.
And then, at the izakaya at Koenji,
He has arrived at Mara.
Cheers!
Why are you gulping?
I'm not gulping.
It's better not to gulp.
While enjoying the food and continuing the interview,
Hello
A very close junior who is very familiar with Komiya has arrived
I'm a little excited
I've been alone for a long time
I would like to ask the junior actors about Komiya
I like to see the girls around me being like,
Wow, this person is so pretty.
That's why you're in the picture.
I went to Komiyama's love hotel.
I bought a drink with my wife.
I was asked to do some errands.
I said, Komiyama-san, and I opened the bottle.
When I said, Komiyama-san, he said, thank you.
He showed me a little bit of his girl's boobs and said,
I said thank you and showed her breasts a little bit.
She said, go home.
The younger one is exposed to the sexual harassment.
A very cheerful Komiya.
What is Komiya to you?
He is a senior who taught me how to be a comedian.
If a prank comes, I will be the one who gets the prank.
What did you learn?
You have to talk a lot.
Don't say that.
Even if the staff says it was a prank,
I have to be a good boy.
So I have to be gentle.
We still have 12 hours left.
It's hard to do.
What will you do if you do that?
It's scary.
I knew it.
It's a prank.
I'm scared.
Don't make a scary face.
He always says he wants to sell it with everyone.
I'm scared.
13 hours after the interview.
The interview resumed at the hotel bar.
You've had a lot to drink.
It's so good.
I'm sorry.
Slowly.
It's okay to drink slowly.
You should drink slowly.
I don't want to drink.
Are you okay?
I'm drinking alcohol.
Let's ask about the love of women.
Thank you.
First, what type of woman do you like?
Type?
I'm a bit of a Yankee, but at night, I like a girl who is like M.
Do you want to show your S?
I'm a Tokoyakuza.
Tokoyakuza?
Tokoyakuza.
It's the S on the bed.
What kind of relationships do you have with women?
We have dating and such.
We have sex at a bar.
Do you have a dating app?
I don't have a dating app anymore.
I don't have any.
Have you met her recently?
I met her at Star Beach.
But I don't have any experience with her.
Have you met her often?
Yes, I have.
How many people did you meet?
I met her, but she wasn't very pretty.
She looked like Suzuki Yami.
And then I met a person who was a bachelor.
You're a man of face, right?
When I heard about you, I thought you were like a Madonna.
That was when I was young.
That's why I'm like that.
Where is your company?
It's in Okinawa, right?
Like this?
I'm like this. I'm really like this.
I'm like this in a bar.
Where is your company?
My company is Ile.
I'm Ile.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
Scary, scary, scary.
What is the best date plan you have?
When I'm drinking, I get scolded.
I was told to accept it, but in the end, the girl on the other side of the street became a M and I was on the bed.
You can't say that.
But I was on a date. I drank at a bar.
I see.
I'll ask you again, but what is the best date plan for Komewarashi?
At night, he'll do something like a monkey dance.
And then, he'll hold me by my neck and pull me.
Women are pretty strong, but they'll be M's on the bed.
Hmm...
How is it?
What?
That's the worst!
There's a girl I like.
What do you mean by you like her?
There are many things.
I like her.
You like her?
Well...
It's a language barrier.
After that, Komiya's drinking pace has been accelerated.
Because he's getting drunk, Komiya has ordered something.
Can I have a cigarette?
I'll do it if I get drunk.
I'm always getting it from my juniors.
I'll give you a cigarette.
Thank you.
He gave me a cigarette that he prepared in a hurry, and the interview was about the looks of the senior comedian.
Well, Mr. Tunnel is cool, but Mr. Uchan, Mr. Downtown, and Mr. Uchan, even if they're not that cool, they're popular.
You made me understand.
Isn't it cool? The people I just talked to.
Who?
Mr. Tunnel, Mr. Tunnel, Mr. Uchan, Mr. Downtown.
I think Tunnel is cool. He's very cool and tall.
Dantan-san, Uchan-nanchan-san, aren't they cool?
If I say Uchan-nanchan-san, Uchan is cool.
Other than that, he's not cool.
But he's not cool.
He's not cool at all.
He's not cool.
You're not a man?
You're a man?
I'm not a man.
You're not a man?
What do you think is cool about him?
He has a mole on his nose.
I just noticed that.
What about you, Kanda?
Isn't he cool?
He's not that tall.
You're right.
I'm small, right?
I'm just tall and cool.
Is that all?
Tall and cool is equal to cool, right?
I'm going to die.
I'm going to die now.
14 hours have passed since the beginning of the interview.
It's been 14 hours.
He's going to go back to his room and rest soon.
The interview will resume.
Next time.
Excuse me.
You changed?
From me.
Yes, I changed.
I think women are better.
That's right.
In terms of mood and mood.
Well, I'm a soft person.
Are you happier when women come to you?
Yes, they say that.
Yes.
Then, let's continue.
What kind of person do you want to see in the entertainment world?
I want to see a person who is still drinking.
Where do you want to end your job?
I want to go to the Tokyo Yoka.
Who is the senior you respect?
I think it's Rega.
What kind of story do you tell?
I tell her that I borrowed her glasses and she didn't wear them.
Oh, really?
You're going to go with your senior's invitation?
Yes, I'm going.
How many times do you want to continue being a fan?
60 years old.
60 years old?
Why are you 60 years old?
I want to be with you.
You can't get it at 60.
I'm 65.
He's starting to get tired of the endless questions.
I don't know the answer.
Then...
Can't we take a break?
Do we have to do this for 9 hours?
We took a lot of questions.
Are you sure you are doing this seriously?
Yes, we are.
I thought we would do it well.
We can do it.
Because the amount of questions is too much.
What is this tone?
Why does it have to be like this?
What is that?
Is it done by an incompetent staff?
It's a long story.
Then I'll continue.
Did you hear?
Listen to me.
I don't know the answer.
Let's talk.
If you don't have a nod,
There are many types of people.
What is it?
Scary.
I'll shoot it with my eyes.
It's stuck.
It's angry.
Is it about the grave after death?
Let's just die.
15 hours have passed since the interview started.
He doesn't let his tiredness go, but he refreshes himself with a test.
Komiyama-san, while you are getting a massage, please continue to tell us your story.
What is the most memorable thing about the formation of Sanshiro?
Please tell us more about it.
I want to be friends with her.
What is your relationship with your partner, Aida?
We are friends now, but we will always be friends.
After 20 minutes, Komiya is completely silent.
Komiya-san, please open your eyes.
I'm not going to open my eyes.
He's a manga-taro.
A manga-taro.
He's scared even though he's getting a massage.
He's really scared.
I'm the best.
You're the best.
16 hours have passed since the interview started.
Wow, amazing.
16?
3 minutes left.
8 hours left until the interview.
8 hours?
How do you feel about looking back so far?
You've been answering the interview so far.
Wait a minute.
Your phone...
How is it?
Please show me your phone.
I can't even understand the time. It's hard.
He can't accept the remaining time.
He's making a fuss.
8 hours left.
Wait a minute.
I'm waiting.
What?
Why don't you sit down and continue with your interview?
No, no, OK, OK.
Let me just show her my phone.
We only introduce you to her through interviews and this is all there is to say.
By Ingredience, yes.
By Cond dólares?
Yes, this is all there is to say.
By Cond PTSIUS.
camp?
Withhhhhhh woke-up
Don't put your Unfortunately to the test!
You have a right to find out, first of all.
So I have your Cats Simon?
Not at all.
Then why did you come out?
You were told to come out, right?
You don't have any power, right?
No, I don't have any power.
So how much longer do you have?
I'm telling you to look at your phone.
Why did you go somewhere?
Anyway, let's continue.
It's already exhausted.
How to get through?
What is the most important thing in your life?
My core.
Compared to Hamada-san.
You're saying that you're a good son.
I think my core is my core.
What do you think about the fact that you're becoming a YouTuber?
I feel lonely when I watch TV.
But I think it's okay.
I think it's fun.
Do you have any memorable love songs?
Hello Again
What kind of memories do you have of that song?
It's a song about a girl I liked and a girl I loved singing along with me
I was cheating on her
I was in trouble
Why?
I was at home, and there was a girl, and I didn't have a cell phone, so I said,
Can I use my cell phone?
I said, sure, and I looked at the screen, and I saw my name on the screen.
It was GEO's Higashi Nakane.
I thought, what is this?
And then I walked away.
I don't want to be in the same situation as you.
The interview continues.
Komiya answers seriously.
There are only 2 hours left.
While the staff is still in a daze,
Finally, this man.
Mr. Komiya.
I'm so tired.
One more minute until the 24-hour time limit.
He drinks a nutritious drink to get rid of his drowsiness.
And it's 9 a.m.
There's only one hour left.
Let's do our best with Dustspout.
If you could grant 3 wishes of the Lamp of the Magic, what would you wish for?
Hmm...
I wish for a blood transfusion,
a cure for my tooth condition,
and a cure for my hay fever.
When do you think Rock died?
Hmm...
Probably when Sid Vicious died.
Do you like Sex Pistols?
Yes, I like Sex Pistols and Japanese Rock.
Gagaga Special, and Ginnan Boys.
So you have a rocker side?
Yes, I think I'm a rocker in a sense.
I think my lifestyle is similar to rock.
What would you name yourself if you were to become a pro-wrestler?
I'd name myself Masuku the Komiya.
Looking back on this 24 hour interview, what would you name yourself?
What would I name myself?
I've talked about a lot of things, but I'm not lying.
I was tired, but I think I was just playing around.
I'm sorry.
Up to this point, he has answered 2837 questions.
And finally, the time has come.
This will be the last question.
What is your life like after 24 hours?
I don't think I gave up.
But I think it was rock.
I don't know what I'm saying.
I think it's time.
Sorry, you have 24 hours.
How do you feel now?
I'm happy.
I really did it for real.
I'm sorry.
Well, that's how it is.
We've seen everything.
I thought it was 8 hours, but he slept that long.
It was really scary.
I thought it was about 5 hours.
The interviewer said that the male person didn't fit the story.
I didn't know that.
It was too early.
Maybe he said it because he wanted to make people feel annoyed.
Well...
Yama-chan, you don't know.
If you do it for 21 hours, you'll get angry.
I'm serious.
Everyone is serious.
I'm serious too.
But I think Shimo is more amazing.
I see.
He's called Tokoyakuza.
I've never heard of it.
Is that a word?
It's not a verb.
Of course it's not a verb.
I don't know.
If you search, you can find it.
Usually, he is a high school student, but he is on the bed, and he is in front of the toilet, and he is in the toilet.
In the toilet?
Stop saying that.
In the toilet, it's OK.
It's OK, but I don't care.
I don't care.
And he is very particular about his position.
I don't like that part.
You just made it come out medic, so I wonder if that person has qualifications or not, and then you said you don't have qualifications, so you're looking crazy
They're next to you
They're in front.
So what's that person doing in the room, he's looking COVID
So you don't have qualifications
I don't even have that right to say that
I think that someone doesn't have qualifications, they would often
see that, if they have qualifications
If you have qualifications, then..
I know
You can't get a good shot without a G.
Then what do you think people with G are doing?
People without G are coming out.
People with G are...
G G, shut up!
Shut up!
That's not true.
People without G are coming out.