I'm Nitta, the child's servant.
I'm Nitta the coordinated thief!
Today we're going to coordinate with Nitta.
I'm getting tired of that costume.
It's not funny at all.
Do you have it?
Yes.
This 20,000 yen you gave me.
20,000 yen.
I have 20,000 yen each.
We're going to buy it again.
We'll take 20 minutes to find Nitta's clothes.
That's right.
Let's call Nitta.
Nitta-kun.
Yes.
You don't like it?
No, no.
Say more.
Yes.
Nitta also wore this costume when he was in 6th grade.
He was wearing a lot of clothes.
Finally, this is graduation.
I'm going to be a manager from today.
When he came in this costume, I was shocked.
What kind of coordination do you want?
I want him to be cool.
I want him to look good in this costume.
You're talking too much.
Don't talk too much.
I'm going to coordinate with Nitta for 20 minutes.
I don't like women's costumes, but I'll try it on.
This costume is made of fabric.
It's wrapped around my body like an Indian.
It's called French Ligarage.
It's 1,900 yen.
It's the same as underwear, but it's only 20,000 yen.
How much is the fabric alone?
It's more than 200,000 yen.
It's only 20,000 yen.
Do you have any pants?
Do you have any flashy pants?
Anyone can wear this.
I'm hungry.
Let's go.
Do you have 240 yen?
I wonder what Hamada is going to do.
B21.
That's not it.
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best for B21.
Now, let's announce the winner.
You're taking too long.
I don't care how long it takes.
I want you to see the Nitta I've been working on.
I've been working on it.
I want you to look at me from the side.
Nitta, please come out.
Thank you very much.
Is this really 20,000 yen?
I only have 240 yen.
That's cool.
It looks similar.
I don't think we'll be able to say what time it is tomorrow.
I wonder what time it is tomorrow.
I think I'm going to hear it from below.
If you turn it around, it's Midranger.
It's like before I die.
I wanted to buy a white enamel because there were two of us.
I've done my best so far.
I wanted a light one.
I've done my best for 20,000 yen.
What Nitta have you completed so far?
I don't have that kind of money.
You don't have it, do you?
I think I'm going to be strong in the countryside.
I helped Nitta a lot.
Nitta was so happy that she looked in the mirror and said,
Is this really me?
That's how she reacted.
Why are you so beautiful?
I don't know what to say.
I left the Egyptian atmosphere.
You left the Egyptian atmosphere?
I think I'll be able to become a face even if I go to a disco.
I see.
I'll look forward to it.
Let's see Mazumoto's performance.
What is this?
You're so cool.
Isn't this a patch?
You're wearing a patch on your head.
This is what a grandmother wears at home.
This is not good.
Is this pants?
This is fashionable.
This is also about the grandmother.
This is her clothes.
This is cool.
This tie is about the same.
This is also about the same.
I want to say the truth.
It's just 20,000 yen.
I see.
That's perfect.
Who is this?
There are two.
Which one will you choose from now on?
Which one? Which one should I choose?
This one.
Not this one.
You were laughing too much.
Why did you do that?
I thought there was a big gap.
I thought you were into it.
I thought you were being tricked.
If it was that one, I thought it was pretty serious.
So, the first Nitta coordinate was chosen by Masumoto-kun.
This one!
I don't know how many episodes will be shown this time.
So, the first Nitta coordinate was chosen by Masumoto-kun.
Congratulations!
Hello.
Today is going to be tough.
What is?
We don't have much time left.
You were like that the other day too.
You were like, let's go home.
That's right. I talked too fast and went home too fast.
I don't mind.
But we have a schedule for the show.
It's a 30-minute show.
The show is about 24 minutes long.
That's right.
So, you have to talk for 24 minutes.
I know.
So, if I don't have much time left and I go home,
I'll be the only one who can talk.
Why?
The other day, you got cut by the delivery guy.
That's right. The Sushi restaurant incident in Hamadake.
The Sushi restaurant guy in Tokyo was angry.
He was late, so he took the sushi.
I said, okay.
I waited.
40 minutes passed.
The Sushi restaurant guy said,
I don't know if I'm on the right path.
I'm going home.
Call me again.
I called him.
He said, I don't know.
He went home.
I said, please go this way.
I said, okay.
20 minutes passed.
I said, I'm going home.
Call me again.
He called me again.
He said, I don't know.
This is how he is.
I don't know.
It's not that I don't know.
His customer is waiting for him.
He lied.
So, we're just going to eat together.
Yes.
Why don't you two make rice for your wife?
That brainless...
Please forgive me. It was late at night.
This is the third time.
I really don't know.
The guest is doing it again.
Please do something like that.
I said while watching TV.
I don't know. I don't know.
I said, I'm done with you.
He said that.
He also has a bad mouth.
I said, I'm done with you.
What is it?
The couple with the reverse seat.
The light went down and the couple didn't come out.
I knew it, but I waited on the table until they came out.
For about five minutes.
The couple was nervous.
Where are you?
I went to the toilet.
I'm not going to the toilet.
They came out for about five minutes.
The couple was nervous.
I thought they came out.
Are you kidding me?
It's a code lesson.
Hey!
You don't know the way.
Why are you making a fuss?
Then I'll do a hundred jobs over there.
What do you think?
Laugh out loud.
You don't know the way.
Why are you making a fuss?
Laugh out loud.
You don't know the way.
Why are you making a fuss?
Laugh out loud.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Then I'm sorry.
Are you kidding me?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You're still talking.
I'm still talking.
This is my hand.
I'm on TV.
What are you talking about?
Let's do it now.
I didn't tell him anything.
He just told me in one try.
It can't be done.
He started were Piglet's place.
I asked him why he didn't kill her.
You were in a taxi, right?
I was eating rice.
I don't know if it was a freshly eaten rice or something.
You were eating rice.
I was eating rice.
When I got in, I was going back and forth.
You were taking a break, right?
You were eating rice.
Yes.
Your legs were like a baka-bon-papa.
That was delicious.
You were in a taxi, right?
You were taking a break, right?
Your legs were like a baka-bon-papa.
That was delicious.
You were like a baka-bon-papa.
You were taking a break, right?
When I asked him if he knew what he was doing,
I was a little confused.
You know what I mean.
You're sighing.
I don't want to. I don't want to ride it.
You don't want to.
You wanted to take a break.
This is my luggage.
That's right.
You wanted to take a break a little more.
Even when it turns.
Kya!
Mori
Wait.
There's a little color.
Are you serious?
You're like this in the back.
It's true.
That's why you're a fool.
The main point is.
It's true.
It's true?
Yes.
It's like this.
I thought, wow, this old man is strong.
And I was riding with a friend.
And when I got there.
I said, please take a break.
Yes.
And when I handed over the money.
I took a lot of money.
No.
It's more than 1,000 yen.
I gave you a little money.
That's right.
I took a lot of money.
The little money fell.
I thought I had to do something about it.
It's true.
I gave you a little money.
And you said, you gave me a little money.
He was angry.
Yes.
It's like this.
It's true.
I wanted to get off there.
He got off.
You.
Apologize.
It's true.
The window is only open from the back.
The driver's seat.
What are you complaining about?
Don't come from Kansai and complain.
You.
Well, it's okay.
You are number one.
It's already over there.
You are the first.
First.
I'm the first.
Kiku-chan.
Hana-chan.
It was a big storm.
For example, if you go to a restaurant and they say there's something in there...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, like, let's just get it for free or something.
Or like, buy it for us or something.
I don't ever say that.
It's bad, you know. You're not doing it knowingly.
I know that, but if there's a small cockroach in there, it won't be a plate, right?
I think I'll probably take it out and eat it and go home.
Oh, really?
There was a time when there was a shell in my ramen.
It was a shell.
You know what a shell is, right?
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's a shell, right?
There's another way to say a shell.
What?
A shell?
You're so mean!
It's hard for us to say that.
A, a, a shell!
You say a shell.
You say a shell, so I don't know.
I'll say it again.
It's a shell.
In your ramen.
There was a shell in it.
A, a, a shell.
It's hard to say.
There was a shell in it.
But I took it out and ate it.
It's a shell.
If it was a shell, it wouldn't be a problem.
It's a shell!
No, it's not.
If you keep saying things like that, the people at the store will feel bad.
It's okay if I don't do it.
You're a student wrestler.
I'm not a wrestler.
I didn't do it because I knew it.
When you make ramen, there's a container that says, ka.
If you put it in, it's okay.
If it was a shell, it would be okay.
If you put it in, it would be okay.
That's right.
If you put it in, it's okay.
What's a shell?
I'm sorry.
If you put it in, it's okay.
If it was a shell, it would be okay.
You're still a student wrestler.
I'm not a wrestler.
There was a streetcar in Osaka.
We were two people, and we were going to work.
We were stepped on, so I came to you, and I stepped on you.
You came to me, and you stepped on me.
We were standing like this.
It hurts, doesn't it?
We were checking each other.
It hurt.
I don't know if he noticed, but we were trying to go to the other car.
We were walking, and we were walking together.
We were walking together.
I don't know anything about that.
We were two people, and we were walking together.
It hurts.
I don't know anything about that.
I clearly remember this.
Let's go to the post office.
Post office.
Yes.
The costume has changed from today.
It's the same as when we met in the opening.
Yes.
Please go home.
We don't have much time, so let's move on.
The author is Tomoko Kayano from Yokohama City.
He's a 19-year-old student.
Good evening.
I have a question for you.
When you were in middle school, you ran down Rokkou Farm and almost died.
Why did you run down? Tell us.
We were walking, and we were walking.
We made it ourselves.
We were wearing jerseys.
We were in middle school.
We were walking up Rokkou Mountain.
We were crossing the road.
It's all farmland.
It's a beautiful place.
The slope is really steep.
There are sheep below us.
The herd of sheep passes through.
It's a fun place to bring children.
We were playing on the slope.
Why did you run?
To catch the monster.
To catch the monster?
Yes.
We were chased.
We ran into the slope.
It was a steep slope.
I was screaming, but he couldn't stop.
I was the boss.
He ran away, and I thought, wow, this guy is fast.
He made me run.
I thought, what is this guy?
From behind, it was really funny.
He was like this.
My legs couldn't reach him because of the speed.
And you hit the tree.
I didn't hit the tree.
You hit the tree.
I was screaming.
I was about to run into the sheep.
It was after the rain, so my legs slipped.
The sheep was right in front of me.
At that time, I really thought I was going to die.
That's right.
You had to be careful.
You were saved.
Thank you very much.
17 prefectures, Saitama prefecture.
What? 17 prefectures, Saitama prefecture?
No, no, no.
17 prefectures, Saitama prefecture.
17 prefectures?
I've never heard of it.
Good evening, Mr. Matsumoto. How are you?
What prefecture are you from?
17 prefectures.
Mr. Matsumoto has a wife, so it doesn't matter.
Please tell me the type of woman you like.
Who do you like?
I don't like her.
Who do you like as a celebrity?
I don't like her now.
I like Misako Konno.
That's a little...
What?
Why?
She has a bad temper.
I like her.
I also like Maako Hido.
What?
Why are you so obsessed with the puberty type?
I don't like it.
I like the puberty type.
I like her.
I remember.
What?
Chisato Muritaka.
When I went to work the other day, I had time.
I took out my wallet and said,
Hey, what?
I took out 10,000 yen from my wallet.
What?
A young girl came and said,
I went to the record store and said,
Muritaka Land.
That CD or something.
I don't like it.
Yes, that's why.
Thank you very much for today.
Is it over?
What?
You should have left it here at first.
That's why.
Is it time?
Yes, it's time.
I see.
Thank you very much.
I'm sweating.
Why?
I'm sorry.
That's all.
Yes.
Have a good time.
Thank you very much.
Today, we finished the first episode of Muritaka Land.
Is it over?
Yes.
That's right.
If it's over, it's over all the time.
I wonder.
It's okay.
One more thing.
Even though it was released today,
I don't think there's anything good about the audience's reaction.
I wonder if it's okay.
Is there anything else?
What?
Oh, the assistant.
I have to put in an assistant.
From now on.
Is it a woman?
Of course.
I'll ask for a good one.
That's right.
It's not like the companion of Atami.
I wonder what happened.
No, it's okay because it's not on the screen.
That fat guy.
Yes.
So what?
Such a fat guy.
Two people came to the party.
I wonder if it's okay.
No, it's not like the companion of Atami.
Wait a minute.
I'll ask for a good one.
Is that all right?
Yes.
Let it flow.
That's it for this week.
Until next week.
Goodbye.
This program was brought to you by TANRAKUTO.