In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai, Chikichiki!
Yamasaki Hosei's drinking habits thoroughly verified!
Today is going to be a terrible day.
Oh really?
It's been many years since Gaki no Tsukai started.
To be honest, there have been times when I've slipped, right?
Well, well, well.
How do I say this?
If you go to an old place, you're a Tsukkomi robot.
Even now...
Even if you just remember that...
There are times when you wake up sweating.
But today, I don't think it's going to be like that.
I'm not sure about this, but...
I think it's going to be a terrible 30 minutes.
Oh really?
Hasn't it happened before?
No, it hasn't.
A few weeks ago, about 3 weeks ago,
Yamasaki had a bad drinking habit.
At the end of the show,
he invited Kokoriko and the broadcaster Takatsu
and made them go out for drinks.
They were secretly recording it.
They were doing it like,
if it's an interesting part, I'll use it.
When I saw that,
something amazing happened.
Something amazing happened.
It's like,
it's a good idea to start our show like that.
For the time being, I'd like you to watch this part.
I have to tell you what it's going to be like for the next 30 minutes.
It's illegal.
Do you come here often?
I'm sorry, Mr. Takatsu.
This is the 4th time.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you.
Did you really do it?
No, not yet.
But I've been doing it since now.
Did you drink Nakai Konsen?
I drank Nakai Konsen a few weeks ago.
I was wearing Shimarade and Nakai Konsen.
Which one is your favorite?
My favorite is Kakiri, Nakai Konsen, and X.
All of them?
Yes.
But I can't wear it like this anymore.
At first, it was just Kaki.
But I think it's getting bigger.
But I don't know when it's going to die.
It's definitely going to die.
This is definitely going to die.
Really?
This is going to die.
Did something happen?
No, it's not that it's going to die.
I think it's going to die.
My stomach is starting to hurt.
Everyone says that it's not going to die.
My stomach is hurting.
What is health?
It's like this.
When we wake up in the morning,
we get really angry.
What is that?
That's health.
What do you think?
I don't think it's going to die.
It's not going to die.
Yes, it's not going to die.
If I say that it's not going to die,
I'll probably say,
please give me 10 million yen.
If you say that it's not going to die,
won't you lend me money?
I won't lend it to you.
Really?
I'm not going to lend it to you.
What if I ask you?
If you say that it's not going to die?
What if I ask you to lend me 10 million yen?
I won't lend it to you.
Really?
One shot.
Come on, drink it.
Mr. Takasu, just drink it.
Just drink it.
Excuse me, water.
Yes.
Please give me some water.
Are you going to drink it?
I'm not going to drink it.
I'm drinking spicy food,
but Mr. Takasu isn't drinking it at all.
I'm drinking it.
I don't care.
I'm not drinking it.
You're drinking it.
It's love.
I'm not going to drink it anymore.
I don't want to drink it anymore.
Yes.
Mr. Takasu, are you finished drinking it?
And certain eindhoven.
Just drink one thing of this, please.
I can't drink it.
Just drink one.
At this rate,
I can't drink it Stop drinking.
Drink one, at this rate,
I can't drink it with you guys.
You're the best!
Thank you!
Yeah!
I'm the best, right?
Yeah.
I'm the best.
You're the best.
I think you're a little different from the last time.
Why are you always dressed like a girl?
You're always dressed like a girl.
It's like a video game.
It's good.
I don't like you guys trying to eat me up.
What are you talking about?
What do you mean?
You guys are trying to eat me up.
We're not.
I'm not.
I'm not trying to do anything.
You guys are saying that I'm a bully.
I'm a bully.
You only did the opening for two episodes.
I'm not a bully.
Are you sure?
Go home.
I'm not a bully.
I'm going home.
Sit down.
I've been preparing so much for the two episodes.
This guy is weird.
Where are you going?
I'm not saying anything.
Everyone likes you.
I love you.
Dantan-san too.
Yes.
Shiba-san too.
Everyone likes you.
Why do you have to buy today's opening?
Why do you have to buy today's show?
I'm not doing anything.
Everyone says that I'm a bully.
You're acting strangely.
I'm acting strangely.
I've been acting strangely lately.
Are you not satisfied?
I'm not satisfied.
Are you not satisfied with the show?
I'm not satisfied with the show.
What are you not satisfied with?
I want to talk all the time.
This is over.
Next.
What are you not satisfied with?
I can't talk.
You can't talk.
Why do you have the right to say that?
It's you.
Do you want to talk?
I want to talk.
I'm a kid.
If you don't have a number, how many numbers can you get?
I have a number.
Do you have a number?
If you don't have a number, you can't go home.
What are you doing?
Do you have a number?
I have a number.
I'm not sure about that.
If I talk, I'll get over 20%.
What if you don't get it?
I can't think of not getting it.
Do you mean you'll get over 20%?
I'll get it.
Can you really get it?
Really?
You're an idiot.
How many years do you think I've been doing this?
Go home.
I'll go home.
I don't want to go home.
Let's go.
I'll go home.
I'll take you home.
Go home.
Let's go.
Why did you throw it?
It's like this.
He said he wants to do it instead of us. If I do it, I can get 20%.
He has given up.
I'm sorry to the winner.
I don't have any extravagance.
Let's call him.
Here he is. The funny comedian.
The funny comedian of the century.
Here he is.
He is very excited.
This will be the opening, right?
Yes.
After this, we will go out.
What will you do?
Yamasaki will do it.
I've thought about it.
I think you should do it.
You said it.
I've thought about it.
I woke up today and I was worried.
I thought I'd run away.
There is a TV station in Izumi.
But I came.
You came.
You have a sense of responsibility.
I have a sense of responsibility.
It's amazing that I can do this.
If I do it, I can get 20%.
I'll leave the talk to you.
Tell me one thing.
How should I do it?
It's a big question.
Just tell me what you think.
It's funny.
I've never thought about it.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
I'm going to do what I usually do.
Stop it.
Are you okay?
No.
It's about to start.
Stop it.
Wait a minute.
I'm waiting.
You said you were confident.
You said it yourself.
No.
I don't like it.
Are you still sleeping?
Yes.
Are you going to run away again?
I'm going to run away.
Let's do it.
I don't care.
Yes, please.
I'm going.
Excuse me.
Are you okay?
What?
I'm not okay.
Are you okay?
Ladies and gentlemen.
There he is! There he is! The funny comedian of the end of the century!
Good evening. Today, I'd like everyone to touch my charm even just a little bit.
Now, let's do our best together!
It's about... It's about an hour and a half!
One hour and a half! I'm going to talk for an hour and a half!
I'm going to make you all fall into my trap!
Now, let's get started.
Recently, I've been...
Um... Wait a minute.
I don't know what I was trying to say.
Recently, I've been really angry.
Um... I don't know how everyone is doing these days, but I've been really angry.
I've been really angry.
I'm sorry, but I've lost all of my energy.
What do I do? What do I do?
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, but I've lost all of my energy.
Your face is really stiff, and the audience has noticed how stiff your face is.
The audience is nervous, too.
Oh, really?
This is the worst.
That's right.
Thank you.
Your face is even scarier now.
I think it was better the way it was before.
Let's do our best today.
Today, I'm going to make you laugh with my stand-up comedy.
Let's go up.
Today, I've been really angry.
I've been really angry.
I have a weak body, so I get sick easily.
Once, I did something called the colon fiber.
Do you know what that is?
The colon fiber is really painful.
I looked at my stomach, and my stomach started to hurt.
My stomach started to hurt, and I didn't know why, so I did the colon fiber.
The colon fiber is really painful.
I put a cord like this in my butt.
But the cord doesn't go in as it is, so I put air in it and put the cord in.
It hurts so much.
It's okay if it hurts, but it's really embarrassing.
I put air in it, and the air comes out.
I thought it was really embarrassing.
There are a lot of things that make me angry.
When I go to Roppongi, I get angry.
There was a foreigner, a black man, who was really scary.
The black man was really scary, so he said,
You idiot!
I don't know if you're scary or not.
I had a lot of feelings like that.
I'm sorry.
My mother and father are funny people.
I've changed a little.
My parents have changed.
I was in a comedy called Team Zero.
I won the rookie award at the ABC competition.
I was nervous because I didn't think I'd get it.
The best rookie award at the ABC competition is...
The best rookie award is Team Zero!
My father stood up and said,
He stood up and said,
You idiot!
I still don't know what that means.
Now, show me your teeth.
Why?
This is a question for Mr. Yamazaki, who has fought various monsters on various shows.
Please tell me how to make it easier for lions.
I don't know what's going to happen in the 21st century from now on.
I'd like to tell you how to make it easier for lions when they're attacked by lions.
There's a lion, right?
There's a lion!
I don't need these teeth.
I've never met a lion before.
Are you stupid?
I'm not stupid.
For example,
I'm sure you'll be able to laugh no matter what the situation is.
My girlfriend always asks me to laugh because she thinks it's funny.
I'm an amateur, so I often slip.
So, Mr. Yamazaki,
Please imitate something that never slips no matter what the situation is.
This is good.
This is the first time I've ever revealed this.
I'm sure you'll be able to laugh no matter what the situation is.
First of all, I'll imitate Adachi Yumi.
If you're going to show sympathy, give me money!
That was really...
Are you really stupid?
I'm sure you'll be able to laugh no matter what the situation is.
Please remember this.
Imitate Hiroko Yakushima.
Eh?
Speed!
Wake me up!
What are you doing?
Do your best!
I can't do this anymore.
Now, let's move on to the Q&A section.
This is the real deal.
Where did he go?
He ran away.
You can't go to the bathroom all of a sudden.
You!
Why are you running away?
Hey!
Stop it!
You scared me!
Why are you running away?
What's wrong?
I can't do this anymore.
You're a scary man!
Do you understand?
Are you leaving?
Wait!
Ose!
No!
Calm down!
I can't do this anymore!
But you have a phone!
Really?
Well, it's a lie.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.