Good or bad, it's up to you!
This is terrible!
My sons are in trouble!
Shall we go now?
Let's go!
First of all...
Shut up!
I won't start!
First of all...
Hey, Futsuo!
Futsuo!
Yes!
What is it, dad?
Futsuo!
Yes?
Why didn't you tell your dad?
You threw the cigarette away in the toilet, didn't you?
I'm sorry, dad.
What?
I thought it would be nice if your cigarette was even one less.
I...
Futsuo!
I was thinking about your dad's health.
I'm sorry, dad.
Futsuo!
What is it, dad?
Yes?
You...
What is it?
You threw the cigarette away in the toilet, didn't you?
What?
What are you talking about?
Why do I have to do such a thing, dad?
Why did the white smoke come out of the toilet?
Dad, I'm sorry to say this, but...
That white smoke is not a cigarette.
What?
It's the smoke of my poop.
It can't be helped.
I'm sorry.
Go home.
Hey, Futsuo!
Yes?
You were hiding from your dad and throwing the cigarette away, weren't you?
Why?
No, it's okay.
I see.
Go home.
You shouldn't smoke.
Close the door.
Hurry up and close the door.
I'm in trouble.
I can't close it.
I'm sorry.
Who the hell are you?
Hey, Futsuo!
Futsuo!
Yes?
What?
I think dinner is ready.
What's for dinner tonight?
What?
I knew it.
Come in, come in, come in, come in.
Hamburger?
Stop it if you're embarrassed.
What?
Futsuo!
Futsuo, come out again.
What's for dinner tonight?
Come in, come in, come in, come in.
Don't be so loud.
Are you a little embarrassed?
Futsuo!
Yes?
What's the matter, dad?
I think dinner is ready.
What's for dinner tonight?
Today's menu is...
Marmalade-style...
What?
I think dinner is ready.
What's for dinner tonight?
Dinner?
This is my recent dinner.
I put a page here.
You know why I put a page here, don't you?
I don't like dirty jokes.
Don't say stupid things.
Right?
You're a bad guy.
Next work.
Hey, Futsuo!
What's the matter, dad?
Futsuo, it's...
It's a new year.
Think about it.
The one who worked hard for a year last year was downtown, wasn't it?
I think it was Nan-chan.
That's right, dad.
What?
You can ask the customers.
Who thinks it's downtown?
Who thinks it's Nan-chan?
Come here!
Futsuo!
Don't say such a thing.
Who thinks it's Denden?
Hey!
Yoshio!
Yes?
What's the matter, dad?
It's a different story.
What?
The one who worked hard for a year last year was downtown, wasn't it?
I think it was Nan-chan.
That's right, dad.
What?
It's definitely downtown, isn't it?
The staff also cooperated, didn't they?
Warubo!
Yes?
The one who worked hard for a year last year was downtown, wasn't it?
I think it was Nan-chan.
Yes?
Who thinks it's Denden?
It's not Denden.
It's Konstantin.
The last one!
Futsuo!
What's the matter, dad?
What are your favorite words?
Well, I love the Giant Army.
Like Nakashima-senshu said, the Giant Army is immortal.
Right?
Did you just say the name?
The name of the name is...
Well, whatever.
Yoshio!
What's the matter, dad?
What's the matter, Yoshio?
What are your favorite words?
Well, I'm a genius, so geniuses come when they are forgotten.
It's not a big deal, though.
Well, I'm glad it was fast.
Warubo!
Nanji!
Tabitabi Nanji!
Tabitabi?
What's the matter? What are your favorite words?
What?
What are your favorite words?
That's not it.
Well, it's not that. It's your favorite word.
Kamishihougatame!
That's a good one.
It's your favorite word.
It's a four-letter word.
A four-letter word?
Gaden, gaden, minsui.
It's a four-letter word like that.
Daisuke Hanako.
Tonight, we're going to have a ginden show!
Ladies and gentlemen.
Good evening.
You're here.
What is it?
You're here, so say more.
It's like a hotel.
It's the first time.
It's the first time?
Why?
My outfit today certainly looks like Frankenstein.
If you don't like it, don't wear it.
I don't care.
The stylist is going to think of this as me.
But that's...
The stylist is going to wear the clothes prepared by you.
I really don't know.
If I don't like it even a little bit, I don't like it.
You're going to step on the kindness of that person.
Are you kidding me?
Seriously.
I thought this was good, so she prepared it.
I know that.
But I'm the one who's going to wear it.
The people watching the TV are going to say,
Ah, it's the clothes that Mach-chan is wearing.
That's true.
It's like I chose it myself.
That's why I was told,
This is Hamada-san.
If you think this is expensive,
You can wear your own clothes.
That's right.
If you think about it.
So the people watching the TV,
This is all my hobby.
If you go to a clothing store and look for it yourself,
You'll think about it a lot.
There's something terrible about it.
This is wrong.
You really need to understand this.
That's right.
I thought it was written on the paper that it was wrong.
That's why,
On TV, everyone...
What was the name of my stylist?
Um...
Nakasone.
That's not it.
What's Nakasone?
I don't even know the real name.
Why are you laughing?
I don't even know the metaphor.
I know it's wrong.
Isn't it Uesugi?
Yes, it's Uesugi.
What's Nakasone?
You're the first one to laugh here.
There's the real thing.
There's a lie.
It's a lie because I know the real thing.
What are you guys?
Nakasone.
I don't need a comment.
What's Uesugi?
I know he's doing his best, but...
If you bring it to me and tell me it's wrong,
I'm going to get mad.
I'm going to do my best so that I can get the next one to come.
Right?
That's right.
I'm tired.
I'm so tired.
How many times do you think about it?
How was it?
I had a hard time when I thought it was okay.
It's Konno Blazer.
The sleeves are like this.
That's right.
The waist is like this.
It's like Yasu-san.
No, no, no.
There's another one.
He's...
We can't fix it.
On the contrary.
If you leave it alone, Yasu-san will bring it to you anytime.
Well, that's fine.
What did you do on New Year's Day?
Quite a lot.
No, it's nothing.
I had a bad New Year's Day.
What?
It was on the second day of the New Year's holiday.
My bicycle was stolen.
I couldn't afford a bicycle.
Which one is on the second day of the New Year's holiday?
It was on the second day of the New Year's holiday.
My bicycle was stolen.
I couldn't afford a bicycle.
I went home and stole it from Yuta.
Your father?
My father.
I thought I had to go to the police.
I had a registration number.
I should have had a reason to do that.
I looked for it, but I couldn't find it.
If you say that suddenly,
you'll be locked up in a cell.
And what did my father do?
He came.
He was the best.
Well...
Don't say that.
He was the best.
I thought I had a reason to do that.
I had a registration number.
I should have had a reason to do that.
I looked for it, but I couldn't find it.
Don't say that.
I don't understand because you're doing that.
I went to the temple.
I was beaten by my mother.
Because of my mother.
I have a screw in my head.
I said, it hurts!
But he hit my father again.
I said, what are you doing?
He hit me like this.
It was the worst.
It was hell.
He stopped my brother.
What did you do?
What?
What did you see?
I was like this all the time.
It was your fault that we had a fight.
What?
You were the one who got hit.
But it wasn't easy.
My father didn't hit the temple.
You shouldn't hit your mother's temple in front of your son.
Mother?
You're a beautiful woman.
What are you talking about?
In slow motion.
I was like this.
What should I do?
But it's not a big deal now.
I don't think it's a big deal.
I haven't seen you for a long time.
I go home sometimes.
What?
The other day.
I went home.
I was going to go home this year.
I was going to go home in two days.
I was going to go home.
You had two days off.
Yes.
I was sleeping in the morning.
I got a call.
I was wondering who it was.
It was my mother.
She said,
It's been a long time.
You're so brave.
She said,
Happy New Year.
I was surprised.
Why?
Seriously.
I was scared.
Why?
My mother's mother.
What should I say?
I was scared.
I don't want to see you anymore.
I don't talk much.
Yes.
Your father is a bad guy.
Sometimes.
He's desperate to make things better.
I know that.
What do you mean by bad guy?
Your father is trying to make you look like a bad guy.
I don't know about that.
You're talking like that.
It doesn't matter.
But you're asking me something good.
What is it?
So,
What are you wearing?
Your hair?
Why is it so shiny?
What's wrong?
It doesn't matter.
So,
I thought you had a way to answer.
I don't know if it's the right answer.
It's so annoying.
It's like,
Is this leather?
That's it.
I don't know if it's the right answer.
You can just go home after a day.
My sister is,
She's funny.
She's good at laughing.
Really?
Yes.
I used to laugh a lot.
Your sister?
Yes.
About 20 years ago,
She was on the phone.
Her sister was on the phone.
Hello?
Is it your mother?
Please wait a moment.
Your mother is on the phone.
Who is it?
Beans?
What is it?
Hello?
It's Mr. Endo.
Did you go home?
I didn't go home.
So,
When you go home tomorrow,
You said tomorrow.
You're talking like that.
When you go home tomorrow,
You said you would go home.
What are you talking about?
You said you would go home tomorrow.
I don't care about you.
I'm talking to you.
I'll go home.
I'm sorry.
Please don't go home.
I'm frustrated.
I'll never go home.
I'll go home.
It's hot.
What were you doing on New Year's Day?
What?
I don't want to do anything.
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
Are you going to go home?
Don't go home.
If you want to ask me something, ask me.
What do you want to ask me?
What are you wearing?
This is Long Keep Gel.
It's been a long time since I applied it in the morning.
You applied it in the morning and left it as it is?
That's right.
You didn't apply anything?
This is...
Is this just beautiful?
That's right. This is beautiful.
How much is this?
How much did you apply?
This is 80,000 yen.
This is 80,000 yen?
Do you shave your beard?
When did you shave your beard?
What?
I shaved my beard today.
You have a lot of beard.
This...
What happened to your beard?
Please come out.
Hello.
You don't have a lot of beard.
What's your name?
I'm from Tokyo.
Can you lower it a little more?
What?
Then it's fine.
Why do you look like you're going to cry?
It's fine even if I lower it this much.
Stop talking.
What's wrong with you?
Thank you very much.
Hey.
What is this?
I'm having a great time with my family.
A lot of idols and stars are releasing photos.
How about you, Mr. Down Town,
releasing a photo album of your downtown?
I've released it before.
Really?
A photo album.
How is it?
It's good.
You don't think it's funny to release a photo album?
What the hell?
That's what I'm saying.
It's fine if you draw it the way you want it.
You don't have to do it like this.
Don't tell me you're going to quit.
I'm sorry.
But I can't take it off unless it's Shinoyama Kishin.
Are you a model?
What are you talking about?
If it's Shinoyama Kishin, I'll leave it to you.
Let's see.
You can't draw?
You're saying that the first class is better.
Let's try it.
Let's take a picture.
Really?
Let's try.
I can't do it unless I'm in a studio.
I can't do it outside.
There's a
I can't do it unless I'm in a studio.
I can't do it outside.
Why?
I'm really weak against fire.
Right?
I can't open my eyes when I'm outside.
I'm strong.
I'm serious.
I can't go to the zoo with three, four, or five animals.
You're smiling and smiling.
I can't take a picture of me smiling and smiling in front of a lion.
I can't take a picture of me going to the zoo with three animals.
Because it's too bright.
I can't do it.
You're going to try again.
I can't take a picture of me going to the zoo with three animals.
I can't do it.
I can't go to the zoo with three animals.
Are you a barbarian?
Look at that.
It's white.
I'm angry.
Let's think about it.
Let's take a picture.
Let's do it today.
I didn't sleep today.
I don't know.
You played with me.
I'm not feeling well.
You?
You.
I really don't know.
You don't know what?
What?
You had a dream, didn't you?
I didn't dream.
Were you worried?
I went to the apartment on purpose.
I said I wouldn't come out even if I played the guitar.
I thought I was going to die.
I don't know why, but I was hanging on the balcony.
I was hanging on the balcony.
I thought I was going to die.
I was worried.
Why did you go?
I thought I was going to die.
Hello.
That's it.
Let's do our best this year.
What?
It's a program.
It has a meaning.
Let's do various programs and do various things.
I see.
Last year, we cooperated with everyone.
Everyone who watches TV cooperated with us.
We did various things.
Let's do our best this year.
That's right.
And...
The assistant is no longer...
What?
Assistant?
I've been using a professional recently.
Let's use a handsome guy.
What are you talking about?
What?
A handsome guy?
I'm a handsome guy.
It's not funny.
What?
Even if a man wears it?
Even if a woman wears it, it's funny.
Don't say that.
Women are more funny.
That's it.
We can't use a guy.
Let's do our best this year.
Give me your hand.
Say goodbye.
Open your hand.
Goodbye.