Today we came to Suidobashi.
We came here a long time ago, right?
Yes, it was a great show.
We were judged by such a judge.
I didn't think so.
From Osaka, I was told that it was a pleasant comedy.
Oh, down?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
What?
Let's go.
What do you think of this place?
So...
I think I can hit P-chan with this.
Who are you?
Today's venue is here, right?
No, there's nothing here.
This is the front and back.
This is the back of the stage.
Yes.
Why is this set here?
Why can't I use this?
What are you talking about?
What?
Because you're late.
I'm not late.
You and I will take 20,000 yen each.
We're going to buy Nitta's clothes.
Nitta will change his clothes like this.
First of all, what about the clothes you chose?
What do you think?
Are you laughing?
I'm not laughing.
Next is Matsumoto's.
This is so funny.
This was the opening.
What are you going to do with this?
What?
I lost my job.
Tell me.
It's in my pocket.
There's still a lot of fun today.
As you can see from my attitude,
I don't regret it.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
Today is a quiet place.
That's right.
It's a family atmosphere.
As I said before,
I don't have a low budget program.
I don't have enough money.
That's not true.
I don't have money.
I don't have enough money.
What are you talking about?
You don't have money.
I don't have money.
You're lying.
The time has changed.
I've been doing this for half a year.
I've been talking about it.
Let's talk about the inside.
Can't you say panpanpan?
I don't say panpanpan every week.
It can't be helped.
From now on,
I have to talk about something that everyone will be proud of.
For example, what does it mean?
What?
It's a good story.
What does it mean?
It means that Gorbachev has become president.
Everyone knows that.
And then what?
It's like a cartoon story.
It's like you're being told what to do by Gorbachev.
No matter what Gorbachev says.
That's not true.
What does Gorbachev say?
What do you think about Gorbachev becoming president?
It's a bad movie.
That's not true.
Then wait.
What do you think about Gorbachev becoming president?
It won't be the same as before.
What?
I think so, too.
I've been on the bullet train a lot.
For three hours,
I read books and read newspapers.
I read political articles.
I'm a person who can read.
I don't open my mouth like you do.
I'm not a fool.
I always keep my mouth open.
But your eyes are open when you're sleeping.
Which is more disgusting?
Ask me.
That's more disgusting.
Why?
I was sleeping and I opened my eyes.
Your mouth is open.
That's a sign of a fool.
There are a lot of people who keep their mouths open.
Not just me.
When I first saw you,
I had a cold.
I have a cold.
It's transparent.
I'm scared.
Seriously.
You'll know when you see it.
Are you scared or not?
Why can't I close my mouth?
It's strange.
You're the one who's disgusting.
That's right.
Because your mouth is open.
Your mouth is open.
Your eyes are open.
That's right.
What do you call it?
It can be a movie.
It can't be.
It can't be Zatoichi.
I'm not the one who keeps my mouth open.
It has nothing to do with Zatoichi.
It's when I'm sleeping.
I'm scared.
Your brother will wake up in the middle of the night.
I'm the only one who keeps my mouth open.
Your whole family keeps their mouth open.
Did you see that?
My father is sleeping.
I think I've said this before.
His family has the same face.
His mouth is open.
When I saw his family,
I couldn't breathe well.
Because your mouth is open.
You idiot.
The air in this room is thin.
Why am I the only one who has thin air?
What are you talking about?
I'll introduce you to your father.
He's here.
Matsumoto-san.
His name is Shuko Wada.
It's an interesting name.
Hello, Matsumoto-san and Wada-san.
I don't have a boyfriend.
I'm watching it with my family.
Matsumoto-san and Wada-san said
that they appeared in Mr. Donut's commercial.
I remember it, too.
Please ask the staff to gather them.
Actually,
How many years ago did we appear?
About five or six years ago.
About six years ago.
We appeared in Mr. Donut's commercial.
I prepared it.
Please give it to me.
Don't pay attention to the talent.
Can you see the front?
I told you.
You don't have to do this.
He's good.
I told you.
You don't have to do this.
No one did this.
The other day,
Osaka staff came to Tokyo.
I interviewed them
in Harajuku and Shibuya.
I interviewed them in Harajuku and Shibuya.
They talked badly about you.
They were scared.
They hit the rookies.
It was interpersonal use.
Did you kill him?
They said that.
How could you ask them those questions?
I didn't ask him that.
I didn't say that.
There are many representative
and威elys.
But my создation was really big surprise.
Did you just kick me to death?
This is incredible.
I can't move my hands at all.
Not just my legs.
For some reason.
Why can't I move my hands when it's so hard to kill?
Why can't I only use my lower body?
So that's it.
He just brought the TV.
There are four patterns.
Did you do all four?
Yes.
I think we all forgot about it.
I want to see it too.
Right?
Let's go for now.
You're happy, right?
I want to see it.
It's been six years.
Let's go.
Go ahead.
No matter how you look at it.
It's a rare item.
It's a customer who doesn't know what it is.
I'm sorry I'm a party bot.
It's a rare item after all.
It's a customer who doesn't know what it is.
A box full of happiness.
Do you want to do it or not?
Say something.
You're not a man.
I'll give you a gift.
Donut. Donut.
What's going on?
You don't have to go.
It's a box.
What's going on?
Paparinko glass present.
Donut. Donut.
It's green. It's green.
It's 8 o'clock.
You'll never know.
This and this.
This is Matsumoto.
This is me.
I saw it in the morning.
I can't see the time here.
It says 8 o'clock, 8 o'clock and a half.
That's all.
The first one is young.
It's young.
I'm still a man with a deep hole.
Really.
Young. Young.
I'm a little chubby compared to now.
Is that so?
I was like that at first.
I've lost weight.
It was nostalgic.
You collected it for me.
Thank you very much.
If there's anything else,
I'd like to introduce it on this show.
The monitor came out.
Our director.
I told you at the end.
Do it with a pair of pants.
I bought a pair of pants.
This is live, isn't it?
In the current situation.
Move it a little.
Our Saito is wearing a pair of pants.
This is Saito.
This is the director.
I told you at the end.
Do it with a pair of pants.
I bought a pair of pants.
Please take a look.
This is Saito.
It's funny.
It's a serious face, isn't it?
Who said that?
This is the best.
It's funny.
Do you think everyone is doing it again?
If you wear a pair of pants, it will look like a brief.
It's like Kawamata-kun's brief.
It's amazing.
Look.
This is also like a brief.
I can't wear such a brief today.
It's like this.
It's a beautiful white.
It's dirty.
But you did it.
If you say it, I will do it.
It's natural.
Yes.
Let's do this again.
Let's think about it at the end.
Yes.
It's okay.
Thank you very much.
You did it well.
Who is facing this way?
Let's introduce the manuscript.
Hurry up.
It's disgusting.
Let's introduce it.
First, this person.
This person.
Rather than asking a question, he asked if it was true.
He didn't write his pen name or name at all.
My friend's company's person is from Osaka.
When he was in high school, he said that he was a scary person.
Is it true?
No one approached him, so Hamada-san always took care of him.
What kind of personality was bad?
Was he scary?
Hamada-san, can you tell me?
Please.
I will say it clearly.
When I was in high school, I had a crazy life.
I had a lot of bad thoughts.
It's not true at all.
I like fighting more than eating sandwiches.
It's not true.
Did you join a gang?
Yes, I did.
The person you were riding on was Chappie, right?
The guy who tuned up Chappie, right?
Even if I tuned up Chappie, I was riding on Chappie.
You know my school uniform, right?
The one I wore in middle school.
There is a button here.
No.
You have to use it properly.
Let me tell you a story.
I was really popular in middle school.
I was popular.
Life is about me.
When I graduated, the button was really gone.
Tell me the truth.
I really don't know.
All of my buttons are gone.
I don't know.
Which one of us was popular in middle school?
Tell me the truth.
I wasn't popular.
But you weren't popular either.
I was really popular.
You were really cool back then.
But you had dark hair back then.
You had a lot of hair loss.
Your face was round like this.
You are cool now.
I admit it.
I'm not that cool.
I'm cool now.
I don't do things like this.
I was really popular.
Really.
I didn't do anything to women.
I see.
If you don't say it, no one will believe you.
Is that so?
I don't want to talk about something I made up.
There are things that can be mistaken.
I said it before.
A taxi driver was riding a car.
And he said,
What?
Isn't he Mr. XXX?
There are things that can be mistaken.
Today, I'm really cool.
I've been waiting for you since the beginning.
I was waiting for you at Tokyo Station.
The taxi was waiting for you.
When I got on the taxi,
I said,
Mr. B21.
I don't even have to deny it.
Does that mean you were waiting for Hiromi?
It's Hiromi.
I can tell even if I wear sunglasses.
I see.
If you say that,
I won't be able to say it either.
So you went to the house to become Hiromi.
Yes.
I think it was a tea party.
He was wrong,
but I felt sorry for him if he got caught.
If I become Hiromi until the end,
it's for this man.
That's what I think.
So,
I don't think I'll be able to use Osaka dialect.
I see.
Right?
So,
I'm embarrassed to say,
please go to the right.
So,
I'll just say,
right, left.
Why?
I don't know if it's right or left.
Why did you say it in one word?
Yoshusho.
After that,
I'll say it in Osaka dialect.
Where did you come from?
You said it in one word.
I don't think I'll be able to use Osaka dialect.
I think Hiromi is a quiet person.
I see.
It's true.
I don't think I'll be able to use Osaka dialect.
I'm often told that I look like Hiromi.
There aren't many comedians who look like me.
Like Kobuhei.
What?
This is the first time I've been told this.
Don't say things that come to your mind.
This time,
I hope I won't be mistaken for David.
It's not a lie.
I think that's enough.
That's enough?
You talked a lot.
I wonder how I'll use it.
Right?
I'm sorry.
I always do it,
but this is the last time.
Out of the 108, how many are there?
There are 108.
There are 34.
What?
There are 35.
35.
Out of the 108, how many are there?
I won't say their names.
You'll know right away.
They're similar.
You won't know if you've done it once.
I'll never do the same thing again.
You'll know right away.
Out of the 108, how many are there?
Another one.
Number 5.
Out of the 108, how many are there?
What?
Out of the 108...
If you say number 5,
it means you've known it for a long time.
The numbers are fast.
I won't say their names.
You'll know right away.
Number 5.
As you all know,
I'm Tomomi Nishimura.
You're really Tomomi Nishimura?
Really?
I didn't know anything,
but I thought you were doing something.
You're really Tomomi Nishimura?
I thought you were doing something.
I thought you were Tomomi Nishimura?
No, I'm not Tomomi Nishimura.
Really?
Number 69.
It's a bit behind.
I'm Kusuzairiko.
Huh?
Kusuzairiko.
Kusuzairiko!
What number?
You guys are like...
You guys are like an auction.
From the next one to the next one.
I only have one left.
You can think about that later.
The last one.
Number 44.
Master Ohira.
Master Ohira is in the middle of something.
You must be talking about the treasure of Master Sakurai.
Number 44.
Master Ohira.
Ah...
You don't have to do it.
That's all for today.
Please come again if you have a chance.
Thank you very much.
So, Master Ohira.
Yes.
The cat you bought in the previous game.
Was it lucky?
Yes.
You said you'd give it to me, right?
About 600 pieces.
Yes.
It's mine.
I'll bring it to you.
Yes.
You can choose one.
Really?
Yes.
This person.
This person is...
Riki Naito.
He's a high school student from Kawasaki.
Congratulations.
What do you have?
Lucky.
Yes.
I'll give it to you.
The name is already decided as Lucky.
Is that so?
Please don't give me a strange name.
Taito-chan, I don't think this is enough.
I have to take off this TK's shirt.
It's true.
I see.
This is fashionable.
Taito-chan, you did a good job today.
That's right.
Yes.
Look.
The other staff members are also amazing.
Yes.
That serious face is not interesting.
It's cold, isn't it?
Yes.
When I heard your voice, I wondered why you did such a thing.
I don't know.
What are you going to do next?
What?
Next?
Yes.
What's next?
Do you want someone to stab you?
That's right.
I have to stab someone.
This person is pitiful.
That's right.
I have to see Tsu-Chi's primitive man.
I see.
Next week, Tsu-Chi is a primitive man.
He will be at the venue.
That's why Tsu-Chi primitive man's Tsu-Chi dinosaur.
Let's do that.
I will come again.
I am Duncan's kid's Tsu-Chi.
Let's do our best next week.
This program is brought to you by
Ooyama International Products