As expected of Karakuchi, the beer is dry.
Ladies and gentlemen.
The 4 and a half years of history of the Gaki no Tsukai Soshuu series.
First, from the nostalgic first episode.
It was said that it was a manzai series.
It was a 30 minute manzai series.
We are Yoshimoto Kogyo.
When we come to places like this, we can relax.
But when we are in Osaka or Kagetsu, it's hard to do this.
We come to see Yoshimoto's Eirai-san.
When we do manzai series, we come to see Yoshimoto's Eirai-san.
The Eirai-san of Yoshimoto Kogyo is behind the audience.
There was no way to say Yoshimoto Kogyo's Eirai-san.
So we call him Yakuza.
This is the 3rd episode of Shinken Shirahadori.
Shinken Shirahadori.
Matsumoto Shidoshi Shinkeni Shirahadori.
Shinken Shirahadori is a recent hit series that challenges the limits of variety.
The 4th episode is about the history of Matsumoto Shidoshi Kiseki.
The 3rd episode is about the history of Matsumoto Shidoshi Kiseki.
The 2nd episode is about the history of Matsumoto Shidoshi Kiseki.
Wow, it's glowing.
It's huge.
Wait!
I got a phone call from a client. He said my sword is like a toy.
A special project for the New Year.
I'm going to do a spiritual unification.
It'll take 2-3 minutes.
Let's go.
Come to the 3rd floor.
It was really dangerous.
It's still dark.
What's going on?
The 2nd time I saw it, it looked like it was wearing a helmet.
That's impossible.
But today...
Are you going to do it?
I'm going to do it again.
What's going on?
I got a phone call from a client.
I'm going to do it for the last time.
The 4th special project.
I'm going to do it again.
This is also a project that will continue until part 3.
The hidden charm of downtown.
Hello, everyone.
Hello.
Welcome.
I and Hama came out of Hiroshima 10 years ago.
We came here to become big.
We came here somehow.
We did it.
I think it's because Hama was there.
What are you talking about?
That's the first song.
It was too sudden.
I can't forget about him.
This is the punishment game for 3 years in a row.
It's Hitoshi!
Hitoshi and...
Mom!
Mom is here.
This is the punishment game for 3 years in a row.
What are you doing?
You're disturbing my singing.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
This is the age of impersonation.
Don't say that.
It's difficult to impersonate a woman.
I'm 18 years old.
18 years old?
That's right.
I'm Shimakura Chiyoko.
What song are you going to sing?
It's Tokyo, Mom.
Let's sing.
It's Tokyo, Mom by Shimakura Chiyoko.
It's been a long time.
What do you mean by a long time?
You're lying.
What are you doing?
You're more excited than usual.
It's dangerous to call someone.
I'm happy.
Hello?
What is that?
You're mischievous.
What are you saying?
Do you have a son who is in the second grade of elementary school?
I have a sixth grader.
What did you do to him?
I'm embarrassed.
It's not funny.
Bring me the money.
I have a second child.
Will you bring it?
Yes.
What are you going to do?
I'll pay you back now.
It's raining.
Good morning.
Hello?
It's me.
Did you sleep well?
Listen to my mother's cry.
Good morning.
Look at my mother's cry.
It's Hitoshi.
It's Okan.
Hitoshi and Okan.
What is this?
Bring me the money.
Will you bring it?
I have a second child.
What are you going to do?
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best next year.
Thank you very much for this trip.
Thank you for having fun.
Take care of yourself.
I hope you get along with everyone.
The second time in history.
Hamashan Ebiyan.
After the high jump match, Hamada lost.
He went to the dressing room.
Bring it.
What is it?
Ebiyan.
What?
Bring Ebiyan.
Bring him.
Let's go.
Are you going to the dressing room?
Yes.
I'm going to the dressing room.
What is this?
It's a punishment game.
The plane carrying Hamada is finally taking off in Japan.
Can Ebiyan make it?
26 hours before departure.
Arrived in Chamonix, the city of silver lovers.
I'm scared.
Look at this.
What are you showing off?
It's easy to understand when you do that.
I'm embarrassed to come to a foreign country.
Looking for Ebiyan, he's finally starting to attack with a rope.
You don't have to drink water in a place like this.
And he arrives at the final destination of the cliff.
Let's go home.
Where is the water?
Excuse me.
There's no water.
There's a waterfall down there.
You can get water from there.
Are you stupid?
It's so cold.
It's so hot.
What's wrong with you?
Where is it?
Let me introduce.
Ebiyan.
20,000 kilometers away from Japan.
Finally, Hamada has arrived at Ebiyan Water, his long-awaited dream.
I'm here.
The blessing of the Alps becomes a sparkling shower and pours into a bottle.
Congratulations, Hama-chan.
This is your punishment for your youth.
Our dream came true with the wind of Mont Blanc.
With a light footstep that was heavy until a moment ago,
the dream bottle becomes a journey of a kilometer.
Ebiyan.
It's a town.
I didn't say anything earlier, but the water of the Alps is the water of the Alps.
Because the water of the Alps came out in Ebiyan, the name Ebiyan is attached to the water.
If Ebiyan comes here, there is no Ebiyan.
That's right.
Does it come out from there?
Hey.
What are you looking at?
If you get off the plane and come here, you'll get hit right away.
Because it's a punishment.
But, the reality is not like that...
It's not like that.
If you say it, will you get hit?
That's right.
The water splashes and pours back into the bottle.
This time, congratulations!
And, well done, Hama-chan.
Our dream has really come true.
You're slow, Hama-chan.
What are you doing?
What is it?
Are you in pain?
I'm fine.
I'll make you fall.
This is for you to eat!
You're too excited.
You!
I'll make you fall!
This is a Metroid.
It's still in use.
But this energy may be useful to humanity.
A heavy Metroid is being stolen!
I'll make you fall!
An emergency test.
Space Hunter Samus Aran.
Stealing Baby Metroid.
Super Phantom Software.
Super Metroid.
An incredible underground fortress awaits.
I met my senpai in town.
He had a good look on his face.
Before I knew it, he was wearing a suit.
I'm sure I was too.
I came up with an idea.
Business School.
Tokyo Shoka Academy.
I'll make you fall!
What is it?
Billy Joel believes in Mini-Discs.
Take and listen to Mini-Discs from now on.
The first ever high school game.
Kaga Mariko vs. Saga.
It's a talk show with famous people from all over the world.
But the two of them have to compete to see how many points they can get.
The 4th round continues.
I change my hair color every day.
You can tell by looking down.
I like you, sensei.
I was the judge.
You had a good look on your face.
Mom, are you okay?
The 3rd round.
Kaga Mariko vs. Saga.
How many points will they get?
I'm a woman.
If you're a father, you'll get 50 points.
If you can put Kaga Mariko's body in a half-transparent garbage bag, you'll get 20,000 points.
The 4th round.
Kaga Mariko vs. Saga.
Today's guest is Kaga Mariko.
Good evening.
We're going to talk about Kaga Mariko's reflection.
No, I'm not going to win.
Why not?
I still have 15 points left.
How many years have you been in the entertainment world?
I've never felt it.
Your hands are white. You're a disgusting man.
No, I'm not.
What's wrong with him?
No, no, no.
Thank you very much.
You're a piece of crap.
What are you doing?
You're amazing.
I'm pretending to be asleep.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with your reflection?
I can't help it.
Kaga Mariko's half-transparent garbage bag is a hot topic these days.
Thank you very much.