Tanaka Kankan.
Thank you.
You're the host, but you're so excited.
Who said that?
It's easy to say.
The captain of this team is...
Hage.
Sashiba.
It's Sashiba, but...
It's Sashiba.
It's our show, so we're the captains.
What are you looking at?
This show is brought to you by these sponsors.
Let's get started.
Tanaka Kankan's first question is...
Tanaka's episode quiz!
That's a common way to get excited.
I don't know what to say.
Let's get started.
Recently,
Tanaka and I
are addicted to
MyBOOM.
MyBOOM is a popular show.
Hage's team.
Let's start with Hage.
What?
You're an idiot.
I don't like it.
Let's start with an idiot.
MyBOOM.
I want a car.
I see.
I want a used car.
You're an idiot.
Next.
Uwamaki.
What?
He looks like Uwamaki.
Uwamaki.
What is Uwamaki?
Table tennis.
Tanuki.
You just remembered how to use it.
Don't say that I like you.
Tanuki.
I want a plastic model.
Wrong.
I got it.
I want to get rid of my hair.
That's it.
Are you guys fighting?
We're not fighting.
Are you worried about your hair?
I want a fat character.
Fat character?
Fat character.
I want to go to a hotel.
That's wrong.
Baseball.
MyBOOM.
I want a pig.
Wrong.
I want a bag.
Tanaka Episode Quiz Question 2.
Lately,
I think puns are very interesting.
When I gathered my juniors
and talked about it,
I used a lighter
as a pun.
A lighter.
I made everyone laugh.
What did you do with this lighter?
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
With a lighter?
With a lighter.
A lighter.
That's good.
It's not funny.
It's not funny at all.
A lighter.
My teeth hurt.
It's like that now.
I can't say it.
A lighter.
This lighter...
It's flat.
Thank you.
That's the end.
This is a very good opportunity.
I used a lighter
at that time.
Is that okay?
Lupo-Lighter is a flint.
Lupo-Lighter,
flint,
flint.
It's like a lighter.
There are three in it.
What's in the box?
Put your hand in it.
Guess what's in it.
Everyone, come forward.
Did you see it in this box?
It's a memorable book.
You said it.
It's a book.
The contents of the box are books.
However,
the title.
What kind of book is in it?
It's a reaction video.
I'll watch it.
At least you don't have to move.
It's hard to do.
It's a book.
It's an open book.
When will it be released?
I don't accept any questions.
I'll go first.
I'll go alternately.
It's a book.
Next
I'll try the first one.
What kind of animal is it?
That is the answer.
It's a papers.
It's called Cinderella.
I can't move.
I told you I was watching your reaction.
I did my best.
What? You didn't listen?
You didn't listen?
Why aren't you interested in me?
Why?
Go ahead.
Ah!
No!
What is it?
Ah! Ouch! Ouch!
What?
Isn't it easy?
It's a book.
Hey, do it.
What?
Do it.
It's a book.
Again?
Why aren't you interested in me?
I didn't listen.
You were watching.
Ah!
It's hard.
What is it?
It's hot.
Ah!
What is it?
It's like a picture book.
Ah!
I see.
Is it that one?
What are you doing?
It's a book.
It's hard.
It's like a picture book.
What?
No.
It's like a picture book.
You can go home.
Why?
It's okay, you can go home.
I'm sorry.
Is it the only book you have?
Go home.
I'm sorry.
Do it.
I have a lot of books.
Do you have them?
I have them.
It's the book No.3.
It's a book.
What is it?
What does it mean?
It's strange.
Time's up!
What?
Mr.Tanakaze Shagun!
Yay!
Yes!
First, Habu Team.
Yes.
Who is it?
Rock, paper, scissors
Agitator
You know it, right?
You will get 30 points if you get this question right
Ready, start!
Nagashima?
I don't have to hit it, right?
Why is your chin sticking out?
Batter
You hit it
Home run
You hit a home run
You ran
Hit it
Banzai
You got a point
Home base
How far are you going?
From the top of your head
Baseball?
1st, 2nd, 3rd?
10,000 points
Wait, what did you say?
That's not fair
What are you talking about?
You were doing it
You hit a home base
I don't know that
Ago
Inoki
What?
Are you ready?
Wait, wait
Hanaka Naoki
That's not fair
You hit a home run
It's the same if you say the type
It's fine
That's right
You both did well
It's impossible
50 points
Who will do it?
Can I decide?
Me?
Please
50 points
Nakamura will do it
I'm sorry
It's the Sashiba team's problem
Got it?
Got it
Okay
Start
Match
It's burning
Crab
Fire
Match
Car
What's that?
Match
Fire
Car
You're leaving the car?
What?
What are you doing?
Fire?
It's definitely fire
There's no fire?
You can talk to each other
I won't lose
You're leaving the car?
What?
A child who is crying
The one who saved
Tanaka
Correct
50 points
It's weird
If you listen to it, you'll understand it, right?
There's no time limit, so you have to keep doing it until you get the answer.
That's impossible.
But it can't be helped.
What are you doing?
Sorry.
That's all!
That was Tanaka Kankan!
Help me!
The only thing I can say is...
I'm sorry for saying too much.
Good evening!
Thank you for finding me.
You should have stopped here.
You really look like House Kaguya.
I don't know anyone called House Kaguya.
That means everyone is laughing, right?
Are you House Kaguya?
Then I'm House Kaguya.
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
That's all.
What do you think?
I had a wonderful experience the other day.
Wonderful?
Wonderful.
I'm going to surprise you with this story.
Tell me.
Do you want to hear it?
There's a lot.
Really?
Why do you look like Hayashi Sensei?
I don't know who you are.
Tell me.
Tanaka and Endo were in the car.
They've already experienced it.
I don't like to colorize the story.
I'll tell you what happened.
It's not a lie.
Last week, I was driving a car.
There was a guardrail.
There was a guardrail and there was a road.
I was driving on that road.
The police officer was driving a white car.
The guardrail wasn't on this side.
It was on the other side of the road.
The car was on the other side of the road.
The guardrail was on the other side of the road.
What do you think?
Was there an obstacle?
No.
Did you have to avoid it?
The guardrail was on the other side of the road.
I can't forgive such things.
It doesn't matter if it's the police or not.
The car was on the other side of the road.
I was careful.
This is my prediction.
I'll tell you what I think will happen from now on.
This is easier to understand.
It's like NG Taisho.
It's easy to understand.
I was trying to be careful.
I opened the window.
The guardrail came.
I thought it was dangerous.
I told the police officer.
It's dangerous.
I thought it was dangerous.
I told the police officer.
It was dangerous.
I see.
The guardrail was in a mess.
This is normal.
The guardrail should have run on the street.
I ran around the street and caused trouble.
I thought it was Matsumoto.
I always see Matsumoto.
I caused trouble.
Please do your best.
Please be careful.
This is my prediction.
I see.
Let's talk about the real story.
I was in trouble.
I opened the window.
I thought I should tell you something.
What are you doing?
What?
I'm being beaten up.
I see.
How can you forgive me?
I'm being beaten up.
I'm telling you something from the other side.
What are you doing?
Why?
Come on.
You can't run.
What are you doing?
You're angry because of the Corax.
I'm scared.
This is a scary world.
That's the theme for today.
Thank you.
The announcer is going to fall.
I heard you did a simulation.
I can't trust that kind of simulation.
In the past,
I did a face with an airbag.
I didn't feel bad about anyone.
I felt like I couldn't trust love.
It was a trauma for me.
I can't trust anyone.
I understand that.
Do you understand?
I can't trust skydiving.
I'm not scared.
Which one?
I can't trust people.
I don't care if they're human.
I'm not scared.
I don't care if I get a slit.
What are you looking at?
Your bones?
I'm not a bone.
No more.
Ever since the airbag.
Ever since then.
I was surprised too.
I was surprised.
I was scared of you.
You looked at my face.
What did you check?
Did you have a nose?
Do you know what I am?
I am a down-to-earth idiot.
You know what I mean.
What you are thinking is strange.
The airbag inflates, and then you put your face in it.
I was shocked.
Before the airbag inflates, you put your face in it.
Like this.
Why didn't you know that?
Why did you do that?
Come closer.
Like this.
Why did you do that?
You don't take care of your nose hair at all.
Since you were 30, your nose hair has grown thicker.
Why is that?
How old do you think a man's genitalia is?
About 40.
About 40?
45.
I think 45 is the most genitalia of a man.
I became 35 recently.
From now on, I will polish my nose hair as a man for the next 10 years.
When that happens, I will have a lot of nose hair.
As a man.
This genitalia...
I like it.
That's good.
I don't want to feel embarrassed as a man.
You don't mind having a nose hair at this stage?
I don't mind having a nose hair at this stage.
But it's not a complete nose hair?
It's not a complete nose hair.
The reason why I have so much nose hair is...
When I turn my head, it looks okay.
Does that mean you can turn your head from here?
For example, when I turn my head...
If I don't have anything, I look bad as a man.
When?
It's not like that. When I turn my head...
If I don't have a nose hair, I look bad as a man.
But I don't have anything to turn my head.
I'm not saying that.
For example, I can ride a bike.
I don't have anything to turn my head.
I don't want to talk about turning my head.
I don't care.
When I go to the hospital and they ask me to wait for the medicine, I don't care.
I'll prepare it for you.
But when I'm waiting, I can't turn my head.
You can't turn your head.
I can't turn my head.
When you tell me that you have a paper to write something, I'll write down your address.
Turn my head.
What are you doing?
When I turn my head...
Turn your head.
Listen to me.
When I turn my head...
If you don't listen to me, I can't talk.
What the hell are you talking about?
Listen, really, listen!
This is...
This is weird!
This idiot...
What should I say?
So, in a building like this,
I don't know what's going on.
There's a fire, an ambulance comes,
and the fire department goes crazy, right?
At that time,
there are times when I go out.
The ambulance says,
are you okay?
At that time...
Why are you talking about that?
So,
the story of Mekure,
no matter when,
Mekure is weird.
If you say that,
I can't talk.
I don't need to talk.
When I went to the inter high school,
I said,
hey,
you put your legs in like this, right?
At the beginning...
At the beginning,
when I put my legs in like this...
This program was provided by the following sponsors.