I can't do it.
You don't have to force yourself.
Gekidoujin Omae Sou Chanka Grand Prix!
Today is the 5th time.
Omae Sou Chanka Grand Prix.
You know what to do, right?
First, I'll introduce the guests.
Today's guests are these people!
Wait a minute.
What?
Why am I the only one here?
What's wrong with you?
Sit down!
Guests! Guests!
When I introduce the guests, the people who don't like me spread out, right?
Where?
They don't like you!
I don't hate you yet!
There was a guest!
Today, I'll write with you.
Really?
Yes.
Don't write something light.
I won't write something light.
Something light is for graduation.
For what?
Don't write something that has a P in it.
You have to write it with the intention of being praised.
It's you!
You're the one who wrote it!
You're the one who put the mosaic here!
The staff did it on their own.
It's true!
You're being too careful!
Really?
I have a different opinion.
Thank you.
As usual, we have a guide interview.
When you reach 5 people, that person is the winner of the Grand Prix.
Let's get started!
Let's go.
The first question is...
This one!
Don't you think you'll win the next election?
Don't get cocky! You're a celebrity!
You stupid!
Wait a minute.
When you predict who will win the next election,
when you look at that person,
you think, oh, that person is stupid.
You don't think that much.
I don't think that much.
Please write it down.
There was a person who said, welcome.
I was just about to write it down.
Don't get cocky!
You stupid!
Welcome!
Did you write it down?
I wrote it down.
I'm not afraid of anything.
Then show it to us.
I wrote...
It's me.
Kimura Taro.
I'm going to hide it.
And?
Hikaru Genji's Moroboshi.
Hey!
Don't touch my head!
Masudoe-san.
Tawara Soichiro.
Retsukushi-san.
Kume Hiroshi-san.
When I say something on the news,
I feel like I want to do it myself.
Masudoe-san.
Takeshi-san.
Giant and Baba.
In the world of politics,
there are 16 questions.
Tawara Soichiro.
Tamaru Misuzu-san.
Kume Hiroshi-san.
San-shi?
Do you often say things like that?
It's Mach-chan.
Tamari-san.
Kume Hiroshi-san.
Takeshi-san.
Retsukushi-san.
Masudoe-san.
Kume-san?
Kume Hiroshi-san.
So I'm going to teach you the answer.
Kume-san, followed by Masudoe-san,
Takeshi-san, Tawara-san,
Retsukushi-san, Tamari-san.
Masudoe-san.
The next question is this.
You're not a waki.
You have a cute face,
but you stink!
A female talent?
Don't be on TV, you idiot!
That's the person.
Please write it down.
I wonder if it's the same person.
I'm sorry.
Don't say it like I'm an idiot.
Then, without it...
I don't want everyone to know.
It's not like I have a boyfriend.
Are you serious?
Don't say things like that!
It's the costume.
The costume is the problem.
What should I do?
You didn't know?
I didn't know at all.
Really?
The costume is the problem.
Please write it down.
I didn't know at all.
You didn't know?
You're not a waki.
I don't like it.
Let's go.
I've already spent my talent life.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
I'll write it down.
Let's just talk about this part.
It's not good to write a letter somewhere.
Okay, Amada-san.
Here.
This is a rumor, isn't it?
This is...
And this.
I was going to do this with you.
I can't wear this costume anymore.
The costume you're throwing away.
Oh, I see.
I'm just asking the general public.
You don't have to give me the right answer.
How about this?
The general public doesn't know that.
No one thinks I'm wearing a costume.
Muroi Shigen-san.
Yoshisamoto.
Wada Akiko.
I feel like it's hard to catch up.
Chiharu.
Matsumoto Akiko.
Sugimoto Aya-san.
Hisamoto.
It's Hisamoto.
It might be rude, but it's Hisamoto.
Hosokawa Fumie.
Hosokawa Fumie-san.
Takao Kazaki-san.
Hosokawa Fumie.
She's fat.
Asano Yuko-kun.
Sugimoto Aya.
Hosokawa Fumie.
The general public thinks it's Hosokawa Fumie.
The general public thinks that big women have a lot of armpits.
Really?
I think it's different from Sumo.
It's different from Sumo.
I think it's pretty common.
I think it's more like Chiharu.
I don't know.
The next question is this.
You!
You're not funny at all!
Stop it!
Stop it already!
I'm begging you!
Stop adding things.
Just leave it as it is.
Please write it down.
No, no, no, no.
I want to write it down.
There are a lot of armpits.
But there aren't many people who have armpits right now.
Of course, that's definitely right.
That's right.
But, you know, if you take this out and put a mosaic on it,
I think this will probably be number one, so you'll get a bang, bang, bang.
Then what's the effect of the mosaic?
No, that's why I put a mosaic on the picture that comes out here.
You put a mosaic on that, too?
That's right.
Then what is this corner?
So, this opening is something that only the people who are wearing it can enjoy.
Then you don't have to do anything like this.
Then what is this guest?
Am I the only one who can enjoy this?
That's right.
That's necessary!
Yes.
That's right.
Then this.
Take a clap!
Then I...
I'll give it to you.
Wait a minute, that clap!
Do you know what kind of effect that clap will have later?
It might be me.
I'm Tomizu.
Jimmy Onishi.
U-chan, Nan-chan.
Downtown.
It would be interesting if it was individual, but it's not very interesting to get together and make a fuss at Uchihoneta.
Takeshi.
Jimmy-chan.
Yamada Masato-san.
Downtown.
I don't like being funny and making fun of others.
Shibashi Takahashi.
Shigura Ken.
Ao Nien.
Jimmy Onishi.
Sendamizu.
Sendamizu is boring.
Everyone only talks about it.
Yamada Masato-san.
Hon-jama.
I'm Jimmy Onishi.
O-Ni-Chan Cup Grand Prix!
You are correct!
You are correct, O-Ni-Chan!
It's your first time, right?
Yes, it's my first time.
This is too much!
It's your first time, right?
No, it's my first time.
You should have done more.
Congratulations.
Thank goodness.
I really wanted one until I got one.
But when I got one, it wasn't this cruel.
Are you tired?
I'm really tired.
How have you been lately?
Hey, I haven't seen that.
What?
The Swiss guy.
He looks pretty cool.
Why?
What?
That's impossible.
I heard it.
I heard that you were in the second round.
I was slow.
I was filling water in a waterfall or something.
Don't do that slowly!
What are you doing?
I don't know about the world.
The maximum number of views you have is 27.
You haven't seen it, right?
The number of views I have is 27.5%.
That's enough.
I can't do it anymore.
That's too much.
If you do that, your punishment game will be better.
The general public's evaluation will be higher.
Why?
It will be better than my Hato.
It will be better than my Color Bar.
You can't watch my show.
You can watch it if you want to.
What are you talking about?
What?
You are kind.
You are annoying.
Are you trying to appeal yourself?
Why would I do that?
You are kind.
Don't call me kind.
No one is kind.
The voice of the general public is like this.
You have done so much so far.
If you lose, you should go on a foreign trip.
You have been sitting in the dressing room for 12 hours.
It was so hard.
It was like this before.
That's why I hate going on a foreign trip.
You may be fine.
But I have 190 years of experience.
How many years do you have?
Why is it so fun?
There were only old ladies on the tour.
The manager was sitting behind me.
He was smoking.
When I did this, the old lady behind me was like this.
I don't want to go.
Why do you hate going on a foreign trip?
I have been sitting in the dressing room for 12 hours.
There were only old ladies on the tour.
I had to put up with it.
It would have been cool if you had gone on a foreign trip for a long time.
You had to put up with it.
Don't you think it's cool to go on a foreign trip?
I don't know what the old lady would have done to her daughter.
The old lady went to the bathroom.
She didn't go out for a long time.
I don't want to go on a foreign trip.
That's a talent.
It's okay to go on a foreign trip and hear the sound of poop.
What is the sound of poop?
It's the sound of poop.
You don't have to listen to it.
I'm happy to hear that.
Why are you happy?
There is no sound like that.
It's okay not to listen to it.
After I went on a foreign trip, I gave her a lot of applause.
When I went on a foreign trip, I was waiting for her.
I hated it.
After that, I went in immediately.
I was waiting for her.
After I went on a foreign trip, I went in immediately.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Do you understand the situation?
Where did you go?
I went to the bathroom.
You have a big dream.
I can't stand it if I'm told that I pooped.
You...
Stop the upper cut.
If you care about the people around you, you should stop being angry.
You can't do that.
I've never been angry.
I'm telling you. I've never been angry.
It's not true.
What's not true?
You should leave it alone.
I found out why people get angry.
First of all, if you get angry, you shout out loud.
If you shout out loud, you can't stop it.
You shout out louder and louder so that you don't lose to that shout.
I see.
But you've been doing it for a long time.
You shout out loud and shout out loud.
Ask the people around you. Which one is angry and which one is scared?
No. I'm doing my job.
You're holding a wire and a megaphone.
That's not true.
No one thinks you're scared by that.
No. You're doing it because you're scared.
That's the impression I have.
You should leave it alone.
What's with that face?
You shout out loud everywhere.
What are you looking for when you get soup at the airport?
It doesn't matter.
It's minestrone.
It doesn't matter how hot it is.
It doesn't matter what kind of soup it is.
I can't even say it's tonjiru.
It's hot.
It's minestrone.
It's your way of saying it.
It's a candy.
It's a lot of candy.
It's like a pirate ship's handle.
It doesn't matter how hot it is.
It might be true.
Do you get it?
Be patient.
If it sounds like that.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
That's the difference between me and you.
You don't shout out loud.
I don't get it.
What do you mean by loud?
You don't shout out loud.
What?
I don't get it.
When a bus passes by, what does it mean for a driver to wave his hand?
I'm sorry.
What does it mean?
Are you doing it?
I don't think so.
When a bus passes by, what does it mean for a driver to wave his hand?
I don't get it.
I'm sorry.
When a bus passes by, what does it mean for a driver to wave his hand?
I don't get it.
I'm not going to the bottom today.
There are a lot of eggshells on the flower pot. What does it mean?
The ingredients of the shell are different from the flower pot.
You're thinking too much.
Why are you thinking so much?
You!
I don't get it.
There are eggshells on the flower pot.
They were born.
No, no, no.
Well, well, wait.
Okay, I got it.
It's getting interesting.
Come on.
What?
The eggshells are broken.
They are.
They were born.
They were born. That's why there are eggshells.
What about the contents?
The contents are gone.
They are gone?
They are gone.
They won't break.
What does it mean?
I don't know.
Are they living?
They are living.
Don't you know?
I know.
How do you know they are living?
I've never seen them.
The eggshells are close to the eggshells.
Good morning.
Thank you for today.
It's over.
The eggshells protect the living things.
They are broken.
They are broken and fallen.
Yes.
After the living things are born.
I don't know what they are.
The living things are gone.
They are born and run away.
I see.
I think you can see them in the morning.
Maybe at 4 or 4.30.
You know the time.
You should have seen them at least once.
I'm not interested in them.
I know what they are.
Open the door at 4.30 or 3.30 and see the eggshells.