I'm dreaming of a white Christmas
Just like the one
It looks so high
Thank you for waiting
From now on, we will start the Christmas Dinner Show in Downtown
Hama-chan, this season has come again
It was really fun to see everyone again
Last night, I couldn't sleep
Really?
I was so happy
It's okay everyone, please eat
Today is the coldest day of the year
Is that so?
My body is getting warm
I don't know if you guys have it on or not
Everyone, are you on it?
Everyone is on it
I'll hide it
First, please listen to the Christmas song from Yamasato Tron's album
It's snowing
The rain is too late
It will turn into snow
I don't know what to do
All in love
I'm sure you're like this
All alone
All in love
I don't know what to do
I'm sure you're like this
All in love
Let's do our best
Thank you
There was a guy with glasses in the audience, but I couldn't see him
Everyone, please eat
Don't worry about the food
Christmas is really romantic
Everyone, is it okay to sing two songs?
It looks like you're still in good spirits
Next is a farewell song
I chose a farewell song for Christmas
I wonder what it will be
I can't speak
It's so cold
Next, please listen to the song from Kariyama's album
What I remember when I open my eyes
I know it's the past
That loneliness
I'm sure it will change me
I want to think
Goodbye, how long will it last
I'm sure you're like this
I don't know what to do
We're scarier
I can finally see everyone's faces
Everyone seems to be safe
Today, Hama-chan is amazing
I can't open my mouth
It's rude
But Hama-chan
It's sad, but it's time to say goodbye
I forgot there was a farewell
What are you talking about?
Everyone, it's time to say goodbye
Please listen to Yuke Yuke Huma
I'm sure you're like this
I don't know what to do
It was a really interesting movie
How was it?
Everyone
Hey, that's cheating
Ladies and gentlemen
What are you doing?
The other day
What?
For the first time in my life, I bled
Did you bleed?
I bled
I hit the glass table
I hit it and it came out
Are you okay? It hurts a little, but it's full of blood
Just looking at the blood made me pale
Are you okay?
Men are really weak to blood
No
Women are really fine
Women are weak to blood
I went to the hospital
I told them not to come to the hospital
I told them to come to the person who hit their head
They're really going to the person who hit their head
They're going to put it under their head
They have diarrhea
I see
I have diarrhea
I have no appetite
I understand
I know
He was sleeping and didn't wake up no matter how many times I tried to wake him up.
He was dead!
Why did you bring him here?
I don't have anyone like that.
I have one too.
When I was a chief.
I was scared.
Why did you become like that?
When I was in elementary school,
there was a kid called Hata who was bullied.
There was a kid called Sato who was bullied.
He said, Hata!
I was next to Hata.
I said, Hata!
Hey, Sato!
What do you mean, Sato?
Sato threw the catcher's mitt.
I threw it at Hata.
It cut and went to Hata's place.
It went to my place.
Damn it!
You were angry because you were beaten.
But Sato is pretty strong.
Stop it!
Sato
threw something
to someone's head.
It hit his head.
I thought he was bleeding.
Who was it?
Was that Hata too?
I saw it on the spot.
I said, Hata!
Sato was already over there.
He was bullied.
Really?
I didn't like
bullying people.
So I didn't do it.
But you did it anyway.
You were with him.
You were throwing fireworks
at an old man in Morioka.
You were doing it with him.
An old man in Morioka climbed a tree
and threw fireworks
at an old man in Morioka.
Wait a minute.
That's an old man.
That's an old man in Morioka.
Let me make it clear.
You know it.
I know it.
But I saw you doing it
with an old man in elementary school.
That's true.
You were an elementary school student
called an old man in Morioka.
That's right.
I know
but I can't call my father
Hiroshi.
That's strange.
There was a puddle
in the park.
There was a drum can.
A big one.
I put a rotten fruit in it.
A rotten fruit?
It's called Kiyomi.
That's right.
I remember it well.
Before that,
I put other things in it
like this.
I thought it was funny.
Then I put a rotten fruit in it.
I thought you would do the same thing.
I put a rotten fruit
in the puddle.
There was a muddy water in the rotten fruit.
The rotten fruit went home.
It's strange.
Why?
I don't like animals.
I like animals.
That's not good.
You are killing them.
I'm not killing them.
Don't lie.
My family is like that.
My father is also like that.
Do you know that?
Do you know what will happen
if I put hot water on my throat?
I've never done that.
Something will come out of my butt.
Wait a minute.
What is that?
I did it in front of my house.
My father told me to do it.
He told me to do it.
My cat caught a bat.
It's still moving.
Come here.
I'll throw a candle.
I'm sorry.
No.
I'll throw a candle.
A bat will come out.
I don't like laughing.
My father is like that.
It's hard for me.
But,
but,
he'll kill me.
He'll kill me.
Everyone will run away after I die.
It's not only you and my family.
Everyone will run away.
So...
I'll put hot water on my throat.
I was so angry that I couldn't even say anything.
You were dead.
No, I wasn't dead.
Was that a baby?
No, no, it was a baby.
I was so mad.
I wasn't mad.
You were just standing there.
Of course I was mad.
I was so mad.
You weren't mad.
I said, I love you.
I said, yes, yes.
I was so mad.
No, no.
How many times have I told you?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I was so mad.
It was funny.
Thank you.
Oh, is that so?
The other day, I was bored in the dressing room, so I said,
come here, and I looked at the book for a long time.
My eyes got weird.
It's not good.
You know, I did Tetris today.
I was doing Tetris for hours,
and when I finished, I stopped,
but Tetris came out of my head.
I understand what you're saying.
Even looking at the window of the building,
I was like,
if I came down now, it would disappear.
It's the same as that.
If you look at my face, it's a little blurry.
That's not true.
That's a lie.
I'm embarrassed.
Really?
Do you want to play?
Sure.
Do you want to talk a little more?
What time is it now?
9 o'clock 25 minutes.
Did you lie to me at 9 o'clock?
I don't know.
Have you ever hooked up with a girl recently?
No, I haven't.
Don't say recently.
I haven't done it at all.
It's dirty.
It's true.
I'm sure it's true.
I've never done it like you.
Hey, hey, hey.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Why do you laugh?
I've done it many times,
you're waiting with a receiver.
There was a guy who said,
Bring it on!
What?
You've changed, haven't you?
Don't talk like that!
I haven't!
You shouldn't talk like that!
How many Christmas presents have you bought?
I haven't bought any.
Why?
When are you going to buy them?
I'm going to buy them!
I've bought them!
I buy them every year!
What are you talking about?
I don't buy big ones.
But I have a lot of them.
That's strange.
Why do you have so many Christmas presents?
Oh, I got it.
Why do you have so many?
Because I'm small.
I knew it!
Stop that!
Why do you have to stop?
I don't know.
Where is the small house?
Take me with you this year.
I don't want to die.
No, you can't.
I can't be honest.
I have a smiley face.
I have a cat at home.
When the cat sleeps,
it makes a growling sound.
It makes a growling sound.
What is that?
It doesn't sleep.
Humans have that.
When it says something,
it doesn't sleep.
In the end, the wild feelings are still there.
Because it's a cat.
It's safe.
Even if it sleeps at home.
Even if it sleeps at home,
it makes a growling sound.
It makes a growling sound.
I thought so.
That's what it means.
Do you know?
The more cowardly an animal is,
the more ears it has.
Is that so?
That's right.
Really?
That's why it has two ears.
It had an operation,
but it came back to normal.
That's not true!
It's a lion.
What are you talking about?
Cowardly animals have ears.
If you think about it,
it's true.
What do you mean?
It's a rabbit.
Cowardly animals have ears
so they can sense when the enemy comes.
Cats too.
Lions are strong,
so they don't have ears.
They don't have long ears.
Do you know where the lion's ears are?
Around here.
You've never seen it, have you?
The ears are always
next to the eyes.
The ears are always next to the eyes.
That's not true.
The lion's vertical hair
is not the ears.
What?
It's not the ears.
The lion's vertical hair
is like this.
Then it's the same as this.
Really?
It looks like this,
but it has ears like this?
Why do you turn the bed?
What are you talking about?
Why do you turn the bed in a hotel?
What's a hotel?
You turn the bed in a love hotel.
There's no point in turning it.
You can look at it from different angles.
What?
It's a mirror barrier.
You can look at it from different angles?
That's a third party.
No, it's a mirror barrier.
What?
This is a mirror barrier too.
Normally, it's just this.
You can look at it.
That's why you're turning it.
No, no.
The top and the sides are the same.
No.
It's a love hotel,
but the two of you are burning in the bed.
But the two of you are burning in the bed.
It's not burning.
It's burning.
It's burning,
so if you don't turn it,
it won't burn properly.
White eyes.
It's hot around here,
but you're burning it well.
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.