Before the recording of Gakidotsukai, we can only see that man who is happy in his private room.
I can only see you.
Yes, I like you.
I'm sorry.
I'll kill you.
Thank you.
Excuse me, Yamazaki-san...
What are you doing?
What are you talking about?
Yamazaki-san told us to invite everyone.
Well, it's okay to ignore him.
He's always like that.
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
He's been happy in his private room lately.
But he's depressed.
He wants everyone to come.
I think it's a good idea to invite everyone to this program.
That's right.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Excuse me.
This way.
He's my senior.
Yes.
Excuse me.
I don't know how to call a senior.
That's strange.
What is it?
You look surprised.
Why are you surprised?
I'm sorry to bother you.
It's okay.
He's my senior.
I don't know how to call him.
I'm sorry.
Actually...
I'm living a good life.
I have a beautiful wife that everyone envies.
I have a cute baby called Momo.
I have a cute baby.
Right?
But...
My luck has gone to my private life.
Do you remember?
I was on a TV show.
This show.
It was a punishment game.
Everyone came in the middle of the sea.
When I came out...
I had a cramp in my hip.
There was a big explosion.
Do you remember?
I don't think so.
At that time, the god was still there.
I can't go down.
That was a long time ago.
A long time ago.
Go!
It was a punishment game that challenged the limits of winter.
Hanagaki!
Bring that bag!
Go!
In fact, the god of laughter had come down from the sea.
I've done it before.
I've done it.
You didn't come down at that time, did you?
What is this?
What do you want to do?
So...
Komu.
Yes.
What do you have?
Why is it Komu?
I don't know.
They're very close.
Komu.
Yes.
He was right next to me.
There's only one wasabi in this.
Wasabi cream puff.
It's common.
It's a common pattern.
If the god is in this, you'll know.
I know.
If the wasabi comes out, we'll be able to record it.
That's right.
If the god comes.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
It's sweet.
It's a common one.
It became like this.
Did you laugh with this?
You didn't laugh at all.
I didn't laugh, but...
But it's one-fifth.
Come on.
Komu.
Yes.
It's two.
I see.
This is different.
It's 50%.
This is...
What are you doing?
Zaki.
Really?
Are you serious?
Are you stupid?
He's laughing.
Should I stop?
That's...
Well...
But...
Today was bad.
It's just a little bad now.
It's the same as yesterday.
It's always the same.
Even if it's one-fifth, it's a failure.
Did this man really get separated from God?
I'm going to say some tongue twisters now.
I'll say tongue twisters three times in a row.
What?
What did you say?
Tongue twisters.
What's that?
I usually say tongue twisters and then bite.
I've been doing it for a while now.
That's right.
That's true.
It's not the basis of comedy, is it?
That's right.
The time axis is strange.
There's a distortion.
Distortion?
Distortion.
There's a distortion.
Yes, distortion.
Well, I'll do it.
Tongue twisters.
I'll say it three times.
Bite.
I'll do it.
Tongue twisters.
I was going to say it three times.
That's why it's stuck.
This is funny.
Hey, Endo.
Yes.
You try it.
Me?
Yes.
I'm pretty good at it.
Try it.
I'll do it in the middle.
Cut.
I'm pretty good at it.
Did you hear that?
Your ears.
Everyone was laughing.
To be honest.
Yes.
They were clapping.
Why?
Is there something wrong with me?
Am I just pretending?
In the end.
I'll do it at the end.
Cut.
Yama-chan will do it.
Please.
Okay.
Okay, I'll do it.
Tongue twisters.
It's funny.
It's really funny.
You said something that wasn't written anywhere.
Yes.
That's right.
It wasn't written anywhere.
Hey!
What is it?
If it was live.
What will happen to me?
If it was a live broadcast.
I'm done.
But it was funny.
It's not about being funny.
If it was a live broadcast.
I'm done.
Hey.
Tongue twisters.
You used your tongue.
Yes.
This time.
Tongue twisters.
Please bring the tongue twisters.
The person who hits the roulette will be hit by the tongue twisters.
Yes.
Everyone, stand up.
This is easy to understand.
It's easy to understand.
Is that so?
This is easy to understand.
Why is there a gun?
Just in case.
Yes.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Yes.
It's me.
You almost hit it.
It's coming.
It's me again.
It's coming in a row.
What are you doing?
Come back again.
Come quickly.
Mr. Oda.
It's just a coincidence.
Yes.
This is completely random.
It's just a coincidence.
I don't care about it.
The next one is a different person.
Yes.
What's next?
Let's change the spot.
Shall we change the spot?
I want to go to the endo.
Oh, I see.
If you come to the endo, I'll hold you.
No, no, it's fine.
I'll take it.
Oh, really?
Yes, it's totally fine.
It's different.
This is the endo.
I'm here!
Look.
What, what, what?
I'm here.
I'm here at the endo.
I'm not happy at all.
Why?
No, it's the endo.
That's why I laughed.
I laughed because I wanted to go to the endo.
It's hot!
There's still one left.
I don't know.
Wait.
So...
What is this?
What are you going to do with this?
This is a blower.
Yes.
What are you going to do?
I'll have you blow it with a blower.
And I'll stop it with my butt.
Oh.
And there's a needle in it.
It hurts.
Just one.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
This is a good reaction.
Right?
Yes.
Are you ready?
What are you doing?
Yes.
This.
Number two.
This hurts.
That's right.
It's a needle.
It's a good reaction.
Here we go.
Ready.
Yes.
It's stuck.
Do you have a chance?
I have a chance.
You.
That was close.
It was close.
It was one, two.
I was going to blow it.
It was a little better, wasn't it?
That's right.
The flow.
Next.
Bam, bam.
Bam.
Finally, the people smiled.
If we could make it to Chucrim, it would be a great success.
What was this?
Which one should I choose?
That's right.
I think I know.
It's okay?
Which one should I choose?
Yes.
I know what it is.
Which one is a machine phone and which one is different?
It's different.
Oh, I see.
Sigh...
Right!
The right is the machine.
I see.
You can do it, Yama-chan.
I can make a good reaction.
I'll do a good reaction.
Even if I don't like it.
Here I go!
Hurry up!
This is terrible!
Why?
I don't know if I can do this.
I'm going to die.
This machine is totally messed up.
It's really messed up.
This is good.
One of them has Taiki-kun's dad.
One of them has an old man.
Here it comes.
Here I go.
I'm counting on you!
It's good!
That was close!
Zaki-san!
I almost got it.
I was almost there.
That was close!
It's hard to get a laugh.
So Yamasaki-san has a suggestion.
What should I do?
I think it's much better than before.
The first half was good.
The kick was good.
I was talking to Yamasaki-san.
The wind...
You did it when you jumped, right?
When you did the wide jump.
From that time, I thought the wind was going to Heipo-san.
I did it!
This little middle-aged man is not only good at jumping.
The fact is interesting.
Certainly, at this moment, the god of laughter is coming down to Heipo.
Certainly, it was interesting.
Well, there are times when it's interesting.
Yamasaki-san is an interesting guy.
That's why he's aiming for the ball.
There are too many balls.
Who is it?
I'm not coming out.
It would be great if I could return it here.
Please let me have a match with Heipo-san.
Really.
What do you mean?
What kind of match?
Actually, today...
Shinjuku and Ikebukuro...
There are two stadiums.
One is a huge fan.
The other one is a normal small fan.
We have each of them ready.
We have them ready.
And then...
Heipo-san and I...
You know...
Pants.
Pants and parachutes.
We'll go to one of them.
I don't know.
Downtown-san.
Kokoriko-san.
I'm not coming out.
Not at all.
You get it, right?
Yes, I get it.
Please tell me.
Shinjuku or Ikebukuro? Which one?
It's not which one.
We'll go to a huge fan.
Let's do that.
It's only natural for Yama-chan to go there.
That's for sure.
Right?
If Heipo-san comes...
If the god of comedy comes...
Then I'll ask later.
I'll ask which one is bigger.
You can do it.
It stinks.
There are too many flowers.
In that sense, we want to go to a huge fan.
Please let us go.
From now on, Downtown-san and Kokoriko will go to a huge fan.
I got it.
Shinjuku or Ikebukuro?
It's one of them.
Which one will you choose?
It's up to Yama-chan.
This is really up to me.
If Saito-san takes me there...
Which one will you choose?
Ikebukuro.
Are you going to Tobiko?
It's about the same distance.
About the same distance.
I got it.
Then I'll go to Shinjuku.
Are you sure?
I'm leaving it to Yama-chan.
I'll go to Shinjuku.
I got it.
It's a match.
Why did you decide to go to Ikebukuro?
Well, I've always...
When I first moved to Tokyo,
I went to Ikebukuro.
It's a big city in Tokyo.
It's a very popular place.
I see.
I think everyone is waiting for me.
I'm scared.
I'm so sad.
Well,
it's up to Yama-chan.
We've been waiting for you.
That's right.
I want him to come.
You want him to come, right?
Yes.
If he doesn't come,
I think it'll be fine.
I'm not going to win.
I'm going to be a normal person.
There might be people who think that.
I think he's calling.
Hello?
Yamazaki?
Yes.
Are you here?
Yama-chan is quiet.
Yamazaki-san seems to be in a bad mood.
No, I'm fine.
Really?
Everyone is laughing at me.
Of course,
if you come in,
you'll be able to laugh.
Thank you.
There's a bigger fan.
That's good.
The fan is really big.
What about HEPO?
HEPO?
Hello?
Yes.
I'm HEPO.
Sato-san.
You're HEPO.
You're wearing underwear.
Yes, I'm wearing it.
That's right.
HEPO, are you ready?
Yes, I just arrived.
You're really slow.
Are you two okay?
What's going on?
What did you two do?
I don't know what's going to happen,
but we're waiting for you.
Please come to the entrance.
Yes.
I'm a little nervous.
I don't want to be nervous about something like this.
Have you arrived at the entrance?
Please come.
What about HEPO?
I'm here.
Yes.
I'll count from 5 seconds ago.
Open the door at 0 and come in.
Let's go.
5 seconds.
4, 3, 2, 1.
Go!
What are you doing?
Here, here, here.
You have to get to this point.
That was close.
I got it.
I got the feeling.
I got it normally.
I'm not going to fly.
So Yamada-san is alive now?
That's right.
Zaki-san.
Really?
We can't see the picture over there.
We can't see it.
We have to see it.
We'll show you.
Over there, there's only one digital screen.
Thank you.
I cried because I didn't want to say anything.
It's cold.
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.