I'm in front of the Fuzigaoka station of the Tokyo Expressway.
You asked for my autograph, right?
You asked me to come here.
I'm going here today.
It's a student dormitory for female college students.
I've been waiting for a long time.
Who is this person?
I won't get caught.
When I'm dressed like this, it's the hardest thing not to get caught.
Being left behind is the hardest thing.
I can't move at all.
I've been told not to shoot the camera.
I can't shoot the camera.
I don't know if I'm going to get caught.
I thought I'd get in trouble.
I was told that I was an ASMR-maniac.
Is that so?
I'm going.
I'm going to be mislead.
Go away.
I'm acting with my face.
That's right.
That's it for today.
We don't have a student dormitory in downtown.
This program is brought to you by
Oyama International Products
Sponsored by
She's here.
She gave me a postcard.
I've been waiting for a long time.
What's your name?
I'm Miiki Okano.
Men are forbidden here, right?
My father can't get in.
Your father has never been in.
Open the fridge.
What is it?
It's funny.
You're hiding something.
You're cutting people up and putting them in.
Stop it.
It's funny.
What is it?
Where are you putting your underwear?
It's a secret.
I'm sure you're looking for it.
Don't look for it.
I'm looking for it in the trash.
There's a trace of powder.
When you were having a meeting,
I already put my underwear in your pants.
That's not true.
Wait a minute.
Look at this.
Don't do that.
I'm editing here.
That's terrible.
What do you hate?
I'm going to take Miiki to the cafeteria.
Miuki, come here.
Wait a minute.
What about the postcard?
The postcard.
In the middle.
I got a postcard.
It's here.
What is it?
I heard that you're looking for a group.
I'd like you to come to our student conference.
I wrote a lot of things.
There's a lobby and a large dining room floor.
It's perfect size for a joke.
It's a lie.
It's not a big deal.
You guys are being a joke.
No, I'm serious.
You're asking me to come.
There are many people who come in January.
I'd like you to come in February.
This is a big problem.
I'm going to be a joke.
Miuki has come to the room.
Everyone's room is the same.
I opened it up.
My ruler came out of the drawer.
It was a thermometer.
I brought my underwear.
This is a lie, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
Where are you going to see me today?
You're here.
Please sit down.
It's a student dormitory.
I've never been to such a place before.
I got there immediately when I went through the entrance.
I saw everyone's works.
304...
50...
I couldn't remember the number.
I wrote down the names.
I put a yellow pen in.
There was something like a yellow button in there.
And it says that the cleaning is done.
The green button.
So when I came back, I saw the yellow letter.
Amazing.
It's like a happy yellow handkerchief.
It's really well made.
But there are some strange men around here, right?
Around here?
Like a pant thief.
When you become like that, what can you do with an old man like that?
Just in case...
The room...
Poor guy.
Isn't that true?
Where did you get that?
When I saw it, I was surprised.
Right?
I took a survey earlier.
I saw a lot of things.
Everyone is pretty serious.
I thought you were doing a lot more.
Let's take a look.
What's your name?
He's my manager.
I'm Nitta Atsuo.
I'm from the production department of Yoshimoto Kogyo.
This is not pitiful.
Even if you know it's hard, you should do it.
Right.
His boyfriend is...
He's looking for a girlfriend.
Is he serious?
What do you think?
Take off your mask.
I have this.
It's okay. Take off your mask.
What do you think?
What are you talking about?
He's my manager.
What do you think?
What are you talking about?
Please think about it.
Please write it down.
I took a survey.
I saw a lot of things.
I'll show you some of them.
If you could make three wishes come true, what would you like to do?
I want to fly in the sky.
You want to fly in the sky?
I can't fly.
This is the world of Miyuki Nakajima.
A prince riding on a horse wearing white tights appears.
Does it hurt?
Who wrote this?
The prince is wearing tights.
It's a bit different.
It's tights.
I want you to be impressed.
I think this is good.
And...
What is your experience as a man?
I've never seen it with one hand.
You're good.
I don't have a yakuza.
I'm like B.
He's underestimating me.
What do you imagine as downtown?
Garakuta.
Come here.
He's underestimating me.
Think about it.
A sinner...
No.
You're the worst.
I don't have any complaints about you.
Why?
It's very comfortable.
I don't have any complaints about you.
I've just said hello to you.
But you're talking like an ectoplasm.
I'm going to kill you.
What do you want to do if you can make your wish come true?
I want to be a match girl.
That's good.
I want to be Hama-chan's child.
What is that?
You're wearing thick underwear.
From Godzilla.
What kind of underwear are you wearing from Godzilla?
Where are you drawing Godzilla?
All of them?
Is this part of Godzilla's mouth?
A small Godzilla is drawing a lot.
It's very comfortable.
It's a Godzilla.
It's a small Godzilla.
What did you just say?
Everyone has a family.
No.
I don't know if this girl is real or not.
There are 22 men.
That's amazing.
I looked at all the surveys.
Most of them said there were zero men.
Of course, there are the most men.
There are only one or two men who said they had experience.
There are 22 men.
That's amazing.
This is the first time I've been told this.
This is a foreigner.
You're a foreigner.
It's you.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You don't understand at all?
You're not Japanese.
You're a foreigner.
You're a Japanese.
You speak a little Japanese.
What's your nationality?
Where are you from?
From Afghanistan.
Where?
Afghanistan.
You're from Afghanistan.
That's amazing.
What's your name?
My name is Freebo.
Freebo?
Fever?
That's not it.
Say Freebo.
Freebo.
Ferrybo.
Let me introduce you to the people who have been watching this program.
There are quite a few.
You have to watch it properly.
That's not it.
Freebo.
Let me introduce you to the people who have been watching this program.
There are quite a few.
This person is from Kanagawa Prefecture.
He appeared before the TV program on Monday.
He appeared alongside with the Takahashi brothers.
It might check out.
They look alike.
You don't like being with the Takahashi brothers, do you?
They seem to be comparable.
The Takahashi brothers will take a break, and we will stand in their place.
We will stand in their place?
Yes.
We will dress up?
Yes, we will dress up.
What do you think?
I don't think this will be a punishment game.
I think it will be quite interesting.
Quite interesting?
For those who are watching.
This is...
Why are you guys there?
If we can do this, I would like to try it.
There are a lot of punishment games, but we have to decide who will win and who will lose.
What do you think about this?
According to what I heard, there will be a person who will be the last one.
Who will be the next one?
There will be a person who will be the last one.
It seems that there is a secret to know the order, but I don't know yet.
Really?
We have to guess who will be the last one, and the person who loses will be punished.
I see.
What?
You have to see it once.
By the way, this week it was Masuo.
What?
To what extent?
Do you have a family?
Do you have a Hanazawa family?
No, I don't have a family.
Look, this is the story of the Isono family.
It has nothing to do with Hanazawa family.
Is that so?
He is just a servant.
Who is it?
For the time being.
It's Masuo, right?
Yes.
I think it's Fune.
Somehow.
No, I think it's Katsuo.
That's right.
We have to decide which one.
Let's think about the punishment game.
That's it.
I want to hear about this article.
It's the spirit of the marathon.
For example, two people participated in the Honolulu marathon a year ago.
Of course, the TV station forced them to run.
Two people ran.
Hama-chan was down at 15 kilometers per hour.
Masuo-chan burned all the energy in his body and dried it.
It was an eight-and-a-half-hour marathon.
It's the spirit of the marathon.
It's true.
Wait a minute.
I have something to say.
It's not a dry run.
It's a dry run.
But even if I say it, it's dry.
You were really useless.
I was pathetic at that time.
A person who hasn't been exercising for a long time ran up to 15 kilometers.
His knees are lower than before.
I can run even if I drop 15 kilometers.
Then you run 15 kilometers.
What?
10 kilometers is a good pace.
Can you do it?
Yes.
If I run 12 or 13 kilometers, I can't move forward.
I can't run like an old man and an old woman.
I ran 15 kilometers in front of the Diamond Head.
Are you kidding me?
I can run 15 kilometers every morning.
You can't run.
You've never exercised.
I can run.
I can run up to here.
You can run.
You don't like to ride a train.
I ran 246 kilometers all the time.
You don't run.
Do you want to do something?
I don't care.
What do you want to do?
Let's run a marathon.
Let's run 15 kilometers lightly.
Let's run a marathon on this program.
Let's gather all the fans who want to run with us.
Let's run a marathon.
Let's do it.
You...
You were making a lot of noise.
Why did you make a noise?
I want to do something for people.
What are you talking about?
I want to give a sponge to people.
You want to give a sponge to people who run?
Who want to give a sponge to people?
I will do it.
I want to do it.
It doesn't matter.
I can run fast.
I will do it before I reach the goal.
I will wait for the goal from the previous run.
I can't take a picture with the camera because it's too fast.
I can put as many as you want.
I'm more confident with the water painting.
Oh, you can do it with the water painting.
I'm good at water painting.
I have a lot of friends in the car.
I used to go to Triathlon.
I've been to Triathlon in Osaka.
Mr. Ike. Mr. Ikeda.
Mr. Ikeda was 47 years old and Mr. Ikeda was 25 years old.
Mr. Ikeda and Mr. Ikeda trained together for a long time.
I was very impressed.
When I approached the goal, everyone was crying.
When I was very impressed, I said,
Mr. Ikeda, come here.
The goal is a little further.
There was a tape of the goal.
Mr. Ikeda, come here.
Everyone was crying.
Everyone was saying, oh, my God.
I was very impressed.
He was cutting the tape.
That's it.
But it was the first time I was interviewed like this.
Everyone has to be able to imitate it a little more.
It's sad.
I'm one of the five imitators.
This is the last one.
There are 108 imitations.
The 74th one.
What?
This is Takeda Tette.
The 74th one of the 108 imitations is Takeda Tette.
Everyone, listen carefully.
This is how you imitate something that makes money.
Good luck.
What?
I'm out of breath now.
Why are your eyes white when you do this?
This is Takeda Tette.
Is that so?
Takeda Tette was looking at me like this with his eyes white.
That's right.
The 74th one.
What?
What is the number of the 108th one of the 108 imitations?
Number eight.
Number eight?
That's a young number.
Did you remember that early?
Yes.
Number eight.
That's a young number.
This is the new one.
The new one?
The first one.
What number is that?
This is the 108th one.
There were 108 before.
What?
This is the 109th one.
This is a lie.
This is the new one.
Hey!
Kato Shimura!
I'm sorry.
What?
I got it now.
What is the number of the 109th one?
Let's think seriously about this.
What?
People who are good at imitations, or people who are good at imitations,
rather than saying their names,
I don't do that.
Kato Shimura, you know who he is, right?
But he never said the name of Ikariya Chousuke.
But that's what Kato Shimura said.
That's what's amazing.
He just said that it's frustrating to make Saigo Hideki.
No one said Saigo Hideki.
It doesn't matter if it's true or not.
It would have been better if he didn't say Takeda Tetsuya.
That's right.
Even if you don't do it, you'll know.
Even if you don't say your name, you can do it.
You'll know who it is.
Well...
Well, somehow...
When did you...
That's Sakurai Joichiro, right?
I don't know him.
Sakurai Joichiro used to do it a long time ago.
Morishige Hisa?
Morishige Hisa.
Who told you to collapse?
It's already time.
Oh, really?
Yes, really.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, everyone.
How was it?
Did you have any clients?
Are you asking me?
Yeah.
Who told you to collapse?
I'm not in the right direction right now.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to quit a lot of things.
Marathon.
What?
What are you going to do?
What about the marathon?
Marathon?
Yeah.
I don't want to go to the marathon anymore.
Really.
Who do you think you are?
Are you popular?
Why are you talking about the marathon?
Are you a marathon person?
It's boring.
I'm a three-distance runner.
Wait a minute.
It's a short distance.
But I can run lightly up to 15 kilometers.
No, no.
Let's have a three-distance race.
Let's do that.
50 meters.
I've ever grabbed a cheetah's tail.
Where is it?
Where do you want to go?
I've ever grabbed a cheetah's tail.
That's why.
Where can you do that?
I'd like to go to see a lot of things again.
I'll do it on my way.
This comedy is big.
I think there will be a lot of battles like this.
I'm sleeping.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
I'll go to your place again.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
I'll go to your place again.
Goodbye.
See you next week.