We're going to a lot of places.
Hello, good evening.
Today, we're going to Azabu shopping street.
There are a lot of foreigners here.
There are a lot of them.
Really?
I'm good at English.
Let's talk to them.
Hello.
That's not right.
What?
You're good at English, so you should say it in English.
How about this?
That's not right at all.
I think it's good for the show.
I wonder if they'll talk to us more.
How about the rice cracker?
Oh, tanuki.
Oh, they're baking it here.
That's right.
They're baking it here.
Oh, this sound.
That's right.
This is the sound.
This person.
Yes.
Is this person dead?
That's not right.
No, not yet.
Yui Asaka is next to her, right?
Yui Asaka is dead, right?
That's not right.
When she did the rice cracker in the drama.
That's right.
She died or something.
I see.
That's right.
Are you a otaku?
What?
Otaku.
We're otaku.
We're called B21.
One of us is off today.
Shin is off right now.
Yes.
I'm Hiromi.
Wow, there's no one here.
What is this place?
What are you doing?
Camera-san, you'd better stop it.
Oh, it's raining.
You'd better stop it.
This is the tail.
Now, let's look at the venue.
Let's do our best today.
I wonder what kind of stage it is.
It's not over yet.
What?
I'll take you down to the bottom.
We're all going to be in a bag.
What kind of staff is there?
It's not over yet.
What?
Is this okay?
It's scary.
I'm going to take you down to the bottom and surprise you with a local person you know.
A local person?
It's a container.
Oh.
This is today's stage.
No, but this is...
The sound has become brighter, hasn't it?
I'm glad.
This is the first time I've heard this on this show.
I've never heard it before.
Today, we're going to start with the container.
We're not going to use the machine, so we're going to record it.
Please take your time.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Good evening, everyone.
Today, we're going to study the words.
A.
Let's study about A.
There are many things about A.
We don't know anything about it.
We're doing research on A.
Let me introduce you to a teacher.
Here she is.
Ms. Uehara Yoyogi.
Nice to meet you.
She's a student of my research.
She's in front of you.
Nice to meet you.
Ms. Masashime.
This is the A that comes to your mind.
Thank you very much.
Next is the A that comes to your mind when you're thinking about something.
Ms. Masashime.
You've already done it.
Next is the A that comes to your mind when you're thinking about something.
Thank you very much.
I see.
Isn't it strange?
It's correct.
Please.
Next is the A that comes to your mind when you're thinking about something.
The A that comes to your mind when you're thinking about something.
Please listen carefully.
Ms. Masashime.
I'm sorry.
I'm running out of time.
I see.
Next is the A that comes to your mind when you're thinking about something.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
I'm running out of time.
Good evening, everyone.
Today, I'm going to make the A that comes to your mind when you're thinking about something.
Let's think about it together.
Now, let me introduce you.
Researcher Mi.
Ms. Akasaka Mitsuke.
How are you doing?
Well then, Ms. Mitsuke.
Please present the results of your research in front of everyone.
First of all,
the A that comes to your mind when you're thinking about something.
The A.
Ms. Masashime.
I'm sorry.
I'm running out of time.
The A.
Next is the A that comes to your mind when you're thinking about something.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to make the A that comes to your mind when you're thinking about something.
Good evening, everyone.
You don't have to be calm all the time.
Today,
I'm going to make the A that comes to your mind when you're thinking about something.
Let's think about it together.
Now, let me introduce you.
The Philippine Researcher, Mr. Gyohei Shinjuku.
Today,
I'm going to present the results of my research in front of everyone.
First of all,
the A that comes to your mind when you're thinking about something.
The A that comes to your mind when you're thinking about something.
The Philippine Researcher.
I'm sorry.
I'm running out of time.
The Philippine Researcher.
I'm sorry.
Next week,
I'm going to make the A that comes to your mind when you're thinking about something.
Let's say goodbye to Mr. Gyohei Shinjuku.
Thank you very much.
Goodbye.
I didn't mean to change anything.
I'm glad I could talk like this.
Well, today.
I feel like my face is getting tanned today.
Why?
I feel like I'm doing something stupid.
If you feel stupid, look at me.
It's weird, isn't it?
What the hell is the Philippine?
Because I keep thinking about the other me.
When I was doing that story.
When I was told that I was doing a Philippine research,
I was reminded of the Philippine.
And I was thinking of the other me.
No way. No way.
I'm laughing when I'm thinking of the other me.
No one is laughing at me.
Today's story was a little short.
That's right.
I did a research on a story I'm good at.
It's been a while.
It's true.
The number of audience is a little less than usual.
This is the best.
Isn't it just right?
I always say that kind of thing.
What's wrong with this program?
It's not girly at all.
That's right.
Right?
For example,
Even with a microphone.
That's right.
This kind of thing.
It's okay if a girl comes out.
It's really like the rubber of Utopia.
This kind of thing.
You are also against it.
That kind of thing.
So, for example,
Asking for an assistant.
That's good.
Right?
Let's ask for an assistant.
Yes.
That kind of thing that doesn't go home at all.
That's good.
That kind,
Of science always,
We will be walking with a sleeping bag on our back.
That kind of things.
That kind of?
If you Usually like to use only this,
What will you do with that.
It would be okay of assistant,
Girls too.
But to ask for an assistant,
aring like this?
Like a man!
Will you choose this?
By a microphone?
Eh?
I'm receiving a note.
Okay.
This is very good품, isn't it?
Yes, of course.
From Nonaka Ariko-san?
Ikuko-san.
Ikuko-san? 19 years old.
Do you two get along well with B21 Special?
Which do you like better, Ucchan Nan-chan or B21 Special?
I hate both of them.
They both work together.
they work together.
They work together at 7 or 8 pm.
Golden Time, the national online.
There is a story of two old Japanese people.
Also, the quiz derby is in the back.
They are strong.
There is no way I can win.
I saw it earlier, there was a hope for four people.
Even though it's a hope for two.
They write down I really want to go.
In a highlighter.
If you can't do it, there are two of you.
What is this?
Just say it!
I got a little weak for a moment.
I thought it would be bad if I was told that I can't do it.
If you can't do it, there are two of you.
It was interesting.
If you look at the news, it says,
It says,
I don't really watch it.
If it's a long show, you can just say something like,
something that's easy for everyone to say.
I don't watch downtown.
That's not it.
It's downtown.
Where are you going to summarize it?
Seriously, I don't watch it.
On the radio and live, it's a place where you can hear a lot of harsh words, but on TV you can't really see the fun in it.
Since we're doing a show at night, I expect you to be able to get the most out of it.
Are you trying to crush me?
We've only just started.
Right?
It's late at night, so you're allowed to say a little bit.
How long should I say it's late at night?
Hmm...
If it's harsh words, you can say,
You can say it's like a golden egg.
A golden egg.
From now on, when you're talking, you can say it's like a golden egg.
What do you think?
Like the missu-zu from Hana-no-Oen-dan.
I can only tell by the sound.
Have you gotten used to Tokyo?
I don't think I've gotten used to it.
The distance between Osaka and Tokyo is really hard.
Why?
There are only two options at that time.
You can take the Shinkansen or the plane.
I don't like either.
I don't know what to do.
Which is better, the plane or the Shinkansen?
The Shinkansen is better.
It's easier.
The plane is no good.
You can take the Shinkansen slowly,
but if the person next to you or the person behind you is a terrible person,
it's going to be three hours of trouble.
There are annoying people.
The monkey family.
The monkey family?
The other day,
there were two people lined up,
and there was a seat next to them.
The husband and wife,
and probably the husband's mother was a grandmother.
There were two grandmothers and two children.
And the children were screaming.
And the children,
I remember them screaming.
That's right.
I've been thinking about it for three hours.
During that time,
me and Matsumoto were pretending to sleep like this.
The monkey grandmother didn't say anything.
The grandmother didn't say anything.
After all,
she was very angry.
Why?
She was on the Shinkansen.
There was a grandmother who loved the monkey family.
There was a father and a mother.
There was an ice cream in front of them.
Shut up!
They were so angry.
It was really amazing.
They were screaming.
The mother didn't say anything,
but the grandmother said,
It's annoying, so be quiet.
It was really amazing.
It was my fault.
I probably should have held the monkey's hair.
Shut up!
I probably should have held his face.
I was angry.
On the day of the
children's holiday,
everyone was carrying too many children on the Shinkansen.
That's right.
In the past, children couldn't ride the Shinkansen.
The children were so angry that they couldn't ride the Shinkansen.
The monkey grandmother was screaming.
The Shinkansen children ate a lot.
They rode the Shinkansen from Tokyo for three hours.
When they arrived in Osaka,
they became a little bigger.
They became a little bigger.
They had a voice.
What did they eat?
Did they eat ice cream?
Did they eat eel?
Shut up!
What did the monkey grandmother say?
She looked like a fool.
The monkey grandmother looked like a fool.
It was my fault.
The airplane was scary.
No matter how noisy the airplane was,
it was better to ride the Shinkansen than the airplane.
You were scared.
I was scared.
Why?
You were scared just by shaking a little.
When I got on the Shinkansen,
I decided to fall.
I thought it was impossible.
When I got on the Shinkansen,
the monkey grandmother said,
Welcome.
I thought,
Is that the monkey grandmother?
I was scared.
My family was on the Shinkansen.
My mother wanted to eat a candy.
My mother said,
Please wait until you get on the Shinkansen.
I was surprised.
You are laughing.
Why are you laughing?
The Shinkansen has a tarp.
There are 2 tarps.
You shouldn't ride from the front.
Why?
If you ride from the front,
you can't see the pilot's face.
There was a time when Mr. Yasui was there.
The pilot was on the tarp and was yawning.
He went into the cockpit and played.
Don't say that.
You are risking a person's life.
Why are you yawning?
I don't get it at all.
It's better not to see the pilot's face.
Why?
If the pilot is a man, it's safe.
If he's a kid, right?
If he has a face like a thin sword, it's like,
Are you okay?
The guy who got on the plane before,
He looks like KENSHI TAKAMI.
Are you okay?
I'm scared.
It can't be helped.
What about food?
I like Osaka food, but I don't like Osaka food.
I don't think Osaka food is that good.
Have you ever been to Tokyo?
I've been there.
I was surprised.
There was a game on the iron plate.
I ate this deliciously with a small iron plate.
These guys, these guys.
This is a little...
What's a small iron plate?
It's kind of sticky.
If you like it, it's going to be hard.
It's going to be hard.
It's still hard.
I don't know what it is.
I had a friend in KITA SENJU.
It's a suburb, isn't it?
What kind of Tokyo do you have a friend in KITA SENJU?
When did you have a friend in KITA SENJU?
What?
Don't say that kind of thing.
Even if I get hit, I'll never move my face.
It's strange that Tokyo people like natto.
Do you like natto?
Everyone likes it.
You don't like it, do you?
Well, there are people like that.
People in Osaka don't like natto.
There's nothing I can't eat.
I don't think I'll eat it because I like it.
I don't think so.
That smell, that smell.
The smell of natto is the smell of my father's feet.
I can't eat it from now on.
What's the smell of your father's feet?
When my father comes home, he's sitting in that area.
Do you know how smelly it is?
My father is smelly.
He's the third in KITA HANKYU.
He's smelly.
Tell me the number one.
My father came home one day and collapsed at the entrance.
Everyone in the family is smelly.
It's a serious story.
I had to change my pajamas.
When I changed my pajamas, my father said,
It's true.
What is this person?
My father said,
When did you fart?
It's true.
It's serious.
There's a lot of things.
Well, thank you very much.
It's time to say goodbye.
Like I said earlier,
What if I do this?
What about that?
I'll tell you what I'm going to do.
If you want to be a model,
I'll give you a picture of my face.
Only my face?
Only my face.
My face is cute, but I can't make money by doing this.
Your face is cute, but you look cute in the picture.
But when I look at you, you're a big guy.
That's hard.
There's a lot of highlights on your face.
You're a big guy.
I'm not a big guy.
I'll be waiting for your comments.
Please send me a lot of letters.
Hello.
Good evening.
It's over.
How was it today?
What do you mean?
I thought it would be fun to talk to a lot of people before I came in.
That's right.
But if there's no one suddenly, it'll be a mess.
I'd like to walk where there's a lot of people.
It depends on the place.
That's why I'm doing this show in a lot of places.
I think I can meet a lot of people in a lot of places.
I think that's a good thing.
When you came out today, there was a car, right?
What was that like?
Isn't it good?
That's about it.
Yeah, it's better than that.
I'll never make the same mistake again in Osaka.
I'll come out in a month and get a paper tape.
There was a guy.
There was a guy in the middle.
It's funny that only he knew.
It's funny that only men know.
Next week, I'd like to go to Soi.
I've heard about the place, but I've never been there.
I'm talking about a man and a woman right now, but it's not me.
So next week, I won't forget my menta.
If you suddenly go, it'll hurt.
I'll go after I'm done sewing.
I'm pretty good at it.
You don't need a mentor?
I don't need one.
Then I'll do it.
How was it at first?
It wasn't good at first, but...
It's a mess.
There's a lot of opinions, so I don't know what this is about.