Seijo Gakuen
A luxury residential area where famous people such as Seikai, Zaikai, and sportsmen set up a luxurious house.
In particular, in the entertainment world, the houses of the residents, including Mr. Ishihara Yujiro, who is now crying, are lined up.
Today, the downtown was guided by a guide and I came to visit the mansion, but I couldn't get in.
So I visited the mansion of this person.
Everyone, this is Mr. Yuzo Kayama's house.
It's strong, isn't it?
Let's go in.
Actually, you can go in here.
You can go in here.
Wait a minute.
Camera.
Oh, it's you.
I've been found out.
I'm doing ping pong.
No.
I can't go in here, so I can't do ping pong.
Stop it.
Are you serious?
You can't go in here.
I can't go in here.
It's Mr. Kayama.
I said, can.
Mr. Kayama doesn't say, can.
You can't go in here.
Let's go.
The entrance is big.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Welcome.
Mr. Kayama's house is great.
No, it's not.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry for the sudden invitation.
It's okay.
Hey.
Why are you calling your wife?
Do you know that?
I know.
I didn't notice it myself.
You're athletic.
That's not true.
Hey.
Coming.
Welcome.
Why are you so surprised?
No.
You're surprised to see your wife.
Excuse me.
We're open.
My wife is always like this.
Your beauty hasn't changed.
You two are...
I'm happy.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Oh, right.
Why don't you take off your clothes?
It's okay.
Don't be shy.
No.
There's food on the second floor.
Come with me.
Don't be shy.
Excuse me.
Thank you for the food.
It's delicious.
Excuse me.
We have to go to work.
Take this.
Oh, right.
What?
Can I?
Let's go.
I'll take it.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Hello.
It's amazing.
We ate a lot.
You helped us a lot.
And you gave me a gift like this.
You should have brought more.
I didn't think you'd come.
I took care of you.
I'm glad you came.
It was worth it.
You're the best.
Let's go home.
Ladies and gentlemen.
I heard that today's guest is very heavy.
Really?
You're laughing a lot.
No, no, no.
I'm laughing a lot.
Yamazaki-kun said last time that he couldn't take it at all.
He said today's guest is heavy.
No, no, no.
I'm laughing a lot.
Huh?
You can't take it, can you?
I can't take it.
No, no, no.
But you're amazing.
It's good.
I'm the boss of the bus over there.
What?
Are you going to make it popular again?
It's a little bit.
Why?
What's popular?
I've seen that kind of magazine.
That stupid thing is popular.
Like the old man from Bulldozer.
What's that?
Cat.
Is that called a cat?
That's popular.
I saw that magazine.
That's totally popular.
It's a coincidence.
It's good.
What's good?
You're like a young man's brother.
You're a leader who pulls young people.
What are you talking about?
No one says that.
I'm not.
I'm not aiming for that.
What's that?
You're a wild man.
I don't watch your drama.
I heard rumors that you make people cry.
That's good.
Why do you say that?
That's what you're going to do.
No, no, no.
I heard you're making people cry.
I don't know.
I'm doing my best.
No, no, no.
You have to do it properly.
You made me cry.
Who made you cry?
You made me cry for 24 hours.
I'm going to cry for a long time.
I'm going to cry for 24 hours.
You don't calculate, do you?
You say this, you say that.
My popularity is here.
I'm doing my best.
Who said that?
This guy and Megumi calculated a lot.
Wait.
Megumi didn't calculate.
Did you see Megumi recently?
She dyed her hair.
What's wrong with her?
She's being selfish.
First of all, she lost weight.
She lost a lot of weight.
That's right.
Why did she become like that?
It's her fault.
I can't talk to you.
No, no, no.
You're wearing a tie.
I was going to close it.
But I thought about the microphone.
It's a microphone that can't be closed.
I was going to close it from the beginning.
That's why I'm wearing it here.
It's cool.
That's how it is these days.
No, no, no.
These days, the tie is here.
I think it's going to be popular.
When you do it, you put it in here.
That's not popular at all.
Who's popular?
I've been wearing a tie for a long time.
Who's the only one who wears a tie here?
I still can't break it.
I'll tell you the truth.
How long are you going to wear a tie like that?
It's your fault.
Wait, wait, wait.
Have you ever seen me make it like this?
That's right.
This is how you make it.
You can't buy it at all.
No, my hair quality is impossible.
I can't do that.
No, no, no.
You have to try it.
I can't do it.
You didn't set it up today.
That's why it's messed up.
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
Put it down.
It hurts because I'm wearing a tie.
You're a Tetsuro Kanba.
Don't be so hard on my hair.
Why don't you try it?
I had my hair tied up yesterday.
I don't care about that.
What?
I woke up a little early today.
I got my passport.
Passport.
I don't care.
I'm going to New York to record at the end of this month.
Thank you.
Don't be so hard on me.
I've already decided on the costume.
That's tough.
I'm going to tell you now.
Why?
What are you going to do?
How do you spend your time on the plane?
There's something to talk about.
What?
With the person next to you?
Is that what Ju-san is doing?
People who talk talk.
Do you know why you're on the plane?
You don't even know that.
You can't get on.
When the plane falls, it falls from above.
What's that?
What do you mean?
Don't ask me if you know.
You've done this far.
When the plane falls, it falls from above.
What's that?
If I tell you, you'll make fun of me.
It falls from above.
What's that?
You know.
When the plane falls, it falls from above.
Oh, that.
Put it here.
Oxygen bomb.
Oxygen is sent here.
What?
What do you call that?
Oxygen bomb.
Bomb.
It's not a bomb.
That oxygen bomb.
It's a bomb.
Put it here.
I want to be saved.
That's strange.
What?
That oxygen bomb is completely falling.
That's strange.
The oxygen bomb isn't falling.
It's falling.
It's not just you.
The oxygen bomb is falling.
Everyone is falling.
Everything is falling.
What are you relying on?
I don't know.
Safety belt.
Safety belt?
When did it fall?
It's always falling.
That's strange.
I don't understand.
It's always falling.
You understand.
I can't say it's always falling.
I don't understand.
It's always falling.
The air is completely empty.
But we also do this.
I put my knees here like this.
What's that?
What?
Does anyone do that?
How did I explain it to you?
Is that the Thai airport?
Why did you do that to me?
Tell me!
Thai guys are scary.
You have to do this right away.
My teeth are getting swollen.
It's scary.
I'm scared.
But it can't be helped.
If I'm going to die anyway, I want to die with the person I love.
What are you talking about?
Because you're so uncool!
You said you were going to record in America,
and you were going to go to Geisha Girls,
and then you fell off the plane and died.
I didn't know that at all.
You said a lot of funny things to the old man at the bar.
About what would happen if I died.
You don't trust him anymore?
He's a soldier, too.
I can't help it.
You're a fool.
You keep saying that.
What's going on?
You don't trust me anymore?
I said that, didn't I?
I don't trust you anymore.
You're a fool.
Why do you say that to a foreigner?
Well, that's fine.
Again?
I'm just trying to get a hold of you.
I think it's pretty popular.
He's scared.
What are you going to do with your shoulder?
Turn it!
What are you going to do with your arm?
What about your right hand?
You're sitting down.
What are you going to do?
You're lying down.
Why are you lying down?
Let me hear it.
What do you think?
Say something.
I'm Aoi. I'm 17 years old.
I'm 17 years old.
This is a hot topic.
This finger.
Really?
I'm an intercept.
That's what happens during a match.
And you're an intercept.
Intercept is not a position.
It's not a position.
What's your name?
Eri Sato.
Are you a singer?
I'm going to be a singer.
You're going to be a singer?
Thank you very much.
I have a question for both of you.
Why do you look at your watch?
I don't know.
Watch?
Please look at your watch.
What time is it now?
Why do you look at your watch like that?
I look like that.
But you look like that.
It's not that. It's a gesture.
It's a gesture.
Look at your hair.
You're so mean.
You're a gesture.
It's you.
What time is it now?
Can you ask him?
Where are you looking at?
Where?
You're looking here.
Your eyes are not the same.
No, that's not it!
Ask him!
What time is it now?
What are you doing?
He's not here, right?
No, he's not here!
What are you doing?
He's not here, right?
So, why is that?
No, no, no, that's because...
Look at the clock.
Right?
Oh no, it's the same.
It's the same?
No, no, no, that's not it.
You can't do it like this.
You can't even look at the clock like this.
That's because you know it.
You can't do it like this, so you do it like this.
Why is he angry?
Bite me.
Who's going to bite me?
The face on the spoon looks like it's upside down.
Is this someone's trick?
The mirror doesn't look like that.
Why?
You should think about that.
That's not it.
Today, your postcard...
You didn't answer at all at the end.
What?
You only listened to people and didn't talk at all.
In your postcard.
Oh no.
No, no, no.
You didn't talk at all.
I don't like it.
I didn't ask you why you didn't drink it.
Don't lick the spoon.
To put it simply, don't lick the spoon.
It's really easy to say now, so I think it's hard to understand.
It's easy to say, but it's hard to understand.
I just said it randomly.
Don't lick it.
I understand that you don't lick it, so why did you say it the other way around?
I really want to hear that now.
Not now.
You can't hear it unless it's now.
I want to hear it now.
Let's close our eyes for a moment.
No, no, no. You should talk.
Then, let's stand up for a moment.
No, no, no.
You don't have to stand up.
I'm calm now.
You should talk.
Spoon.
Spoon is curry.
Wait a minute.
Don't lick the spoon.
You didn't say it at all.
You should have said it from the beginning.
Spoon is curry.
Curry is spicy.
Wait a minute.
Who told you to say something like that?
Spicy is kimchi.
Right?
Kimchi.
Kimchi is pickled.
Yes, yes.
Pickled is upside down.
And upside down.
Let's go home.
No, no, no.