Tokyo, Japan
Ladies and gentlemen
It's been a while
We've been to Okinawa
To the southern island
Tokyo is...
Not Tokyo, but Japan was tough
What was tough?
The typhoon
It was tough, wasn't it?
Listen to yourself
It was really tough
But Osaka was tough, wasn't it?
Osaka was tough
The typhoon was so strong that I almost fainted
It's rare in Osaka
I had to go out
Why?
Why did you have to go out when it was raining and windy?
I was going to send this
That was a lie
It's fine
It was so windy
What do you call that?
Just like that
It was so windy
Just like what you said
Look
It was so windy
When did you prepare it?
It's winter today
I'm wearing winter clothes
I'm wearing all the summer clothes
Stop it
What is it?
It was so windy
There were about three typhoons today
There were
Was it really a typhoon?
My mother also said it was a typhoon
You have to say it
It was really a typhoon
I don't want to hear it
For today's opening
We went to the preliminary round
Let's eat
Here you go
Thank you
I'm wearing the same shoes as last time
Please turn to your right
Thank you
There are three places
I'm sorry
Please take care of it
Thank you
You should have taken care of it
You are a regular
This is the second time
I'm still nervous
I think it's better to start from here
I'm a professional when I put makeup on my face
So it doesn't matter if I put a mole here
It doesn't matter
I don't have that much time
Excuse me
Sen Masao
No
I don't have that much time
It's totally different
It doesn't look like Kin-chan
But it looks like Kin-chan
Don't hide it
It looks like Kin-chan
Next is No.155
I'm glad
I'll give you a score
I'm sorry
I did my best
Please give me a score
Are you doing it by yourself?
I'm doing it by myself
Please give me a score
You are so cute
Just a little more
I did it
Did you do it by yourself?
Yes
You did it by yourself
Please give me a score
I did it by myself
I brought this by myself
You are so cute
Please give me a score
I can't win
Don't lower it
Please give me a score
I got it
Thank you
I did my best
I got 100% of my power
Thank you
Let's have an interview
This is the best
You are so cute
Please give me a score
I did it
You are so cute
Hello
Thank you for the interview
Thank you
This is the result of the screening
I see
Thank you
I know you are watching
Where are you going?
Tell me
I want to ask you
Where are you going?
What?
I see
Where are you going?
Hey
What is the result of the screening?
I will tell you
We passed the screening
Really?
Are you kidding me?
No
Really?
We did it
Thank you
We passed the screening
He was kind
He didn't say that before
Yes, he was kind
I thought I could do it
Let's hear from Momoya
No
It's 3 o'clock
What are you talking about?
Let's go
We will continue next week
But the screening is already decided
We have to go forward
What are we going to do next?
We have to think about the next step
The staff is moving
Are you going to do something else?
Yes
What is it?
It's a word
Are you going to do it?
Yes
It's a word
We are going to rent the Tokyo Dome
We talked about it
No, we didn't
If we rent the Tokyo Dome
40 million yen
Give it to me
Give it to Mr.
Give me 100 yen
40 million yen
This is amazing
It's cheap if we rent the Tokyo Dome
It's noisy
40 million yen for the event
40 million yen
If we don't return it, we will be fined
It's not a rental video
We have to return it
What are you talking about?
This is impossible
40 million yen
We don't have that kind of money
We don't have money
We have to pay for the whole set
We have to ask people to come
How many people?
Well
We have to ask a lot of people
Yes
So we have to ask 1000 people
1000 people with long beards and kimono
1000 people
We are talking about 1000 people
What?
These guys are crazy
I laughed for 10 minutes
You can't do that?
I can't
I laughed about insects
Ants?
Ants
You call them ants?
Are you stupid?
Ants?
You are crazy
So what?
1000 people
1000 people is 1000 people
These guys are crazy
1000 people
1000 people is 1000 people
I can't talk about politics with you
How many people?
More than 1000 people
We need more than 1000 people
1000 people is not enough
Why not?
It depends on what we do
I see
What?
We have to ask people to come
Yes
We had a meeting with them
I hope they come
These guys are not cooperative
They are not cooperative
They may be ignored
For example, 150 people are here
If we don't do anything, I will go
Yes
Half of 150 people are here
This program has 39% of viewers
Really?
It can't be
It's midnight
You have 39% of viewers at midnight
The next day you have to go to work
What are you talking about?
I think 5000 people will come
It will be great if 5000 people come
I think they will come
Really?
They will come
It depends on the place
Yes
Let's decide the place
Dome is out
Where is the wide place?
In Tokyo
Around here
Edogawa?
Where is Edogawa?
Is there a place like Kasenjiki?
Is there a place like Kinpachi sensei's walking?
Is there a place like that?
There are thousands of places like that
Really?
I don't know
I don't know the wide place
Is there a place like Kinpachi sensei's walking?
It's complicated from the top
Everyone is dressed up like Kinpachi
Let's go to Hagaki
Hello
My father is big
Your father is big
I didn't say that
Really
You can say it twice
Let's introduce
Yano Yumiko
He was born in 1946
He is 8 years old
19 years old
Do you live in Shinjuku?
I was born and raised in Shinjuku
That means you are from Hakata
I'm from Katakare
Who are you talking to?
I'm talking to my mother
I've been talking to you for a long time
I'm good at English
You are not good at English
Are you kidding me?
Don't talk to me like that
Why don't you talk to me?
Like this
You are cute
Thank you
Let's introduce
Hama-chan used to have a surgery in a hospital in Kansai
The nurse who came to get her signature was my sister
It's embarrassing when you get sick
I was there for a week
When I had a fever
I had to put a medicine in my butt
I put it in a lot
I don't understand
I don't understand, it's here
I don't know where it is
If you touch it with your finger, it's here
I couldn't put it in
The nurse came and I did it
It's my job
I couldn't put it in
I pushed it back
Why?
Why did you push it back?
Why? I'm weird
Really?
Yes
You have a lot of acupoints
I have a lot of acupoints
The acupoints were bent
I had to put it back
It was like a vending machine
The acupoints were bent
I don't like it when I can't look at my butt
But if you have acupoints, you can put it back
I've never had that
Like a nuisance
Men get excited
One of my friends went there
He got really excited
He was like an old lady
Young nurses get shy
But old ladies get used to it
I've been doing it for decades
What do you think?
He got really excited
The old lady went like this
It's true
Really?
Like this
Men get excited
Kimura Satoko from Nakano
She's 23 years old
Please introduce your boyfriend to me
Is there anyone in the staff?
I'm waiting for a call
Kimura Satoko, please send her a photo
Yes
Send her a photo
Send it to my staff
For the one who's going to do the interview
Put them in the opening
You can ask the person
Put them all together
I'll be in the photo
Why are you in the photo?
You know
Japan is a multi-labeled country
God only gives to one woman
When I went to Alta on the 5th of September
Hama-chan was nice
Matsumoto-san was not
But it was the other way around
The first time I went was last August
I was waiting next to the grape tree
When Hama-san came
We were glared at
We were really scared
The next Matsumoto-san's friend said
Excuse me
He raised his head
He didn't glare at me at all
Matsumoto-san and Hama-san
Which one is kind and which one is scary?
Please do your best
There's a technique like this
I'm not glaring at you
You're glaring at me
I'm not
In the past
Your bad habit
You're glaring at me
In the past
When we were doing Kinden
In the last episode of Kinden
Taisho
Kin-chan
He read everyone
And pointed out your bad habit
Matsumoto-san was perfect
He didn't say anything
Stop it
Really?
Thank you
Hama-san
You're glaring at me
That's not good
You shouldn't do that
You're still like this
Is that so?
Taisho
He's a man who got beaten up
Don't say bad things about me
You're always glaring at me
Why did you say sorry?
I don't understand
I didn't say anything
He didn't talk to me
It's fine
Other people are not that kind
Other than us?
Yes
Like you?
They're not that kind
If they're not that kind
We shouldn't think about it
Right
Can you do it?
What?
I don't do scary things
But you say I'm scary
What can I do?
I told you before
You're always glaring at me
I can't see
But you come to me
And ask me to sign
And I sign
What?
That means you don't do scary things
There are times when I do
Listen to me
I ask you to sign
And you sign
I want you to write your name
What's your name?
Nani
I have an exam
Good luck with your exam
Are you kidding me?
I won't sign
I'm serious
Good luck with your exam
You're so lame
Hey
Hi
Excuse me
I want you to take a picture
Sure
I can't do that
I'll do this
Can you take my sunglasses?
Sure
I'll take it
I want you to make a peace
I won't do it
I'll do it
Thank you
There are people who say I'm scary
I can't stand it
You've gone that far
There are people who say I'm scary
What?
This is new
I've never seen anyone do that
You've gone that far
I'll do it
I won't do it
Hey
Feel free to make your choice
I'm not afraid of it
I'll do it
You're so lame
What?
You've gone that far
Spare my life
I'll do it
I'd appreciate it if you could do that.
I don't know how many of you there are, but I'd like to do it.
Yeah, but it depends on the number of people.
It's better to decide what to do after you know the number of people.
That's right.
So I'd like to do it.
Please do it.
Let's do it together.
Oh, and the costume.
Next week, the continuation of the costume will be released.
Yeah.
The main story is out.
This is interesting.
It's more interesting than the costume of the main story.
No, I'm serious.
If you don't watch it next week, the continuation of the costume will be released next week.
Well, I'm looking forward to it.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best next week.
Goodbye.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.