I went to eat Cambodian food the other day.
Oh, your country's food?
I was like...
I was like, excuse me, can I have yakisoba?
Can you say it?
No, I want yakisoba.
What?!
I can't hear you!
Hey, you!
What?!
It's funny!
Are you serious?
Are you full?
No, I'm not.
Shut up!
Are you still full?
Yeah, I'm full.
Do you want anything?
I'm fine with anything.
What do you want?
Do you want yakisoba?
It's boring.
Excuse me!
Excuse me, yakisoba!
Get out!
He said yakisoba.
Where did you come from?
Did I change?
I'm full.
What about you?
I almost ate it.
Do you want anything else?
I'm fine with anything.
Do you want yakisoba?
Excuse me!
Yakisoba.
What?!
Are you serious?
It's so funny!
I'm full.
Are you serious?
I almost ate it.
What do you want?
I'm fine with anything.
I'm not full.
Are you serious?
Cambodia.
The Asian country located on the Indian Peninsula.
The fertile land where the tropical monsoon spreads,
and the national nature is still alive.
The mother river, Mekong,
flows through a total length of 400 km and makes life beautiful.
The Angkor Wat statues talk about the nature of the Khmer people.
The Cambodians are very experienced.
The Cambodians are known for their beauty.
The Cambodians are very polite.
The Cambodians are a peaceful nation.
If you raise your voice,
they will think that you are making fun of them.
I think that's why the Cambodians were so impudent.
The journey to Cambodia begins.
This is the Cambodian restaurant that Mr. Matsumoto told us about.
The Angkor Wat.
There is an old lady who is a fan of Cambodian food.
I only do 50% of Cambodian food.
I will show you the real Cambodian food.
Let's go.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Which one?
Bring me some water.
What did you order?
I didn't order anything.
You have a head that looks like a crane.
This is Cambodian food.
This is not enough.
How old are you?
31 years old.
Do you want to eat?
You are old enough to eat anything.
You are in your 20s.
You are in a club.
This is not enough.
Excuse me.
Yakisoba.
I'm embarrassed.
This is a lie.
Yakisoba is too obvious.
You can't say that.
Yakisoba.
Excuse me.
This is a lie.
Yakisoba.
This program is in the evening.
What time is it?
It's about 8 o'clock.
It's 2 o'clock in the morning.
You are still sleeping.
You woke up at 9 o'clock.
I woke up at 9 o'clock and ate yakisoba.
I gave you a tie.
What should I do?
I don't have time today.
I have to go home in 10 minutes.
I don't care about you.
You guys are angry.
Why are you laughing?
You guys are bad.
I'm not angry.
You don't have money at all.
I will check your wallet.
You are crazy when you are in a hurry.
In a different sense.
How are you doing these days?
There is a small newspaper.
I have something to say.
Say it.
There is a small newspaper.
What is this?
I have a small newspaper.
There's a Yu Kanji, isn't there?
Ah, there's a Yu Kanji.
No, there's a Yu Kanji.
I'm going to change my name!
There's a Yu Kanji.
Yoroshino.
What is it?
There's a Yu Kanji, isn't there?
Ah, there is, there is.
Moe.
No, no, no.
Ah, there is.
Ah, there is, there is.
Hey, hey.
I was on my face.
Oh, the Yu Kanji.
I was wondering what it was.
I was told I was in debt.
Eh, what's that?
Is that still a scoop?
I don't know what it is.
I don't know.
I was in debt.
I looked it up.
It says I have a secret code.
Really? I didn't know that.
What kind of newspaper is that?
It's a modern one.
You're getting worse and worse.
I'm not.
I looked it up one more time.
I was in a bubble.
The bubble burst and I was in debt.
I had that money.
I borrowed money for two reasons.
I borrowed money because I had a lot of debt.
When I asked the people from Yoshimoto, they said it was some kind of mistake.
That's the reason.
A certain production manager from Osaka said,
Hamada was putting his hand out on the stock.
Who the hell are you?
That's the first time I've heard about putting your hand out on the stock.
I'm not putting my hand out!
That's the first time I've heard about it.
I don't really know much about the Kaku Shigo case.
Stop it!
I don't know that much.
I was in middle school.
That's not true!
Why is it so big?
I was in grade 11.
Hideaki-kun.
I was wondering what the idea was.
I was surprised.
I was also writing something.
A kid's staff, an AD,
asked me to use something as a kid.
What was it?
He said, eat something alive.
You said that?
I was the one who said it.
That's right.
Stop it, Suji-kun!
Stop it, Hideaki-kun!
I get it!
You said you forced an AD to eat something alive.
When was that?
Stop it!
Sae-san!
You keep on writing things on your own!
Have you been writing that?
The other day,
I remember something.
I don't know!
My phone.
I have a lot of phones.
When I say something,
I get a bomb.
Yesterday,
I said,
Thank you for going to Bombay.
It was you, right?
It was worth it.
I will write a new song!
I'll say,
Let's play!
Who are you?
I told you to play with me.
I didn't say it, but he always talks about it.
He's a man, right?
Yes, he's a man.
He comes to the bar and says,
Hello, Machan! Machan!
Who the hell are you?
Die!
I don't want you to die.
Who are you talking to?
I'm not talking to you.
Who the hell are you?
What?
That's not what I meant.
I'm sorry.
I've been a celebrity for years,
but I've never been called that.
Who the hell are you?
Bye bye.
Stop talking like an old man.
No matter how you look at it, you're not a woman.
That's right.
You're wrong.
That's not true.
I'm not bad, am I?
You're bad.
I don't think so.
It's okay if you're bad.
But he's big.
He's big.
He's really good at hunting.
You're laughing.
You're a bad guy.
You're playing too much.
Where do you get the secret cheese that you always use?
Secret cheese?
You don't even turn your tongue?
Compared to when you made your debut,
I'm curious about how close you are to Matsumoto.
I'm a sneak.
Look.
I don't know.
What's a secret cheese?
What's that?
It's a secret cheese.
That's something else.
What's a secret cheese?
There's cream inside.
If there's cream inside, why are you wearing shoes?
You're sweating.
What?
That's not it.
It doesn't say secret cheese.
You're sweating.
I'm talking about secret cheese.
You're talking about secret cheese.
You're sweating.
I don't know if you're talking about secret cheese.
It's secret cheese.
The letter says secret cheese.
You're sweating.
Why are you wearing secret cheese?
I'm not wearing it.
I don't know about those shoes.
I'm not wearing them.
What's that?
These are normal sneakers.
He's talking about secret cheese.
But I'm not wearing them.
But you're talking about secret cheese.
I'm wearing them.
But I don't know what secret cheese is.
So please tell me.
Okay, I'll tell you.
Secret cheese means cream inside.
Why are you wearing those shoes?
I'm not wearing them.
Don't say that.
Sorry.
I should have said that earlier.
Secret cheese means cream inside.
I'm wearing them.
You're wearing shoes.
I'm not wearing them.
You're not wearing them.
Okay.
Don't wear them anymore.
I'm not wearing them.
I got it.
Do you feel better now?
I feel better now.
I'm okay now, right?
Yes.
Thank you.
You must be kidding me.
I don't know.
Who was the first person you talked to?
And what did you say?
What did you say when you first talked to me?
I said, I was born in Nagaya.
What are you talking about?
Why are you looking down at me?
You should treat him well.
What did you say when you first talked to me?
I said, I was born in Nagaya.
That's normal.
When I asked my parents, they said, I was born in Yoshinba.
Did you say something about that?
I said, I was born in Yoshinba.
What is Yoshinba?
Even if it was Yoshinba.
So there was something, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm stupid.
I heard that you were crying in Nagaya.
Yes, yes.
When my father told me, if you cry any more, I won't forgive you,
the first thing I said was, even if Yoshinba cried.
That's a long story.
What did you say?
Who?
When you first talked to me.
Don't these people start with shouting?
You can't talk to them for the first time.
Conversation?
What do you mean?
I don't know.
What do you drink?
Your memory of the circuit is now 1.
Matsumoto-san, you used to be in a group called Sexy.
Are you still active in the Sexy group that Matsumoto-san was in?
It's a story that hasn't happened yet.
You were in it properly.
Rather than saying that you were in it, I put you in it.
What?
Who?
I made a group called Sexy.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's why everyone put me in it.
I put you in it.
So you were the head.
I was the head.
Where did you run?
I ran a lot.
You made it with rain, right?
Yes.
Where did you run to?
Well, I ran to Yokohama and Shonan.
You ran to Yokohama?
From Hyogo prefecture to Yokohama?
I said I ran a lot.
You ran a lot in that sense?
Yes, yes, yes.
If you went to run once, you wouldn't run for a week, right?
That's right.
That's why you rarely...
You ran once and went to the toilet around there.
I had a lot of luggage.
Did you stay overnight?
That's right.
You prepared to stay overnight to run?
That's a little trip.
It's not a little trip, it's a little trip.
What little trip?
Well, it was really amazing.
It was cold.
What?
I couldn't continue because it was cold.
What do you mean it was cold?
You want to run whenever you want, right?
But we're cold.
Because we only wear bras.
You know, the long ones with the sleeves.
Sexy uniforms are usually worn with bras.
Because it's cold.
Because of the feet.
It's hard to wear this in the winter.
Basically, I wear it like this.
I wear heels like this.
That's a scooter.
But it's sexy.
Basically, I wear it like this.
Like this.
What?
Brandy.
Sometimes I eat chocolate.
What are you talking about?
I eat kiss chocolate.
Your eyes are fixed.
Everyone sees it, right?
I'm sexy.
There's a drink over there.
It wasn't popular, was it?
No, no, no.
I can only get five people.
I can't help it.
There's still one left.
I'm in a hurry.
Don't think it's normal for everyone to come like this.
Yo, Kami!
What are you doing?
I'm doing this.
You look like a frog.
You're a frog.
What am I wearing?
I always wear heels like this.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.