In the first episode of Aki no Tsukai Arahen, aim for a prize of 300,000 yen!
Aki no Uwaa Uwaa Sanbon Shobu!
Everyone, it's already autumn, so we have to move our bodies
Yes, it's the first month of the service
Today, we have Madsonsu-san and Endo team
Yes
Yama-chan and Tanaka team
The two teams, let's have a Sanbon Shobu
The winning team will receive a prize of 300,000 yen!
The losing team will lose
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
Let's go round and round! Toilet paper!
Haya-maki-tori-taiketsu!
It's easy
Yes
The team with the fastest start wins
I see
With this
I'm good at this
Let's start
Ready
Ah, it's a flute
The flute is...
Oharu Shoya
Pa pa pa pa
It's just a game, you can just bring the flute
What's wrong?
Why are you so angry?
It's not what you think
It's a flute
The director of Gaki no Tsukai, Komura Saki Kozo
With his charming smile and unique character, he captivates everyone
He's a famous idiot
Who is he?
A flute
A flute?
I don't have a flute
I didn't order it
You didn't order it? Why did you order it?
I brought the flute by myself
Who do you call a flute?
No, no, that's...
I'm sorry to say this
Why did you order it?
I didn't bring it
Who do you call a flute?
No, no, no
I didn't bring it by myself
That's strange
Who would bring a flute by himself?
Did you bring it by yourself?
I didn't bring it
What's wrong with you? How do you do this?
It's a good flute, so I can do it
I want a flute, but I don't have money, so I can't buy it
How much is it?
You can buy a flute
Don't you have anything?
What are you going to do?
I can't do it without something
I don't even know the price
Okay, I got it
Let's do this
I'll do it
What?
I'll do the flute
I don't understand what you're saying
What do you mean?
I'll do the flute
Let's do it
What are you going to do?
Do it for me
What?
Stop it
What are you doing?
Are you going to give it to me?
Give it to me
What?
That's a strange way of talking
It's a strange way of talking
What are you doing?
You have one minute
Okay
Let's go
Ready
Wait a minute
What's wrong?
Why are you laughing?
What?
It's him
It's not like that
It's not?
I think you have to use your smile
What?
You have to use your smile
I don't think that's a good thing
Okay, let's do it
I'll use my smile
Let's do it
Okay
Ready
Go
You're good
You can do it!
Time's up!
It's over.
It's hard to tell.
You don't know the answer.
You're just drawing.
Just drawing.
Bring it on.
OK, next game.
If I do it now, I don't know.
I don't know what this is
No-Ten-Kin-Kaki-Gori-Hayagui-Taiketsu!
This is the same
The time limit is 1 minute
How much can you eat?
It's going to be hard
I'm going to say 5 words in front of everyone
How much can you eat?
Come here, you're talking to me
Hayagui-Taiketsu!
Ready!
Go, go, go!
This is hard
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
I know, I know
Come on, hurry up
Let's go, let's go
Crush it, crush it
It's over!
Did you see that?
What?
If you say it after someone says it, you'll know
But you said 1 minute, didn't you?
It's not going to be a match
Then at least say it
That's impossible
It's hard to understand
It's the easiest to understand
Then can you say it?
I can say it
How do you say it?
I say it like this
That's hard
It's hard
I think it's hard to laugh
It's not hard
Are you laughing?
Just a little
Why?
Why are you laughing?
Bring it on
No, no, no
It's hard to understand
It's hard
It's not hard
Do you want to quit?
I'll quit
I'm getting goosebumps
Don't laugh
I don't understand
Crush it, fire badminton match
Winner
So far it's draw and draw
It's a draw
The prize money is 30 yen
The one who gets 7 points wins
7 points
Ready
I got it
Good
Which one?
Did it go in?
It went in
Which one did you get?
Yama-chan team got 1 point
What?
You got it?
I don't understand
Your voice is too small
That's fine
Ready
Don't laugh
What?
Are you laughing?
Your voice is too small
Stop laughing
Ready
I got it
Good
No gan
If it's no gan, laugh
What are you doing?
Can you see it?
It's starting
It's like...
It's like you're trying to make me laugh
I can't do it
You're not going to do it
You have to set the character
Bring it up
You're sweating
At least change the hat
Bring it up
Seriously
Bring a new hat
Is this a new hat?
Is it okay?
It's okay
Really?
That's fine
It's 0
You have to be confident.
You're confident and you're going to send it, right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Let's go.
This team first.
Ready!
What are you doing?
It's too long.
Why is it this side?
Let's go.
Good evening.
It's been a while.
It's been a while, right?
Well...
Road construction...
Can I eat this?
There's a road construction site, right?
They do this at night.
They do it like this.
When you're driving, they do it like this.
I don't know where you started.
You can do it like this.
You should study more and make rules.
I'm doing it properly.
Well, well, well.
I was driving at night.
I had two cars.
You don't understand the meaning, do you?
No, no.
That's why I told you to stop.
No, that's not it.
I was doing it like this.
I was having fun.
I stopped.
I opened the window.
I said, what are you doing?
The road is bumpy.
I want you to slow down.
Do you understand?
I don't understand that.
It's different from the originality.
I thought you were angry.
What is it?
The Japanese series will start.
The Japanese series will start on Saturday.
Kakeoka.
Which do you think it is?
That's a giant.
Really?
I'm a giant fan, so I have to cheer for the giant.
It's been a long time.
It's okay.
Where are you?
Naturally.
Well, then.
I'm a giant.
I'm not saying I'm a giant.
I pretended to be a giant.
I'm a giant fan.
I don't care.
Kakeoka,wrote a line that makes you laugh.
I re?
What's the matter?
Why do yo say that?
It's fun.
You can't do it.
You have to cut the intrigue.
I don't care.
You can use it as many times as you want.
I mean, there's no one who can kick his partner's ass as much as he wants.
You're right.
What do you think, Son-dan?
I don't think I can kick his ass.
Oh, really?
But you can do it.
Why?
Because I still have to leave my wife.
I have to protect her.
Oh, I see.
You don't have anything left, right?
I don't need it.
Oh, really?
I didn't know that.
You don't need it.
I just remembered.
You forgot something.
You're weird.
I don't need it.
You don't need it.
Why do you need it?
What do you use it for?
You can use it to pee.
Wait a minute.
How do you prove that you don't need it?
No, no.
That's just a hole.
A hole?
Yes, a hole.
I'll make two holes for you.
I don't want to prove it.
Just make one hole.
Then I'll make a hole like this.
Why?
I'll give you some momentum.
Like a rubber nozzle.
Like this?
You don't need it, right?
Why don't you need it?
I'll cut it.
Because you don't need it.
You don't need it.
Your wife will be happy if you don't have it.
Why?
You always make fun of me.
You don't need it.
You really don't need it.
I don't need it.
Go to Macao.
What?
Go to Macao to cut it.
Why Macao?
You go to Macao to cut it, right?
You're old.
I made a wooden box.
Why a wooden box?
It's not your belly.
Do you put it in a wooden box?
I put it in.
Where do you put it?
I put it in the trunk of my car.
I said, there's no way.
Who are you explaining it to?
There's no way.
When I became weak.
Who?
You.
When you were in the car and became weak.
There's no way.
Who are you explaining it to?
Well, it's the police investigation.
When I got angry because I couldn't give it to you.
If you don't have it, it's a little...
It's like a fire.
You're an idiot.
It's okay.
There's no way.
I'm still here.
I'll do anesthesia.
So.
You should cut it.
Why don't you cut it?
I got it.
You think I'm going to cut it right away, don't you?
How do you cut it?
The pattern of the cut cheese.
I made it a wave.
It's like a carrot.
How do you cut it?
The carrot next to the stage.
I'll think about it.
What is this guy?
There are a lot of people I don't know these days.
A long time ago, there was a famous person who came out.
If you say that, something strange will come out.
I think Bob Sapp will come out.
It's hard to have someone come out.
You have to laugh a little and return it.
That's true.
What's that?
You know.
I'm doing what I want to ask you on the website.
I'll send you an e-mail today.
I see.
That's amazing.
There's a creature called the last chimp in the back of the mountain of fangs.
Please tell me what it looks like.
This is scary.
I've never heard of it.
The last chimp.
This is scary.
Please tell me what it looks like.
It's the last one.
It used to be a flock.
It's about to disappear.
I see.
It's amazing.
Please tell me what it looks like.
It's wearing a skirt.
The whole body is dirty.
Which one?
Which one do you want to ask?
A creature?
It's a human.
It's wearing a skirt.
It doesn't have hands.
On its shoulders?
It's wearing a skirt on its shoulders.
And it's wearing a pendant.
It's holding a bunch of pachinko balls.
It's hitting the trees.
It's in the back of the mountain.
The last chimp is scary.
The last chimp is really scary.
It used to be a flock.
It's amazing.
Where is it going?
What?
It's a favorite animal.
It can't take it because it's stupid.
Normally it's like this.
What is it doing?
It's biting grass.
It's this fast.
It's not very fast.
When the ball falls, everyone runs.
Run?
It's like a chimp.
It's amazing.
It doesn't matter if the ball falls.
It doesn't care.
It doesn't use anything?
What?
What about the pachinko balls?
It doesn't use anything.
It just runs away.
That's right.
The boss is the only one who has the pachinko balls.
I see.
Everyone is doing this, but there's really nothing.
It's the boss's dream.
It comes and eats it.
What does it eat?
It's a ball.
It's a mix of many things.
It's amazing.
The last chimp.
The 4LDK in the apartment has 3LD.
It's so much that it's occupied by pet animals.
It's a favorite animal.
That's what I think.
Lions are famous for being so strict that they only raise children who have fallen to the bottom of the valley.
I heard that even lazy people raise their children harshly.
What kind of method is it?
Do you know?
That the lion has fallen to the valley.
I've heard of it.
You've heard of it, haven't you?
The lion is the king of the beast.
It only raises strong animals.
I see.
It's not that lazy people are the king of the beast or anything.
On the contrary, even if it's strong, it can't be helped.
It only raises those who are so lazy.
I see.
On the contrary.
That's why it's amazing.
What kind of raising method is it?
What?
Your voice is loud.
The lion will fall to the valley.
If you raise a lazy animal to a certain extent, it will burn its butt.
When it turns 20 years old.
The father will be like,
Fua! Fua!
What are you doing?
It will burn its butt.
In the city?
In the city.
Even if it burns, it will be like,
Fua!
I don't know if it's like this.
You shouldn't make a fuss.
Even if it smells like shit, it will be like,
Fua!
Even if it's like,
Half of it is burning!
It's really hot, isn't it?
It's really hot.
If you do this quickly,
It won't be good, right?
There's water in there.
It's burning its butt.
If you do this quickly, it will be like,
Fua!
But if you do that, it won't be good.
If it burns its butt, it will be like,
Fua!
It's already burning, but...
I want to go there quickly.
The real thing.
The father will be watching that.
How lazy is it?
You're in a hurry, aren't you?
Even if it's a little,
If it's like this,
Fua!
Take it off.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.