Please do not use the child.
Let's play together tonight.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
It's like this in the house!
The first game is Tsukichi-Ganmen Ose-ro game with Gagi-no-tsu-kai-ara-en!
It's good to see you're so excited.
I'm so excited.
You're such a fool.
Normally, there are four ways to play Ose-ro.
From the beginning?
Yes, from the beginning to the end.
Let's decide the color one by one.
Let's start from there.
You're black, I'm white.
I'm black.
Then I'll go from here.
The first game is Tsukichi-Ganmen Ose-ro game with Gagi-no-tsu-kai-ara-en!
I'll go from here.
I'll go from the glasses to here.
You're black, I'm white.
Then I'll go from the glasses to here.
Then I'll go from here.
I'll make Tsukichi-Ganmen black.
Then I'll go from the head to here.
You're Otomo.
Otomo, why are you so quiet?
I'll go from the glasses to here.
Then I'll go from the glasses to here.
You're so noisy.
If Yano goes like this...
Motoyuki Takasu will be black.
Sugano will be surprised.
Then Yano will...
Wait, wait, wait!
Then Yamazaki and Suga will be black.
Kanazaki!
If it goes like this...
Like this?
Suga-chan, you've changed a lot.
Suga-chan, today's opening will be a great success.
Leave your ears to the flow of time.
I'll be dyed in your color.
I'll go from the glasses to here.
Then I'll go from the glasses to here.
It's a strange hall.
What?
How many times have we been here?
It's the second time today.
It's a strange hall.
It's cheap.
It's not about the price.
You've never been in a catecho before.
I've never been in a catecho.
You've never been in a catecho.
There's an electric board on it.
There isn't.
I saw it with my own eyes.
That's wrong.
That's a catecho.
Wrong and catecho are completely different.
It's not right.
Wrong catecho.
I've never been in a catecho before.
It's not right.
It's a catecho.
It had been different.
It was heavy, wasn't it?
No, it's not like that at all.
It's not like that at all.
What is that?
Around here, the part of the neck is loose.
It's a shoulder.
No, it's not.
The numbers are different.
Shoulders.
It's not at all.
It's a good shoulder.
Are you stupid?
You are really...
It's not a shoulder. It's a complete Japanese word.
It's not a shoulder.
The shoulder of the shoulder is Kanji.
The shoulder is not a Katakana.
There is also a hiragana.
I've never had a shoulder.
You've had a shoulder.
You're so stubborn.
The numbers are different.
The shoulder is hard.
Your story is the number difference.
It's not at all.
There was a person on the Shinkansen.
He was wearing a hat and a face mask.
He was sleeping.
The numbers are different.
Do you know what?
Ask me.
It was like this.
I have a strong body.
How can you have a weak body?
It's a stupid story.
Ask me.
It's a strong story.
It's a stupid story.
I have a strong body.
It's a strong story.
Did you take a picture?
Of course.
I don't think it was taken.
The number of cameras is different.
What is he doing?
I don't think it was taken.
I think it's gone from the screen.
I was able to catch it.
Don't say stupid things.
Jump again.
Jump.
You jumped.
I was able to catch it before the time was over.
Thank you very much.
It was a bad time.
You jumped as hard as you could.
I'm a strong man.
You have a great body.
You know, I'm 28 years old now.
But I'm still 17 years old physically.
Are you an idiot?
No, I'm serious.
What are you talking about?
I've never seen a sport where you lose.
You're not good at sports.
Are you an idiot?
Even if I run, it's like this.
The first secret of the year.
That's dirty.
Let's keep it a secret.
Why is it a secret?
You don't have to say it.
Everyone loves Macchan.
I love Macchan.
Why do you say it twice?
There are a lot of people all over the country.
But the secret of the year.
The secret of the year.
Don't say it twice.
Suddenly, the secret of the year.
First of all, why can't you show your power in sports?
Why do you think you're such a macho man?
Where is it?
I think everyone thinks so.
Muscles are also moving a lot.
You're not good at sports.
Why can't you do sports?
It's not that I can't do it.
To tell you the truth, my muscles are too big.
That's why I'm not good at sports.
What are you talking about?
If I tell you the truth, I won't lose.
I don't think so.
No matter what you do.
You haven't done it.
I can do it even though I haven't done it.
I'm good at using my grip.
Really?
Yes.
What do you use grip for?
Arm wrestling and finger wrestling.
I don't have a table.
I can do it here.
If you can't do it, you can't do it.
I can't do it.
Let's do it together.
It's been a long time since I saw a manly man.
Are you crazy?
Why don't you sit down and do it again?
I can laugh here.
Sit down quickly.
Don't do it again.
Who said this?
Tell your brother.
My brother?
What are you doing?
Like this.
The grip and arm wrestling are different.
You said it.
This is true.
The grip and arm wrestling are different.
But the power here is different.
It's okay if you use your fingers.
What fingers?
This.
You use your fingers.
What is this?
This is unexpected laughter.
I thought about it twice.
Should I hold my finger and do this?
This is not decided.
Let's do it again.
With what?
With something.
Okay.
Let's do it.
It's been a long time.
I haven't done it since baseball.
Did you play golf?
I played golf before that.
What are you talking about?
I played golf and baseball.
I want to play a penalty game.
What is it?
I want to get a frame.
5 minutes.
I want to watch a comedy with you.
What is a comedy?
I want to go out with you in the morning.
I want to do a comedy with you for 5 minutes.
Okay.
I want to see it.
Are you stupid?
Are you a team player?
It doesn't matter if it's a team.
Let's do it as a team.
Let's divide it in half.
If you lose in a team, you will be in front of American kids.
Do you really call Ashiko?
What if I lose?
I want to play a penalty game with you.
Will you come?
I can't come if you call me.
I'll think about it.
I'll think about what to do.
Shall we play rugby?
I've never played rugby, so I don't know if it's fun.
Let's try it.
If you lose, call your mother.
I haven't decided yet.
Penalty game.
Let's do it.
It's going to be a mess, but you can grab it and run.
That's right.
It's more fun than sumo.
Sumo is different.
Let's show your ass.
I won't show my ass.
I don't know if you're used to showing your ass.
If I show my ass to everyone, I'll do it smoothly.
Machan.
Shall we do it?
What?
I don't know how to relieve your stress.
If you show your ass, I'll do it smoothly.
Machan said that he drew it when he was looking at his uncle's back.
I tried it, too.
I was looking at my nose.
It's weird to see it from the front, so I looked at it from the side about three meters away.
I think it's a child.
Then I drew a nose and then I put it in my mouth.
Then I said,
Eat it.
Why don't you say it twice?
You didn't draw it twice, did you?
It's a lie, but it's true.
If it's Machan, he'll believe me.
This is a great story.
It's amazing that you ate it.
What?
It's more than that.
First of all, I bought it.
If you say you bought it when you see it, it's over.
I'm sure she's more than she thinks.
You're an expert.
No, I'm not.
It's more like a peck than a cactus.
What are you talking about?
That's right.
Cactus is an extracurricular thing, isn't it?
Extracurricular?
Isn't it extracurricular?
Isn't it just a bowl?
A bowl?
It's a peck, so it's an intracurricular thing.
What are you talking about?
It's human instinct to put it in your mouth.
Is that so?
It's the same with an eraser, isn't it?
If you smell something, you'll go like this.
I don't breathe when I smell it.
I sometimes go like this with that softness.
That's human instinct.
Human instinct is to put something in your mouth right away.
Something that makes you feel good.
I know that.
You put it in your mouth right away.
It doesn't have to be dirty.
I want to eat it.
You think it's human, don't you?
Have you ever eaten a cactus?
What?
No, it's dirty.
It's even dirtier.
You put it in your mouth, don't you?
Laugh a little more.
I'm going to the shrine right now.
I'm curious about my dad who's sitting in the bandai.
When I take off my clothes, I look at the bandai and my eyes meet.
The other day, he smiled at me.
And last night, my underwear was gone from the basket.
This is the only way to make my dad feel better.
What do you mean?
It's a strange bandai, isn't it?
Is that legal?
It's there.
For example, if you're an old man, you can't see women's clothes.
Is that okay?
That's right.
You can see everything.
You can see my underwear, too.
Your underwear?
Wow!
But you can see things you don't see.
It could be zero.
It could be negative.
You can see things you don't usually see.
That's right.
It's amazing, isn't it?
You can see things you don't see.
You think, wow, but you think, wow, again.
You know, a 70-year-old old woman has a great body.
You can show it off.
It's not a V-shape.
It's like this.
Once, like this.
What is it?
It's a square.
It's because you were born.
Where did you see that?
No, no, I've seen it.
When?
I haven't even been to a bathhouse.
It's like this.
It's like a demon in the corner of hell.
There are dozens of them.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's tough, isn't it?
It's tough.
What should I do with this?
There's a homo bandai.
There are two kinds of homo.
There are.
Brother and brother.
What is a brother?
Brother is the one who takes care of you.
Brother is alive.
Brother is taken care of.
It hurts.
It's a strange world.
Brother comes from behind.
But brother is excited.
Brother is taking care of you at that time.
It's a strange story, isn't it?
It's a strange story.
It hurts.
It hurts, but it stands.
It stands.
It's even possible for a brother to come in front of it.
It's possible.
And again, brother, brother, brother.
It's possible for it to be like Jutsu.
It's connected.
So I have no choice but to take it so that it will be hated.
I bought a pair of panties.
I'm going to take off my panties.
I think it's best to think about these panties a little more.
I don't want to take them off again.
I think it's best.
Even men want to take off their panties when they see a beautiful girl.
I don't know much about it.
Shut up.
I just want to be with you.
That's because you looked down on me during the day.
Let's take it off.
No, it's like this.
What kind of feeling is it?
Well, rugby.
Yes.
Let's do our best as a rugby.
It's noisy.
It's okay. Let's do our best.
Really.
Let's do it.
It's been a long time.
Well, the season is good.
It's getting warmer.
It's getting nice.
Look at the weather.
It's like a bust in the summer.
Yes.
In the summer, there are a lot of crimes in the country.
There are also kidnappings.
A kidnapper took a little boy and called the kidnapper.
Hello.
Oh, you scared me!