I did it!
Let's move on to the next one.
The first one is...
Wada Ben, right?
And the next one is...
Shigeki-chan.
Shimoda Kageki.
Kageki-chan.
Shigeki-chan.
The color is a bit...
If you look at the bottom, it looks like Wakabayashi.
And the next one is...
Kaganobaba.
That's enough.
Thank you very much.
This is not something to play with.
I thought I could do it.
And this time...
Guts.
I wonder how much you can tell the difference.
Guts is...
Guts Ishimatsu.
His real name is Yuji Suzuki.
He was born in Tochigi Prefecture in the year of Showa 24.
Since he was a child, he has had a strong will to lose.
Even if it was against an upperclassman, he has never lost in a fight.
Guts Ishimatsu.
He made his debut in the boxing world as a transfer student.
He cut through the path of the rock with one fist.
In the year of Showa 49, he challenged for the world title.
He won the eight rounds of KO.
He was the first Japanese to win the world lightweight title.
Even after his retirement, he made a comeback in the movie industry.
He was a producer, screenwriter, director, actor, and actor.
He was the center of attention in the entertainment industry.
I'm Guts today.
It's a kiss special.
Basically, it's a kiss.
Hit me.
I hope you do something good today.
100 points.
Let's go to a bug.
A bug?
Let's dig up Guts' shoes.
This is the best.
Tighten your neck.
From the back.
This is not a big deal.
One point.
If you tighten your neck and say one point, it won't end.
From the back.
I like it.
About 30 points.
How about kicking up your butt?
I like it.
50,000 points.
100,000 points if you say AITAAA.
AITAAA.
If you say AITAAA, Guts will be like this.
I'll start dancing.
Start.
Your face shape has changed.
I'm Guts.
Today's theme is boxing.
I'm looking forward to it.
In many ways.
Can I read it?
Let's call him.
Guts Ishimatsu.
Thank you.
Today's title is this.
How long have you been boxing?
16 years.
Even if you quit boxing now,
if someone's hand comes like this,
will it go away in an instant?
It doesn't go away, but I avoid it.
You just avoid it?
You don't punch after avoiding it, do you?
I don't do that.
You don't?
What are you doing?
We met a long time ago.
Do you remember?
Why?
What are you talking about?
I think it was about 10 years ago.
We had an interview once.
That's right.
It was 10 years ago.
After that, I was a judge.
You were a comedian.
I was a judge.
I always had a good taste.
Is that so?
You had a good taste.
Guts, are you okay?
Do you still train?
Sometimes.
Sometimes?
What are you talking about?
This is...
It's Yamachan.
It's not Yamachan.
It's Hama-chan.
Guts has been calling me Yamachan.
No?
It's Hama-chan.
Do you want to arm wrestle with me?
Arm wrestle?
Let's do it.
This is good.
Ready, start.
Don't do it too seriously.
You're dirty.
If you do that, you won't be able to throw it.
I'll show you how to do it.
Your arms are big.
Stop calling me a snake.
You kicked me just now.
Guts, let's do a shadow.
What was your name again?
I'll show you again.
When it comes...
Ouch.
I'll kill you.
Ready, start.
Ouch.
It really hurts.
It's Yamachan.
I'll show you how to do it.
He's throwing it.
It's amazing.
Please remember this.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
Let's announce the result.
You two were really scared.
It was really scary.
I was really nervous.
When you were doing this...
Even though you were being taught, it was really scary.
Let's see the result.
Matsumoto's score.
68 points.
My score.
I still have one more line. 163,446 points.
Let's do the
last one.
I thought I'd never say it, but I said it once.
That's 100,000 points.
It's big.
Today was the scariest out of the three times.
That's what I'm scared of.
My legs are shaking, too.
It snowed a lot.
What's that?
It doesn't snow in Osaka.
In Osaka?
No, in Tokyo.
It doesn't snow in Osaka, so I'm not used to it.
I can't handle it.
Why do you say it twice?
I don't want you to laugh like that.
I couldn't get out at all.
I couldn't get out on that snowy day.
It snowed twice this year, didn't it?
I don't know.
It snowed twice, didn't it?
The first time it snowed was funny.
I was watching TV alone.
In the middle of the night.
I was watching TV alone in the middle of the night.
Then I heard a sound.
I looked out of the window, and I saw a car crash.
I got out of the car and looked at the car.
I looked at the TV again.
The car crashed again.
The taxi driver crashed again.
There were about five cars in Akihata.
I couldn't do anything about it.
It's okay if you're an amateur.
If a person who is famous for his face falls into the snow, it's very cool.
The entrance to the video studio in Shibuya is very slippery.
When I was told that it was a match, I was surprised.
I was surprised.
It's over.
I'm a fool.
What?
I'm tired of being fooled.
That's not true.
I went to the hospital yesterday.
Hospital?
Why did you go to the hospital?
I want to have beautiful seams.
Aikata has found out.
I told him to hide his chest a bit more.
When he came out, he was all stiff.
Oh, that's amazing.
Right?
When he came out, he was all stiff.
He was like this.
He didn't burn, but he was like this.
When he came out, he was like this.
He was laughing like this.
When I looked up, I saw two ugly nurses.
They were laughing like this.
That's hurtful.
You can't say that.
He was like this.
I've been doing a lot of research.
Right?
About being lucky.
Lucky?
I think everyone needs to know more about being lucky.
Of course, I think about it every day.
You think about it every day?
What do you mean by lucky every day?
Everyone uses the word lucky very wrongly.
Really?
For example, let's say you're in a hurry to go home.
You don't stop at any traffic lights.
If you can go without stopping, that's lucky.
That's not lucky.
Well, well, well.
You can say that to me now.
10 minutes later,
Mr. Matsumoto is nice.
No, no, no.
Please hug him.
I can't do that.
I'll ask you.
For example, let's say you went to eat something.
What do you want to eat?
Do you want to eat curry rice?
Or do you want to eat hayashi rice?
I don't eat the same thing.
Let's say you have two friends.
You want to eat curry rice.
Your friend wants to eat hayashi rice.
Hayashi rice was very bad.
The curry rice was very delicious.
Are you lucky?
Lucky?
No!
The curry rice there is delicious from the beginning.
If you do something different, that's right.
For example, if you go on a trip,
you're always looking at Mr. Hamada.
When you get off, you're told,
I have money today.
Are you lucky?
Lucky?
No!
What did you say about money?
Are you stupid?
Did you listen to the class when you were a third grader?
I don't know what it is.
It's been three years.
No, no.
Are you lucky?
You really don't understand.
That was your idea.
That was my idea.
Are you lucky now?
Well, then.
What is it?
I'm curious.
Let's look at the answer.
What are you doing?
If you're a third grader, you'll understand.
Everyone is nervous.
Let's look at the answer.
What did he say?
Let me tell you about curry.
That curry was originally delicious curry.
That's fine.
I've noticed something.
Lucky changes depending on what you're lucky with.
But that's not for me.
Everyone can't say lucky.
But it's for me.
Well, well, well, well, well, well.
Listen.
This is where it really comes out.
What are you looking at?
I'm not doing anything.
I don't accept anything.
I'm lucky because the signal has changed.
Listen!
But!
When I wanted to eat curry, I happened to go into that delicious curry shop.
I'm lucky about that.
I dropped my wallet.
What?
You dropped your wallet.
Have you gone crazy?
What should I do?
You have to be careful.
Next, click, click, click, click.
That's not the case.
Click, click, click.
Click, click.
Well, well, well, well.
That's enough.
I want you to tell me the details.
I dropped my wallet and was depressed.
I found my wallet about two days later.
Were you lucky at this time?
I was lucky.
You're really stupid.
I dropped my wallet and was found.
You're really late now.
You have to work hard.
You're really bad.
I didn't wait for you.
It's okay.
You're lucky.
You don't have to look so cute.
Click, click, click, click.
That's enough.
That's not the case.
I want you to tell me the details.
I don't have any.
When I first said it,
about 10 minutes ago,
everyone was surprised.
But after listening to my speech,
Thank you, Matsumoto.
Do it. Do it.
What are you talking about?
People who say that.
Please raise your hand a little.
That hurts.
That's enough.
Everyone, come over here.
Danbaron.
Thank you.
Is that so?
Okay.
What is this?
What's okay?
Are you lucky to have me and downtown?
It's okay.
Hmm?
I heard something.
Your wife, Natsumi, used to be a fan of Matsumoto.
Liar.
Is that true?
What?
Wait a minute.
What was that?
What?
I didn't know this.
No, it's not.
That's right.
Is that so?
No, it's not.
I'll send you 50 roses.
Thank you.
Your child is also a fan of mine.
Why?
Well, well, well.
Say hello.
Hello.
Why do you close your eyes when you kiss?
Matsumoto, do you close your eyes?
If I open my eyes, it's hard to die.
What?
Do you close your eyes?
Wow, cute.
Men don't close their eyes.
Women do.
You keep your eyes open all the time.
I don't know how much you know.
What are you talking about?
Eyes and mouth are opposite.
What do you mean?
Eyes and mouth are closed.
When your mouth is open, you close your eyes.
For example, when you get on the roller coaster, you scream.
Hey, hey.
What?
When I do a French kiss...
When I do a light kiss...
French kiss?
My eyes are open.
Disgusting.
When I do a deep kiss, my mouth is open.
Why do you close your eyes?
Telecom, telecom, telecom.
I'm sorry, Machan.
I love your work.
I've been your fan for a year and a half.
It seems that the world we live in is too different.
It's hard for me to be sad anymore, so I'll say goodbye here.
I was happy to see a lot of Machan in a year and a half.
I wanted to see Machan with my own eyes just once.
Don't send me a blue note.
Goodbye and thank you.
It's really blue.
I don't like it.
I'm sorry, Machan.
Why do you want so much?
You can just watch TV as a fan.
I'm a little too into it.
You're trying to get into it, aren't you?
I said something like that the other day, but I don't think so.
There's someone who wrote me a letter saying that I'm saying it to my man.
I'll never forget what you said at that time.
What did you say?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You don't even know that you're different from what you really look like on TV, do you?
I'm really like that.
You don't change much, do you?
I usually wear a microphone like this.
Why?
You're a pervert.
When I see you on a regular basis, I think you're completely different from what I imagine.
You really make me laugh.
Why?
What do you mean?
When I see you on a regular basis, I think you're completely different from what I imagine.
It's called justice.