Uchimura and Yuya-chan, when you come to the dining room, you eat curry, right?
Ramen, please.
Are you angry?
Ramen, I'm sorry.
This is the real face.
I'm fine.
It's the 10th year next year.
Hama-chan, please introduce our members.
Thank you.
This is the leader.
I'm a child's user.
What are you talking about?
Tanaka.
I'm the second.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Asayama.
This person.
Nice to meet you.
This is our captain.
Hello.
I'm the captain.
You introduce the members one by one again.
This is the leader.
I'm a child's user.
This is Masato Irie.
Nice to meet you.
This is the leader.
I'm Asayama.
This person.
I'm the second.
Nice to meet you.
This is the opening of the bag.
How do you introduce the members?
I want more.
No one is coming.
I'm a child's user.
It started.
Why do we have two groups here?
Nan-chan is doing a program called Sharara.
After that, we are the child's users.
We do it every 30 minutes.
Let's do this one by one and go to the program.
It's all messed up.
If you notice, we're all dancing.
I don't think so.
Why?
Please change.
Today, the members of Sharara are here.
How are you doing?
Is your program interesting?
To be honest.
The highlight of the program is the Chiki Chiki corner every time.
Isn't that our program?
We do it every week.
Sometimes it's just the two of us.
And the one-man play.
That's interesting.
Is that interesting?
Nanbara, please talk.
What about us?
Is it interesting?
It's more interesting than the snake and the tiger's hole.
Let's get started.
Please say the title of the program.
It's a little long.
There's a campaign in front of you.
Let's go.
U-chan, Nan-chan, and Round-Round-chan.
Sharara's使いや愛!
Let's start with the last part.
Let's start with U-chan, Nan-chan.
Please look at the board in the back.
There's still a lot left.
We've got this much VTR.
I've done a lot of things.
Let's take a look at it.
What's the latest one?
The latest one is...
Find a poor man.
How do you find a poor man?
I'm looking for a poor man.
Just like that.
I've seen a movie called Tenryu.
Really?
I've seen it.
I've got it ready.
Really?
I haven't seen it.
I've seen it a lot.
You've seen it a lot?
You've seen Nyororo, right?
I'll leave it to you.
I've got 1 million yen.
What haven't you seen?
I haven't seen skydiving.
I haven't seen it.
I want to see it.
I was scared.
Really?
Let's start with us.
This is what he went for.
He said, let's do a punishment game.
How would you play if you lose?
This is What the Shinabichi Shogun was doing back then.
No one knows.
Nobody knows.
Is it an old thing?
Hello? Hello? I'm on my way now.
I'm sleeping right now.
Look at where I'm going.
Zoom in towards Shizuoka!
Shizuoka, Shizuoka, Shizuoka!
It's like this.
However, if you go into the shade, it will be slippery, so please be careful.
Let's go to Nippon Netto's new movie.
Zoom in!
It's not a prank!
Hello? Do you like me?
Will you still look at me as a partner?
I did it.
Did you see it?
Tome-san is a little angry.
Next is the bird-human contest in Hamada.
It's nostalgic.
It was Su, right?
I thought he was drunk.
I was waiting for the ball.
Tome-san ignored me and asked me to do it.
When I came home, he said he wouldn't get up.
I couldn't talk to him until the morning.
I couldn't do it anymore.
Don't ask!
We are good at curry, but we are also good at Tenryu.
Are you good at cooking?
I'm good at it, but I don't hate it.
I'm lazy, so I don't cook much.
Tome-san!
I'm scared of the microphone.
I'm not good at cooking.
You eat a lot at night.
How many people eat?
I don't eat much at night.
Young people eat.
But you can eat two or three people, right?
I can eat five or six people.
You didn't go to eat barbecue, did you?
I didn't go to eat barbecue.
It was more delicious to eat meat and smoke.
Is your hair a perm?
This?
I've always wondered if you were going to get a perm.
Are you going to get a perm?
Tenryu made it all.
We are good at it, but we are also good at it.
That's the right answer.
Tenryu is the best!
I have a lot of capacity, but I'm not good at it.
I don't like people who have big feet like me.
I often say that.
The fourth round is a power competition.
Wait a minute.
Why don't you compare this?
Humans are not big.
It's all about energy.
I'm going to beat Tenryu with my energy.
You're a tiger.
You look like a tiger.
That's right. I'm going to do my best with that energy.
Don't die, Tenryu!
You're the one who's dead!
I'm going to die!
I'm going to do my best.
Let's do it at the end.
I'm going to die.
I'm sorry.
That was the most painful thing I've ever had in my life.
I couldn't get a perm for about three hours.
Really?
It was swollen.
You're not in the army, are you?
Yes, I'm a guard.
I'm the main character of Nambara.
Let's move on to the next round.
I'm going to be the virtual captain.
I got 1 million yen for the virtual captain.
Which one is this?
Both.
I fell down once.
You didn't die?
I tried again.
I saw both.
You saw both?
I'm a fan.
I fell down.
I like this one better.
Here you go.
This is the first time.
I got lost.
Come on.
Help me.
I don't know if I'm going to make it.
Thank you very much.
It's finally the last one.
You look very nervous.
I'm nervous.
Let's go.
No.40 pass line.
How was it?
How many points did the judges give?
I'm sorry.
I'm glad.
I'll give you a little more points.
It hurts.
Congratulations.
I'm glad.
But I failed.
I can't win.
I'll give you a little more points.
Why are you looking up?
Please.
Don't use your legs.
I have plenty of time.
My legs.
I did this twice.
It was a famous trick.
I missed it on the way.
You came back in that outfit.
You look very happy.
I didn't make it to the second place.
I thought I would win.
There weren't many people with high scores.
When I won, I did this.
I didn't have to be happy.
I'll give you four points.
I haven't won yet.
You haven't won yet?
You have to win.
I'll give you four points.
You should think about it.
It was an amateur trick.
It was from Amagasaki.
The first trick was a chameleon.
It fell.
It took a long time for poop to come out.
We don't like practice, so we didn't do it.
Next, we did something with the five of us.
It was a play.
It was a holiday before the year.
You went to play?
Yes.
That's good.
It's fun.
What you saw was Tetsu's roller coaster.
His face when he was on the roller coaster.
It was a close-up.
I went to play.
It was delicious.
You went to Okinawa, didn't you?
What?
I went on a normal tour.
It was cheap.
Let's use the drinks in front of us.
We'll play a game.
We'll play a game with the person on the roller coaster.
We'll guess the character.
Uchimura team.
We'll show it like this.
Wait.
Are you ready?
I'm fighting with Dustin Hoffman.
Let's start.
How is it?
It's going to be fast.
Dustin Hoffman.
It's coming.
It's definitely going to be fast.
It's going to be fast.
It's scanning the test.
Don't give me a hint.
I know.
It's scanning the test.
Don't give me a hint.
I know.
It's scanning the test.
I was not afraid when I rode with you.
10.
Here it comes!
I can not!
OMG!
I!"ll get nervous at first.
He'll be envious for the 2nd time.
Your face is really bad!
Next time, let's change the order
This time, the two of us will do something serious
Let's do it seriously
Tetsu-chan laughed
Again?
Tetsu-chan also tried
You also have a good character
Wajima Koichi-san, the world champion
Wajima-san's boxing challenge
Good evening
Nice to meet you
Here?
What are you doing?
One, two
One, two?
Come on
Why are you laughing?
I'm scared.
Fight!
It's fun.
I'm scared.
Stop!
You win!
Don't lose to a frog.
You're done.
I'll give you a punch.
I'm ready.
You're good.
I'm scared.
Stop!
You're done.
I'm scared.
Stop!
I'll give you a punch.
I'm scared.
You're good.
I can't remember anything.
It was a tough fight.
You were out of breath.
You were crying.
I was about to hit the corner.
I hit the corner.
But I hit you.
I hit you.
I was trying to beat him up.
Suddenly, I thought it was fun.
Next, we have a guest who is watching our program.
He is a big fan and a guest.
Please come out.
May I?
The guest is this man.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm busy.
Hurry up.
Uchimura, why didn't you become a boxer?
I didn't know.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you.
Please sit down.
You are always beautiful.
I'm used to being told that.
I've never done that.
Really?
He is watching us.
I'm sorry, but it's 1 o'clock, right?
Yes, it's before that.
I'm sorry.
I went skydiving.
That's great.
It's like the night before you fall.
I was really scared.
That's scary.
Thank you.
How about this one?
It's funny.
Uchimura is preparing for the show.
Ready, set, go.
I'm scared.
I'm really scared.
I'm still scared.
Let's go.
It's scary.
It's coming down.
He is waving his hand.
Can he land safely?
The landing is the problem.
Congratulations.
It was scary.
It was really scary.
I don't know what to say.
I'm really moved.
Thank you.
That's great.
I can't do that.
Have you ever been separated from the person on the top?
If I was separated, I would say goodbye.
Don't you have a parachute?
I don't.
If you were separated...
I don't know about that.
I feel like I'm going to get hit by a car.
I was scared before I flew.
I was working in Osaka the day before that.
I couldn't sleep.
So I went to karaoke.
I was singing, but I couldn't sleep.
I couldn't sing because I was too excited.
This is a penalty game.
That's right.
Which one of you said this?
This one.
Actually, I like the sky.
You wanted to fly, didn't you?
I wanted to try it once.
I see.
It can't be helped.
Your mother saw this.
I cried.
Thank you very much.
Does your mother cry?
Even the demon's eyes are full of tears.
How was it?
I wanted to try skydiving every time.
Really?
But listen to me.
I felt like I was going to fall.
I felt like I was flying.
But I was just falling.
How many kilometers did you fly?
300 kilometers.
At first, the wind was strong.
But after a while, the wind came from below.
So I felt like I was flying.
I experienced it.
The wind came from above, not from above.
I did it in the air.
But the wind was too strong.
I couldn't breathe.
I felt like I was flying.
That's why the wind is strong.
Next.
Please look at it together.
Mark Costabi.
He was going to explode this fall.
He is a liar and an artist.
Mark Costabi is an artist.
He challenged pop art.
All of a sudden?
All of a sudden, art came to my chest.
He drew anything that caught his eye.
He drew it.
Oh, no.
It's just dirty.
This is art.
Don't look at it.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh.
What are you doing to my face?
Costabi.
What are you doing?
Don't talk to me.
One more time.
What are you doing?
Don't talk to me.
I like this work.
Did you like it?
I'm honored.
This is great.
Great.
It's not funny if I translate it into Japanese.
This is...
There are a lot of book seals in foreign countries.
There are tens of thousands of them.
When it's over, I'll translate it into Japanese.
This summer, there will be a big boom.
This fall, in Japan.
Do you know that?
No.
I don't know at all.
You guys only lost money.
This is...
We just watched a video of art.
We have a guest.
He's a painting teacher.
That's great.
Let's see.
Please come in.
Oh, teacher.
Teacher.
What's his painting?
Animal painting.
There's no animal in Japan.
He can paint a lot of things.
For example, can I draw something?
Is there a dog?
Can you draw a dog?
He's quick to draw.
This is a dog.
Wait a minute.
Is this person really a painter?
Mr. Kagasawa.
I can't do that.
Wait a minute. Does this look like a dog?
What does this look like?
A rotten pig.
Let's draw a rotten pig.
This is a pig.
It's the same.
What?
It's the same pig.
It's hard to praise a father.
Please sign this.
Thank you.
Actually, I haven't seen it.
We don't know, but there's a fun video.
Let's watch it.
You guys are stupid.
It's funny.
You're young.
Thank you for editing it.
It's a video that shouldn't be done as a person.
It's funny.
You're holding back a lot.
Don't do it.
Hey.
You shouldn't do it.
Of course.
But Mr. Kagasawa will be angry if you get hit.
I don't like it.
That's right.
I'll do it seriously.
You can do it seriously.
You didn't come to my academy.
I told you.
What are you doing?
Who was the first one to come?
It's you.
It's me.
It's funny.
It's Mr. Uchiyama.
This time, we did the choreography of Omitoshiman.
This time, it's a special episode.
The two of you from Downtown will do the choreography of Omitoshiman.
Do you want to do it?
I'm very motivated.
I've already decided on the costume.
I asked them to make it this color.
I'd like to call you.
I love dancing.
I'm from Downtown.
I'm Mr. Uchiyama.
This time, we did the choreography of Omitoshiman.
This time, it's a special episode.
The two of you from Downtown will do the choreography of Omitoshiman.
Do you want to do it?
I'm very motivated.
I've already decided on the costume.
I asked them to make it this color.
I'd like to call you.
I love dancing.
I'm from Downtown.
Please.
I'm very motivated.
Can you take a picture of me?
I'm sleeping.
I'm a trainee, so my cape is short.
How long does it take to get there?
It doesn't take long.
I can dance from the cushion.
Don't talk nonsense.
I have a dance program.
I'm just watching.
Dance, dance, dance.
I'll change anytime.
We're not the only ones who choreographed it.
This is the choreography of Omitoshiman.
The wink.
You just have to wink.
Mr. Igarashi.
Mr. Hamada, come anytime.
What's wrong with him?
I have a dance program.
Show us.
I don't know.
It's a good choreography.
Idiot.
Brothers.
Brother.
Which one is my brother?
Are you both the same?
No.
Which one is difficult?
I don't like Nan-chan's choreography.
Nan-chan's choreography is difficult.
Which one is difficult?
I like dancing.
I like Uki-chan.
That's why.
Hama-chan is my brother.
I like Mach-chan's face.
Idiot brothers.
Please leave it to me.
I have a dance program.
It's a dance program.
It's a bow.
Turn your body like this.
Cross your legs.
Again, turn to the right.
From the back.
Turn your legs.
From the inside.
Ready, go!
Turn your legs to the side.
That's good.
Hide your face behind your mask.
Here.
I'm back.
I don't know how to do this.
What are you doing?
How do you do it?
It's a step.
What do you do with your hat?
Like this.
Right, left, right, right.
You can't do it at all.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it at all.
How do you do it?
When you bend your right leg,
your left leg bends.
Can you practice this first?
Practice.
Old man.
Anything.
Please do something.
Well, well, well.
You can't do it.
But you can do it.
I got it.
You got the first part.
You, you.
No, no.
The one to go to the side.
No.
And this part is...
...just right.
Ah, I got it.
You step on it like this.
From close up.
Ah, that's good.
Just step on it.
Okay, okay.
That's good.
Smile, smile.
Your heart is my...
...soul.
Have fun.
Your heart is my...
...soul.
SOUL.
I'm not sleepy enough.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait a second.
That's right.
Anything is my...
...soul.
SOUL.
Your...
...soul.
Your heart is my...
SOUL.
When I was 1,
You were such soft.
Though you fell.
Although you were such soft.
Like this.
yourkew?
O-Mi-To-O-Si-Ki-Ko-Yu
Good, good, good
That's the best
From the right
Good, good, good
Say something
O-Mi-To-To-Ma-Shi-To-To-Ma-Shi
Free
Say something
Turn back
And then
Hama-san is
Go to the back
Good
Wow you can do it
I'm tired.
Come on.
Turn your back.
You can do it.
Good.
Excellent.
It's so bright.
Each of them has their own characteristics.
They're all unique.
Come on.
And pose.
Please forgive me.
After this, in front of the audience.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I did better than I thought.
But I'm the only one who's angry.
It's a special edition.
I want to be a part of it.
I want to be a trainee.
I want to dance.
There are two people who want to dance.
I want to invite them.
Come on.
Who taught you that?
We were forced to do this.
It's really lame.
It's a little lame.
The cape is really short.
What's the difference?
It's the difference in the choreography.
I want you to wear this glove.
The sky is really blue.
Because you're a weirdo.
The sea is really wide.
I want you to see me.
I want you to see your heart.
I'm tired.
I'm really tired.
But it was fun, wasn't it?
Nan-chan and Duncan Special Chiki Chiki Ultra Special Exciting Powerful Super Human Bowling 1990
Today is the first episode.
Let's start right away.
We're going to do human bowling.
Today is special.
Just like the title.
The person who loses will be punished.
It's just like we always do.
But can I ask you one thing?
Why?
What does it mean to have two timekeepers on the show?
Don't you feel something weird?
I think it's because I'm a male.
I don't know if there's going to be a kick or something.
Let's get on the show right away.
Uchano-chan.
This is it, isn't it?
Uchano Chiki Chiki.
I'm watching.
For example, I don't know if Uchano is going to hit me or Nan-chan is going to hit me.
What are you going to do about that?
Is this a punishment game?
There's a punishment game.
If you lose, the two losing teams will be in this bowling ball.
This is the case of Ikuta Studio.
It's weird, isn't it?
I'm doing it as a talent.
Why is it a punishment game because I lost?
It's weird.
All the staff are looking at their faces.
That's a punishment game.
I'm more like Hamada-san.
That's the way it is.
I'm confident about this.
I'm serious.
I brought a big ball today.
It's my ball.
I brought it.
This is it.
This is the biggest.
It's amazing.
I'm serious about this.
I'll do it.
Leave it to me.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Which one are you going to throw?
Here.
How do you throw it?
From this line.
The line is fine, but how do you hold it?
You can throw it.
You can throw it from above.
It's up to you.
Teacher, our troupe...
Say it.
What should we do with the troupe?
Excuse me.
Please put on the special item.
Thank you.
You can put it on.
I'm in the same situation as her.
What?
What do you mean?
Thank you.
I'm sorry to bother you.
You hit me from the first word.
We're friends.
But he's a troublemaker.
Number 15.
My team will go first.
I'll go first.
This is the first round.
It hurts.
Ouch.
Mr. Hamada, who made a good strike, will get a gold medal.
It's easy.
What is this?
It's like a baka.
It's easy.
We have 10 points.
Captain.
I'm not confident.
How can I hold it?
It's up to you.
What do you think?
What is this?
Please.
Let's go.
This is strange.
What?
Did you have a meeting?
Two.
If you knock down all the numbers.
Hey.
I'll throw it from there, right?
Yes.
It's up.
How many did you knock down?
Two?
Why did you knock down?
I'll give you three.
I didn't knock down at all.
Help me.
The second one is the pillow.
I don't think it's possible.
Let's go.
The pillow is too light.
It's hard to knock down.
It's difficult.
It's impossible.
I knocked down one.
Are you serious?
I'll give you three.
Idiot.
I was holding back.
Didn't you knock down before?
What?
You knocked down.
But the way you knocked down is correct.
It's up.
When you knock down, go back.
That's right.
Don't say unnecessary things.
You're throwing it from a great place.
I have to run.
The second one.
Let's go.
I'm holding back.
Don't make a fuss.
Nambara, who showed us a great kick, will receive a gift from Tokyo Station.
This is the last one.
How about a double game?
Please appear.
It's okay.
Are you ready?
What is this guy?
Let's go.
I'm holding back.
Good.
You're fast.
Ichimura, who showed us a great kick, will receive a gift from Yoshimoto Co., Ltd.
Don't fall down.
I don't know.
Let's do it one by one.
It's 11.
You won if you knocked down five.
I have to knock down five?
I'll do my best.
I'll do it, too.
Good.
Let's go home.
This is a good chance.
Stand up.
Hoshita, you've been bowling and you've been getting pins.
That's why...
Matsumoto, who decided on a great excuse, will receive a CD radio from Masaki Entertainment.
But I'm still winning.
What?
His eyes...
Stop it.
How many more do you want?
I'm counting on you.
Three more.
Three?
Don't fall down.
It's easy to ride.
What is it?
You can take a nap.
No.
Get down.
Why?
15 to 10.
It was close.
We won.
We'll give you the director's award and the production director's award.
Director's award?
Thank you.
We won.
We lost.
It's a punishment game.
Get changed.
Stop going down.
What?
You lost.
It suits you.
I envy you.
Stand up.
I'll give you the ball.
There are many things to think about.
Let's go.
You!
You're scary.
Stand up.
Stand up. I'll go next.
You're scary.
I'm serious.
You...
What?
You don't know how to be funny.
I'm serious.
Let's go home.
That's the end of the corner.
Help me.
I'm hungry. Go to the cafeteria and get ramen.
Run.