On May 4th, a girl was born who was waiting for Kokoriko Endo and Chiaki. Her name is Iroha-chan. Endo became a happy father.
It's cute.
Thank you.
It's good.
I didn't think you would bring it.
You should have acted.
It's not acting.
It's like a hand of a mummy.
It's cute.
The eyes are similar.
Really?
Good morning.
Everyone might know this.
A twin was born.
Good morning.
A cute baby was born to Tsuyoshi from the Nakagawa family.
He is twice as happy as the twins.
Congratulations!
What's the relationship between you two?
It's a boy who met Ten.
It's a boy.
It's cute.
They have the same face.
You two should celebrate it in the Nakagawa family.
It's Yamazaki and Dawn Dawn.
Thank you.
I think the order is the opposite.
What do you mean?
No, I haven't received it yet.
It's a sin.
No, but...
It's fine.
I'm not saying that I want money.
That's fine.
No, the order is different.
The order is different.
It's fine to say that I'll give it to you.
But that's strange.
It's fine to say that.
Who was born first?
I was born first.
Oh, I see.
No, but...
There's a way to date.
But you haven't received it yet, have you?
You said you'd give it to me if you could.
What?
It's fine to say that I'll give it to you.
No, the order is different.
You said you'd give it to me if you could.
It's fine to say that.
That's right.
You said you'd give it to me if you could.
What the hell are you talking about?
Hey, hey, hey!
Stop it.
Stop it!
You guys, stop it.
What?
The order is...
Hey, what?
You said that.
Oh, my God.
It's strange.
It's strange to give it to you.
No, no.
I'm wearing it.
I'm wearing it on purpose.
You're not wearing it on purpose?
I'm not wearing it on purpose.
I'm here to say hello.
You're not wearing a
This is weird.
What?
You're not wearing it on purpose.
I'm wearing it on purpose.
Stop it.
I don't know if you're right.
What's going on?
Nagakawa and Kokoriko.
That's right.
11 years.
How many years?
That's pretty much it.
Well, the way we came out was different.
We were in Tokyo.
Senpai, you don't have to be afraid.
We were in the same class.
You're the one who's embarrassed!
You haven't said anything about being embarrassed!
You've said it every time!
Do you remember 5 or 6 years ago?
What?
I was on the radio in Nagoya for a week.
Suddenly, the director and producer there told me to make a fool of myself.
What's that?
Why?
I asked why.
They said it was more famous.
Then it became 0, when it was airing in Tokyo.
It became nothing but a theater station.
It wasn't until then, when we justальной that number it got 0.
It wasn't until then, when we justintealized it got 0.
It wasn't until then, when we we became gunnybugs.
If you guys continue to do that...
I know, but they say that's was actually still making a fool of themselves.
Stop it!
Since then, there's been a suggestion that I realized confess was not a good idea.
I think it would be better to have a deep love for children.
For example, it would be better to do a joke in front of the children, and the one who gets it will receive the gift.
I see.
I've never done it in front of the children.
Me neither.
I see.
I don't know about you, but what about you, Yamazaki?
I've done it before.
Yes.
The genius TV-kun and I, Yamazaki Ichiban, are holding the children's hearts tightly.
What?
We haven't done it yet.
So, what do you do to receive the children?
And from Yamazaki, the lecture is about what the children will receive.
Now, the battle between the children of the Nakagawa family versus the children of the Kokoriko family begins.
Yes, this is it.
This program is brought to you by the sponsor.
The Children's Artist, Chibikko Theater
Hey, it's Yama-chan!
Everyone!
It's a boob!
From now on, the brother will tell everyone a little story.
Once upon a time, there was an old man and an old woman.
The old man went hunting in the mountains, and the old woman went to the river to wash clothes.
When the old woman was washing clothes in the river, a big, big poop came out of the upper part of the river.
A big poop came out of the upper part of the river, and the old woman went to the river to wash clothes.
From now on, two groups of friends will come out.
And the two groups will come out, so please judge which brother was fun later.
Do you understand?
First of all, let's welcome Mr. Kogoriko.
Everyone, please give him a round of applause.
I'm hungry. I'm really hungry.
I haven't eaten anything for three days.
That's right. Let's call Anpanman. Anpanman!
Anpanman?
Did you call me?
Are you Anpanman?
No, no, no. Anpanman won't come today.
In place, my brother came.
Who is your brother?
My brother's name is...
Oshiri Anpanman!
Oshiri Anpanman?
Look, his head is shaped like an ass.
That's right. His ass is plump.
What happened to you today?
I'm hungry and I haven't eaten anything.
Okay, then I'll give you this.
What?
Eat my ass.
No, I don't want to eat your ass.
This ass is delicious.
Really?
Munch, munch, munch, munch.
Eat it.
It's delicious.
Do you want to eat it too?
Yes.
Then tear it up and eat it.
Give it to me. Give it to me.
It stinks. It stinks. It stinks.
Your ass stinks.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
My brother's ass is smelly.
Stop it. It stinks. It stinks.
Okay, tear it up and eat it again.
Yes.
It stinks. It stinks. Your ass stinks.
It came out again.
Okay, this time...
It stinks. It stinks.
It stinks. It stinks. It stinks.
Okay, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Eat this.
Yes.
It's delicious.
Isn't it?
Yes.
Hey, hey, where did it come from?
The Oshiri Panman came from the Oshiri planet.
The Oshiri planet?
Yes.
The Oshiri planet is a planet that is split into two parts.
In the middle of that, a smelly smell comes out.
That's a fart. It stinks. It stinks.
That's right. This is it.
It stinks. It stinks. It stinks.
This is it.
Stop it.
It stinks.
I don't want it anymore. I don't want it anymore. I don't want it anymore. I don't want it anymore.
It stinks. It stinks.
Sometimes, the middle of that planet is split into two parts.
From the middle, a brown object comes out.
That's poop.
I hate poop.
From the Oshiri planet, you already have a souvenir.
A souvenir?
Look inside the land cell.
What is it? What is it?
I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it. Is it in here?
What is it?
Hey.
It's poop. I hate it. I hate poop.
It stinks.
What is it, Oshiri-pappa?
This sound is the sound of something happening in Oshiri planet.
Shouldn't we go quickly?
Why don't you come with us and fight?
I don't want to. I don't want to.
Are you going to fight?
Yes.
If you fight, your mom and dad will be full of poop.
I don't want to be full of poop. Let's go.
Then let's go.
Yes.
It stinks. It stinks. It stinks.
It stinks. It stinks. It stinks. It stinks.
Yes.
That was the children of Kokoriko.
But you were thrown on the way.
You can get angry when you meet.
I'm angry.
With elephant's nose.
Next, let's see the brother of Nakagawa family.
Everyone, clap.
Nakagawa family.
Oshiri, Oshiri, Oshiri, Oshiri, ching, ching.
This is poop.
Oh, no.
That's all.
Next, let's see the brother of Nakagawa family.
What are you doing?
Hey, it's me!
Hey!
Hey, you're pooping!
No, no, no, I'm not!
You're pooping!
Then, you have to poop three times!
Hey, you're pooping!
You're pooping!
You're a mess!
Hey, if the other person did something bad, you should have brought 2 million yen!
Huh?
Hey, you should have brought this!
Who are you looking at?
We just had 2 teams do it.
If you think it was interesting,
get ready and run!
Not yet, not yet, not yet, not yet!
Let's go!
This way, this way!
Ready!
Go!
11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16 people!
11, 12, 13, 14 people!
That means, Kokoriko's brother wins!
Then, let's give Kokoriko a round of applause!
Thank you very much!
This year, Kokoriko will appear on M1 on this show.
Really?
Nakagawa is dirty, right?
Who are you talking about?
You're a grown-up!
If it weren't for that, I wouldn't have won!
I'm a grown-up!
Good evening!
I'm sure there are many of you.
Right?
I don't know.
What is it?
What should I do? A punishment game?
A punishment game?
What should I do?
Are you talking about bowling?
That's just having fun bowling with everyone.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What are you talking about?
You keep saying it's hard to lose.
This punishment game is tough.
It's tough, right?
It's going to get harder.
So what should I do?
You're too good at having fun bowling by yourself.
Everyone's bowling with four people.
You make it look like it's easy.
But in the end, you get beaten up.
And then you end up with a girlfriend.
You're a professional.
I'm such a fool.
You did it with Katsuki before.
I wonder what I did.
It was a great show.
This is really...
What should I do?
If it's not that hard, it's meaningless.
Mentally and physically.
I'm sorry.
I'm an S.
You're an M.
People like you don't know the limits.
I have love in the end.
Why?
I really have love.
It comes out of my pocket.
I can't help it.
You had love in the past.
I had love.
I wonder if it's okay.
I don't know what you think.
There was a hotel before.
That was a week ago.
I was depressed.
I really didn't like it.
I understand.
We've experienced it.
You're such a demon.
Mentally and physically.
Yamazaki said that.
He used to spend 10,000 yen.
Do it for 48 hours.
No, no, no, no.
Let's do something like that.
Otherwise, it's meaningless.
I don't have any budget for this show.
I only have 20,000 yen.
I can't do anything.
It's a little crazy.
I can't do that either.
You can think about it.
But there are four of us.
Yamazaki didn't get hurt that much.
He's on TV.
He's still young.
He's a little crazy.
He's in his 40s.
Entry number one.
It's the worst.
The other day,
I was doing something cowardly.
I was eating.
I was in a private room.
There was an iron bar.
An iron bar?
It's a guy with rough eyes.
I can't see it from the other side.
When I got in, I thought it was noisy.
It was a stupid family.
There was an old woman, a father, a child.
It's like a child actor.
Hey, here's the ice cream.
Here's the ice cream.
It's not a bar that brings kids.
I don't know what this kid is doing.
I can't see it.
I think it's...
It's not open.
It's...
It's making a sound.
Sometimes it's...
It's hitting the body.
Now, everyone is pulling me.
Hey, that's...
It's something a child does.
I said it's something a child does.
I've been hit more than 10 times.
I just gave it back once.
That's the problem.
When the other person complains,
When the parents come,
I said something.
It came out like this.
What happened?
After that, it came out like this.
It came out like this.
Hey, I'm sorry.
It's something a child does.
Oh...
I can't say anything.
It's this.
I can't help it.
That's cowardly.
It's hard if you do that.
That's a problem.
I can't help it.
I'm addicted to it.
It's the opposite version of the tiger.
The safest thing to do is to have a lot of children.
What?
It's very comfortable.
What's safe?
It's the safest thing to do is to have a lot of children.
I have a question for Mr. Matsumoto who likes the part of the circle of the zoo.
The circle?
The circle of the zoo.
Oh, the circle.
What kind of rabbit is the rabbit that Mr. Matsumoto used to have?
Oh, there was one.
Oh, really?
Yes.
It's zero.
But it looks like a rabbit, doesn't it?
It looks like a rabbit.
I don't know if it's zero.
That's right.
First of all, it's 2.5 meters.
May I? May I? May I?
Don't put your ears in!
If you put your ears in, it's 5 meters.
He told me to put my ears in.
If it's a measurement, it's a measurement.
That's no good.
That's why it's zero.
I don't know if you're going to put your ears in!
I don't know!
It's rolling.
It's pooping! It's pooping!
It doesn't change.
It's like a junior high school student.
By the way, what's wrong with that?
Did you throw it somewhere?
I threw it away.
It's 5 meters long.
You're going to get caught.
It's going to fly away.
I'm here to throw it away.
I can't throw it away!
It's pooping! It's pooping!
I'm here to throw it away!
After a year and four months of silence, that fateful confrontation approaches Yamasaki's body.
Will he be able to defeat the strongest champion in the world?
Yamasaki vs. Moriman will be released soon.