Old man, old woman, are you watching?
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai, we will be investigating Dan-san!
As you can see today, we will be investigating Dan-san.
Oh, is that so?
Yes.
How far will he go?
As you can see, right before we went to the toilet,
two girls were in the women's toilet.
They were saying, if you don't hurry up, it will start.
There were two people who were exercising.
First of all, the old man and the old woman.
Oh.
The old man and the old woman.
I will show you this photo.
Which one of you do you like?
They are asking like this.
You can't see it.
This is downtown.
Here we go.
Downtown, Kinya Kitaoji, Koutaro Satomi, Ryo Tsugi, Hideki Takahashi, Ken Matsudaira.
You don't have the confidence to win this.
How do you win?
They are asking the old man and the old woman.
Among the old man and the old woman, which one do you like?
That's right.
First, let's see it.
Of course, it's Kitaoji.
Koutaro Satomi.
He is very handsome.
I don't like him.
Koutaro Satomi.
Hideki Takahashi.
Ryo Tsugi.
Ken Matsudaira.
He is handsome.
Koutaro Satomi.
Kitaoji.
Hideki Takahashi.
Ryo Tsugi.
Kitaoji.
I don't like him.
Hideki Takahashi.
He is very manly.
Koutaro Satomi.
I don't like him.
It is not entered in the first vote.
The middle of the old man and the old woman are Hideki Takahashi.
Koutaro Satomi.
Kitaoji.
Ryo Tsugi.
Koutaro Satomi.
For us, Reihou is Reihou.
Reihou is Reihou.
Reihou. That's why I'm saying it to Kouji Satomi.
That's right. Even if all of them die, it's still Reihou.
There's nothing I can do about it.
I see.
It's completely different from Kii-chan's version.
Completely different.
It's like I'm not interested at all.
Now, let's move on.
The next one is the high school girls' edition.
This is what it looks like.
Downtown, Eguchi Yosuke, Fukuyama... What is it? I don't know.
I don't know, but Fukuyama is very popular these days.
That's right.
As a man, I'm definitely higher.
Mook.
Fukuyama Masaharu.
Eguchi Yosuke.
A wild place.
Downtown.
Mook.
Hosaka Naoki.
Fukuyama Masaharu.
Motoki.
A sexy place.
Fukuyama Masaharu.
Downtown.
Eguchi Yosuke.
Fukuyama Masaharu.
Downtown.
I like it because it's romantic.
Fukuyama Masaharu.
Eguchi Yosuke.
Mook.
Fukuyama.
A cold place.
Downtown.
Mook.
Eguchi Yosuke.
Fukuyama.
Oh.
It's a public place.
I don't care if you do this with me.
I don't know at all.
This, this.
Where did you come from?
I don't know at all.
Tell me.
Why?
Why did you come out?
Drama?
Did you come out in a drama?
There was.
What the hell are you doing?
Hey.
You're crazy.
Next, the foreigner edition.
I was very popular with foreigners the other day.
What is it?
I was popular with the scary guys.
A little more.
I'm listening to the foreigners.
Yes.
Well, of course, Akebono.
Shiwachan.
Sankon.
Kevin Costner.
Michael Jackson.
Oh, here.
Michael Jackson or.
Isn't it Kevin Costner now?
Is that so?
Yes.
I think I'm better than Akebono.
No.
I don't know.
This is.
I'm better than this.
If it was Akebono, I'd be better alone.
No, no.
It's not about Timo.
How do you say this?
I think it's about the heat.
Arnold Schwarzenegger.
No. 1.
Kevin Costner.
Arnold Schwarzenegger.
It's Kebron.
Kevin Costner.
Akebono.
Akebono
He symbolizes the American spirit in Japan.
I like Arnold.
Schwarzenegger, yes, in downtown.
Osman Sanko.
He has my first, my same name.
Akebono
Kevin Costner
I think Kevin Costner is my favorite.
He seems to be really like a family man.
Downtown
Akebono
He is the best.
He is not Akebono.
Akebono
He is the best.
He is good in time.
He is not good at the game. He is losing to Sanko.
That's true.
He is getting more and more interesting.
Do you understand?
Interesting.
Let's go to the last one.
The last one is Okamahen.
Okamahen in Roppongi.
Let's go to this one.
This picture.
Downtown
Ucchananchan
Katochankinchan
Tunnel
Honjabaka
Yasushi Kiyoshi
I don't want to be number one here.
Downtown
Tunnel
Ucchananchan
Katochankinchan
Tunnel
He is a good man.
Yasushi Kiyoshi
Downtown
He is a naughty boy.
Honjabaka
Tunnel
Ucchananchan
I think he is very cute.
Downtown
Katochankinchan
Yasushi Kiyoshi
Downtown
Yay! Yay! Yay!
I don't want to be number one here.
Yasushi Kiyoshi
Honjabaka
I think I am number one here.
I think so too.
I am not saying which one is better.
I am saying downtown.
That means you are number one here.
What do you mean?
What is your strategy?
I don't want to be number one.
What about your children and your grandparents?
I am in charge of the girls and the parents.
I am in charge of the younger generation.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
It's been a while.
I've been up early these days.
That's not a good thing.
I've been up early.
I see.
When I woke up at 12 or 1 in the morning, I was really sleepy.
I was really sleepy.
Your body temperature was changing.
My body temperature was changing.
I would wake up at 10 in the morning.
In the morning?
Yes.
I would go to the convenience store downstairs and eat by myself.
At school?
Yes.
I would eat while looking at the wide screen.
You were a housewife.
Yes, I was a housewife.
I would go to the convenience store and watch TV.
You were lying.
Did you go there everyday?
Why do you weigh yourself?
Well...
Didn't you get sleepy at midnight?
Yes, I would be very sleepy.
So you would wait to go home and work.
Yes.
At 12 in the morning, you would go to bed.
I would go to bed immediately.
Did you go to sleep?
In the past, when I was sleeping, I didn't sleep until the morning, and I couldn't wake up until the evening.
Even if I woke up, I couldn't wake up when Okamoto was still in bed.
I don't understand that, but you couldn't wake up.
In the past, I couldn't wake up. Now, I can't wake up. I'm an old man.
When it's midnight, I go to sleep.
And when it's midnight, I wake up.
What are you doing?
What are you talking about?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Hey!
The king's ears...
The news is also strong now.
I know it relatively well.
What is it?
The one with the arrow.
Yes, yes, yes.
The crow, the crow, the crow.
You've been doing something all the time, haven't you?
That, that, that.
Everyone's been talking about the crow with the arrow.
The crow with the arrow.
It's hard to say.
I can't decide on a name.
I've been saying Yagamo recently.
Yagamo.
It's abbreviated.
I want you to stop using that name.
I've been saying Yagamo.
Why is everyone talking about it so much?
It's on sale.
If you're going to pay attention to that kind of thing,
I'll put something on your shoulder.
I want you to pay attention to it, so I'll put something like this on your shoulder.
No, let me do it.
You're the one who put it on my shoulder.
Are you sick?
You're old.
But I might get angry if I say it like this,
but that crow is a little...
It's a little...
It's a joke.
Is that so?
That's not really stuck.
It's not stuck.
No, I've been a little weak lately.
I've been holding my legs.
I've been acting a little too much.
That crow is a little too much.
My sister's been taken from the side.
Think about it.
You can't say that for a week without getting through to your body.
No, well, that's a good thing.
That's a good thing.
You can't get through.
It's just that it's not as bad as it seems.
If it had been like that forever, it wouldn't have happened.
It would have been pulled out.
That's why when everyone saw it,
it was stuck.
It was stuck.
Why do you decide on your own like that?
No, I just saw it.
It's stuck.
So you don't even know if that's a crow or not.
I don't know what the maid wrote.
I'm sure it's a crow.
It's been stuck in my back since I was born.
Yeah, I guess so.
That's not true.
That's the only thing I can think of.
No, that's why it was shot.
It was shot, so it's stuck in his back.
You don't even know if it was shot or not.
What, are you doing this yourself?
Around here.
That's a little weird, isn't it?
Well, you're doing your best, aren't you?
You brought the net and said,
I don't know what to do.
It's stupid, isn't it?
That animal is like that.
I thought I'd saved it, but it ran away.
I don't know what to do.
Why do you have to catch it with such a big net?
Is it that hard?
It's so close.
Why do you have to make such a big net?
I can't do that.
I'm afraid I'll be taken to the hospital.
Why don't you do it?
It's so easy to hold.
I can't do it.
I can't catch it.
I'm going home.
He's going to jump, isn't he?
I'm going to jump, isn't he?
He's in a good mood.
That's good.
I was somewhere again today.
What?
I don't know.
Can you shoot?
I can't shoot during the show.
The enemy is attacking us suddenly.
When the enemy attacks us from the front,
I thought he was my enemy, but I couldn't do it.
That's his weapon.
I thought it would be fine if I tried it once.
It hurts.
No, no, no, no, no.
What are you talking about?
I'll tell you something.
If you don't have a mouse, you'll be lonely even with a cat.
That's right.
So if you chase it to the corner, it will run away at first, but if you think you can't do it anymore, it will run away.
Will it come out?
Isn't it like this?
What is this?
Like this.
Oh, like this.
Question.
What kind of bridge does Akiko Wada use?
Is it a bridge?
Don't get angry.
Don't attack.
I'll keep it quiet.
I've been watching that guy a lot.
I was saying something like that the other day.
I was writing a phone call for the New Year.
I'm not sleeping.
It's quiet.
You're not sleeping.
Even if I tell you how I'm doing, you won't tell me to do this.
I'm not sleeping.
I haven't slept since 7 o'clock last night.
Is that so?
Wait a minute.
There's someone who didn't sleep with me.
It's Mr. Tokomitsu.
Mr. Tokomitsu was caught last night.
I'm sorry, Hama-chan.
We've been together all the time.
Is that so?
I won't be able to go home.
That's right.
I'm about to cry.
I won't touch you anymore.
Don't touch me.
I'm going to tell you something else.
Yes.
What is this?
Pen name.
Mr. Makuri Mukatsuki?
It's a cypress.
It's a challenge corner with a quiz for Machanin.
Who's going to challenge?
Art.
E.
U.
A.
O.
100m.
We've competed.
Now, who will be the first to reach the goal?
Thinking time!
I don't want to do it.
I don't want to do it if you give me a hug.
Answer!
The answer is...
E.
U.
100m.
Yay, yay, yay!
I have a question for you.
Even if you bite your nose, nose water will come out again.
Where does this nose water come from?
Why does nose water exist?
Please tell me.
Nose water?
I'm about to cry.
That's why it's some kind of information.
I understand that your body is in bad shape.
If you say that kind of information, I understand.
Are you drunk?
I don't say that kind of information.
That's right.
I'm a shogun.
I look at your face.
That kind of information.
I'll give you a kiss.
A kiss?
I'm scared.
Why?
Your body is in bad shape.
That kind of information.
Does it come out in that sense?
Nose water is a waste of water in your body.
It's a waste of water?
It's a waste of water.
When you drink too much water, it becomes nose water.
That's not true.
Why?
Why does it come out as nose water?
It's a waste of water.
Nose water is the sweat of the heart.
What?
I don't understand if you say tears.
Nose water is the sweat of the heart.
It comes out when it hurts the heart.
Ouch!
What is the biggest volume of the TV for?
Is there anyone who watches TV with the biggest volume?
I said this before.
The volume changes when you watch a normal program and when it becomes a commercial.
It changes.
I don't know if it's a big deal if it becomes a commercial even if I watch it at a cafe.
I want you to stop that.
It's a big mistake if you think the product will sell with that.
You should stop that.
People are more interested in the smaller one.
When it suddenly becomes a commercial, it's hard to understand what you're looking at.
The picture is out.
The picture is out, but I think it's the opposite.
Everyone is doing the opposite.
You compare it with other products.
My detergent is better than yours.
It's the opposite.
It's funny.
It's funny, so it's funny.
It's not falling at all.
It's the worst.
It's the worst detergent.
You know, there are many companies that offer this program.
But you can't tell me one of them.
You can't tell me one of them.
Why can't you tell me one of them?
It's a broadcast code.
Why?
It's on the screen.
It's similar.
Isn't it the same in the theater?
What's the difference?
What?
The beauty of ice is from Shinjuku.
Oh, in the adult movie.
In the adult movie.
Yes.
That's it.
If we had a sponsor, we wouldn't have.
We all have our own companies.
Some companies who don't allow people to use the program are like Ин våeye
Ин oureya.
Is there such a company?
Isn't that kind of salesman cool?
Thank you for your viewing.
Please subscribe to my channel and give it a high rating.