I don't do that!
You're a mysterious transfer student!
I'm sitting here with Yamazaki
I thought it would be better to find a partner
Even if I'm doing it alone
I'm much less popular than when I was in Team Zero
Really?
How about you? Do you feel that you're getting less popular?
Yes
I really don't want to do it
I'm a fool
I want to be in the spotlight
I want to be in the spotlight too
What do you mean?
It's like you're a fool
I'm already a fool
I'm already in the spotlight
There are people who say that
Yes, there are people who say that
But there are people around me
Takasu and I are good friends
Right?
Yes
What are you talking about?
Takasu is a former nabe pro
I'm a soccer player
But sometimes I get the feeling that I want to do it
Right?
Say it
I don't want to be in the spotlight
Actually, the target of this prank is Producer Suga
Looking back on his childhood, his star quality is very high
And his popularity is rising
He doesn't seem to be a fool
This is the script of this time to trick him into becoming a star
Will Suga-chan be able to get along with Yamazaki?
He's like our boss
What do you think about Suga-san becoming a star after becoming a staff member?
I'm very happy about it
Because he's the next star after becoming a staff member
That's right
I don't think it's the other way around
There was a time when Saito was famous
He was a star
There are times like that
I think I failed
But I think I can do it if I do it with this person
You think so?
Yes
He's in here
May I?
What are you talking about?
May I announce it?
I'll announce it
I really want to do it with Suga-san
He's a long-time friend
I see
Suga-chan is a long-time friend
Okay, I got it
You have to respect his will
Can you give him a joke?
I have a joke that warms me up
I'm going to do it today
He said he's going to do it today
Give him a joke
Okay
You want to do it too, right?
Yes, I want to do it
Okay
I'm going to do it tomorrow
I'm going to read it first
I want money
Suga-chan is really into pranks
That's the difference between him and the producer
Is it for the show?
Or is it just for the stars?
The more he talks about it, the more he gets excited
It's the first stage of the new couple who are looking forward to downtown
It's the second stage of the new couple who are looking forward to downtown
It's the second time
You like to say that
Why? It's different
It's a little different from your face at the opening
I want you to say it
I don't want to say it
Don't say that
I want you to react
I really like it when you say it
I like it even more
Normally when a talent goes to a night club
People will come and put up a rope
They'll say, don't go over there anymore
They'll come
I know, I know
He'll get drunk
He'll get drunk and get in the car
I want you to say it a little more
He's so annoying
I really like it
I like it as much as you like it
It's different
I don't like it when you say it
There's something on your face
It's the skin
The skin is peeling off
I'm waiting for the opening again
I really don't like it
It's only here on your face
When you turn your face
It's gone
Wait a minute
Inside?
Inside already
I'm looking out the window
Why?
I don't like it
It's not like that
I'm working hard
You are
I peel off the apples
Do you have a water bug?
I don't
You don't?
It's a water bug's
You all know this, right?
What's that?
It's not a mold?
It's a mold
You wipe your feet
I think that's why it's like this
It's not a weird disease
It's not sick at all
It's sick
Why is it like this inside?
Boku-chan is like that
What's Boku-chan?
I'm very excited
You are
You are fine
The important thing is that it's not sick
Everyone has it
You have it too, right?
It's red
It hurts
It's scary
Stop it
It's too red
Are you still doing that?
You are 30 years old
You have children
You are Hamada-san, right?
You have to do your best
You are not a newcomer
You have to do your best like a newcomer
That's right
Right?
You don't have many customers today, right?
I don't
Why?
I don't know
Are you not popular anymore?
What are you going to do?
If you are not popular anymore
It's hard
No one can say anything about you
I'll treat you like a normal person
You'll treat me like a normal person
There are a lot of comedians like that
Who?
I'm going to be deceived by your applause
You are going to be deceived by my applause
There are a lot of people who are not on TV anymore
But you are like that
You are like a trendy actor
Who?
What?
That's not true
Who?
Who said that?
Nanjo Yutaka
Who?
That was years ago
You were riding a horse with Momoe
That's a long time ago
That's right
You were a trendy actor
Do you know who is popular now?
It's your son, right?
That's right
He is always in a bad mood and makes a record
I don't understand
How many times did you say the same phrase?
Are you a fool?
And also
What kind of makeup are you wearing?
Who is he?
Why is he wearing a shadow?
But he is popular, right?
He is popular
You know that drama
Recently, there is a drama called Ani
Really?
What? Your lover is small?
What?
Don't spit it out
What are you doing?
You are watching it
I'll get back to the topic
Do you hate him that much?
I don't hate him
He is doing his best
What if he doesn't do anything?
For example, if he comes from the hallway of Shakespeare
If he hits you
If you say sorry and try to go
That's not good
You shouldn't do that
Do you want to go to the hair salon?
That's not good
But it will happen
If you do the same thing
How?
If you hit him
If you say sorry
What will you do?
But if you hit him like that
That's not good
I don't hate him that much
I want to write it
Kick
Last week, it was cut
I kicked it
Sorry
Hey
Did you lower your head to the AD?
I have one last question
The debut single of Geisha Girls is only available in America
It doesn't sell in Japan
I really want it, please think about it
Do you want it?
We are going to be in New York
You guys
Recording
Ryuichi
He made 2 songs
Ryuichi said he wants to make 2 songs
Ryuichi is amazing
He said he wants at least 1 week
That's
That's impossible
He can finish it in a day
What?
If you ask me if it doesn't sell in Japan
It doesn't sell
It doesn't sell in Japan
He's strong
But the audience will be like
What's wrong with me?
That's what I think
I'm telling you to be careful
I want you to say that
I'm a bad guy
It doesn't sell in Japan
What?
Shut up
A chicken's leg has one claw
There's one in this picture
Really?
There's one here
It doesn't touch the ground
It doesn't mean anything
Why is it there?
That's not true
Then what is it?
I'm going to ask
Do you know Takayaba Kiribasami?
It's Takaeda
There's Takaeda
It's a better one
It's better than Takaeda
I know
What is it?
Speak
You'll understand
You don't need words
What is it?
I'm sorry
It's like a switch
If you press it, the leg goes like this
Why?
What's there to press?
The bird does it
Did you kill it?
When you try to grab something
A small hand comes out
If you pull it, it goes like this
What's a small hand?
This hasn't been solved yet
That's what it does?
That's not it
That's also a bird
This is all a bird
That's right
What about this?
You said this is also a bird
This is also a bird
It's a different word
You're human, right?
This is human
What?
This is also human
This is human
That's not it
I don't know
Elvis
Elvis Presby
It's not Elvis
That's not it
Who is it?
Elvis Presby
That's not it
When you're on stage
What's the use of the flutters on the side of your costume?
That's a design
It's similar to this
It's similar
What was that?
The one you do this
I don't know
The flutters start like this
If you don't have that
When you go like this
It comes like this
Wait
Do you want to drop it?
Here?
That's right
That's how it is
If you don't have that
It comes like this
That's right
What about Presley?
What?
When Presley sings
He does this
I don't do that
Today's guest is different
Let's do this and go home
What is the black net you put on your shoulders when you dance?
I don't think it has anything to do with the bow
What do you call it?
This kind of thing
I have something on my shoulders
Why did you start doing this?
Wait
Let's just say the meaning
Do you know Kamen Rider V3?
I do
Double Typhoon
That's right
Father, mother, and sister
All of your siblings were killed
Blood is spilling from the shadows
They were killed
Father, mother, and sister were killed
That's right
That's why you got angry
Double Typhoon
That's right
Do you understand?
I understand
You understand, right?
You would be angry if your parents were killed
That's right
For example, if your parents were killed
You wouldn't be able to forgive them
That's right
You would be angry
That's why
If you say this, it's fine
Do you understand?
Isn't that the explanation of V3?
Explain this
Everyone in my age knows the explanation of V3
The reason why I started doing this
Before I started doing this
I was being teased
What are you talking about?
Gaki no Tsukai comedy star has been born
A new star
Yes
Today
Has been born
I'm nervous
I don't know how long I'll be able to keep up with everyone
The story has just started
It has just started
Normally, I wouldn't be able to accept it
But I'm sure they'll do it
I'm sure they'll do it
I'm looking forward to it
Let's continue
Please take a look at this duo
Thank you
Yama-chan who disbanded Team Zero
Has found a very energetic partner and is trying for the first time
With a high-spirited talk
And a calculated sense of humor
She has been thrown into the comedy world
It's Team One
Hello
Hello, I'm Team One
Nice to meet you
I want money
I want it too
Do you want to play a game of Gingogo?
Do you want to play?
Yes, let's do it
You want to play?
You do it, I'll do it too
You're so cute
Let's play Gingogo
First, we need a tool
We need a tool
A knife
I don't have a knife
I do have one
Why do you have one?
And two
Why do you have two?
Japanese television
You're so good
So good
You're so talented
Stop talking like that
I'm not
You make me feel bad
You're right
I have a knife, I have the weapon
I have underwear
Panties
I'm embarrassed
I do have one
Why do you have one?
I also have it
Why do you have it?
I have two
Why do you have two?
I have two TVs
You don't have one
How about this?
You can't do it like this.
Don't cover it up too much!
Hurry up!
I'm going to do it like this.
Wait a minute.
I've never done it like this before.
It's my first time too!
Teach me how to do it.
I'll go into the bank and say,
Give me the money!
I'll practice.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Give me the money!
Okay!
Don't get cocky!
I'm going to get caught!
What are you doing?
I'm going to open two automatic toilets.
Let's go!
Ouch!
What are you doing?
I got caught in the automatic toilet.
Give me your hand!
I won't give it to you!
I'm going to the bank!
I'm going to do it again.
Are you okay?
Hey!
I'm going to the bank!
Give me the money!
I won't give it to you!
Hey!
Give me the money!
I'm going to open two automatic toilets.
I won't give it to you!
Look outside!
Outside!
Hey!
The police are here.
Really?
If the police catch you,
You're going to jail, aren't you?
I won't give it to you!
Thank you very much.
You guys did your best!
Your timing was bad!
Wait a minute.
My timing was bad.
Your timing was bad.
Maybe it was you who pulled his leg.
Do you want to do it again?
Yes, I did my best.
Thank you very much!