It's so sad.
Yeah, it is.
It's so sad that we can't be with Downtown.
I don't know what to talk about.
But you're the senior.
Even if you say that, it's a long story.
Hey, hey.
Oh.
Good morning.
Hamada-san, what happened to your black outfit?
You can tell by my outfit.
Don't you miss me?
Yes.
Everyone, do you know that today is Matsumoto's birthday?
That's right.
And it's the Tokyo Olympics next year.
And I'm wearing this outfit.
Do you understand?
I remember it from the past.
You mean that's what you're wearing today?
That's right.
Up until now, he has been able to fulfill many of Matsumoto's dreams by doing black-and-white in the past 7 times.
The beginning is the world record of running and jumping.
And continuing to the first half of the long distance,
the sky miracle play of skateboarding.
He hits back the 150km high-speed ball.
The world record of weightlifting.
The 50cm fire rainbow dance.
And he swam 25m in 10 seconds.
He set a lot of records.
What kind of challenge will Matsumoto face on his 56th birthday?
I said it was okay, but I said I couldn't do it.
The most important thing for me is that he will do this for me.
Birthday present.
Birthday present?
But you still don't know what you want to do, right?
Let's watch this.
It was skateboarding.
Yes.
Actually, he wants to do this.
No way.
It's a fishing rod.
It's a double spin.
It's a double spin while jumping forward.
This is the one you like the most.
This is the one.
This is it.
This is the one that Kohei Ichimura showed at Rio Olympics.
This is Matsumoto.
Matsumoto wants to do a triple.
No, no.
Why are you doing that?
I'll change my clothes. Can you change yours?
Let's go.
Let's do it quickly
After 14 years, Kuroko-shu has risen again
Matsumoto Hitoshi challenges Uchimura Kohei to defend
He has the most strength in his body
If you bring it, I'll talk to you.
That's right.
Good morning.
I'm really sorry.
What are you doing?
I told everyone.
It's a strange request.
No, not at all.
What do you mean?
If it's a woman, she'll give you a ring as a present.
If it's about this, it'll be a fishing rod.
I'm sorry, I'm not a servant.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I mean, you are the one who is willing to do it.
I'm embarrassed, but I'm happy.
What is it?
Ah, that's it.
Ah, you're crying a bit.
But I can't do this anymore.
Ah, but...
Let's stand up.
Let's do it.
It's more expensive than I thought.
I know.
Let's do it.
First, Mr. Kuchimura.
It's heavy.
Mr. Matsumoto.
No, no, no.
Don't hold this!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Ouch!
Wait a minute, wait a minute!
Wait a minute. What's going on?
Let's push her down once.
What's going on?
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
What?
Wait a minute.
Hey, sensei, sensei!
We still have nothing to do with this.
What are you doing?
They are not doing anything!
It came to us first
What about now
Are you upset?
They are not making me angry
You should go to apologize
No, we should go to see their situation
Museum has done something that upset people?
No, no, I didn't do anything.
Why?
No response...
aganjou.
harden
The good lead
I don't have any plans to do it.
I'm aware that I'm forcing myself to do it, but I thought I could do it a little more.
That's not true.
I've already lost my tongue and my sigh.
What did you think was cold?
I don't know who it is, but there was a guy who twisted my arm.
I thought, maybe this is it.
I thought, I'll take this home with me.
I was watching Hamada's school days in Kuroko.
Tanaka said, let's do it quickly.
I thought, is this a bad thing?
Hamada, are you doing it properly?
Sorry, sorry.
You should talk properly.
There are things that you don't understand.
Yes.
I'll say it properly.
You!
Yes?
You twisted your arm.
I thought you were going to say it.
I'm definitely going to check you.
I didn't twist it.
If you had worked a little harder, you could have done it.
I'm not doing my best.
You didn't get it, did you?
I'm sorry.
Please, do your best.
I can't finish this.
You don't have enough shako, right?
Yes, I don't have enough.
Let's go.
Are you waiting?
Please.
Let's go.
The second challenge.
It's like this.
Excuse me.
I feel refreshed.
I went to the toilet.
I'm sorry.
We were a little bit nervous.
I'm really sorry.
Let's start.
Please.
Watch out.
Hold his hand.
Right foot.
Hold his right foot.
Left foot.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
Now, don't moveヤ
Hey, put the claw off
It'sแ
Wake up!!
Put the hawk and Fujiwara up
Okay okay
Okay, I'll get that one
A nice robin
Nice blobs
One more please
If anyone else got their heads measured, there's a risk
Your head
Isn't it better to put them mortise them?
Make mortise them
I'd like to mortise them
ya, mortise them
Should I?
Let's mortise those
How about that one?
Stop it! Stop it!
Give me your hand!
Hey!
Mr. Matsumoto!
You're angry, aren't you?
Yes, she's angry.
Aga-chan, I'm going to the bathroom.
I was a little close. I thought I could have done it a little more.
Well...
My head...
It hurts so much I can't think.
That's not true.
Is that what it is?
I wanted to ask him about it.
He was like a stick.
He was pushing me.
He was shouting.
He was screaming.
I was scared.
I lost my sight.
The skin on your armpit is crooked.
Tsukite, you're a goat, right?
No, I am.
What do you want to do?
I want to use the stick again.
I really hate sticks.
What is that? What is that name?
What kind of order is that?
Where did you put it?
And where are you going to put it after this?
I'm curious about that.
We'll do our best next time.
It's okay.
You said you'll do your best next time.
I can see it.
We can do it.
Don't be shy.
Thank you.
The third challenge to regain his spirit.
I used a stick because of that.
I was told that the stick was painful.
I didn't get hurt that much.
That's good.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
I'll do something like this.
What a strange request.
I'll do my best.
Let's do it.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's really okay.
Masamu-san, please turn your back to the front.
Okay, right foot is okay.
Put your leg on your hip.
Lift it up a little.
Are you ready?
Yes
Ready, start!
Go, go, go!
It's not going up at all
A little more, a little more!
Get up, get up!
Go, go, go!
Go!
Don't you get in the way!
A little more!
I can't do it
Wait a minute
You got it.
Fuyuhara-san, you got it.
Yes, I got it.
Shijimono.
Matsumoto-san, I got it.
Umm...
Yaegashi-san...
Yaegashi-san, I got it.
The fearsome villain that obstacle a big deal
Ryuichi Chigawa
He wasn't nice to me
He just disappeared
Get out!
Get out! Get out of here!
There's no way I can do that!
It's all falling down on my face.
We talked about it, but we went overboard.
Let's stop with the magic tape.
Like a
How many more times do you have to do this?
I'll break the rules and get out of here.
Let's do it next time.
I'm confident in the next time.
I'm confident in Tanaka.
I'm the only one who trusts Tanaka.
Please.
Thank you.
Don't be like a king of the cave.
Like a king of the cave.
I'm scared.
I'm getting nervous.
Yamaguchi-san.
Will he succeed in the next challenge?
They are very good at it.
They are good at it?
They are pushing me.
I'm relieved.
I'm relieved that they are in a good mood.
Sorry.
No problem.
This is the last challenge.
I'm listening to you.
I want you to win the fishing rod again.
Let's decide.
Thank you.
Start!
Fire! Please!
It's going to collapse!
Once more!
From the back.
Yes, yes, turn to this side.
Then, bring your legs this way.
I did it before.
Put your legs...
You did it.
You caught it.
Slowly, slowly.
Good, good.
Your left leg.
I'll take your left leg.
I will hold him.
I will raise my hand.
Please pull him back once.
I will pull him back.
I'll do it firmly.
Ouch!
I'll go.
Can I push?
Ready, go!
Ah! I got it!
I got it!
Hold the ring.
Yes, yes.
It's okay.
Ready, go!
Okay!
Go!
Wait, wait, wait!
The rotation is different.
Stop!
It's looking good.
It's going forward.
Right?
Yes.
Matsumoto-san, you can't rotate.
I'll do it again.
Matsumoto-san.
Mr. Kazama.
Excuse me.
What's wrong?
I was thinking of using the power of the wire to rotate it, but I thought that if I changed the magic tape to a string, I could make a reaction without pain.
I don't know what I want to do at all.
It hurts, and I don't like it.
I don't want to do that.
I really want to do it.
I want to do it with my legs only.
Some people did it without knowing.
Oh, that's right.
Well, well.
It's no use doing it without doing it.
After all, you guys just look at it like this.
You were looking at it, right?
I didn't cooperate at all.
I said it at the end.
What is that? I don't know.
I don't know.
I put it on and I got a lot of energy.
I'm not in the mood.
I finally did it.
I thought I could hold the ring.
I thought I could hold it.
That's a little different from my character.
Let's cut that part out.
That's not it.
I see.
You know, you were shaking my hand.
I was saying, it hurts.
I was saying it hurts like I was in middle school.
You shouldn't have told me that.
Can you see the beauty?
Yes, I can.
Stop using the harness.
I'm not going to do it.
Oh, well.
I'm being told that I have a harness.
How do I get into the studio?
I don't have a harness anymore.
I wish I had a harness.
I didn't have a trough.
I'm going to do another show.
Of the company.
I'm going to start now.
The fifth challenge is no longer allowed.
I've seen it before.
You've seen it before?
Ah, I see.
It's okay.
My present.
I want you to sing it.
I understand.
A gift of justice.
Let's decide with this!
Yes!
Let's go!
Thank you!
First, I'll take this.
Will it reach?
Sorry.
I got it.
It's here.
OK.
Patting.
Please lift it up a bit.
You have to lift it up again.
It's already spinning.
No, no.
Please clean it up.
It's here.
Straight, straight.
Ushiro, you're in the second round.
You can do it.
You almost kept it!
One more time!
One more...
Two times
One time
On top
You did it!
Yeah!
After overcoming many hardships, Matsumoto successfully completed the spinning technique that surpassed Uchimura Kohei.
56 years old, congratulations.
You did it!
Okay, okay, okay.
Thank you very much!
Are you happy?
You said thank you very much.
You gave me a wonderful present.
It was good.
7th Gen Kimono