Tenjin-Yama Ski Resort
A place where many skiers and snowboarders gather
The members of Gaki no Tsukai have gathered
The first episode of Gaki no Tsukai
Chigichigishoku Millenium
Slippery Slippery Charismatic Ski Resort
It's a bad title again
We're outside
Long time no see
Let's do something together
The weather is nice
It's nice
What do you think of these two?
I don't know why they're here
It has nothing to do with you!
What an interesting reaction!
There's no mistake
Today...
What are you doing?
You don't have glasses?
We're going to try skiing today!
I can't do it
You can do it!
You can't do everything
You have to expand your scope
Can you do it?
We can ski a little
We can do it
Why can you do it?
6 years ago
I was a reporter for a ski show
Why?
I don't want to do it
There's a phrase I hate
Why did you react to it?
Whose?
Aoyama's
Why?
Can you do it?
I can do it!
Really?
He says he can
I wore it last year
Really?
I was wearing it with my girlfriend
We're going to stay like this
We're going to stay like this all day
Today's final goal is...
This!
Ta-da!
Are you okay?
We're going to take the torch
And line up
First of all, Mr. Hamada
And me
The end part
Isn't this the end part?
That's right
This is...
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
If you're going to talk, talk
It's funny
What's wrong with you?
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
Yamachan's Ski Gathering
Ski Gathering
Ski Gathering?
First of all
Let's introduce the members of Ski Deck
First is Downtown
They've been on the board once or twice
But no one taught them
They're both amateurs
Next is Kokoriko
He used to work as a reporter for a ski program for half a year
They're both quite confident
They have the ability of a heavyweight
And the two staff representatives
On the other hand, Tsuchinoto has zero experience in skiing
They're both amateurs
First of all
I don't want to ski
Are you ready?
Why?
First of all, the cold
I'm really scared of the cold
Are you scared?
I'm not
I'm scared
But that's why everyone is dressed like this
Your ears are sticking out, right?
No, they're not
Your ears are sticking out a little, right?
When your ears are sticking out a little
If you leave your ears in the cold all the time
It's called a frostbite
What does that mean?
What should I do?
So please don't do that
If you have a frostbite
Your ears will fall out
There aren't many people who have frostbite
There are people who go skiing
Yes, there are
Everyone is here
It's okay for today
Well, I know I'm already skiing
It's about time for a big laugh
A funny laugh
Today, really
You're weird
Go home
There's something I really want you to pay attention to
What is it?
This is a snowstorm
A snowstorm?
Snowstorm
Please pay attention to this
The weather is really nice today, right?
Really
If you don't wear goggles at all
If you keep your eyes open like this
You'll get snowy eyes
Your eyes will get burned
What kind of situation is it that your eyes get burned?
I thought my eyes were completely red
No, it's not
Why do you look like that?
My face will be like this
Will you get snowy eyes?
Is that a snowstorm?
Is this a snowstorm?
I don't want it to be like that
It's scary
Is it going to be like this?
It's Jackie
Snow!
First of all, what kind of way do you slide?
Please ask
What?
What does that mean?
For beginners like us
We just slide like this, right?
What do you call that?
It's called Bogen
Ah, Bogen
We slide like this, right?
That's right
For Bogen
You slide like this
If you slide like this, you won't get hit
Yes, that's right
You think so, right?
But if you slide like this, you'll be like this
What do you call that?
It's called balance
Can you raise your bangs?
What's going on?
There's a lot of sweat
Excuse me, I've only done it 3 times
What does Yukimen mean?
Yukimen is
Please pay attention to this
If you say that, it's scary
What does Yukimen mean?
Mr. Heipo
Yes
Which one do you think is the correct answer?
Falling from the buttocks
That's right
Correct
Even an amateur can tell
This is absolutely
Falling from the buttocks
I see
If you don't fall from your head, it's wrong to hold it
If you fall from your knees
Your knees will get worse
It's just getting worse
If you fall from your hands
Your hands will get stuck
That's why you fall from your hands, right?
Please fall from your buttocks
The correct answer is number 3
Yes
Wait
How do you stop?
I won't let you say anything
I haven't heard how to stop
I haven't heard
Have you said how to stop?
I haven't said it
Really?
How do you stop?
I'll hit you
It's fine
What kind of training will the members of Yamazaki who didn't do anything do?
We'll start the training
Actually, I've prepared a special instructor for today
Really?
Mr. Fujiwara
What?
Please
Amazing
What is this?
You don't have a stock
Amazing
Is that a pig?
That's right
Is that a raccoon?
Amazing
What is this?
What is this pig?
It's really delicious
It's amazing
It's short
Really?
It's called mini ski
Amazing
Have you been doing this for a long time?
I went to a ski resort for a part-time job when I was in college
Mr. Fujiwara has a 2nd class license from the All Japan Ski Association
Amazing
Fujiwara Hiroshi, the manager of Yoshimoto Industries, is 31 years old
Is this why people are different?
He has a 2nd class license from the All Japan Ski Association
His skills are cool and dynamic
The raccoon who draws a school in silver has a powerful face
Please take care of Mr. Fujiwara today
Mr. Hamada
Mr. Fujiwara is in a good mood
Yes
Today's goal is to go somewhere else
That's right
I'm going to do a prank
Actually, it's a lie that he's going to draw a school in silver
Fujiwara, who teaches skiing, is going to do a prank
This is Hamada's regular violence
Why?
I'm going to show you
There's no such thing as a prank
It's completely different
Tanaka cried before
Tanaka once made an unreasonable prank on a man
He made a man cry
It's a lie
Hamada's character, who is afraid of getting cut, should also be included in Fujiwara
I'm going to get cut by Fujiwara
I'm going to teach you a lot
I'm going to get hurt somewhere
I'm going to get cut here
I'm going to bite you, but I'm going to hit you
Will you get hurt?
No
I'm going to bite you
Will you get hurt?
Everyone watching TV
Where and when will you get hurt?
I'm going to get hurt
Fujiwara is going to bully you
I'm going to bully you
I'm going to show you
Will Hamada really get hurt?
Fujiwara, who doesn't know anything, is about to start recording
First of all, I'm going to ask you to wear a ski mask
It's my first time
I'm an amateur
Are you okay?
I'll do my best
Wear a ski mask
If you wear it straight like this
It will slip in front of you
It's 90 degrees on the slope
I see
It's better to have a ski mask
First of all, put your toes on the ski mask
If you step on the ski mask
Is this okay?
It's convenient
Do you know when it's not convenient?
I'm a little scared
I don't know if it will slip
It's slipping
Are you okay?
a little
Jump
It's 90 degrees on the slope
Don't do it
It's terrible
It's easier to start with a warm-up exercise
I'm going to do a warm-up exercise
Let's do a warm-up exercise
First, stretch your muscles
Relax your stiff body
Are you okay?
I did it
Lesson 1 How to walk
Walk normally
Raise your knees
Straighten the board
Like this?
Next, Mazono
Walk slowly
I'm scared
Are you okay?
Yes
It's terrible
Are you okay?
I'm scared
Yamazaki and Kokoriko are experienced
But the way is
Saito, this way
Saito is behind
Not yet
Saito
It's like a doll
It's terrible
What is that?
I can't do it today
I'll take it all
Let's change direction
Raise your hips
This is for your body
Turn it over
You're going to slip
It's stopped if it's perpendicular to the slope
Turn it over
It's too fast
It's dangerous
Are you okay?
That was terrible
My neck is getting stiff
Both
Don't lose
It's terrible
What should I do?
It's okay
Can you raise your stock?
You should move
I'll wait for you
Good luck
I don't like it
The members are falling
The reason for the prank is
Will they be able to do it?
Lesson 2 How to stop
When you stop
You don't have to close your eyes
Put your body under your hips
If you do it like this, it will stop
Please slip
This is really hard
You have to push your heels out
I'll do it here
Kaito, please
The lesson is starting
It's dangerous
Where are you going?
Hamada
It's perfect
Matsumoto
Push your heels out
Like this
It's dangerous
Fujiwara's lesson is starting
Isn't it too fast?
You have to do it slowly
One by one
Lesson 3
It's the same as before
Can I stop?
It hurts
It's a safe weapon
I'm sorry
Are you serious?
It's okay if you get hurt
It's dangerous
Kamada and Matsumoto are doing their lessons
They cleared the slope
It's okay
Let's turn
Turn to the right
Put your weight on your left foot
You will be able to turn
Can I do it?
You have to touch your shoes
What should I do?
You have to put your weight on your left foot
You can't turn
It felt good
You have to put your weight on your left foot
You can't turn
What is this?
Lesson 4
It's the last lesson
It's the last chance to prank Fujiwara
We didn't turn
That's impossible
Fujiwara
It's dangerous
Do it slowly
Is it okay if I do it slowly?
Yes
There are times when you suddenly speed up
How do you do it?
If I do it like that
I think it's okay as long as I'm doing it here
It's dangerous
Fujiwara is worried about the dangerousness of the lesson
Matsumoto starts to slide at the perfect timing
What's going on?
Matsumoto is losing balance
You're going in the wrong direction
Danger! Danger!
Are you okay?
Huh?
Ouch! Ouch!
It's hot! It's hot!
Huh?
It's hot!
Can you move your back a little?
Okay.
I can't move at that speed.
I think you got caught in the snow.
Huh?
I can't move at that speed.
I'm sorry.
It's hot! It's hot!
I can't move...
I think you should roll over.
Can you move your back a little?
I can't move at that speed.
Hey!
I'm sorry.
You should have told me earlier.
Yes.
Hey!
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Hey!
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Huh?
Yes.
Hey!
I'm sorry.
You should have told me earlier.
Yes.
Hey!
I'm sorry.
You should have told me earlier.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You should have told me earlier.
Huh?
Yes.
Alright, stop it.
Please stop.
I don't want to see it anymore.
It was a big success.
I wanted to see it.
I've been looking at it for a long time, and it was making a lot of noise.
When I saw it for the first time, I was wondering how it was going to be.
I don't know what kind of world he's in.