I think you should do it again.
From the top of your head?
You're so fluffy.
I can't do it. My legs are so stiff.
I'll do it again.
From the side.
I think it's better to do it again.
Thank you.
I don't know what you're talking about.
The first time, at the Gagi no Tsukai Arai,
Chikichiki Yamazaki Hoosei presents,
The world's first, no one knows the loss!
Please, raise your hand.
What is this?
No one knows the loss.
I don't need a laugh like this!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Let's explain in place of Yama-chan.
This time, it's a battle that will never end.
The winner will receive a luxury item, and the winner will be treated by a special guest.
Today, we have a wonderful guest who is celebrating his 30th anniversary.
Is there such a person?
Of course there is.
But why are we here?
That's because we are friends.
Friends?
We've been friends for 15 years.
This year is our 17th anniversary.
What are you talking about?
It's been 17 years.
You're slow.
I'm cold!
I'm going to the toilet!
If you have the guts, go and do it!
You're too much of a fricador, you're going to the toilet too.
If you have the guts, go and do it. If you don't, don't.
Why are you coming?
So, to celebrate the 30th anniversary of the entertainment industry,
we've come to see the beauty of the industry.
Wada Akihiko-san!
Nocchi-san!
I don't want to explain it normally.
I wonder what's going on behind me.
I'm going to kill you.
Thank you very much.
What is it?
Wada-san has celebrated his 30th anniversary!
30th anniversary!
Congratulations!
That's amazing!
It's been 30 years!
Wada Akiko is the super big star who is celebrating his 30th anniversary this year.
He has always been the top of the entertainment industry since his debut.
He is the super big star who has taken over the Kouhaku's bird.
Thank you!
Today is the farewell party.
Hey!
What's wrong?
It hurts!
It's a gorilla.
It's going to break.
We've been together for 30 years.
It's double.
I don't like it.
It's going up.
Who are you talking to?
Are you ready?
We're going to meet with Mr. Zantaro.
The winner will receive a luxurious prize!
The winner will receive a set of Omi beef from Asakusa Imai in the year of the ox.
The loser will receive a huge gift.
Akko-san's huge gift!
The gift for the loser is this!
A bow from the heart!
I don't want to do it.
Why?
It's a punishment game, right?
It's a punishment game!
This is...
Why are we here celebrating our 30th anniversary and getting punished?
No one is losing!
Why is it like this?
Onii-san, you know...
Onii-san, you're wrong!
It's not like that!
It's here!
It's not here, it's here!
Don't do that, you're so mean!
I saw the shape of the cake!
It's already our 30th anniversary!
It's night time!
I'm sorry.
I'm not going to do it anymore.
I'm not going to edit it.
There is no problem with this.
Akiko, please be more beautiful than you are now.
You know that?
I don't know what you mean.
I don't know what beauty is.
To polish it even more, we need to do a color change!
That's not happening!
Let's do it
Really?
It can't be helped
This is the color change
Then, color change
Wait for me
Let's go!
The first round is...
The winner is...
The fastest sneeze battle!
We'll make a small ring and the winner will sneeze first.
I see.
Let's start.
The fastest sneeze battle!
Ready...
Go!
If I don't sneeze, the gorilla will be waiting for me.
A beautiful baby is waiting for you
This is so sour
Don't follow me!
I'm a man!
I thought a gorilla was coming
Sorry, I can't do this
It's true.
It's not coming out.
It's not coming out at all.
There's no sign of it coming out.
Ah! It's coming out!
It's coming out!
You should have just put it in!
What are you holding this for?
It's amazing.
This game is a draw!
We won!
We have prepared the next game.
It's over?
It's over.
Which game?
Look at my bad body.
Let's go to the next game.
The next game is...
We are the third?
The battle of despair and hanging down!
The battle of despair and hanging down.
This is a physical game that the two are not good at.
The one who hangs down longer wins.
The battle of hanging despair!
Ready!
This is tough.
It's 35, you two.
Are you okay?
Huh?
It's still 20, 25 seconds!
It's 26 seconds!
Are you okay?
I'm serious.
Thank you very much.
Please be serious.
Old friend.
Wait, wait, wait!
I won!
I'll do it again.
What are you doing?
I won!
Wait, wait, wait!
Thank you!
It's cold!
Let's have him on the stage!
It's a little bit noisy
It's Akko-san!
Please come on out!
Akko-san!
It's a bondage!
Akko-san, listen!
Come on!
Then, Akko-san,
Please do the chest dance!
I want you! I want you!
How was it?
I don't remember my childhood
What a great girl
How to say it
The style is not bad
What is bad?
Nothing is bad
Let's go to the second round
The winner will receive a diamond watch as a gift.
And the winner is this!
A kiss mark on the wrist.
Can I wear this?
Of course.
You wear it for three days.
Have you ever worn it?
I have.
I'm looking forward to it.
This is the first time I've seen Akiko-san wearing a mask.
She's a top-notch entertainer.
Akiko-san, please come back.
My black-haired badminton match!
I'm confident about this.
You're lucky.
I'll explain the rules.
You'll do this, right?
Put the ball in the basket.
When the ball is in the basket, you'll start the baton.
OK. Rock, paper, scissors.
Ready, start!
I have to sing.
It's coming.
It's still okay.
This voice is cold.
Why is this?
The voice is coming out.
Do it again.
What the hell!
Let's do it again!
What kind of attitude is that?
I don't know.
What?
I don't think I can jump that high.
No, no, no.
I'm the one who's going to win.
Please listen to Yamazaki-san.
1-0.
Okay, then.
It was too early.
Too early.
I'm sorry.
I'll go first.
Hanada, you go first.
Let's go.
I can't lose.
It's still okay, it's still okay!
I touched it! I touched it! I touched it!
I touched it! I touched it!
I'm a fan of Aki!
No way!
You didn't even touch the net!
That's not right!
Hamada-san wins!
What?
Why?
No way!
The game is over.
Nyan, please come out.
Yes.
Please come out!
Akko-san, please come out!
I can't do this!
What are you doing?
This is a dream of a man!
The manly y-shirt!
Acco-san, thank you for making my dream come true!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
You're so hard-working!
You're pointing at me!
Don't use standard Japanese!
Come on!
I'll help you.
What is this? It's a celebration for the 20th anniversary, you idiot!
Even in the comic, you can't dress like this!
If you wear this kind of cap, it's been about 25 years!
You should try becoming one of our mini-bosses!
I'll be done soon, so come!
Don't do that!
Be quiet!
It's so funny!
I'm really listening to you! I'm really listening to you!
This is the best!
Hey!
Why are you going back so slowly?
Your face is blue!
I'm going home now.
You're going to the apartment?
You know, when I was being beaten up, I was really scared.
I was really scared.
I was sitting in the middle of the street, and I was completely covered in blood.
That was wonderful!
Let's go to the third round!
The winner will receive a diamond ring from the shining star of the Kinshichi TV.
And from Akiko!
Deep kiss!
If I get a deep kiss on my head, I'll have multiple personalities.
You'll have multiple personalities?
I'll have another personality.
Wait a minute. What about my will?
What's the point of celebrating 30 years?
I'm just doing it.
Look at the two of you. How cool are you?
It's wonderful.
Where is it?
You're one of the three most beautiful people in the world.
What's going on with my feelings?
What are you talking about?
Finally, Mr. Akutani, the color correction is amazing.
Everyone is so beautiful that they say,
What are you doing?
No, this is fine.
Why are you so cold?
I want you to do something good.
If I were a monkey, I would have run away from the fire.
I can't do it anymore.
It's okay. We'll do it again.
We'll do it again.
Do your best.
Thank you.
Deep kiss?
Deep kiss.
I'll chase after you.
I'll go after you.
Yama-chan's painting song!
In the third round, the two of them will draw a picture at the same time to match Yama-chan's painting song.
The winner will decide which one is better.
The third round goes to Yama-chan!
It's good, isn't it?
If you push the button, what will happen in a flash?
I don't understand anything!
Why can you laugh at this?
The answer is this!
King!
Haaaaaaa!
How do you write it? Can you repeat it?
The banana peel was falling down
Three beans were falling
It was locked up in a goldfish tank
And water was being born
I don't get it!
When you covered it with a pin
A pin?
Let's start with Matsumoto-san.
You write like this, right?
But this is a bit like a king, right?
No, it's not.
It's close to this, right?
Yes, if you say that, the face is close.
It's close? You said it's close.
I'll decide after looking at Hamazawa-san.
Hamazawa-san's face.
Please, come in!
This is...
What is this?!
Wait, wait, wait!
You're still cute!
I shouldn't have written this!
Get out of my way!
That's right, you shouldn't have written that.
Ah, this is bad!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Hamada-san, deep kiss!
I don't know! It's not changing!
Hamada-chan, kiss!
Akko's deep kiss is coming!
Akko-san's color change is over!
Akko-san, please!
Why?
I'm scared!
I'm laughing!
And finally, Seijin...
Again, you're wearing a wedding dress!
And finally...
Wait a minute.
You're holding a bow.
I'm so jealous.
Akiko-san!
Wait a minute.
This is...
What's wrong?
I have a stomachache.
You're a middle schooler.
You're in first grade?
This is the best!
This kind of thing, rather than women doing it, men should do it.
What is this?
Do you want to open it?
I'll close it.
It's a peach!
Why?
Don't say no!
Do it gently.
It's fine if you open it like this.
Ah, under the hammer?
You knocked him down with your knee.
Wait!
It can't be helped if you lose.
It can't be helped if I lose.
It's a
Let's get on this.
I see.
You lead.
So, Katariko.
I'm a real one.
It's the reality.
Reality.
It hurts, right?
It's the reality.
I really have to do it.
Can I just stay still?
Of course.
It's Deep Kiss.
I'm so happy!
Cut!
Don't laugh!
I don't usually do this!
You're making me dizzy.
Okay, then, deep kicks!
Welcome!
Oh!
I was serious!
I was surprised!
It's been a long time!
Can't we do this in a series?
Why?
What kind of series is this?
Please forgive me!
Please cut this out!
And then please go home!
Don't come near me!