第4回ガジの使いあらゆるネットで芸能陣お前そうちゃんかグランプリー
ああああああ
じゃあ
次々お前そうちゃんがグランプリもう回を重ねることで今日4回目ということですね
じゃあそれじゃ行きましょうさっそくゲストの皆さんですどうぞ
ああああああ
私はつまりはいたまたまたさああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああ
もういかにもというメンバーですよね
女の子出た人誰もいないんだってどうぞあたり初めて私だって友達つくられ声でしょ
俺に出る女はあなたしかいないんじゃなさそうかなぁ
早速入ろうやるの行くぞあの問題にもソラリゼーションかかってさーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっはーっ
You are interviewing with a match card, right?
Yes.
When you reach 5 people, that person will be the target.
Let's get started!
Here is the first question!
Here!
Don't look!
A sports player who used to be bullied.
Who is a sports player?
When I was a kid.
I was bullied by my friends.
I was told to go home early and cool down my hair.
I was told to do such a thing.
That's what I thought.
Please write it down!
I don't know.
I'll write it down.
The sound is playing.
Who is it?
It's dirty.
3, 2, 1, 3.
No, no, no.
Let's start with Mr. Otake.
Here is the song.
Yes, yes, yes.
He is a tricky person.
I was bullied in the past.
I know.
3.
I think this is possible.
4.
It's quite...
Write it down in kanji!
I think I was bullied when I was in elementary school.
Mr. Otake.
Yes.
It's funny.
This is what you think.
No, no, no.
3, 2, 1.
Kenji Inuma's wife.
That's...
It's funny.
Wait a minute.
That's...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
So how were you bullied?
That's right.
There is no such thing as bullying in this era.
Not really.
What is that?
I wasn't bullied in the past.
That's why...
Well...
If you were bullied in the past, it would be Ito Midori.
Kuwata.
Ito Midori.
The younger brother of the marathon.
Kiyowa.
Furuta.
Mr. Kuwata.
Mr. mug.
Motoki Daisuke.
Kuwata.
I'm kind of weak.
Ito Midori.
Nakashima Kazushige.
Kyojin Kazushige.
him auf Nagashima.
Ok, here I have the leader of Kattan-chan
Mr. Nagashima Kazushige!
Mr. Ito Midori is in third place.
And Kuwata.
He's not in third place at all.
And the Sō brothers.
Oh, really?
And the next question is...
This one!
The Owarashi talent that just happened to sell!
You just happened to sell, didn't you!
You're really funny!
There's no answer like this, is there?
No, no, that's not it.
I'll give you 5,000 yen later.
Don't give me that kind of money!
But I don't know if it's selling.
You don't know if it's selling, do you?
There's a lot of people who don't know if it's selling or not.
Hey!
Where are you looking at?
I don't know!
Let me participate! Let me participate!
Let's draw it. Here you go.
Did you go to elementary school properly?
It's dirty, isn't it?
What you're drawing is dirty.
Oh, that's it.
I think so, too.
I love you.
It's the last one!
What?
Hurry up with that! Hurry up with that!
Let's start with Otagai.
Moriaki-kun!
Hey! Everyone's doing it with Hama!
Hama-chan said,
I'm on the same side as you!
Don't cut it!
Let's go with Isamu-san.
One, two, three!
Yamada-kun, I'm sorry!
Yamada-kun!
But I don't think so.
Well, let's say it's possible.
Let's say it's possible.
Let's go with Mano-san.
No, no, no!
Wait a minute!
Wait!
No, no, no!
What?
Let's play!
Downtown?
That's a lot.
Roo-Oshiwa.
Dachau Club.
Matsumura.
Jimmy Onishi?
Uchano-chan.
He looks like an amateur.
He's not that cool.
Dachau Club.
Matsumura.
Roo-Oshiwa.
Uchano-chan.
He looks like an amateur.
Jimmy Onishi?
Paul McKee.
Uchano-chan.
Dachau Club.
I don't think he's boring.
Uchano-chan.
Tunnel.
Dachau Club.
Uchano-chan.
The winner is Uchano-chan!
What?
What are you doing?
I don't know what you're doing.
The next question is...
This one!
Tama-kun!
Why are you in the train?
Why do you look like that?
Dekkan-chan!
Why do you have a bag up to here?
That's it.
I can't believe it.
Next question, please!
Sayu-san.
It's a man, isn't it?
It's a man.
Of course, it's a woman.
It's a woman, isn't it?
Otake-san.
The answer is...
The exit.
You guys are amazing.
Please show us another one.
Another one?
Another one is here.
That's why I can't appear in dramas anymore.
Next, Anno-san.
This one.
Karasawa, right?
Yes, Karasawa.
It's that one, isn't it?
The one who appears in a tea commercial.
The one who dances.
Next, Sano-san.
Yes.
It's Akiyuki-san.
The one who has a horn here.
I saw him when I was watching a drama.
Taishu Kase.
Mokkun?
No, Karasawa.
Taishu Kase.
He has a good figure.
Taishu Kase?
He's strong.
Taishu Kase.
The one with a big nose.
The one with a big mouth.
Shunichi Ishida.
Yoshida Yusaku.
Oda Yuji?
Shunichi Ishida?
It's Yoshida Yusaku.
I think he's really big.
Kazama Thor?
Azuma Miki?
Shunichi Ishida.
It's Yoshida Yusaku.
The one who looks strong.
Shunichi Ishida?
It's Yoshida Yusaku.
It has to be Yoshida Yusaku.
The one with a big nose.
Yoshida Yusaku-san.
Yoshida Yusaku, Shunichi Ishida, Taishu Kase, Azuma Miki-san.
The one with a big nose.
Is it in?
Don't look at me like that.
The last question is...
A foreign talent who looks like he has corn in his poop.
Your grandma is a dirty grandma!
You can't get corn in your poop!
Call the person who came up with this.
Write down the answer with your right hand.
Here you go.
I'm sure you'll get it.
I think you'll get it.
It's a foreign talent.
One, two, three, four...
Who wrote the foreign talent?
Write it down!
Let's start with Mr. Otake.
Don!
This is Kento.
He's got corn in his poop.
I'll leave it to you.
Isamu-san, I'm sure you'll get this one.
Yes.
Three.
I'm sure you'll get this one.
I'm sure I'll get this one, too.
Masao-san.
I have a feeling you'll get this one.
I don't think I'll get it.
But...
I have a feeling you'll get this one.
Kento.
Delicato.
Yes.
I think I'll get Chuck.
Schwarzenegger.
Dave Spector.
The hair is like this.
Kento.
Delicato.
Sankon-san.
Michael Douglas.
Dave Spector.
It's like this.
Sankon-san.
Hibinkotsuna.
I think I'll get corn.
Tom Cruise.
Ben Johnson.
I think I'll get anything.
Hibinkotsuna.
Akebono.
Schwarzenegger.
I don't think I'll get it.
Kento.
Delicato.
Sankon-san.
The winner is Sankon-san.
I got this one for the first time.
I got it.
Yes.
Sankon-san.
The winner is Sankon-san.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Let's start.
The winner is Sankon-san.
Sankon-san.
The audience treats you like Furuyo-chan.
Really?
Yes.
The only person who laughs at me is Furuyo-chan.
I've been doing this program all the time.
The broadcasting time.
I'm finally going back to normal from this week.
Really?
I'm glad to hear that.
There were so many special programs in the morning.
Really?
There were so many.
What?
I was caught by Mutsugoro.
Mutsugoro is good.
Why?
I've told you many times.
Don't be fooled by that old man.
I told you to wake up.
I've been doing it over and over again.
I don't think there's anything wrong with Mutsugoro.
You're so angry.
I'm not a fan of Mutsugoro.
You're a fan of animals.
That's right.
I'm not a fan of Mutsugoro.
I don't think there's anything wrong with Mutsugoro.
Mutsugoro is walking around Shinjuku.
Mutsugoro.
There's no one who says,
Mutsugoro, come here and give me a hand.
There's someone like that.
I don't think there's anyone like that.
If that's the case,
Mutsugoro is better.
Mutsugoro.
I don't know.
The world of TV.
I don't think it's good.
Touch it.
It's a round shape today.
You can wear a suit like usual.
I don't care if you stick your hand in your pocket.
You're here.
Tell me.
I don't think it's good.
I'm going home.
That's right.
Don't wash yourself.
If you do it, wash it.
That's right.
That's enough.
I won't wash it.
I can't even blow it.
I'm scared of women.
If you think you're blowing it,
It's got tissue on it.
What are you pulling?
I don't know.
I can't help pulling it.
Tommy is getting worse these days.
That's not true.
It's normal in our conversation.
I don't talk like that.
That's right.
You really don't do it.
The girl on the staff.
From behind.
Momono.
You really don't do it.
Why?
You said that, too.
There's a man on the show that I've been working with since I was a kid.
She's also a human being in this world.
But if you do this,
I don't know if she's going to go out with him.
In front of this man,
I can't stand it.
If it's this man,
Hama-chan is mine.
He's my father.
Even if it's a boy or a girl,
He's not my father.
But he's definitely my boyfriend.
To be honest,
I've done it a few times, too.
You're lying.
It's true.
To be honest,
I've done it a few times, too.
Hama-chan, stop it.
You're the only one who can do it.
Inawara, come over here.
Come on, come on, come on.
Do something.
You're so good at it.
What?
It's the first time you've followed me.
Of course.
I didn't know that.
You have to be careful.
I'll be careful.
You should stop asking questions about other women.
I got it.
I haven't done it lately.
I don't think you can see anything.
What do you mean?
You're in the middle of something.
Why?
This is a serious story.
Sometimes I'm in the middle of something.
I'm smoking a cigarette.
I hear a woman's voice.
I'm in the middle of something.
There's an Clay Symbol.
I'll appear on TV.
Everyoneайs laughing.
It's funny.
For example, when you see someone and say,
Stop it.
Don't do it!
About Heikin
In the last week's broadcast, Hama-chan talked about Macchan 15 times.
Only the broadcasted part is 15 times.
If you put in the part that is not broadcasted, I think it will be more.
Good luck, Macchan!
Is that so?
No, that's a great number.
If you think about it until now.
So it's 15 times only last week.
If you put in the part that is not broadcasted, I think it will be about 30 times.
How many times have you done 30 times in this program?
It's 174 times!
30 times 174.
Even if you do it lightly.
It's a great number.
What are you talking about?
I understand.
But I can say this like a joke.
If you are hit this much, after all, when it is about 70 or 80, the side effect will definitely come out.
I'm not talking about side effects.
I'm talking about side effects.
Did you drink something?
Something will come out.
It's like a boxer.
That's right.
What should I do?
Last week.
The other day.
My friend.
That's right.
The costume is already like this.
I'm sorry.
Last week.
The other day.
I don't like it.
Don't do it!
You.
Don't come right away.
The other day, my friend called me and asked me if I could get someone from Yoshimoto to come to the university festival.
Koji Imada and someone told me that it was 600,000 yen.
I thought Koji Imada was more expensive.
This picture means that.
A picture that is expensive?
That's cheap.
It's 600,000 yen.
And I'm not alone yet.
Even if you read Hote Toro, it costs 50,000 yen.
The content of the job is different.
Do you go to the university festival?
Sometimes.
I don't go to the university festival at all.
I don't think the company will accept it.
I went to the university festival last year, too.
How many times did you go to the university festival?
That's what we say.
I'll tell you the price here.
I called Yoshimoto and told him that I saw a child's teacher.
How many times did you go to the university festival?
Why are you telling me?
You tell me yourself.
I'll tell you the price.
I don't go to the university festival in Japan.
2,000,000 yen?
Yes.
Do you call a person with 2,000,000 yen?
I'm wearing this again.
What is it?
Atsuko Asano was doing a live-action version of Mr. Sadai.
What kind of live-action version do you want to see?
There was a long time ago.
The Queen of Tomorrow.
Who is playing the Queen of Tomorrow?
Is it Shoji Ishibashi?
In a live-action version.
Superman.
If a Japanese person plays Superman, it's Shinichi Chiba, isn't it?
Is that so?
I don't think there's anyone else.
I think it would be better to have someone who's more aggressive.
Who is it?
Konytan?
Konytan is good.
Who did Senzai Bakabon?
My Yamada Arako.
Bakabon.
You can do Bakabon.
Hajime Ingen Gyatob.
Hajime Kurano.
Doteijin is Kuruma Sankichi.
That's right.
I'm addicted to it.
I'm thinking about it.
There's nothing I can do.
Is that so?
Yes.
Then I'll win.
You can make a monster.