Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
I haven't heard anything today, so I don't know what to do.
What should I do?
Today is the downtown special.
It's our 10th anniversary this year.
That's right.
It's our 10th anniversary.
You haven't done anything to us for the past 10 years.
We've been suffering because of you.
You don't know how painful it is, do you?
When Hamada stole gasoline.
When your job went wrong.
When someone lent you money.
When Hamada ran away with a woman in Tokyo.
It's been 10 years.
Today, we have a guest.
For example, we'd like you to write a theme song for us.
For example, we'd like you to write a symbol for us.
For downtown, we'd like you to write a symbol for us.
Do you have something like that?
Bring it on.
You're in a good mood, aren't you?
If you say so, I'm in a good mood.
We'd like you to make such a song.
Let's have you as a special guest.
You ate curry, didn't you?
I don't know what you ate.
I know you ate curry.
This program is brought to you directly from Japan.
Let's start with our theme song.
This guest is a representative Japanese artist born in Kansai.
That's right.
This is the person who will make our theme song.
Thank you very much.
It's been a long time.
Something's changed, hasn't it?
I didn't know it at first.
We've skipped some songs, haven't we?
Yang Jin's song.
Yukie Yukie Kawaguchi.
What else?
There are many more.
The next song is Aho ga miru buta no ke.
Aho ga miru?
The next song is Aho ga miru?
I don't think you know this.
Aishu no kuro chikubi.
You don't know this, do you?
We didn't sell this at all.
We made a new song.
Oh, Aishu no Kuroshikubi.
After that, Yukai na Mokkori.
This one didn't sell at all.
Oh, the one that's a bit like Shimo.
The one that's a bit like Shimo.
This time, Tanba de Lumba.
Oh, that's the one.
I know that one.
After that, Shoshimi.
Oh, I know that one.
Oh, with Omura-san.
This summer, I've been changing my own cymbals.
What song was that again?
It's called Yatte Misou.
It's still the same.
The title of your song is still the same.
Yukkei-Ikkei Kawabuchi Hiroji.
Yukkei, Yukkei, it's still the same!
I see.
We're done.
That was a problem.
How many songs have we made?
You mean songs?
If you include this song, it won't be enough for 2,000 yen or 3,000 yen.
It will end in about 2 seconds.
There are a lot of fast songs, right?
There are a lot of fast songs.
It will end in a little while, right?
That's right.
That's why...
Fast?
That's right.
We want to hear that.
A theme song.
And then...
We talked about it a long time ago.
I sent you a lot of materials.
I asked you what kind of song you wanted to sing.
When I saw the materials you sent me,
I saw that all of them were written by Matsumoto.
It seems that you are crazy.
Especially Matsumoto.
This guy is crazy.
Idiot.
I'm not crazy.
Stop it.
Wait a minute.
Stop talking like that even when you're older.
To be honest,
I don't know why I'm not crazy.
You idiot.
You don't know why you're not crazy?
Well, that's true.
I'm not crazy.
Shall we go?
Well...
Let's see how you went until you got there.
It's downtown, so I'll start with a fast song.
It's hard to write down.
I'm not good at singing fast songs.
I have a song called Downtown by Eppo.
You have?
It's called Downtown.
It's cool.
Hey!
I thought it was a bit straight.
We used to sing that song in front of people.
Is that right?
Yes.
I thought about it a lot.
It took a long time to make this song.
You said you wanted to make it earlier.
If you really like this song,
and you want me to use it,
what will happen to the money?
How much do you charge?
What?
For example, if you write one or two songs.
I'll get paid for that.
It depends on how much it sells.
Oh, I see.
I sometimes get asked to write a song for someone.
I don't write that much,
but I still make Kitaro's albums.
If you ask me to write a song, I'll do it.
That's a lot.
The theme of Kitaro is Yoshi Ikuzo.
That's right.
So, what am I supposed to do?
Please give me a moment.
But I don't have a angle to do that.
Kitaro and a moment.
There are many.
The theme of Sunakage Baba.
I request songs by Hekome Musume.
They're my albums.
I'll give you a moment.
I can make a song for a moment,
but I don't know much about it.
You want to know the data of a moment.
If you ask me to send you the data,
I want to send you Yokai Daihyakka.
If you look at that,
One feature of Momen is it is soft,
the other is soft,
so When you're bad, even if you break into the water
it will return, there's only 3 features
I have to work on 2 choirs with only 3
1 train version...
1 more Doctor Momen
But it's good, isn't it?
It's like a water-splash.
You're a fool!
I can't get used to it.
It's fun, isn't it?
Have we made it yet?
The part we've known for a long time,
the old downtown and the present downtown,
we'll divide it into two parts.
The first one is the old downtown in Osaka.
It's a mess now, but there was a hard time,
including the past.
The second one is the present.
It's like a girl who was born in Osaka.
It's a song of a girl who was born in Osaka.
What?
The title is the downtown born in Yoshimoto.
I see.
Can you tell us?
Shall we listen to it?
That's right, but I'd like to hear the other songs of Kamo.
That's right.
I'll leave it for later.
Is it okay to sing it at the end?
Shall we sing?
It's a song of a recent place.
Thank you.
The old downtown is a mess now.
You're too fast!
I'm an old man who can't move anymore.
It's snowing.
Are you ready?
I'm getting wet in the rain.
I'm changing my clothes.
There's konjac coming out of my nose.
I can't leave you, I can't let you go.
You gave it to me.
Kirinji, Saka, Hokuhoku, Tenyu.
I loved you, but I didn't know Hanako was there.
Four, six, twenty, four, four, seven, twenty-eight.
Four is thirty-two, four is thirty-six.
Namihei got on the boat and made Sazae.
There's a lot of things.
It's delicious.
The last one is the best.
Let's play downtown.
Let's play downtown, which was born in Yoshimoto.
I'm tired of talking.
Our laughter is not like this.
I thought I lost while looking at the popularity of Tomizu.
I'm crying.
Downtown Yasakai was born in Yoshimoto.
I can't go to the theater on the 20th.
I can't sleep.
When the second half of the show was a boom, the company's attitude changed.
Number two.
The second half of the show was a peak.
The company told me to go to Tokyo.
Keishu, who shatters in front of my eyes, fell in a flash.
It's well done.
I can't believe I thought of it at school.
It's wonderful.
Everyone, Keishu and Tomizu came out.
I'm a little bit of a maniac.
I don't think I'm a maniac.
Keishu did his best in Tokyo.
It was faster to go to Tokyo than Downtown.
Yoshimoto is also strong.
All Night Nippon suddenly became popular.
It's not funny at all.
Keishu disappeared from Tokyo.
It disappeared in Osaka.
Let's think about our catchphrase.
We have another guest.
Let's call him.
This person.
Mr. Asakuraku Shino.
Nice to meet you.
It's like a killer's shoe.
It's okay.
When my staff went to ask for it,
I thought it would be rejected.
Did you throw it away?
That's not good.
It's okay.
What do you say?
It's easy to do.
Is that so?
I didn't know until this afternoon.
What are you talking about?
But I'm glad you came.
Do you know the program called I don't know?
What is it?
I haven't told you yet.
Do you know it?
I read it in the article.
What is the pattern this time?
How did you twist it this time?
This time...
From home to here.
What is that?
But that's amazing.
Excuse me.
Did you wear underwear?
It stinks.
Idiot.
From behind.
I didn't do it.
How many did you think today?
I'm a little embarrassed.
Really?
Three.
Let's use the best one.
I don't know if it's good.
What is the first one?
The first one is delicate like a demon and bold like an angel.
I see.
The devil is bold and the angel is...
What is it?
It's different.
It's a technique to show the opposite.
I'm really sorry, but don't you think it's wrong?
I'm not good at writing.
Isn't it wrong?
Isn't it weird to write bold?
I've been checking it.
I'm sorry if I made a mistake.
No, you're wrong.
I'm sorry.
Do you mind if I hit you?
The next one is...
The more I think about it, the more I feel at ease.
I think the first one is better.
Even if you make a mistake?
Even if I make a mistake.
That's fine.
There's one more.
It's...
Anti-trendy, anti-degadance, not light, not heavy, a little sweet and bitter downtown.
Which one is a little sweet?
That's...
Even if you ask me...
Both of you are handsome, so sweet? Mask?
Is it wrong?
No, no.
It's bitter.
You bite little by little.
No, no, no.
It's bitter.
It's not a catch copy.
What are you going to do if you get angry?
I see.
These three.
I think the first one is the best.
Really?
Yes.
When do you use this?
Catch copy.
What?
When do you use the catch copy?
When it came out.
In the past, Mr. Katsura said, Margaret on the window, Mr. Katsura.
It's not like that at all.
He said that.
Right?
Yes.
Mr. Katsura said that.
When it came out, he said that.
The first one.
Margaret on the window and Mr. Katsura.
I can say it quickly, but that's long.
I can't say the third one.
I can't say it.
Excuse me.
They came out together.
Anti-trendy, anti-degadance.
It's not light, it's not heavy.
It's a little sweet and bitter.
When it comes out with this guy, it's complicated.
Why is it complicated?
There's something like this.
The devil is talking about this guy.
Why?
That's true.
My face is serious, isn't it?
It's true.
The devil is talking about you.
The angel is talking about me.
You can say that yourself.
That's right.
What is this?
It's okay.
I like this one better.
It's more comfortable than I thought.
I got three of these, but I don't like any of them.
When I thought about this, I couldn't stand it anymore.
I like this one as a word.
I like this one better.
If I put this in my mouth, I can talk with it.
Then, this one.
I'll release a CD next time, so I'll go get it.
It's too late.
It's already in my mouth.
You don't know it until you get it.
Shina-san, put this in your mouth. Let's do it with three people.
I'm pushing this one.
Shina-san, you push this one.
Let's do rock-paper-scissors with three people.
Let's decide who wins.
Rock-paper-scissors.
I won.
Thank you.
How much is this?
What is this?
This is the price.
You can't use this without permission, can you?
Please use it without permission.
I don't like this.
Is it okay?
Please.
I don't feel good.
How much do you want?
Ask me after a while.
I don't know how much you want.
You are making Osaka people your enemies.
How much do you want?
Next.
Yes.
Our Mars.
I wonder if we can do it.
This is what I'm talking about.
We're going to make something on the show.
We made a G-jan before.
There was a staff.
There might be a T-shirt in the summer.
At that time.
We're going to put it in.
We're going to make it for that.
Let's introduce that person.
It's Kazuhiko Hideto.
Hello.
This is Macaro.
You've changed a lot.
Once in Nagoya.
We were doing a talk show in Nagoya.
You came once at that time.
Yes.
I think I was more stupid than I was then.
That was about three or four years ago.
That's right.
In Nagoya.
The head of the commercial is worse.
The head of the commercial is more dreadful around here.
I don't know if it's dreadful now.
It's been about three or four years since then.
At that time, on our show.
This person is amazing.
He has power.
I asked him to put a mark on it.
It's like a chainsaw.
I cut the set.
I asked him at the end.
What do you want to do in the future?
What did you say?
I want to hurt the earth.
That's a cool word.
I want to hurt it.
How about that?
I've done it a little bit in Sendai.
It's like this.
It's like this as a scar.
What's going on these days?
It seems to be on TV.
That's right.
You don't hate it, do you?
I don't hate it.
I don't like that I can't fight without a picture, a brush, and a paper.
I see.
Even if I don't have anything, I want to do something.
What do you think of yourself?
When you go out, do you think you're the type to be pulled by a brush?
Or do you think you're the type to be pulled by a chair?
I don't think so.
It's a little bit more than this head.
If it was a long time ago, I think it would be funny.
What's this head?
It's like this.
You think I'm stupid, don't you?
I don't care because you're doing it.
I don't think I'm stupid, but I think I'm stupid.
Your head is tough.
Do you sell this kind of clothes?
I don't sell it.
What did you do?
I don't have a single piece made.
Do you say that yourself?
There are people who always make clothes like this.
You can't wear this kind of clothes, can you?
I don't have any left.
Everyone is scared.
If you have this kind of head, you have to have this kind of past.
You can't get a relationship.
I just happened to have a head that I thought would be valuable.
What are you talking about?
It was pretty hard.
I was easily attracted to it.
Was it hard?
I often do trademarks at work.
What kind of things have you done so far?
There are many stores.
If you go to a store with a logo, it looks like this.
It looks like a store.
But this doesn't look like downtown.
What doesn't look like downtown?
This doesn't look like a normal restaurant.
This doesn't look like that.
There are various variations.
For example, this kind of thing.
That's great.
You are amazing, Mr. Hibino.
This is like this.
Who is writing a stone?
For example, there is a person who is down.
This is downtown.
This is a building.
This is a person who is down.
This is good for a T-shirt.
This too.
This is a back print.
This is really good.
If there is such a game,
For example, it is good to mark the characters of two people.
I think it would be nice if I could omit it.
I write a lot.
I write Machan and Hamachan.
This is Hamada.
I write a lot and then I use a pen.
I think it looks like this.
It's a little thicker than I thought.
Then the expression comes out.
I took it out of here and expanded it.
This is cool.
I understand this.
What does this mean that the back is brown?
The image we have is brown.
I made it brown because I liked it.
This is good.
But this is also good.
This is very difficult.
If you want to make it look like a wakuten,
You can use this in some form.
I will use this as it is.
Why?
Can I use all of this?
You can.
But I have to pay for it.
If I use this and this at the same price,
I'm a little angry.
This is Hibino.
But if you use it,
It takes some time.
That's right.
Isn't it 300,000 yen?
It's a little cheap.
Let's use three.
I don't know if it's similar.
Of course.
I don't say much about money on TV.
I don't say much.
Do you listen to it?
Then we will create our own song.
This person.
He made this song.
Today's guest.
Next guest.
Please welcome.
Mr.Ozaki Ami.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
I can't bow to you.
It's all right.
Don't be surprised.
I'm not hitting anyone.
I'm a little scared.
Odaki, do you know us well?
Of course.
When I asked you to make a song,
did you listen to it?
Of course.
I like it.
Really.
I was surprised.
You are a real hit maker.
I think so.
You wrote a song for someone else.
There are many songs.
The one I remember the most is that.
My feelings.
That's a song you wrote yourself.
I'm walking.
About 13 years ago.
How old were you then?
About 13 years ago?
When I was a child.
You were always listening to songs?
When I was fourteen.
It doesn't matter.
I did it myself.
What?
Why?
For instances like that.
For instance like that.
Seeking for Bolivia.
a girl when plays in Karaoke.
You can sing.
Matsudaira Ken-san also wrote a song today.
Is there a commercial song?
Yes, there is a commercial song.
I just sang a commercial song.
Kobayashi Asami-san was running.
Is that so?
It was a song called My Fair Lady.
Kobayashi Asami-san?
Kobayashi Akira's song.
I'm really going to use this.
Really?
Will it be used?
Well, I'll tell you later.
I don't know until I hear it.
Hey!
Well, even if you say that, it's a miss.
It's the second image.
Really?
Yes.
Hey!
Ozaki!
How long did it take to make it?
The time to make it?
This came out almost immediately.
You're not putting in any effort.
I have an image of downtown.
I'm from Kansai.
I'm from Kyoto.
In Kansai,
there's always a strange boy.
Isn't there?
No, there is.
I'm being teased.
But it's so much fun.
It's really interesting.
I wonder if this person is okay with Jiro.
It's like that.
Also,
the sound of the fire crackling.
the sound of everyone shouting
in front of the club room.
Also, the smell of the shoe box.
When I say smell, it's smelly.
It's like that.
I see.
I thought that I had to
make it dirty.
Was it too clean?
No, it's not like that.
It's not supposed to be sunny.
It's like that.
When I was getting wet,
I didn't walk seriously.
My back was itchy.
I heard that.
I see.
It's okay.
What's your original character?
It's cold.
I have something heavy.
It's just like that.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Ozaki-san,
before you sing that song,
can you sing
while listening to Olivia?
I want to hear
your original song.
Do you remember the lyrics?
I don't remember.
Even if I step on
the pedal,
I can't step on it.
Who are you?
Wait!
What are you doing?
The pianist
who brought the piano.
I don't know him at all.
Can I start?
Let's start.
Ozaki!
I'm sorry.
One more time, please.
My favorite song
I'll listen to it alone.
Olivia is a lonely heart
Because she comforts me
Jasmine tea is a drug that makes me sleep
I want to spend a day like me
On a night like this
When we met
I didn't think this day would come
We said
Making up despair
No, we just spent time
Exhausted
You, my illusion, I loved you
Walking in the rain
As time goes by
The smell of rain from the shoulders
The smell of after school from the back
The sound of closing the door on the sixth floor
The sound of laughing and whistling
Where are you going while getting wet?
The honest back is melting
Walking in the rain
As time goes by
Talking in the rain
Walking in the rain
As time goes by