High Tension is the Best!
Good evening!
It's been a while!
It's been about a year and a half.
Yes, that's right.
Yesterday, I was with Miyasako-san and Endo-san.
But your tension was low.
Why is my tension low when I'm doing this?
That's why I brought you here on the same day.
Let's announce the rankings!
Yes!
First, the 10th place this week is...
112 points!
Gekirin 8122!
Kogoriko Tanaka Naoki!
Congratulations!
Tanaka-san always comes in 10th place.
He's always in the top 10.
Don't you think your tension will go up?
That's right!
If it's fun here, you'll say,
I don't care about this!
That's right! I want to do it here!
What are you talking about?
Then, please stand by.
Then, the 10th place this week,
Kogoriko Tanaka Naoki,
Gekirin 82002!
Kogoriko Tanaka Naoki
Idiot!
Thank you very much!
Let's move on.
The 9th place this week is...
135 points!
Musical Cats!
The 9th place this week is...
Congratulations!
Arun-san, are you in the 9th place?
Yes, I am.
What's your best so far?
I think I'm in the top 9.
9th is the easiest to do.
I see.
I can't say that the atmosphere is good right now.
That's right.
I didn't want to come out.
I heard that this time is scary.
I'm scared.
It's like a small tool peeking from the back is scary.
That's right.
We've been found out.
Then, please stand by.
Thank you very much!
I wonder what it's going to be like.
I'm nervous.
Let's go.
Then, the 9th place this week is...
Osarude Musical Cats!
Musical Cats!
I'm small!
I'm dead!
Let someone come back to life!
Doctor!
Nappa-chan!
Change the sand!
When you're done,
Please open the gap!
Please give me a daughter!
Thank you very much!
I always think about this.
The people who finished are sitting next to each other.
They never leave.
The 8th place this week is...
158.X Showtime!
Jogans Mimata Tadahisa!
Please come over here!
Thank you very much!
It's Mimata-san!
Yes!
Mimata-san!
There's a phone call from someone.
Please take a look.
Who is it?
Hello?
It's Chao-san.
Who is it?
I'm sorry.
She's my girlfriend. We've been dating for 8 years.
What is it?
What's her name?
Her name is Hisako.
Hisako-san!
Nice to meet you.
It's always a pleasure to meet you.
Have you ever had a fight?
A fight is...
When I'm stressed out,
I want to complain.
I want to complain, but...
Yes, yes, yes.
I want to show my manliness.
I want to push him down.
I want to take off his underwear.
I want to hold him down.
I want to stretch his stomach.
I want to push him down his mouth and nose.
And then...
I want to say,
It has nothing to do with me.
What are you talking about?
Hey, this is a TV show.
Standby, please.
This week's 8th episode of Jodan's
It's Showtime!
Cha-san!
I want to get a job this year!
Ladies and gentlemen,
It's...
Showtime!
One, two, three, four.
Right hand, showtime.
Left hand, showtime.
Yes.
Yes, Tsutajo Imaichi, showtime.
Pan, pan, pan.
I want to make you laugh.
I don't want to be laughed at.
There was an era like this, too.
Showtime!
Thank you very much.
Next, the 7th episode of this week is...
The winner is...
189 points!
The winner is Ueshiba Ryuei!
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
Ueshiba-san.
You made a great impact today.
Thank you very much.
I can't look at you directly.
I'm shaking and my heart is pounding.
Well, then...
Are you ready for standby?
Yes, please.
I understand.
Well, it's wonderful.
Oh, standby is ready.
This week's guest is...
Ueshiba Ryuei from Gacha Club!
Ueshiba!
I fell in love at first sight.
I'm cute.
Ebisu-kun!
Let's go!
Ebisu-kun concert!
Music start!
Encore!
Thank you very much!
That's all!
That was Ebisu-kun.
You are the best.
Thank you very much.
There wasn't much inside.
This week's 6th place is...
271 points Aito Seishun no Megafight!
Amewarikess vs. Miyasako Hiroyuki!
Yeah!
Well, I have a bad sense of humor.
It's been a while.
I think I smell a bit of alcohol.
It's okay.
It's okay?
It's because you drank a lot in the morning.
That's why you're so excited.
It's from yesterday.
It's okay.
I don't drink alcohol at all.
Really? Does it smell?
It's a bit...
Why do you want to drink?
You drink, don't you?
I've been drinking since debut.
I'll do my best!
Yes!
Thank you very much!
This week's 6th place is...
Amewarikess vs. Miyasako Hiroyuki!
Aito Seishun no Megafight!
It's cold!
I got something on me.
I can't take it off.
Let's go!
Glasses, go!
Glasses, elbow!
Glasses!
Eat sushi!
It's cold!
Thank you very much!
Why are you between Osaru and Tanaka?
This week's 5th place is...
290 points!
Who is it?
2002 version!
Fukawa Ryo!
Congratulations!
Fukawa-san!
Fukawa-san, 5th place?
Yes, thank you very much.
I think I can do well this time.
Thank you very much.
Let's go!
This week's 5th place is...
Fukawa Ryo!
Who is it?
2002 version!
I can't take it off.
What should I do?
What should I do with this?
I'll do it for Fukawa.
I lifted it.
It's still there.
Dad!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
This way!
Are you going home?
My bicycle fell down.
I lifted it with an ad-lib.
I don't want to get hurt.
It's like this.
I feel like I can't see the floor.
Next week's 4th place is...
364 points!
Don't be fooled!
Kokoriko!
Endo Shouzo!
Congratulations!
I think Endo-san's appearance is a little fast.
There are a lot of people today, right?
This time, I'll do it in an electric way.
You're doing it yourself.
I was surprised the other day.
There's a volleyball team called Yakult Salos.
There's a player called Laviles.
I saw it.
He was doing it.
He was doing it after the home run.
Did you go that far?
He was doing it.
I thought I'd do something new.
I see.
Let's do our best.
Thank you very much.
It's amazing from the beginning.
Next week's 4th place is...
Kokoriko! Endo Shouzo!
Don't be fooled!
What is it?
I'll say it to the teenagers these days.
I'll say it to the 20s these days.
Thank you very much.
The staff members who clean up the set are beautiful.
Did you think too much?
I was looking down.
I gave up the game.
Next week's spotlights!
This week's spotlights are...
Kendo Kobayashi!
He brought a treasure that Kendo cherishes.
What is it?
When I was on a school trip,
I almost fell down with a bus guide.
I see.
But he's an adult.
I thought it was me,
so I gave up and took good care of it.
Do you still have it?
What is it?
It's a marimo.
I'm nervous and my hands are shaking.
Why are you all so nervous?
It's okay.
Number three, please.
It's wonderful.
Number 36 this week.
Kendo Kobayashi's Hedatari.
Let's get started.
Are you going to sit down?
Get your head off me.
You know that, right?
Feel it.
I don't want to do this.
Feel it!
Love will not exist between us humans and chairs!
Thank you very much!
It's wonderful.
People who haven't taken a video are frustrated.
I guess so.
They can't send it quickly.
Number 36 this week.
456 points.
How to walk on Earth.
I want to get rid of the rain.
You're stuck in the panel.
That's right.
There is a photo-chan kitchen in Oike.
What are you doing here?
I'm the manager.
Really?
To put it simply, it's dirty.
Number 3, please.
Number 3 this week.
How to walk on Earth.
I want to get rid of the rain.
Thank you very much!
You're stuck in the panel.
Number 2 this week.
485 points.
How to get rid of the rain.
I want to get rid of the rain.
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Here I go!
This is the 6th episode, right?
That's right.
This is the first time I've been invited.
Did you want to come?
Of course.
This is the first time I've been invited.
If you look closely, you can smell the smell of my big forehead.
I was surprised by this.
Mr. Egashira doesn't care about the information.
Everyone is in low spirits.
This is no good.
Let's do it!
Number 2 this week.
485 points.
How to get rid of the rain.
I want to get rid of the rain.
This is the end.
Thank you very much!
I'm not in a good mood.
He's very excited.
This is the first place.
If I say a little more, I'll be disappointed.
I think it's the first place.
There's someone above Mr. Egashira Tadai.
There's someone above him.
Who is it?
Let's find out.
Number 1.
537 points.
Yamachan Yamasaki.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
You're number one.
I didn't think I'd be number one.
537 points.
Thank you very much.
When was your child born?
I was born on April 8th.
Which one?
A girl.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
What's your name?
Momo.
It's Momo.
Momo-chan.
What's your name?
It's written as Hyaku.
It's written as Momo.
It's read as Momo.
Let's go.
Stand by, please.
Yes.
Let's go.
This week's number one, Yamasaki Hosei.
The Beyblade King, Yamachan.
La la la la la la la la la la.
His face has nothing to do with it.
I'm really good at the Beyblade.
I'm going to have a match with Balix.
It's Balix.
I won't lose.
I won't lose to the Beyblade.
I'm waiting.
I won.
Oh.
This is terrible.
Finally, let's take a group photo.
Everyone, face the camera.
Ready, go.
Pose.
Yamaguchi-san, you look sleepy.