Good evening.
Today, we are going to do something.
Yamazaki-kun wants to change his style.
Yamazaki wants to do a gag.
He thought of 50 times.
He thought of 100 times, but he cut it down to 50.
It's going to be so much fun.
Let's call him the gag angel who came down to the stage.
That's cool.
Let's go to the venue.
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching.
That's amazing.
It's so much fun.
Yamazaki-kun, gag 50 times in a row.
1.
2.
3.
White dog, Shiro-chan.
Shiro-chan, come here.
You've been dirty lately.
From now on, you are not allowed.
4.
Ero soldier.
Next time you go to the third base.
Brother.
5.
Seiko Hashimoto.
6.
Gag.
Today, we are going to do a surgery.
Surgery?
We are going to tie up the captain and the captain.
7.
Jackie Chan.
Suiken.
Jacken.
Next, the third base.
Nagiken.
8.
Shiro-kan.
Hey, that's not Mugi-chan.
9.
Yoshako.
Yoshako in USA.
OK-kan.
21.
Katatsumuri.
That's all.
22.
The heavy man on the left.
Kiritsuki.
Hey, turn around.
23.
My sister.
Do you want to do the bed?
24.
Mamoru-kun.
25.
Hiroko Yakushima.
26.
Soprano yay yay yay.
What are you doing?
Yay yay yay.
27.
Aki-no-ta no kariko no ikono.
OK.
After.
What?
When I talk while I'm in the sea turtle.
It hurts.
It hurts over there.
43.
Anxiety of the eyes.
It's coming out.
44.
Missile launch.
45.
Hijoaguchi.
46.
Flower rock.
47.
Cinderella's one word.
Bon bon bon.
I have to buy it quickly.
I have to buy it.
Tomorrow is sunny.
48.
If the match is Ojiro.
I hate it.
49.
Do you support Ojiro?
What?
I hate it.
50.
Super Saiyan.
It was a wonderful performance.
Yes.
How was it?
It was good.
Was it good?
Yes.
What was your most confident performance today?
Naki-ken.
Naki-ken?
What was it?
I got it.
It's funny to see it from this distance.
Really.
When I see it from there.
I can't touch it.
There is a gag that I can't do on TV.
I wanted to do it.
It's called fure.
I want you to ask what it is.
What is it?
What should I do?
I've been waiting for a long time.
When I saw the opening today, I thought, this is what an entertainer is like.
When I saw him.
That's not good.
Can I be an entertainer too?
There are many people like that these days.
That's right.
Why?
That's why there are many people like that.
That's right.
Right?
I'm annoyed.
Recently, I've been told that I'm cheeky.
Why?
It's you.
What is it?
Do it first.
It's your fault.
I think you have a bad attitude.
I don't say it to anyone.
There are young entertainers.
I'm normal.
There are young entertainers like that.
Good morning.
When I look at it from the front, it looks great.
But that's too much.
There's no one like this.
They keep appearing.
I can't say good morning.
I can't say it.
Why?
When I see a young entertainer, I say good morning.
It's annoying.
Don't do that.
Why do you keep appearing?
Young people.
That's why I'm getting more and more arrogant.
Right?
That's right.
I don't want you to create such a situation.
It's the same as the monsters in Ultraman.
When they appear, everyone screams.
I don't want to do anything.
They just came out.
It's the same as that.
You're the one who saw it.
It has nothing to do with me.
But downtown has become a big deal.
That's what the people are saying.
I've never seen anything like that.
Young people say good morning.
That may not be the case.
But you have a bad attitude when you come into the studio.
I'm sure you'll be told that.
What kind of attitude did I have when I was in the studio?
That's a big deal.
You have a long toothpick.
Why?
Give it to me.
Give me a long toothpick.
I'll use it when I'm in the studio tomorrow.
I know.
You're the new leader of young people's fashion.
You're wearing long sleeves and short sleeves today.
I want you.
It has nothing to do with me.
I know you've always been a good brother to young people.
But you have a bad attitude when you come into the studio.
I don't have a bad attitude.
I don't know if you have that kind of atmosphere.
When I go to the disco, I sit like this.
It's a low chair.
So I don't sit like this.
But you don't need a hand.
If you look at me like that, I'm wearing a long sleeve.
I don't know what's good or bad.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You're always in a bad mood at the end.
I'm doing what you said earlier.
I don't remember telling you to say hello properly.
And then...
Wait a minute.
I'm going to get hit.
For example, let's say there's a Tamori.
And I'm Tamori.
It hurts, Tamori.
If you do that, Tamori will hit you.
That's right.
I didn't do anything.
Don't say that kind of thing.
If I say something, he'll get angry.
He'll just say, good morning.
I'm not saying anything.
I've seen a lot of things.
I think it's better to do this.
Who?
Who are you talking about?
Don't you understand?
Don't lie to me.
I'm scared.
I'm serious.
If you're doing that, it's okay.
I don't care if you tell me.
I can tell you anything.
You wrote something earlier.
If you refuse to kiss Tamori, he'll get angry.
How about you?
I'm number one.
Do you understand that?
Yeah, kind of.
Why?
He'll say, take off your underwear.
If you refuse to kiss him, he might get angry.
He might get angry, but the meaning is different.
The reason is different.
The reading is different.
Of course.
Why are you crying?
I'm scared.
I'm a mother.
I haven't heard that reason.
It's not because your pride is hurt.
I don't want to kiss you as much as you refuse.
So let me kiss you.
It hurts.
Adults hit me.
I'm serious.
What are you talking about?
It's you.
What's the reason?
I don't know.
I'm angry because you brought me here.
You're angry, too.
I don't understand why I want to see you.
I'm angry because you brought me here.
Wow.
It's not because you're angry.
I can do it.
I understand.
It's the feeling of youth.
You don't let me kiss you.
What is this?
I don't throw it away.
It hurts.
What are you going to do?
What?
You sit here.
I know what you're going to do.
You don't cut it out.
I see.
You're watching TV.
What are you going to do?
Nothing will start with this.
You're watching TV.
You're doing this.
Nothing will start with this.
You don't like women.
I don't like women.
Do you want something to drink?
Yes.
What?
I'd like some oolong tea.
Oolong tea?
Yes.
Calbee soda?
No.
I'd like some oolong tea.
I'll go.
You all mean that you didn't need to remember or listen to something.
May I ask?
Yes?
You were invited.
You didn't attend, and you didn't even return it.
Do you really have nothing to do with TV?
No, we don't have anything to do with it.
You have nothing to do with it.
I see.
And?
You don't have anything to do with it.
You have nothing to do with it.
Yes, I wish you'll enjoy yourself
on TV.
I understand. I'm close to that.
I used to live in one room.
I can go with the flow.
Yes, yes.
Where to battle, that's the only way.
Right? But recently, my bedroom is different.
I see.
It's like this.
But I can't do it here.
I have to go there.
I have to hold hands.
This feeling is...
It's not good.
This is the worst time.
I don't know what kind of face each of us makes.
What is the feeling of being carried away?
That's right.
I'm laughing a little.
Are you laughing?
I'm laughing a little, but my legs are strange.
You don't like that, do you?
I understand that.
That's embarrassing.
Tokiya is the most embarrassing.
When I have to go to the bathroom.
That's because the movement is slow.
If you suddenly take me to the bedroom, I can't go anywhere.
That's true.
That's because I try to do it with my back.
I hold my knees.
The woman is like this.
I've been doing it so far, but I'm still going to the bathroom.
Why do you stretch your nose hair?
I don't stretch my nose hair.
How far do you stretch your nose hair?
What are you trying to do?
I'll tell you.
I couldn't tell you today, but I'm going out again today.
You're going out today, aren't you?
And you're going out tomorrow, aren't you?
I'm going out.
Why?
I want to see something unknown.
I know. I'm going to stretch my nose hair.
It's almost the 21st century.
It's a big event for the earth.
If you think about it, I can't stretch my nose hair.
That's right.
I think the human body is made precisely, but it's stupid.
I just need to stretch my nose hair.
I'm a fool.
I can stretch my nose hair as many times as I want.
People look down on me.
I'm sorry.
There are some places where you can only stretch your nose hair.
I can't stretch my nose hair all the time.
That's because you know your position.
Listen to me.
Who are you talking to?
I'm talking to other people.
I'm the president of the company.
That's a big deal.
Come here.
I'm angry.
If the president of the company is so angry, it's a big deal.
If we stretch our nose hair, it won't be fashionable.
If we stretch our nose hair more than the president of the company, it won't be fashionable.
I'm the president of the company.
Do you feel the same way?
I'm sorry.
Give me some tea.
What about me?
I didn't know that.
Hello.
I've been wondering about this for a long time.
You always turn around when you appear on any program.
Why is that?
When you come out, do you come out like this?
I don't know.
But I come out a few times.
Why do I come out like this?
You have a reason and a meaning.
If I have a reason and a meaning, I'll know why I come out like this.
I don't know.
It hurts.
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.