7.Juice
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
What kind of person are you?
I'm sorry
It's not like that, I really went too far
If I go like this, it's weird if I wear a suit
So today I'm like this
I thought I should talk about why I went too far
I usually do it at home with a barricade
I do it
I usually do it a bit longer
About 5mm
I'm done
I went to the bathroom
I do it in the bathroom
I went to the bathroom and looked
This part was a bit long
But I already cleaned the barricade
I cleaned it with a brush
I was curious about this part
So I jumped into the bathroom
And went
When I cleaned the barricade
I took off the attachment
There's one
The one that takes a few millimeters
I took off all of it
Bye bye bye bye
What is this sound?
It's too short
When I looked in the mirror
I looked like a Kamen Rider
You did it all at once
I had to do it all at once
I had to do it all with my skin color
After 3 days
I was able to show it to everyone
It became a product
I don't know if it'll fit in my mouth
I'm sorry
What is it?
Is it okay?
This...
Really...
Nothing happened
I was smoking while doing it
I thought I should throw it away
But it hit me
Hey you!
What are you doing?
It was just before I went to the bathroom
It hit me
It was like a cannon
After that
I was taking a bath
You washed your hands right?
I washed my hands
It went out
If you put your hand under the faucet
The water will automatically come out
It was like that
It went out
I was like
I'm sorry, can you stop it?
What?
Can you stop it?
It was automatic right?
Really
My brain...
I went to the bathroom too much
I'm really sorry
That's the reason
It's fine
It's my revenge
I didn't do anything wrong
You're going to get hit
That's right
Have you decided on your vacation?
What is it?
Where are you going?
I'm not going
Why are you so down?
Where are you going?
What?
2 weeks?
I can't do 2 weeks
If you're going to do 2 weeks
Do it slowly
You understand right?
Go
Where are you going?
I'm not going
I really
I really don't have money
I'm really sorry
You don't have money
I really don't have money
I have a lot of cars
You have a lot?
You're the only one who has money
I have a Mercedes
Wait a minute
You have 2 cars
No
You have 3 cars
I don't have money
What are you talking about?
You have 3 cars
No
I only have one car
I also have a Jaguar
What is a Jaguar?
It's like this
The one in front of the hood
Show me
Show it to the camera
I want to see it
I'm really sorry
You're the only one who has money
Your head is like this right?
Where are you going?
I don't have money
The holiday trip is in a Harley
Yes
What are the conditions for a man who looks good in a Harley Davidson?
This is
Are you riding a Harley?
You just said, are you riding a Harley?
I want to say
Are you riding a Harley?
That's how much I want to ride a Harley
You don't have a license
I have a Harley license
You have a Harley license?
You guys are so stupid
It's easy for you to understand
I have a license
I have everything
What are the conditions for a man who looks good in a Harley?
Let's think about what it means to not look good
For example, you're wearing glasses right?
What do you think is the thing that doesn't look good on people who are wearing glasses?
Glasses
What?
If you put the same thing on top of each other it doesn't look good
Just now
The audience saw me with very fascinating eyes
What are you talking about?
Don't you understand?
So you're saying that you shouldn't wear glasses over glasses?
That's...
No one does that
So let's go back to the Harley
People who are wearing back mirrors don't look good right?
Where?
Here?
Well you're wearing it here right?
That's right
So it doesn't look good on people like that
But no one is wearing a back mirror
So you really don't know how to say an example
No no
I understand an example
That's an example
Don't ask me for an example
If you ask me for an example I won't answer
If you ask me for an example like that no one will understand
For example, someone who wants to ride a red Porsche
The person who doesn't look good in a red Porsche is a red person
It's red
But I'm not that kind of person
So don't ask me for an example
Don't ask me for an example
I'm talking about how you don't look good in a Harley
I don't look good in a Harley?
What?
What are the conditions for a man who looks good in a Harley?
That's an example
That's why I said it
It's the first time you're saying it
If you didn't say it earlier I would have said it
You don't listen to me
I don't understand
What are you doing?
Wait a minute
You're talking about an example
Okay okay
I'll take it
I'll erase it
For example, when you're looking for a room
If you say something you don't need
You'll see the room you're looking for
This is also an example
No no
Don't take an example from now on
I don't need anything
I don't need a Japanese room
Yes yes yes
A room without a Japanese room
If you keep talking about your dreams
It will get bigger and bigger and you won't understand
So think of it as an elimination method
If you find someone who doesn't suit Harley
You'll see someone who suits Harley
I understand that
I said earlier
There's no one with a mirror here
This is a good thing
Right?
That's why
The example from the nose is strange
There's no elimination method
But
You can go in from the nose
Yes yes yes
But
One of them disappeared
That's an example
You really
How did you raise him?
What kind of trauma did you have?
I don't have one
The example is strange
So
Overall
It's a person who doesn't suit Harley
There's a lot of people who don't suit Harley
Everyone
Why everyone?
You suit Harley
I don't suit Harley
I'm Harley
No no you're not
I don't know what you're talking about
That's
It's about the reactions when you take a picture
It's not cool to be happy
It's just a strike
If you have a good line or pose
Please tell me
You rarely
Your fingers are crooked so you can't take pictures
What do you do?
If you have a good line
I'll tell you one thing
You have a good line when you have a good line
But when you don't have a good line, it's really bad
There are times when you have a stupid face
Your mouth
There are times when you don't have a good line
Do it well
What do you do when you take a strike or spare?
What do you do?
I said
I said together
It's Onobori
Why?
Bowling Onobori
It's not cool at all
I got 196
That's not good
196 is not good
I really
I'm really amazing
The light bulb of the crown of the previous strike was cut off
That's your fault
The light bulb was cut off
I can't catch up
It's too bright and I can't catch up
Again?
What am I?
I still can't catch up
I'm like a fool
If you can do that, that's right
Now, when you take a strike
When you take a strike
Please tell me
Isn't this enough?
Come back and do this
I don't understand the meaning
I did it
What's the meaning of the second arm?
Is that right?
It's going to be good, isn't it?
I'm going to be going this way
I'm going to say goodbye
I was like, there's more to it.
And then I went home.
You know what I mean?
And then I went home and...
I was in my bed.
I had a book.
And then I went to sleep.
That's all.