A new year's party will be held.
The 11th Gaki no Tsukaiwaraen Chikichiki Millenium New Year's Party!
Alright! Alright!
I'm Yamazaki, who broke up with Dancing Yamachan last year.
Nice to meet you!
Alright!
Do you want to see Dancing Baby?
Ah!
Can you do it?
Otsunomutsu and...
Usoendekisoba!
Today, I want to make it rain!
Thank you!
And...
Obachan!
First of all, I'd like to hear a greeting from the angel of Harleys, Producer Suga.
Nice to meet you!
I'm really looking forward to this year as well.
This year as well?
Everyone, please have fun!
I'm looking forward to it!
Thank you!
And now, the main character of this program!
The character?
The downtown person!
Please say hello and look in the mirror!
Thank you!
I'd like to work hard as Kotori as well.
Today, Hamada-kun's...
There's also Kurotabushi.
Eh? Are you going to show that?
That's the main character.
I've been training him since two months ago.
I'll do the spear myself.
And now, please look in the mirror!
Ah, that's right!
Yes!
And now...
Please look in the mirror!
What is this?
I'm sorry.
How do I say this?
Just look in the mirror!
One, two, three!
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
This year's Gaki no Tsukai is starting again.
Everyone is excited to eat and chat.
But in the midst of this, Matsumoto has started to show an unusual tension.
Please say quit!
Quit!
Don't quit!
Matsumoto-san, please quit!
The second round! The third round!
Yes, yes, yes!
You're going to die!
Ah!
Matsumoto-san, the next round!
The next round!
Next, the wine!
You can't drink it when it's hot!
It's okay, it's okay!
I told you!
Is your body okay?
It's definitely going to be bad!
It's okay, it's okay!
It's the first time I've seen you drink like this.
It's the first time I've seen him drink like this.
It's okay, it's okay!
I quit!
It's really bad!
It's definitely going to be bad!
Then, Hamada-san too!
It's hot!
It's okay, it's okay!
Why are you doing this?
The wine is for Matsumoto, isn't it?
Just in case.
Drink the hot wine before the wine.
I'll make you a sandwich.
There's milk in it.
It's like cheese.
I quit!
You're going to die!
I'm drinking a little bit of alcohol.
It's okay, it's okay!
It's really bad!
I quit!
I don't care!
It's okay!
Are you serious?
He's a crazy person.
He's like a
I've never seen anyone like this before.
His face is all red.
The third time, we're going to make you laugh.
Millenium Manzai
This time, out of 25 people, I'd like you to choose 5 groups.
First of all, I'd like to choose the first group of people.
It's a group of 5, right?
Yes, it's a group of 5.
It's a group of 5.