Tsunahiki大合戦!
Good evening everyone!
Today we are in Nishi-Shinjuku.
Today is the day to bully Shono in this park.
SHOOOOOOON!
Are you ready? There are 6 boxes in the back.
Why are you looking at me?
There are 6 boxes in the back.
This is the big Tsunahiki competition.
There are 3 more skaters in the boxes including us.
I see.
We did it together, so I'll do my best.
We will choose 3 more skaters.
Each of us will score 3 points.
And then there will be a partner in the box.
Emo.
Matsumoto.
That's good.
Emo.
I got it.
Where are the rest?
What are you doing?
Hey!
I don't like it.
I'll do it like this.
I'm the only skater.
I'm the skater.
You look strong.
Nice to meet you.
You are a good skater.
I got it.
No.3?
No.3.
No.3, please.
Here he comes.
Amazing.
What is this?
No.5.
You look strong.
No.1.
You really look strong.
My skater is No.2.
No.2.
You look strong.
I got it.
No.4.
You look like a skater.
Amazing.
Are you a skater?
Don't reply like that.
That's all.
Let's do it.
This is a female skater.
Everyone except me is a female skater.
Captain Taika.
Only this part.
This outfit is mine.
Let's do it.
What are you doing?
Let's do more.
Do you want to do it with me?
Are you a skater?
What are you doing?
This is strange.
What?
Let's see how far you can go.
Let's do it.
I'll do it with you.
Ready.
I knew it.
You look like a skater.
What are you doing?
It hurts.
It's over.
What?
This is a 30-minute program.
You came to a good place today.
That's right.
It's beautiful.
It looks like it's just been made.
It's just been made.
The audience looks beautiful too.
With this beautiful chair.
It's not a big deal.
I found something amazing today.
Something amazing?
I'm amazing.
What is it?
I've been doing a lot of research.
When?
I've been doing it all this time.
I realized something.
What?
No matter what you say, I can do it with my bare hands.
This is amazing.
I can do it normally.
You can do it normally.
I can do everything with my bare hands.
I don't know if this is amazing.
Why bare hands?
I've been thinking about it a lot.
This is the best.
There are a lot of things.
I found out that I can do it 100%.
That's great.
Shall we try it?
Sure.
What should we start with?
Anything.
Slipper.
Pampers.
That's fast.
I can't think of anything.
Pampers.
Watermelon.
What?
What is it?
Watermelon.
Yes, yes, yes.
I know what it is.
You don't have to say it.
Everyone knows what it is.
Say it right away.
Yes, yes.
Carrot.
Slipper.
Pampers.
That's fast.
What is a pampers?
You do it like this.
You don't have to say it.
Say it right away.
Chicken rice.
Smart ball.
That's fast.
Slipper.
Pampers.
Mexican dance.
Special.
What is that special?
Isn't it special?
It's roux.
Rumania.
Rumania juice.
What is that?
What is that Rumania juice?
It's red.
Who is talking nonsense?
I can't accept that.
What is Rumania juice?
Accept it.
What?
Come on.
Say it faster.
It's fast.
Slipper.
You can't say it.
Say it.
It's a sparrow.
A sparrow.
Sushi.
It's fast.
Cinderella Express.
It's amazing.
Sudachi.
Chikan.
Chiran.
What?
Tyrannosaurus?
What is that?
That's great.
Is there such thing as Tyrannosaurus?
Yes, there is.
There isn't.
As a result of my research, there is no doubt that it can be returned.
I don't know if there is no doubt.
Please try it.
More and more.
With bare hands?
Yes.
It will definitely be okay.
Really?
100%.
You can return it with bare hands?
I've been writing it on the Shinkansen for a long time.
What is that?
There is no other way.
It's normal.
Really?
There is nothing that starts with Tsu and ends with Tsu.
Tsu is the head.
Yes.
The butt is Tsu.
Everyone thinks about it.
There is only one.
Yes.
Tsu of Tsubame.
This is the only way.
Really?
There is absolutely no other way.
You are like a machine.
Really?
Yes.
You are right.
If Kina came, I would be very happy.
Why?
Kinran-donsu.
I wanted to say that.
Yes.
It's a good word.
If it is D, it's a good word.
Rhythm and Blues.
It's a good word when you say it.
It's a bit late, but it's fun to talk with people.
How many times did you write it?
There are many.
There are about 1000 times.
There were many times when I wrote it in the Shinkansen.
There were about 200 or 300 times when you wrote it in the Shinkansen.
Why didn't you write it immediately?
I think it was a good idea to follow the memory.
It doesn't matter.
I've been following it for a long time.
I don't know how to finish it normally.
But it's fun now, isn't it?
Yes.
There was a game where you had to say something irrelevant.
I'm good at that.
Really?
Yes.
It's hot.
What time is it now?
It's getting really hot these days.
Your face is getting red.
What time did you wake up today?
What?
What did you eat for breakfast today?
I'm hungry.
I have to eat something in the morning.
My eyebrows are like this.
What?
Wait a minute.
If you just focus on one thing, you can do anything.
What do you mean?
You have to say different things one by one.
If you just focus on one thing...
This button is big.
But seriously, what did you sleep last night?
I'm tired.
That's dirty.
You didn't sleep at all?
Not at all.
I can't do this.
It's quite fun, isn't it?
It's nostalgic.
What kind of game did you play?
That's...
You make it square, and then you split it in the middle.
1, 2, 3, 4, then you shoot a number.
You do this with a dodgeball.
Like this.
Yes, yes.
I've been thinking about that.
I'm a very honest person.
I don't die like this.
Right?
Yes, yes.
Did you have that?
What?
It's called Dossun, right?
Yes, it's called Dossun.
Yes.
Also, there was that.
A mirror game.
A mirror game?
You don't know?
It starts with a mini-comic.
Yes, yes, yes.
You didn't play that?
You don't play rock-paper-scissors.
The loser does this.
Stop it! Stop it!
I'm going to kill you!
I'm going to lock you in here.
3 years later!
Hoi!
You didn't do that?
It's definitely 3 years later.
After I kill you...
3 years later!
Hoi!
If it was 3 years later, you wouldn't be here.
Now, let's introduce the postcards.
Okay.
So, today...
Where's Nitta?
What?
Nitta?
I wanted to see Nitta.
Where are you going?
What are you doing here?
I don't know if this is being edited or not.
But I wanted to hear your story.
Which one is she?
Which one should I take?
You like her that much?
We're both drowning.
We're so far apart.
There's only one float.
Which one?
I can't take it anymore.
You're the float.
Which one?
Which one should I throw?
Throw it and I'll take it.
I don't like this woman.
I'll help you with the opening today.
Thank you very much.
I'll read this one.
Tokyo and Arakawa are 16 year old Miwa-chan.
I want you to tell us about the time difference game you played when you were a student.
And if you have any tips on how to succeed.
This was quite interesting.
The time difference game.
I'm sure some of you have played it before.
It was good when you were going to school.
When you go to school, there's always an emergency meeting.
You have to stand on the first floor of the school building.
When your friends come, you say,
Hey, it's been a while. What class is next?
You talk to them and tell them that you're on the first floor.
When you go up the stairs, you run down the emergency stairs.
You have to wait 4 or 5 times.
When you say, Oh!
This is the time difference game.
Just like that?
That's all for today.
There's still some time left.
Okay, I got it.
Let's start the game.
I'll decide the winning and losing.
What are you going to do?
What am I supposed to say?
I always win and lose.
Okay?
If I lose,
I'll say,
Good morning, it's Asahi.
What the hell?
You only say Osaka.
What do you mean, Good morning, it's Asahi?
Where are you coming from?
Zoom in, it's Asahi.
What the hell?
I'll ask you to do something instead of that.
Wait, wait, wait.
At that time, it was decided that Zoom in, it's Asahi if I lose.
But now, there's nothing.
What if I lose?
I can't do anything without that.
No.
I'll think about it now.
Now?
It's a TV show.
You should have told me earlier.
I can't understand.
I see.
Before this show,
I started it.
That's right.
But I can't do it.
I can't do anything without it.
Why?
I just know it.
I have to do something more funny.
What?
I can't do it.
I'm telling you, I have a dream diary.
Dream diary?
I can't do that.
How can I do that?
I have to go to Kyoto.
What the hell?
Dream diary?
What kind of dream diary?
I'll eat you.
I'll eat your dream.
Only dream?
Yes.
What the hell?
I'll eat your dream.
I'm scared.
There is a person over there.
Who?
That person.
Morio Kazama.
Yes.
Turn the microphone to him.
Ask him the reason of the Super Cup.
He seems to have a reason.
I can't do that.
I can do it from here.
After a few months,
if you don't do something new,
I can't do it, either.
If you don't do it,
it's better to lose the game.
You can't do it again.
OK.
I'll do this.
If I lose this year,
I'll be here.
That's the problem.
I can hear you.
If I lose this year,
I'll be a kid.
I'll be a kid's servant.
It's very sad, but...
I'll take a break once.
What are you doing?
No.
You're stupid.
I don't want to take a break.
What are you talking about?
It's very sad, but...
Are you a kid?
I'll take a break once.
It's very sad, but...
I'll take your wife.
Are you stupid?
You two...
You two can't do this.
Why?
You lost the game.
No.
I don't want to take a break.
You're dirty.
I don't care if you say I'm dirty.
I don't care.
I want to take a break, too.
If you lose this year,
I'll stab you with a scissor.
Wait.
I'll put up with the pain,
but I don't want to repair it.
I don't want to.
No.
I don't want to get hurt.
Don't.
I don't want to.
I don't want to get hurt.
I just thought about it.
What kind of a kid are you?
You said that when you thought of it.
It can't be helped.
That's...
Let's play a game next week.
Sure.
I'll play a game in the corner of the post box.
I'll return all the cards.
You return the cards one by one.
And the loser...
Let's decide that.
The genius will be like the police officer.
I don't like that.
I'll make sure that you're the master.
I'll give you a needle and a thread.
Why do I have to get a needle and a thread?
Let's think about the punishment.
I'll think about it too.
Sure.
It'll be quick.
Let's do it like that.
Let's do it like this from the beginning.
That's right.
There's no end to the thread.
You have to cut here.
If you cut it, you can't see it.
You have to remove all of this.
It's like a mother crying.
Even if her children are watching,
they'll think,
I've been working for a year.
Let's do it like that.
Sure.
Next week,
let's play a normal match.
Sure.
Let's do it.
But,
can you stop attacking me with a normal move?
What do you mean?
You started with a normal move and stopped with a normal move.
So the end is a normal move.
It's not a normal move.
That's right.
It's a normal move that's heavier than a normal move.
I see.
You lost.
You ended with a normal move.
So the head is a normal move,
but the butt is not a normal move.
Not a normal move and not a normal move.
That's right.
I see.
What's next?
There's one more.
You have to admit the move.
Yes.
In your case.
For example, if you come in a car,
I might call you a carpenter.
Don't say that.
That's a circle.
A circle?
Yes.
I can't decide.
Don't sleep.
I got it.
Let's do it like that.
Okay?
You lost.
How about a penalty game?
What?
A penalty game.
I'll think about it.
There's a mayonnaise.
Yes.
Put it in a container.
Put it on your butt.
Yes.
And you have to poop.
You have to poop like that.
Yes.
It's fun.
It's my first time.
Why?
Also,
in the postcard,
there's a question.
Please do something like that.
The answers are all the same.
Please write more in the postcard.
Goodbye.