What are you buying?
I'm practicing.
You're going to buy it by piling up?
I don't know.
What's wrong?
Thank you.
You don't know the players either?
You've been playing a lot lately.
Yes.
It's about marriage.
Marriage?
I'm 34, and I'm 35 in September.
You're so old!
It's been a long time.
If I go on like this, in a few years,
I'll be living with Master Sakata.
You're going to be a great man.
But it'll be like that.
It'll be like that.
My body is getting stronger.
It's bad.
My hands are not going up.
My heart hurts.
My body is getting stronger.
You're so mean.
No, no, I'm just kidding.
For now, I want to know what marriage is.
I've been to other people's weddings, but I've never been there.
That's right.
I want to know how the bride's family feels through this program.
I think I've experienced that in the heroine.
Yes, yes, yes.
I think it's a problem if you get carried away when you do it someday.
It's cool.
That's not good.
It's my first time.
Yamazaki.
Mr. Oso.
Mr. Akiyama.
Such a friendly person.
And then,
Well, I'm in a school of the road.
Yes, yes, yes.
I don't have a priest role.
You're right.
I'm a new actor.
I've watched a lot of men's movies.
I'm very worried about it.
I'm thinking of acting in Hamada.
Why?
It was a little early.
But Hamada is the best.
Why?
It's a good idea.
I have to raise the level of the downtown line.
Why?
Which combination do you want to do?
No, no, no.
I feel refreshed.
Let's do it right away.
Why me?
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Why me?
Thank you very much.
Please give them a round of applause.
I'm happy, you can be happy with me
We are now going to perform the wedding ceremony of the family of Matsumoto and Hamada.
First, we would like to introduce their profiles.
The bride and groom, please stand up.
Shintaro Hitochi was born on September 8, 1938 in Amagasaki City, Hyogo Prefecture.
He was a very spoiled child, and he was always with his mother no matter what he did.
However, his personality gradually improved after he entered Shioe Elementary School, and he became a member of the broadcasting club after he entered Taisei Middle School.
After graduating from Amagasaki Industrial High School with excellent grades, he enrolled at NSC of Yoshimoto Industrial, and here he showed his talent in 12 parts.
He started with Japanese TV program Downtown's Gaki no Tsukaiya Arahen and made many other programs hit, and his position became an immoral one.
I heard that your hobby, billiards, is quite a skill.
On the other hand, the bride Masako was born on May 11, 1938, in Amagasaki City, just like the priest Hitoshi.
It is said that when she was a child, she was a girl with a round face like a boy, but she was also a child with a childlike personality.
He was a popular student in the school.
After that, they made great success by using the personality of Masari Otoko.
They were active in dramas and songs, and also appeared in the drama, The White Poet.
Their meeting is the same as the meeting of Shioe Elementary School.
They became friends in the same class, and they were conscious of each other as friends.
After that, they will go to different high schools, but they will meet again in 3 years.
Here, the feelings that they have secretly thought of each other became unbearable, and Hitoshi proposed to Masako, and they were able to celebrate the goal in today's goal.
It's simple, but I introduced them.
I'd like to ask the audience to give a few words of encouragement.
First of all, I'd like to ask Mr. Kenji Suga, the producer of the Japanese TV broadcasting company Hensei-kyoku,
and the producer of Gaki no Tsukaiya Arahen in Downtown, to give a few words of encouragement.
I met Hitoshi Shinro 10 years ago.
I told him that I wanted to do a new show.
We met 9 years ago.
And then he became a superstar.
I met Shinro for the first time today.
I'm very happy that the point of choosing the wife is the same as the heroine.
I feel like I can protect Hitoshi as a mother.
Congratulations.
Now, we will have the wedding cake.
Please give them a big hand if they put the knife in the right place.
Now, the bride and groom, the wedding cake is here.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Let's celebrate their good luck and make a toast.
Let's pray for the good luck of the Goryo family.
Cheers!
Please come out.
living solution
Finally, the class can start
Good bye
Let us continue
Now, the bride and groom, please enter.
I knew it because I was loved by you
I'm in a great mood.
You're noisy.
That's good.
Thank you very much.
That was good.
That was really good.
Happy birthday!
It's the night of the sun.
We'd like to start with a few words of celebration and a song.
First, we have the bride and groom.
They are the younger generation of Yoshimoto Kogyo.
They'd like to say a few words of celebration.
Masako-san, congratulations on your wedding.
Congratulations!
Masako-san, you are always making jokes and making people laugh.
I'm sure you make people laugh by making jokes with Masako-san.
But at night, you might be making jokes in bed.
I'm sorry to say this, but I'd like to tell you an extra story.
About a year ago, I was still working overtime.
I was told to help.
At that time, I heard the marriage proposal.
I'm the only one who heard it, so I'd like to reproduce it here.
It was a Chinese restaurant incident.
It's good, isn't it?
It's really good.
This meatball is a popular dish in the neighborhood.
Really? It's really good.
Ah, the last one.
Kisou-san, eat it.
No, you eat it.
No, Kisou-san, eat it.
I'm full, so eat it.
No, I want you to eat it.
I want Kisou-san to eat it.
After two hours.
No, you eat it.
No, Kisou-san, eat it.
Let's get married.
Like this.
Like this?
I did it!
【 hair一下子】
It's cold.
Is it cold?
Please just like now
The flower that bloomed is still blooming
But it's still beautiful
Hey!
The three of you are humming together
I want to make you happy, you're a slumber
You can always smile
Don't cry, don't cry, Samba
Don't become a bird
Ah, that's the way it is
That's the way it is
1, 2, Samba, 2, 2, Samba
Oh, oh, oh, Samba
I'm taking a picture of you guys.
By the way, you guys are not in the picture.
Who is thinking?
I'm doing a simulation.
Is it OK?
You can go up to the top and take off your clothes.
Masako, you're noisy.
I'm sorry.
I'll make a face and make a mess of my head again.
Hey.
I'll get angry.
Please stop. Everyone is happy, right?
Hey, stop using standard language.
I want you to say it.
Thank you very much.
Please give him a big round of applause.
Now, we would like to have a short interview with the bride and groom.
Thank you very much.
First, I'd like to hear some words about your real proposal.
So, Matsumoto-san, you go first.
Well, the first kiss was after the first stage.
After the first stage, the first kiss.
At that time, I was glad, I was happy, and Masako came to me.
From the front?
Yes. Masako is like Yoshimi Tendo right now.
She is very beautiful.
She has the smell of Osaka.
Yes.
She is beautiful.
At that time, I said that I would marry her.
Next, if you get married, you will have children.
I don't know if I can say this in this seat, but I've already won the award.
I'd like to hear your favorite food.
Well, I can make truffles.
Truffles?
I can make truffles.
You can make truffles?
Yes, I can.
That's right.
It's a trick, isn't it?
Yes.
Now, let's welcome the bride's junior, Mr. Yamazaki Hosei.
Hitochi-kun, Masako-san, congratulations on your marriage.
Isn't she my junior?
But, Masako-san, you are...
Masako-san, you are...
You are such a charming person,
a really cute girl,
and really...
Thank you for raising me.
Ah, in Franklin's words, there are these words.
Today is worth twice as much as tomorrow.
I've become a bit stiff, but thanks to Hitoshi, who has been living his life seriously,
I've been able to...
I've been able to make this seat.
Good morning.
Good morning, you!
I know.
I know that you are seriously thinking about living from now on.
And that this is the real start.
Why do you know?
Why do you know my feelings?
Thank you very much for the speech that was sent to WIT.
That's what the company said!
You just say what's written in the book.
You even read what the host says.
As the host of today's show, I would like to extend my gratitude to the guests who have come today.
Thank you.
I am very happy that so many people gathered here for us.
I am also very grateful to Masako and her friends.
I am very happy that we were able to hold a ceremony like this.
You are very happy.
You are not in a good mood.
But I have something to say to everyone.
You are the ones who need to practice.
I'm actually a hole-in-the-wall.
A hole-in-the-wall like this is not suitable for any scene.
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you very much.
That was good, Masako.
Did you get a second round?
I've already taken care of the room.
I want to take it off.
You want to take it off?
Yes, I want to take it off.
Then I'll take it off too.
I'm going home.
What's wrong, Masako?
I'm going home. I'm going to be left alone.
You're a loser.
I'm going home.
Everyone's a loser.
I wonder if I was such a crazy kid.