You're under arrest for defamation.
I don't know what you're talking about.
In the last two trials, even though he was sentenced to life imprisonment, he never showed any signs of remorse.
In the last trial, many evidences were presented, and it became clear that he was a liar and a pervert.
It was also revealed that his words caused a lot of trouble to the people around him.
What was the verdict given there?
The verdict is the punishment of the Human Breaker!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
At midnight, in a classroom where only one light is on, Kei comes down to this place. Will he be able to withstand this terror?
Kei-pou, the punishment of the Human Breaker, starts!
The light is on over there.
The classroom is in that room.
There was an iron bar in the classroom, and he fell down in five minutes.
The light in the classroom went out in a flash.
It was so dark.
We were scared, too.
The staff was worried that he would jump out of the window.
He almost fell down.
Kei-pou.
Ouch!
No, no.
I just read his name.
Kei-pou.
Yes.
Are you ready?
I'm scared.
You're not scared of anything yet.
It's still bright.
You just have to do your best.
It's only five minutes.
I'm scared.
Can someone come here?
You just have to do your best for five minutes.
I'll wait here.
I'm so scared that I can't move.
I can see you, so I know.
You just have to do your best for five minutes.
Five minutes?
Yes, that's right.
Can someone come here to help me?
What are you talking about?
What are you scared of?
It's a bright classroom.
You just have to do your best for five minutes.
Yes.
What?
Kei-pou, stand by.
He stood up.
I'm scared.
What's going on?
What's going on with five minutes?
It's a delicate time.
Kei-pou, let's go.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Human breaker.
Ready.
Start.
I'm scared.
Help me.
No.
It hurts.
I'm scared.
No.
Someone is coming.
Watch out.
It's not even 30 seconds.
No.
Help me.
I'm scared.
No.
Help me.
Where can I hold this?
I wonder if there is a person who can hold this.
It's not in the picture.
No.
Someone is coming.
I'm scared.
No.
Someone is coming.
Watch out.
I'm scared.
No.
Watch out!
I'm coming!
Where?
HEPPO!
It's not scary at all!
It's scary!
Look at this!
What is it?
It hurts!
You're taking a lot of time.
There's a ghost here!
There's no ghost here.
I'm not coming.
Where is the ghost?
When I look at the viewers,
I feel like I'm being bullied.
It's not scary at all.
It's scary.
If it's this scary, take off your glasses.
You're trying to look good, aren't you?
If it's like this,
I won't be forgiven.
You're going to regret it?
You have to think about
how to overcome the fear of HEPPO.
You have to think about it.
If you think about it, it'll be scary.
Why are you doing this?
What are you doing?
Let's end this together.
It's not scary at all!
It's scary!
Hang in there!
What are you doing?
Don't stand up!
I'm scared of the skeleton.
He said it clearly.
Are you Summers?
Let's go!
After this, Ichidou cooperates to get rid of the fear of Heipou.
Please go with me.
What if I turn off the light here?
What is this?
Please, my heart hurts.
I'm scared of the skeleton.
I can't go to such a place.
Let's go together.
I can't go alone.
This is scary.
It's coming out.
He ran away.
I'm scared.
He's coming out.
He ran away.
It hurts.
I'm scared.
It's really scary.
Why are you wearing glasses?
You can't take it off.
It's really scary.
I'm scared.
There was something.
I can overcome this.
You don't have to.
Stand on the wall over there and go home.
I don't want to.
I'm scared.
Why are you scared?
Why are you scared of the floor?
Are you scared of the floor?
I'm scared.
If you don't have a floor, you're more scared.
I'm glad.
I can't help it.
I'm scared.
What should we do?
It's over for today.
I'll think about it next time.
How did you feel when you found out about Matsumoto's abandoned inn?
I'm going to die.
I'm scared of the floor.
Look at the floor.
What is it?
It's a tiger's eye.
It's not a tiger's eye.
I'm scared.
Help me.
I can't help it.
I'm scared.
I'm scared!
What kind of voice is that?
Help me!
Hello!
How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
Really?
Not at all.
I'm fine too, but there was a funny guy on the way here.
The old man who was riding his bike.
He was screaming like this.
It was serious.
He was riding his bike and screaming like this.
I don't know if that's true.
He was screaming like this.
He was going fast.
I feel sorry for him.
It seems like he's having a hard time.
He's a terrible person.
I don't understand it at all.
He was crying, right?
What the hell are you guys doing?
There are people who cry.
There are people who sneeze.
There are people who say they feel bad.
I don't feel bad.
I didn't mean to say that.
But I don't know if he'll come suddenly.
It doesn't matter if he doesn't come every year.
Maybe he'll come this year.
But I'm a little pissed off.
We're a duo.
It's better to have a lot of experiences.
Yes.
Right?
When I came out here,
If you say you've never had a pollen allergy,
It's over, isn't it?
That's right.
Right?
Which means,
It's better to have a strong pollen allergy.
The story gets more exciting.
Well, in a sense.
In a sense.
That's why I'm going into the main subject.
I'll do my best next week.
I don't know if I'll be able to do it.
I'll try to climb the tree.
From the tree to the tree.
You can't do your job.
If you think it's true.
It's fun, isn't it?
It's better to have a strong pollen allergy.
I don't want you to stay.
But in terms of pattern,
It's more interesting if you stay.
I don't know that pattern.
What's that pattern?
There's no meaning to being healthy.
I've been wanting to say this for a long time.
I've been wanting to say this since the third time I was a kid.
How many years ago?
I don't know the meaning of being healthy.
So I think you should just die.
But even if you die suddenly,
There's a schedule.
I don't want to die in a hospital.
So if you stay for about a month or two,
It's okay, isn't it?
I can't do that.
Why not?
I can't.
I can't do that.
You have to be careful.
What do you mean?
Even if I'm careful,
There's no one who can do it.
You're the only one who can do it.
I have a bad mouth.
I don't have a bad voice.
I'm doing it with that kind of character.
I'm not saying it seriously.
That kind of thing.
But that kind of thing...
Shut up.
I don't want to hear it anymore.
That kind of thing.
Yes, really.
Then take it out.
Pen name, Shoshinmon-san.
This is a question for Matsumoto-san,
Who likes parties the most in the entertainment world.
In Yoshimoto Kogyo,
It's said to be the most grand party.
At the birthday party of Nishikawa Helen-san,
What kind of things do you do?
I went there about 4 years ago.
Helen was 72 years old.
You'll get scolded.
Sorry, I'm still young.
When I was about 50 years old.
Oh, really?
Yes, I went there.
What kind of men are you wearing?
That's...
I think it's about you.
I didn't wear it in Yoshimoto.
You're lying.
No, really, really.
I didn't wear it as much as you and Master Kinji.
After that, I didn't wear it at all.
You don't have to go there.
I'll go alone.
But, after all, there...
He's a strong man who is willing to do anything for his family.
That's amazing.
On the contrary, I have to celebrate it.
The way they welcome me is amazing.
I've been coming from Shin-Osaka.
I said I'd be there.
When the Shinkansen started to run,
Helen was naked on her upper body.
What?
I don't understand the meaning of being naked.
Why are you naked?
It was amazing.
That was what I was hoping for.
I don't understand the meaning of it.
The K-Bow was like...
The K-Bow was like this.
The Shinkansen was going like this.
It was going this far.
It went down a little.
I was in the 9th car.
I was going down.
I was going to go home.
I was going to go to Nishikawa's house.
I was going to go to Mino's house in Kiyosu's car.
Helen was going to run.
She was wearing a bonnet.
It was a secret service.
That's right.
I wanted to know what she was going to do at her birthday party.
At Nishikawa's house.
There were all kinds of food in the world.
That's amazing.
It was amazing.
I don't know what it was.
It was about 120 square meters.
It was in the bedroom.
It was in the living room.
The living room was 9 square meters.
I was waiting for you to put the bed.
It was about 120 square meters.
There was a map of the world.
There was food there.
From that country?
It was a little different.
What's different?
There was a toothpick growing in the middle.
You're so stupid.
There were all kinds of food in the world.
But there was a toothpick.
There was only one toothpick.
If you ate it too much...
You wouldn't be able to use it.
You wouldn't be able to eat it.
You have to eat it with a firm feeling.
There was also a hard one.
That's not how you feel.
You have to eat something soft.
There was a party in the living room.
It was a fighting game.
Helen vs. poisonous scorpions.
Today, Helen will fight with a poisonous scorpion.
No, no, no.
Helen, are you a villager?
It's your birthday.
Helen, take your time.
I want to do my best.
I'm so happy.
If I could get the chicken...
I would invite her.
I would invite her, but she wouldn't come.
That was...
That was amazing.
Helen!
Why?
Helen wins!
She didn't come.
You were just playing with the keyboard.
You don't have any souvenirs.
That's amazing.
In the end, it's a kiss.
Helen's.
Really.
Helen's...
Who is it?
I want to give her a real kiss.
I don't want to do that either.
If I get the chicken, I'll hit her.
Don, don, don.
I'll hit her.
Helen, come here!
Where is Helen?
I love her.
She's in a transparent box.
Matsumoto uses this technique when he thinks she's licking him.
What is a spiral hurricane?
I rarely use it, but I use it about five times a year.
When did you use it recently?
The week before last.
You used it the week before last?
I used it the week before last.
The guy at the parking lot was doing something funny.
He was saying, aye, aye, aye, aye.
I was a little annoyed.
Really?
Aye, aye, aye, aye.
What kind of technique is it? Tell me.
Spiral hurricane.
I can't do it unless I put it on.
Oh, you put it on?
Yes.
Oh, I see.
The guy at the parking lot was saying, aye, aye, aye, aye.
And then?
Hey!
So I put it on like this.
I put it on to prepare for the spiral hurricane.
At that time, I was like this.
I was about to come out.
I was sitting low.
When I came out, I felt a tingling sensation.
I felt a tingling sensation.
You should have done it after that.
It's amazing, the spiral hurricane.
How did it feel?
What?
It felt like a translucent green color.
My butt.
And then?
What?
What happened?
It wasn't just a translucent green color.
It's fine.
When I came out, I was like this.
I was facing the old man.
Yes, bang!
What?
A light ball shaped like a rhino.
Yes.
I was facing the old man.
I was going to Muzo-san.
There.
It's amazing, the old man.
What?
What's a light ball shaped like a rhino?
It's confusing.
There is a lot of information.
That's fine.
If it's like that, it's fine.
You can start over from the beginning.
It's strange that it's connected from the part where he says that he's tired.
Or that he's blowing.
That's a good thing.
Until then, everyone was laughing.
That's why, even though there's that, after that, there's the light of Ishigaya-san.
You can't tell from there anymore?
Eh?
That's a lie. What was that earlier?
There was a doubt, right?
What was it like?
There was, but...
That's right.
At the place where it was half-transparent and turned green,
I knew that the audience was completely separated.
Right?
You can't tell at all, right?
Even at that stage?
What's with that?
What do you want to do?
That's how it's been lately.
That's right.
What do you want to do at that stage?
You can't tell at all.
That's right.
I know that.
How many times have you failed at that?
At that time, I couldn't change it.
I was wondering if Kiyoshi-san was doing well on the stage.
And then I got on the stage.
I thought that Kiyoshi-san was doing well.
I thought that I should have pulled him a little more.
It was as heavy as I thought.
Kiyoshi-san was doing well.
So I thought that Masumoto was riding.
I thought that I was riding and that I was heavy.