After a Long Relationship
It's been awhile...
Yup...
I didn't see you anymore...
Look at him! He got back all of hisGIVEAWAY Cl willing
Look at him!! He got back all of hisGIVEAWAY Cl willing
His face looks like he got something back from someone else...
He got back all of hisGIVEAWAY Cl willing
He looks so Release A similar expression that he took off last week...
Look here! He's got a真振运!
Well, well...
But...
At least his face looks like it has been returned...
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
I'm starting to get angry.
What's going on?
Say it already.
There's probably some people who quit smoking, but...
Oh, you're still smoking?
I'm still smoking.
You're still smoking.
No, no, I'm not smoking.
It's not like I want to smoke.
Really?
If you don't have that kind of will...
Then jump in!
I don't have that kind of will.
I'm not a professor, but...
Professor Heihachi just said...
He said there's nothing good about it.
There's really nothing good about it.
Oh, really?
That's why I said it.
He said it's good for your stomach.
That's a lie!
Really?
If you ask a guy who went on a trip abroad and came back...
How was it?
He'll say, it was fun.
It's the same as that.
What are you talking about?
It's a lie.
It's easy to say it wasn't fun.
It costs a lot of money.
I see.
I want to say it's good.
It's good.
So you want to say that you quit smoking and you're good at eating?
I want to say it.
I want to say I have stamina.
I see.
I don't have anything.
What is that?
It's a lie.
It's completely a lie.
I get irritated.
I get irritated a lot.
Your parents must be irritated too.
I do.
I do want to eat gum.
You want to eat gum?
Yes.
When I come home today...
There's that thing.
There's a lot of stuff in there.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's like a drum can.
If I open it while driving...
Bam!
Everything!
If you look at it...
Only the paper is left.
Bam!
That's your fault.
But you put it in properly.
No, no.
I put it in the right place.
Damn!
You want to say that you quit smoking.
I really quit smoking.
I really quit smoking recently.
The other day...
I was surprised.
Why were you surprised?
You know...
Yuta worked really hard, right?
Yes.
Well, that's a bad thing to say.
I think he's making quite a bit of money.
The other day...
I woke up in the morning.
Why are you laughing?
I was taking a shower.
Yes.
I was doing this.
It was cold in the morning.
Why is it so cold?
My heart was throbbing too.
No, you shouldn't talk about it.
I went to the toilet many times.
Apparently...
The gas was stopped.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I've been trying to stop it for months.
I think it was in the mail.
It was in the mail.
But I didn't see it.
I only saw it once or twice a week.
I didn't know.
It was in the kitchen.
I turned it on.
When the gas was on, it was like a flame.
I see.
When I didn't see it, my heart was throbbing.
I turned it on.
I was like an old woman.
I was like a young woman.
Ah...
I turned it off.
It was like this.
Oh...
The whole panel was like this.
Ah...
No, no, no, no, no.
It was so cold.
I turned it on again.
Ah...
I turned it off again.
I didn't notice it.
I didn't think the gas was stopped.
That's right.
I was like,
Don't panic.
It's a stove.
I turned on the stove and looked at it.
I was like,
Don't drink it.
I made a mistake.
I see.
I went to the manager.
It was cut in half.
The gas was stopped.
I was a junior high school student.
I said,
I'll do something.
I looked into it.
I'll call you back.
I was in my room.
I said,
The gas store was here.
I made a mistake.
It was cut in half.
I see.
I turned on the gas.
The manager looked into it.
I paid for the gas.
Is that okay?
Say it.
I'm sorry.
It's not automatic.
I was in the parking lot.
I was in the parking lot many times.
The gas was cut in half.
By yourself?
Don't drink it.
It was cut in half.
I was depressed.
I thought I had to fix it.
I looked into my past.
It may be fixed soon.
If I leave it alone,
It may be fixed.
Natural gas.
I'm glad to hear that.
That may be the case.
I don't know if that's the cause.
If everyone quits smoking, I'll smoke.
I don't like being with people.
You smoked a lot.
I didn't smoke as much as you thought.
That's enough.
What are you doing?
You can smoke.
I avoided it a little.
That's why I don't like it.
Among the top ten things you shouldn't see in this world,
I forgot the 9th and 6th places.
I can't remember.
Mr. Matsumoto, please tell me.
That's true.
It's a little hot, so I'll get a tissue.
I'll get a tissue.
That's true.
Can I have one or two?
There's a lot more.
Can I have 15th place?
That's enough.
Excuse me.
What is it?
Among the top ten things you shouldn't see in this world,
I forgot the 9th and 6th places.
I'll tell you.
Did you forget?
Why did you forget?
I don't know.
Why don't you remember?
I forgot.
Why do you ask such a proud person?
I don't know.
Please tell me.
What do you think it is?
What kind of system is it?
I think it's like that.
It's like a parent's child.
That kind of thing.
You haven't seen it?
I've seen it four times.
I haven't seen it.
It's like a testimony, right?
I've seen it in the way that my father and father-in-law are treating the green man and the old lady.
The old man.
What? Be my child.
You guys don't have to ask.
I've seen it.
That's right.
What kind of trauma is it?
I've seen it in the morning.
Go ahead.
Well, that's about it.
There are a lot of them.
The 9th and 6th places.
I don't really like them.
Is that so?
Yes.
Go ahead.
There are still a lot of them.
I think you'll be addicted to them.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
This is a question for Mr. Matsumoto, who is known all over the world for his suit.
Yes.
Please tell me five things about climbing a suit.
Isn't it hard to wear a suit and climb?
It was hard.
Why do you do it?
I was asked by everyone.
Why don't you do it?
That's right.
I think this is a famous saying.
But did you know it was hard to climb a suit?
What?
Did you know it was hard to climb a suit?
Are you thinking about it now?
What am I thinking about?
You should act before you think.
I'm sorry.
You knew it was hard to climb a suit, didn't you?
I knew it, but I didn't do it.
Please tell me those five things.
I don't like the way you talk lightly.
What is it?
It's a relaxed feeling.
Something like this.
That's enough.
Please tell me five things about climbing a suit.
Climbing a suit is a must.
It's a must?
That's right.
Why?
Climbing a suit doesn't matter.
It's useless.
When you climb a suit, your necktie goes like this.
It's not funny, is it?
You don't like it, do you?
I'll tell you.
Climbing a suit doesn't matter.
Your necktie goes like this.
I made a mistake.
That's one thing.
It goes like this.
It's not good, is it?
But you don't do it, do you?
That's why I said it.
Do you know why?
When your necktie goes like this.
It's scary.
It's a world where the roses go like that.
The necktie goes like this.
Which mountain are you climbing?
You climb such a mountain in a suit?
I thought it was a snowy mountain.
I thought it was a normal mountain.
It's a snowy mountain.
It's a snowy mountain, right?
The roses go like that.
Of course.
It's a world where the roses go like that.
If you don't wear a necktie there,
why don't you wear a tie?
A tie?
If you say that, it's really scary.
It's really scary.
It's scary.
I've seen a lot of friends who went like this.
I went all the way to the top, but it's all the way here.
It's like a red elephant is coming out from here.
I see.
You should wear a tie.
You should.
That's fine.
It's a mountain of neckties.
That's a caustic button.
You come all the way here?
You should wear a caustic button.
You should.
It doesn't really mean anything.
What do you mean?
Why? Are you stupid?
Is that so?
What are you going to do if this part goes like this?
No, you should stop the button.
No, winter mountains aren't that sweet.
It's really cold.
It's colder than you think.
In that sense, you should stop the button.
That's definitely...
Then you should wear hiking clothes.
Why do you go all the way to the top and wear a suit?
Say it again.
What?
Then you should wear hiking clothes.
Then why?
Why do you go all the way to the top and wear a suit?
Then why do you go all the way to the top and wear a suit?
The caustic button.
There's a lot of that.
There's also a rice cooker.
I don't need a rice cooker.
Why?
I definitely need a rice cooker for a suit.
But you don't need it.
You don't need it.
You're stupid.
When you feel like you're going to get lost...
It's SOM's Oda.
I think I'm going to die at that point.
Why?
So we went.
I'm curious.
Party.
Oh, hiking.
Oh, I get it now.
You stupid, you get it now.
I get it.
If you go to a party in a suit, all you do is a Christmas party.
Why is he angry?
Is it Christmas?
A party in a suit?
This is a mountain.
It's a snowy mountain.
You're stupid.
I'm sorry.
You're going to die.
I'll die when the time comes.
Next is an example of a rice cooker.
You should plug in a full-size room.
What do you use that for?
The ink will flow here.
Oh, I see.
It will flow.
Okay, okay.
That's how you use it when you're in trouble.
Like this.
There's a helicopter.
You can't see Yuta.
You can't see him when he's wearing a suit.
Then you use the ink here.
You!
What about the other one?
You're so cool.
What are you talking about?
There's another one.
The flag.
The company's flag.
You put the company's flag on the roof.
I see.
I have to bring that.
You have to bring that.
I see.
Huh?
It's stronger than I thought.
What are you talking about?
You're noisy.
What do you mean I'm noisy?
It's on my show.
So I'm a little noisy.
What happens to people when they go into the sea or the mountains?
The mountain god is the sea god.
I see.
So the mountain god says no, but they go in.
The sea god says no, but they go in.
That's not going to happen.
What happens then?
For example, you have a house in the city.
I do.
It costs 2.5 billion yen.
What kind of house is that?
Are you stupid?
It can't be.
I have a house.
It's a 20-meter wall.
What?
There's a 20-meter wall.
Is there?
If you go in there, what will you do?
Everyone gets angry.
But it doesn't mean anything.
The mountain god and the sea god.
The mountain god says no, but he doesn't hate people who like the mountains.
It's getting complicated.
So?
So you can't go in, but you're angry about coming in.
But you like the mountains, don't you?
I don't hate you that much.
So what's going on?
I know how you feel.
So if you go into your house, you're like, hey!
Hey!
You really shouldn't come in.
But the mountain god says you shouldn't come in.
But you like the mountains.
I know that.
I don't hate you that much.
That's how he gets angry.
I don't get angry that much.
Huh?
I got it!
So the sea is the same?
The sea is a little different.
It's a little different.
It's different?
Yeah.
But this guy stopped it.
It's different.
It's a completely different interpretation.
Then tell me.
What?
Tell me about the sea.
If you go that far.
Then I'll tell you.
The mountain is a little manly, but the sea is a little womanly.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Did you know?
I didn't know.
The mountain god is a man.
But the mountain god is...
What the hell!
You're making me nervous.
I'm going to rip you apart.
I want to see it.
You just said the mountain god is a man.
I said the mountain god is a man.
You're making me nervous.
I didn't!
The mountain god is a man.
That's right.
And the sea god is a woman.
That's why I'm saying it's a little different.
Then tell me.
If you go into the sea before the opening of the sea.
Then I'll tell you how to say it.
That's right.
I'll tell you.
I'll tell you that.
The mountain god doesn't want you to go in.
I don't think so.
I see.
Who are you talking to?
A crab.
There's a crab I like.
Do your best.
And?
What do you mean by do your best?
I'm telling the crab.
I'm telling the crab I like.
I'm telling the crab that it's been a while.
But I haven't told this crab how I feel yet.
That you like it?
But the crab has already noticed.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong with that?
It's not like that.
I can see the crab.
I see.
That's right.
I don't think so.
So the crab knows that I like it.
It knows.
But there's a crab I like.
That's not good.
There's a crab I like.
It doesn't matter what crab.
It's a crab.
And I'm saying things like,
I'm saying things like,
I don't know.
But it says that.
And it says,
I don't know if I'm really that jealous of it.
And,
The crab that I like
That's what it says.
But if I say that,
The female crab might be like,
Are you saying something again?
I see.
So your face tells me you don't really know.
That happened.
But that's not what I'm trying to say right now.
I don't know what you're talking about.
If you're in the warehouse and someone comes in,
the crab will pinch your leg.
I see.
But stop it.
This is the sea crab.
Stop it is the sea crab.
And then...
And then the mountain crab...
What the hell is that?
Solve it yourself!
I can't look at it.
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.