Let's go
I can hear the sound
Here it comes
What's going on with the set?
I can't listen to this
Let's take a look
Good evening everyone
I'm Akira from Nantan
Today is the first day of the new year
We had a lot of talk
We did a lot of things
Why is it like this today?
Why are you here?
Where is that guy with the black face?
Where is that guy?
He has a bad complexion
I heard he has a stomachache
You're bothering me again
Let's take a look
First of all, what Matsumoto predicted
What?
I saw this
I'm sorry but let's take a look
First of all, what Matsumoto predicted
The person watching you on TV said
Matsumoto is amazing
Stop it
There are a lot of people like that
Wait a minute
Matsumoto is praising you
I talked to you in a talk last year
It was perfect
I...
What is it?
I don't know what you're talking about
I talked about a lot of other things
Why did you suddenly become energetic?
Let's take a look
What Matsumoto predicted
Let me tell you a story
Stop being angry
What are you talking about?
Who would be happy about that?
I was happy when I was eating cup noodles
50 years
Matsumoto predicted
Today's event is over
A part of Tokyo Harajuku's pedestrian heaven
has been systematically destroyed
due to the noise and traffic jam of the rock band
A year ago
Matsumoto predicted the lack of glasses
What was the result?
What will happen this year?
There will be a huge planet on Earth
A huge planet
It will rise
Australia on Earth
Gung Gung Gung
This program was brought to you by the sponsor
10 minutes of this program will make you think of it as a meteor
This talk is based on Jimmy, who is retiring from the entertainment industry
I don't think there's anyone who can beat him
In that field
There's no one who can beat him
Well, I can't beat Jimmy
I can't beat him
He will go
That's right
And this program was born
Jimmy Onishi
His real name is Onishi Hideaki
He is a unique character in Japan's comedy world
His love for comedy
continues to give us peace and dreams
That Jimmy is now saying goodbye to us
He is about to leave for America
This is a great miracle of a comedian
Let's see the main character of the day
Please
It's a gorilla
What is it?
Today is the day of departure
I told you to look forward to it
I said it earlier
You don't have a show to say goodbye to Jimmy?
Not at all
You don't have one?
I'm laughing
The story of memories is getting more exciting
It's finally time for Jimmy to leave
I'll give you a bouquet
It's time for Jimmy to leave
Thank you very much
It's finally time to leave
Virgin Road
I want you to leave
Take care and go to America
Thank you very much
See you again
I knew something like this would happen
Are you okay?
Why didn't you do this until the end?
This is the story of a certain incident that Machan experienced
Actually, the other day
When I went to the coffee shop
I wanted to order iced coffee
It was a little strange
Did you bite it?
I said it was delicious
But I couldn't bring it
Iced coffee
That's where this project was born
Where is the ice coffee?
I'm going to the limit of iced coffee
First of all, Yamazaki will test the limits of iced coffee
Iced coffee
Do you think you're serious?
I'm sorry
I'm going to change clothes
I'm going to go higher
Will you go higher?
I'll go to the last stage
Oyan Fui Fui
This is definitely
I can't go to Oyan Fui Fui
And I can't find out
I don't know
I want cream soda
Oyan Fui Fui
I'm sorry
Please order
Oyan Fui Fui
Iced coffee
Did you say it?
Did you say it clearly?
What is this?
Oyan iced coffee
I was crying
I was crying at the end
But Matsu-chan didn't get tired of the limit of iced coffee
Iced coffee
What do you call it?
It's a Chinese dish
It's hot
Please forgive me
I don't need anything hot
Chinese food
And again, the limit investigation begins
The second time, I'm not a kid
How far is Chinese food?
I'm going to the limit of Chinese food
Thank you very much
To find out the limit of Chinese food
I sent Yamazaki, a market investigator, again
The second time, I'm a market investigator
The third time, I'm a market investigator
The fourth time, I'm a market investigator
The fifth time, I'm a market investigator
Let's go to the limit of the time
Mr. Suzuki
Today too
It's time to change clothes
Again?
It can't be helped
Are you going to cry?
I won't cry today
Change your clothes
It's perfect
What's perfect?
Excuse me
Yes
Well
Miso ramen
Here you are
Well
Mr. Suzuki
Suikyouka
Four
Well
Suikyouka
Suikyouza
What is this?
Well
Chinese cold noodles
Cold noodles
Well
It's a big one
Chinese cold noodles
Well
I'll take this
What?
There was a food called Suikyouza
Well
I won't take it anymore
I cried again
In the letter of the question
He found that it was actually a mountain climbing tool
So
He gave the mountain climbing goods that look like tools
To the beginner Hama
I want to go to Tateyama
It's Tateyama at this time
It was strange
It's Tateyama
And then
Manager
Why are you calling me manager?
I climb because it's hard to climb
It doesn't matter where you climb
The mountain is good
This is about 15 seconds
And Hama went to buy the goods
Broken Thunder
How far is the Broken Thunder?
How far is it?
Do you understand?
I'm going to buy mountain climbing goods
It's exciting today
It's not exciting at all
It's dangerous when you fall from the mountain
It's like a sponge
But it's plastic
And Machan
The mountain climbing goods were lectured
I'm fine
I'm going to climb the mountain
I'm going to go with this foot
As a feeling
I understand
Shall we go?
The mountain is good
Rock climbing
Please
The mountain is good
I want to go to Tateyama
At this time
Don't laugh
Don't call the manager
Manager
Are you the manager?
No
I went to the exhibition
You know about the mountain, right?
Well
I want to climb Tateyama
I want to climb in front of the station
Tateyama Station
What?
Well
It seems that the mountain is good
That's right
Well
It's better to be away
A little away
Look at various things
The mountain is good
Jopper
Well
Can you give me a jopper?
Jopper
Well
Please give me a dango
Excuse me
Laugh
Look
It's a cushion
Put it on your shoulder
That's a jopper
Jopper
The mountain is good
Laugh
As if he understood something
Machan suddenly started talking about this
It's hard
Laugh
Who?
To live
It's too late to say
Laugh
It's not too late to say
I think it's really hard
I don't know when I'll die
Laugh
Well
You don't know when you'll die
That's right
That's how this opening was born
The first prank
The prank
Nakamura died
Good evening
Today
I'm going to prank Yamasaki
I'm used to being pranked
I'm careful
That's right
I thought about it
Nakamura
He died
He's going to die
In my opinion
He's dead
Laugh
First of all
Let's call the actor
Laugh
It's scary
Let's give Nakamura a spot
It's not the most plain place
Laugh
Even if you die
Actually this time
The prank has already been done since last week
Nakamura approached Yamasaki unexpectedly
Yamasaki, who won the opening cannonball race
I promise to give you 100,000 yen next week
I'm going to die next week
The last conversation with myself
I had an impression on Yamasaki
Laugh
Nakamura, who was supposed to die in a traffic accident
Appear on the back seat of the car
Will Yamasaki be able to withstand the fear?
It was hot
Laugh
He is empty
I'm going to end the talk
Laugh
I do not think so
What?
What about you, Sano?
I can talk to her.
I'll be right there.
Really?
Is it today?
Yes, today.
Tomorrow, the day after, or the day after tomorrow.
What about you, Okamoto?
I'll be right there.
Thank you for your hard work.
What's wrong?
Don't cry.
I don't know what's going on.
What's wrong?
Did you have 100,000 yen last week?
You had 100,000 yen last week, didn't you?
You were worried about that, weren't you?
You've been saying that all the time, haven't you?
What happened to your 100,000 yen last week?
That's not good.
What's wrong?
I'm scared.
We're still in the middle of the show.
How was it?
We've seen it.
This is the first time in the new year.
This is the second time in the new year.
Next week is amazing.
You'll see it this week.
Please watch it next week.
It's a masterpiece.