Good evening, everyone.
Please come in.
Let's start the show. I'm Hamada Masatoshi.
I'd like to introduce myself.
I went to Australia the other day. I picked up a girl, but I failed, so I bought a ***.
I'm Yamasaki Hosei.
I'm Edson.
Nice to meet you.
I look like this, but when I go back to the company, I'm in a pretty good position.
I'm Kenji Suga.
Our work is really hard.
Yesterday, I swallowed a big sponge.
It's true. I almost got ***.
I'm Matsumoto.
Let's go.
Read the Atakamo!
I think you know the rules, but please read the Atakamo and pass it on to the next person.
Here's the first topic.
How to make a ***.
What's ***?
You don't know ***?
I don't know ***.
***?
Read it! Read it!
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
How to make a ***.
At one point...
At one point, there was a mother and a father.
The father loved sex.
That's a great book.
The father had a child.
The child was named Peatan.
When the child grew up, Peatan became a pirate.
The child wanted to be a pirate.
This is a big story.
Peatan was born and became a great adult.
What should I do?
Peatan wants to be a pirate.
Peatan went to look for his friends.
Passed.
I don't know.
Peatan asked Peatan something.
I have a bandage in my back.
It wasn't Peatan.
Which Peatan?
First, to make this Peatan...
I enlarged it.
In it...
There was a cell...
Peatan was out of season.
Why?
You said it was a bandage.
This is a big story.
Let's continue.
It wasn't Peatan.
Peatan was...
I think it was a chick or a chick.
Peatan was Peatan.
And...
Peatan...
You read a book.
I read a book.
It's written like that.
If you put the 3 like this, it will change from Pi-chan to Pi-tan.
The changed Pi-tan is...
It will be like number 1.
You're the only one who can read that.
You're laughing too much.
It's already over.
If in your class...
A bit of a bad guy, Hanikamiya-san, changes his class...
Will that be Pi-tan?
Let's move on to the next topic.
The King Sadaharu Story.
That's not true, Nagashima-san.
Is this the right order?
Ah, let's change it.
I don't like it after Jimmy and Yamaaki.
It's a bit crazy.
The King Sadaharu Story.
That's not true, Nagashima-san.
Let's move on.
Nagashima Shigeo.
I call him Chou-san.
I see.
Chou-san doesn't know much about the rules.
No-out.
Number 1. Number 2.
The opponent's player...
Gave a fly to Naiya.
Now, what is this?
Eh?
Eh? I didn't hear it.
It's next to you.
Listen.
That will be connected later.
Yes, I understand.
The King...
Gave a fly to Nagashima.
Eh?
Is that Pi-tan?
That's not true, Nagashima-san.
It's over.
Chou-san.
That's Yama-san.
I'll bring you Fanta.
It was so easy between the two of you.
I see.
One thing led to another.
There was a big fight.
There was a big fight?
Why was there a fight?
The King was very angry.
Why?
Because...
The King...
Was late in the morning.
Why are you blaming yourself?
The late King said to Nagashima...
You...
I was late and you drank too much yesterday.
He said that.
Nagashima was also drinking with him.
What did you talk about at the bar?
Tell me the cause of the argument.
Tell me the cause of the argument at the bar.
And then...
The Director of the Ministry of Justice...
What is the Director of the Ministry of Justice?
The person who gets in between.
The person who gets in between is the Director of the Ministry of Justice?
The person who gets in between...
I said it in a difficult way.
I'm sorry. I didn't notice.
The Director of the Ministry of Justice...
came in...
and used the money...
to get rid of him.
Headphone!
He put on the headphones.
I'll play the music loudly.
I'll tell the next person...
what the person is saying...
only with the movement of his mouth.
Jimmy.
The subject is...
this!
That's good.
Please face this way.
It's Jiro no Hamada.
That's good.
I don't understand at all.
Say it.
Calm down.
Stop it!
Jiro no...
Hamada.
Kikou mo Hamada.
It's okay.
Kikou...
mo...
A...
ma...
ta!
I don't understand at all.
I'm sorry.
Kikou mo...
Hamada.
Mazo-san, you're correct.
Isozuri Hamada.
Kokon Tozai...
Oketsu ni Monmari!
Do you understand the rules?
We'll play Kokon Tozai.
If you can't answer, you lose.
Mazo-san, if you can't answer,
Jimmy-chan will come to you.
That's so dirty!
Isn't it raw?
Yamazaki-san, the producer's butt...
The producer's butt is getting closer.
Let's go!
Yamazaki-san first.
Kokon Tozai.
Kokumin no Shukujitsu.
Tenno Tanjoubi.
Midori no Hi.
Taiku no Hi.
Kodomo no Hi.
Keiro no Hi.
Setsubun...
Jimmy-chan, start!
Ok!
What are you doing?
It looks like a hole.
Ian, hurry up!
This is no good.
It's really...
It's a good example.
If you listen to this,
you'll lose strength in your body.
But today's guest is always healthy.
Now you can even look at someone's butt.
You're looking at everything.
Now you're looking at me.
I'm in a bad mood.
No, no.
Like you just saw,
Jimmy's butt came up to there.
Since then, my right half of my body has been numb.
I know, I know.
Well, let's move on.
Is this a new joke?
It's not a new joke.
I've never said it before.
It's one of those 100 jokes.
Why?
I'm 31 years old, right?
I've been a cherry boy for 10 years.
So what?
Listen to my reply.
That's a good reply.
I had my first experience when I was 16.
How many years has it been?
I've been a player for 15 years.
I'm a little tired of it.
Is that so?
I've come to understand women's stupidity.
I see.
Women are stupid.
What?
What do you mean by women?
Did someone teach you?
What?
Is there a manual?
When you do it?
Yes.
What is it?
Well...
That's not it.
There must have been something between you and me.
But women always say that.
Well...
What's wrong with you?
You're like a light and a shadow.
You always say the opposite.
Are you an amateur?
No, no.
You always say, one, one, meow.
I don't understand what you're saying.
I agree with you.
That's strange.
I want you to say, sit down.
Sit down.
What are you saying?
I don't hate it when you say, I don't like it.
I see.
If you don't say, I don't like it,
you're forcing yourself.
No, no, no, no, no.
You can't say that.
If you don't say, I don't like it,
if you don't say,
I don't like it.
You can't say that.
No, I can.
You always say, I want you.
Who taught you that?
Moe, Moe.
Well, that's how it is.
I'm saying it.
Well, well.
No, no, no, no, no.
That's fine.
What?
What is that?
What kind of dance is that?
What?
There is a dance called the Matsumoto style.
Is that a dance?
Yes, there is.
There are various things.
Yes, there are various things.
Well, shall we go to the post office?
Sure.
The opening is really long,
it would be a waste if we talk too much.
But you see,
I'm always on the back of the program,
I'm in charge of the video now.
I don't know what you're talking about.
There are a lot of videos.
You, you,
I've been thinking about it for a long time,
I have to be careful about you,
What?
You have nothing to do with what you're saying.
You'd better stop that.
You're in charge of the video now.
What is this?
No.
It doesn't make sense.
I'm in charge of the video now.
You're in charge of the video now.
You, you,
Stop.
You're in charge of the video now.
Stop talking.
What kind of behavior did you do when you were said that?
I don't understand.
You're really funny!
I'm in charge of the video now.
Wait a minute.
What kind of behavior did you do?
What kind of meaningless behavior did you do?
You did it.
I don't know what you mean. You should do it properly.
You're funny too.
You should do it properly.
I can't do it.
What do you mean?
I should be careful.
We should do it together.
Come and do it!
I can't do it.
Let me do it freely.
So in that video...
I can't do it.
In that video, there's a lot of it.
That's what I mean.
Normally, it's edited a lot.
Okay.
Please brush your teeth.
I don't know what you mean.
I almost died today.
Why?
I drank spondia.
That's why.
Spondia?
No, it's hanging.
It's a game with legs.
If you fall, it's a mountain of sponges.
I drank it.
I ran with a big face.
I was too excited.
I drank sponges.
I'm serious.
Are you okay?
I'm sure you're okay.
When Machan eats at home, why does he have 7 chopsticks in his head?
There are 7 types of food.
Say it.
Meat or...
What else do you think?
You said you had it, so you say it.
Fish.
Fish or...
What else do you have?
Say it.
I'll tell you later.
Let's put it all in.
What do you mean?
Meat or fish.
When you eat fish, you say it's okay.
It's almost summer.
I have a weak body, so I can't go to the beach.
How can I be a macho man like you?
How did you become a macho man?
I'll tell you.
I'll tell you later.
Let's run.
When did you become a macho man?
I'll tell you later.
We came here about 5 years ago.
You became a macho man in 5 years?
If I started on Monday, I would have become a macho man on Tuesday.
Pascal says that if Cleopatra's nose was a little higher, the world would have changed.
Mr. Matsumoto, how did it change?
History is scary.
It changes a lot with a little change.
With a little change.
For example, you are now doing something called Tsukkomi.
That's right.
For example, if this hand was longer.
For example, if this hand was 2 meters.
Only this hand?
If this hand was only 2 meters, downtown's comedy would be like this.
But at that point, would you choose me as your partner?
A man who is 2 meters tall.
He's walking with his arms pulled back.
That's right.
From that point of view, downtown didn't exist.
If it was longer.
If it was longer, downtown didn't exist in Japan.
It didn't.
There is a man who is walking with his arms pulled back because of the rumors.
It's a scary story of elementary school students.
A dog often chases its tail and turns around.
What is that? Mr. Matsumoto, please tell us.
After all, this is a high spirit.
A dog?
A dog that wants to raise its rank.
A dog itself?
A dog that wants to move forward.
A dog that wants to live a life that is one rank higher.
It has nothing to do with a dog.
For example, a dog that wants to raise its rank as a talent.
That's right.
Everyone wants to be one rank higher.
Even a bird wants to fly higher.
That's right.
Even a dog wants to turn around.
A dog wants to turn around.
A dog wants to turn around and become an old man.
What makes you sad?
You can't be an old man.
Ah!
No, no, no.
My line is...
Aoka, you...
Everyone stops you immediately.
When a dog turns around, you say,
You idiot.
And you hug it.
Please leave it alone.
A dog turns around and becomes an old man.
Hamada-kun, you...
It's true.
It's scary.
You say,
Let's do a lottery.
I don't have any money left.
From a dog to a brand new dog.
I want to see that.
It's true.
It's amazing.
When a dog turns around, it's true.
A dog turns around and becomes an old man.
Can you take a picture of me?
Why?
You have a round face.
It's true.