Ladies and gentlemen.
Today, we have a lot of things that we have to do.
Listen to me!
Normally, we go out for the opening.
What are we doing today?
Are we in Nippori?
We are in Nippori.
But we are not doing it today.
We are not doing it.
Why?
There is something that you have to see today.
I said it at the beginning of this year.
This year, we are going to participate in various programs with high ratings.
Let's go normally.
Let's go.
Let's wake up from Amagasaki.
That's right.
The other day, I went to the audition for the costume of Kin-chan.
We did it together last year.
We don't know if we will pass or fail.
We don't know.
The staff doesn't know either.
But we brought it today.
So today, in front of everyone,
we will announce whether we will pass or fail.
I don't think there is anyone who has been there.
It's a great atmosphere.
After all, it's serious.
The father takes the child with him.
We are the same as the amateurs.
That's right.
That's where it starts.
When we change our clothes, the father is next to us.
That's a great atmosphere.
That was amazing.
I was a little nervous.
When I came, the person who finished the audition gave me a lot of luggage.
I took the child with me.
I was a little nervous.
It was a great atmosphere.
Everyone was painting their faces.
We did it.
What will happen?
I was very nervous.
It will be amazing if you get the main line.
It was amazing from the preliminary round.
I was treated like an amateur.
Number 67.
Matsumoto Hitoshi who was raised by Amagasaki.
It's not a phantom.
Matsumoto Hitoshi
I think there is a root.
When we started, the judges were angry.
It was the last time.
I had a face that seemed like it was angry.
When Hamada jumped out of the chameleon,
You hit me with your hand!
This is it!
I made a face that said this is it.
I see.
After this, I'll announce it.
Yes.
Masumoto Hitoshi-san is also wearing a hood.
You have to watch the V-app.
I'll watch it.
But before that...
Commercial!
No!
This program is brought to you by Sunlux.
That was a nice announcement from Momoya.
What are you talking about?
You're making me angry.
You look like you're good at pigeon fishing.
That's right.
Yes.
In that case...
The other day, we...
On Nihon TV...
On the other channel...
I was there early.
You were late.
I wonder if you're in there properly.
Yes.
You're in the rehearsal room.
Let's watch it until you get the audition.
Yes, please.
But this year, I'm going to do it for real.
I'll be on the show.
I'll apply like an amateur.
You have to apply.
For example, what are you thinking about?
I'm thinking about...
That...
D
I
This is a satin-like fabric, so it's hard to tell if it's good or not.
Look at the side.
Like this.
He's eating it now.
It's like this inside.
Even if you go like this,
if you look at this side, you can tell it's Kameleon.
Is this a gym?
Yes.
It's the hardest to tell if it's Kameleon or not.
It's hard to tell if it's Kameleon or not.
No, no, no.
I can't do this.
It's hard to tell if it's Kameleon or not.
Hey!
You ate it, didn't you?
Look at the front.
It's like this inside.
You can't do this at all.
It's hard to tell if it's Kameleon or not.
Look at the back.
Are you going to quit or not?
What are you going to do?
Are you going to do it or not?
If you're going to do it, take this.
Take this.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to do it.
It's hard to tell if it's Kameleon or not.
Dad, are you done?
Are you done?
Yes, I'm done.
Let's meet at the main line.
I'll do my best.
I'm not going to pay.
Who's going to pay?
Good evening.
Nice to meet you.
I'm from Amagasaki.
I'm number 67.
Number 67, Hitoshi Matsumoto.
The title is Kameleon.
He's lost his way.
Come on.
Thank you.
He's angry, he's angry.
What should I do at the main line?
To be honest, there's something exactly the same as this about 10 times.
What is it?
Exactly the same.
What should I do?
I don't know if it's funny or not.
It's not very funny.
What's that?
A fly?
I don't know.
I don't think it needs to move.
It doesn't need to move.
It doesn't hurt, does it?
It doesn't hurt at the main line.
It's a little more fashionable costume.
The wings are attached here.
That's why we're going to make a million yen.
I've been in the theater for three days.
I skipped it.
Thank you very much.
Did you see that?
It was cold.
It was like a human being.
That's it.
I'm looking forward to the results.
I'm going to my next job.
Thank you very much.
I got lost in the way.
Come on.
Thank you very much.
This is the making.
Everyone was laughing, but it was really embarrassing.
What do you think of this?
What do you think?
No?
You're cold right now.
Shall we bring it?
Let's bring it.
I'm really nervous.
Please.
Thank you very much.
It's amazing.
It says Matsumoto Hitoshi.
That's right.
Everyone's excited.
Especially the staff.
If you really pass this, you'll be able to see it again.
Of course, you'll have to practice more.
I wonder how it will be.
I'm nervous.
Can I open it?
I'm doing it with Matsumoto Hitoshi.
What?
You're the only one who can see it.
How do you get it out?
Wait a minute.
I brought a chameleon here today.
Let's get it out.
Let's get the chameleon out.
And then I'll come out.
I'll get it out at that time.
It's cute, isn't it?
That's what it was.
That's why when I went to the preliminary round the other day, the judges told me that I didn't have to spin it.
I don't have to move.
Let's get the chameleon out.
Let me see the inside.
The inside is like this.
It's like a poop helmet.
This is a mouth, so I'm going to poke this inside.
It's well made.
It's like this.
So, is it a pass or a fail?
Get inside.
Get out of here.
I'll get it out.
I can't stand it.
Let's see.
It's a pain in the ass.
If it's a fail, it's a chameleon.
I was wrong.
That's right.
Now, let's put the chameleon on.
I did my best.
What is this?
It's doubled.
Don't peek.
It's a pain in the ass.
I don't like it.
So, we did our best.
We did our best.
What's the result?
The result is...
Where is it?
I can't find it.
So, you're saying that the chameleon is doubled and the chameleon is doubled.
I know that.
Hurry up.
I'm going to announce it.
Where is it?
Why?
It's dirty.
What is the result?
It's doubled.
I can't do it.
Please take a look at it!
I don't know why, but I wonder if this line came out or something.
Did you mess it up?
That's good too.
Well, that's about it.
Well, I think you all have it in your hearts, but it's all Hamada's fault.
What? Why?
I don't think there's such a bad tongue.
I told you, didn't I? It comes out in 0.5 seconds.
Can you do it?
Hey, hey, hey!
You're kidding me, aren't you?
Are you used to being lost on the road?
In other words, you can eat even those who are lost on the road.
I'm in this world of weak meat and strong food.
Don't say stupid things.
I don't care.
What should we do with the 31st episode?
I'll be on the 31st episode.
That's right.
Well, it's 9.
It's in the fall.
From today towards the fall.
Oh, from today?
That's right. Our leader is starting from today.
You look like a high school detective.
Of course.
I'll do it.
Do you want to do it?
Yeah.
What about next time?
It's a waste, isn't it?
Should I give this to you as a gift?
The guy who gave this to me did the same thing and won the championship.
Let's introduce the postcards.
I don't have much time today, so I can only do one or two.
Don't do that.
Oh, I see.
Let's go this way.
Takahashi from Tokyo.
Is this called Chikoto?
Yeah.
Don't you have a concert?
Don't you release the record anymore?
You've released two records so far, haven't you?
I can't have a concert, so I'm having a hard time.
You came to Tokyo in October this year.
Yeah.
If you can, let's have a concert in Tokyo.
That's what I'm saying.
I don't trust him, so I don't want to do it.
What are you talking about?
You're trying to lie.
I'm really trying my best, but you're lying.
Then why don't you do your best at the rehearsal?
When I had my first concert, I did my best at the rehearsal.
At the end of the show, the two of us cried because we were moved.
There are times like that.
We're just angry.
It was really good.
The audience was crying, and we were moved.
That's true.
We shook hands and hugged each other.
There are times like that.
At that time, I thought I was going to die.
When I was hugged by you.
The staff was crying.
When I came to the dressing room, I was still in a state where I couldn't cool down.
I was still in a state where my tears were still left.
The man who was crying until a while ago.
What do you think he did right after the concert?
He was pooping.
When I asked him where Hamada had gone, he said,
Puripuri.
I don't want to do a concert with a human being.
I was nervous, but when I was done, I was relieved.
That's not a lie.
I did my best.
Everyone was crying at the venue, and I was pooping in the back.
That's true.
I think it's okay to hold a concert in Tokyo.
I don't know if I'll hold a concert in Tokyo this year.
If I hold a concert in Tokyo, I'll promote it again.
I would like everyone to come to Tokyo.
That's all for today.
What's going on?
I don't know what to say.
Aoki.
Just one.
Do you know Aoki?
He's a professional golfer.
Let's play with Aoki.
Don't get angry.
After playing golf, I came to interview you.
I won the tournament.
I put it in.
I won.
Congratulations on winning.
Don't get angry.
Thank you very much.
That's all for today.
That's too bad.
Did you know all the bad things about this concert?
Did you know?
I knew.
Next time is for sure.
The 31st time.
I'll do my best.
Next time is for sure.
For sure?
You're a bad guy.
I don't know how many times you've changed your mind.
So, there's someone who wants a chameleon.
Really?
Yes, number 67.
I'll write down the number of people who want it.
No.
The number of people who want a chameleon.
And number of people who want a helmet.
Write down the number of people who want it.
I'll write down the number of people who want it.
You should put your wings on that.
That's silly!
I wonder if I'll be able to fly.
What do you mean?
I'll be like, I'm lost.
A birdman.
I'm lost!
I'm having fun.
That's all for today.
This has been downtown.
Until next time, goodbye!
I'll be waiting for you tomorrow.