The first shot.
The second shot.
The third shot.
The fourth shot.
The fifth shot.
The sixth shot.
The seventh shot.
The eighth shot.
The eighth.
The ninth.
Let's see...
The eighth shot...
Next one is Glen.
It is okay!
I feel it!
I want to see the big one.
I can't do it.
It's hard.
NIIIIIIIIIEE
I don't know what you are talking about.
I don't want to know.
What the hell is this?
Ouch!
Be quiet!
Which one should I start with?
Let's start with this one.
Ouch!
Be quiet!
What the hell is this?
Ouch!
Be quiet!
What the hell is this?
Ouch!
Why is it so big?
What the hell is this?
Tanaka, pull it like this.
Pull it like this.
Ouch!
Not yet!
Pull it from the front.
At the end of the second round, 18 stories were revealed.
The results are...
Heipo 6 times.
Endo 5 times.
Matsumoto 3 times.
Yamasaki 2 times.
Tanaka 2 times.
Hamada 0 times.
Say?
Say!
I can't see anything.
This is it.
Oh, this is it.
Let's take off the gloves.
I can't see anything.
Please don't do this.
Be quiet.
I can't see anything.