It's already the end of the year.
What do you mean?
Everyone knows that, right?
Does anyone have a stomachache?
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
It's been a while since we've met, right?
Yes.
It's been about four days.
This is the first time I've said this, but I don't think I've done anything good this year.
Why?
I haven't done anything good.
It's only been a little while since it started.
It's been a while since we've met, right?
I moved to a new house.
What about the auction?
I saw it.
It's a one-room apartment.
You're lying.
It's a 7.5-story apartment.
It's a mid-sized apartment.
It's a mezzanine type apartment.
It's a woman.
It's a female student.
When I woke up, the ceiling hit me.
I asked her if she wanted a pot.
She said she was going to the eastern part.
She's alone.
She's alone, but she has two daughters.
They're playing with each other.
She said she'd give her to her wife in the new year.
She said she was going to the hot spring.
She has two daughters.
The upper child is calm.
The lower child is still a little tired.
She has three or four children.
She's still a little tired.
I had a bad feeling.
Kim was drinking wine next to me.
I put it on the carpet.
Bang!
The red wine on the carpet that I had just moved.
Please forgive me.
I was in a bad mood.
I had to put it on the carpet because I had a child.
I was angry.
I saw the red wine on the carpet.
Why are you sad?
I didn't think I would be angry.
It doesn't matter if you're angry.
It's what old people do.
It's okay.
It's okay if you know.
I understand.
I'm going to take care of the eastern part.
Please apologize to the old man on the spot.
That doctor said,
It doesn't matter if you apologize.
I don't understand why you don't want to apologize.
Shut up.
You don't want to apologize?
It's a lie.
The next day, I was in Guam. I was really worried about the stain.
Why? Don't do that to yourself.
Yu came to me.
He told me to sprinkle salt on him.
He sprinkled salt on me.
I was like, is this for real?
Look at this! Look at this!
You were able to take it off, right?
I used a vacuum cleaner and sprinkled salt on him.
The stain was clean.
It was clean.
After a few hours, I had to go to Narita.
I was really worried.
I was really worried about the stain.
No, that's not true.
It was like Gorbachev.
It's just a little stain.
It's not that big.
That's all.
No, no, no. I went to Guam. I went to Guam. The weather was bad.
Oh, really?
The weather was really bad. The people in Guam were surprised.
The weather was like this in the middle of the month.
It was raining all day.
I had a cold.
Oh, really?
Guam has a cold, right?
But I was burning up.
The weather was good for about two days.
After about five days, the next three days were always raining.
It's the worst when you catch a cold in Guam.
Ishida was also coming from Osaka.
He said, let's play.
He was playing ballet.
I bought it.
I bought it and said I could eat anything.
When I went to Chuka, my nose was stuffed and I couldn't taste it at all.
No, I'm full.
That's all.
You know my first dream?
No, I don't know.
It's the dream where Dondoko's Yamaguchi beat Hikuson.
I don't understand the meaning.
I'm watching it at the venue.
I'm telling you to do your best.
I don't understand the meaning.
But you're happy, aren't you?
I'm happy, but I'm telling you.
I'm telling you, but I can't.
I can't say anything.
Where have you been?
I went to Kobe.
Kobe?
What?
I saved money again.
Do you want so much money?
It doesn't matter if I go to Kobe.
It's okay to go to Kobe.
Are you a movie star?
I'm not.
It's a movie star.
It's not cool.
I think it was on the screen.
It was on the screen.
It disappeared suddenly.
I don't understand the meaning.
I'm telling you to do your best.
I'm telling you, but I can't say anything.
It was hard.
Did you go to Kobe?
I don't understand the meaning.
I went to Universal Studios.
Are you going to the movie theater?
I'm going.
Are you a movie star?
I've been there before.
I've been there.
I was a bad guy when I was young.
What is a bad guy?
You have a family and children.
I have a family and children.
Children are stupid.
I'm not stupid.
Let's have him take it out.
He didn't say anything last year.
I still don't know his name.
This is a question for Mr. Matsumoto, who especially likes hunting.
It seems that Yoshimoto Kogyo once led a group of comedians to hunt in the mountains. What were you looking for?
Well, I've said this a few times before, but when I read this letter, the customer's appetite was this bad.
I'm not interested.
I can't tell people who aren't hungry that this food is delicious.
I don't think that's the case.
Really?
That's because Yoshimoto...
He's a member of the board of directors of comedians.
I see.
Mr. Kiyoshi.
What?
Yes, yes.
Kibouga.
Kibouga was looking for Helen.
I didn't participate.
At that time.
I went into the mountains and saw it.
Kanoko saw it.
Oh, this guy.
I can't chase after Kanoko.
But I lost sight of Kanoko.
I went into the mountains and saw it.
Helen.
How many times did you say Helen?
I'm sorry.
I wasn't looking for it.
But I found it.
Well, you found it, but it was dead.
It was dead.
It's okay.
I won't fight you until the end.
Is that so?
You've been dating a lot of comedians.
Among them, you had the hardest time breaking up.
Please show us a picture of you breaking up.
Well, after all, I'm an old woman.
Don't say that.
What?
You're married now, aren't you?
That's right.
Before that?
Before that.
I was wearing a little bit of makeup.
You were wearing makeup?
Yes.
You were wearing makeup, right?
That's right.
You're being beaten up.
Well, that's right.
Where did you end up?
What?
I went to the library.
Why did you go to the library?
I don't know why I went to the library.
Did you go to the library?
I went to the library.
A woman came to the library.
Why did you talk to her?
She came to me.
I see.
Why?
She said something amazing.
Approach?
Approach.
That's right.
And then you dated her?
Well, that's right.
That's right.
I said I wanted to break up with her.
You did?
Yes.
About two years ago.
You haven't dated her for two years?
You should have told me earlier.
Yes.
But...
It was a one-time thing.
No matter what I said.
That's right.
It's a little funny.
You said thank you at the end.
How did you end up breaking up with her?
What?
I had a hard time.
I see.
I had her buy me a lot of things.
You're so mean.
What are you talking about?
What?
You had a lot of things.
That's right.
You're so mean.
I had a lot of things, like a car.
I had good memories of her.
If you say that, you'll end up breaking up with her.
If I say I have good memories of her?
Even though we broke up?
No, no, no.
If I say I have good memories of her?
There were a lot.
What kind of memories?
We had a good chemistry.
We had a good chemistry?
Yes.
How did you end up breaking up with her?
I had a good chemistry with her.
Your voice is loud.
Ah, this is loud.
It's like a voice that pierces the darkness.
It's like Gao.
You're a foreigner.
This is hard.
Your nipples were amazing.
It was like an indie dance.
Why?
It was amazing.
Really?
You broke up because you didn't like it?
Of course, of course.
I actually liked the indie dance.
I see.
There was no reason for it.
We dated for two and a half years.
I didn't know.
I knew you were cheating on me.
Ah, at that time.
Yes, yes, yes.
So I was being played.
I see, I see.
I was the only one who had an indie dance.
You have an indie dance?
Yes.
Well, that's good.
It was like a pistachio.
It's getting bigger and bigger.
I'm sorry to ask such a stupid question.
What's going on in the afterlife?
I don't think I've ever talked about this before.
Oh, really?
If you talk about the afterlife,
everyone calls it Samba Tetsurou.
Yes, yes, yes.
But to be honest,
Samba Tetsurou is not a big deal.
Is what he's saying true?
It's almost a lie.
Really?
Yes.
What's a lie?
For example.
What is it?
Please tell me the right thing.
The afterlife.
Oh, that's fine.
In the end, the afterlife is
basically the same as now.
You can say it's exactly the same.
I see.
But everyone has a bad face.
And it's exactly the same.
There's a convenience store.
Really?
Yes.
Basically.
There's also going to hell.
Oh, yes, yes.
What about that? Are you really going to hell?
No, that's true.
But basically, it's almost the same as now.
Even if you go to hell?
Even if you go to hell,
it's almost the same.
If it's the same, there's no point in going to hell.
If you go to hell, you'll get beaten up.
Should I change that?
If you don't change it,
it's because your face is bad.
Should I change it?
Is it that bad?
You can always change it.
Please change it.
What is it?
If your face is bad, it's okay.
But if you live the same life,
it's a little different.
Based on what you just said?
Basically, I don't have a good appetite today.
But I'll figure something out.
You'll figure something out.
Right?
I'll figure something out.
I'll do that.
What do you want to do?
I'll start with something.
I'll do anything.
Is it a world of work?
Yes.
Please.
Is there heaven and hell?
You can start from there.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's said that there is.
There is.
There is?
Yes.
But there is a difference, right?
Of course.
There is an absolute difference.
Please tell me about it.
The absolute difference is the T-shirt.
Are you wearing a heaven T-shirt or a hell T-shirt?
Who did you get that from?
From a demon.
There is a demon at a branch store.
At that time, you ask if it's M or L.
I just saw it.
You keep asking if it's M or L.
I just want to wear it roughly.
I want to wear it roughly.
I'm sorry.
So what?
If you get a hell T-shirt, you get hell.
And you're going to hell.
Yes, yes, yes.
To be honest, I'm going to hell.
I've done a lot of bad things.
You've done a lot of bad things.
I've killed 12 people.
I'm going to hell.
Why?
Why are you going to hell?
I'm going to hell.
You're going to hell.
What are you saying?
Matsumoto-san, who has always been careful when using words...
...tell me how to use it in our everyday conversation.
What is that in your everyday conversation?
People often say Inoki Bombaye, right?
Actually, there are many people who don't understand the meaning.
I don't understand, I don't understand. What?
What?
Inoki Bombaye.
Well, I'm saying it because it makes sense.
What is it? Tell me.
What is it? Inoki Bombaye.
Inoki Bombaye!
Bombaye!
It's embarrassing to say it.
It's not embarrassing at all.
Inoki Bombaye.
What is it?
There are things you use in your daily life, right?
Tell me.
When do you use Inoki Bombaye?
In your daily conversation.
Tell me.
Do you use it?
I heard how to use it.
Oh, that's how you use it.
Well, for example, where are you going?
What?
Well, where are you going with you today?
Where are you going?
Well, I'm going to the amusement park.
Oh, the amusement park.
Let's go to the amusement park.
There are a lot of places to use in the amusement park.
Really?
Yes.
How do you use it?
Well, for example, what do you want to ride?
What do you want to ride?
What do you want to ride today?
Well, the roller coaster.
Let's go on the roller coaster.
Well, I wonder where the roller coaster is.
Bombaye.
What?
Where is the roller coaster?
Well, that's...
I'm sorry.
The roller coaster is...
Bombaye.
What?
Oh, this way?
Bombaye.
It's better to say, I'm sorry.
You can use it for anything.
That's right.
It doesn't mean anything.
Is that what it means?
What do you mean?
If we say it like this,
I'm sorry.
It's close to, I'm sorry.
Why?
Why did you say, I'm sorry, Inoki?
What?
You said, I'm sorry, Inoki.
That's why you came in.
That's right.
I don't understand.
Why?
I'm sorry, Inoki.
You shouldn't apologize for that.
Why?
What?
Why shouldn't I apologize?
Well, you're already losing with your chin.
You don't have a chin, but you say, I'm sorry, Inoki, just like Inoki.
What?
You're crazy.
That's not it.
What are you talking about?
Inoki can do a lot of things.
That's right.
Right?
If it's Inoki, everyone here can do a lot of things.
That's right.
But what about you and me?
Have you ever lost to Inoki?
Raise your hand if you have.
You haven't.
Inoki has forgiven you for that.
That's strange.
That's why I said, I'm sorry, Inoki.
I'm really sorry.
You're sorry for being forgiven.
Inoki knows how to use Bombayi, but in the amusement park, he says, I'm sorry, Bombayi.
That's the only way you can use it.
You can use it anywhere else.
Where do you use it?
I know how to use it now, if you explain the reason.
I'm sorry.
Bombayi.
Where's the jet box?
It's over there.
Bombayi.
I know that.
Where else do you use it?
It's getting cold, isn't it?
It's Bombayi.
What?
Why are you holding it?
It's Bombayi.
That's strange.
I don't understand.
You said it in the morning.
It's not good weather today.
It's Bombayi.
How many times?
I don't understand how you use it.
I don't understand.
I understand.
It's not good weather today.
I don't understand.
It's strange.
I understand the elevator.
Why did you go to the train station?
I understand that.
Coffee.
Yes.
Do you have a cigarette?
It's a super light.
I don't understand.
I understand.
The coffee was cheap.
It's Bombayi.
That's strange.
Why is it strange?
It's not Bombayi.
It's strange.
Mothers use it a lot.
When you wake up in the morning,
it's Bombayi.
It's Bombayi.
I don't understand.
I don't understand your last word.
It's Bombayi.
I don't understand.
It's not Bombayi.
How many times?
How many times do I have to tell you?
It's Bombayi.
My mother is a noisy person.
What the hell are you doing?