Hey, where are you going?
I'm sorry.
What?
What are you doing?
I'm Kendo.
Oh!
Can you do it?
I can do it.
I'm really strong.
Do you have a Nandan?
No, I don't have that.
Excuse me.
You don't have a Nandan?
I was the head of the club when I was in middle school.
Really?
Yes.
Excuse me.
I talked to the two of them today.
But you don't have a job.
We don't.
We don't do that.
You're going to do your best, right?
No, I won't quit.
What?
I'm going to do my best with you two.
You're not going to quit?
I'm not asking you to quit.
Hey!
I'm sorry.
I'm going to do my best next year.
It's hard to go up.
It's hard.
The top is full.
That's right.
Many people from Osaka to Yoshimoto are coming to Tokyo.
I think that's one of the reasons.
If that person is gone, we can go up.
Honestly, the top section.
It's Hong Kong.
Hong Kong?
Why?
I sometimes get in touch at work, but I hate it.
You guys are so annoying.
We eat together on the special show.
I'm concentrating on the show.
But he keeps looking at me.
He asks me how I'm doing.
That's not true.
I can't concentrate on the show.
When we're on the show together,
he's looking at me like this.
Really?
He's looking back at me.
We don't look at each other.
We can't look at each other.
I'll show you today.
That's strange.
Mr. Kuraoka is coming to Japan Electric today.
He has a camera in his school.
We're going there now.
Mr. Kuraoka doesn't know.
I'll show you how much he hates Hong Kong.
He doesn't hate Hong Kong.
I'll see how much he hates Hong Kong.
Then we'll make a decision.
Yes, please.
I'll show you how much he hates Hong Kong.
Then we'll do it.
This program is brought to you by the sponsor you are watching.
Good morning.
Are you okay?
Are you sick?
No, I'm not.
We came here to see you.
We heard that you were sick.
I have a cold.
Are you sick again?
I have a cold again.
I have a cold all year round.
Do you have a sandwich?
You know that, don't you?
I'm not busy.
I only have three sandwiches.
Do you understand?
I don't know if I can win.
I don't know the content.
I know a little about the content.
How many years has it been?
It's been six years.
It hurts.
I don't care if you hit me in the head.
Why are you laughing?
I told you to hit me in the head.
I'm angry.
I'm kidding.
We're not kidding.
You're the only one who's excited.
It's my fault.
I can't see you.
You guys are busy with work.
It's over today, so I'm going to take a rest for seven days.
Seven days?
It's been seven days.
It's terrible.
I think so, too.
This is not good.
I don't intend to do that.
It's always like that.
I'm going to give this back to you.
Let's all work together and send it back.
Is that okay?
I don't know what you're talking about.
We don't know what you're talking about.
Thank you very much.
I have a sense of justice.
Don't move.
What?
You're fat.
You're not going to eat it, are you?
Why are you so fat?
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
Don't hit me.
It hurts.
Are you really going to eat this?
I'm not going to eat it.
What are you doing?
It hurts.
I'm going to send you back.
Why?
If you're here, my juniors will have a hard time working.
I'm going to send you back.
You first.
Don't move.
It hurts.
What are you doing?
I'm going to send you back.
It hurts.
I won't do it.
I'll wrap theん in your mouth.
we hew his.
Are you okay?
I'm fat, why don't you do that?
I thought he would die.
OK.
I'm going to leave it here.
This refrigerated food was bought at the store.
Let's cool it down.
It's good that it's fresh.
It's not fresh, is it?
It's not fresh.
He's saying it's hot.
Is he saying it's hot?
It's smelly.
Let's put it on.
He's saying it's hot.
It's hot.
Stand up.
Don't do that.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
I can hear your voice.
If you come back with this, we'll have to do it again.
I'm the only one who can do it.
The staff will be like, good job.
No one can say that.
But he's really going to the NGK.
I'm a little worried now.
Is it really hot?
It's hot.
Don't do that.
Is it hot?
He's really enjoying it.
The other day, the player, well, those who watched the show will know,
He made ramen.
He made it, right?
Well, I'm sorry, everyone.
We were also surprised.
It was so sweet.
It's strange that miso and soy sauce are wrong.
I thought it was dirty.
Well, that's fine.
I didn't react well to the back.
I went faster than I thought.
I wasn't shaking properly.
You weren't shaking.
I wasn't shaking.
I was shaking.
The next day, my stomach was pretty...
It was a strange thing.
My stomach was pretty...
Your stomach is fine.
I know your stomach.
I had to stop the pain with painkillers.
It was a terrible thing.
I called an ambulance.
You're lying.
I didn't call an ambulance.
I was about to call an ambulance.
I went that far.
I was about to throw up.
I thought it was strange.
It was strange.
I laughed, too.
I don't know where the staff is now.
What do you want me to do?
Money.
Why is that?
Do you pay with money?
20 million yen.
Are you a fool?
Why?
Why 20 million yen?
It was really hard.
I sat with the first and second guests.
We sat apart like this.
The first guest finished.
I didn't talk much.
He said to me from here.
I had a hard time.
What happened?
That kid's ramen the other day.
It was really hard.
I have a basic physical strength.
I can't stand it.
I have a sense of justice.
My stomach hurts.
I have a sense of duty.
A sense of duty?
I don't know.
I have a sense of duty.
It was really hard.
That's how it was behind the scenes.
It was a behind-the-scenes story.
If I didn't get hit, it would have been a mistake.
You look ugly.
You look ugly, too.
I have a feeling.
I think I'm going to have a heart attack.
Don't look at my face.
You don't look like a man.
No one said that.
You think so, right?
That's right.
But I'll be clear.
You look like a man.
You look like a handsome man.
I don't understand.
What do you mean?
You look like a handsome man.
I think you're a handsome man.
You look like a man when you're on TV.
You look like you're being watched.
You look like a fool.
It took me about two hours to put on makeup.
That's why I look better when I'm on TV.
You look better when you're on TV.
I don't know.
I haven't put on makeup yet.
To be honest, it's hard.
I can't do it.
Sometimes I feel like I'm going to stand up.
I can't tell the difference.
I'm excited.
Is this a movie?
To be honest, I'm glad I became a talent.
That's not true.
That's not true at all.
It's the Olympics again.
You got a gold medal today.
That's right.
I think it's amazing if it's meaningful.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Please continue.
What are you doing?
There's a clay shooting.
I think it's a great movie.
There's something like that.
Do you understand?
For example, in a marathon, everyone runs.
I think it's amazing that it's fast.
I think it's okay to admit it.
But there's a game that I don't understand.
What are you going to use it for in real life?
For example, there's a girl.
It's like this.
I understand.
Calm down.
I'll wrap you up in a bus.
There's no difference.
When you come back.
When are you going to use it?
It's good if you go to a ski resort.
I don't have to do this.
If you do that, it's this.
If you do that, it's curling.
That's what you're doing in your life.
My mother will be happy.
I'll do this, so you go in.
I'm in trouble if you do this.
I'm not in trouble.
Curling itself is strange.
I'm making a big one.
If you do that, it's round.
If you roll that and go to the other side.
I was told what to do.
What are you doing?
I've been watching you all the time.
I don't know what to do.
I'm going to do something.
Do you understand if I look at you?
I don't understand.
There's a lot of games.
What's going on?
I don't understand.
What are you guys?
Ryuji?
Who is Ryuji?
I'm the one who says yes.
I'm not going to apologize.
I'm sorry. Apologize.
I don't want to talk.
I'm sorry.
Ryuji?
What is it?
I'm sorry.
Say yes.
I understand.
I'll do everything.
No.
One person is going to slide down the slope.
I see.
Is there such a scene?
Yes.
I've never seen it.
I don't like it.
Why are you scared?
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
You.
I'm sorry. I was just playing around.
I've been doing this for a while now, and everyone's crying.
The other day, I cried because of the speed.
I lost my speed.
What would you do if you were taken by a camera on a highway?
Have you ever been taken by an Obis?
Of course I have.
Really?
When I was in Osaka, I couldn't make it in a few months.
Were you on my side?
I was clearly in the picture.
I was asked to take a picture.
Someone next to me asked me if I knew him.
I looked at him and said, it's you.
I was clearly in the picture.
I don't remember at all.
You were clearly in the picture.
What would you do if you were taken by an Obis?
I was clearly in the picture.
I looked at him and saw the owner of the car.
I called him.
You were wearing sunglasses.
What would you do if you were taken by an Obis?
I've never done that.
I'm a fool.
I always drive like this.
I don't think this is right.
I drive like this.
Why?
I don't know.
I want to hide my nose.
If you were in the picture, you would have been taken by an Obis.
This is dangerous.
It's dangerous.
If you were in the picture, you would have been taken by an Obis.
Why?
I don't know.
I think it's an expression.
There is an expression.
I don't hate him.
I forgive him.
If you were in the picture, you would have been taken by an Obis.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Don't let go of my hand.
If you were in the picture, you would have been taken by an Obis.
If I were in the picture, I would have been taken by an Obis.
I'm sorry.
Let's talk.
I thought it was dangerous.
I thought you were in the picture.
I'm running at a high speed, so I can catch the speed.
I think so.
You should do this at that high speed.
Of course.
I want to raise the speed limit a little before that.
The speed limit is 40km per hour.
It's not a problem if you run so fast.
Is that so?
There are a lot of them running around
Yes, they are running around
Even when they turn, it's so hot
Are you holding the net upside down?
If you drop it, it's hot
Where are you going?
You're holding the net
I have a question for Matsumoto-san
Matsumoto-san, when you're talking with your friends like Shizuoka, Shizuoka, Shizuoka, and Janet Jackson
You have a face that says, yes, yes
Matsumoto-san, tell us where your strike zone is
I have a face that says, yes, yes
Do you have a face that says, yes, yes?
You're saying amazing things
Normally I wouldn't say that
I have a face that says, yes, yes
Wait a minute
Let's look at the bottom
Do you have Yamada Hanako?
I don't have one
I don't have one either
Do you have Kisamoto?
I don't have Kisamoto
You don't have Kisamoto?
I don't have one
I don't have Kisamoto either
You can't do that
It's like that
It's like that?
When you say musical instrument, it's like a percussion instrument
I like musical instruments
Which one is a musical instrument?
Which one is the bottom?
Moriman
I don't have Moriman
I can't do Moriman
But I can do Taneumaman
I can't do it
I can't do Taneumaman
That's tough
Because there's a pig, it looks like a horse
But it's this one
I know it's tough
But I think Taneumaman is better
Please
You don't know that, right?
At 4 or 5 in the morning
Who is it?
It's Taneumaman
I can't do it
Which one is a musical instrument?
I don't need a musical instrument
I can't do it
That one
I'm very depressed
It's like a new car has been wrecked