The usual music room
What's up?
What are you doing?
Nothing. I'm in the past.
What is that?
This is amazing.
This is a celebrity safari park.
What is that?
What is this?
I didn't say anything.
It says, please enjoy the entertainers who are active at night.
When you drive a car, you can meet a lot of entertainers.
Really?
If it's normal, it's normal.
It says, please get close to the entertainers who are powerful.
What?
It's hard to understand.
It's all about meaning.
So you can go by your own car.
Like a night safari.
Lock the door and never get out of the car.
What?
There's a cameraman?
So you're like an animal?
Like a lion or a tiger.
No, no, no.
But you're interested in this, right?
Well, if you have it now, you won't make it.
If you have it now, you won't make it.
If you use the highway, you won't make it.
Are you going?
I should go.
I want to see it.
The opening I was going to do today is also a mess.
I quit.
I'm not thinking about that.
Do you always think about the opening of a mess?
If that's the case, let's stop.
I want to go.
I'm fine.
I'm going to drive.
Really?
I want to go.
Let's go.
This is amazing.
It's amazing if it's real.
I feel something.
It's so hot.
What is this?
This is the house.
It's open.
This is it.
It's a celebrity's safari car.
It's so well made.
It doesn't feel salty at all.
This is my first time seeing this.
Is this really possible?
What is this?
A person who receives the night safari and receives the guidance of the park.
The park will proceed according to the guidance of the park.
It's okay to stay like this, right?
Please put it in front of the car.
In front of the car, right?
Then let's go.
So you will guide us?
Yes
I'm looking forward to it
Are you recording?
Yes, we are
It's OK
I don't want to be late
Thank you for coming to the entertainment park today
There are many celebrities in the park
Please don't go out
Please enjoy the entertainment park.
How much is this? 20kg?
This is not good.
I can't see it.
I'm a little nervous.
Was it 1000 yen?
1400 yen.
It depends on the price.
It depends on the entertainer.
Sh倉回 Understood, I see that.
By Buddhism is the same as the human race is, so it seems to know, But Iweight people are possible.
What are also many places is express,
Did you feel gone as well,
It comes with a lost.
Is this a celebrity?
Stop it.
Who is this?
I don't know.
Umezu Sakae
His main job is a stage actor.
He is known for his overalls and his coolness.
He looks like a modern person and has a very human personality.
I can't imagine his clumsy moves, but he is surprisingly skillful and has a T-shirt design.
He likes grilled sea bream, and konpeito.
He eats konpeito.
But he is cute.
He is cute.
Really.
He is affectionate.
He is used to it.
He is getting close.
Wow! it's quite a fright!
this is a little frightful
I should hear a lot of DuHab Netta
now coming
such face OK, Arthur Shang
No! no! What the Walk!
Get a flash!
Wow, guys watching!
Magnificient
Cried
Wow, WORLD's scary
What's that?
He looks so sad.
He had this kind of face?
Wait, wait.
I'm going to take a picture.
Ah, sorry.
Take a picture. Take a picture.
Ah, amazing. He just laughed.
He laughed, right?
He laughed completely.
Ah, scary.
He's so friendly.
Ah, what's that?
Minju?
Ah, that T-shirt.
That's the design.
Ah, I've heard of it.
You've heard of it?
Did you get it?
Wait a minute.
Don't cut it.
I'm scared.
Just a little bit.
Not yet.
It's a different version.
You dug it up.
I did it.
It's amazing.
It's not here.
This is...
That's right.
It's so beautiful.
Just the two of us.
So let's go!
It's moving!
It's moving, right?
It's moving.
Do you want to go for the moment?
Right now is fine.
Here we go!
It's fine, it's fine.
Let's go!
It's moving.
It is.
It's going to push.
Yeah, it will push.
Wow.
But this T-shirt is like a photo taken in the past.
It's a little bit up.
This is the last memory of summer.
It was amazing.
You took off the seat belt, right?
I took off the seat belt.
So I had a face on the side.
I thought it was a real face.
Be careful when you go out.
Let's be careful.
Let's take a picture.
Take a picture of the microphone.
Really.
I'm on my way out.
Ah, here he comes!
What is it?
What is this?
I heard something.
Who is it?
Tarzan Yamamoto.
Tarzan hates taking a bath.
He hates it.
Among the celebrities, he is particularly violent.
When he gets excited, he gets up in the middle of the event and makes the staff of the pub get up.
He is the editor of the proletariat.
He appears in erotic magazines.
His subordinate is sleeping with his wife.
The details of this situation have not been revealed yet.
We have to explain it.
I was told that I was going to be in danger.
I'm a violent person.
I'll take a picture of you.
I'll get off the car and go closer.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
I don't think I can move.
If you think it's dangerous, don't come.
Be careful.
If you come, close the door.
I know.
Shut your mouth!
Hey! stop it!
Are these entanglement OK?
Let's see.
They don't like our
Scary!
Oh no!
No!
Oh no, he's here.
Hey!
We're in trouble!
It's a blackout!
It's all automatic!
It's scary!
No, no, it's scary!
You're so angry!
Scary!
It's so scary!
It's scary!
I'm scared!
No, no, no!
Wow!
That was amazing!
Let's go!
Hurry!
I'm scared!
That was scary!
That was a miracle!
A miracle!
This is scary!
The moment of the zugi!
The moment of the zugi! This is terrible!
A miracle!
This is terrible!
Let's not call Miyami out of the blue.
Yeah, we shouldn't violate the rules.
We should call Yoko and cause an accident.
We'll get in trouble.
It's like a huge fog!
This is so cool.
Something is moving.
It's moving.
It's eating rice.
It's slowly getting bigger.
It's eating rice!
He used to be the main character of adult videos.
Nice is too much!
He was a very nice guy.
He was too nice!
Nice! Nice! Nice!
Too nice!
He said, too nice!
Please wait!
The end is a series of shots!
Wow!
Just push it down.
This is how it's done.
It's too nice!
Let's take a picture together.
I want to take a picture!
Let's go.
The camera is not ready yet.
It hurts!
I wanted to get a lot of this!
Wow!
That was really good!
That was good!
That was rare!
It was the first time!
That was amazing!
That was really high!
You're really energetic!
Even though you couldn't break the moth!
You can get that much out of just pushing it!
It's a very emotional scene.
It's amazing.
There's a person in the game.
What's wrong?
There's something moving over there.
There's something moving.
What?
What is it?
Something is moving.
What you are seeing is not a real unscrupulous criminal.
He is a comedian called Kannazuki who is good at playing the guitar.
He is a member of the same group as Kikuo, and he is also good at drawing like Masahiro Chono.
He is also good at drawing different types of guitars that are suitable for different environments.
I saw the video of him drawing.
What kind of guitar do you want me to play?
There's no such thing.
It's close. It's so close.
It's hard to get close.
It's close.
I can hear it.
What is that?
It's you, isn't it?
I saw it earlier.
It's gone.
That's right.
It's decided.
This is a good photo.
Wow, amazing!
The power!
Wow, you could take that!
This is the real power.
It's fun.
It was good.
I'm glad I didn't ignore it.
I thought it was a trick.
What's this?
What is it?
This is a group of mini-games.
They are not bad at all, but they don't know how to attract the attention.
They are trying to get rid of the taste buds.
Snack candy is their favorite.
They are very happy to give it to them.
Snack candy?
This is okay, right?
Let's go down.
This is okay.
This is cute.
They are having fun.
This is rude.
All of them are different species.
This is male, right?
We are looking for females.
But there are no females.
Hey, hey, hey.
Please give it to me. I want to eat it.
There are sweets.
You ate it.
He ate a lot.
He was hungry.
Wow, what a great appetite!
I was hungry!
You didn't cry at all, did you?
I didn't cry.
You didn't cry, did you?
Don't fight!
I don't want to eat such a thing.
I want it directly.
Directly?
That's right.
He fought! He fought!
Don't fight!
I don't want to fight!
He looks a little depressed.
Did he drink water?
I was angry for a moment.
You were angry?
I was pushed.
I was pushed and I was like...
I think there are some age differences between senior and junior.
Yes.
Different from the office.
That was tough.
I was angry for a moment.
It was like a
I was scared.
I was pushed.
I was pushed and I was like...
I think there are some age differences between senior and junior.
Yes.
Different from the office.
Now it's tough.
I don't like it.
It's like a gender-neutral relationship.
I wonder how to do it.
Stop the car and listen.
No, no, no.
Yes.
Z!
Huh?
Huh? What do you hear?
I hear something.
Ah! Something came out!
Huh?
Ah! It came out!
Z!
To hear the voice of the old man, many people from all over the country come to see him.
It's the first time I've heard it.
What kind of voice is that?
It's a voice that's not very common.
I'm looking for something.
It's the voice of an old man.
Z...
You can't say Z?
No, it's inside.
It's inside.
What is it?
Is it pointing at something?
It's looking straight ahead.
What is it?
Z!
You cried a lot!
You cried so much!
So much!
It's a rare cry.
There was a pattern like that.
What is this?
I was surprised.
Yoshizumiya.
Is it real?
I forgot the name again.
The person you are watching is not the real Yoshizumi Ishihara.
This is a celebrity named Kanazuki who is good at acting.
This is one of the two characters that Yoshizumi Ishihara plays.
I think that's enough.
The name of the actor is in the news.
You speak clearly.
I speak clearly.
I'll come to your live show.
You should go.
Wow, amazing.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Did you see your father?
I saw my father.
I saw him.
He speaks clearly.
That's a good picture.
Your father lives here, right?
That's right.
It's a bit surprising.
That's what happened.
Oh, there she is.
What?
She's a tsugai.
Tsugai, tsugai.
The wife of Ayako Zana is a Japanese female professional.
Her husband is a doctor.
Really?
In the Japanese family, the wife has overwhelming power.
Her husband is absolutely
She's a tsugai.
The mother-in-law is losing her posture of absolute obedience.
The wife is pregnant.
She is worried about the labor.
But she can see a cute baby at the end of the year.
At this time of the year,
I don't want to get close to her.
I'm scared.
I don't want to be a violent fighter.
What are you talking about?
Dangerous! Dangerous!
What are you doing?
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Don't say such things.
You can show it.
No, no, no. I'm sorry.
We can't move like that.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's finally done.
It's really...
Did you take a picture?
Yes, I did.
Then, from here...
Let's take a picture.
Oh, he's kissing her!
Ah!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
He was really close.
When he was kissed.
Ahahaha!
That's amazing.
It's so easy.
Okay, good.
That's good.
Thank you.
I saw it.
How many times did you fall here?
It's amazing.
Oh, he's kissing her.
Amazing!
There's a lot of people here.
But the people from Tatsuki are really popular.
That's right.
It's different from the ones you see in the studio.
It's more of a neighborhood feeling.
Wow!
Gida Yu.
He usually lives in a herd called Takeshigundan.
He likes to eat hot oden and spicy cream puffs.
That's not true.
He is a very violent person, and he is often attacked by the people around him.
Really?
Let's be careful.
Let's go to the side.
Gida-yu, you're wearing short hair for summer.
From there, from there.
He's eating something.
You!
Flash!
Gida-yu, too.
Gida-yu, you're so rough.
You should go.
Yes, it is, yes, let it goっ
Wow, that Viblerini might stop
I have no temporary
I go, I go
This time I'm going
It's scary, scary, scary
I can not, I can not, I am doing well
Wow!
It's crazy!
Why are you so angry?
It's like this.
This is a great photo!
This is scary!
When I saw this at Shimbashi in Nagano, I thought it was cold.
I'm a little...