Tonight's opening is Yamazaki vs. Kokoriko Endo's Gag Battle.
The final stage is nearing completion.
Yamazaki, are you okay with the Gag?
Are you okay?
I'm okay. Why do I have to fight Endo?
Today is the Gag Battle between Endo and Yamazaki.
This is the first time.
That's right.
I'm counting on you.
I won't lose.
To be honest, Yamazaki and Endo have the same character.
So I want to be sure.
Which one is better?
Wait a minute.
Is it that far?
That's right.
That's me.
I won't lose.
Ryu-san.
That's right.
I'm setting it up now.
At that time, a man suddenly stood up in front of everyone waiting for the set to be completed.
Excuse me.
Komurasaki-san is laughing and I can't set it up.
Can you hear me?
Who is laughing?
Komurasaki.
What if I go?
It's going to be hard.
Komurasaki-san is laughing.
That's good.
It's going to be hard.
Komurasaki Kozo, the director of Gaki no Tsukai.
When he was making the Gaki no Tsukai calendar, he appeared as a model in June.
He made everyone laugh.
And when he started laughing, everyone around him started laughing too.
He has a mysterious power.
I can't do this.
What's going on in downtown?
Let's talk for now.
Excuse me.
It's too late.
I can't set it up.
Sugai-san.
Yes.
Let's leave it at that.
It's cold.
I know.
Sugai-san, please.
Why are you drinking beer again?
It's in the way.
It's funny.
I'm drinking a lot.
I can't stand that smile.
What's going on?
Do it.
Komu-san.
I'm sorry.
Do it now.
I'm drunk.
I can't lose.
The damage caused by Komura-saki subsided and the setting of the stage was resumed.
Sugai-chan, are you okay now?
I'm fine now.
What's going on?
There was a car accident.
I went back to my hometown on New Year's Day.
I was spending time with my family.
That's my hometown.
That's your hometown.
What kind of hometown is that?
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
Komura-saki-san, you're smiling again.
What?
I told you earlier.
If he moves, it's over.
We have to go.
Yes.
Please.
It's such a town.
I'm sorry. It's not such a town.
Sugai-chan, say something.
I'm sorry.
What's that?
Are you drunk?
Komura-saki appears again and gets in the way.
What did he do this time?
What is this?
Why are you eating chocolate?
You're going to eat it, aren't you?
I'm hungry.
Sugai-chan, let's do it.
I know.
I can tell from the sign behind you.
Komura-saki is everywhere.
I'm from Edo.
Seriously.
Sugai-chan.
I'm sorry.
Please.
I got it.
I'm going to eat it.
You're going to eat it.
I know it's fun.
But you have to enjoy it over there.
I'm going to eat it.
What are you laughing at?
It's more fun when I'm going to eat it.
He returns to the bus and prepares again.
And the production of the set was done in a hurry.
I'm sorry.
You can't do that.
I don't want to get in the way of the staff.
That's right.
I'm so motivated.
You're so excited.
I'm excited.
Let's go.
Komura-saki is laughing.
This is a little...
It's a little awkward.
It's okay.
Let's go.
Let's do it right away.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
This time, it's a sudden down town.
He is nervous.
The staff around me are laughing at me.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
The staff around me are laughing at me.
Hey.
I can't do this.
Komura-san.
I can't listen to you.
I can't do this.
Komura.
Do it again.
I can't do this.
He laughed.
Why are you laughing?
I can't do this anymore.
Let's go home.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this anymore.
In the end, Ikko gave up this week's opening and went to the talk show.
Let's go home.
I'm sorry.
Be careful.
I'm sorry for saying harsh things.
I can't do this anymore.
Do you want to do it another week?
Why don't you do it again next week?
It's okay.
Let's go back to the talk show.
Let's go to the talk show today.
Yes, that's right.
When the bus with Ikko was about to head to the venue...
Excuse me.
What?
Please come here.
Excuse me. Please come here.
This is bad.
Hey!
Hey, hey!
Sugai-san, please...
Excuse me.
Please get out of here.
Let's think about it.
Come on.
Seriously.
Let's go. Let's go.
What is that?
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
Idiot! Idiot!
Like this?
I don't get it.
Isn't it too small?
The sound is too loud.
Let me talk.
It was good that the sound was loud.
Let's do it again.
This is no good.
Grandma! Grandma! Grandma!
Grandma!
She is so dumb!
Say it backwards.
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
Idiot! Idiot!
Idiot!
Like this?
It was good.
But it's our new device.
It seems impossible to make.
I wonder if there's a way to make it better.
The background should be better.
If it's just that, it's not like we can get out of here with just Bakachiko
Actually, the first time I went this year was last year's Kure
The 400th anniversary
Yes, this is actually the first time I went this year
That's right
Did you take your time?
I did
Where did you go this year?
This year, I don't really want to say it, but I went to Hokkaido
I went to Hokkaido from Gantan
In slippers?
I didn't want to wear slippers, so I wore boots
I don't know what to say
Why?
The food was delicious
I ate ramen all of a sudden
That's good
Miso ramen
There was a photo of you at the Miso ramen shop I went to
What was that?
I had no choice
There was a photo of me with the store manager
Why didn't I take a photo of you from Gantan?
That made me feel bad
Is that so?
Yes
Clockwork ramen
Yes, clockwork ramen
I arrived
I ate ramen all of a sudden
I wanted to eat ramen in Hokkaido
I ate ramen
This was delicious
It was better than Tokyo
It was delicious
It was different
Now that I think about it
That was the peak
After that, it was a mess
It was a mess
It was 5 degrees below zero
It was night
That's right
I wasn't walking alone
You didn't choose a place like that
I didn't know
No
There was a town
I went to a coffee shop
A coffee shop?
That's good
I went to a coffee shop
There was a fortune teller
It was on the table
Yes, Gantan did this
There was a ball
I hit it and there was this
It said the lucky place was Okinawa
Ouch
It was like a lie
I was at the edge
I didn't do anything
It wasn't that bad
The miso ramen was the peak
It was like an organ
Did you know that?
The wind was strong
I didn't go
I waited for 2 hours
It was New Year's
At night, I couldn't eat
The hotel was full
No
I couldn't go
I didn't think about it
I couldn't help it
I put on my TV
You were talking
I was doing a fire challenger special
Let's go eat
I wanted to go eat
I went to a crab restaurant
There were many crab restaurants
I couldn't help it
I waited for 1 hour
I waited
I went back to the hotel
Why did you go back?
You should have looked for it
My ears hurt
I shouldn't have bought it
I should have bought it
My ears hurt
I went back to the hotel
I was shocked
I didn't know what to do
You're really bad at traveling
I was going to stay for 2 nights
You should have gone home
I tried to run away the next day
I went to the airport
I went to the airport and looked for Tokyo
It was full
I made a reservation
There were about 100 people
I was worried
I didn't want to go to Hokkaido again
I went to another place
I looked for it
Nagoya was open
You should have gone to Nagoya
I went to Nagoya
You should have gone
I arrived in Nagoya
The restaurant in Nagoya wasn't open
I was shocked
I couldn't even take medicine
You were talking
I wanted to go home
You're stupid
I came to Nagoya
I got on the plane
I wanted to stay
The next day's Shinkansen was full
I had to go home
I couldn't go home
I wanted to go home
I didn't have a car
There was a manager in Nagoya
I forgot his name
I rented a car
I went to Tokyo in the morning
I went to Tokyo
It was the worst
It was terrible
Are you crying?
I couldn't go home
I went home
I don't know what you went to do
I don't know what I went to do
I went to eat ramen
I came back to Tokyo on the 2nd
I spent 500,000 yen
What did you spend it on?
I only ate ramen
You spent 500,000 yen on a hotel and a plane?
There was a lot
I had to fly to Nagoya
You went to Nagoya
You didn't go to a hotel and a plane
You rented a car
You can't rent a car for free
You have a face
But you're a company person
I'm not a company person
I was told to leave it alone
You're a company person?
I'm a company person
Do you understand the flow of the story?
Why did you come to Nagoya and become a company person?
Did you pass the exam at the station?
I don't think so
I was told to leave it alone
It was really hard
But the crab was delicious
Did you eat it?
What is this?
You're a company person
You shouldn't be told that
We've been together since our debut
You have a role of a company person
You shouldn't be told that
You're a company person
What is this?
If you don't go home early today
It's going to snow a lot
It's going to snow at night
It's worse than the other day
The other day when I was going to work
I was going to take the expressway
But the expressway was frozen in the snow
I had no choice but to tell my manager Fujiwara
That I was going to be late
So I called him
The expressway is frozen in the snow
I'm sorry
It hurts
That's not why I called you
You're putting out a lot of oil
The expressway is frozen in the snow
I don't know what time it will arrive
But I'm sure you'll be late
I'm really sorry
What are you apologizing for?
Are you a company person?
After working for two years as an emergency fund
As a Tokyo girl
Matsumoto Yoshimoto
Yes
You often categorize women's breasts
As the O-an type, the Tsurigane type, and the Rocket type
But you categorize them into seven types
Please tell us the remaining four
Actually they say eight
But there are seven
There are seven and eight
Really?
And then there's the theory that it doesn't matter
Who says that?
The remaining four
Yes
And the new type
What type?
It's the new type
I'm only saying the new type
It's not just the appearance
What type?
Wait, there's more
And then there's the latest type
And then?
There are two more
That's not good
What is this?
You have to say three more
What do you mean I have to say three more?
Please say it
I'll say as many as I want
Please say three more
The twist type
Why did you stop there?
I'm starting to get excited
Don't you have the courage?
I have a lot of courage
What?
The new type? The latest type?
That's not possible
That's strange
You're stupid
You got caught
You got tricked
I'm sad
The one type, the twist type, the rocket type
The twist type
There are people who are a little twisted
About two out of three
That's not me
The twist type
And then?
This is the last
No, no, you're the only one who knows
It's only you, right?
Ah, I made a mistake
I'm asking Matsumoto-san, who has thousands of secrets
How many thousands of secrets do you have?
Why, why, why?
Men and women have straight hair, but why do they have curly hair?
Why do they have curly hair?
What do you think?
There's no point, right?
Even if it's curly hair
Even if it's straight hair
Why is there no point?
Is there a way to use it?
Curly hair?
There's a way to use it
What do you use it for?
The easiest way to use it is when you make bubbles with soap
You use it from here
Bam, bam, bam, bam
If you don't have that, there's nothing you can do
You use all the bubbles you made here?
That's right
Of course, you just blow it up
Isn't that obvious?
Everyone does that
That's just me
No, it's not just me
Everyone does it, right?
I don't want to
Why do you bring a person who made bubbles here?
That's strange
Is it you?
No
The bubbles, the bubbles
Is it you?
No
You've done it once before
Once
Twice
Twice?
You have to clean it properly
Three times
Three times?
Twelve times
Twelve times?
Yes, yes
Is there anyone like that?
That's right
I don't think so
Just once, just once
There is
There is, isn't there?
Well, well, well
I'll tell you one of my private things
I don't want to hear it
Just once
What?
I don't want to hear it
Everyone does it
I'm sure of it
These guys are trying to make it look good
What are you trying to make it look good?
They are trying to make themselves sweet
Also, the season is when the temperature is high
Is that so?
When you go hiking or go to the snowy mountains
It's high
That's right
When you go on a date
What?
You wait for the ambulance
I think the funny laugh is the best
The one that goes up little by little
I mean
It's not funny
It's funny because it's a joke
When I was thinking about it
I've heard it before
The most comfortable thing in the body
Is the sex
In a woman's body
It's the sex
Because the temperature is the highest
So when you think about it
I think it's a direct question
Because the temperature is high
It's burning
It's like
It's like a little boy
A little boy
It's small
It's like a little boy
Everyone runs around
It's like my son
Why?
Everyone wants to try it
Why are you so motivated?
Everyone goes home when it snows
What are you doing?
Bring the camera
Why?
Take a picture
It's such a sexy shot
Why?
Let's go home
Thank you very much
What are you talking about?
Nothing
Thank you very much
To the cord here