After this, it's time for Gaki no Tsukai Yarahen.
It's over.
You change your weight every day.
I can tell from the bottom.
The third episode of Gaki no Tsukai Yarahen.
Hit the chicken with a bat and see how many points you get.
This is the third episode.
We've been talking about men.
This is the first time we're talking about women.
Today's guest is a scary one.
Please bring her in.
What kind of clothes is this?
What should we do? She's a woman.
She's a woman.
If you kiss her on the cheek, you get 50 points.
Do you kiss her on the back of the hand?
I'll give her 20 points.
What kind of hand is this?
5 points on the cheek.
If you kiss her on the mouth, you get more than 50 points.
Can you kiss her on the mouth?
You said it.
I don't know.
That's about it.
What else can you think of?
Let's dig her shoes.
It's a lot of work to dig shoes.
It's a lot of work.
She's scary.
If you dig her shoes, you get 10,000 points.
It's more than a kiss.
What else?
If you throw it.
How many points do you get?
I'll go home.
I can't participate.
If you can put her body in a half-transparent garbage bag.
I'll give you 20,000 points.
I'll give you a chance.
What kind of chance?
I'll give you a chance to dance lightly.
Who?
I will.
You?
Okay.
I'd like to talk to her now.
Good evening.
I'm Masumoto from downtown.
I'm Hamada.
Today, we're going to talk about actress Kaga Mariko Hansen.
She's our senior.
I think there's a lot to learn from her.
Let's invite her to the stage.
Today's guest is Kaga Mariko.
Good evening.
I'm famous Kaga Mariko.
You're here like a hero.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
I'm Catherine de Nouveau.
I didn't see you.
It hurts.
You're always like that, right?
Don't be like that.
It's okay.
Have you been standing there all this time?
Please sit down.
I'm worried about you.
Today, we're going to talk about actress Kaga Mariko Hansen.
No.
I'm not going to talk about her.
Why?
I'm not ready yet.
It hurts.
How many years have you been in the entertainment industry?
I've never been in the entertainment industry.
You're in your teens, right?
Is that so?
How long have you been in the entertainment industry?
I didn't start in my fifties.
You've been in the entertainment industry for a long time, haven't you?
No, I haven't.
You're normal.
You're a disgusting man.
I don't like you.
It hurts.
What's wrong with him?
No, no, no.
Thank you very much.
You're dirty.
You're like a sloth to me.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I'm really sorry.
I want to talk to you properly.
Does anyone have a swimming suit?
It's your choice.
Did you buy these shoes yourself?
Can I show you?
No.
Please.
I don't like you.
Please show me.
I'm sorry.
Let me put it on.
You are.
Stop it.
I'm pretending to be asleep.
I'm really sorry.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
When I talked to Kaga-san,
the half-transparent garbage bag was a hot topic.
Did you complain?
I didn't complain.
I have something here.
It's something like this.
It's not something to play with.
Who do you think you are?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Call the producer.
I'm sorry.
Kaga-san has become a leader.
Do you have some tea?
I don't need it.
I'm sorry.
Do you have a sore throat?
What is that?
Kaga-san.
This is a weapon.
Kaga-san, I have something here.
Kaga-san.
I'm sorry.
I'm tired.
Let's go home.
Don't let your guard down.
You.
What are you doing while I'm looking at you?
I want to touch you.
Let's hold hands.
I don't want to hold hands.
You don't want to hold hands?
Where is it?
This is amazing.
This is a glass.
Is that so?
This is amazing.
Do you have bad eyesight?
I don't have bad eyesight.
This is a fashionable outfit today.
What did you want to do?
You wanted to carry me on your back.
I wanted to try throwing you on my back.
Shall we get on your back?
This is amazing.
Hold it properly.
What should I do from now on?
Thank you very much.
It was Kaga-san.
Let's announce the results.
The hard fight is over.
I changed my bad habit.
I don't want to imitate Chibikko.
Let's announce the results.
Let's start with Matsumoto-san.
What is Matsumoto-san's score?
1390 points.
This is zero.
This is amazing.
What is my score?
3580 points.
Matsumoto-san's score is 10000 points.
That's all I got.
No way.
My father's score is only 50 points.
Really?
Why did you get 30,000 points?
I threw my shoes away.
I covered them with plastic.
That's not true.
That's why my score was high.
Your score is only 10000 points.
Kaga-san's score is only 50 points.
I threw my shoes away.
That's all I got.
That's enough.
Welcome.
It's been a long time since I saw you.
I didn't want to say it.
I didn't start it now.
I forgot my name when I came here.
I can't say it.
Why don't you say it?
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
I can't let them do it.
They have nothing to do with it.
They can do whatever they want.
That's true.
You have to think about it.
I won't say it.
You won't say it?
Who are you?
Why are you talking to me?
We are guests.
I'm talking naturally.
This is the first time.
I was thinking about it.
I can't say it.
I think you can think about it.
I can think about it.
I'm in a group.
I'm a vocalist.
I'm fat.
I'm ugly.
I'm wearing a mini skirt.
I'm a vocalist.
Is it that bad?
Look at me.
You're pretty popular.
I can tell from your face.
Why are all the famous musicians ugly?
I can't say it.
I can't say it to everyone.
I'm sorry.
You often say it like that.
I don't say it.
You just said it.
You don't have a chance to meet people like that.
Wait a minute.
I don't attack people like that.
I'm being called ugly.
Who are you talking to?
You're just saying it.
I haven't seen anyone who is not ugly.
I don't think I'm that kind of person.
You seem to have unpleasant thoughts.
I think so.
I don't.
Really?
What's unpleasant about watching TV?
I think it's okay.
I don't understand.
Why?
He's being called a good person.
He's not a good person at all.
Wait a minute.
What?
Do you know it well?
I know it well.
You just say it by the appearance of the TV.
No, he's a bad guy.
You should remember it.
About 6 or 7 years ago,
when I was not known in Tokyo or Osaka,
I did a hit parade of the New Year's program.
At the Meiji Jingu?
At the Meiji Jingu.
I was asked to do a manzai in front of the audience.
Yes.
Before that, I was asked to show what kind of story I was going to do.
I said, you can't do that now.
I said, hey.
I went to the CX.
I said, good morning.
You said it right.
I said it right.
You changed a lot.
When I went to the CX,
no matter what kind of story I showed,
it was like this at that time.
I did it.
At that time, I liked baseball the most.
I wanted to do baseball story.
That's okay.
I wanted you to do a story other than baseball story.
What?
I asked why.
It was the same.
I wanted to do a baseball story.
That's why I told you to go home.
It's not their fault.
It's their fault.
Why are we doing this?
It's the fault of that rotten comedian.
Anyway, I wanted you to change the story.
What kind of story?
On that day, I went to Amazing on New Year's Day.
I was on standby early in the morning.
Early in the morning.
An hour ago.
Even though it was early.
Amazing.
I can't think of it now.
It was like a microbus.
What are you doing?
It's true.
It's fine.
It's fine like this.
What is this?
It was amazing.
It's true.
It's a good guy.
It's a lie.
It's fine like that.
And then,
I said,
Good morning.
I'm a senior.
Right?
And I'm older.
But I said,
Good morning.
I said,
What are you doing?
At this time,
Are you going to make an egg?
Susa!
I'm scared.
Is it from the pocket?
Susa!
Shut up!
And then,
There are many kinds of comic books.
For those who are watching,
It may not matter.
Who goes first?
It's OK for me to be a senior,
But it's humiliating.
I'm going to be the one to be hurt.
I was replaced by
Well,
Get out!
Baseball!
You returned the story to me.
I said hello.
I made a paper cigarette.
What kind of story are you giving in?
I was surprised.
But that's fine.
Even if I say, good work, he'll blow again.
What are you doing?
You came with a microphone when you came.
Don't go home.
Don't make me laugh.
I can't tell you how he is.
Why?
He was popular when he came.
I don't know why he became like this.
I really hate this kind of person.
It's the worst to be a bad person.
What?
Is it true?
Is it me?
I said it once before.
I didn't say it because I didn't support him.
I said it once.
You said it in a bad way.
I didn't say it in a bad way.
Really?
I said it.
He's a person who comes right away.
He's strong.
I was in the back of the school.
I hate it.
He's always like this.
He's doing shadow.
Hey!
We're the same age.
He's older than me.
I'm the same age.
I didn't say anything bad about him.
I don't have the right to say that.
I don't think I can win.
I think I can win.
He said he was talking about me.
I didn't say anything.
What?
For now.
For now, I didn't say anything.
He's a bad person.
I thought he was going to say something bad next time.
Next time?
You.
I said it next time.
Do you know what happens if you make me angry?
You're here.
I said it.
You said it.
Yes.
What?
Three times!
Three times.
You said it three times!
Three times!
No way!
It's the third time!
You!
What are you talking about?
If you and I fight,
you're gonna be an adult and little kid.
Is that so?
That's so annoying!
If you and I fight, you're gonna be an adult and.....
I'm the little kid.
Pachi- Pachi-
You don't need to say it!
I'll be careful from now on!
Sorry...
No, this is...
This is because I'm bad
Ah, because you said it
Yes, yes, I said it wrong
Ah, I see, I see
Because I said it wrong, you got mad
You can't say anything if you got mad
That's right!
For example, if I say something bad on TV,
I'll be like...
Wait, wait
Say that you're not going to shut up
I'll be like...
At that time, I'll be like...
What are you talking about?
This is the photo that was at the Victoria Museum in Canada
What kind of picture is this?
This is me, right?
Yes
Look at the person near the monitor, it's similar, right?
Then, I'll be the one to shut up
I'll be the one to shut up
This is similar!
It's similar!
That's it
It's the time when my Masao will be okay
What?
Hello, I have a question for the best Japanese teacher, Matsumoto
I took a pen
From autumn to winter, I often see birds flying in a row in the western sky in V-shape and Y-shape
Does that have any meaning?
Is it a code to people?
If it's a code...
I'm saying this because I know how to write it
What is it?
Birds don't want to say anything to humans
That's not true
I don't want to say anything
Birds fly in a circle
It's a correction
What?
That's not true
It's not true?
It's the trend of this year
It's a fashion
Fashion?
This year, V-neck will be popular
The birds are telling me
Good morning
What?
You have a lot of savings
I'm comparing your savings
Are you asking me about my father?
I know this
What is it?
It's the same
Is that so?
I'm sorry