Let's do it!
Let's aim for the top!
Glico Championship!
Masao-san
Yes?
Takada is playing Glico
Yes
Why are we wearing heavy equipment?
Well...
We have to wear heavy equipment
It's because we're going to die
It's not because we're going to die
I want to play with these guys
Yes
Here they are!
You can choose
You can sleep
You can wake up
Here they are
Look up!
We're going to use these stairs
Let's play Glico
The first person to go up
There's a button on top
You press the button
And a gift will come down from the top
I don't need that
But you have to know that you won't get hurt
Who's going to get hurt?
So it means you won't get hurt
Yes
You have to go up with Glico
It's like a tax avoidance
What does that mean?
It's not a loss
If you do that, everyone will know
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors
Everyone
We have to play rock, paper, scissors with 6 people
One person only
That's right
Wait a minute
I feel like I've seen something
It's not that fun
It's not fun
Shut up
Let's go
Rock, paper, scissors
It's hard to decide
I got it
Let's do the one with less
Rock, paper, scissors
The one with less
It's me
Pineapple
I'm jealous
It's just this
Rock, paper, scissors
It's me
But it's Furiko
Furiko
Rock, paper, scissors
It's me
Glico
Rock, paper, scissors
It's me
Yamasaki
Glico
Rock, paper, scissors
It's me
It's the worst
Rock, paper, scissors
It's me
Wait a minute
I don't think so
Why?
Because you can't win
Let's do rock, paper, scissors
You
You are like this
You should say it
How many fans do you have?
Why are you doing that?
Let's do the next one
Rock, paper, scissors
It's me
It's you
It's the worst
Pineapple
Rock, paper, scissors
It's me
It's true
How can you win with scissors?
Choclate
Really?
You have a character
Rock, paper, scissors
It's Suga
It's me
Rock, paper, scissors
You look happy
It's me
It's Okamoto
Choclate
It's the worst
Wait a minute
There are so many items
Are you stupid?
You should think about me
There are so many items
Choclate
Rock, paper, scissors
It's me
It's Okamoto
Pineapple
Rock, paper, scissors
It's me
It's Riko
Rock, paper, scissors
It's a waste
Do you want to use all the chocolates?
No
It's the same
Rock, paper, scissors
It's me
Pineapple
It's dangerous
Rock, paper, scissors
It's over there
Choclate
It's dangerous
I'm sorry
Rock, paper, scissors
It's me
Pineapple
Rock, paper, scissors
It's me
Pineapple
Rock, paper, scissors
What are you doing?
It's me
Choclate
It's amazing
It's hard to see
Rock, paper, scissors
It's me
It's dangerous
Choclate
Wait a minute
It's almost done
How many steps left?
3 steps
3 steps left?
Yes
No matter how many steps
Let's go
You are the first
Yamasaki and Matsumoto are the first
Where are you going?
What should I do?
I want to be on camera
Let's go
Rock, paper, scissors
Pineapple
It's OK
It's dangerous
Wait a minute
Am I a baby?
You are a baby
Rock, paper, scissors
It's me
No
Wait
I'm scared
Rock, paper, scissors
It's burning
It's hot
I'm scared
Why are you laughing?
From above, everyone is in a vertical position
It's dangerous
You can sing the opening song
Why?
I can still go
You can sing the opening song
You can laugh twice
I can still go
There is another stupid song
I was called out by Wada Akiyo
Why did you have to do that?
What did Wada Akiyo think about it?
Did he see it?
I changed my phone number to Wada Akiyo
I told him what I wanted to change
He thought he could hug me
He thought he could be Matsumoto
He thought he could be Miyaku
He changed his phone number but he couldn't tell him
He thought he was Pinko
He had a red tail like a lipstick
You look like him
He sat like this but he came out like this
That's a dog's tail
He came to me
He came to me like this
This is bad
Wait
I can see the female part
This is scary
I don't know
I told him to come
That's what old men say
It's early in the morning
I told him to come
I told him I'm sorry
He said no
Are you serious?
I didn't ask
Please forget about it
Shut up
I don't want to hear it
I told him I can't do it anymore
I ran out of battery
I thought I was lucky
I changed my phone number
I thought he was going to get angry
I told him I don't want to hear it
Stop it
It's true
It's too much
You have to put up with it
Ouch
It's too much
That's because it's a phone
If you call me somewhere
I'll pull the car
Stop it
What are you doing?
Why are you laughing next to him?
I did something wrong
Please forgive me
That's what you're doing
If you do a show like that
Stop it
I don't want to hear it
I can't hear it
It's like a message song
It's scary
But I told you
I told you
About Hamada
No no no
I thought he was going to get angry
I'm not that kind of person
Stop it
There are good places in Hamada and bad places in Matsumoto
They're both good
But in Hamada there are bad places
I see
The reason is crazy
At that point
He's aiming at me
It doesn't matter if it's bad or good
I'm going to eat
Stop it
I'm going to hide the camera like I did with Hajime
I'm going to take a picture
I've been kissed
Wow
I wonder if I complimented him
He's saying jori jori
It's an unknown world so I want to see it
It's scary
I'm going to get on top
Stop it
I'm going to hit him more and more
I'm going to get on top
I'm going to blind him
I'm going to grab him
If you're tied to the chain you can't escape
It's fine if you're tied
What are you talking about?
I'm holding it from the back
If everyone goes out to eat and you notice
One person will be gone
I'm going to go to the toilet
Two people will be gone
I think Akiyo will be like
One person will be gone
This is my way of doing things
Matsumoto-san, I heard that you don't know what life is
What was the most dangerous thing you've ever done?
I don't know what life is
You've never thought of it as scary
You've never heard of it as scary
Today's opening was scary
What was that?
That's a different kind of scary
The most dangerous thing I've ever done
When I got bitten by a gorilla
Where?
Around here
Bang!
Where did you get that?
I was playing baseball
Where?
At the Grand
At the Grand in Amagasaki
I've never heard of that
Then listen
Bang!
I'm a home run putter
Are you stupid?
I don't care
Bang!
I don't have a bowl
I broke the glass
I went to apologize
The gorilla was there
The gorilla was there?
There were two old men and a gorilla
There was a gorilla next to the old man?
What are you going to do about it?
The gorilla was like this
You're a gangster
I was like this
And?
I was like, what do you think?
I was still a kid
The gorilla came out
It came out before
And?
Why didn't you apologize?
Did he talk?
The old man said it
I was surprised
The old man said, why didn't you apologize?
Hey, hey, hey
The gorilla?
The old man
What old man?
You talk a lot
I said, okay
I said, I won't apologize
I said, I'll take revenge
Bang!
I took revenge
Wait, wait
Who is that?
The old man
The old man?
He comes out many times
I said, let's put the gorilla in front of the old man
I said, I'll avoid it
And then
Bang!
I don't know if it was a stone or a desk
Are you licking the gorilla?
The gorilla
The old man
This is the gorilla
What?
You said it so lightly
That's the gorilla
This is the gorilla
This is the first time I've heard the gorilla
You don't look angry
The old man
This is the gorilla
Oh
Right?
The old man
You weren't surprised when the gorilla spoke
That wasn't strange
I was shocked
I thought it was strange
I shouldn't have apologized
I said, you're injured
You're from Kibuya
This is the gorilla
What?
I'm not injured
And then
Bang!
I'm scared
It's this high
It's high
Bang!
It's broken
The old man did it
What?
Don't you live with the gorilla?
It has this much destructive power
It's fake
The old man said it
What?
It was a strange day
You weren't hit
I'm a 17-year-old man
I'm the same height as Hamada
I'm 155 cm
That's fine
What should I do now
I'm going to go over 2 meters like Matsumoto
I'll teach you
I'm going to go over 2 meters
Dantan is
In other words
It's a big combination
It's amazing
You're taller than St. Louis
Why can't I touch my face?
You can touch your face 2 meters
I don't do that
Everyone is wrong
The way you measure
The way I measure
Why?
I'm 170 cm
What do you think this 30 cm is?
Of course
But this 30 cm
I don't care
Why?
30 cm is what?
That's right
This is my heart
So my heart is 30 cm
You're a fool
Do you understand?
You don't have a heart so you're attracted to me
Everyone has one?
Everyone has one
How many cm does everyone have?
It depends on the person
In my case, my heart is 30 cm
I want to feed you rice
Don't panic
What?
Let me eat
Say it
What?
You want to feed me rice?
Of course
I always want to feed you rice
Even when I'm talking to you
Don't panic
I want to feed you rice
Me?
I don't think so
I never thought of you like that
When I'm talking to you
I want to feed you rice
I never thought of you like that
Don't you understand?
That's why it's 155 cm
Don't panic
Really?
Of course
That's why it's 30 cm
To make it easier to understand
I always put a jar on my head
In my heart
In your heart
Whenever I open it
The steam comes out
The rice puffs up
I'm having a fight with my mother
It's a good story
Sometimes you have to read this kind of letter
I haven't heard from you for three days
I'm not bad
What should I do?
He's very serious
I haven't talked to you for about a month
I liked you
But you stole my erohon
I was so angry
And you cut it and made it into a file
I just remembered
I still remember
When I was in elementary school
When I went to school
My friends told me
It's okay
In that moment
There was a mother
When I passed by
We did it!!